sorry
hey guys what are we attempting today
what's an evolution
i can say
oh
wow airway oh wow my bites wow
welcome to australia really good didgeridoo one
lauren do a didgeridoo wow
you look like you're sucking my car
gods why they strike one well it's
because nobody strikes you i get ten
okay i was just speaking to todd
so he thinks he can speak to
me that way oh my are two
very different people
what is your real personality lauren doesn't
netflix is a character that's true which
scotland the whole time i watched it
yeah yeah he'll never compliment me on
it i think you i think i
gotta thanks at it yeah but so
did you get what i think i
gotta thank god has things because we
talked at some because i read the
script or something and he told me
to fuck off yeah
you to fuck off where's my thanks
what a world we live in and
what a world welcome to the show
man this is three-time i'm scott i'm
scott i'm scott
and we're all scots and that's why
all three to three scars i'm paul
seriously seriously your ball and seriously i'm
obviously the woman and the rest yeah
the woman the rest
do you want show and the rest
do you think we should make it
for them and get another woman in
here without making more comfortable yeah i
honestly feel really uncomfortable lately we just
want the outweigh the scales well also
we're super alpha we're both super alpha
here's what i'm getting you kevin oh
i forgot he was
paul kett i mean i'm starting to
room by paul kevin scott and ryan
and you feel sad right now they're
right into the separate room and that's
the only thing making me feel safe
because i'm blocked because ryan ryan is
the problem ryan is very impressive he's
very good we went on tour together
ryan was on almost a one hundred
percent of the tour with us
us and he was so angry and
screaming the entire day it was uncomfortable
he started every day asking us about
our sex lives and everything was really
uncomfortable pushed us to our edge and
and he would just say do a
better show tonight tonight i think you
should do when that was good you
know and there's just a lot of
hurtful comments like that updates on that
sex life yeah yeah make the audience
come and then
i'll try to say we're on we're
on tour we're not having sex right
now and then you just say well
you got any updates it was really
weird do you know anybody who's having
sex right now anyway call us all
guide go any updates on that sex
life guy paid you jerk off vega
yeah it was a lot of things
alone js guy you check our schedule
yeah you want to know i don't
know why
i never got an answer and he
mimed drinking off all xylem you said
hello
he'd be like hey hello what do
you ask about sexy did the jerk
off motion which is to say something
yeah say it it's my justify have
to say something you were
please ah sweet aw i'm trying to
get everyone's attention for lauren please cough
while i'm talking
so you said you didn't want to
say fuck you so only talk when
you want to you say you didn't
want kevin to get spanked but you
want to scream about ryan being aggressive
and talking about jerking off and that
one's fine okay that was good we're
gonna try again i would say just
type up those ah lyrics
a little bit okay try to make
a little more universal if you could
use really
and you should be in the booth
shit isn't the problem alright see i
think i had it but you guys
want it ok
i'm back
go you say i only piss when
i want to the universe wow everyone
pisses i like it could land say
i only do it when i'm happy
me me me me i'm a sick
person
mimi
oh boy it's fun because yeah we're
coming off of um you just did
another podcast i believe this is my
third podcast of the day just to
be forth and i just did a
little bit of improvisation oh so a
little too vulnerable right now i mean
it's
it's tough coming down from grand outcast
appear appearance coming off that high is
like nothing i've ever experienced mean you're
just you're just high it's why i'm
always chasing the high it's the toxic
any medium it truly is unlike anything
else unlike anything or radio i guess
now
it's just like radio because radio you
have to do radio you're censored by
the man you're wants to talk about
radio you're doing those ads you know
for the local car dealership or whatever
and he's like lip it's all like
oil sugar quibble oh i see never
gonna equip ah never did equip know
don't quit
ahead i've done i wonder if i
set a record for leesa mattress adds
i do feel like you exclusively do
lisa i think because exclusively there were
my only sponsor for the for the
the end of my podcast who knows
what sponsors we have today this is
exciting we break to find out ah
oh yeah we won't find out for
a long time yeah
yeah yeah i'm so sad about that
i know now i don't know our
sponsors now it's the most exciting part
of podcasting it running out of your
sport i love is getting those pieces
of paper and looking at them and
seeing oh that sue my sponsor is
good stuff really relatable too i feel
everyone out there is nodding their head
everyone should have a sponsor everyone should
my friend jim if you were who's
your friend jim
oh i can't say oh no it's
bill you don't know i was jail
bill w bill w a friend of
bill's yes if you um had a
sponsor in real life and you had
to kinda like wear a jacket that
said their thing on it or would
it be charmin
everybody goes
dirty sharman i love those bears oh
man last minute addition to be one
of the the one i didn't know
the i like i've said no i
know raised by tv oh my guy
did send in a voice over audition
to be ultimately bears the bears ever
spoken oh they speak all the time
think they know too much frankly um
i
i think i auditioned for the mom
and the baby your filthy piece about
that because you're not using a good
wipe
um yeah i would love it though
the rules of the bears they're all
over the place and it makes me
very what are the rules of the
bears candidate because i don't know the
changing i don't know the sherman bay
rules please thank you very much okay
here we go i know some rules
about i'm looking typing the show and
this show yeah the ready all the
time
even you need to be spanked you
need to be spanked and you need
to be say look under your chairs
you got spanked alright learn the rules
of the sherman bears yeah they live
in the woods they don't want to
shit there i don't wear clothes but
they do have bows in their hair
now they live in a house like
you know they do have close yeah
they have toilet paper stuck to their
butt because it's a cheap brand
why do they have like suddenly they
realised these anthropomorphic bears were nude and
adva clothes on him i that people
got uncomfortable because the society can't handle
like bare dick the machine a bear
and a human exactly if you're thinking
about them in the woods huge labor
turnout the moisture from us and what
do we do we fuck and at
that point it's great
get out of here
don't let him grab the line don't
be a bear because you're gonna have
to wipe with your ass in the
air too don't wear a shirt because
you are there oh here's a shirt
you're supposed to pick it up now
just enjoy get off your phone i
loved it well look i have to
lie i'm juggling sharman i like what
you say did you say i'm a
juggler man on my time has started
juggling during their high got charm in
on my butt
i'll do anything to save my bow
fc
to introduce
do you think sherman's ever gonna hire
you if they hear this show gives
him a ton of ads for waiting
right now when the toilet paper i
love chairman i used i use it
i love it did you say it
was a cheap brand now the seconds
ago no i say the bears had
a place on there but because i'm
not using sharman and they learn oh
i see here's the thing to bears
you know when they had the toilet
ever stuck to their fucking bear asses
yeah it was all over the ass
i mean the series why is that
a piece is on your heart sharma
lore is part of the sherman laurie
that they had toilet paper stuck to
there and you know what's incredible is
that some of the halls of sharman
when they tell this ten this is
what it is like it says there's
somewhere where like there is that story
on the wall and like all the
people who
worked there know it intimately like carved
into the wall and they are like
on a whiteboard and like okay so
this time and everyone knows what the
sherman bears would or wouldn't do well
the sherman like the mom would never
say that yeah exactly yeah nothing's off
limits they could do anything can they
were gonna find out they'd have to
break here's
alright when we come back yeah those
offers first i want to know why
they don't really talk about the wet
wipes and also here's a breakdown of
the white bears the bears don't talk
about what we want to talk about
what they have a brand of werewolves
oh sherman does so i'm assuming right
well i think by now you're just
assuming are you sure i have that
brand they have
the bears on them but i have
to tell you so this is a
p say to everybody out there by
the way just right behind me lit
up so bright i was like what
is going sharman dot com and there's
all the sharma the television behind me
apparently there are two families paul there's
this family in the blue what about
the brown family the way it is
the rab the younger they
and then the ultra strong family now
here's what i need to say the
red family works out a lot even
though they have glasses and look like
nerds what is going on with these
mom and the daughter have bows on
both families okay so let me the
two genders you cannot flush what baby
royals do roles come on come on
kevin these other
rules about wet wipes okay i need
to learn some way oh wait the
rules went away
okay one change the tab see the
you cannot flush wet wipes they make
you think you can what you show
yourself to do with them or wrap
them in some tp and shaming the
toilet seventieth minute toilet ash can oh
did you guys over there hear that
about terrence howard that he terrace house
yeah what about him
first of all you didn't think one
plus one equal to know he was
mistaken about that yeah i know why
why did he say he said when
you really think about a oneplus one
actually probably equals one when you could
and he had like a piece of
sculpture in his house that that illustrated
the fact somebody like did you even
did anyone ever go to one piece
of sculpture and go named one plus
one's know you had a whole theory
about it he was like when you
really really take a look at it
it makes more sense that an equals
one how stoned was
no this isn't an interview who is
the roses de terrans room the rumor
about him was he would only be
with it'll give her and tell her
if a lady was if he was
to be with the lead this is
allegedly by the way we don't know
allegedly please don't take me to court
for i thought that was he that
the ladies must use only wet wipes
while they were at his house oh
my god was his pipes is clogged
his pipes is sweet if you have
wet wipes back there you're supposed to
let your doesn't mean you have shit
everywhere in your in your head i
would suggest you wipe enough with a
dry that there's no shit on the
wet and then what's going to be
on the weapon
and what's the point of it it's
wish to clean residue is shit residue
is shit residue shit shit this way
twenty is kept in the title
i know it's tempting but they can't
anyway look i had been doing it
for years and eliza skinner tweeted about
it and i i looked into it
facts are facts and has day your
toilet or the fact that you asked
this question it didn't call you a
new place that i moved into so
every time you've ever had you're just
clogging it up with your shit wet
writes every single day
regularly but some people do use them
every day i don't want to get
shit like once or twice a month
i don't want to get into when
i use them but you said you
like going do you like shitting what
are you gonna ask me outside of
the house better like in in public
restrooms or would i like that blue
what kind of person i don't know
what you like
like that's like a fetish maybe around
mike you don't want to do it
all of it yeah that's fine
i think if your relationship has rules
where it's like you gotta play new
rules so to say come on chevron
i think if your partner makes you
feel bad for taking a shit you
gotta work that out because that is
a body function and we're yeah and
don't think that happened huh my weight
is even really feel bad for dye
know people who shame each other or
have to leave or do something and
it's a whole thing leave when i
get up
apartment or oh my god or they'd
prefer that you do it somewhere else
okay yeah wrong i don't approve of
that i mean if it's a tiny
if it's a tiny i knew someone
who if it's a tiny if it's
tiny i knew someone who in their
master bedroom at this house they were
renting they had the bed right and
then there was a tiny long maybe
you
call it
maybe call it a pony wall like
a tiny wall that's about like vi
and the top truly what it's called
and the toilet let chess the toilet
was on the opposite side of the
pony wall next to the bed that's
just so that's that's weird it's horrible
who on earth who on earth and
that tony will not toilet wall in
that in that situation
i'm sure i would be like look
can you can you go elsewhere do
you need to be shitting right yesterday
badly that's discussing i did say like
weird hotel and i stayed at a
hotel with erin whitehead we are sharing
a room we are somewhere for wild
horses high and she's the badass fucking
way the bathroom number is a mere
pawn
all the bathroom had no door on
the like the tears all my way
out showered didn't have a door and
so then were like can you not
look at me while i shower right
you don't have to go somewhere but
can you never turn around like oh
that's the whole thing about hotels these
days around oh wow yeah my neck
and button
ah the things about hotels these days
is and and cool i've been i've
been traveling a bit they all have
these like windows into the shower like
like no one goes to hotels for
sexy time and sometimes you want to
be alone like yeah but if you
are doing that it's like then you
want a moment of privacy while you
may have like a glass or glass
doors into the you know they
yeah they have a separate toilet room
but there's a glass door and it's
like what is the fucking problem here
somebody shoot some privacy it should always
be a room that can be closed
off yeah yeah and should also have
event yeah san that's going boom boom
make some new boom
with some new kind of shit
but i don't really care or at
least are some old ass pipes that
like gaffe about crazy rat right so
it turned it on did you pick
on aaron or did she pick on
you i picked on aaron and i
looked in there and she was going
and i saw her take about it
h every which way came out what
a few guys confess to each other
later like i spied on you hey
i had to tell you
you i picked on you
we've never really would never would absolutely
never yeah i don't like it no
so how does all your friends see
you naked
oh
i'm trying to think of a single
one who has
yeah is that a that's i mean
is that common with wyoming incredibly uncommon
because if you go say i don't
like going to a spa or something
yeah well cliff was telling me the
other day that she was at a
spa here in town and she saw
and most bananas
an old friend of ours and they
were being into someone and they were
both naked and it's like hello hello
is that's why i don't want to
do that i want i do like
those spas but i i either go
with a my best friend right okay
yeah as we all know who she
is and grade school friend grade school
fowler alone where it but i don't
want to know any
one and the idea of knowing running
into someone where you're not expecting it
is weird that's why she's like you
gotta go to a spot that's at
least like an hour and fifteen minutes
away that's a hassle i would never
do i don't like to do public
nude things spa stuff like that yeah
part of it if first of all
because i've deep shame but so
suddenly just about being a human i
hate it but secondly ah i tend
to get i don't get recognized all
the time but attending weird place to
get erections
a ticket reckon
but cheerfully
i organize it a nude spa once
and santa oh shit i found it
extremely unkempt like the person said hey
are you laura la cause they were
staring at me long enough and i
knew i knew what it was happening
like it was not you wouldn't you
don't stare at anyone in that environment
yeah and what does they recognize you
from from the look of their eye
theo's orange is the new black okay
that's better from the year i would
say it was just new black that's
probably better than like it being someone
who listens to this show that's one
thousand re worse things it was all
women i think it'd be way worse
i would never ever i mean i
wanna discuss that imagine a woman that
had to this i know can you
become on we have plenty of women
like guys aren't getting a rao will
you please
make the sherman bears go away from
the tv they're right behind me aren't
they
like billy crystal but it cuts to
the new rules kidz bop kids why
do you feel like the lakers didn't
have that cash raise the right behind
me arthur he's right behind me isn't
he from monsters inc he would do
it in movies and stuff he's right
behind me as is it musters probably
is no there's something look up billy
crystal he's right behind me isn't he
this is fun this is this is
a fun idea to me i love
when i'm pretty sure he's started failing
wrong because i love digging into the
people it's very fun when you actually
know yeah we go okay i do
to other people all the time and
i sometimes feel like it can be
mean but i don't mean at me
yes and so when someone does to
me i feel like cities like her
daddy monsters
lake city the slickest of cities my
number one guy what does that from
batman batman batman yeah yeah my number
one i did a table read with
billy crystal from new movie he was
doing and i don't know if it
ever happened picture what is going to
be in it but um i was
just there for
table explain why anyone would ever do
a table read for a movie that
you are not going to be in
well because because i can't say have
it first of all well why they
have is because they want to hear
it out loud here and they don't
know who they're going to cast but
then that i've never understood why an
actor would glance oh my i would
do it yeah oh because then i
get to meet all these people like
for me it's good because i then
i got to meet billy chris
i'll show him that i did a
good job so and if it ever
comes up that there is some other
thing maybe they'll think of me but
that's the weird part it's like all
these actors go to these table reads
and do these parts under the under
the knowing they know that they're not
going to get these roles no surrender
that knowing but the thing is maybe
they make an impression on somebody owning
my god homes and wants
from being in the table read and
how did that work
zoos do not affect my page yeah
i don't yeah well maybe later i
got
yeah july i mean my my
tall you know here's one thing about
scott
really quickly scott loves to rub failures
in oh people noel missed your failures
since
wow
hello ah yeah i truly i i
you love it i love it when
am i ever done it you like
to do a little rose you love
to row when am i ever what
are your i don't even know your
other field i don't need don't tell
them because you have already roasted them
what what you don't even know look
how good you are not even name
of thing you've ever been in yeah
okay that's see that's a really rude
one but i'm not doing that and
you know what i support everyone and
i think everyone's great so give me
a little bit of pedal
it is true lauren does support everyone
if you see they are all great
you pry here you are very funny
in holmes and watson i just haven't
seen it yet i was i was
on the fence do i buy it
do i rent it oh you know
what i'll lend you my dvd do
you have a dvd one in the
mail actually a messenger drops off if
anyone sat behind the scenes hollywood wow
just did a little dropoff yeah i
thought it was very exact tried to
give me zach elvin icos try to
give me a blu-rays of a wrinkle
in time because they that yeah they
dropped like five offices housing yeah that's
yea i have to see that no
one's ever given me a copy of
it i've never had a substantial role
in anything i guess that's what guy
okay i gotta cover your shirt to
them
buddy walk over and give me a
dvd i thought it was a little
bit much it's a bit there's a
little bit but say good for you
random ah as we all know i
don't want to spend twenty dollars i
don't have to spend so i was
happy to have it weighs a dvd
not blu-ray dvd and blu ray standard
definition yeah oh borrower does blu-ray play
in my x-box
yeah i don't know but tell you
what i'll borrow it and i'll let
you know what i'll let you know
what i don't want you to watch
it why oh man no it's totally
fine you sound like a real fan
yeah what do you mean as if
lauren offers me devi i would rather
you watch the like you did come
to the unicorn
supported me yes i went to the
music core high
but because it was a madhouse there
with all your friends know and i
wasn't going to party i'm not trying
to shame me i said i didn't
i not send you an email you
don't morning after i was actually really
surprised you came so i'm trying to
give you credit now okay the other
side of the coin is that you
actually are very supportive you i send
you a very nice email about it
and
like to let you know i was
there but it was very nicely you
can say la and all you wrote
back was can i ask a question
who gives a shit
wow what are your thoughts on this
and being supportive and what are your
thoughts on scott well i have my
my my stance of being supportive it's
very specific um i think i think
that's got is very supportive he once
well when he chooses to be he
he wants
and i choose to do it all
the time god is very supportive he
i remember him say i remember him
saying that he's on on his show
he said i will text people to
say they did a good job in
something if i've see it um but
ah he doesn't that doesn't mean he
sees everything know that a person can't
see everything but it's always ah if
i ever see a friend in ah
tv show or movie i'll usually text
them right away to say hey you
good job i do that is me
too and i also like going on
my way to watch people on stuff
and i feel like there are a
lot of people in our community who
actively don't yes i think you and
i probably watch people we know and
stuff because nothing gets neat yes like
there's no single episode of lucifer oh
my god i thought that was so
funny wah
it's that you are lucifer i'm like
wait did i see that i don't
know i think i did honestly honestly
one of the weirdest things i've aged
on totally worth checking out extreme i
think i fast forward it's a strange
thing i fast forwarded through the show
until you were on and then i
watched your scenes
yeah that's me too
i mean no i didn't um well
i will say when i first started
in the nineties it was more of
a thrill to see someone that we
knew on t i'd be like oh
my god i know that person new
members people are also getting their first
job never stops him at this point
it's like you know i mean i
was saying the other day on on
a show like three of the coachella
headliners are like people who have been
on comedy bang bang it's like not
you know that writing anymore yeah yeah
especially because they're clearly doing better than
you yeah exact well
no i mean it's great but it's
like yeah yeah i see people i
know on tv lol but yeah yeah
i remember like the first times i
would see people like from io and
chicago like in a commercial and i'd
be like whoa i still like i
do in privatizing a commercial like it
really started to make it the business
like make more sense to me too
i could understand like how the path
can that made you understand commercials
i never knew what was happening in
those these little tiny movies no but
i never understood oh who was in
them or how this was happening and
then it's like i started to understand
you do commercial auditions know i used
to i used to too they're such
a drag there really are some of
them mean people actually just talked about
yeah this it's really just a tv
with just chaffin but the
the we were going off about it
because they are some truly the casting
people not the casting director i don't
know excretion never in the audition the
people running the additions are usually the
meanest people and they want you to
feel dumb and they want you to
feel bad and the wardrobe people want
you to feel ugly and we are
near bodies wrong yeah and they and
like i'm sure there are exceptions but
i don't think i've met it's because
cause it's all the all the um
the pretense of art is stripped away
now it's just commerce yeah it's like
oh yeah what does what does your
look we don't have to pretend we
like you know right you're staying out
here idiot yeah yeah i went to
i went to an audition once where
i had this was after i said
i wasn't gonna do commercial auditions anymore
for that
very reason i never and it was
like it was like i was booking
stuff like my wife goes on commercial
dishes sure she comes to me no
but she but she books e-commerce yeah
i got a much thicker skin about
that study say something to the effect
of like unless you're in a groove
like a lot of people we knew
would get into like every commercial yeah
for
a couple of years ago yeah their
face was too recognisable but um they
say it's like one out of every
hundred of auditions maybe is that's that's
how often you would book something and
i was like i don't have that
kind of time because there's a million
people going out for them yeah and
and also they're very they're very finicky
about what look they want or whatever
and all these different people have a
say
a in it and it's it's a
mess so i went in when you
do one by the way not to
interrupt but when you do what you
did there are twenty people who all
have that say i wanted guys don't
have heavy and they're all staring at
you like you're doing a terrible job
and yeah the wrong choice yeah and
they're they're not there's nothing about it
that's supportive like when you're in there
in the room
the the early spring conversations yes oh
it's usually very just you go in
for theatrical audition that everyone's there once
you to do well yeah there are
at least not slow down the production
yeah but they're and they're giving you
like they're giving you space to do
your best gotten the material in advance
most of the time yes whereas with
a commercial edition you just walk in
and maybe read off a board
yeah and they're supposed to do it
naturally or you're just supposed to like
note do a bunch of weird actions
with no props or eat something that's
like supposed to be something else like
eat this bun but yeah it's like
fucking orange teller mime a weird thing
like extremely specific thing yeah reminds me
that's like really physical and hard to
do by yourself because yes not real
and i also carry
and they pair you up with yeah
people and a stranger a stranger and
you have to pretend you've been married
for twenty years so anytime i watch
a commercial now and there's people who
are like arm and arm and going
well when i well we thought and
it's always strangers yeah and that's just
banking oh what were they talking about
between right takes yeah anyway so yes
so i had sworn off doing
ing them and then i got a
request from ah you know my agent
says i'm the director the director requested
you to come in for this yeah
and i was like oh captain trap
that happened oh so much time and
it was a campaign that was like
you would be you would be the
the star of this campaign and so
could be very lucrative right you know
and i was like ok
so i go in and um the
the casting assistant starts reading off names
and saying or not the assistant was
one of the people who ran the
company and one of the one of
the the heads of the casting company
is reading names saying okay you you
you you're reading for this part over
here and they put me in the
group for
for the character that had like one
line as opposed to the supposed to
the thing the thing that i was
told and i said um oh actually
i was told that so you spoke
up for yourself which is good yes
i would have just been like yeah
so i was taking reading for this
other part and she said well i'm
telling you now that you're read
paying for this and then the other
fucking actors laughed and everything ross was
like grade school that's so so crumple
up the pages throw them better i
i stayed and i did the other
part ah and then i called my
agent immediately and said this is what
happened right and they said that's not
right that's almost supposed to happen so
they straighten out i went back in
and then i saw the two casting
directors talking to each other and looking
at me oh no one came up
to said sorry no ma they weren't
in the room when i went in
law it and then i heard what
what if the die oh good what
the fuck ah
ah that's the punchline to this and
you feel great about it's the the
petty ist i've ever felt in my
life what i did i did for
one second i was like a person
would mean to me i tell you
about i don't know if i told
you so does mean to me as
done
um one day on are you feeling
high
one day i was going to brunch
on new year's day hey this is
quite new years day quite a few
years ago this is back in the
nineties um and i again the nineties
that's nice
and he just started trying out a
song that sounds like fuckin what does
it what does it back in listen
day now any kids so good that
life in the past wow
also the closing credit song from bojack
horse oh the oh it is nineties
i was in a very famous tv
show oh really it would be if
i didn't say oh they're ooh there
is a sigh oh i sit correctly
i support it
well more instead of a small tract
and it's ice supportive but support name
you see so there isn't a song
i didn't realize i was in the
story it's true
so i was making a left into
the parking lot and ah it was
one of those parking lots where it
had two driveways one was an end
in one was an hour oh and
i was hooked
i was making the left into the
in well that's and then then a
woman in a car oh started trying
to go out the in driveway and
so confused so i'm i'm in the
driveway right and this woman in this
like sort of su ve is is
like beeping and beeping and and saying
like backup and she's wanting me to
back up into traffic i think like
to reverse endeavor she is going out
the wrong way she's going out the
wrong way and so i'm like good
presumably safely back enjoy bylaw and so
i was like first you try to
point and go on a row you
have it wrong like there are new
rules okay one i
in my head was like one first
county first you got a point just
trying to make her realize she made
a mistake too then you get out
of your car and then you make
fun of her hello that's nah you're
gonna leave your car in traffic yeah
well no i was in trouble i'm
in the driveway you pointed running hey
you're going like no
gives me ma'am and then she's like
angrily beeping like you know you back
up and then i got out and
i started like pointing i love me
my i'm making fly and pointing pointing
arrows so much better than pointing at
her laughing laughing she rolls down the
window and says you just made a
big mistake
take because i'm a casting director oh
and then she peels our roof nurses
because these are traffic laws yeah but
i always say i always wanted it
to come back to bite me in
the ass somehow of like to get
into an audition and she wonderful turns
around is like well well well well
well well guess you won't be on
the new season of golden girls when
you're wasn't looking
i mean back in the nineties back
in the nine mm is make sure
you you let me know when he's
gonna be here so i can turn
the chair around and yeah just let
me know because i don't want to
be facing him i wanna see who
comes not expectedly i have to steal
my thing what is that how noxious
is that the typical casting director behavior
like i hear a lot of nice
casters were
when i had to praise them all
now sure yeah
really great great people love them so
much but um you pay for catholic
drinkers every day i only pray for
them they put you in hockey watson
they and that's alison jones who actually
yeah because there's another candor but she's
the one who got me and i
love alison jones yeah love all the
newscasters she's around degrees
excuse me i'm choking on my own
cough stone but i want to say
that yesterday i was driving down a
one-way street going around a corner and
then a car was coming towards me
but i couldn't remember the one way
because i was like right so confused
because it's just yeah yeah you're going
to see it i know stone had
my gourd and but he was so
nice about it oh wait he's already
backing up because i was really just
confused but then he used like i
know sorry i was going wrong then
you couldn't do anything because it was
like too long that he made a
mistake and he was like huh huh
huh and i was like oh yeah
and i just drove i try and
try to be i try to get
into a headspace when i drive words
like i remember i made photo boyfriend
because someone was like like doing
an unsafe turn in front of him
and eddie said careful hun huh and
he didn't get mad or whatever you
just careful hun and i tried to
get into the careful hun mindsets now
when i drive i there and the
our local post office they don't go
there don't go there step dot com
ha i mean this will turn anyone
ever damn okay they change the in
and the out of the parking lot
why because it was it was illogical
okay it was that the um the
inn was on the far side of
the lot and the bulgari larger stores
it's like
yes it was a cow standing on
his hind legs directly
the cat was wearing glasses of course
um that if you are driving towards
it um you had to go past
the the out to get to the
inn and so it caused a lot
of consternation because a lot of consternation
but peasants were very superstitious associates it
had been this way forever and so
even though there were
signs all over the place people were
going out the wrong way and and
going in the wrong sometimes you just
blow it on purpose i'll just go
hey that's wrong that's easier for sure
people did that but i was pulling
in one day and a guy was
coming out this guy was like it
was a muscle car with tinted windows
ooh sexy
sounds so hot i say stick is
huge high etc and i jerked off
ah we've ruined yeah oh yeah i
allow myself to only do it here
yeah okay good thank you so i
want to turn in this guy was
coming out and i like had to
mn
hoover around him now and i just
kind of shook my head inside my
own car oh instead under my breath
you fuckin idiot
oh so then i go hard he'll
he saw me he saw you shaking
the head and doing that thing yeah
it's like h i couldn't ask them
my a i couldn't see him it's
like the c c oh yeah sam
my
so i park in this guy comes
up to my driver's side lettuce hey
you call me you call me stupid
and i just play dumb and i
was like this is because i i
decided early on this was going to
be my move in situations like this
which and this comes up a lot
every single day
i always say i'm talking shit i
just i just say super innocently i
don't know what you're talking about right
yeah and they can't do anything if
you're like if yes if you are
like women you shouldn't have done this
it's like well fuck you oh yeah
you know it just escalates where if
you're like what whatever are you talking
about my dear boy but i did
have some myself saying actually i called
you a fucking idiot right
yeah exact correcting don't paraphrase me you're
not great at lip reading fucking alien
but you got the g you've got
yeah alright we need to go to
a break we'll be right back
hi we're ah i didn't get a
speaking sink memo
well yeah you have to check your
memos have you checked them have you
checked your spam folder ah no it's
freezing in here right it it's cold
it was super cold when we first
started and now i feel like it's
heating up not me whenever i call
to have an email that was spam
at gmail dot com oh i think
very
cool about someone on this done that
i bet someone always has diseases about
somebody did that what was your first
email i was on aol well yeah
right your first email noel no my
first was earthlink because i was in
the church sides oh my yeah my
first was earthlink i was ie carstairs
at earthlink ducky car
stairs yeah and i got net excuse
does that mean that was a the
name of a character that i played
in a sketch does that interest i
don't want my my email address to
be my name will know back in
the day everyone was like you gotta
come up with a fun name that
means something to you for email you
know which why it just seemed more
interesting
being ah mine was it was a
hold over from no telling what else
will he was a holdover from screen
names from chat room yeah for me
because my mind was the screen name
which was my email right and it
was lackey thirteen u t t which
looked like but ah intentionally or
okay yeah i was wondering if you
went to aqi thirteen utility know i
was
but a child
oh and my other one was ironic
and it was elmo and me too
and i was like i'm too old
for elmo but that's why it's funny
because i was like twelve not a
pretty developed senses yeah yeah what was
yours i can't say because i still
use it hell why use your first
one first one at first one last
one
that's how i felt about it he
might um what what platform what blood
for excuse me
to play for web platform i don't
want to talk about it guys really
yeah well do you use an aol
screen name don't you worry about what
i use don't you worry about my
ah get it what kind of computer
did you have laura lee i'm trying
to compaq with a cue com compact
cwa what year um what when we
first got our computer yeah i was
really exciting i believe i was i
believe
it was nineteen eighty five fully believe
it was it was mentioned five we've
got a compaq presario computer i had
in carta which i would use for
school projects what does out it was
like an encyclopedia dough thing even though
i had all the world books right
collected them but it was just more
fun to do it on the computer
didn't know exciting yeah didn't feel like
you're doing homework
some reason it always stands out that
i wrote this paper from in elementary
school about um the statue of liberty
or something or like something yeah it
was that the title of the paper
yeah but ah well what i loved
about it was that you could download
a picture and make and print printed
out and make it your co yeah
but i um
i yeah use the word emigrated instead
of immigrated ah causing harder kind of
told me to do that stupid and
corrected on it and i never forgot
for some reason and i love acknowledge
okay yeah tutors i well i found
it frustrating because and i still feel
confused about the difference feelings to words
because i do believe emma
great means to move somewhere to live
there doesn't it yeah but i think
one emigrates right and then and and
then you emigrate from a place right
and then emigrate means to leave one's
country to live in another great means
is to come into the country to
live permanently yeah right oh so emigrated
not
permanent doesn't have to be migrated to
move like birds in the winter the
christian emigrate immigrate and migrate depends on
the sentences point of view oh yeah
my teacher might have been wrong what
was your point of view oh i
hate that when teachers are wrong but
you know what i mean like maybe
my sentence actually did make sense onto
the computer correct today yeah i've always
thought about the office what statue of
liberty
i've always thought about my i think
i probably talks about my newspaper teacher
when i drew the cartoon newspaper teacher
i don't recall but yeah newspaper teacher
too i was on the school page
you are on your school paper no
i was on the school paper and
i wrote artists high school or grade
school high school so this is like
what was your your section i
horoscopes we would do it
yep advice column ah we would do
whatever we you know we would just
pitch stories and whatever i was the
human editor so yeah occasionally like i
would write a record review
all those shows you were not casting
yeah no i actually talked about movies
and another terrible production i wrote funny
little columns about things i think i
wrote a lamb like ah a takedown
of al gore's wife typical oh sure
temperatures trying to censor media with a
p marcio um but but there was
an article
about spanking that someone wrote and occasionally
i would draw cartoons right oh and
so i wrote i drew a cartoon
of um charlie brown being having been
spanked by justice spanking since you were
but a tween
so charlie it was it was i
think it was an article about teachers
spanking students or something like that and
i drew ah charlie brown being spanked
by teacher and him saying good grief
with like you know embarrassed that's what
he'd say yeah so it's one of
his favorite things to say i do
you think it's his favorite thing to
say or it's a thing that he
ends up saying because his he hates
say
ng for knee jerk response at this
point right you know what he's the
architect of his own misery and fuck
him here's my lucy is the architect
can i finish the story can finish
can i finish absolutely so the teacher
three times the teacher points like gets
the entire class around takes out the
cartoon and says can someone to
tell me what the problem with this
is
this is copyrighted material and someone said
that gets copyrighted anyway and he said
exactly and spammed you know rolled up
and in my head he drew squiggly
line in your forehead in my head
i knew the count i knew what
this concept of the concept of fair
use was but i didn't know how
i didn't know what it was called
know what it was i'm sitting there
going
like i'm pretty sure this is fine
to use because if you grew up
with like mad magazine and stuff like
that you haven't you have an idea
in your have an idea of what
is this satire you and it's usable
so but i didn't know the term
fair use i'm sitting there going well
i guess the teachers right and he
made a fool out of me in
front of everyone and then made me
re-draw the the comic and everything and
then once i am
yeah the boys speak the boys mind
the boy is my yeah yeah michael
jackson not to bring him up
during the monica marandi version of boys
what if yeah he's saying the girls
via you said the boy is mine
with that of tip anyone off honestly
yeah
what is your problem you were gonna
say your problem is something
we're talking about teachers were talking about
the newspaper newspaper class yeah thinking on
it huh i had a cheap i
got interrupt you when i want grade
i had to write a paper and
i used the phrase ah i'm gonna
say it wrong i think one noel
calandra is at one in the same
one end the same one
one and these these two people are
one in the same one emphasis one
end this and i think i wrote
one in the same right and the
teacher one like in the stink took
a mark off for that and corrected
it right and i remember at the
time being outraged like
i get that i was wrong but
still you see the shit every day
from kids my age hey anything any
other dum dum sage i knew remember
phrase right parents never playing scrabble when
i was a kid and i put
down aura but i spelled it o
r a and they were like what
did you not know that and then
i was like how do i know
aura like it's like yeah
it's pretty random org going with yeah
i remember when i was when i
was eight but i'm not the dumb
one here when i was eight the
teacher maybe stand up and spit because
i was a really good speller and
i was like okay well how do
you spell rhythm and made me stand
up and i was like i don't
know to this day i was like
r i t no wrong damn she
finally took
you down yeah just because i was
like so yes you're right i wasn't
even talking about i mean some of
my teachers would have me read to
the students from books because they were
like tired or whether you're a really
good read and like most of that
yeah yeah i think we're all we're
all the same we are the same
well there's that there's that alright let's
say let's take a break know more
about your teacher
do you really want to talk about
your teacher before
it because we're gonna move i really
want to you want to go weird
you need to i need you to
i'm begging to hear what you're gonna
say i had a teacher i thought
about her today my eighth grade teacher
was was someone that
huh yeah
hearing the words eighth gray like oh
okay um i follow and she was
very she clearly was very um when
i look back on it it's very
complicated because she's real clearly very encouraging
of me but we were at odds
all the time and she would frequently
make me stay after class and
when i think about it now i
can't remember why i'm sure it was
just like i was you know being
disruptive in class or talking or whatever
attention cool but i wasn't like
i wasn't like like doing shit that
was like look at me look at
me like i would make jokes or
whatever i loved doing that saying look
at me look at me you know
some jokes in school yeah it's the
best it's so fun yeah so fine
i guess it is maybe a desperate
need for attention at the core well
it's like if you're trailing certainly trying
to be liked by your appear yeah
you
no and it's like and once you
get a taste of it you you
it feels good when you're just like
you're getting that you're getting that that
approval from other people and i was
like oh you're also figuring out this
is a thing i'm good at yeah
you know and so i yes every
once in a while i probably would
say something out loud you know
to get a laugh from the whole
class but more often than not it
was just like my little group of
people around me or whatever right so
she would i remember her trying like
she was clearly trying to get through
to me like break through to me
but when i think about it like
it was there was never going to
work like like you're a comedian like
like you are born this way
yeah like i don't know what what
i think about whatever lesson it was
that she was trying to instill in
me it just didn't work yeah and
it was clearly never going to work
i know like for some reason i
never got punished for that even though
i'm sure it was annoying at times
but i i that's interesting i maybe
i wonder if it's a boy girl
thing where it's like they would make
him stay
after class to try to go like
you really shouldn't be like that right
it's like it almost seems like like
it feels like because more it seems
more aggressive maybe i don't know but
it almost seems like in a sexist
society that they would try to tell
the girl i said that's not ladylike
to jack to make jokes like that
or whatever yeah i don't know i
had a teacher come up to me
ah i think twelve years after i
gr
graduated or some something like that and
ah knows ten years i remember because
ah the we had just been nominated
nine nominated for emmys for the for
the history story you have told a
story and you will get spanked will
i get spanked were know your your
homework what you'll write your homework
iirc i know right buddy you know
who is next like i'm not telling
that part of the story you know
who is next to her oh my
lol jags my casting director oh that
my newspaper teacher oh shit he was
parking parking lot turn on the story
you don't do your homework my newspaper
teacher was right there next to her
and he was
just loving it the entire time and
and then i knew what fair use
was by then i was like hey
hey yes oh yes remember me
fair yes guy okay so my new
age i know oh i don't like
journalism teacher as we call ya p
i have a photograph that sounds better
than newspaper picture i have a photograph
of him lifting up his shirt to
show a t shirt that he's wearing
underneath his sweatshirt okay and it's that
janet jackson cover with her boobs wax
and he's proudly showing i took a
picture of my disposable kick why does
he show me that everyone is he's
funny i don't know alright very funny
let's go to a break we'll be
right back
we're back we're back it's time for
a feature this one comes from listener
on our twitter feed at super long
weekend super long weekend yeah but w
candy okay it's called carmela and livia
first person carmela gives the second live
compliment livia gets five seconds to twist
into an insult for a point back
to carmela to defend back to livia
five seconds to twist that defense third
person judges and counsel livia points longest
livia streak wins i don't know why
they're named carmella and livia from the
sopranos oh it is okay that's something
that that those characters would do
do i guess maybe so it's pretty
fun this is a two person thing
yeah the third person judges it okay
encounter the livia point and so when
when the person turns the compliment into
a ah slam and then the other
person is trying to turn that slam
into water back into a compliment or
into know the person so yeah i
comp
mind you you twisted into an insult
for a point then i then i
defend what i meant and the new
twisted again oh oh sorry so you
so only points are available from the
olivia's yeah you compliment a person then
that person can has to make it
so that it's an insult another common
yeah okay got it got it let's
try it let's try it who's one
of course let's try
okay um who wants to go and
of course she wants to go first
and of course i was gonna say
don't hurt each other's feelings ah this
is why everybody ok alright your own
feelings know the compliments yes exactly that's
why it's ok alright you guys go
first alright can seem safe am i
livia joint time anything or no i'm
just watching or mike we should definitely
time it because it feels like we
don't want this to go on forever
um okay who do you want who
do you want to be i'll be
carmela okay and i'm gonna use the
stopwatch oh yeah beautiful feature we are
a feature of the give it to
me yeah and so how long would
go a minute yeah a minute okay
starting now i love your long ponytail
you didn't like my hair the way
it was before like suddenly you like
my ponytail and suddenly a more handsome
to you i mean that doesn't make
any sense i've i think that i'm
good-looking enough that my hair doesn't really
matter know you're here definitely doesn't matter
i just noticed that you put some
extra effort into brushing it and it
looked really extra effort extra effort to
look beautiful i think i can look
beautiful without any effort i don't know
why i need to to add effort
to something in order to look acceptable
to your eyes honestly you look wonderful
whether you brush your long ponytail or
not and actually i didn't why are
you noticing when i don't brush my
i normally brush my hair
in the morning okay like standard operating
procedure for me no you're not sitting
around like not brushing my hair all
day no you're right and one one
thing that's great that you don't have
to brush is your perfect eyebrows and
mustache fuck are you serious right now
it my eyebrows you know that i
cut these every single name i'm not
sure how this is a game
ah how many points do i get
that game clear to you
oh seriously
it's also kind of easy isn't it
yeah let's try it again alright so
the only way to know if something's
gotta do it three times what do
you i would say probably you should
keep your everyone's the change exchanges should
be brief okay sorry yes i'm going
off to you okay i mean who
does you know what suddenly i talked
too much for you
is that when replaying you compliment paul
okay but analogy this
go hey paul i really wanted to
say that i saw bojack horseman the
other day and you so funny in
it
oh so you saw it the other
day you know you haven't been watching
from the beginning why
you know i don't have time to
watch every bit of media that's out
there but um yeah i knew that
you were on it i got that
info and i decided to do it
to watch it and it's just wonderful
you do a wonderful job i'm glad
you eventually got the info that i've
been doing this show for the past
five years well i don't you're not
a bragging type of guy
i didn't even know that you were
on it i mean you're you're very
humble and you you keep that information
really close to the vest i'm humble
because i don't have much to brag
about no you have a lot to
brag about that's why i'm saying i
had no idea that you even were
on this show until recently and the
minute i found out about i checked
it out and your wonderful so you
don't listen to me well that's what
i'm trying to say is you're not
the type of guy
to go out there bragging about all
of your accomplishments which are many so
i'm too good for you now yeah
ty actually i agree i think my
mistake was it creating a character for
scott it because then it could be
anything that you say would make sense
whereas this
is harder when you did a great
job and i think that's five or
six thank you um okay say so
i would do it again but little
i'll do my whole compliments lauren
are you gonna timeless know
you have your hands now i gotta
open up alright here we go where
no oh no i gotta go all
the way to my phone i gotta
open up
what how do i do the time
recall my phone landlord to let me
in what do i press to do
the time you slide it over to
the stopwatch
look at this ape
sliding sliding down in a stopwatch i
don't think you're in the stopwatch oh
okay got it good
alright ready and wait a couple of
anymore yes okay and ca
lowering your eyes are very like sparkly
today oh so they're usually really dull
no i just mean that so maybe
it's the time of day or something
like you just they're just like radiant
wow so normally they just look like
two empty pennies no i think i
think you always look nice i think
you you're always lovely and you you
dre
rest well and you just i just
noticed your eyes like maybe the way
the light is hitting them oh so
i have to have my eyes going
to the light in a certain way
for them to look nice or otherwise
you won't notice them know everyone notices
them you have very very striking oh
so my eyes are so weird that
everyone's looking at them and noticing them
because they're so unusual that it's actually
alarming to people no p
people are delighted they they they love
seeing you people can't help but smile
so people don't want to hear a
word out of my mouth they just
wanna look at me so i'm just
a fucking shell peep know people people
i think everyone enjoys you and they
look forward to seeing you oh really
so when they're not seeing me they're
thinking about this time
that was hard no point for the
last one but yeah yeah last one
i was was just yeah it was
hard oh sure i'll do it again
because i think it's it's harder okay
ready still might not be a game
okay my man it's a feature right
you can't argue with that yeah obviously
any future being featured in future ready
and go wow you're so tall
yeah i'm like a giant fucking giant
who everyone likes a point laughing oh
i think a lot of guys would
like to be taller so i think
it's great for you that you're tall
well guess what they would like to
be but they're gonna find out it's
no fucking picnic oh really okay for
fighting
ah well whatever i whatever and oh
yeah sure yeah whatever i say doesn't
matter no i didn't mean anything by
it i mean bonus point you look
nice and your shirt today it's a
very nice place where are you looking
at me without a shirt you fucking
weird i've never once seen you without
a shirt i'm just saying that you
start creeping on me i'm not re
creeping on you
what the fuck is wrong with you
i'm telling you you're sure it looks
nice oh really i don't want to
say it at all because i am
such a weird fuckin body that you
think like finally i've dressed myself to
disguise it no i just think that
it's it's a nice color on you
with your skin tone my my weird
blotchy skin tone you fucking whore
it's time yeah ah that was excruciating
ah
oh excruciating your feature in the book
better first guy make up a character
with a long ponytail
we received some cds from a listener
cool wow alright we'll see next time
someone sent us some cd
are you shell shocked because of the
game what are the cds
what's happening this one says doku doku
doku
don't
no take of dooku
oki doki doki was the say i
gotta get yeah thank you
dough comin okay he was well how
would you say that e bow
what does happy people silva g document
evo i released this what does it
mean i don't know i have no
idea thank you thank you to doku
evo thank you doku man
um this one ah israel by x
x or x x by it's real
i don't know this is like somebody
is a music manager this this guy
wow this guy who has two thumbs
instead of cds
hell i think that brings us to
the end shop lamb chops oh i
like lamb chop dana yeah i'm chop
um guys i had fun got a
little contentious maybe because of the feature
yeah yeah the featured is a little
aggressive at the end too aggressive i
have a lot of record what we're
working let's i'll fix
him in the next one week well
i don't mean anything i said during
that feature i apologize i meant every
word you're sure he's these
i man i didn't mean the compliments
oh that's not how we should end
this we gotta go all right well
we really gotta go alright hello
uh