sorry
ah hello
a lady at bagley juniors that we
were saying yep ed begley junior begley
my favorite curse word yeah janis joplin
look at this place
okay instead of i beg to differ
a bit
good
differ advice and maybe different really good
name and family name if your name
was ed begley junior and there's already
one in sag you can just change
it ed begley jr yeah if you
were if your name was ed begley
junior
yep i'd go with epically different and
and that you're gonna be inside you're
also an actor but you're not related
to him no my name is ed
begley different yeah
um ah do you think that ed
begley sr lived long enough to see
himself eclipsed by his savoie was he
an actor i don't yeah wow wow
so you don't even know that i
personally have seen all of his films
tv shows
acting place
hurdles
were those original
i'm assuming he was always grandfather what's
your favorite sucking every monday
candy that sucks you yeah
yaakov worth a million yeah um i
remember as a kid i was very
drawn to lifesavers because i thought that
package was amazing it is amazing was
it and then also specifically the different
flavors like like the you would get
a whole roll of butterscotch you know
whatever you liked everything about it i
liked everything about it so you can
you didn't like variety if you could
why would i do but i did
like the variety i liked them all
is what i'm saying oh look more
like this style that class id tags
yeah the classic lifesaver like rainbow assortment
yeah is very that as very iconic
you like things in that shape like
pringles and stuff like things like tubes
things that are tubes like yeah like
all identical
oh yeah you're thinking of the short
pringles yeah for code there they are
playing one long pringles like a lot
of chose our can like cho chose
her or thick chips are thicker than
they are long i know but they're
more mean makes them to bring toys
like gases long
long yeah i know what the toxic
pringles is like but i mean if
if very good more very good you
covered a penis that was shaped like
either of those things it would be
frightening yeah me either yeah classic pringles
you're not flat at the top if
yard and i mean like any buffalo
it's wonderful but if your dick looks
exactly like a pringle
can you have a problem she already
loves a guy like brain goes gad
you have wow especially with mr pink
pink pinkel yeah there he gets his
name his name is mr pinho mister
penguin sells pringles yeah you read that
they got his name he doesn't sell
them maybe he represents them i'm mister
dingell jr yeah yeah
i'm in springville different
just what i meant to say ah
funny how you're lying you're gonna set
us up so well that it was
like actually better what what it was
a happy action it was whatever what
it was is that we got to
say the joke yeah yeah that you
thought yeah yeah yeah so paul your
t-shirt is is it missing the dough
or is it missing the f his
shirt says are
r i t o s so it's
either torrijos or freedoms we don't know
fritos cheetos fritos f
i didn't think like well what is
fun rico's um it is not missing
either of those why did his short
for cerritos and that is the oh
that's a chip on your decks right
yeah great oh great i love it
i love you you guys lovie how
many people fell of you two were
okay
those are my friends and i love
you that's threatening yeah with the knife
have we had nah god
how many people ask you if it's
doritos though no i don't wear this
in public oh okay i got a
sweatshirt over it i don't wear this
in public i'm not your friend i'm
not you're not the public okay wow
and you're dropping like mooney when you
consider t-shirt wearing worthy my wife viet
wow
um scott i didn't get to hear
what candy you love to suck the
most yeah let's say of all the
things we've ever talked about let us
not lose sight on out there is
wondering what he was gonna say who
cares yeah i know my thing i
love ah huh just saying although i
had a lot of cough drops recently
because i had bronchitis for a couple
of weeks yeah and ah there was
one day that was really what it
was weird because i was totally past
being sick and everything but there was
one day it was very hard to
talk so i did it was a
good day for everyone around you well
know i had to do already know
i had to record
in episodes i did that and no
oh no and i and then i
went to a concert that night too
and i felt so happy to hear
that you had bronchitis you were just
out no i was i was over
like being you know sick with it
and all that kinda stuff it just
it it it was like a week
and a half later it it just
was very difficult so you couldn't even
cheer for your favorite band i know
oh that's so stuff l e t
fox is
but you had your your scarf of
course i were waving over your head
yes i eat raw count cone raccoon
raccoon and ya what was wrong yeah
i'm talking you the thing that you
shout and megaphone well like doesn't make
voters it's like a card is wrong
did they say ra and then sometimes
wow re la ra ra rasputin oh
wow rios rivera rios rodriguez rodriguez rios
are you alright
i don't even know what that is
because new zones so i had to
sing it yeah if it was called
sanford and daughter would you have watched
yeah probably they're doing the reboot of
san francisco is it sanford and daughter
i bet it's woke it is wrong
and there's there's unlike sanford's it's i
believe taking the place of the son
character is a trans child this is
real comfort has this is real they
are rebooting all the show can i
tell you something there's a little earworm
i have from a tv show and
i think you'll know what i mean
when i explained the okay phenomenon
do you sometimes you hear a phrase
that you remember is the pay somebody
sank
i'm not talking but that's a different
phrase in different okay but if you
say it are listening to this music
call in this is if i of
course if i ever see the phrase
that pays yes you call it out
that said it's where over one hundred
episodes yeah you have never said the
phrase that pays know i will i've
i've promised that i will on one
of these episodes yes say the phrase
that pays and then the many you
say it then the piss picks call
all in and then they have a
chance to win how much i think
it was like seven fifty seven hundred
and fifty dollars seven hundred and fifty
thousand episodes that we'd seven hundred and
fifty thousand dollars alright somewhere in between
it's either it's between seven hundred and
fifty eight dollars fifty thousand dollars they
say it is a dollar and if
i do say that phrase which i
can't say now all these
you can say it now no but
it is the phrase but we said
it like way warren is on her
will ya hundred and sixty six episodes
know why yeah lott well wait so
we get to two hundred we need
a party yeah it's part everyone's in
highness cast party at mom's house cami
romper okay i'm sorry what
we go to the howard johnson's go
to the whoa joe's jump into lesson
you will ever know each other um
probably a cast party at high school
musical yeah i went to ho jio's
um i've been there once in my
life since then but i remember in
eighth grade we went to springfield as
a trip springfield illinois yeah i was
in a hotel we stayed in a
hotel we stayed at howard johns
and there was a pool i say
at the howard johnson's in new york
and nineteen hundred and eighty two do
they still retain are they still around
first of all i know they retain
the same color scheme because it was
like teal and orange yeah hi gorgeous
it actually worked really well yeah i
can't look at it let me look
like ron x howard johnson's iconic it's
so i looked at my gallery
john psionic oh my god scott is
literally on his phone oh my so
fucking room ah if you if you
have ah if you have a phrase
like a common phrase that you hear
anaheim is the first some reason you
have in your head you remember somebody
in a movie or a tv show
saying oh i went today that i
was thinking of so whenever anybody is
if something is
somebody says is that real
i here's what i think of yeah
i think of
that movie that tv movie the late
shift was on a yeah with ah
what's ah john michael higgins yeah letterman
and daniel roebuck is jay leno daniel
roebuck ever do anything afterwards or was
he executed james executed
he was executed in aj's garage whoa
no way no you were the paul
stewart and now you want if daniel
roebuck should do that actually took jay's
place when jay had the accident and
that's why he's he's like oh i
have facial scars from it but it
was really a off situation i like
that that's a really good idea like
i don't have really a face on
because that's what all the prosthetics but
someone had to
make a face off but here's what
will the fire took j's face off
but it didn't really it was it
was it was a face aussie was
a total it was a total nothing
ever happened it was just the way
they explained why he had scarring he
had something scars why don't you get
about
it's other i don't get it it's
that i didn't know where he suffered
his damage his face his major malfunction
yeah his major malfunction what's g's damage
he's some metro functions
yeah
so that's what i think of okay
so i think of rich little as
johnny carson whole right he made some
announce that he's retiring or whatever and
then he walks off stage and he
says to whoever people are stunned that
he says to whoever it's real i
said it it's real sad
anytime anybody questions the veracity they say
the word if they say is this
real or is that real you say
what i think it's real i have
to fight to not say about that
i feel like this one i don't
even know why it enters my head
but today i was having a long
thing about it and yep in my
head and the fr
res is and i'm sure you won't
know the film but the phrases why
because i don't think i am almost
positive scott hasn't seen it because of
his podcast got you have to do
it on scott oh my god i
can't don't even know what it is
yet i think we've talked about it
because i we might talk about but
anyway the line is if bullshit were
a bra you'd be top-heavy
that's from ah the one where christopher
plummer plays like wallace from the insider
yeah the insider no that's from that's
from where christopher plummer no he took
the place of kelly's kevin spacey know
all the money in the world no
that's the one where christopher plummer yeah
mary
these juliet truths oh yes why didn't
that why wasn't christopher plummer that wine
was in the sound of music yeah
if bullshit could wear a bra
why wasn't christopher plummer in the mario
brothers movie it's right there and i
am that's a great question and i
don't have an answer yeah he should
have been he shouldn't he should have
done a cameo as himself at least
where the mario brothers look at him
and go wait a minute are you
if somebody was a need a plumber
and then he's like we were talking
about me and then the mario brothers
go no amanda
and why wasn't david toilet in it
good
keep been up to lately which was
executed by jay leno no david toilet
got execute some goodbye
wait so what movies were my girl
two oh yeah i'm seeing the gun
yes yeah i know we gotta do
it you should watch my girl without
me now let's do it tonight know
my girl i do a podcast you
never favorite fucking way i have to
do five
a week you know i realize that's
kind of how i socialize is knowing
it's honestly he's doing shows well used
to be of maybe seeing people backstage
yeah and now it seeing people doing
pot but i'm i know it's be
nice to go out and see but
somebody and not not have a microphone
i know it's kind of i at
least wear a lot if there was
a level of my trip
last because that i really enjoyed because
of the fact that it involved no
okay extra extra lauren went on a
trip i did i did lawrence travel
corner wait before we get into that
segment which everyone loves yeah can i
say another one that burdens me and
yeah yeah movie your worm is in
it's from that thing you do ah
huh
i love i used to watch a
play those drums down
hey put those drums down i think
you stole those drums didn't you i
think it's worth i have a worthy
onedrive is
ah no it is yeah that comes
up a lot
whenever anybody says oh meters
um it's towards the end of the
film everything's falling apart
and jonathan shy
he quits him out yes who is
angry he was the fourth guy we
know i think i mean i know
i hit the guy even that narrow
i don't think we get enough of
the guys from this movie like nowadays
i'm like where are you at yeah
ye um he quits the band and
when he does he says um i
forgot i
i don't remember how he gets into
it jonathan sheesh but he quits by
saying i quit i quit and i
won i despise i hate having that
in my head that is really annoying
to hear in your head yes so
when you come to like it when
it happened i didn't like when he
did it it comes up when you
want to quit things no if somebody
says if i hear somebody say i
quit or they quit or whatever
so essentially we surely would just hackfest
if you do it don't tell me
just let me find out by showing
up here and the door's lock what
if we just say i'm no longer
doing it without help are you so
like oh that would help queer
i hate it the snaps can i
say something about related to the late
shift i pushing you out today yes
so before we gonna be some sweet
sounds coming down so the late shift
um i i o
he was a tv haunted hall bear
oh jay leno
oh oh jay leno um okay but
i was i saw a g car
through it's a johnny carson clip huh
i was thinking jay carney
hey yes his initials j yeah so
do you think jay leno got it
because his initials the same do you
think everyone's gotten this kind of racial
yeah johnny j jimmy jimmy yeah oh
my gosh but okay so i was
watching jon and who knows who was
watching johnny carson clip and i was
like
i don't know how anyone with a
family or a rabbit and i know
a family watched this for a job
could ever stay up to you know
how people are like i turned it
on i fall asleep people were staying
up till midnight or twelve fifteen or
twelve thirty when they had to work
the next day or take care of
their kids who are these
okay glad it all when voting day
and night now what he taught everybody
was drunk all the time that's it
you didn't they would say i would
pay out till midnight and i'm going
what am i doing and i'm like
well having a good time it's surprising
to me sometimes when i text you
and you're yeah you're up yeah at
a late hour and i'm like what
for you guys i like you as
me and nine
i'm asleep yeah i like my little
time you know i like my little
time to yeah janie always goes to
bed before me janie goes to bed
i had to but hey how is
it how is it possible how did
how is it so how did enough
people do it god what did people
do it that he was popular and
johnny carson got rich i mean it's
like
like it doesn't make any sense that
people were staying up till midnight every
night you mean during during the no
other way to watch it they had
to watch it at midnight there's no
there there's yeah i think can't type
it you've got a lot of people
who were young lawyer about being hired
no i don't think it's different at
all i think if there's just don't
care about who don't have a job
people who are younger
kids and teens and there it wasn't
two maybes and twenty and only it
was tina good values johnny carson didn't
have like a teen audience are you
kidding me know if anyone's love you
but like when i was a teenager
i loved watching conan and staying up
until mean yeah sure yeah no but
i mean when you're a teenager yeah
because you're you naturally stay up late
but i just don't know like how
carson was all
also the age of three channel tv
yeah and so there was it was
a and when people still had the
the common viewing experience like the idea
of we're all watching this at the
same yeah it was on at midnight
it wasn't new tens i live in
thirty it used time used to be
on a midnight and then he liked
negotiated to go back to eleven thirty
three midnight it was nigh
ninety minutes long yeah but that's the
thing zeit is crazy even staying up
till eleven to watch the news is
like we're a weird idea me now
i don't know i think you're talking
specifically about yourself and you're making it
about everyone you're trying to make a
universal i think everyone stays up at
different hours some people stay up all
night sweet eleven some new i'm just
saying people who have to get up
at
six in the morning edge tool to
have
initial fanbase and tell me
i'm saying generally look yes there are
exceptions to your dumb exception slip up
but if there's only fucking basically one
show around at that time yeah if
you're awake that's what you're watching so
that means that anybody in the country
on any given night who is awake
and wants to watch tv it's gonna
watch that show specifically so that means
he's
famous and everyone cares like it'll balance
out everyone will eventually watch it it's
gonna happen and then he's probably hosting
all sorts of other things and you're
like i'm gonna steps manually night and
watching it finds a way you know
before before your baby did you have
the same problem oh yeah well yes
but also how late i mean means
it before michale would could you go
like eleven
or something i usually go to bed
early but but if you knew there
was a tv show you interact you
could push through any when i was
younger we have ddr and you don't
have anything when i was younger i
would stay up till two in the
morning but if you're well yeah two
in the morning but if you are
i'm saying now if if it were
if you were you now and it's
still three channel tv yeah and there's
a late night show that is one
of the only late night shows i
just you liked it
i bet you could do it i
think there'd be a lot of me
staying up late watching that well i
was trying to watch i see a
lot of that and of me in
that scenario i think i'd be a
big carson hey i think i'd be
saying johnny carson you're the best you're
my king this is applicable i was
trying to watch coachella this last weekend
only likes a monologue and then i
go frank ocean does the book um
but i was trying to stay up
to see some of the later things
in black paint came on at nine
thirty and add a half hour i
was like i guy that's you i'm
betting yes but i i think that
i have that in common with
people especially during the work you're not
alone i don't think you're alone and
all but i think if if someone's
like i'm going to watch coachella it's
this person i want to see your
group is on at nine thirty but
that's fine dvd to take a break
that's so unfair
and we're back oh how convenient these
things
provably have audiences i know i'm just
saying that nobody like people aren't lying
like my wife stayed up till like
thirty but my question is what how
was life different for people back then
why how could they do it right
you know what i mean like what
were people just like oh i don't
give a shit how tired i am
when i go into the office every
day and people just were drinking at
work and yeah i
main person yeah and if i'm only
living to fifty anyway yeah you know
i gotta say this latest part but
maybe if i said before i die
you want to get a few laps
and get a few laughs it and
you know what sometimes with johnny carson
with babu's even funnier than with the
jokes did wow i love that yeah
i feel like i didn't get to
see jodie carson at his
peak because like if you watch him
in the sixties or whatever it's funny
but like we were watching him in
the eighties and it was yeah pretty
creaky but and how did you stay
up shit
yeah anyway tell us about your trip
lauren okay i went to portland last
weekend for my friend mariah smith's birthday
again i'll plug the smith sisters live
on serious exam time is a week
really hilarious show um it was so
fun it was a group of girls
seven of us and hot um yeah
she's really hot and we just had
a great time just you know drinking
and needed and shopping and drink and
eaten piss and chinking yeah right oh
hi all did all of that yeah
i assume i don't want to assume
you probably have your you were gone
three days you probably it was it
was basically how many limbs thursday night
i was there friday saturday so
sunday left sunday night i pooped probably
na nine times i would say probably
twenty seven thirty times if i'm being
honest thirty to thirty five thank you
for your candor upwards of sixty if
i'm being honest
probably be my hundred and twenty there
wasn't much time where i was yeah
where people concerned for you or no
no you're all doing that oh everybody
bathrooms just like we got at a
room with one hundred toilets wow side-by-side
one room a hundred toilets tonight on
johnny carson who wants to be a
toilet air um but it was really
fun and it was nice i don't
typically go do things like that where
i'm traveling just for fun with friends
yeah ah these days at least and
um i had a great time and
i was really able to fully relax
in my my days did you get
into a pool
rule no we did not um but
we did eat so much good food
we went to like a lot of
fun restaurants and did you ever have
a tortilla did it have a tortilla
yes i had tacos you didn't have
talked okay interest we had we had
tacos we had we had ah sees
zen's in the sun exactly yeah i'm
gonna ask you once more and this
time be honest did you get into
a pool and remember you're under oath
no but did you drink pool water
yeah ah i had to to get
that law because it was overflowing yeah
you're telling me you guys never carpooled
or an uber pool oh we did
coke haha i know i've tried to
start uberpool karaoke and people just get
mad wow
oh and i really wanna meet a
few interesting uber situations um but yeah
you know i suppose i'm also not
getting into uber's that much in my
life these days but really yeah yeah
you because you own a monster truck
yeah because i want a monster truck
and i ride over everybody and i
just did everywhere for minutes fly straight
line yeah your truck is named lady
elaine it is based on elaine bennis
yes yeah the fictional character from steinfeld
yes um and i love it so
much and it's neon green and it
is do you think anyone out there
is still seeing steinfeld what style it
was just because everyone thought it was
a very common thing they were saying
stop dying biltmore sigh no way
a i never heard steinberg that's yeah
gilding a lawyer heard it at all
never no long glad i could introduce
me to we do everyone i know
everyone i ever heard talk about it
got it exactly right we did do
hailee steinfeld seinfeld jokes when she was
on ferns yeah yeah seinfeld jokes doo
dah doo dah i don't recall that
joke specifically but i um did you
actually like what's the deal with being
stein family
like any press the button in the
theme song um
so why don't you if you liked
it so much why don't you make
it a regular thing where you go
out of town five days a week
yeah you know yeah like i just
go yeah i'm gone monday night i
am um ah i do feel like
i should take more trips but i
was when i got home hollywood cemetery
told you this part but that made
it also like really fun because i
feel like i got to go away
we were able to face time and
she wasn't up
upset which is like a new thing
she's like cry some amp nice and
so now it was like we got
to cry when you saw your face
because i wasn't there like she would
like be like i want to like
tell you shouldn't be three dementia yeah
but then now she was really just
having fun on face time and then
by the last day it was kind
of like too many days do you
think she would cry if she was
watching the wrong miss
see and you are just the other
room um yeah she probably cried she
gets really offended by like potty humor
no
um but her reaction when i got
home was so sweet that i was
like i should leave more often just
to get this kind of re feels
amazing we could give you the interception
you should scream and run all over
the room when i have to say
you're always you're always here before paul
so you should come find me later
like you can scream enough to keep
it going until he gets here
ah well why don't you hide for
five minutes okay but why hide and
if you find a good game i
find you i have to scream yes
so i probably won't really try okay
yeah so you'll be safe wherever you
are if you just were phased out
on the couch i just would pretend
into you what was the game
what was the game you would play
where i can remember the name of
it one person died hide and seek
sardines sardine sardines wait well is it
already thirty one person high
e play is only me there because
you can perfect narrow perfect area i'm
glad we were recording this me too
because you should sell it to number
one single to ah music producer yeah
yeah solid you know i think just
that the first fifteen second long number
one single yeah
no try to nobody that's the thing
there was mayhem too long it's like
yeah losing people by that yeah thirty
seconds if if trump you know ah
the cheeto in chief if he can
get to not the president anymore no
matter how many times i have to
tell you this but he has retained
the lifetime title of chief see i
see
if i was like by the way
i'm cio and chief number two
hey i'm also you know he'd be
like chester yeah because jersey d hey
here's it you know i was thinking
you doing know ma i was thinking
biden because you're like ooh obama and
you said obama giroux and then he'd
be like chester cheeto because he like
cool cool yeah sunglasses yeah longer face
but if if you could get to
number one
one on the item charts with some
dumb song yeah we could get to
number one with just that you singing
what was it sardines sardines you were
saying it with me i know i
wasn't alone how long is the average
pop song three three fifty right say
yeah i said charles short let's fight
yeah
although basketball days it was two and
a half i would imagine back in
the sixties there so yeah you know
that thing like nine years the average
length of a pie klong me again
which does anyone want to guess again
giving any chance whatsoever hand larry fourteen
ski yeah
scottrade it's larry oh yeah average length
of a pop song is three minutes
and thirty seconds larry fourteenth member him
do you know who that is lord
um no does it sound familiar at
all um no larry forty
it's key was one of hollywood legend
elizabeth taylor's final husband's wow i think
the final husband was the last one
i think one of her final husband
but she's got amazing she married eight
times so many times she married richard
burton twice that's that's horrible that's insane
yeah um but ah larry fortescue
he was like a construction worker was
doing work on our house or something
oh it's always one of those yeah
i like the way he looked people
who get married a lot often throw
one of those in there yeah yeah
especially later in life yeah um i
why not i'm rich but i have
judical violent i feel like yes just
kept giving away hearings because they were
lucky andor white diamonds
yeah um i feel like it comes
a more human more than we think
that people marry the same person again
really any leaks i believe did that
really who did she marry twice her
husband oh right he's since passed greg
greg what's his name umm i know
somebody
that got married and divorced i don't
but they got back together but i
don't know if they got married again
i can't remember ah i was at
the first wedding but none at the
second wedding yeah how many how many
times will you go to a person's
weddings like i like if someone's married
multiple times yeah different people to different
people i guess depends how much i
care about the person because i lie
love weddings yeah if it's some asshole
that keeps inviting me i'm like sure
honestly i'd go
oh i go to a fun party
yeah i feel like people who invite
you are your real friends most of
the time and rarely get some champagne
for your event and i think i
would go until they were done i
would go to eight weddings for one
person over the course of my life
i would go from one person i
would go to four weddings and one
funeral yeah who's
well that person oh okay yeah i
think because i figured that by the
time you're like the third one for
that person because like two having been
married twice island it's that big of
a deal to go to but after
that point it's just getting interesting well
now you're like i'm here for the
spectacle yeah what's up with this person
what's with their family when i went
to my friend's second
if the second one i was like
this might be it for me and
then there was a third but i
was not delighted to think that there
was going to be a third at
the second i kind of was like
i wonder if there's gonna be a
third yeah i thought it was going
to be well i mean the odds
are fifty fifty but i i was
sort of like i bet there's gonna
be a third night yeah but i
would go to it but then my
aunt
married your friend yes so there was
a third
my aunt got married four times i
think and the one i sang the
nissan head are so wedding night and
one knows whoever thing oh yeah is
that we said the theme comes to
the store anything
time is on my side
i love making it up but i
was picturing you do
you wanna say for real
time is on my side it's a
good deal like it's got guns i
do it woo guns got consonants
scott has got a beautiful voice what
if he did what have you saying
just like annouce yeah oh
did you really sing i sang on
my on your shore on my shore
i would assume orinoco flow sail away
sail away say well you're on queen
mary and i've been drinking crystal light
or whatever we were on the queen
mary that will guarantee dangerous munching away
i went to a wedding on the
queen mary one's really news i don't
remember hugo's it was
is um someone i'm not close to
who i just happen to huh you're
just walking past it was a friend
of a friend of yours situation that
i just was in right yeah yeah
it's always weird when you meet sounds
like this has happened to me where
i meet i meet someone for presumably
the first time and they say oh
i was at your wedding yeah and
i go wet and i know they
they
we're dating someone that used to date
shah that i well like when mike
and i got married but you don't
so you mow somebody's girlfriend who is
so small that we had nobody there
that we had not met so that
was kind of nice because you know
the happiness you're meeting someone on like
most important day of your life yeah
but then you forced your guest to
meet other people
yeah which i think is not fair
a lot of meeting happening on sometimes
your wedding news it was interesting because
you were like ok everyone looks to
your left now everyone look to your
right by tomorrow one person won't be
here yeah yeah and it was realised
because
yeah yeah it was just a place
where it was like rachel came into
the plant yeah yeah um what about
if somebody's getting married a bunch of
times and you're like you feel like
oh they shouldn't do this yeah that's
how that's kind of where i was
out with when i was at my
friend's second wedding i was like i
don't think they're taking it all that
serious
mostly so i don't know if i
come in like co-sign another one you
know what i mean another one i
thought i was asked to officiate a
wedding once and i declined because calvin
klein i did because it was calvin
klein e d client and i said
you're married fashion
being honest um and i i did
not think it was a good idea
wow i think any better mind the
invitation but you didn't say to thy
decline to officiate the wedding but you
went to shit but i was still
invited to the wedding and here i
think that's another family another mutual no
one gave me an out by suggesting
to this this mutual
a friend of ours there was a
bad idea to have me officiate the
wedding which i was like oh come
on maybe he sucks did their wedding
i can get something else and in
divorce yes it did many years later
i found out it was a horrible
marriage and i um i felt i
felt terrible for this person that's horrible
it was but it was like worse
than i would have imagined wow and
i was really i retired because i
was not close enough to this person
this to say you shouldn't marry this
portray but you but they thought you
were close enough that you should officiate
it but there's kind of yeah that's
a very specific world it is yeah
but also like telling someone that may
basically is not going to lead to
anything besides you being an asshole you're
not gonna see in that moment as
they're getting ready to get married that
your right unless you're unless you're the
closest person to the other side and
even i've told me i'm the person
who's like what do you think about
this honestly yeah hey the person poses
it maybe yeah but i don't i
even don't think that's true if it
was i think i've told you this
story
way of okada somebody i went to
high school with um who got knocked
up and then she's gonna marry the
guy in cleaved shiv creeped out the
day she was ah she's very young
like she was you know like just
jealous
high school seven t embryo you know
what i mean so she was gonna
marry this dude this is catholic times
yeah you definitely don't want to do
that and her father at the back
of the church like getting rid of
standout oh no okay
i object they were getting ready to
walk down the aisle and he said
to her you don't have to do
this you can leave right now no
one will judge you i won't judge
you your mom won't judge you you
don't have to do this did say
this and wanted or was she freaking
out and he said it unprompted and
when it just knew you'd just use
like no i want to do this
and then of course they got divorced
because he was a horrible asshole yeah
so if anyone ever says you you
know you don't have to do this
no matter how you feel about it
just don't do it don't do it
someone who's obviously you think it's it's
worth saying that if you're in a
situation like that you do not have
to do it and it doesn't matter
how much money the wedding costs yeah
doesn't matter what pressure yeah and all
that stuff it's impossible to see them
although
though anything above five grand prize she
just got through you should just go
through but you know you don't have
to do is submit the marriage license
to the government true yeah you have
to pay them anything you don't have
to pay tax you can try not
paying taxes is illegal yes you actually
have to go through with the wedding
and then you could just not send
that paper in and then when you
want to end it
you're not married that's a good point
you just keep the paper and you
say to your significant other like oh
yeah i sent that in do you
know what is a weird thing you
find out when you get married when
you get the license you're essentially married
um it's kind of an anticlimax what
what's that when you get when you
get the marriage license it's like yeah
you're but you have relented after you're
actually married because you signed it has
to
signed sealed delivered in the source yeah
oh i got ah but you could
just have you take it anybody you
don't have to have a wedding you
could go no i mean i i
can i got married at the courthouse
okay okay we're going to have to
get gay wedding sorry to tell you
our wedding over number
i'm just saying everyone should everyone should
get married everyone should get married to
each other yes yeah yeah maybe so
crazy if there was an odd number
of people in the world and then
one person couldn't get married
wow that would be so sad what
if we knew that person oh no
me so sad it was me so
sad no one said woes and that
was he sorry i will feel bad
for the soy sad stories your next
door neighbor that would be so much
pressure on you to be like okay
i'll divorce or like your
like let's you show his hang out
with us like yeah like friends with
your immediate neighbors and like now that
are closest um i've never met you
live know i may hide them um
all of them um but they're my
my neighbors are hardly ever here but
i've never met them
but there is one who ah who
hasn't said hi to me or left
room for me to say hi and
that's okay but i'm just kind of
like i wanna just say huh yeah
i see you all time nick you
want to make it as i look
in your window and your friend i
just want to say ugly naked guy
yeah yeah yeah that
was mean wasn't it oh i was
just gonna say it was me it
was like everyone's going to guy that's
not unless you're like you know we
never saw him miss playboy playmate miss
you know like hey play old baby
boy nineteen eighty eight like however much
bad naked how ugly was he like
it's like from so good so
science is far away that scuse me
that's how good sex is that everyone
is terrible naked and it still happens
if they just said naked guy that
they were afraid the audience was gonna
think well somebody's hot yeah they were
probably we should say ugly ever ever
two hundred and eight if he if
there's potential for him to be hot
but i mean if they just said
naked then it's like oh we guess
was somebody i don't want to see
naked yeah but they had to be
like no funnier if he's ugly
how many does he have a great
body laura so he's facing interface is
up yeah yeah how what percentage of
men in the world and has this
according to women have you had to
and you are representing to all women
according to all women in your or
their representative or what percentage of men
in the world are ugly
one hundred yeah
yeah any single brand argue with it
oh my god
okay well hey okay okay we're back
you know what we mentioned elaine bennis
yeah we did i just want
i just want to say i really
love her new podcast julia louis-dreyfus podcast
where she speaks to women who are
over seventy and for like and they
just talk about life and advice and
stuff and it's so wrong that i
listen to the only two episodes that
have come out so far but the
isabel allende episode is like amazing wow
i cried it's really good you help
too you'll be on that someday yeah
yeah yeah yeah i shown forty years
hundred and something yeah and i heard
she's only taking payment of seventy dollars
from from the guest from the the
yes payer just say to play situation
hey your age yeah yeah hey hey
when we used to go to philly
the big yellow house is that with
what the chain was but it was
ah it was it was basically it
was a restaurant that was they would
bring everything family style so your
the whole table would get like a
big giant plate of fried chicken everyone
and it was all you could eat
right and they would say like this
piece is the brother this pieces of
the day as just pieces of furniture
is a family of chicken or does
anybody remember it's being or did they
like it all together as one body
and be like this would it used
to look like before we chopped up
into one of the oh my god
magic they reassembled a fried chicken but
you had to you it doesn't feel
so good
if you are over
if you are over twelve you add
to his step on a scale and
then yeah you will love it your
way yeah that's fuck time to pay
over twelve yeah that's expensive what you're
over the age you're saying i'm bridget
at twelve or younger idea any person
why we're fixated on over twelve was
that's when kids start to become dense
i just mean if you're under twelve
should pay your age pay your amie
pay your way paperweight because you'll be
like forty bucks forty bucks what are
you talking
no i'm saying you had you pay
you don't pay your five dollar per
pound i'm saying that there was a
scale wait okay tell me what that
means i'm saying if like say you're
two hundred pounds yeah paid two hundred
dollars that's what i'm thinking that's right
and i'm going that's terrible i was
like i'll do that it was probably
it was probably something like a penny
per pound or some back but
so i shouldn't have to stand on
a scale and show people oh that's
hard to get into a restaurant that
but it was bunted but this little
fact that they bring built-in and you're
gonna yeah where in the body this
is how crazy white people back in
the eighties were it was fun for
us ah yeah
because we play with plastic bag yeah
alright on your head all the time
for reacher is half or three chair
and let me tell you something your
little game volga recap reader this a
while ago and i'm glad to have
it back a trail fun thanks to
matt producer for flagging it and saying
this was one we did before and
that it should be brought back and
let me open up the doc one
last time and here we go now
i i'm gonna have to turn off
do not to disturb in order to
get these texts why won't you receive
them anyways i receive oh maybe maybe
it will okay it's not it's yeah
it's not that it doesn't block them
from thinking just now just a little
dings or the the airplane mode you
have to
on the moon mode yeah yeah yeah
you'll come to okay it's why he
would use if you are on the
moon god i hope so
why do you think i'll get there
i hope so i hope so scott
i want that for you i want
i will so mad i just need
the travel time how you want to
look up at the moon and know
that you're standing there waving yes and
yes it'll take a long time for
the wave to the speed of light
you know for it to get to
you but i just want to wave
you one
i just whenever i look at the
moon i love knowing that you guys
are looking at the same moon at
the same time yeah yeah
every name this shit is called i've
got some bad tombs and it was
submitted by luke benson look the song
ooh this was submitted by filmmaker lucy
to thing luke
it's perfect it's very pretty so beautiful
a force luke it is a three
church
perfect obie oh you're doing darth vader's
wow pie
oh awesome i'm your guy
hey look he was jay leno halo
he was yeah
i'm having a fabulous oh give me
a kiss on my chin
what a shayla know only accepted kisses
on it's chin you
i've got some bad to okay one
player chooses a scenario or scenario where
someone has to deliver some bad news
another player chooses a song that the
other players will know okay then the
third player happy birthday ab swans yeah
the one single thing was it let's
say has to deliver the bad news
from the given scenario to the melody
of chosen great yeah so we're texting
you this all star yes so scott's
gonna text you a song and i'm
gonna text you a bad news scenario
okay what's your name hi i'm paul
and you're in my contacts yeah under
ass face
yeah i saw at that time oh
no
um alright i'm gonna
text you this song space here you
go
okay
so if you're loud you're laughing lawrence
suggestion i mean it is indeed bad
news yeah okay
alright did you send me the song
i did but i'm on do not
disturb did it go oh my god
i don't know i had i was
in the wrong window think okay how's
window
well mace windu it's a callback to
lauren na what colors is lightsaber purple
yes oh my god mais sick what's
in your it's weird that that mace
windu didn't have like laser makes you
know they spread yeah weird you know
and honestly that's weird because everything else
in that world was like exactly how
it should be yeah did you see
the the truman capote a job of
the hut what are you fucking talking
about and don't worry there's a there's
a high heard about the to toxic
job or toxic job to anyone's job
box like java ee gods autos all
okay okay come on alright but he's
speaking hotties no he's he's glee well
i didn't attempt to
when the hindu there be the layer
it's crazy all right hazing alright hey
i have some bad news oh no
what's happening well it's opening day you're
okay i'm okay but you guys are
gonna be mad when you hear this
it's the opening to ever a restaurant
yeah we're just about to open the
door yeah i know it's it's ah
nine pm we're just about so but
yeah for the first time for the
ff
for the french dinner rush this is
gonna be amazing there's a line
a french people and it's all reviewer
yeah yeah but i have to bet
all wearing berets i have some bad
news is that oh no a bird
is loose
upvoted those working now
bitch it's love
ginning it to everybody and every part
we're gonna get shot day oh and
oh yeah he'll pop anywhere from ah
one god again ah di nah they'll
put a zine for all to see
get bad reviews that will be it
oh sorry
wow well there goes scenario over okay
that's that's how we met out or
that's great i love that i enjoy
that um who wants to go scott
yeah quite so i'll send you a
song and paul's anyway that was to
the tune of start me up by
the rolling stones okay wait i'm sending
which you're sending some bad news no
no
oh no sorry you're sending bed just
to use me to me is sending
bad newsies to muse's
now i have do not disturb on
we'll see if this comes up i
haven't gone to i have an unto
you have it on t yeah but
you oh okay i did i did
get pulse by the way do you
have you noticed that everyone you send
a text to now it says they
have notification silence oh what time of
day or night working turn them on
everyone no i think they i because
i this happened with janie
if he was like no i didn't
turn i didn't turn that off maybe
it's just like having your phone on
silent it's a glitch i think it's
a glitch by the way i don't
i don't like the dot dot dots
when you're typing something i don't i
don't want anyone knowing what i'm up
to you know what i mean yeah
like your brother being and then you're
ticking yeah
you know or like or like i've
notification setting that's none of your fucking
business yeah this is my life that's
true like you shouldn't have any reason
to understand whether i'm rolling back or
not or what's going i don't also
i don't care to everyone's gonna get
a fucking android then if you want
all those existing show beep apa just
go okay you only pick da picking
i live
can i think of anything except for
the can you think of this one
for words that you send me yeah
okay i was struggling to start me
up i was like how did this
go you did it perfect i was
i was sort of like yeah it's
really good i forgot there were some
peaks and valleys to that tune it
was great
hey guys hey hey thank you for
coming over thanks for having us ca
um tex was so manic was mysterious
yeah mysteriously manic i'm so nervous right
now to tell you what i have
to tell you yeah hey we're your
friends or something why don't you tell
us what things i think you're my
family aren't you yeah well family can
be friends
nz usually isn't though yeah well my
wife is my best friend weird okay
i know my best friend is a
friend of mine yeah steve is my
best
what's going on sweetie
what's going on here well
i'm down in the da hopes because
i'm saying okay okay i've got the
ma oh
i've got ah ma homes huh
i'm coughing daniel phase
why you invite us over to jail
why did you think i want to
get you sick and have the mums
with me oh i have black nain
you have the mumps vaccine yeah that
gene vaccine baxi smell you please don't
infect me she's real over yeah ok
know the success rate i loved that
i was to tune
yeah drives me crazy
by the fine young cannibals um alright
so now for lauren i'm going to
text the problem and paul you time
going to solve the problem
right i'm going to test the song
um they'd be people people people people
too what's a song that all love
us will know oh
um ok
okay yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep yep yep yep
alright
there we go
we have each texted each other okay
okay
okay hey ding dong hey danzon play
is what ding dong what's going over
sr like this before oh no what's
the matter remains roommates yeah we're your
roommates thing dollars ding dong we would
never move out oh my god
i hit my elbow on the sing
today oh no and i think that
it's broken in a but my question
is should i get x-ray i don't
know if it's broken or not
nah dales i don't know if my
insurance will cover it so i tied
it up and i long to die
do you want to die because oh
dear john don't see that don't don't
say the bye oh wait you're serious
thing die
it was love and now as say
good-bye oh my god yeah because doctor
rosen now i'm a ghost in awe
just wanna say don't have say ding
dong today oh we can't even say
the scenario over
ah my guy off tune singing really
scared you at a certain point you
were worried for me and that's felt
i like when you looked at your
you are doing a little acting like
your broken elbow it was all really
days off ding dongs dying wish has
never say my name
it's always a possible alright well look
that's gonna do it that this episode
is a fun game and good looking
out man up ah ah producer yes
and what needs to be said okay
if you want to send us a
three year your own goddamn self write
two threes ma three three say three
huh
three captain threes and two burrito have
you seen
with your laptop it's in the shop
right to ah threesome usa at gmail
dot com if you'd like to call
us leave us a voicemail ah maybe
you need some advice on something maybe
you don't um then call us at
hag claims eight and if you'd like
to listen
in a free ad-free versions of this
fucking show for you i would imagine
the ads are a yeah yeah i
can't live your life i can't leave
your life then you can go to
um stitcher premium or cvb world dot
com and that is going to do
it for this episode i just want
to say hey way
way to plug summit the comedy bang
bang book comes out on tuesday and
you guys both wrote stuff it's true
yeah i read it was fun the
book looks great book looks great i
want people to buy it the first
week it comes out if you can
make it big make it a best
seller yeah you can get it anywhere
yeah buy books or you can go
to cb world dot com slash book
and if we're doing plugs
yeah you guys have a show i
well i also have a show ah
coming up many for twenty i'm going
to be watching succession well here's the
thing
we're going to screen the episode that
night's episode right after the show right
yeah wow huh lodge room has a
gigantic screen but i'm not like a
mystery science theater i'm not gonna be
fucking deal for everything we're just we're
going to have the show so fine
right afterwards we're gonna watch okay should
i get caught up and come to
bed get caught oh caught
up and so i get cut off
at one bar and no duh
oh my god i didn't fuck up
here so yeah it was my my
musical director jordan katz it was his
idea yeah we asked lodge room if
they'll do that and they they're into
it so yeah i haven't watched any
of the season yet which is getting
more and more annoying because of course
everyone's spoiling yeah better hurry yeah everyone
has a race to spoil everything about
succession all know i didn't really finish
shh i don't really watch season three
closely i need to go back i'm
going to say the people that want
to spoil succession are worse in some
ways than the characters on the guy
agree whole heartedly or is this season
no this is the season for this
lauren any plugins for you um when
does this come out thursday oh yeah
i'm sure
oh tomorrow um ah check and see
if there are tickets available and you
can maybe come in person there sell
same-day tickets if some open up and
also ah we're doing a live stream
so you can watch it online and
for anywhere you are and you don't
have to watch it live you can
watch it later it'll be archived yeah
and um yes to go to dynasty
typewriter dot com this show is called
a very good time it's friday
at seven pm in l a and
i hope you come because with that
lineup i won't say it's sean distin
it's paul f tompkins it's stephanie allen
arten marine and eugene cordero it's just
amazing cast i love this my third
show the second one we did a
couple months ago or whenever i feel
like paul was paul's first time doing
it i said we really hit our
stride with the show it was like
so fun
and it was a ball it was
it was truly such an like electric
night that yeah i'm very excited to
this it's like i can't wait okay
um check it out alright yeah i'm
suddenly know i'll be at the chicago
humanities festival on what the fuck is
that it sounds boring i'm saturday saturday
even when i wasn't i invited so
i'm going to be opening a lie
wanna be invited to nineteen
no what is that it sounds great
it's if some book thing is for
the book that's expired i'm being interviewed
by someone you're cool that's oh i
know you're really rubbing our faces in
it so it's an event people can
attend yes oh great i mean they
would have to buy tickets and they
get a book that's how it works
so much better than us because you
wrote a book and he's gonna do
it this is humanity's first cinch
chicago you should chi this sounds cool
what do humans like janky and read
boo zat ne goodbye the end by
uh