three
yeah
yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
imam
yum yum yum what if it were
three d o three de una zona
de yah mo i got three dimensional
ice cream cones yum absolutely absolutely of
course this is what we should do
i didn't even know until know i'm
tired of eating two dimensional snacks
that tastes like paper now and our
paper don't eat paper donate paper welcome
to the show paper donate paper john
yoni paper my young friend welcome to
the show scott ackerman here paul f
tompkins here lauryn lipkis here and we're
all present
and accounted for that's right yeah what
if you are doing a show and
then suddenly someone was in there and
we were just like lauren ah hello
can i just say i have the
iphone eight plus it's large yeah you
go ahead brag if you want want
to say um i fry thirty five
on my shoe really i feel that
i'm getting like i
i don't know if it's called which
carpel which hand my right wrist that's
your bean flicking hand it's like jerking
working jerkins work in that ah you
see a you mad um but i
can feel the differ i think that's
just the first step in human evolution
we're all going to be like a
fucked up next because it's your neck
because well you're always looking down you
know well you know i've talked about
this before but i have a pinky
divot yeah my old phone y'all are
and it might wood restoration share pd
oh my god i don't have it
on the other hand it's really it's
yeah creepy yeah i have a tale
yes same i never got off my
heart's on the outside yeah my brains
in my ass no
no kidding and that's erin goes
brain fart yeah
don't tell me about that don't ever
tell me oh that's er tell me
about that don't you fuckers
ooh whoa ooh brokers trade no one
has single wanna you ma exactly yeah
is that from the is it from
the quebec i know won't see day
i couldn't watch the comeback are you
fucking kidding he doesn't have hbo isn't
your thing log
thank you can't wait you don't like
i watch it the first series when
it was out okay i follow and
then i think i watched the first
episode of the new one huh and
i had a hard time with what
felt like and this is i'm not
saying it's a bad
good show i had our time was
like the ritual humiliation of the character
yeah because you feel that in your
own life
i watch tv to escape well i
mean in a way yeah it's like
it's not it's not there's another showing
i go to escape rooms to just
sit there and so they kicked me
out the scenes the scenes in love
where where paul rust is at work
get away sin it this is the
scenes in love with paul ross does
it work and everyone is just so
so horrible to him yeah i found
that those scenes really bummed me out
because it's like i don't like it
because it replicates our relationship and when
he was working on the show because
he based all those on on my
relationship we have i just did an
interview where i had to talk about
something more lauren talk about everything
but
i just think that west conference under
rated and lord was under-rated and you
said something about waiting to see the
come back but i felt that it's
not under-rated i feel like a lot
people it's appropriate your show did okay
yes i'm saying so then i decided
to talk about episodes have you seen
episodes and yes yeah jamie loves it
oh yeah jamie's is a huge episodes
fan yeah i love that lol i
just wanted to say i will
say the comeback new episodes are two
of the only shows that like it
can be taken very literal their titles
you know like episodes there literally are
episodes of them and to come back
was off for many years and then
came back there's no title more literal
than sixty minutes that's very true one
hundred and twenty minutes maybe
with matt pinwheel oh wow don't you
think it's very derivative of sixty minutes
yeah maybe what about the news
news news welcome to the new
what if someone copyrighted that title the
news in a good mood everyone just
say no and every anchor had no
pants but you couldn't see their mind
started to settle they'd be all panicky
inside knowing they know pant to be
a yogi baronet behind those desks paul
is making fun of me because i'm
touching my hair but it looks like
your my admiring
ling a rat tail that doesn't exist
if i had super long hair like
a rag doll that doesn't exist like
it's like a long if i super
long hair i would constantly be doing
that yeah sure really yeah fun i
touched my hair all the time do
you ever think about getting all shorty
nope what's the shortest you've ever had
um i in height while like when
i was
a kid i always had like a
blunt bob when i was um like
my mom just it was it was
very cute and then with things and
then when i was um that's what
isaac was at it kind of hits
haircut because i thought it was exclusive
to like the seventies and eighties for
our oh well maybe it was also
like no i don't assign at the
time i
i think that well our generation had
there were like little kids that you'd
see on tv that were that has
like like adam rich on eight is
enough that had like ace like really
long yeah bowl cuts that i had
where it was like you had to
look just like your face peeking out
yeah this helmet of and i had
ah it's it's like a circle it's
like a moat
recycle yeah and then straight across the
eyebrows money and that's what i had
all the time i think of it
is that one character on fat albert
duh dumb donald the guy who had
the weird hat yeah yeah yeah and
if you just cut out the front
of his hat and we're like you
copy the hair hole yeah harold my
holes and great show written by a
wonderful man harehills
but the last time i had a
short i was um in high school
and i cut it like a hear
like midway through my yeah she's pointing
at her my butt so kind of
care was out of the four um
nobody wants her neck about halfway down
or her change pointing her and it
was she pointed
huh but
didn't really know i didn't really care
to style it i was not right
concerned with such activities at the time
i was concerned with such activities at
the time a great trial so i
was not concerned with subjectivities at the
time and you're speaking like a police
officer has to deescalate the situation
i do not wish to style my
hair in that manner
ah so the perpetrator and so i
simply walked away and didn't do anything
to it what's the what's the worst
haircut you've had that's probably got oh
but you know what a few years
ago i had one that i hated
it was like two thousand ah twelve
or something i cut my hair above
my shoulder but it didn't
i mean your over the shoulder boulder
holder sadly but to me it was
just a horrible length because i just
think i either need to have longer
hair or short about i don't know
i i'm too afraid to go short
anymore but i think it was i
think above my shoulders is dangerous because
it's like it kind of like falls
in this weird way i hated it
so much that i would straighten it
every day because i thought it looked
so
so stupid and then that i hated
to i just hated i'd said wait
for it to grow out but it
was like i wanted to take a
risk but i didn't make a big
enough one for to do anything he
just became like an annoying thing yeah
i remember when i was eighteen my
friend cut hair my best friend at
the time and he and i i
think i'd had a very similar well
i did
i cut my hair like anthony michael
hall in weird science when i was
sixteen or seventeen so i kind of
like like joe kind of why you
instructed the person to do so well
sort of i had like short on
the side and back a little bit
but it was like droopy eyed as
a friend i mean ah but then
but then i remember ah my friend
was like oh
let me cut your hair for you
because they use concern for me or
so and and he was like well
what do you want your hair to
be like and i was like you
know who has like kinda cool hair
is like neil finn crowded house and
he liked like he's like let me
take a look at a picture you
took a look at a picture he's
like oh yeah just short but like
put up you mean i'm just like
put up
do you mean because like every haircut
oh yeah because you weren't putting down
finance i wasn't putting stuff in it
so he's like let me just give
you a short on the sides and
back and and you know slightly longer
on top cut and then we'll put
it up and you'll see what this
and i did it and it would
look great and was like oh you
can do this here yeah i think
like well
that's interesting because i felt like it
was like a california temperature to no
stop de-escalating the city with
that's the sign i think like nobody
else i grew up with put shit
in their hair like no dude really
did that it was like maybe it's
very midwest to not do that but
like there was with those like tuna
transsexual or something or just no one
cares like yeah there was like we're
from chicago we all got a winter
hat don't give a fuck but like
there was a point from chicago
we all look dumb i just impressed
but the only time people did it
was when it was really popular to
do like that little flip in the
front it was like just a triangle
yeah and um then people would be
putting their gel in and it's like
straight out jimmy jimmy whom i think
a cartoon character neutron oh i thought
even you have martin short when he
was like oh yeah agree
yeah yeah yeah who dressed up as
ah when in high school you know
martin short no i've never met him
have you met him i have met
him yes i love him he i've
always been very fond of march shorn
so sctv was like a huge thing
i would pick out in every interview
they'd say who's your dream guest like
that's that's the one question interview it
ah
yeah yeah although i would i think
i said i would say peewee hi
simon we know many did it to
try to make sure that it's a
movie theater
did you ever have a bad haircut
paul i i had a bad haircut
that lasted for a complete year because
i kept a did it for a
year i kept trying to correct it
and i went to different places three
different places that all ignored what i
told them to do and they did
the same
same thing that the original person did
so they're working off the blueprint they're
like this guy doesn't know you so
yeah i'll just give me the same
thing yes it happened but it happened
on the sarah silverman program where i
was i played a cop sometimes and
this one hair person for whatever reason
was like yeah cops don't have hair
like that and then like cut my
hair
like like oh scary warning why aren't
messing with your looks yeah but also
for this thing like i'm here for
a fucking day said that one at
that this show isn't like you know
it's not a drama right what are
you doing anything my hair was a
problem on both episodes i did to
the point where like people were mad
at me or you you looked insane
you have
yeah di busby died my the first
time they dyed my hair jet black
because sara felt like the character would
have black hair that's very stupid and
so they dyed my hair jumps back
and was like alright because i was
a cop or i was a i
was like an fbi detect and they
died died they died they died at
once brown and she's like why what
did you
came in and slapped dark enough and
they died it again jet black and
then the second time they were human
like they didn't put an wash out
color they don't die they died it
that is so weird and then the
second time i came in they they
just cast me and they said um
you you're playing someone who's mistaken for
jay and i said ok but i've
really short hair right now and i
think rob said oh yeah it's totally
fine he came and took a look
it was like yeah we can fix
it and then sarah like flipped out
and was like why are we casting
and he doesn't have hair like j
anymore and so they put on like
a wig or something
but then weren't you on again with
super short blonde hair as a cop
now that was clear enthusiasm oh that
was see why you know it's just
my regular haircut show yeah i've seen
that yeah i've seen that i've seen
folk scene yeah but no's so crazy
to both experiences on that show where
i was happy to do it and
like oh wow and i got the
ib jon hamm for
that part for the first one before
he was on madman wow and it
was like oh great oh like i
got this gay and then immediately to
be on set being yelled at i
just wasn't right i just worked on
something yesterday and i my and all
your troubles were so far away i
remember that
i just got a part that jon
hamm does that frees you in your
tracks it vices what we do on
this show it froze my blood
the blood so you died a blood
i died of blood they cut off
my balls i died of blood ma
it comes out so the guy so
i was very excited to do this
show to show that i like if
i it doesn't matter i don't want
to embarrass the person that said this
chair yeah but i was very excited
to do this
and then and it's going great and
i'm having fun it's a really fun
role and the shooting is is a
ball and it's like so you know
it's like the testicle you smelling out
of ah yeah soft and sloppy you
know it's the done it's not always
like that like you don't like sometimes
it's yeah i'm grateful for this work
but it sounds like this is actually
finds it's
hard and sometimes it's you gotta understand
so um i was so in the
like we're almost done and then the
guy i he's like finish thanks for
doing this he was like um he
said something embarrassing music p p groopman
may be corn
oh i told you the story it's
a usa but show yeah he said
he people go in my big hole
by the way paul thanks for doing
this pp going big
i just want to tell you guys
that but i know there's a person
he told i think one of the
writers said it's so cool to have
you here and then um he says
something that led me to believe i
was like the like the six note
or what are you saying oh noes
i yeah its its are you know
it's funny how we end up with
people on the show because oh you
know we'll have like i forget how
do we end up with this person
like we went out to this person
and all these other people said no
and then this person known is like
that the story you tell i actually
it's one of those things it didn't
hit me right away and then like
as he's still talking you after a
few seconds i'm like rain man yeah
mom
ah you always i mean on bang
bang i don't think we ever unless
it was like a last minute hey
man someone dropped out can you come
here and do us a favor it
was we always said someone was our
first choice to do it oh yeah
yeah oh yeah in order to get
some like yours and yeah insulting for
no reason yeah i mean i got
married i was like yes i want
to marry you bob
right so i just find my brother
so i just said i don't like
to leave that part out i say
yes you're the person that i want
to marry
it's polite it's just polite don't want
to hurt their feelings there there's never
a better day to be polite than
on your wedding day carol if you're
out there
carol you come to me she comes
to me all night
what if karol came to the guy
down kitchen carol kane would have carol
kane k peril from the movie yes
i love carol kane yeah she's cool
she's so cool you're like a modern
day care you are like a modern
day carol okay get and also i
just realised we're not
talking about carole king which is what
i was thinking until know carol kane
she's funny carole king is funny too
in her buildings hilarious you know i
mean if like have you ever heard
really tell a joke have you ever
heard a lyric songs there how literal
golden girls i mean she's saying do
that it doesn't she's saying that she
did the gilmore girls
pls
i'm serious but what if you're out
on coming home those are the same
the show and so cool what is
the different twenty eight doctors really do
is the sans yeah oh yeah got
a friend if you through nah i
actually know
no this will sure you host raised
by taino but i actually do the
sketch this will be embarrassing if you
can't remember i can't right now soo
something was this guy she did it
was pretending that that that that singer
was our favorite performer and we were
at the concert and then that was
only song it wasn't like a great
scuff
i bright think about that a lot
like people one hit wonder not hated
who have like one i didn't say
it was good but it was funny
i've heard this many times of bands
that had one big hit and they
would open and close their show oh
yeah that song yeah so i was
like ok here's the song here's the
thing that's gonna give you some energy
all throughout the reservoir bullshit ninety nine
percent of you are here for this
one song yeah your nose i would
do it guess what will play to
the end too i want that i
when i go to any any concert
i wanna hear their best song twice
i would love it if they did
in the middle too i'd love to
hear three times how amazing would it
be to have written something that everyone
knows you know i mean i was
thinking about that what's wrong
songs i'm like how why don't you
just ask me but you know hey
nell frizzell bit but even if it's
like you know hey man you're an
all-star whatever like just just the heavyweight
every single person in the world knowing
or at least the unites that's amazing
what if you had to pitch songs
before you could record them too yeah
but
the idea is to a record company
yeah it's like ceo size it's like
it's encouraging it's saying you're an all
star and you know so maybe somebody
called you a loser but you're not
a loser and ah um ah where's
that water it's kind of something that
will be played a lot in like
movie trailers we hood don't you think
even if you write a song that
everyone thinks
is annoying you're still amazing yeah no
just like you wrote something like remember
knows what confluence of events of payola
vs luck you know from yale law
paola paola what is pale oh yeah
i'm c j i'm gonna send you
ah vino nun it's where record company
these would know i'm done explain to
i'm going to send her
somebody why money on van why is
this why is not the simplest thing
oh i may send her a link
to a thing that she's she's okay
why don't i send you a link
to my mouth saying to lauren oh
no oh
here we go i'm sending it to
her
is this from a game h q
i started playing that
yeah i just i just sent you
a thing that'll explain all appeal
oh my oh right you first of
all i'd even look at my last
shiny coins right that's what rick rowley
never sent it i just had to
do he didn't he started to meet
saying the things up it's rick ads
but i'm like wait who did i
send it to not want a terrible
rick roll link rick astley never gonna
give you up i said to you
yeah you did
well we do it'll get you you're
playing wrong game like i feel like
that's rick rolling where i'm like looking
for something you're like what are you
hearing it's like what are you did
but you understand what i was doing
now paul right so what's pale yeah
i know i got okay if that
ever happens again sammy i'll know i'll
know okay course of cool
a pale is where you go not
song why is everybody always picking on
me
everybody picking on me why is everybody
always picking on me always picking a
book boy i'm doing puppy i got
a snug like the cause but there's
a lot wrong with you sabet cmea
bill you're you're ugly to sort of
i don't know the song oh shit
it's from the what is it who's
that by doesn't sample that old song
charlie brown note why is everybody oh
it's really a bloodhound gang
yeah like yeah i want a new
drug fuck animals or whatever the fuck
things i want to fuck you and
my baby kemba mammals and the other
thing you'll want to fucking know about
being a pretty fly for a white
guy not saying that that was offspring
spring yes you're right mayor any any
any any any any new new new
um haley
any any any any pillows where ah
record companies would basically give money off
the books to disc jockeys to ensure
or to radio programmers to ensure that
they would say janitors who worked at
a radio station i don't care anymore
to play the songs which would turn
them into hits no no use me
but this says the
practice of bribing someone to use their
influence a position to promote a particular
product or interest whatever fuck did i
just say it didn't take a bribe
when you said it
i have that way about me so
you don't think it's a bribe but
you're actually being bribed
here let me say how do i
know to accept the money
let me send you something what do
i tell her anything you send me
ever again oh no you cried wolf
scott now just look at this you
cry scott wolf whoops way already a
failure
i thought i copied and basics of
thing but it was the last thing
i liked i thought i copied and
pasted you the rickroll link but i
send you instead like something here something
i'll copy something from my digitally way
how did you end up sending none
girl penis yeah right
ah yeah iraqi what is the yeah
right like i can't achieve it or
yeah right this is the best i
actually love that just happen because i
always have that fear when i copy-paste
send like you're trying to do it
so quickly because we're on mine that
like sending the wrong thing because you're
but it could be so dangerous yeah
that feeling of
ah i gotta find the the perfect
stupid ziff just sam sand immediately before
they get it out before the rhythm
of our conversation but over somebody another
text will come into the thread exactly
yeah i mean my life is hard
we have so much disposable time speaking
of disposable time we need to take
a break
well we took
a
british hired british firetruck buddhist fire truck
way lawrence santos something in the night
oh it's a little british fire truck
gif of what my dear bow of
rick astley my dear woman you've been
recalled ah not really you've been reading
make you click on it you just
sent me
something i had no choice but to
look at you always have a choice
to know what i've never going to
click onto our text thread again
you opt in every time you open
it and lauren will you pass me
that bottle of water oh paul nice
to juice ah i need to juice
up it's bottle steroids you want the
last bit of a cookie i do
i want we can play with paul
we can can split a canvas play
a game split it a kinsman of
his payments
oh won't want cookies i get the
chocolatey part
you have the coffee part there's some
chocolate in there sigh no i love
you sammy whoa up and down i'm
gonna roll around and desert he's handsome
right yeah guess a doorway oh if
you fuck a goddamn you like dorks
donald rick ray
roasted fucking like cool guys do people
in chicago like like is there do
do different towns like certain types of
guys does that make sense you know
how people people in jersey shore they
don't like certain guys do da do
da i think it's different now with
the internet i do think that jersey
shore like there are certain areas that
have like very specific
ic types of style right i mean
there's definitely i look about certain the
midwest dude that exists
a dude was dude really hit know
your buttons day i know i don't
need to speak i don't need to
add any but what do you what
would you say the chicago guys like
you know like flannel shirt and like
don't give a book kind of thing
yeah no show gel in their hair
yeah sometimes doing the little triangle yeah
but then there's like the like the
like city like ah banker kind of
guy that's just like that but like
um like it's kind of like the
new york version of that but there's
like zara body type you know the
joy
jersey shore guys are like massive mostly
um there's i wouldn't just like you
know um people not really working out
feels accurate oh really so like so
like if they're in the park on
a saturday i mean tons of people
are very it was the fourth of
july i'm saying i guess i'm thinking
about like ah people i hang out
with laughing people dancing
and a man selling ice clears definitely
a lot of people are gonna argue
with this of course there's every type
of person in chicago it's a big
yeah metropolis yeah of course but there
but but is there something but there's
like the wrigleyville douche bags and yeah
lincoln park trixie is there's always different
wrigleyville douchebags that what are lincoln like
cubs fans are like a certain type
of duke
shh bag and then like um lincoln
park tricks these are like the girls
that i went to college with who
would be like ceiling is it though
it's like girls who like i mean
i don't know how it would be
defined right now but when i was
in college it was like short skirt
straighten your hair wear like a sports
t-shirt and go to cubs games and
be like wow like i'm getting drunk
and like just
yeah this sounds like me yeah does
um but i didn't fit in with
them oh no you went to college
with all them but you didn't fit
in with him what was your personal
style um improv girl person what is
the is that like what like wearing
overalls ah it's like you're into
t-shirts okay i mean i liked my
style but like i um there's a
certain difference i mean kevin agree why
are you looking to kevin because he's
from don't look at him look at
us know i want kevin wait where
are you from don't even think yeah
kevin he's from chicago was ah yeah
you were you guys you don't and
kevin you look at anybody coffin comes
to me at night
he gets me his instructions which i
anticipate with great relish
so what so but you felt you
feel like that styles will know i
mean well here with my friends but
there was like my my dorm was
a lot of girls that i just
didn't become friends with but i think
it was partly because i was in
my own world with my improv stuff
and i didn't really try to make
friends at school i only had a
couple of friends at school around here
it was because i lived in sort
of a beach town it was more
like surfer guy was the california that
was what everyone was always like like
yammer for grat guy is definitely a
look and style in chicago in certain
neighborhoods like yeah like frat douche drunk
dude like that's like the people i'd
be
walking through every night going into an
improv show but i was yeah i
was wondering like did you watch big
brother by the way recently no okay
so but on the bachelor router big
brother anytime they interview them before they're
going on there there's one thing that
pops up all the time that i'm
always curious about because they're always they
always say like okay what do you
hope is going to be there and
the women are always like you know
tall dark tall dark is like one
thing one thing like they mean guys
with with jet black hair like me
and the sarah silverman program i mean
i guess should i've kept it i
think tall dark and handsome is like
from what is it from
romance novels it doesn't feel like anything
when you anyone actually subscribes to like
wooden tall blond be just as fine
they don't or they don't i mean
i think people what do you think
about tall blond yeah i'm literally telling
like me yeah
um you guys notice i was still
here i think um yeah we're desperately
trying to keep this afloat people on
dating show oh what do you mean
interruptions he's me have you watched the
proposal yes ma'am we talked about it
on a previous episode so having much
good get out the drain oh yeah
wow da
wow mad fell man oh man film
it alright bend over baby all that
it's not the filming is not happening
yet yeah chevron has the gradle and
say action paul remember speech sound speed
ah i forgot
cool and not the other i forgot
to press record he was so excited
oh yeah it's i won't do that
again
it's only one spanking per look you
missed it you missed it i'm the
videographer and say doesn't get spanked did
that count as ah so say things
before my sorry i think if you
if you don't if you even ask
like if we talked about the really
years my question you're asking after i've
been spanked
that's not fair to say you say
you wanted to be spared
yeah actually tried to and you handed
me your phone to video ah you
were like no mom don't slap me
again can i pose you were like
trying to get in there to explain
no i'm saying that you're like the
person who wants to explain and wants
justice oh damn it all comes back
up it all comes back to that
one element from your childhood so fascinating
well yeah that was like proust's madeleine
um ah the what about the proposal
though my dear since you've already been
saying and already been sparing you should
bring up anything you um ah
i just wanted to say that i
think that people you know when you're
on a dating show like that you're
kind of hoping that there's a general
look about the person right and i
think there is a safety sort of
ah default setting of human well i
guess i guess people tend to say
they like but they don't even know
really
i would think that anything that pops
up you'd be like oh wow that's
my feeling is if you're on a
show where you want to marry someone
within either three minutes or seven weeks
seven weeks you can't be that picky
about who the fuck is right because
you are desperate oh yeah that's insane
yeah like if you're agreeing to do
that in the first place that's just
nuts nuts and then the
people on these shows i just feel
so bad thinking that they're these moments
especially in the proposal because it's even
less time in the bachelor where they're
just standing there going like you're the
kind of person i'm looking for it
they've asked them like three questions maybe
and they don't know anything about them
they've never heard them like talk for
inherited period of time they've never had
a great conversation like like this yeah
and like where it's just fire in
the room and everyone can feel it
yeah it's just the electricity but like
they're just going like i always wanted
someone like you wanna live like i'm
so excited to be with you and
like you don't know yeah what is
happening in your life that that you
think you need to be married you
need
right now and you don't care to
know the person how what is a
realistic i'm not even saying like oh
we should be married within seven weeks
but couldn't you i don't want to
marry you at all but don't you
like tall and blonde know what i'm
saying is like you can know can't
you know what quickly seven weeks quick
early of like you know what what
i could get married to this person
barring yeah it comes up but i
couldn't i mean i think that they
don't spend enough time actually kyle dunnigan
and i were talking about this that
they should have a timer on eat
on the bachelor on each guy and
then whenever he starts talking to the
bachelorette right you should have to shut
up know it
timer goes to you just know by
the end how many minutes they was
actually spent together yeah right because it
seems like it's three minutes yeah and
they have these really twenty years probably
like seven hours like it's probably not
that much time anyway that's what we're
not getting from those shows is we're
not getting like all of the boredom
and just random like conversations between them
of like oh so what do you
do well you know what
what's happening now i don't desperate for
that i mean yeah where were the
cameras are not rolling that that seems
like when you just have no idea
of these people would like each other
from just this date you actually talked
about religion have they talked about politics
i mean just things that like you're
gonna be dealing with they're not allowed
to talk about politics i believe
that's true i just heard this awful
imagine you picked somebody in there like
i fucking love troll i just i
just heard this on some other info
of trump and maybe as i'm throwing
shade or on or on their their
premium show where somebody
was talking to to some producers some
some former contestant that like during that
election of a k wherever i'm to
talk to each other about politics which
is such a fundamental thing you need
to know oh yeah i mean so
so much of oh because what were
your arcane probably i wonder if they
were able to talk around
is it like no i love abortion
they'd be a great way to get
it out like just be able to
say that and you could tell right
away if you are a match with
somebody yes the only question you'd like
i gonna go on do you love
abortion yes or no you love abortion
yes throw don't do not add another
word to that sent those are your
own choice or
no answer it yes or no what
are you getting one yes or no
yes yeah
c point d one one um ah
yeah you want me to perform it
i really don't know how much we've
talked about the proposal so i won't
go on um but but ah there
was a new episode but there yes
but they didn't air one because the
guy was abusive to somebody he abused
he assaulted somebody in novell
ember i think it would be fun
to go on one i mean people
you know they don't have people of
ah that look ah like me on
these shows i mean even though the
proposal seems to be scraping the it's
a little better with like real people
being on it yeah everybody has a
six pack and well yeah that's i
mean i would like
like to see a simple one the
bachelor was fat yeah little fat batch
i don't know who is and always
will be bobby it's such a great
personality but he was a fan but
that's the thing it was good personality
but you know what i mean i
would like to see a bachelor type
show where it was regular people well
yeah because when i watched the bachelor
now what i think is okay she's
getting in a hot tub with this
guy who is like ripped more than
anyone i've ever seen yeah you're just
gonna be like wow know what i'm
thinking is that's all he fucking does
yeah and that's all you have to
do is have our i had a
friend in college who he was an
acting school with me and he was
ripped like that he was like so
ripped and i was like and i
know i hadn't was
never into this or working out or
whatever i just had pretty much you
know the same body type throughout high
school and college or whatever and i
asked him one day i was like
what are you i mean you don't
work out every day do you always
like oh yeah every day i'm like
in my head kinda going like
well not for a long time like
what do you do like yeah twenty
minutes is in my head was like
an awesome time yeah he's like he's
like no i'm there to two and
a half hours in the morning and
and before before acting school and i
was like dude we're an acting school
twelve to thirteen to fourteen hours a
day why
yeah and he's just like look at
me and look at you yeah exactly
but that's what it takes on me
yeah you know and it sometimes takes
two to the admire people who care
about them their bodies and wanna do
all these things but just so many
of those guys among they are not
more interesting than that they don't have
more to say than that like you
can tell they're the they just fight
with each other and
because here's the thing if you want
to see a bachelor with just you
know normal looking people average looking people
yeah but are they just the same
level of doneness as the people on
the show because i think they would
be more interesting nah i don't know
that's not to say the good looking
people are not as interesting no no
but before that i was like people
are inf
apparently more yeah well let's just say
a lot of people on that show
are average looking but they work out
really hard yeah that's that's what i
mean i would rather see i would
rather see just as pretty or whatever
people but who just don't work out
all the way over here obsession but
i think that it's like if if
you want good looking people who are
interesting those
those people have made other chart of
the half-day relationship if they yeah they've
been able to make other choices in
their life that does not lead them
to being on these shows yeah you
know i guess although i i don't
know i think that ah is that
discounting people who are just like i
don't know i want an interesting experience
i don't know when i look at
sure there are some people like this
but i think
i want interesting experience i think i
want to see oh goes on the
bachelor that is not as good as
your girls on films i just or
are we judging these answer here okay
i'm sure there is good to know
all who are on they're just they're
interesting people and they are trying to
have an interesting time but it doesn't
feel like those are the people
will that create the content that they
want on the show and so we
don't see a lot of that we
see it edited down to people being
like dude oh well no like the
first season of ah of ah what's
the show started talking about the jefferson
proposed the jeffersons no thing brother big
brother yeah was was just nice people
all who are boring and they were
like and and america voted out the
the the ones who were yelling because
they were like i don't want to
see people yelling that was back when
america voted on a chain and so
they voted out the people who were
and and the it was from another
country and they were baffled by this
they were like well in other countries
we keep the interesting people who are
creating conflict but in amoy
erica we wanted things to be just
like that's the thing about americans they
want everything to be just and and
for justice to have happened so they're
like this person is yelling they do
not deserve this and they vote them
out which makes for poor teddy actually
seems that surprises me because on the
show think in this country they would
want to keep the fuckin weirdo know
before we were
all reality tv obsessed and like and
started getting so yeah d that we
couldn't back or something yeah back at
the time it was like no i
want i want things to be fair
that's the one thing about americans is
they always want things to be fair
i think american who oh who am
i to talk about take a bray
off course that's the thing about americans
just wearing a bray
does this thing about americans um but
no i just you see it in
so much of life of just like
you know i always feel like that's
how we feel about i don't know
politics in the world and stuff like
that is like we're like it's not
fair that's our biggest problem with it
is is not is that the liberal
snow
flake cuhk perspective it's not involve air
baby no that's what i mean is
like when you realize that life is
generally there is no justice and there
is no karmic scales of balance activists
and well but but i think the
reason we get upset about that is
because that is up to us like
there i'm not talking about karma
but in terms of things being just
or unjust in this country there's so
much we could do sure ensure that
it is and we know what those
things are but people don't want to
do the shore you know for um
but here about kuk i think it's
you never hear that anymore yeah i
know you do i haven't heard it
i haven't seen it in such a
long time
diaphragm is it really where did you
see it i don't want to say
ah okay your twitter yeah i'm a
i'm a cook soy boy note on
your fridge otto yeah so i feel
like soy boy has sort of eclipsed
it a little bit but it's the
same because like some people you are
getting offended by cook i think we
wind out of it
sale yeah well i think we we
all have to start laughing about soy
it's fucking ridiculous never heard of soy
boys that's the new thing that's a
new thing is they say that or
or they say they're not what is
it's tea like to testosterone is there
the low low to you because i
guess soy increases your estrogen or yeah
yeah so they so so they say
that anyone
is not manly enough as a soy
boy and that's the yeah it's so
stupid bless you was that zeus ne
me it was a little more and
did oh i'm reading the twenty one
things they don't want you to know
about the bachelor okay well twenty one
but number nine it's dumb know a
lot of these things but some kentucky
superfan spend thousand
hands on a new wardrobe for the
show simply some condition spoon thousand on
a new order show how's that one
that's your best one thank you willing
yup i did not feel quite good
because i've always wondered about this yeah
the food on dates goes to waste
because the contestants already ate i'm always
like why are we eating yeah that
since no one wants to talk to
me about food
going to waste huh
i want to go to ass
it's your food goes to your waist
oh i got it one on one
dates will often end in some sort
of dinner or dessert component which is
laid out romantically with gorgeous candles yet
the gorgeous never seem to try anything
that turns out the producers filled them
up before the date even starts so
they'll do less chewing and more talking
about how much they love each other
that makes sense okay
they also don't think to watch tv
on one day a week like they
have one day off and they get
to watch tv that one day um
oh i've never heard that i think
the agents know but they can't have
any tds or music on in the
house because it's copyright and they wouldn't
be able to broadcast it but so
i think that they they they film
six days a week and then they
give them one day to like
watch tv or do whatever you can
be hard for contestants to stay in
shape since there's no gym in the
mansion and there's no says one day
i ran laps around the outside of
the house cool my workout time was
cut in half courtney robertson says from
the floor from zero to zero i
would push myself more in the thirty
minutes of time i had sometimes i
would get more if someone didn't eh
austin schedule there you see these people
are now complaining about not being able
to the cameras are filming twenty four
seven i didn't know that because sometimes
they don't have footage of certain things
i feel like like people sleeping
that's what i want to see
um okay what if this show where
it was just us asleep one week
wait this took one look at pedro
overnight fantasy suite dates don't happen back
to back that's good because i always
thought oh fucking kidding wait they're not
like on successive nights i always thought
they were what is it like how
so in other words the star of
the show isn't saying goodbye to one
man or woman before welcoming another contestant
into a suite later that night the
stars need
time to take a breath and think
about the further for their bowl their
pussy to get ready again
they need time for their balls and
pussy names are not provided in the
fantasy suite dates what we have to
buy them they're provided at the fake
dinner we go to anyone chain in
theirs looks like robert oh my this
is insane what i'm reading everyone gets
ten everyone gets tested before the show
and and this one says i was
on the pill
ill maybe well what about trading the
money if i had known i was
the last one to get a fantasy
suite date i would have definitely thought
about it more because it's like you
tested between eat well i guess everyone's
tested zudem to test again but the
idea of what the person raw dogging
three women in a roach this is
very cool roddick oh crazy yeah
that's so crazy that is nuts oh
wait these are nuts um we need
to take a break here not so
we need to take a break
but
and we're back and um it's time
for a feature and i've got one
here it is um from twitter from
max susanna spear at the morava winning
gm are you partition right now what
does artesian are you partition them
merovingian i don't know how to say
this everything in okay the game is
called we to not you the game
where each pair lorna and paul lauren
and scott and paul and scott have
sixty seconds to find as many things
they have in common as they can
but if the third person also has
that characteristic it doesn't count low
iran for instance is trying to keep
scott and paul from finding anything they
have in common that she doesn't also
have in common with them her score
would be the total number of things
scott and paul managed to find that
she doesn't share and low score wins
ooh that doesn't doesn't share low score
wins i'm confused i would think high
score wins isn't it
because if you find most games high
school no but if it well other
than golf i would also think golf
you know what i mean if if
lauren finds a bunch of things and
doesn't have them in common with paul
than the more things she has so
high score wins i would think
yeah let's play these ruins let's try
to understand it okay i think i'm
doing it yeah yeah so you do
you want to do it with me
first and you're trying to find out
things that we have in common that
all does not having okay okay yeah
and will and don't say you have
it in common or irish should you
say i have it in common while
we're doing it what do what you
think is best way um or afterwards
oh no say so that yeah so
that's all because it'd be too hard
to yeah okay hold on a second
so if you have this in common
with lord isaiah fact about us and
you're like me too yeah here's what's
called hashtag me too you're just asking
me questions you will be confusing hey
guys we're playing this game use this
hashtag you're just asking me questions you're
not guessing at things about me
right you're just like hey you ever
done this and that's something that i've
done yeah okay right or some fact
is it just broadly anything anything any
headline any no it's anything at all
anything oh yeah and but you can't
have it in common which is okay
is the yeah ready so sixty seconds
right o'clock
kevin gives us the thumbs up that
yeah sixty seconds of the clock he
has not turned his phone on or
is looking at the clock app at
all and realised it but you are
right that sixty seconds should be on
the clock on the clock okay
he just gave me the full confident
like yep you got it sixty seconds
on the old clock or and
go have you ever had a cat
no yes wait i don't have to
answer you don't ya
um have you had a dog yes
we both have dogs yes paul doesn't
okay good looks one um ah yes
miss me no no you're i'm nothing
oh i only ask yeah okay um
ah blond hair yeah we've always children
especially children yeah um ah
maybe it is both of us because
we repair yeah okay yeah did you
ever have red hair no okay um
you ever put lipstick on yeah you
do yeah yeah oh yeah see i
ever kissed a dude yeah you know
in a play oh damn um um
okay have you ever um you ever
ah
have you ever done oh shoot yeah
you ever owned ah brittany spears cd
yes yes haha have you ever done
double dutch yeah
okay okay um have you ever ah
shit sixty okay how many do yeah
put a noise on the thing we
had for maybe low score maybe one
from sixty x it'll go off maybe
the low score does when go no
low scores low low score is really
the thing it's like as few as
he can say was yeah
meanwhile lets do it three ways and
we'll see if the low score should
okay yeah so okay so now so
now it's me and paul
okay ready oh yeah you ready yeah
alright i think you know it should
be high score like as many people
figure it out after okay right okay
ready three
are you a guy yes yes i've
ever spent the night in the hospital
yes me too
have you do you have a penis
um have you ever had a mustache
yes i have to had a beard
yes have you ever shaved your ah
facial hair just so you look like
wolverine yes yes so my fair um
have you ah have you ever engaged
to a woman yes have you ever
married a woman yes i have
so making a blur
so thank you e-mails edric have you
ever played horseshoes yes you have to
okay have you ah ever gone kayaking
know i should um we should done
that
um have you ever have you ever
been in a fistfight
yeah me too
okay um have you ever played baseball
on on an actual team yes okay
great
um have over over over over
okay well that was great for you
guys um now okay
a ruddy counted down chef chef counting
down chevrolet okay
have you ever been in a commercial
yes i have fucking whoa have you
ever um develop your own film like
in a photo likened in a lab
the dark room um okay asked me
something to alright um
i've never written in the front of
a roller coaster ah yes i have
of course okay i've have you
have you ever thought you've seen a
ghost um yeah
i haven't
i have so many things you have
um have you ever um have you
ever supposed to be things we have
in common have you ever volunteered to
help people who are less fortunate yeah
she's this ah well yes i have
have you ever done any money to
a charity yes yes to this is
cheating oh my goodness yeah
um have you ever um huh i
think i know what it means by
low score wins like my low score
because i'm the one outside of it
would win right so we don't know
so so so in other words who
has what what team has the highest
score you and paul
the lowest score is what i mean
what team doesn't last call yeah so
i win oh okay yeah i get
it get it get it yeah don't
get it you play again yeah okay
okay let's take are there any things
so of course there are i can't
random this terrible game because it's like
this one of those things where i
blanch trying to think of things yes
okay alright so do you want is
a you and me
now lauren is out yeah because we
started okay
ah okay
um
okay and wait are we going oh
sorry can you start over i didn't
know where you're going okay to what
have you ever dressed up as a
woman for halloween yes yes have you
ever um worn contact lenses no oh
um have you ah
ah um have have you ever cut
someone's hair ah my own zak yeah
have you ever cut your own hair
yum yeah yeah okay um have have
you ever um
do you ever have ah brother no
no do you ever have a sixteen
as i guess both of everything do
you ever have a brother
ah you do you ever go to
the drive-in movie theater yes yes damn
have you ever um gone um have
you really ever have you ever gone
on a labour day picnic no damn
you ever bought a ah what ah
what other day wow oh my god
what we lose a game she only
got one today i found out lauren's
never been to liberty
while you might win again you might
win paul you only have one we'll
see alright so now it's me and
paul alright okay let us know shove
three two have you ever been nominated
for an emmy yes oh oh damn
ah spun yoga on the writing staff
of the tv show yes i have
i have not um have you ever
been on mister show the television show
yes i have sorry have you ever
been ah you ever been on curb
your enthusiasm yes yes so vi you
have you ever been on brooklyn nine-nine
yes i have yes i have two
people think i'm chelsea right ah have
you ever been mistaken for d j
qualls yeah no i don't neither
ah if you have been addressing world
ah meaning the amusement the the ride
in no the movie have you ever
been in addressing park movie
maybe oh i get it
while yeah have you ever been to
universal studios yes i have yes have
me too damn um you ever been
to magic mountain i have i no
yes i haven't but you haven't mountain
wow okay ah you're over over how
many rude do we get six whoa
paul you're gonna win
in last i can have all of
them in common with you okay holly
it's yours to lose at this point
let's see have you ever done a
voice on big city greens yes i
haven't ah yes you did i did
say your article that said you were
on it and maybe i did okay
i did a couple of shows
you know what they are now that
was it wasn't out yet so okay
um alright i guess yeah i could've
got on with that but i didn't
um have you this might win a
time as ever um have you ever
had somebody um rob your apartment yes
no have
you ever um ah ah we read
your car towed yeah i have to
tell you guys for um have you
ever gotten a hippy ready to go
to court for a ticket yes yes
so am i oh i knew that
have you ever been arrested no
oh no neither one um have you
ever um i have no freaking oh
i can't oh man have you
yeah when i when i believe in
a game i don't understand how the
winning outfit because you guys couldn't come
up with anything in common that i
didn't also have in common
damnit okay okay so i have the
lowest score i yes yes and you
only had one and oh my god
so you're really riding high right oh
my god i feel so fucking good
right now believe it oh this is
like doing
sway when i was winning it was
because it was because she and i
could only come up with one thing
that you didn't have in common with
both of us okay that whole sixty
seconds we could only think of one
that i can't remember what it was
but we only had one thing and
so it was yours you only had
one thing in common common that you
didn't often also have
yeah and we could only come up
with one thing and so it was
yours to lose because we we only
had one than when you and i
were doing it we came up with
six things that we have in common
that she didn't haven't called me so
she wasn't ever gonna win oh and
i have nothing in common that i
don't also have in common with only
connection to you is him and the
same
no other way well we're not in
this room together i forget that you
exist i say i find it saying
that we're all on big city greens
whatever that is yeah yeah huh you
played like a podcasting bug or something
really yeah we the things that came
out the other day yeah oh okay
i do know what that is then
i don't know i did a couple
i did i did a cartoon recently
where like
like they were they said like oh
you're gonna be in ten episodes and
all this kind of stuff and it
was it was literally two years ago
i recorded the first one and i
never heard back and i went in
to pitch another show to them recently
and the head of the company was
like hey by the way you're back
on the show
huh whatever happened with it some animations
can i have not been called i've
not been called ford sense but anyway
you do one day that they split
up into ten episodes no i did
one that one episode when you're john
green thing yeah
i'll just say one word it'll fade
out every episode of speaking of fading
out fading out we got a fade
out ah this is it lawrence gallego
yeah like you got any songs for
us we go yeah you wanna do
have a new song that i really
like yeah um do you know mason
jennings no um he i
loved him like when i was in
college and he has johnson i have
no idea know that shooter jennings and
the song is called cursive prayer i
think her siv first like like ham
recent jennings i can play it on
my phone if you want to play
would rather use seeing hill al ruin
it
cursive jennings no plane shooter mcgee heritage's
tastes through good into my
the sons
please god that was a nice way
to lose a nice way to go
out to rip off billy ocean yes
huh
he was the first person to say
get in my car oh yeah raz
you know off the bus the baby
would have been impossible to have written
that song like in the early eighteen
hundreds yeah you'd be like get onto
my horse
kinda on to my arse
um we'll see next time on what
is the name of the show three
oh my
a this has been an era with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com