three
oh hey ha ha no no i'm
a vampire speakers vampire do you think
people are listening to this other high
fun i hope sir hi to everyone
hopefully ever welcome to three rainbow yeah
no we didn't say that last episode
but hey we're back yeah and this
is our final episodes you can use
to hold your hand every time yes
final episode so far of well every
episode so far that's what i mean
but this is this is the final
episode of the of the season the
season and um the wellcome well scott
i'm paul
i'm lauren and we're doing it scott's
list name is aquaman future paul's last
name is tomkins and lauren last name
is duke here scott that's my nickname
hey i never explained i have parties
by the way i've poured my booties
i'm forty so the thread day a
phantom thread from last episode i just
saw your phantom thread song wrong
see ya oh you're said about new
articles cisco pilot bob newhart was in
that's why when you just say well
i knew that they tried to make
a sitcom with cisco yeah we was
bob newhart and cisco that is so
so insane pop why did they try
to make a pilot with cisco i
you know he's he
was popular at the most popular i
remember so i've talked about my roommate
bagel yes yeah cats that's cool nails
carmel yeah they used to be roommates
i mean the cat used to be
remember i gave it to camille and
you talked about bagel on a different
coach o on a live show when
we did the gillian improv in okay
in austin so do you mean i'd
if i had when i went when
i lived in a house made of
food and me my ring was a
big was bagel high
angle
i went to when i went to
college you know i was in an
acting school with like twenty guys when
he five other people right right and
we are living situation i've talked about
my original living situation where i slept
on the couch instead of in my
bed yes um and then i was
alone for a while and then for
the second half of the year i
moved in with
with one of my classmates um and
his roommate was bagel who had moved
up to it's a person that's hurt
it was his nickname i guess i
just gotta nail this down because a
person one time a guy named pockets
tried to make me smoke opium oh
this is way more interesting now go
ahead bagel
now your bagel guy big finish so
so bagels moved all the way out
to the middle of nowhere just because
he was good friends with my roommate
so okay they were really good friends
my my where was this santa maria
california but now central california my my
roommate got accept
added to the school and his good
friend bagel moved all the way out
so seemingly normal
did he have a real name that
you ever found out fellow know i
must have known but it's been so
long at this point that i don't
remember i just remember bagel now legal
belongs to the more interesting but my
roommate who i will not name ah
what we talk like this all the
time i think it was from hawaii
bryan posting ah
yeah um but he i there was
there was a party we were at
where he was complaining that no one
liked him and he was like what
is it who would like me oh
my god parties and so anytime anyone
says they are having a party i
think in my head i have parties
slightly annoying
person but he did what there was
one time when these two this is
his other catchphrase these two door-to-door magazine
salesman who were like twenty year old
girls came to the door to try
to sell his magazines and he was
like a come back tonight um we're
gonna have party oh and his other
just good as this
working so we had an impromptu party
so that's helping me it was hoping
they would come and the ah my
roommate lured was the cute one in
quotes into his room by saying commuter
will show you something oh no boy
so we would say that all the
time camaro
would show you something
but this made bagel so upset that's
also someone's worst habit
but that is i don't see so
they so they had sex in the
in the room was he attractive yeah
he's pretty so they had sex in
the room while bagel had his sights
set on that one and was really
upset and he was drunk at the
time so he cried and he he
there was a a cupboard where we
kept them
mops and the trash can and he
went inside there and said i'm just
going to stay here the trash where
i belong fuck saddam are you from
that's i remember that story but didn't
say so ridiculous show you some
just the most okay the most artless
pickup line i've ever heard in my
life and it works disgust usia something
god
huh that's what i wanted to show
you
but you're right it could have been
a terrible experience we have no idea
sure it was um um um yeah
my story is much quicker because i
don't really remember much of it pockets
yeah i was at a party it
was completely dark for like black lit
things and then a creepy white guy
with dreads who was like really nasty
looking name up sky noise
yeah he was ne
it came up to me i was
like sitting on like a futon on
the floor and he was like if
you're gonna imagine you know just picturing
well see what futon i was in
college while just like it was gross
okay and this guy's like are you
hanging them home to see like my
name's pockets they call me yeah they
call me because i don't have any
what and then murder them
out of baggie from my guest his
books a pocket baggies of oh what
he said was opium or what do
you say i guess he said it
was opium i don't really know what's
certain drugs look like but it looked
like leaves and then he was like
you wanna smoke opium i'm like no
and that was the end of it
were you by yourself
self i'm sure it's with a friend
but i was just like what no
hotheads ever find out who who pockets
was with no i don't even remember
whose party i was at ah this
is insane i tell you about are
the holiday party i had that you
guys were at yeah why would you
tell us about it i remember that
diary nobody
paul you you remember the dude who
is smoking indoors yes that guy told
us about this on the show yes
okay now doesn't hear the album one
to one story we've caught that we
know we know that was probably episode
one too oh circle don't go
step forward
because you think it was by now
reading the same thing we would have
parties in that apartment with bagel and
my roommate where we also with the
the people who were upstairs from us
had the winter school with us so
we would have team parties with them
where we were very proud of this
we had a heaven and hell party
where upstairs it was heaven
in and we were held and it
was decorate gotta give it up that's
farmer that's clever over sixty said party
sixty seventy s party where upstairs with
sixties downstairs thirties as the time gets
more when you go down weekend up
and down party where the upstairs was
up and the jester down
we were doing new york
a man and his apartment and otherwise
the second apartment we did upside down
party where the downstairs was the upstairs
party upstairs with counterparts yeah we did
a party where the party was a
priority party
wow
ah i actually had parties all the
time in college and um i would
invite everyone in the improv community to
my parties and they would be really
good it was always the best i
had like a really like long apartment
it was like had a very long
hallway and then two big rides dan
yeah and i would just post
pst on the improv message board and
say whoever wants to come and then
it would be full it was always
the best time and the cops would
come oh yeah it's very funny but
now i think of it and i'm
like i want to go to a
twenty year old party if i was
like thirty yeah come hang out my
long hallway
but it was a different time it
was ah i know me we we
got the place where i yelled at
the guy where i yelled at my
neighbor yeah that was fucking tv off
that same building i had there was
a unit over my house and it
was these three young women they were
in there too
lenny's who worked i think two of
them worked at that that that weird
clothing and like jewelry store that's on
franklin next to the u cb oh
yeah i've never gone in there yeah
it's so it's so weird that there's
that one store and it's been there
for every no because it's a nice
group didn't check down
they put an ice cream know that
was a different place oh okay yeah
that was a different place i think
and um so they they were they
were like these young women that were
like in the prime of their life
that were going out having fun time
they almost exclusively wore eye ills and
they had obviously no carpeting to speak
oh my guy here then walking around
all the time but there was something
that was weirdly reassuring to me about
it because i was like i was
about to enter my forties and i
thought this was so like i just
loved them i loved the idea of
them going they were yeah oh my
god that's so crazy they never bothered
me otherwise that way
yeah and just hearing you used to
drive janey crazy it would drive me
insane i don't really i can't really
understand people who want to wear heels
all the time i have a hard
time but if i were your early
porno but if i were short i
would do it because there are so
many cute shoes i take it all
because you're a hotel or five ten
and then when i wear heels i'm
like six one yeah just like over
you know it's over forget it over
i'll do it i'll do it but
you know if i were sure i'd
probably wear mall in time some fucking
get it parties used to be a
very big deal
yeah i don't want to go to
a party now really i it takes
so much for me to go to
a party even though i just came
to my party you guys i was
gonna say that was one of the
few parties that i looked forward to
of course but i thought this will
actually be fun but lots of guys
mixture yeah but yeah we we have
to go to a lot of baby
show
showers now was never like this for
men you never had to everyone's co
baby showers for men but yeah baby
show but baby she's also used to
be like maybe six people right and
i'd be like a datetime yeah yeah
isn't it oh also with people who
want to have babies too that's kind
of you know what do you mean
no it's i would say it's like
the close friends typically like traditions there
are none said thing of big bang
wrong way gonna come to my baby
shower if you're interested in having a
baby if you're not well i know
you know my date was just op
a baby shower yeah it was what
was expected of you from society like
of course you were going to die
but as a woman you just go
i go to things yeah yeah yeah
but now
now it's like now it's not only
coed but it's a gigantic party right
where it's like i don't you know
do i have to go all the
way out there and you know everything
so much and yeah everything i'm amazed
whenever anyone goes to anything coming to
shows i'm amazed that people would do
it i just saw yeah yeah thanks
well you ought to say hey thanks
you live in the middle of nowhere
now i know i'm moving though i
can't take it it's fucking annoying because
you almost got wiped out in the
mudslide yeah well i can't i can't
deal with good by the time this
comes out i won't live there anymore
so no will come find me but
yes i did experience that and it
was horrible and um i don't want
to live far away from p
people anymore i was saying the time
i loved it because it's so quiet
there was like a lot about like
and the house is really cool but
now my street is all trucks going
up and down everyday taking away mud
it's like a freeway it's the when
we camp yeah bb and we can't
park on the street i have to
walk up a hill it's it's a
nightmare we've been learning what different vehicles
are as excited ie he knows that
a shot
ah hey there it's really obnoxious and
i'm gonna i'm planning to move some
more flat yeah flat as a pancake
so that is a punk her kansas
kansas county zealous girl
girls oh grams oh my god did
um i used to have ah an
upstairs neighbor that was deaf like ur
old super old so she would blast
the tv which doesn't bother me and
so that was the greatest because she
could never hear why doesn't that bother
you i don't know it's just so
annoying to me to hear
what anyone else is doing i'm so
lonely so i don't know it just
never but i can i can deal
with like someone's tv blaring what drives
me but it was great for me
because i could blair whatever i wanted
and she couldn't hear it at all
sure that's so it was it was
perfect for me well she should turn
on the closed captions while yes you
alone of my apartment in new york
where i
i i lived in three apartments within
fifteen months due to annoying circumstances but
i was i remember my mums are
all can you give me the numbers
again three apartments in fifteen months and
it was horrible yeah i really struggled
to move three times in the first
month i moved i lived in one
place for eight months and then i
moved somewhere for a few months once
more
a few months and then i was
my neighbor was like a kind of
cute guy i don't remember looks like
but my wall share were like i
shared a wall with him my bedroom
was he like sort of like a
screech type yeah because i was very
attracted to him and i heard him
like jerking off one time oh or
something but i'm really nosy with with
like hearing noises or putting my hear
hearing the way people jerk oh well
i just love overhearing something like if
someone's having a fight like i need
to my neighbor is my last place
we have a fight i would be
like ear to the wall like i
wanna hear what's about i love you
meet him and i was just trying
to hear him and um
what was his style enough grunts die
because i was trying to figure out
if he was with somebody um but
yeah you know i like to eavesdrop
yeah
did you ever try the thing of
putting a glass of guy hat yeah
yeah i haven't noticed any significant difference
but i've never been sure which way
your stats are part of glass and
i've tried both always little little ah
closed-end to your ear that's what i
thought yeah but i tried it both
ways it didn't really make a difference
yeah i think i was able to
hear who you're listening to my brother
i think i loved spying i was
little yeah would you be a professional
spy if you could um know but
what was i just okay i was
just watching oh citizen rose that rose
mcgowan thing oh yeah they showed like
the first episode but they're gonna
show the rest in the spring and
um she had a spy following her
oh yeah and it was a woman
whose job was to spot i mean
i find it fascinating she's a fake
has a fake name and then sits
behind somebody and just fucks with shit
like gathered dirt on gather dirt and
i think she had something to do
with um there was
a claim that rose had left something
behind on the airplane that had narcotics
with it but it was planted ah
now this is just like harvey weinstein
yeah there's this person and he hired
someone to to steal her book before
it was published and they got a
copy they got to make sure that
he was i don't know why he
would do
with it but i think would be
fun to be a spy although from
everything i've heard it's just like a
lot of waiting outside somewhere i think
the part that would suck if if
you had to be like have a
fake identity and like pretend to get
to know someone i'd feel bad right
the part i don't probably fall in
love with them and then there'd be
a big argument after we fell in
love yeah like google lies
may tell you is because oh actually
i'm actually mixing up two stories about
rose i don't know if where the
spy was but there was one point
where she was spending time with the
spy like hanging out with her and
spent a whole day on oh and
told telling all these personal things wow
i don't like that yeah i don't
like it i there's a thing that
drives me crazy on cop shows where
the big bang
someone's far the name your shah you
love for cop shows they love a
cultural i love offshore household clothes catching
the bad guy
i'm gonna go big bang but this
time it's funny well it's like they
do this a lot where like one
of the one of the characters will
have the cop will have a wife
who's like mad that the police work
seems to be taking so much oh
yeah life i think the only thing
that cops wives can be mad about
it seems like it's like but it's
also over your life and i never
i know i'm gonna get the call
i know but i feel like in
real life
you know that that's what this person's
job yeah and you probably have yeah
like you want to be annoyed yeah
like oh you're doing more police work
it's just what good is we were
supposed to go to the movie yeah
you probably would have had a conversation
too like yeah hey what's your schedule
today on evening from exactly from seven
till or it's like the cop gets
call it dinners like i gotta go
otherwise like oh i made this dinner
somebody got fucking murder but i even
think it's like acting it's like like
you can't be annoyed if your spouse
gets a job they have to leave
when you know that's what their whole
yeah it's like hey ran their job
is unexpected like we get emergency bags
all the time just trying to help
you and your relationship
bill cosby
you'll see ya see ya gotta go
will your match cali
john burden and mother oh cool yeah
here honest question okay okay okay yeah
if bill cosby everything we know about
him now okay that's what i'm doing
but i did if if you need
look like mark baldassare know if he
and just be totally on okay if
he
called you up and said look i'm
this is bill cosby obviously i've been
in the news everything you've heard about
them wow will you come over and
have dinner with me what did you
do
first of all he never oh oh
don't know
what i way you know he wouldn't
know you're pretty sad about that um
bill cosby it's about time yeah calling
women like look i know i've been
in the news a lot lately can
you have dinner at my house dinner
bring your own beverages i mean that's
as insane as i'm doing comedy
yes it's a little more insanely happy
to call random people person exactly who
he doesn't know wow i will say
i will say that like right before
this whole story broke someone i know
works with him i don't want to
say i want to give any clues
but um the she she reached out
to
shake his hand like hello mister cosby
thank you so much for being here
he reached around and grabbed her bra
strap
what yeah grabbed her bra strap yes
and like gave it like a little
like a snap yeah yeah thank you
as an eighth grade yeah so disgusting
wow allegedly he did that well i
believe her believe women but we were
gentlemen you see this woman i won't
identify jersey i'm just saying when i
meet women and i'm i want to
get out
agree that a lot of times from
introduced to a young lady what i
will do is i will reach up
and i will unfasten whenever earring okay
and i will show it to her
and then put it in my pocket
and walk away helping says a trophy
is a joke it's a joke it's
a joke of just eating around when
you will do it's a joke fee
while i mount them
poster board i put them on my
bicycle at my penis do a prince
albert i put the earring inside and
then i saw my penis back
it's like a safety deposit box yeah
in the body it's the safest place
i know we've been hearing the safe
is play sai no but seriously bill
cosby i'd love him
do you think a bank has ever
burned down and everyone's safety deposit boxes
were burned yeah probably although they're metal
they'd be so bad they'd be so
soulful do you have things that bank
and safety deposit i've never had a
boy mom does that and i now
have a key to it and what's
the number i'm not gonna tell ya
well i never find it i don't
i don't have anything to keep in
there i feel i feel like i
would do that with like documents if
i had the wherewithal to make copies
of documents but yeah yeah but his
documents and documents won't you sit with
your birth certificate you can only get
like two in your life like i've
got an i don't know you know
no that that was the big problem
for me when i was trying to
propose to cool up oh right that
i that i was trying to get
my passport because i was doing it
in vancouver yeah i got my birth
certificate sent to me by my parents
and then showed up at the passport
office and they took a look at
it and said this isn't your actual
birth certificate i get a coffee this
is a copy yeah i had copies
my whole life and i got the
real one like a few years died
and i said you had said you
can only get two or it was
some limited number in your lie i
don't know it is yeah i i
had something for years that i thought
was my birth certificate but it was
not it was just sort of like
a i don't know if it was
almost like the obama situation was like
a certificate of lawyer
or from kenya i'm like that too
but it was like it had a
seal on it yes it's printed yeah
it was real however yeah it's the
same thing and and i forget what
i was trying to maybe i was
trying to get a passport and they're
like this isn't a birth certificate right
and um i and then when i
saw my when i got my birth
certificate i was like oh yeah this
is like this looks very official
my birthday that i got printed now
looks like a like a good thing
you would get in fifth grade is
like i can like a prize like
yeah it's like i blew eight by
ten it looks like the perfect yeah
right neared if sag were to say
hey if if they had when you
became sag if they had said we
already have a lauren lucas
what would you take lauren cosby
i've done that
um no but i know what i
would have done what was you doing
i would have gone with my other
middle name i would have been lorna
allegra lorna la gray resize a nice
name it is a nice name although
i will say it sounds sort of
ethnic so you may diversity hires while
jeez i wish she'd done it would've
been typecast typecast what
hey guys playing made look we have
to take a break speaking of me
okay um jesus i'm sorry well you
poke acts like i talk to you
you know what let's do this in
front of everyone do this in front
of lauren and everyone are gonna get
married let's get married that's what i'm
wearing your birth certificate oh no
we're in vancouver all right we'll be
right but about the development
hey welcome back laura news ah she
looks to be wearing a prison uniform
from the waist up no that's scott
that's my wave rune to beach outfit
which way would you first of all
yes sure strep prisoner stripes are horiz
aantal not verdict this is a vertical
striped button-down dress that i just doing
the line okay oh yeah that's something
okay i didn't just get of one
would you oh yeah wait what is
what is if you had to go
to prison
um what would you have done with
oil cost
what's what's the what like what amount
of time mentally would you be able
to say like i can handle this
this is this is gonna be i
mean it will probably be like what's
the maximum amount of time yeah like
where we're at what point do you
think you'd be like i just can't
do this i think i could handle
two months
and then i'd probably start to really
because two months worried yeah
two minds like i could do i'm
sure i could do longer i think
you mentally your brain just adapts to
think two months is like doing a
stint in the big brother house or
something but months can feel really long
i don't know if you're i mean
especially if you're in jail where especially
go especially if you're doing january why
does your face oh like for maybe
fifteen minutes long
i don't know i'm saying realistically you've
done something wrong and we caught you
for your thing yeah i'd have a
hard time okay but how long because
here's the thing you really go before
you are like me where you're here
if you're talking about just confinement i
could do that easily i think not
some more easily but if you're talking
about everything
thing that being imprisoned in tales there's
a lot of stuff that i think
i would have i'm very okay would
get my ass kicked i have you
watched a lot of like lockup raw
or and like when msnbc at night
on the weekends yeah i'm fine
over his channel i like to love
that show it's pretty good but like
i just think there's so many there's
so much politics going on that you
would have to figure out and be
a part but so paul this is
my question like you've done something wrong
you have to go
i got fifteen minutes you just you
think you think what would you do
well i guess ah i mean say
say it was a two month sentence
they're like you know what a you
i'm sorry but you have to spend
sixty days right like when would i
get used to being sexually assaulted probably
oh well like i can you know
you try it out on you before
i go
yeah would you listen one of these
days oh no you're stupid just surprised
we're hitting the just surprised me um
yeah i mean when i dick popping
out of me when i think of
jail i don't even think of it
in terms of like oh it's it's
i'd be locked away from society i
just think about it as being in
constant fear that you're gonna you're gonna
get yeah fuckin i guess i would
get my i feel like i would
be afraid of getting beaten up but
what if you could just stay you
know there
you see all those prison movies like
shawshank or whatever there's always like an
older dude who just keeps to himself
and plays chess with the pigeons or
whatever like couldn't you be one of
those or whatever like yeah like when
after you more like fall in love
with someone so it's not bad when
you hook up no but i mean
you know what i mean i am
a romantic yeah it's like it seems
like all the bad stuff that happens
in prison on those shows and everything
it happens it happens your first ten
years and then after a while you
just get used to it i you
don't be the scariest thing i think
is being locked up abroad that oh
yeah and then you're in a jail
where you don't speak the language and
the rules don't really matter even like
their regular yeah yeah though there everyone
just is it's
awful conditions right now i'd be so
do you want to experience it though
at some point oh what talking about
i mean there are those shows where
you can voluntarily go to jail there's
one show where they're like you'd try
out how you would do right gel
addition yeah it's just there's so there's
it's such a big part of so
many people in this country's experiments like
there must be something to know but
don't get any weirdness so many people
are doing that jail is a thing
it sounds so like yes you should
be spanking so yeah give me twenty
spankings i love doing yeah why don't
we take the canings like they do
in that where was single yeah where
is it but it's so crazy when
you think of all people i mean
there's not
whatever to google or a loved up
for doing something so dumb and that
oh yeah drug offenses yeah them they're
in there forever it's just that's devastating
and you ruin people that way yeah
i think i don't know i like
one night would you do one night
i'd be very scared anymore night i'm
sitting two months is assuming i become
adapted yeah
that's what i think one night might
be actually scarier than the remarks because
it's like you don't know anything yet
if if we're talking about just the
idea of being locked away from your
life as you know it right the
whole oh yeah roommates
a sell me
hey roomie
i see yeah about shitting in yourself
everything i have that oil with no
seat on it i want to freeze
the worst like i would say is
there a private bathroom anywhere i shouldn't
hurt anyone really know speaking to shit
here we talked about the text to
say what oh i can't remember what
this way can i can let me
answer the question
oh no well as ah i i
honestly don't know i honestly don't know
how long i could do that because
the i it's it's a horrible experience
and i don't know how how quickly
or how long it would take me
to get broken by it writing yeah
and then yeah you can never how
long could
you keep ya wonder that how long
could you keep your sort of like
composure of like this is you know
your sense of self yeah yes there's
something on the other side of this
is just two months yeah yeah i
don't know yeah hey i don't know
i don't know oh i'd be so
sad what about what about the army
oh never do i could do it
i couldn't do due to jail before
the army
no i could do the number before
i could do jail better i think
i would do jail beverly does it
somebody says the cool activities
jail before army you're being smarmy army
before jail i got a bad yeah
okay so this is what i taxes
lower in the other day so here's
the situation and i are the detail
i get a somehow the there's there's
two places that have my address and
i've kept my address you know
yeah it's not public always been this
way um they're designed fullness if we
come there's there's kind of
i mean you drug us when we
leave there's kind of no way to
find out my address okay well don't
give people a chance no but you
know it means there's like because of
situation anyway so this situation to placing
how to do that the two people
who have are the two organizations that
figured out my address are the church
of scientology oh boy they'd like send
me stuff
biking right oh right okay okay crazy
i don't know and i don't know
how that happened and then now the
republican party is sending me is sending
me stuff and the trump campaign like
trump himself is sending me fundraising you
letters he's sending me fundraising cramps crumbling
i've never donate
added to them i don't know how
it's happening but i got this i
got this email the other day from
trump saying like how how much will
you donate to make sure trump keeps
his his thing going or whatever and
so euro bag zero well what i
did was even worse your big fan
gu saying what i did was and
this
and this is what i texted lord
is it funny or too gross to
tweet a picture of a trump fundraising
letter i got that i took a
shit on
i wrote not asking pmt because i
know his answer and i thought it
was hilarious but i didn't know i
should post that she she writes ha
ha hahahahaha i use my health than
l o l and then oh i
did i did laugh a lot and
um and then i think it's funny
and disgusting but very funny
haha um huh and i said i'll
sleep on it and she wrote on
the paper
so um i decided not to do
what you did so i decided not
to do it if you the worry
the post this where i was going
to send it to him i like
i got your email or write your
letter ah ha i even heard on
twitter yeah on twitter i was going
i got your oh oh oh just
directly to
yeah yeah i got your letter i
want to make sure you got a
response really um where are you going
to do a deal like please follow
back i use it very forum
remember
black berry was when when smartphones were
taking over blackberries like please remember i
still forget about us guys yeah they're
like they were trying to make bb
ems oh yeah she's really kept saying
that black bayou la vie used to
take bvm like a little blackberry pearl
miss a little track yeah this girl
is another thing pearl like pearl jam
like it comes of purr yeah like
semen what is a thing like that
yeah yeah approaches yeah yes sorry almost
any band that exists i am so
with so-called passive you with cum like
name any man
ah counting crows oh and it's discussing
it's basically like counting how many siemens
you have for you like crow and
and shoot em on yeah oh gonna
crow yeah ah any other band that's
all i know those that's the only
band you know
the beat i got now i like
jerking off master bow now i got
it yeah wait got you thought you
got it before hitting your dick using
your dick hey guy
you gotta hit the nick would you
hit my dick
gray pu hit my dick do you
think hitting do you think hitting a
dick
like do you think like if someone
were to come up to you and
say hey i'll give you five thousand
dollars to hit my dick yes is
that sexual i don't care do they
have any cash yeah like i think
you could divorce it from sexuality where
it's just like it's not sexual i'm
just punching some of it but sexual
for that person well yeah it was
somebody for that makes it you're involved
now in a sexual
will act but i think it's just
you're punching someone's what if you're doing
it for free what if you're asexual
and somebody says five thousand dollars give
me a oral sex job and then
you're like i don't care about sex
but this person does it's nothing to
me but talking to me putting my
mouth on an oregon
that would be i think worse if
it meant yeah if it was something
that was disgusting review you passed my
oh wait you were gonna do ah
help me oh
um yeah yeah i don't know you
don't know scott i don't know don't
know is it time you act like
you have all the answers right yeah
we gotta go to a break guy
when we come back with eleven feature
hi we're back and it's time every
every episode including this very final episode
we have a feedback this season of
the season more potentially ever awe of
the season
we do a feature in the last
segment and paul it's your turn to
come up with a feature dancer i
have a feature everyone knows what a
feature is yep and this is no
different this is no different than any
other feature i've been featured this is
a little feature called
wait is it christmas find out who
game though we did christmas friday a
game christmas find out okay this is
a features a brand new feature to
the show we've never done this one
before okay it's a little feature called
toothless vegetables when i was thirty two
toothless vegetables
it's thirty two toothless okay good
explain this for me because i don't
know what is it called thirty two
hours late so it's sort of a
list of list of games that was
number thirty two but we went early
number thirty two funnier if it were
thirty-two well because your thirty two teeth
in your mouth that's true that's why
they are thirty two is it krqe
isn't it crazy that teeth fall out
when you're young and we just go
oh yeah got my new teeth in
and then it never happens to you
again i should have savored it teeth
huh when you're young boy when you're
older you put teeth in yeah oh
doi doi this time ravages all my
dad had dentures yeah
it was weird it is shocking my
grandparents other than take them out yeah
we see and when you were little
he had him when i was little
well it might my parents were older
because i'm fifth out of six kids
oh yeah and he had and he
had dentures and he um i would
see them in the cup you know
like within the the effort
efferent or whatever and it always creeped
me i was like the seeing the
pallet attached to it yeah you get
dentures when all of your teeth are
gone is that when it doesn't have
to be all your teeth just some
years he had partial denture oh it
wasn't all the teeth it was like
the idea of having to get them
is so bad it bums me out
yeah i never want that i would
never want that so scared did i
tell you
when i went to the dentist now
a year and a half ago after
i finally finished on comedy bang bang
which was an all day everyday job
seven days a week um i hadn't
been in three seasons i think so
three years i hadn't been to the
dentist and i was like fuck alright
gotta go let's just and i and
i'd resign
myself i steeled myself to i said
today's a day whatever happens you just
gotta accept it whatever happens you just
you know i mean it's your fault
you just got too busy i went
in they took a look at my
teeth i was like ok i haven't
been here in three years so what
have you got they said okay it
all looks good try not to make
it so long next time
i've been sad happen to a friend
of mine who hadn't gone for twenty
years i know and then nothing happened
i was like that's not fair i
have made came out yeah because i
went after i'm gone in ten years
yeah and i had a deep cleaning
of my gums which is so it's
horrible right it's they pull your go
no
away from your team
yeah and it's it's so boner it's
so painful it's so painful and then
the guy told me you'll have to
now you have to go every three
months instead of every six months so
i was doing that for awhile then
moved to new york we were therefore
a year and i never went to
the dentist while i was there i
never i never found anybody and i
just like they fell by
the wayside and when i came back
i went to the day i found
a new dentist and went to the
dentist and it's like a new day
it was and it was fine it
was like i didn't have to go
every three minutes they will we'll have
the same right now they want is
that the new thing know like you
to do that as a three times
a year someone's but yeah have to
go for every four months i had
been obsessing about it though for three
three years at that point like it
had been on my mind and been
like your man or yourself worse right
yeah you're horrible and then i went
into such a like alright later because
you took care of your teeth you
did a job loss every day so
there ya go that's the one thing
that they they say is the one
thing you should do now don't do
that now there's really doesn't matter no
no i see i don't think that's
true
by the way we have the days
they say coffee is bad for you
they say is good for you we
have the same dentist by the way
really a new and neither of us
go to him anymore
oh that guy yeah in larchmont yeah
yeah yeah that fuckin guy what did
he do to you do you want
to say or no i can't remember
oh
he yeah it was something where he
he put in a crown and it
fell out like right away or something
like that it was something that he
it was like some shoddy work on
his part and i said hey this
is messed up and he brought me
back in and then like rushed me
through the procedure like shot me with
nova cain and then immediately started working
i'm like hey
oh hey i'm like em you feel
bad oh my are you supposed to
wait at least us five seconds and
like he's like oh yeah you're right
and then just like kept working it
was the weirdest fucking thing it was
horrible i i that is so scary
yeah you know he did to me
is i went in there and he
made me wait forty five minutes before
taking me and then um called me
back a week later and said hey
that wasn't cool so we're not gonna
charge you what
boy was terrible so i like my
the death servo i like a lot
and i i think about this all
the time and i don't know if
i've ever talked to anybody else about
it do you have this experience where
the dentist will ask you can i
put my kind of readiness in my
mouth
my mom
martinez sit in my mouth do you
think i can do it
now do you have this experience or
a better bike and then they just
get on the floor and they just
try to tell y'all again and it
takes up most of enforcement like i'm
sorry
next somersaults here ah wasn't able today
come back next week
that's okay so yeah so you do
have that okay so
it's gonna happen it's a woman yeah
yeah yeah toy yo-yos know really what
they will ask um can i put
my instruments in your yes and i
mean on your chest
have you had that experience playing us
yet i mean they asked me to
hold something these days a day
ah laura
no they're doing x-rays they go i'm
gonna ask you to hold this and
i thought of this yesterday when i
was at the dentist i was like
is this because you don't have an
extra person to thing that goes in
your mouth yeah you know when they
take an x-ray know like the the
little like car thing your mouse yeah
well you know how sometimes you're supposed
to buy down and yeah you want
you to stay open they're like we're
gonna do you mind holding this oh
i've never had
no oh but i hate those things
like oh was getting into your throat
why is it not gotten better one
time they gave me child-sized version and
it didn't hurt at all like then
they kept giving me the giant ones
again i'm like it cuts your whole
mouth inside like a small version knows
my mouth was cut today that it
might be ah it's like i stick
a car goes to worse for me
i can't figure out about doctors is
i went to i went to see
my doctors this year and he's like
alright well here's the part that is
always uncomfortable and you know the whole
the bill
yeah
grey
are you are you bankrupt yeah i
go to the doctor too
no but the the finger of the
bud
yeah all the time for man it's
all the tie my whole point is
like
but it's says it's a standard procedure
yeah yeah certain age yes yes so
my point is like this would be
job one of like fuck curing cancer
if i were a doctor it would
be like that we gotta figure out
another way to do it yeah you
gotta have a tool that can do
something yeah still the best way yeah
that's what he was saying he's like
there's really no other way to do
this so
let's do he could duke e to
me
do you gotta be cleared out now
that he doesn't you know it's probably
better if you don't because there's a
lot more to work with because less
no a hefty size what feature is
thirty two toothless vegetables anyway i instruments
on the chest oh yeah i find
it to be a it's emasculating no
guys able i will you like find
the opposite wavering i find like a
thundershirt i like the extra i like
the question
because it's so it's so formal and
it's so like there's something that's very
intimate about it and it's also very
like old fashioned like you don't have
a deal you can put in front
of me and put this almost like
essentially obviously that's the easiest thing to
to put them right there it's like
my it's the shortest distance to my
right right but there's something i love
that they have to add
ask i don't know why it it
it weirdly touches me oh interesting anyway
just off we look up
thirty two toothless vegetables we love this
on the wall eight
you here's what happens okay players tailless
turns
players take turns to name a fruit
or vegetable without showing their teeth oh
no repetition allowed so we will go
around will name a fruit or vegetable
you have to say it i guess
is distinctly as possible without without showing
teeth and if and if we see
teeth we can call it out or
what if you show teeth or laugh
you're out okay okay so why not
i start yeah seems fair okay
i'm gonna start with this one and
that's awesome d thriving
did your shitty yeah but go ahead
you haven't said you smiled
tomato i don't want to know but
that was all one tooth which oh
it's impossible so much so that was
that counted that counted okay alright you
got one on dec
don't have
of kyoto
good didn't see it because it didn't
say it okay data say it then
say it not going to see it
not guys say it through no wait
your microphone you're blocking you're blocking it
oh my god you look so shrill
re
didn't see it did you know didn't
see it and see it
and
brutal ruger rid of yeah okay okay
no no
yeah what did you say something what
was it you said let us oh
lettuce oh notice okay alright
oh right
was that grape okay okay okay ah
okay
how many are we up to familiar
we at thirty two
kurt oh that was really good thank
you you have a future as a
ventriloquist saying carrot o'doherty the twist i
see the teeth on worked well that
that's what i'm doing visual you do
yoga girl very yeah i now i
like guys
laughter
she laughed after i heard strom it
doesn't have to laugh i'm still in
huh
mango pineapple
this is the thing we should be
busy say get me to take another
running slow worse game to listen to
here for the delay guys hi there
it's a bad idea huh okay what
didn't matter
not good huh okay pineapple oh my
god somebody get out
russell's grown oh my gosh your mustache
is helping okay i to say i
want to i want to have a
fake mustache
yeah
cute orange
okay okay
try a different tactic okay i'm trying
to think of
um trying to think of a fruit
or vegetable
there's only like five left oh
grow your own good great
oh my god
yeah
yeah okay we're going
i go lucky and by the way
so awesome
always leave em wanting something else
i'm giving up i mean the three
doing this is there any value to
this it's a completely visual thing
it's also we're not gonna laugh or
jerky and we've figured we've cracked the
code can we come up with thirty
two like i'm i've run out of
fruits and vegetable oh i haven't ooh
what he got it's just feed around
okay
turn up
bagel oh yeah bed that's how you
play thirty june two lettuce vegetable bowls
yeah that was me
i'm sure the listener at home
or at work or at work enjoyed
that
well guys this exam believe it this
year at the end of the road
here the end of the line
wrong but i can't play doh as
well to ma na mamdouh me
i wish any of the song boise
man i mean i know what it
is but other words if i wanted
to join in i felt bad defined
if seller from philly but he's embarrassed
yeah if boysen man called paul
they called you and they made you
begged you to make dinner with bill
cosby no i say they they said
look
by the way i had a friend
ooh not really friends so many which
is cool okay that makes more sense
who like was one of these compulsive
liar people who would tell the most
outlandish lies and you would you want
it's so crazy when you know someone's
lying friend they're trying for no reason
you're like why do i know you're
lying it's maddening it doesn't matter it's
maddening but it's
to me it's like always like you
think i'm stupid yeah like you think
i'm a i'm a dumb person that
you think that anything that is obvious
lie that you're we've been lying during
any of the episodes on the show
i've actually lied all the time that's
why i said it right yeah i'm
down no but i have i had
a friend who was like he swore
that the summer before
or the gin blossoms were going through
town the band the gin blossoms who
had just started having big hits with
hey jealousy and everything and their drummer
had ah hurt his foot or something
in town and they were going around
town going does anyone drum we have
a gig tonight and he's like i
play drums and he had to learn
all their side
runs and played with them that night
and this is like one of the
series of sly oh my heel toe
like if anything of course they know
drummers
they would just call someone else say
the idea that they would just have
to throw it out to the world
so is there anyone around here to
play draw but this but it's something
that i
i've now thought of because you know
twitter's around you can get a hold
of people like i want to write
to the general awesome shea you showed
has did this ever actually happen there
was the other the other weird thing
that happened i and i think about
this i want to reach out to
him and i just have never done
it is i was in a video
store in orange county in nineteen ninety
three
three and i was looking for the
new twin peaks video orange county was
a video stores
um i was looking for the new
twin peaks video tapes that had just
come out on v h s and
i asked the clerk the guy who
worked at the video store in orange
county said hey i'm looking for twin
peaks and he goes oh i worked
on that show i'm like really who
are you what do you do on
it he goes i'm harley peyton i
was a producer and i was like
really what
and they worked in videos and he's
working in a video store and i
was like oh cool and i for
years i was like man i met
harley paint and that's interesting no sense
so and now he's on twitter i
want to ask did you work out
of it maybe he did i have
no idea but it doesn't seem like
you never know coffin was a busboy
yeah but i don't believe he was
real but
i just don't think it was hymns
but then what an insane lied to
tell sam that to me is a
good lie it was like yog yeah
i'm this guy well yeah usually knew
the name too so it was like
oh you're highly paid and yeah cool
like but so stressful i would know
someone's life well what what happened that
you would go from producer
like a hit television show to that
i will twin peaks i'm sure it
was filled with just weirdos who maybe
that was the only show i ever
worked on or whatever but it's a
way to rationalize it but i have
no anyway i want to write to
him and see if that it actually
was him but those are those are
two lives but why we were talking
about oh yeah so avoids de men
yes if boys to men you are
in philly yeah they called you
up and said paul um were shot
were short a member we've heard you
singing on your many podcasts um this
is weird but we want you to
sing our concert with us um and
we're going to tell you all twelve
songs we're going to do and you
don't have to learn our entire repertoire
why would you do it how how
much time do i have you have
all afternoon to learn the songs no
i can't do that what you haven't
like they call you in the morning
that's but ten shows that night but
these these songs and they're gonna they're
gonna send you the parts your part
picked up i would say i would
like to do that you wouldn't do
it i
i know that i wouldn't i wouldn't
have it down by the time and
they tell you look to be honest
we're going to carry you all you
gotta do is come out kind of
mount if you ever get lost just
mouth rutabaga rutabaga rutabaga why wouldn't i
mouse say no because they know that's
your favorite vegetable from thirty
i gotta do it like with your
lips no it won't look like you're
saying anything it is it is one
of my great heartbreaks that i i'm
very slow to learn harmonies for things
okay when i've had to sing in
public and i have had to do
like a sort of intricate even slightly
ah involve
solved harmony i've blown it many thai
hate harmonies it's it's i like them
i love your you out but you
have a natural ear for them i
think oh i can't figure out harmonies
it takes me a long time what
ifs what okay so then what if
it wasn't a singing thing what if
it was a play someone called you
haven't said paul um there what was
the play that we saw
new york hamilton no
oh yeah what was that called the
steam steam no it wasn't saying sweats
right yeah oh my god i was
just staring you i was like i
guess so yeah no idea sweat calls
you up they know you've seen it
before they've heard us talk about it
and they say hey do you want
to can you this actor dropped out
it would be
a big thrill if you were to
take his place that happened to me
really yes and it was ah it
was a small part for nice girls
so i think yeah well you're a
small man the it's me i'm a
small um it was the apple sisters
and they were doing a show at
largo and they said this part is
usually done by r
friend chris he can't he had to
drop out can you do it and
it was the same night and it
was fucking nerve wrack i don't think
i could do that it was really
nerve-wracking i the lines like right off
stage right and so i would like
hastily try to like all day i
tried to memorize it and it was
like you know it was like an
like a little bit of evolved wordplay
kind of thing and the
timing of their size musical stuff happening
at the same time so it'd be
precise and i did like a very
i think i did like a a
an okay patrick job but it was
not not my best work and i
felt bad about it i think and
i still feel bad about wow
oh my god lauren learning laura no
i'm not okay coffee needle and fell
down huh do we need to end
i guess we need to and you're
gonna end up guys cough shows then
cough shows the end cough shows the
end
christmas find out who gave that to
tea cough show the end cough show
the end i wanna say thank you
to everyone for listening to all ten
eps yes thank you i know they
listen to all of them yes i
want to thank you guys for doing
this this was a lot of fun
this was a lot of disbelief this
was a lot of fun i'm glad
we finally did this and it's always
so much fun to hang out with
you guys
i hope we do more i hope
we do more too but you know
what i mean the audience will be
the judge of that they need to
call the phone lines we all hear
well you've got to flood those phone
lines guys and remember it's sex one
for yes and two for no yes
and don't switch him out paul and
while you're on the phone text one
or two yeah look we're gonna be
up and say i text twisted one
one look i'm gonna be honest if
you texted to that you don't want
to we think you'd probably just fuck
up yeah and you might you've got
oil in you wouldn't care that yeah
yeah so we're gonna go vote we're
just gonna assume you all wanna hear
more so let's do more okay okay
ah
uh this has been an year with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com