three
ah
da one million oh let's help him
oh palsy
hope oh oh hey the most wonderful
dream we were that i was joking
yeah you're going you're face is turning
blue you're rolling around on the floor
because you get your throat i look
like i was an avatar you know
i had a dream with lauren it
the other night
we were somewhere we were like on
the road somewhere with some other people
like maybe a comedy festival something like
that and we were having the best
time that's we're hanging out offstage i
love to get in that dream was
i up for it did i just
missed out i think you were holding
things down at home wow and we
talked about it we were like god
is great
i'm so sorry is holding things down
yeah got it i mean you know
got a lot going on at least
got us all of these data back
oh i love that that was a
fun dream it was a fun dream
i it really made me happy when
i woke up because it was very
true to life i love that yeah
i i've been having you know i
always have pretty intense dreams i would
say yeah
but i really like that i like
when i wake up and i'm like
whoa i was just in a whole
world yeah you're fine i like that
too i won't bother transport canada guys
really this is the second avatar reference
i've made i know and both of
them really just fell flat sunk sunk
know i remember once you watch it
would you say paul
nothing fucked zero fucks you know
i also had a dream about pandora
recently this i would qualify this as
a nightmare okay which i haven't had
a long time okay but then when
i woke up it was pretty fun
um most of the dream was myself
at some other people that i did
not know were held hostage by armed
this armed gang
gang right yeah folks they were thugs
so to speak and they were making
us do ah like practical dugard well
they were making us feel like we're
guessing his dream yeah manual labor um
and tasks and things like that but
then there was one where
day the guy with a rifle
it said ah told me that i
had to write as many
i had to tweet as many one-line
ah jokes as i could um while
he hunted me with the rifle and
so they had made a fake comedy
club
so this guy was on stage with
the rifle and i was hiding behind
chairs and shit like that haha but
i had to send the tweets on
a like a nokia cell phone like
i was doing routine nine texting yeah
and somehow they were reaching twitter but
i was like hiding like a booth
and refreshing selected jokes is that your
subconscious
just telling you you need to write
more
no i think it's my subconscious telling
me go back to a flip phone
oh okay yeah yeah because i was
very good at t nine texting yeah
the dream and in real life yeah
i loved i loved t nine i
loved my flip i loved it all
and then you know the smartphone came
and it changed my life and it
changed changes everything change
just every night see i'm gonna do
a movie where i started steve jobs
inventing the already made jobs you know
what and now we have no cash
whoa yeah
no johnny carson what i was going
to like matt damon thing where i
like you know it's like hair with
hair with hair hair yeah had the
invention of hair the hair was the
h is silent
err you think it confuses cockney people
and oh see hey all these movies
about ah yeah i'm like it is
whereas the age of aquarius low it's
the age of michael jordan i list
notably without her that's true and isn't
aquarius did he ever have hair already
played i watched all of the last
dance i don't remember him having here
he didn't have hair he's like an
opposite samson
yeah where he had really long cubes
but no hair that's part of samson
nope cubes you need to read your
script
i think they mentioned the cubes i
added i think they did did they
know because it's that's a big part
of it right when they introduce each
character in the bible don't they mention
what you linger hughes's because you need
to be able to imagine them so
yeah surely yeah yeah just going clause
so you can always managing them swing
side decided
do that if you're like setting someone
on a date or doing something like
what functions are slight he's really tall
you do go out a date he's
really tall he's he has brown hair
his power to blank his pupils he
keeps them a little trim reporter length
i dreamed of i dreamed a joke
the other day baseball tee yeah it
wasn't it wasn't raglan sleeves raglan regimens
right when i love raglan sleeves i
do too i think that's very gratifying
cut although they're not long enough for
my tastes i'd prefer them to go
to the wrist okay great
um i dreamed a joke the other
day dream to jo da da um
and i i woke up i was
like well i guess i got to
put it on instagram i guess i
gotta because i dreamed it i kept
i kept dreaming like go you remember
this remember this when you wake up
yeah and it was basic
really just like four pictures one was
ah it was about sex and the
city it was about kim control but
you dreamed a cartoon dreamed cartoon well
cheers didn't know they were moving images
actually about twenty nine point six six
for pictures yeah no but i it
was basically kim control saying she wasn't
going to do sex in the city
reboot and then the the article that
said she agreed to do the sexton
city reboot and then i posted that
terrible thing that everyone always posts of
ah these ninety nine for quotes of
the government told you not to believe
your eyes i saw your jokes and
you know what i was really surprised
by this this this
she's very funny because i think it's
gone it's gone it was this story
for but here's the thing you've that
you were surprised i was tweeting citing
the time it's here why the fuck
is scott making a joke i honestly
was like first you posted the news
and i went really and i think
yeah it was a sequence of four
but i went with her and she's
gonna get ie if it
was you because i was like why
and then you posted the thing with
her saying she would never do it
huh and then the thing where she
says she will do it yeah and
then and then the quote of the
what is it the the whatever know
not to believe yeah right yeah it
was thanks for something yeah which everyone
is always using these days and it
made me laugh
in the dream no it was posting
about something stupid valid joke and it
was a funny joke yeah but it
was so out of what you normally
out about yeah like i'm like wait
what do you typically get into this
sort of pop culture commentary know but
anyway well now that i'm off twitter
i'm i'm using instagram for these types
of jokes and ai and it did
not get the engagement
i wanted to me to us and
you know what i posted um is
a screencap of my notes that i
that i wrote down the notes i
gave you about your last bang bang
yes and i said look at this
you believe the shit
i wrote it i had like had
this weird dream and i wrote it
down i thought this is really funny
and ah and then i forgot about
it and then i looked at the
notes and it just said
animatronic pillsbury doughboy doll funny animatronic hugh
grant ball and i don't and somehow
how are they connected i don't remember
okay okay you grant loves blow jobs
he probably was like hey it says
sticking my dick do this you'll also
she got arrested yeah sounds the first
thing i think when i think of
him
i think of that factually the only
thing you see are of navigation screen
and of course paddington to my note
he likes to stick his penis into
ah sex workers mao this so what
do we want a way of saying
what if he did it into the
pillsbury pillsbury doughboy stomach okay what oh
probably what you're thinking what i was
thinking because
but i thought would be kind of
funny as if an animatronic hugh grant
walked up to the pillsbury doughboy and
used his animatronic fingertip polk the animatronic
pillsbury doughboy and then they both said
like oh whatever they say
i think in the dream i was
do you think my injection if he
had said yeah whooo man i thought
we were past it i really felt
really like in the middle of songs
he'd be like yeah who would that
have been as popular z i think
if how popular is he
i mean he did it wow he's
also shamwow unpopular yeah well if you
mean popular i call known yeah it's
well known but i don't think people
are like i love when he goes
he he i remember being confused by
shaman and then knowing like still it's
pretty good and you saw shamwow yep
and then i saw shaman but if
you were like vince got run
ooh alright i think in the dream
it was definitely that i was i
was thinking there should be an animatronic
pillsbury doughboy that you could poke in
the stomach because they sell like a
little doll of the variable but the
way if you poke it stomach too
hard it never seals the doughboys say
he heals back up yeah
i want an epic tronic
oh boy that if you break through
through the other side it just like
magically goes like uses a bis uv
i want to get one that's something
you want think about
book three six yep we get to
that of this technology and here you
don't want the more modern one no
no i want the old for the
moral system see those in cameron experiment
with
but that would be good wouldn't it
yeah a little low pillsbury doughboy in
a base one was going to look
around stomach and he lost i think
that that part i don't unless you
could like insults i don't know he
just had to take it i don't
know i can't tell you but i
do have a vision of my head
of a hugh grant head
on like a sort of chucky body
and overall little in the middle yeah
but i got much back yeah wow
yeah yeah i got a very sad
hugh grant face hangdog face so a
hugh grant face on a pillsbury body
no chucky body oh chucky body oh
okay i'm i took your body just
keep wanting to buy tickets based on
chucky
but cheese is normal body thinking but
it's amazing i'm just talking about a
huger talking about a chucky buddy his
normal bodies like a double chubby
thanks yeah make yourself as like three
chuckie
i'm three twinkies and you were on
like if you were lying on a
dating app it's like talking like three
chucky wanna like jackson instead of going
he went to what if what if
my jackson said i'm going he went
ha ha ho ho
very chris many took it from santa
and then we went i think it's
kind of a michael jackson one santa
then was forced to go
yeah just traded up and couldn't write
what could be good to make santa
say something else at this point at
this point to lee onto him saying
whoa whoa whoa i feel like we
can't add anything to the canon because
people are like don't mess with it
we know what works yeah what if
i mess isaac so you know after
he delivered presence and he goes case
no clue
what do you think is the best
way how you object how did you
learn about santa just a
how did i learn about santa yeah
i'm sure fred de tabel ism i
know because i'm like how what capitalistic
things should i use to teach hollywood
about sand yeah why do remember being
five or six and i think my
parents saying like by the way they're
santa isn't real but i knew it
by away
or alert yeah by the way we
should put in a little spike wow
what santa brought you by saying there
is a conversation about santa that you
should skip because some children to listen
to the show that's true um but
me knowing it in my heart already
yeah we have a six year old
weird place by eight now she he
oh gee you better know she um
but i knew it like i knew
it in my heart but i still
felt like
i needed to be upset about it
or saying also i was kind of
like oh come on why were you
lying to me but i also knew
it i don't know these know but
but i want i want to get
her excited for she's just so little
that it's now is the time to
have some fun and so i think
we have to watch some movies but
i want to see the great depictions
well
what about the rankin bass stuff i
guess sam was coming down with roger
from general pub yeah okay alright p
you should drink yeah he's had them
think about it
finally i can write compete
the english beats bother you please let
me rank but you had older siblings
i did so that was probably a
lot of it was that mean like
santa i mean it must be i
don't you could do that santa i
so for saying it yeah oh yeah
see i am definitely going to be
saying oh sanchez gonna be coming oh
right see what i always just say
the word santa until holly can say
what are you saying cuba yeah what
is santa um i don't remember learning
about santa i do have the vague
memory of kind of figuring it out
like nobody there is a lot
anybody spoiled context clues yeah it was
just like i got old enough and
it was just like oh yeah that's
oh see when i was in school
so i was gobbling me that their
older sibling told them right and i
told them my mom was really upset
and she really wanted me to cry
for as long as possibly i knew
the tooth fairy wasn't real but i
still liked the quarter
yeah and so then when my parents
forgot i like left they that my
mom actually sewed me a pillow with
a pocket for a tune so cute
and smart because it's easy to grab
yeah i'm just gruesome and they they
forgot to do it on one of
my last teeth and i was so
upset put the tooth back in
oh they just didn't you woke up
and there's a tooth and the tooth
was there and i was like hey
and luck i've been there like oh
yeah sorry you know the tooth fairy
is real and i'm like i know
but i want my corner
how long you have to sneak in
and get it are you going to
save holly's teeth now i don't know
about the saving some people do it
i know i'm gonna eat them myself
i don't think i eat see her
grow here's three or something yep on
one hand i'd go no i don't
want to save them and they're gonna
go i'm gonna throw away
if they're part of all i know
it's kind of cute and also kind
of amazing to see i wonder where
you can do with them i wonder
what kind of projects they have nowadays
on etsy with tea you can put
them in dolls and it's really two
weeks really just that's too weird i'm
talking more like guys on a chain
or so i would say look look
it up before in like a little
tube on a necklace yeah go go
to etsy
like one of those charm bracelets yeah
that's so grow like a cannibal oh
my but you can look them up
on etsy there's doll you can make
a doll with baby teeth in it
and they're they're really creepy but they're
also pretty funny oh my god i
gotta see i think it's crazy that
we have we're born with all of
our adult teeth and her baby teeth
and they just like go yeah
it's really weird o d v m
i'm showing in any pictures you just
got one giant to a tv um
got a shutting up from the bottom
of her mouth tuffy um a toughie
ah there's a lot of things that
really cute you can in the words
your phone case with a smiling holly
on that q
it's very cute to splurge um there's
a thing where you can put how
much effort don't suitably beefy dollars yeah
actually i don't know because mike mike
bought them but ah it's from case
to fi which is not not a
cheap situation q please describe but look
here's the thing where it shows like
a who's two it's like even the
baby pic
usher in the versuchen picture in the
middle and there's it's holes all around
it in different sizes and you put
in ruth what date they lost to
them but the tooth in their clea
and whoa it also says oh yes
cheese and your road to see your
specified day joseph and sarah here and
there as well
yeah i think we should say one
at a time let's do tea let's
do mister geez let's do her hair
but does it do why mixon no
yeah come on no no they're kind
of all made of the same thing
right you know when you think about
it like we're constantly shedding skin cells
we're constantly shedding hair now maybe we're
shedding our teeth i bleed all there's
probably like a second one of us
out there
if walking right if you put it
all together oh okay if you put
it all together so we should save
everything and then we have you know
two children right lauren exactly that's why
we will not vacuum in our home
because ryan's hills in there because it's
like honestly so long
it's here that i'm kind of in
with christians we're here for life this
is a great idea this is akin
to that tooth fairy pickup thing that
you hang on the door and that's
good i'm it's a little whatever you
don't have to disturb the yes yeah
put it on the door but i
think isn't the fun that it's on
it's under your pillow isn't the fun
now did you have extra mud
any on a fat mean that wants
fifteen dollars did you ever can dollars
it has their name engraved
did you ever catch your parents assault
with the teeth come on i couldn't
answer me that catch my parents know
i never did i never ever caught
them i don't remember ever catching them
yeah crazy you think who would be
like i still can't catch them my
two so
yeah they never stopped i keep regrowing
them your parents know i take two
to the keepsake doll and i'm not
seeing annie getting yet keepsake out of
there okay baby tooth doll yep okay
have a baby just baby look up
just baby tooth dollar funds on etsy
some babies
yeah i'm gonna need you to do
the googling on this one but okay
okay what do you need what do
you need baby what's not happening here
baby to all with real teeth but
that's baby doe's real teeth ok real
teeth
first thing that comes up is this
insane picture of a gross thing that
it oh no real teeth to huh
wow wow real teeth duh wow
this insane picture of a gross thing
is that it
i look i don't know baby hydra
i this is too scary is this
i'm too new only i see this
now i venice or something but then
when i click on it i maybe
i don't know what to do at
sea like a million pictures come up
goddamn will get off of etsy then
well i love etsy and i wanna
stay on it i love it
here i never want to leave at
sea i love my etsy shop i
love my love my shabby shop i
love my etsy shop i love my
etsy shop i love my etsy shop
i love show
as a bed tea shop member see
jungle camp
one lets you shop you can stop
we have to stick right okay
and we're back and paul has been
furiously on his phone looking for this
so ups i am furious like furious
style is very also don't fund and
oh gil somebody
do your paul killed somebody says just
because he couldn't find his couldn't find
it and he'd be all willie and
you'll see that was just being a
song
but i'm from i'm the same i
texted and texted a link to both
of you oh boy this is exciting
i have it here do not disturb
horns just flat out on her phone
that's not true i just am okay
wow oh wow
oh no actually it's gonna barf oh
so you know those ugly dolls like
that's what that's that's the forum for
that oh yeah the other thing that
i that's the thing that came up
but they put real eyeballs that i
don't like real eyeballs too big well
what what i mean do you want
have you lost your baby eyeballs yet
and then the teeth or my wisdom
eyeballs are about to come
in which is gonna hurt i really
don't like this and i actually don't
think there's any reason and i think
it should be illegal and i think
we should stop parents from doing this
is this is we should make law
early one of your not apparent oh
so your advice if i said you
can i have holly's baby teeth to
make one of these dolls that i
would stop talking to whoa
what if i just said
whoa what if it was a mixture
of holly's baby teeth emmys baby tee
i would kill in my regular normal
teas and one of your and then
see if you can guess okay i
need to pull one of scott's teeth
out with like a pliers with wire
yeah he puts it on the hanger
on the door yeah he puts it
in the hangar and get solution for
it
guess the lotion did you ever do
the thing where you tied something to
your tooth that was coming out like
a string and iraq in my brain
i think we went back you know
my dad would grab a piece of
kleenex and then he'd just go grab
my tooth out of my mouth and
pull wow just go yeah i can
like taste the kleenex my teeth and
did you want it out or was
yeah when it was
like wiggling so much but it just
won't fall out i love that feeling
though let me just get around to
the lock i've no idea i don't
think i liked that i haven't been
able to feel it for some for
decades at this point we can make
a surface yeah so say you want
us to make cute little
hey you want me to be good
you look it's like a setup nobody
would see coming yes maybe no flying
punch step outside i'll make a teeth
wiggled would you like me to make
to look a little sure what wow
when you got sour candies know i'm
gonna punch your teeth until they wiggle
oh yeah somebody's our candidate feels like
oh hey my teeth are wiggling it's
going crazy so are you has going
green has holly lost her teeth nope
are you going them are you going
to do the same thing where you
pull it out that way or you
got some other item see myself why
does i wouldn't i guess i'd be
okay with doing that if she was
ready for me to do that
when do your teeth start falling out
well like i remember this happen feels
like like zab in a ivor yeah
i think it can't arrive no i
don't think you know i remember it
it's more like seven eight nine i
moved when i was left seven twelve
and i remember them all falling up
before that so it can't happen at
six okay maybe i was i think
five might be a little err
early okay i would like it if
they allow his early one at a
time and in order yeah i like
that too but we ordered that they
fall out in
oh so whatever that means
i mean like starting back to front
so it goes and it goes like
just all the way around like that
at one point you just have your
medal
yeah yeah
all right or all make that happen
they should fall out six at a
time okay or they the back teeth
fall out first and then and the
anti rollback in so that at a
certain transition point you have adult back
teeth and a little baby teeth that
would be really cute it would be
cut
kind of know and make you you'll
be cute the other way around if
you had a rusty big big buckley
i don't know that there's any cute
option
buckwheat big buckwheat
no yeah the absence of tea what
am i thinking you're thinking of buck
teeth buck teeth yeah oh cool buckwheat
yeah yeah big buckaroo top buck teeth
was like when i grew up on
nineties was what one of my favorite
characters i loved buck teeth the cowboy
yeah but about cowboy just like seetha
cowboy dentist with the big long teeth
and the big
roberto floss with the big blog teeth
then the rope made a floss it's
bog te
say hey i said wheat with the
big front t and the royal may
never floss it's buh we
ah you know we ate lunch right
before we started recording and i thought
that's going to interfere with our energy
but luckily it's making us go and
say yeah the good thing is i'm
really tired and my eyes are shutting
yeah i hit a steak minutes ago
oh yeah i did have a steak
i did let's say i want it
you had a you had a full
steak along with ah arugula salad kind
of situation i just got two sides
of the arugula fennel lemon and then
you had a site of thanksgiving turkey
and stuffing you know the side of
thanksgiving dinner at a side of melatonin
i meant to get the salt and
pepper chicken oh get the fried chicken
i was happy and i feel like
i subconsciously did that earlier ones better
actual like you or anyone you know
tums would not allow you to press
yes the button of the healthier chicken
never used that feature that you used
last night it was great we're not
doing that for ubereats right no we're
not but it
was a good feature we will do
for tender greens though there it was
a good feature that you sent out
a link sent out late i'll add
our order to it yeah i like
that i like great too hey if
ubereats wants to sponsor the show i'm
more than happy lot more tender greens
honestly yes we both got a state
they combined to make this powerful zoltan
of lunch
for us was trying to me it
was delivered and it was cooked and
both things yeah all things came together
yeah more about zil e-tron maybe i'm
the voltron maybe you are but older
ones cool yeah it was ultra tell
me like it's from big big but
who is na are you guys your
race hs ultra is an american rock
music
the poster designer oh right of course
that's who i was thinking of what
wait does he know i'm thinking i'm
just talking ah
who da tell me my wiz shows
zo tie what i'm sorry
here we go
yeah those autos very scary especially when
you find out he's not pluggedin yeah
what the fuck now that's gonna freeze
yes sentient then xl tar is that
what they're implying is that he sent
hint he is even adjusted had he's
from hell i think so
why else would he do that it's
a good point what weird lesson to
teach a kid who wished to be
big because you don't mean what was
the point of that whole exercise if
he's not a demon from hell i
mean right he gets to have sex
yeah but then he traumatized this woman
who's committed statutory rape me but she
doesn't know that she's just at the
end she finds out she finds out
that yes
transform into a little boy sort of
heartwarming at that point oh right but
the weirdest part of it bending the
end is he's gone for how long
has he caught for eight years like
he's gonna say yeah knows married has
children has gone for a while because
he fully gets a job he's right
he's gone for a long time that
promoting terrifies his mm
mother his mother comes back to his
mother's like where were you for the
last twenty years that mercedes rahel oh
yeah whatever happened remember city's rule i
don't know i helped the family all
went to therapy but i hope that
i hope so well you know i
don't what if they didn't just bottle
it all but i don't think that
he should even try to explain what
really happened why everything sounds like a
pitch
ich my yeah big sql i know
starring colin hanks and call yeah
yeah okay no it's called small gotta
be called it's called too big
it's called medium now it's probably the
the real way to do it is
like his son wishes he was big
and he's like let me take you
to the carnival well it's like oh
let's not know his teen wolf the
dad is we don't want to see
that what i'm saying is i want
to see but they both go in
and they've swapped play yeah let me
finish
so they both go to the carnival
he's like sohn i got a machine
and we're going to be best buds
now because we'll be the same age
and then xl tar makes colin hanks
small and then he has to hang
out with his son for an entire
summer and he's like he has paper
out he gets a paper lady wu
wei will awake
that's a good idea has chores yes
to go to bed he gives himself
chores yeah
yes go to school learn arithmetic well
sort of like back to the future
situation because yeah it's like you're hanging
with his three teenage mom i want
to see the psychological fallout of what
happened does is grow that much between
high school finishes broke that much between
high school and calls on if you're
excited or not you might be yeah
well i think his penis wouldn't get
that small do they do they grow
that much between me seeing pamela anderson
or nazi
so when you see her at small
when she walks away yeah i don't
want to go
but because elizabeth perkins is still around
she's still arrived on still around right
now logie is not not there yeah
do we want to get his like
on this in this if if it's
present day of course he'd be dead
he was an old man then but
what if socom hanks is still around
and tom hanks is still around have
colin hanks wish he
was older and then who you i
don't want this you don't want any
wishes no results soldiers right there though
no zol tar is gone to the
dump guys guys guys stop fighting and
just make the movie
trust in yourself and it will be
great without a script honestly the only
way to sell this argument is to
start working together i think so
i think so in a great partnership
huh
i feel you just you're only interested
in like an interior drama where it's
just the examining the psychological ramifications you
don't want any magic i want to
see the weirdness of them having to
deal with it and just the mother
has the mother accepted that it happened
or is she still in denial about
everything everyone has acce
and everyone that was involved in this
believes it they know that it happened
so the mother walks home in a
suit that's for a man but that
could happen tomorrow or later yeah haven't
you ever been kidnapped by someone and
they put you in their basis what
he's defending east protecting the murderer they
just go just why they murder haley
really murder took your clothes there
want to be younger they just they're
successful it's actually creepy they took his
regular clothes and they they're like fine
just wear one of ours back we
already really ruined we already ruined your
back okay so this is what the
mother believes her mind snaps so she's
going insane so she's rubber mind has
snapped within the first eight minutes of
the film elizabeth perkins has become a
nun because she can
not yale with what has happened yeah
yeah who else is in this
those are the only ones and people
that i can think yeah it was
a three hunter what other best friend
his best friend his best friend is
there and his best friend has been
trying to find zoeller ever since then
yes i want to have sex tools
he's got a red yarn board i
think their relationship probably have she still
isn't that sex
he's waiting for salter i just called
waiting for volta i think when when
they get when when the kid gets
regular size everyone's like the sequel to
pig is called waiting
ah
strange choice how can they haven't made
that into a musical yet big yeah
because it's already got a great song
dating dating dating dating dating dating dating
blir so big was the opposite of
lead aware it's so bad really don't
want that to happen but if they
did they have to do the like
like shimmy shimmy cocoa puff shimmy shimmy
rye yeah mommy cocoa puffs and that's
like an eight thing that's all part
of koko bop thing okay i don't
yeah and it makes me go pop
shimmy shimmy rye how does it go
imad girlfriend a trinket she said a
tryst get a biscuit ice cream soda
topic very well that's up ooh show
me walking down the street ten times
a week
i meant it i said it i
your mom's credit suck me in the
seventeen more ty i don't know what
you wow that was actually extremely close
yeah what is it it was from
big it is he and his best
friends how they prove when he's big
he comes back into
ah heels because supposed to be sure
that goes through like it's crazy does
yeah um one of my favorite that's
the only time that convention has worked
for me yeah because it's a convention
that they use a lot when you
want to stat i'm the only person
who knows this thing no no no
these people have known each other for
a long time yeah right and so
they they see each other and they
immediately go into some light elaborate choreographed
thing or
or rhyme or whatever yeah that didn't
really work so because it feels really
authentic and yes part of it too
is that tom hanks who worked with
the kid actor ultra and studied him
yeah tried to act like him yeah
please also did the same thing before
it's gone he worked his shadow killer
free
the kid actor had a strong accent
and so instead of having the kid
speak differently he had adapted yes that's
why it's so bad
ah i haven't watched that movie since
i was a teen probably so watching
him yeah good i liked it i
remember thinking at the time it was
like a epic historical film it's honestly
it's a great stunt you know what
i mean like the that aspect of
it is still i think very good
but i remember i did not see
the theaters
as this was when i was working
a tower video and it when it
finally came on v h s i
saw it and on a sixteen inch
screen yeah in the store
and i was like this is bad
no i think i think i brought
it home and and watched it and
kept it know that want to get
back
oh bad sports stuff that you gave
that one back you hit back in
the stacks yeah hid all the copies
so would would fight
i turned them all backwards
alright well like hey guys why i'm
not supposed to look at you don't
look at me i told you going
to the pygmy had a rule we
would look really do the podcast you
don't look at me we face away
from each other yeah yeah we're all
three standing with our backs to each
other we do this by the way
we do the show standing which i
don't think people appreciate yeah they started
to attach all you know we always
did super ego standing really really oh
yeah i remember doing y yeah i
don't know i couldn't tell you because
we could easily have sat down but
i do remember once jeremy carter doing
spontaneous nation and saying he can't improvise
v sitting down that's probably what i
would imagine that's why i think for
i guess for
energy but it it actually ended up
stashing energy more yeah
yeah and also we couldn't see each
other that well because we had these
big shields big by the way i
sound baffling shields in front of the
space goes down down baby down down
the roller coaster sweet sweet baby sweet
sweet don't let me go shimmy shimmy
cocoa pop shimmy shimmy rock shimmy shimmy
cocoa pop shimmy shimmy rock imad girlfriend
tris get cheese said tris get a
biscuit ice cream soda pop vanilla on
the top
usia leto walk in the street ten
times a week i'm in it i
said it still enormous credit i'm cool
i'm hot sock you in the stomach
three more times that was nice we
should all learn that and then if
we're ever big yes yeah do that
and we should cut this out because
then other people can use it when
yeah trick us because someone
lawyers say oh she be cool
no way is that an existing thing
was yeah i think it's an existing
thing um is it so here let
me it exists definitely well because like
like nellie later uses some of that
one really jimmy jimmy yeah lighted it
up and take a puff as dina
alright so let's not oh baby we'll
put up a baby
i mean i don't know it's there's
no way to find this out either
unfortunately
oh wait i'm looking at samarra for
people oh yeah go ahead
talking to you
i i'm i want to get scott
we need to get okay
that kind of thing
talks with it there's a little bit
of follow-up and liquidity issues in my
senior root juice in my rooster
did you find the answer lord no
i'm reading like they'll get the juice
out of your just reading saga post
that is o'connor's tom hanks doing the
rap a wemo thousand and nine
here's tom hanks doing the raf in
ten thousand ninety so they say to
you what are they shout out what
are they asked to you betcha we
chart ah they yell out wilson quite
a bit from the of the costumes
yeah the the jonathan ross forrest run
even though even though i say life
was like a box of chalk you
say this a lot of
i've got to so
i've gotta ask you a question
here's my question
you know my favorite movie yours
we go
ah someone screamed like it was the
funniest thing for her hers on the
bbc oh that makes there's no comedy
in english ninety two times and sarah
fluttering neo saying no actually houston we
have a problem
and they say ah um nice takedown
jonathan on the show they say that
what take guy jordan to take down
did they ask you that will do
the lat from big the flats i
can't be against a movie it makes
me wow just wow don't get me
into dizzy's territory
this is you still have the mood
well it was actually um it was
actually a a thing that my son
learned at summer camp oh looking for
something ruining the movie he knows it
would almost talking about china wait this
it might be chet haze down now
and this is the original rat's sweet
sweet baby sweet sweet olympic shimmy shimmy
koko bop shimmy shimmy rock show
she we talk about chimneys in iraq
driskill cheese ice cream sort of puppet
along the top usia leader walking industry
ten times a week man city has
the mom's credit
no i'm sorry
that was one of the most charming
things i've ever seen now do the
drag rack to see it
do the dew pepsi tree back so
it was from summer camp from summer
camp i wonder which i bet it
was chet haze in that because it's
nineteen eighty eight yeah that's what film
got him into doing ram yeah that
makes sense yeah because he was like
i can't really hear a beat under
this yeah it's
i could be like a big boom
boom yeah yeah this is good yes
and i was good to talk in
a rastafarian accent
we have to take a break
we're talking about instagram during the break
yeah and here's my problem yeah i
watched one mr bean look in motherfuckers
video where he's doing magic yeah and
now it suggests all of them yeah
oh by the way ah mike found
the guy that
i can't remember his name i don't
want to say his name again soldier
mike pouncey of this guy
is this the big long jesus christ
stupid
i gotta say good news
you know these games for five years
by that question oh five years oh
my god what are what are we
watching did we talk about this previous
episode yeah this is the guy where
he would do that thing with his
watch on his ankle and like toe
your time with it oh i don't
remember oh guy anyway i'm not saying
his name okay just wanted to say
i found him
e
know i want to say when i
was a kid there were bumper stickers
that said i found it that were
very popular and i think they have
some religious connotation like jesus yeah like
jesus they called him in it yeah
i feel like the mr being guys
gone away maybe like i didn't click
i say mr bean guys you
looks like monsieur looks exactly like but
he's like italian and they call him
the italian mr bean or something and
he looks exactly like him and then
every comment under he does these magic
tricks with a crazy face and every
comment underneath it is mr bean
ah now they just think that's all
you want to see now they think
that's because i clicked on one because
i was like oh how do you
do that magic trick and i kind
of figured it out like i watched
it three times and other like well
i guess every video you want to
see as this italian mr bean that's
weird
that's weird that's way that is weird
what are you looking at i'm looking
up i found it oh yeah reacher
tie found it i really really yeah
you know what i want it okay
found it i really really found it
let's try it let's try to role
play this okay you just have your
natural reaction to me saying i found
it ok ok i found
oh great we found what a new
life in jesus christ oh i fuckin
got you oh now you're a christian
oh shit yeah it works yeah yeah
and if you're a cop i have
to tell you yeah it's like when
you smirnoff someone so how do you
wait how do you smirnoff ice someone
i don't know this you
you hand them a smirnoff ice out
of nowhere and then they have to
take a knee and drink the entire
thing
yeah you guys just you guys i
haven't heard of the sydney ah two
thousand and five much hey she doesn't
five called they want you to be
present when their
what was i doing in two thousand
and five guys didn't know about this
everybody knows later maybe layers twenty ten
oh really a condo i would say
two thousand and five i was in
college and that was a thing that
was happening okay look this up smirnoff
ice what do you call it smirnoff
ice you got it you nailed it
no but if i look nice in
it guys
nice bear bros i spayed the smirnoff
icing people still do it now i
sung as a game i'm an internet
meme that was popular in two thousand
and ten oh hey i was doing
right lie people die
i was doing a movie already was
obviously chosen to be icing somebody up
a new baba ji woo baba ji
baba do badoo upa de vudu bovada
be happy to be bumpy but to
die there's been some doubt over whether
this is an organic phenomenon or a
marketing stunt by smirnoff which the company
has flatly denied oh my
hey guys let's take them to court
i need i mean i want to
put them on the stand beyond him
solicit nothing slur on the beverages taste
i doubt any alcoholic beverage company would
want to be associated with a drinking
game that stretches the boundaries of good
taste and common sense like this one
does at the same time the viral
spread of the game has seen a
boo
boost in sales for the company oh
interesting
they only want to be associated with
the tasteful drinking games yeah what but
what is you have to you that
okay they touched the bottle and then
they have to drink the whole thing
i believe so yeah cool we should
play this really cool do you want
to play this on the next day
i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna get
some deliberately yeah i'm gonna ice you
buy three smirnoff ice
isis i think we shoot videos where
we surprise each other with asia
and then we're all wasted
sounds good it sounds great to me
speaking of game yes sooner three games
on the show we don't do them
okay and this one i thought of
the other day i thought of it
fondly and i said i want to
get my pals to play this with
me but yeah it's called the jitterbug
game the jitterbug game this is where
we snap our fingers mm
much like the row areas
here who is jitterbug
on the italian mr bean
no no no no none na na
na na hey he's holding his shoes
up
that's not funny at aw
what the fuck is so nobody's hands
aren't there he puts some sneakers looks
like they're on the wrong people we
don't even have to explain he's just
he's the italian mr bean who cares
i can't i can't let the camera
person that's going oh no no i
think it's i think it's easy to
also-ran yeah yeah right mill
worked on the page gender blurs okay
so the way the way we do
this game is right now now i
realize i've clicked on it again now
i'm gonna get twenty three yeah now
that i heard the audio my funds
gonna go oh you wanna see that
one but couldn't find it that's why
i wrote on your mirror in lipstick
welcome to the wonderful world of johnny
mister
why did you opsec oh just write
things on mere yeah you just carried
for that purpose
to welcome people to vote for worlds
um so the way we we do
this is we ah we snap in
time ah like the um the song
the wake me up before you go
go by kwak yeah wham was signed
but jitterbug due abode and so we
have to ah think of
three syllable phrases right that will fit
that rhythm right yeah and we keep
doing it until we stopped doing it
yeah which will be very soon and
somebody else will start accept me because
i always get the timing wrong at
the okay here we go one two
a one two three and voting blocks
i didn't know i was going oh
i didn't either one on start over
one two a one two three four
microphone
parking lot
mr mike
mr bean
bean salad
italy
pizza pie
pizza box
that project
cheese munster
archer
sesame street that's me oscar the grouch
ah grover the clown
wow
ah i like the cheese monster i
like the cheese monster oh yeah let's
do it again new rule new rule
to try to make some reason serban
said oh okay i don't know what
that means don't say do we have
to do a google search before we
do know
okay okay
getting tired of snapping
we don't all have to do it
oh i have arthritic fingers okay
mobilize
boba fett no one's ever said that
alright
the second one that's still good so
good let's keep going okay okay i
don't know
dirty flag
ah
back to me oh no i thought
were yes he rigs you hearing shit
standing man
brain cloth
baby rock okay cool um coolum cooling
the gang
yeah a little bit is cooled cooling
the gang okay let's do it again
okay
fatty belt
boot sucker
tasty toes oh
ah ah ah little book
i mean not the most common
yeah probably only been to three times
huh
ah well but
do i need one more yeah okay
same same rule same roles it's fun
so i'm like yeah
ring of ice
sweat or bug
al candy like al candy oh okay
okay yes yeah
but are not
squash i don't know
ah
ah i think we did it we
had fun alright do we still have
time why why didn't know if we
had to make an announcement fills yeah
we'll make an announcement
where we never have to fill time
we get to spend time together well
well we spent we can spend time
together off bike no i meant to
spend this time together i think it's
time to go have a laugh of
things let's promote things let's from wendy's
come out yeah good question i have
the same question if i guess two
weeks from today okay fuck it should
please
thanked one episode
ya sure what you're really yeah listen
july sunday july ninth at la dream
in highland park you're in los angeles
of riots opie with paul f tompkins
it's going to be very fun we're
back with this can we watch succession
after this one or yeah we're gonna
start succession from the first season
watch them all in one and watch
them all in one night so bring
your pajamas and beef jerky going to
have a live show that i'm excited
about doesn't have a date yet um
but i'm about december twenty fifth ah
in a private christmas day um no
but you know keep your eyes peeled
i'm sure i'll announce it once actually
now i'm sure you will please follow
me on instagram or you will yeah
yeah
follow me on instagram i'm almost on
blue sky now the fuck is that
i saw you post about that it's
like early twitter kind of okay but
now i can't get an invite you
have to be invited you have to
be invited and i can invite anybody
having been there long enough man i
don't want to go i have to
be a good little boy i um
by the comedy bang bang book yeah
bye
that book by the book um it's
good people like it you look you
guys are new york times bestselling authors
and that's really exciting true that's really
excite so and by default you were
too
and follow us on social media freedom
usa write to us at three am
usa gmail dot com if you'd like
to send us an idea for a
three-tier like the kind of fun game
that we just played okay well i'll
admit it's a game yeah yeah oh
my god he knew it anyway if
you want to call us and leave
us a voicemail maybe you need some
advice maybe you
you like to do something different leave
us an under thirty second voicemail when
you call if it's thirty one seconds
though paul said okay no absolutely not
you only uptime these
thirty is the absolute cutoff really yes
okay okay so you want to call
us at high claims eight it's great
it's great and then look if you
want ad-free episodes of this and you
know you do you learn how you
do you little piece vague dirty little
piss pig um go to stitcher
premium or cb world they both have
the ad-free episodes and you don't have
to listen us rambling on although i
personally i would listen to the ads
because we do them so well i
love em i love ads yeah advertisements
i call him alright remember incidents to
remember that show admin yeah yeah it
was good yeah
alright goodbye bye
a
uh