thereto
oh
oh ma do you know what that
is still a great theme so great
i was thinking about the malarkey i
enjoyed every time i hear it i
was thinking about it the other day
welcome to three and by the way
but i was thinking about when we
um i'm paul f tompkins i'm lauren
key lucas i'm
i'm sd aquaman are you q oh
my guy for just a dewdrop i'm
queuing on oh to tell you i
was gonna tell you and then i
thought i don't think they refer to
themselves as q and i were queuing
on oh ding dong hai work you
know yeah i'm sure whatever they do
it's really cool i was thinking about
when we came up with the title
of it and then we premiered it
at comic-con and everyone it was met
with a collective shrug oh yeah that
panel really sucked that was uncomfortable and
we almost didn't do the show but
then here's here's the other thing i
was thinking about was like did the
theme song save it
look the theme son does a lot
to see lot of the heavy weight
but but you know the name just
it doesn't matter a whole lot a
second we didn't have this we didn't
have the we started recording before we
had the final name and stricter oh
that's right we were trying to figure
out the name of the person we
didn't have the theme song yet but
we but we went back and laid
in the theme song i
think of course we did for what
i'm saying with three dm as a
title be as good if we didn't
have that great theme song now we're
getting down to ninety de gracia answer
is no no there's no way because
everyone will go who what where when
why the reporter's questions yes it's like
the movie
a titanic d without ah seven without
my heart will go on that movie
nobody would've noticed it yeah you learn
who what where when ah when y
is the five w's and the h
no i remember my how the new
mickey mouse club there was a song
who what where why when and how
day
a something something purple cow day did
you know they would fuck they would
break bad every day would be so
high every day would be a different
like mondays or this day two's do
you remember the i never walked club
you everywhere in it i kind of
did when i was a kid like
like ryan gosling
i'm talking about the one before that
way with blair from facts life oh
the one from the seventy s not
the one from the fifties well the
one from that funny yellow the one
from the fifties i used to watch
because they wish they would air it
on the wonderful world of disney or
whatever on sunday so i became fascinated
with the the mickey mouse club and
you know you got
cubby and you know we're actually sure
cubby broccoli you went on to shepherd
the james bond exact eyes and cello
was on full house as like a
crazy awesome guest spot yeah and it
just is another one of those examples
that you didn't give a shit though
writers being
old yeah rotation exactly she had a
bit of a renaissance in eighty seven
or so things like backstabbing attract to
the beach yeah where people were like
oh remember how cool and fun cello
was but i agree like kids it's
just so funny to put that on
a kid show yeah yeah although i
had big crush on an f in
cello for
just just from those she's gorgeous there's
no way around she's gorgeous just one
of those kids crushes though where it's
like oh wow she'd be a great
girl i wish you made my mommy
i wanted to be my mommy in
other ways too but then the seventy
s version came out and i had
the
the the record of it and i
would listen to it all the time
what record did you hold
most listens to this record she's still
too i mean i guess i would
have thought she was older she's only
seventy she's no with she's a real
girl pho she died in two thousand
and thirteen yeah so she would be
seventy it was aside she was like
i don't want to look i don't
want to look worse sorry that did
not make any sense budget well yeah
she of course roselle with no kilt
with m s is that right well
she died in bakersfield well that's the
worst part of her swing she died
in baker's fee you have you been
to bakersfield and have been to bakersfield
what did you do there ah that
was when andy richter and i were
shooting ah the winner's guide to winning
a series for ebay huh and at
some point we're in bakersfield interview maybe
an auctioneer
oh wow oh wait it was you
random let a little little bit on
labor there
remember there were there were there were
there were those oh if you went
to an auction and that's all they
did i would love that everybody out
without early i would didn't even get
a chance to bid
eight points or something was sold for
one million dollars oh
alright jeez
and then we had both annie and
i had that that buck owens song
in our heads the whole time we
were there oh yeah you don't know
me but you don't like me i
share a bed yeah of course we
still do
if it ain't broke don't fix it
hey
where do you say goodnight to janey
yes she goes off to her apartment
that's training i'm sorry but it's my
house
he comes over to your place you
tuck yourselves yeah that's right
i don't know nightcaps it's very so
cute laurie your nightcap sent each other
yes if you could see it it's
very cute it's nice to do that
and we're gonna do it on instagram
live and i was like this is
personal we should but i can't stop
talking about it because it's so cute
meanwhile chinese driving forty five minutes back
to her i told her to get
a place closer she wanted to bakersfield
yeah
yeah you don't know me but you
don't lie to me it's called the
streets of bakersfield
my friend was from bakersfield never been
there who's from there my friend not
my friend with the fives don't worry
as your imaginary friend i think you're
feeling froggy here right now who lives
there and commutes for like jobs what
is too far i know well he
wants to move but he has a
family
and so it's kind of like more
five family he has a family everyone
has family his family his relatives near
there too so it's like just everyone
lives over there everyone should move this
guy's kind of get his shit together
look spanish are you listening he's great
and he will can be great i
mean he has a shit together but
he wants to move i did the
i win
to bakersfield once in my life and
i did the would you kill there
what do you mean you did that
there like now where you walked in
the center of town
yeah but it's a literal soapbox we
did it as as a dinging dinging
in a presentation to like local high
schools or whatever they all filled it
like a big auditorium and we did
like to demonstrate what acting is yeah
this is if you work really hard
you can act like this when you
kill who did you kill no why
do you kill a lot of tears
rs lot of tears in that from
my story and it was a west
side story romeo and juliet mashup oh
no where i'd already put it in
and it was actually really good where
did romeo and juliet meet tonia maria
because here like we can't meet each
other this will disrupt the space time
continuum and juliet get together romeo and
maria but it was um they took
scenes from romeo and juliet and like
underscored them with west side story music
and then it kept like going back
and forth from tony and maria to
romeo
julia showing the parallels of the state
and it was very powerful show is
not a thing you're saying that
wow
would not have been as powerful if
it were kiss me k
and two gentlemen of verona as i
was facing taming of the shrew oh
that's right they're doing jimmy get the
true in the thing hey i only
saw once when i was seventeen i
want to see a high school musical
seventeen again mashup for zach franzen both
hell yeah shit how dare he zac
efron from bobby cox fox pilot when
he was fifteen wow he's dating a
way
interest now i just learned really yeah
from the musical restaurant yeah so when
the musical i worked at a restaurant
i wonder for all of the times
the waitresses have been hit on by
their customers how many times does it
work only with zac efron i bet
it works a lot really zac efron
ah you know in a place where
where like i feel like elmo i
bet you of people why do you
think the same lodi it's records are
city place what fru up in central
california if you oh really if any
like you'd make fun of lodi a
lot and then if anyone was like
i was in a bad place you
get lota you get a huge laugh
well i have no frame of reference
creedence clearwater revival much ah is it
lodi where the prison is too that's
the other part of it anyway go
ahead and say i thought you were
talking oh no we're talking about the
waitress so i mean i guess i
think i know you mean a place
where i kind of assume and lay
where you there are attractive people on
both ends of that
deal new customers and waitresses that you
get people hooking up not to get
too far into restaurant roundup but
i i think i remember a couple
of times where like a fellow waitress
would say like oh i'm going on
a date with like this customer or
whatever and it always seemed like it
was because just because you jealous well
yeah
because i i'd asked them out and
they were telling you why they were
busy i can't i'm going to do
with ah
smooch smooch nah just play along
oh well if my ring at home
but it always said it didn't sort
of always seem because we were right
next to studio city ramos district it
always same thing even though it doesn't
make any sense it always seems like
brains are so deformed from doing this
podcast yeah why did we decide to
do this show when our brains
good for you we do the show
where literally everything makes us think of
ten other things do you remember we
were warned that this would form a
brain and we still did josh told
us yeah nine out of ten doctors
told us that josh is nine out
of ten doctors
chachi is nine-tenths of a doctor
it's in the constitution
oh my god yeah debris deformity
tibbets what's the the just like a
rock looking brain what's the the any
relationship in the past where you're like
whoa i can't believe that i planned
on food i pulled that off or
like oh wow if i had the
bravery or or to talk to that
person or
i can't like if this didn't go
right i would never would have met
that person anything like that oh yeah
i mean oh yeah i think about
stuff like that ah pretty often i
mean it's like i think it's like
but remember i told you about that
dream where i went back in time
to like two thousand and six so
im back in
at times it's just sick and i
was like ok this is great because
i already know janie we're already together
yeah so i just have to from
here on um you know i can
i can make different decisions like this
like i really relate to make diversions
from but i'm not going to ruin
my relationship yes exactly but what if
you make great does
visions and it does ruin your relationship
well i'm not gonna do that but
why
i'm just not going to do oh
right but okay so wanting you to
i guess you would have you and
have a chance to course correct at
that point do you know what i
mean yeah like if you if you
made a decision that was different than
the decision made before but then it
started to negatively impact something else right
i feel like you being the all-knowing
person
would um that you have knowledge that
other people do not have you know
of the alternate universe that you've already
lived right so then you could
it's like groundhog day you could you
could take care of people you murdering
yourself when you go back in time
by the way and taking your own
place going back in time she met
about and yeah and what janey notice
no she doesn't notice it no one
here thinks you're sixteen years older than
me in bed she's like what are
you gonna wake up leave no wins
and you gonna wake him up and
take off his makeup i can't wait
to leave my apartment what have you
tried that you were like i'm gonna
go back fifteen years and see if
she notices i'm not the same
however because no so physically how would
she not no no no it's not
you don't i don't look the same
as i do now and then i
just go back to i'm saying yeah
the same as you do now you
go back murder your younger self to
take take your yoga i would not
do that would she noted i would
not do that i would define let
me say it
want to do that if my younger
self saw me now i would be
the one murdered
by yourself like i cannot allow this
i like the idea though of you
like slitting your own throat you like
that idea and like just sidling up
to cheney and going let's go home
or going fuck
with god
i like paul's grandfather i like the
idea of you splitting your own throat
sidling up to janie and saying let's
go home
it's the latest example of brain deformity
from by the podcast not good what's
happening here ah i always had visually
comfortable no they're not run out of
things talking about there
they keep sliding back on my head
and it's driving me fucking crazy new
and are really hard now i've had
these since we've been doing this since
we've been doing this
since women
i can breathe for the first why
would no but i was able to
screams for you to turn off your
music kelly clarkson yep
he turned off your great music
the tour of your bootleg of kelly
clarkson singing acapella perfectly
wait is she really there turn it
up like well that's my red hot
chili pepper story when we first moved
in here i was hanging out here
in the pool and i kept hearing
like someone playing a red hot chili
pepper song over and over and i
was like are they testing their speakers
because like parts of it would be
turned up where you
and like hear the drums super loud
and my friend my favorite by the
way parts of it would be turned
down and then um like two days
later it turns out the red hot
chili peppers were playing in like a
backyard over there
there were sound checking that day that's
very weird years that's not normal you
know it's not normal to have the
red hot chili peppers just playing hope
you went to a doctor i did
and they were like you're insane
doctor doctor i keep hearing the red
chili peppers playing in the backyard next
to me but i am the red
hot chili
and the doctor was a woman
all the heads ah oh my god
but lauren that's why that's why me
i mean you know i know that
you've had such limited romantic experience in
your life yeah i wish i could
know what it was like but um
but if i never did clipped and
everyone i met mike
that's true and that's important to me
yeah he is you know we crossed
paths like a thousand times knives without
knowing it really yes we he used
to take theater classes as a child
in my town of evenson whoa and
at the pivot theatre where he is
he friends from chicago he's from the
south oh okay
but but that see that um the
pivot theater is right next to like
places i've referenced on this show such
as al's deli where i used to
go get candy from the deli and
the guy get me shock tarts and
say i'm shocked to see sing mike
no jeremy vivid
oh um i'd love to know more
an old old comedy banking reference i
don't know it but from ten years
ago the jealous part of yeah yeah
well so mike was around at that
time and so he also went frequented
a bunch of other like locations that
i often went to as a kid
but he was four years older than
me but we probably were around the
same place at the same time he
was how old is he
know how many years here same really
same am i always say the same
yeah he's four and then we both
were on um we both did improv
at io and he was on a
high school team when i was in
college he was on team with some
high schoolers and i was friends with
some of them woe and toy
probably saw him but you know he
also had like a growth spurt like
later like i feel like i would
do like he looks like a little
kid notice department hey um that difference
is so strong when you're like call
college and i is a penis department
what you know and he was in
the penis department even during you but
ignore it's just
interesting when i'm how how i think
women think about this where i'm saying
it was so weird i would never
even look at a high school i
want to do them when i was
a freshman in college however there's full
on forty plus year old men that
we know who have not know personally
but we know of who dated women
younger than that yeah right yeah disgusting
like i when you are
looking at me
when you know you can screencap snapchat
like when a guy is fifteen that's
like really vast when i'm nineteen a
guy is fifteen that is really vase
anyway woody allen is what i'm thinking
of but right well um can i
ask you do
do you think the chicago of it
all is something that you related to
and that led to you guys liking
each other or is that sort of
like a bonus where it's like oh
cool and he also is from chicago
it's both i think when i first
met him so we had to like
have they had they sort of wanted
us to meet up as a cat
just before we started this the pilot
right and we i met up with
him at um lot wait separately you
were all supposed to meet well no
i was gonna meet a few people
but he got him i got there
first we want you to pair off
and have snarky meeting groups of twos
and i got there either to take
a month and there was gonna be
one other person joining us
i don't know why it was just
that group that time but we all
met up at different times i got
there first and he joined me and
hugh we figured out all these connections
that we were both from the same
area and they were like a lot
more other little things like that like
sort of but i really thought he
was like kind of a frat guy
or something like i i totally had
the wrong was because he's in the
bruise brothers that came later
but i totally had the wrong impression
of him and i remember it wasn't
because of how we dressed or how
he acted or what he drove i
i didn't see what we're watching that
he had no it's i guess it
was his clothes which wouldn't i don't
really remember probably like a button-down and
some jean you know probably not right
he doesn't change his style and he
weighed between then and now
oh yeah he knew taylor molino weird
or now oh but he at the
time i just don't really i just
i don't know if i even thought
about it but i was just it
was just like a vibe and i
think what he's talking about chicago it
was like oh my dad went to
the same high school that mike went
to like a lot of weird things
though was he talking about the super
bowl shuffle a lot or i just
had this feeling
like there were all those like l
a girls around me and i was
like oh he'd rather be talking to
them which is a show because it's
so not true was fine and in
retrospect now that you've spoke i'm presume
you've spoken to him about this he
talks a little bit what what
was he was would he rather have
talked to you on that night yeah
he was so excited to talk to
me because he already knew who i
was from improv stuff and so conditioning
and my babysitting career that he was
he already like was excited to like
he was like thinking we'll get along
right but i just just was you
were
only farming yeah guys wow oh this
job i much rather talk to the
model i was married but also i
was so i wasn't just trying to
he wasn't like flirting with me but
i'm saying there was just a feeling
of like you imagine oh this you
know meeting an actor i'm like oh
he's an actor you know i didn't
get his whole background immediate
yeah plus someone who moves out to
l a to be an actor who's
like good-looking like him you probably assume
that oh this dude just wants to
like rape you remind me a lot
of people like that to me like
whatever but rpi you meet a lot
of guys who are actors who are
not fun
yeah yeah so i just didn't expect
to be enjoying the time and i
figured he would rather be talking to
someone else but then he was great
and then we were joined by matt
cooke whose from the groundlings who's hilarious
and it was we all got along
so well you know what's funny is
that i liked mike more when i
first met him yeah i do miss
my slow decline but
like opposite yeah so oh so that's
interesting
wow that's crazy
did you was your first impression of
kula
um i e ll okay i met
her at a mister show taping ah
because why was she there she was
there because she there how the hell
did she get in
long story that charles from i'll try
to shorten but i had been dating
someone who was in charge of a
christmas party that my roommate and i
went to noctua plaza yes you are
dating someone who is in charge of
like put together an office kind of
dating someone who was in charge
of a christmas party so i was
invited to this christmas party um and
i brought my roommate and then we
were and and this this is the
kind of coincidence that you can't really
replicate like if it didn't happen i
don't know that i ever would have
run into her but i met i
met this christmas party that my then
girlfriend is is
is in charge of whose name was
cooled yes um and we're my roommate
and i are at the bar and
this woman just comes up to us
at the bar and starts talking to
us and is pretty much flirting i
guess but we can't tell with whom
or you know and i'm with someone
so i'm like
you know like have at it guys
yeah and so so my roommate avada
guys good luck because my voice one
which i enjoy yeah my old ball
j the christmas party organizer
so as christmas morning mrs claus okay
i knew it
that just got back together with santa
that was it wacky hipped horrors happening
luckily wobbly slug
by the way should there be exhibits
of wobbly hymns so no there should
be alright good that's why we have
to pay royalties to whoever wrote herself
yeah rodgers and hammerstein um so anyway
so so my roommate gets her number
at the end of the night talks
to her for a while a few
months
later um invites her to mister show
which was taping and she's like can
i bring my three roommates and that's
bold
for the invitation kind bring three other
people but honestly you need them at
a taping yeah boring
um so and cool op was one
of those roommates and oh i for
sure thought cool i've been to oh
so when yeah no off was one
of the roommates and so and at
that point i was no longer with
the christmas party girl and so i
met cool up at the taping and
was like oh wow she's cool ah
ah cool op ah and i figured
out her name and oh wow she's
cool up so then like she's sort
of became friends with us in a
way we went to go see blade
i remember just as friends my roommate
and cool up and ah and i
think
you know who knows and then a
year later on her birthday knows ah
a year later ah for her birthday
rather she called ah our apartment wanting
to invite us both to her birthday
party and remember back in the days
when like you were eighteen and nineteen
you would get every single friend and
every single acquaintance you go to a
restaurant and not figure out how to
split up the check and diving yes
so ah
and i ended up talking to her
for like two or three hours i
think that night on the phone and
then i asked her out on the
phone i said hey we have a
cardiologist sure i gave her before restaurant
yeah and i to deal with seals
now i remember we talked about prints
and music and because she's from minnesota
and all that goes and i asked
her out on the i didn't i
didn't i'm not i wasn't into the
whole string along of like let's go
out as friends and then try to
make a move i just like was
like hey we should go out on
a date and so we and it
worked and it worked and so we
went out on a date and
and so just right off the bat
you thought she was cute and you
were like i thought she was curious
boomers oh no but it took a
year because i still was like
the christmas party girl was kept being
on again and off again and it
was like every christmas every should suddenly
appear she suddenly was under my tree
would come down my chimney january free
december twenty six we would break up
i don't know what happened no but
but a year later i was totally
unencumbered and and asked her out yeah
and paul yes your turn well i
remembered the story of you having a
dinner party with your when you brought
janie and
everyone could tell that you yes loved
j yes yes yes well i met
janie ah through mutual friends i would
not know my wife if i had
not worked on the first ten episodes
of real time with bill maher oh
wow what did you do he was
on it i did a little segment
in the middle
of the show that no one including
myself enjoyed what i enjoyed well thank
you they they do not exist anywhere
by the way scott relaying damage again
yeah they're like scrubs there's there's i
looked for him one time i think
it was none of those scrubs i
think a lot of things should just
be scrubbed and more there's too much
shit we don't need to have a
record of every time
for one thing the only other things
pop up anytime you make a new
show delete a different show exactly just
like the marie kondo method you know
is only what sparks joy yeah no
paul used to do these really funny
like topical like he'd pick a subject
and then do a pile of can
style stand up like weekend update estate
actually kind of riff on yeah kinda
like a little package and it would
be just a little break from the
smugness and then yeah there are different
smugness whoops baba papa upa be repeated
that day
i don't know my fiddly cell phone
got connected to my computers hey guys
go here rather low
i don't know if they just automatically
do that without your provision
anyway gone up so yeah oh yeah
you dare
so i met so i became friendly
with um bill maher the well
can you magic your friend and my
best friend oh yeah you were more
than friends
he's the third of that bed
i became friends with ojai mad you
andy and bill maher hilarious should be
a podcast
please both of you put a pillow
over my face
um so i became friends with the
guy who was the there were two
segments that that ended up being dropped
from the show there was my segment
and then there was a sort of
variety segment and they would have a
stand up or musician used to come
to embark to the comedy show just
sort of scout things and remember that's
how
jerry minor and craig robinson god yes
because bill maher came to the actual
yes anbar to watch it and just
um so i became friends with the
talent booker this guy ken crosby and
we felt like we were very much
ah you know different than everybody else
that worked there yeah everywhere you know
everybody was fine really everyone was nice
but
these guys the the writing staff or
people that had worked for bill for
years like a lot of them were
politically incorrect guys and everything so we
felt like there was a unit of
these people and then there was us
um and so we became fast friends
then he introduced me to you know
other people that he knew um for
this regular sunday night gathering
at the cafe deserts which isn't there
anymore um and one night to wonderful
a regular it sounds so great i
wish i chose loved it yeah i
know a thing yes yeah it was
an early evening sunday thing we get
together like five and have a couple
of drinks and maybe if we if
we stay there long enough
if we order food you know and
it was great it was great for
a while and then it did just
stop tapping yeah um like everything like
everything like eventually we will stop happening
you know sometimes thing about that and
then cry so yeah one night joe
wanna die
so janie came in one night as
i was about getting ready to lose
you're killing me to not sing and
i was zany came inside because i
know i would you
i'm just saying i'm not doing it
i know i heard you and i
heard you i'm sorry
nah hey we agreed no apologies on
the ship that's right we will never
apologize to each other oh no we
can't we can't be here all day
they're both new so she came in
and i was struck by her instantly
so you didn't know her before from
them when i looked up natalie wood
what year is this two thousand and
three okay jamie looks so much like
natalie wood that i found engineering to
look so much like natalie and you
literally uncanny i was staring at the
picture for yeah we met we were
all on a text chain and and
that was a big topic of discussion
for one day was hey look at
how much janie looks like natalie
i don't really know what natalie wood
looked i have to heard about her
but anyways so i can imagine how
oh yeah janney walks in the room
it's like goldy shit yes she she
doesn't believe me by the way to
this day just like you know my
word yeah that you were struck by
her beauty i was struck by everything
about her like right absolutely sorry but
then when i was talking
to her it was like she is
really cool i like her you know
she's like she's like one of those
lit from within people you know yeah
how how fucking lucky to have the
person a celebrity that everyone tells you
you look like be one of the
most beautiful seasons change jesus whenever i
get hey you know that horse who
used to be the movie gus
i remember that place kicking mule yeah
you look like yeah i mean there
was a horse too yeah it was
just a threat from was before he
got into football and then he just
like lost track of all barnyard friends
sorry hanging out with dick bucky
oh you make friends with tim conway
now i see how it is i
do remember a random time we're making
cross paths so that he remembered an
i didn't remember him whoa game brought
mandy moore ryan adams and garry shandling
to ask cat you'll see book how
does he know them he was on
a pilot with mandy moore when he
first moved to la okay
that makes sense but the other two
ryan adams was married to her oh
i didn't know that garry shandling oh
yeah why he was the one who
married them now why was gary during
the film hero plants will enter you
from gary wanted to go to a
comedy show and then mike city would
take time it's not out of character
for garry shandling to do something like
that yeah mike said he would go
to
hey camhs yeah and it was just
happened i don't remember yeah um but
anyway yeah the studio got out after
and my mom said the only time
i ever met him was after that
and i was like to to my
girlfriend at the time i'm like kinda
chose me introduce me
well i got to meet them and
mike was standing with them and i
didn't remember him at all because i
meant that sure yeah who's gonna remember
mike and of course i thought he
was a slight brag this story before
i'm sure on three-time but then i
was outside and gary shilling found me
and told me a nice thing ah
i tell you in a nice garry
shandling story he has the same name
no it's decidedly different
i was nice ass
just just to be clear just zoe
oh hey nice yes
yeah so i say up there and
i just want to say nice come
like i've been watching larry sanders for
the first time oh it's so good
yeah um i was opening for collin
hey at the old largo wow speaking
of good call him hey colin hayes
colonies the greatest his audience at that
place was the worst they
did they only were there for him
the end they denial they didn't like
the whole vibe yeah everything the guy
bombed it largo so many times opening
for musical acts it was a combination
no but it was it wasn't like
with amy or michael and all that
kind of job brian yeah all those
people everyone coming to those shows there
was such a
an inherent ah fluidity between comedy and
music people that would come to those
shows would go to other largo show
yes but there were some accidents were
going to largo five nights a week
yes yeah absolutely but there was some
people some acts that only they had
their one they had their audience that
only came to see them yeah and
nothing else right so but also like
for me to have been doing
in comedy for as long as i've
been doing it at that point to
be as as just successful in general
as i have been at that point
and two
actually eat shit on that on my
way home i love this goes well
but you can do something about it
um so i i'm opening for collin
i'm doing poorly people are starting to
like heckle me oh no which is
that's insane at largo that's crazy yeah
what did did funny or the bouncer
go around and shushing them at all
no so then um they gotta protect
they own somebody started talking to me
from the crowd and then i'm talking
to this guy and then i see
a figure moving up towards the stage
i'm like what the fuck is happening
now and it's garry shandling oh no
he gets on stage to say hey
you guys
you're being you're being unfair in these
very funny and you should be more
respectful it's nice but it's also embarrassing
it was mortifying yeah yeah like somebody
fucking that was humiliating yeah and i
know he he was coming from a
good place or whatever but it's like
you don't do that that's why it's
like he's like we heard he's a
parent who
who came into scold yes you actually
very funny now please list i'd met
him briefly doing mister show promos back
in the day would you have if
i don't think he he would not
have remembered that why would he if
you had said like hey gary stay
up here with me and and and
do like you know the next five
minutes with me i would that have
been fun or you know
i mean like hey if you're up
here stick around maybe i don't know
but it was like in the entire
human sorta it's not popular it's too
much to process yeah yeah yeah so
much to process i'm just saying like
then you were a standup and you
had sort of a and you were
always very moment but you had to
prescribe to act like if it was
if it was during a live bang
bang show and that happens like
i would be like hey hang out
let's see you know it's like hey
go together and i'm gonna say see
what happened would just get worse yeah
like this feels like the pressure's ten
but then it wouldn't just like the
silence of everyone like being shushed into
like well then it's also it's like
oh we'd like to see this famous
person but all he did was come
up and tell us we should like
this guy we don't
like and leave it was it was
brewing a surreal but i swear but
i appreciate him doing that though i'm
glad he didn't tell you and i'm
not quite there buddy embarrassing yeah yoga
you should be bored i think i
went straight home like as soon as
like oh my god i would go
cry but what is colin hay in
that situation do because he likes you
he likes me but i don't i
don't remember if he was in the
room when this happened he might have
been an ambiance
that's what that's about coleen would shock
less my award your friends
yeah we're friends from largo days yeah
that's right saying yeah yeah we've there's
a great comedy bang bang episode where
jillian paul and i all sing back
up with colin hay in the video
join us for a song he had
the videographer with him at the time
and the video is up online and
it's a beautiful song and ah paul
and i sound good jillian you know
ah
oh show you know he's a great
dude check it out and i'll put
it in the notes on three m
usa h instagram dot com oh check
that out but while you're checking that
out check out these commercials because we
have to take a break movies or
commercials
welcome back everybody it's still three edam
you haven't switched podcasts mid pod who
you mustn't i hope you didn't you
mustn't do that unless you switched from
something to us yeah i'm interested oh
more tell me more
elmi marred and yeah god da ah
ah i love to do grease as
the cookie monster ah c is for
cookie you really love musicals don't you
i do i wish i could do
one really fun but i'm too old
to do the
good parts of any more i remember
when i was starting out like doing
them i stopped doing them at twenty
three right but i remember i was
always like oh i can't wait till
i get old enough to do these
good parts naive aged out of those
yeah you just missed it you missed
the sweet spot of like thirty when
you're theater factor where you're like okay
i don't look like a baby anymore
more what about a meal de becque
who amelia back from cell-specific oh yeah
no oh my god i can't wait
to get a broad whoa dream in
my heart i miss theater i'd like
to see some yeah i miss every
was the last theatre show that you
guys saw the one that we saw
together no ooh no no no no
someone was
when was what what month was that
ah it when we were on tour
in september no that was the all
day play yeah the inheritance yeah now
i see haze town
after that i believe hey these town
right was monitoring welcome to hades tau
and not like you know my life
but i yeah you saw these things
i still hate his town after that
i think and i don't know what
else but you know it's just so
fun to go watch people do something
amazingly well yeah the last play i
saw was the father starring oh alfred
molina weight but that's not not the
that's not the movie the father that
yes anthony hopkins yeah it's based on
this based on that
yeah i even heard of that till
i got the screener well i went
did anyone talking about that well i
didn't know even the screener i didn't
know it was a movie until i
got the show but he talked about
that movie like it's like it never
even know i didn't even really know
what it was until the academy awards
were very interesting i didn't think it
was a great play while i'm curious
film and a have a few i
want to auto launch minori minori rallied
i love munari i like to watch
it but i'm like manila i always
think of when i'm kind of tired
and i'm like i want to be
able to just embrace my song called
night it's so no it's great you'll
like it it's very funny oh no
i mean i'm i'm excited to watch
i'm saying i i think of it
when i'm tire
and then i'm like yeah you'll like
it you'll like to know it'll wake
you up please yeah
let me slap you right before no
things
hedge funds are making my ears her
i'm sorry kramer oh no minorities i
actually like menara better
i like minori better than nomad land
and no midlands really good but i
don't watch any like minori so much
hello and remind you all i only
watch horrible things
true true to character down every broadway
show i've gone to but i can't
find the notes write down every show
yeah this got this is something you
do yes i do it ie look
at versailles law he's looking for somebody
like osama rider yeah so you're saying
about yes it was accorded an epoch
sort of add to cart i'm the
guest and we one thing i didn't
bring out to cool up is that
if people aren't letting people like threesome
and they're not listening to add to
cart they're missing out on some good
scott gossip that's how i i got
cos i've had to ask her to
curtail that okay thank you
drive it i think it's hilarious well
she got she got mad at me
over an episode two weeks ago when
she brought that up to complaining about
her interrupting but i say to jack
him up because i do it all
the time i brought it up no
she heard it okay i heard about
it
the one episode she ever listened to
by the way oh well cause i'm
sure someone told her she's gonna let
you know what janie does is she
joking no kind of fantastic did shoot
she stopped saying dude no do i
say that a lot of course anytime
i sing janey she looks oh you
look at paul like dude
so i'm gonna say so shut this
motherfucker huh
i dare you to try dare you
she sees every um ah not every
drama but every everything that has any
kind of um ah mysterious element to
it where there's you know like if
it's if it's a crime thing a
mystery something like that she sees mr
foot not just that she sees it
as a challenge
to guess what is going oh yeah
oh and constantly offer those guesses yeah
yes ev running guesses and then she
has to update like okay he didn't
die so this is what i think
is right yeah see like us tells
me what he thinks is gonna happen
not necessarily a mystery but like just
a show you're like oh they're gonna
do this and like
just based on the writing yes i'm
like oh my god i did not
think of that and now i know
and then it does happen then i'm
like yeah great guy because tv i
really try not to assume i know
what's gonna happen even from a writing
standpoint of like just from paying more
attention or being in things you start
to understand it more and whatever
i don't want to do that because
i like to just watch you like
to be right in it well sometimes
though like you know because cool up
and i both write stuff sometimes it's
nice to go like oh by the
way this is what we were talking
about earlier this is the right to
exist good way to learn stuff but
then i and i get why it's
fun but then makes it was like
what's wrong with like he thinks so
spoil my obsession with spoilers is a
problem because he thinks that it should
just be like if you already know
then you can watch for how they
got there though and then i'm like
yeah but i want why would you
watch anything then i i he thinks
it's fun he he appreciates the journey
i like you like you're like i
like the
journey and the destination can i have
both i want to not have any
clue where anything is going on my
tend to not be very good at
predicting one of the first movies that
i saw with coop was um obviously
blade we talked about that but obviously
six cents which by the way these
two movie choices even though she said
she was scared itself you can't blame
me for thinking that she's fine with
scare
the stuff when those are two of
the first movies that we see together
cool point um so i held onto
that forever when i wouldn't have gotten
to the mexican devil mask twenty years
later and you say you saw six
cents
oh well let's extend but i guess
i guess she told me later she's
terrified out of her mind during sixth
sense but wanted to go because i
wanted to go into skid scares it's
very scary but sir at a certain
point i figured out the big twist
and would you lean over and say
oh no i went oh and she
looked at me like you know tell
me where thing
i was like oh no i'll tell
you afterwards because that's polite yes
no he doesn't lean over and tell
me at a movie like this catalina
but he's already over on me because
we want movies i'm happy
it's more like well more like it's
more things that i i'm not even
that invested in yeah in his perspective
that he'll just be like calling something
out and then i'm like oh man
and he's like what do you care
and i'm like i guess i don't
but i guess i do i don't
know you guys need to watch television
separately no
wow i hate when you apes ah
but you love to watch him go
oh and those basketball shorts huh
with a jock body
why two basketball shorts gets so long
used to be sees me so years
it seemed but seems like it'd be
better for movement wouldn't we love shard
show and i wish they were still
super short it's fun to watch them
in short i think it's a good
look i think it is good looks
they look like fucking huh yeah but
okay okay well they are really good
athletes if you are that good of
an ass
elite in your legs it looks awesome
like that would you i can only
imagine people are like a two why
are you showing off ninety percent of
my leg can i have some fuckin
daddy i was also sort if you
had to buy like that huh you
wanna show it off it was the
style at the time and now they're
wearing board shorts i know i wonder
what it'll be next mid i hope
it's like
i get even shorter i think they
should get even longer like kevin smith
it's a shorts to come up to
me it's so funny how his style
has been stayed exactly the same while
he has shrunk about fifty percent yeah
well he had all those custom things
made is that what it is although
those hockey jerseys i think they're all
custom and then the idea of them
taking them i don't know i don't
think so sure
oversized kevin be the fourth person on
ford okay that's it that's so finally
found the one person that makes sense
not very ah sorry mary you're no
kevin smith
no um should we do an episode
where we have one more person or
do the fabled episode where our three
spouses that we should do national media
loves finally listen to an episode of
airline did not like what you heard
it's like do you always play games
i was like this is the first
one you've ever heard they're called features
literally we do it every time huh
um didn't know but do we do
that episode where we're over their shoulders
going you can do it honey come
on do we go over or do
we just walk away and let them
do walk away no week we said
here and we go shut up don't
say that wrong not true
cutting that cutting that are there's two
sides to that story
what's the gas that you've heard about
me on descartes oh yeah i why
already brought up the one about your
cd collecting and so it made the
reason i even thought of it because
you were just mentioning that you have
a log of the shows you've been
to and that's rather like you have
a you have a desire to collect
log store well i'll tell you why
i stay
i'm doing the broadway thing and that
was recently because i was trying to
think of a show that i had
seen and i was saying like oh
it's like this show that i saw
but i can't remember anything about it
and so i was like it's this
thing i think it's based on like
it's an updated raisin in the sun
or something like i was like what
is ate a plum in the sun
yeah
so in the snow so it's
and i couldn't you guys think raisins
go wow i thought no it would
be a different this would be hid
that's an upgrade bigger wow way plums
turn into what plums turn into dates
dates and grocery grapes turn into ray's
yeah i'm starting two dates yeah i
think so no um um yeah what
do what do
runes are for prunes that's maybe prelims
qualms problems or rune slums your brand
dates or just dates there never any
i thought they were their own states
or just dates yeah they just come
out like that yeah a bacon wrapped
date is so fucking saw so oh
my god i want anytime i would
it right on a platter yeah
fifty i tell yourself that you go
to the timoshenko you get the devils
on horseback what's that's bacon wrapped dates
sort a little like being blurry cheese
in there but nah i don't think
well i think it's queen we gotta
go we have to go back to
the tamu chancellor happened this year it
might happen this year they will do
it this year anyway i was gonna
say i was just trying to think
of this show jan's
i had to then i remembered what
theater it was i was so i
instead looked up the theater on wikipedia
and all of it's notable productions until
i finally found it i was like
you know what i like with the
inheritance the fact that you guys could
remember the title and i couldn't ah
that would drive me crazy so instead
i just have a list of like
i really loved that show every every
the ones that have been shut down
like unceremoniously well it it was up
for tony's yeah it didn't have the
long run that it should have so
that's weird i'm glad we get to
see it i guess i don't know
how long run you can do of
a show that that that is that
long oh really you gotta think you
can do it you know for i
mean standard broadway contracts i think are
thirteen
and that that everything is can you
imagine saying it because it's always a
shower i mean they don't do they
don't do it all day every time
thank you so sometimes they split it
up yes so sometimes sometimes they'll only
do like the a part that row
right and then they'll come back the
next night and do the b part
or the the you know like sometimes
they mix em up different order
we saw it on a weekend i
think where there's a matinee so we
get to see both parts on the
same y'all dinner between with dinner said
saris oh what a broady guys we
have to go back to new york
we do think of everything hey also
let me think of other things she's
talked about at yale you probably heard
it although
i mean like been told you've lived
it no one ever hits me up
to say like oh cool i'm i
like being horny for you
she's she's more like cool ah gotcha
i i'm i'm putting it into this
ah i just talked about buying you
underwear buying herself matching know yeah yeah
yeah that was nice and and on
a day where we suddenly realised we're
wearing the matching ones that's a very
special day
to me undies because they make they
make a matching sets for yeah viewing
your partner if you're out there listening
can they sponsor us yes me on
these please sponsor us please sponsor i'll
do the ads i want underwear for
free
oh man the ultimate indignity paying for
underwear it's it's mortify and it's just
saying that we only the government should
pay for to the pharmacy they have
in that glass case the government should
give you tampons and underwear for free
they actually should get less they want
to ship one thing that was not
one is ridiculous that that's not it's
well it's also crazy how expensive they
are yes not only should they be
free if they're not only free it
should cost no more than toilet paper
emily yeah it's i mean it's the
woman tax yeah it's fucked up yeah
really is anisha there's well it's just
that i like salon type places
okay should be free they have the
no there's no woman tax or whatever
like there's like a sticker in the
window what's that tickers i don't know
enough about it to really speak on
this but i think that there's when
we talk about nfc non fungible token
i just learned about
so stupid yeah by digital art well
okay let me liken it to this
this is what i thought bitcoin was
well it's it's related to be going
where it's ah the reason they're bad
for the environment is that these computers
here it was bad for the environment
yes and if teas are bad for
the environment and the reason is is
because shane order to
authenticate them computer is cut down forty
trees
to make computers know these computers have
to constantly be solving these complex equations
which takes up so much processing power
that takes up so much energy the
energy to like make one bitcoin can
can ah power like a small town
for five years or something like this
yeah so it's ridiculous so anyways the
whole stupid but the end of teas
are like basically it's a way the
good part about it is is a
way for digital artists with no dumb
people
who's willing to pay for anything no
it's it allows like like the mona
lisa okay a print holding but i'm
likening it to a print the mona
lisa print the mona know it but
here's here's what i'm trying to say
the mona lisa the original is where
it is everyone knows that the louvre
but you can have i was pretending
to know
you can hire is that everyone knows
good gray i love that cover but
you can have a print of it
yeah and invite people over to your
house and no one thinks that you
have the real mona lisa and you're
very cool like this dude's got the
real mona lisa very cool but that's
what's cool but that's what nfs are
to digital art is you
yes anyone could make a a gif
or a or a you know jpeg
of someone's digital art and pass it
around the the owner or sometimes owners
because they split it up amongst people
of this digital art they're the ones
they're the ones who have the original
and they're the owners you know so
it's like me saying like oh i
own the mona lisa i'm a fucking
rich
weirdo you know i mean that's what
it's good for yeah because digital artists
their work is devalued um because anybody
can just anyone can just print up
a print go i own this thing
so but this is like a a
a physical print that you would hang
on the wall no it is just
exist on computer just can exist on
a computer you could do whatever you
want with it but you
are these certificate owner it's like having
it's very weird to put that on
your phone yeah it's out of money
it's having a certificate of authenticity for
anything that anyway i'm not i think
digital art is amazing but i think
that this is it by by just
by the fact that it moves but
they're trying to say that right they're
kind of going i'm not going
to sell this they're trying to say
that in the future we're all going
to have these like digital wallets on
our phone that anyone can check out
at any time in it's like when
you play a video game and you
buy an outfit for it so so
not fights pride in your ranking you're
like i want my wall i'm not
buying an outfit for some digital painting
to buy one though you would deny
miss the point you would you go
to saks fifth avenue and buying outfit
if you are so mean of course
i would they would it matched the
painting well i would hope so well
then you understand what i'm talking about
if sachs has retained any shred of
it's former equality lauren you are slouching
down hearing me
explain an f t's much like you're
talking about realities hey guy i'm i'm
interested in knowing about it i'm just
getting tired i'm just trying to explain
z but hey i think it's great
right you don't have to apologize but
peelers austin people are selling things like
hey i'm i'm selling you remember when
i was in your town and i
stage dived a band ice i did
a
stage dive event ah you know into
the audience you are the owner of
that stage dive yeah no i mean
i guess i guess the thing that's
so peter lerner is doing tweets and
all this because it feels like to
say
i own this it's it's own brand
what it feels like to me is
like having a rolex that you keep
in a safety deposit box you never
wear exactly or it's like having wash
and figures had never take out of
the box like it feels even that
makes more sense because you like having
a hundred dollars right in your wallet
paul and pies huh
pulse not getting like having breakfast lunch
and dinner every day
simultaneous things like the bare minimum it's
like having a roof oh my
i want a non fungible token but
i'm santa christmas i'm saying we need
to start selling three men of t's
oh now i'm amara oh yeah
yeah so oh jimmy won't you queer
be one to me lassie so long
okay with clippy don't call me quit
bc so wow wow would be sick
a break will be ribbit
oh guess what y'all rule three your
chao wow gee wow use your indoor
three would you do it here are
the bar you just read your country
anyone not doing creatures
you medially sin back to the state
lab or woman from i think ukraine
has to live in the ah in
new orleans with this idiot on ninety
day fiance
so it's reality god yeah yeah let's
just a quick reality recap we have
a three-tier for you this is called
drunken sailor it was submitted by nicole
kez de this is to the tune
of the sea shanty drunken sailor she
sea shanties had a big resurgence during
gaurantee i did not watch a single
video
that i i kind of did too
not out of any changes no i
really just saw i don't want to
know i just couldn't like the ones
they seem to aquaman snyder cut sea
shanties became a thing on tiktok with
young people yeah honestly it was like
i do not need more information i
don't understand what that means i can't
understand what that could possibly be and
i do
don't want to know i never clicked
to find out if they they were
actual sea shanties or they were making
shit up but you know like right
now i'm sort of curious but about
seaward chances
oh my god
alright so to the tune of the
sea shanty drunken sailor and we're gonna
play that for you right now yeah
let's play the drunken sailor song hopefully
there's not an ad beforehand nope there
is herbie
i mean really aiding yeah we went
to this age we finally went into
a pool he'd never seen water before
even drinking it
he kept drinking the pool water we
kept telling him to stop and he
will listen
what will they do and they don't
even say or do with the drunken
sailor
in the barn and way up she
rises way hay up she rises way
hay up she rises are hard and
save his belly with a rusty razor
shave his belly with a rusty razor
lie in the morning way hay up
she rises way hay and up she
rises way hay up she rises to
a palate cleanser okay we'll go along
totally sober put them in a long
motility sober put them in along motility
sober lie in the bar cut cut
cut copy right away i came up
she rises way hay oh my god
i'm so embarrassed
great scene in any comedy when the
sound drops out somebody saying something really
loud yeah love it so stressful so
that is the song and ah the
game is so stressful everyone to
you just said learn like equates things
distressful
so stress
ah ah you could you put seventeen
please so stressful
um so the game is everyone takes
turns inserting what you would do with
the drunken sailor examples from the song
as we heard shave his belly with
a rusty razor from the longboat till
he's so but that's ne as nasty
the game is a similar style to
our old favourite hey fred schneider he
might make an appearance in this one
well for the groups
sings the song together and repeats the
chorus after someone comes up with their
free okay let's do it yes let's
do it let's do all your starting
okay yeah i'm not gonna be good
yeah so we'll do what i do
on drunken sailor into way way up
here and then the game is a
vote and the way hay up she
rises yes early in the morning okay
five six
six seven eight one d d singular
sensation you do suck at this data
ok ready one two three what do
you do with a drunken sailor what
do you do with a drunken sailor
what do you do with a drunken
sailor early in the morning way up
she rises way hay up she rises
way hay up she rises early in
the morning scott oh i thought you
said you retard
you know i started this on what
we said that your eyes i thought
literally you meant start the song oh
and then you i didn't realize you
had the power just say someone was
gonna die neither until the moment when
i realised i don't have anything
oh i understand yeah oh my my
impression of this which is that it
can be anything and i can see
okay great lauren you stay ready are
you gonna do go into ya what
do you do when the drunken sailor
what do you do with a drunken
sailor what do you do with a
drunken sailor early in the morning way
hey up she rises way up
rises way up she rises early in
the morning put his glasses in a
washing machine but it's still a machine
but his glasses in a washing machine
or lie in the morning way she
rises way hay up she rises way
hay up she rises early in the
morning come on the head didn't put
him in
meet trunk and maybe try kucoin and
bottom guy in the morning way hey
up she rises way hay up she
rises way hay up she rises early
in amari put his hand in a
pan of warm water put his hand
and a padawan wow
handed a better one water early in
the morning way hay up she rises
way hay up she rises way up
she rises early in the morning but
joint in the middle of his buttcrack
join the little fucker lie in the
morning way up to rises way hay
up she rises way hay up she
rises early in the morning pour diarrhea
all over his head for diarrhea all
over
rely on the morning hay up she
rises way hay up she rises way
hay up she rises or lie in
a bar with an outcast because you
disgusted with the podcast because you just
gotta take the bad guys and cause
you to lie in the morning way
up she rises
his way up she rises way hay
up she rises are lie in mornay
and the cass city printing forward embrace
a farm with the podcast gets you
ready to see foreigner lie in the
morning way hey up she rises way
hay up she rises way hay up
she rises early enough
morning quit the podcast and jump into
full time day job
jump in the pool or lie in
boarding way rises way hay up she
rises way of sheer
and the ma man i thought he
was gonna tell was i really thought
he was gonna go in to what
the i really that was that's so
excited that was a bait and switch
i threw something else in the pool
for the sound effect damn it it
was so i'm wearing clothes i can
get is gonna be the most funniest
thing you ever did i can't get
my t-shirt
and and chinos with my crush don't
give me those wow kind of kicked
me on these wet so that was
fun ah that was fun it was
fun thank you all for listening you
offer love and freedom usa on twitter
and instagram yes and three of them
giblets go by and three don't geocache
hopefully last
i really thought he was gonna jump
in i knew who that was so
funny and the urgency of someone who
is going to jump in my crux
on oh oh my god alright bye
guy
ugh