right
get my early freedom
no more tiny three dollars you got
to hang out now
oh i love my new system ah
yeah let's do it next week three
three three three three three so much
gallons how many games can you say
in ten seconds three hundred thirty three
years okay
in my tiny oh they have to
be distinct okay timeless and they say
three to one
okay right right yes i'll carry two
one go freedom freedom freedom freedom freedom
freedom freedom freedom freedom freedom freedom freedom
freedom freedom freedom freedom time
that was like i lost count oh
my guy like oh i think that
was almost forty three times whoa yeah
i have to go now i rule
well i didn't expect him to get
so high i was just telling my
fingers hey you knew it timer you
a timer you'd hey stop color yeah
wow okay ready ten seconds okay ready
and three
three two one go three m three
mtm three i'm three and i'm twenty
three and i'm turning thirty i'm doing
thirty three i'm three and three three
and three and date of death date
and third and three dated three i'm
thirty three and i'm thirty two and
term three and i'm thirty i'm thirty
three and thirty three
twenty three what that was less than
you yeah
there's no way i was pretty slow
so playback no neutral thorny palace tearing
miles turn right oh i'll do it
okay i was wrong too one forgot
through either
students are thirty thirty thirty thirty thirty
thirty thirty thirty thirty thirty thirty thousand
them nineteen hundred thirty four good season
and that's really one i'll get to
go through your you have to say
remember that no no when you're playing
oh football so it's like yeah or
a hide and seek or something like
that football is why
and it's like it's before you can
rush the passer essentially one alligator two
all your three olga
and people would like try to cut
corners when i go through with one
two three yeah we we were mississippi
gang my son or so he said
one week we were west of the
mississippi so we
ou say alligator we were east of
the rockies yeah yeah what happens in
between the mississippi and the rockies
i don't know but i do know
this out of the wilderness north of
the border comes a bear to america
made to order and every beer man
with mood said it is hey dad
is going to be a mossad man
for la live a moosehead man for
life
labatt blue
what beers and lowering that of course
is moosehead and whose head is a
beer moosehead is it because i was
ahead oh yeah yeah moosehead was ahead
see it when you've heard of moosehead
you go oh ahead
well why don't most just say head
why don't they just say that what's
stopping them like buddy like they can
say one word it would be head
oh i want to share the story
with you tommy i love shakes before
this was the first that's literally how
that's our catchphrase for the show i
know
why anyone who says yeah
so we just tell stories we just
don't
exactly i need to say the catchphrase
everyone knows it when moot when moody
zirkle always say that i do that
or sometimes you just look sometimes you
would go who did that yeah mm
wow
so sometimes rally here she's fully aware
that he did it people want to
just say look he just doesn't look
yeah um when mou said was a
new beer like a new import to
america you've never told this
he might have that might have been
like the prologue do a story we've
heard a million times somebody brio is
a where someone's that i have parties
okay somebody brought a case of it
to my cousin's house aka cases by
the way twenty four oh i could
drink a case although they've started ooze
you're saying i could drink a case
of woe come back from all know
i'd still be well raw what about
joni mitchell people who come in but
about the big cases that are like
thirty haven't haven't they started making those
so much bigger than twenty four j
k so so so it was like
a it's like a fourth of july
or yeah my family used to have
have like cookouts and so are invited
to the cookout wow well yeah when
you throw it you're invited they had
a a good that's so true they
had the best ah they had a
better porch for it so that's where
like the picnic table would be and
so we'd hang over there and then
in the in the evening people ended
up inside and somebody
a case of moosehead to this gathering
and so when they
when new people would come in to
the room
i don't remember how this started but
they would ask the new person hey
do you want a beer and the
person would say yes and they'd say
do you want like a schlitz or
miller highlife or a musette and the
person said mou said
they would sing the entire song and
then the more people was like that
that game sardines sardines where then that
person would now be part of the
course of prime so that's fun it
was fucking hilarious or whatever not funny
it was you know where every time
it was jimmy paredes podcast yeah that's
so do the outside
i heard he was the first person
i could do this you know everybody
everybody that goes
wow you're younger
um bt dubs icing someone with a
smirnoff ice e g jobs right what
do you remember how i said i
thought it was happening he doesn't five
idea but guess what it was doing
okay because people i'm seeing and recently
there wasn't lucas scott googled it and
it was like two thousand and eight
but i was leaving college at that
time
yeah and in my memory people were
icing and college and i'm seeing means
or you know what a lot people
are doing right now there are these
a lot of women i'm seeing who
are who are technically people yeah people
and people say that and i believe
him can they give birth is that
what you're saying i just don't know
but i believe what they do
um okay so that was my trp
impression that was just free falling away
noch i was doing it i didn't
even try i was try did trump
come out as a trans ally
ah saudi revolutionary oh my god someone
should do a trump impression where he
says all liberal thing yeah um it's
not going to be me um the
you don't a judge judge yeah yeah
yeah trim judge shrimp judge yeah sure
judge has to do it um but
what i was gonna say was something
bice oh no i'm seeing
ah sort of a comedy like like
knish in instagram of like women my
age going like here's what i like
me getting ready for the for the
club and doesn't five and they have
all the clothes that exact it's like
i don't know if it's it's it
is comedy i don't know if they're
comedians or if they're just anything on
instagram is supposed to become
yeah i don't know i don't know
how you would categorize what it is
but they're doing these sort of nostalgia
videos where they put on like the
exact clothes you're trying a little bit
of this it's kind of fun like
i will go in a little wormholes
with them because i'm like i had
all the fucking clothes that they have
it's like very specific a brown shrug
with glitter over a tank top three
layers of tank
tops over like y low rise clans
i don't have them now but i
had them yeah i was addressed like
why did they have the old clothes
that's what i wonder how how and
why do they have all the old
clothes one person who it's clear that
her mom saved everything so she just
has all of the stuff it would
be sad if they're buying clothes just
to make a video but
but i don't think that's i think
something that people do a lot i
think that's joyful i think i think
it's sad if you buy clothes just
to wear them you know it sat
close you know etc a billion
anyway it was happy nude beach do
you think you'd be interested in what
the happiest place on earth do you
think he'd be interested in a video
of somebody getting ready for their day
in the exact way you did when
you were they know
ah you know what i mean getting
drunk before going out to get drunk
her you know what i've noticed is
that there's a new thing where people
are like trying on clothes but they
start in their underwear and just feels
like this yeah just to show just
because they want to be in their
underwear people are
really interesting aren't they and because it's
a really long time depend on the
green not that one not that one
but it's very weird very eyes over
in front of the camera the very
end of the video they put on
a shoe
don't you think you'd start with the
dress here's what i don't need yeah
a video of anyone getting ready i
really don't need it yeah i really
don't like i wanna see people coming
back is it am how was it
tell me what has owned me what
happened i mean while you undress i
found the dead yeah we also want
to see yes i would like to
see that
look look if you're gonna come back
from grief please make a video i
feel like new one time trend i
think i understand it more when it's
someone showing how to do your hair
like this or how to do but
i don't understand it's just like here's
what i wore maybe like a tank
wanting to show their butts but they
but it like is more classy yeah
it is like an inuit intimacy all
dull
it up yeah but it's like yo
y'all showed your butt anytime a butt
is being shown is because people made
the video because i want to show
them but there's no question i also
don't like what are these videos calling
i don't like the captioning but ca
to anyone putting a caption for when
they just posting swimsuit picture yeah either
funny or like inspirational or like thinking
about pizza you know it's just like
no no just just right this is
my butt yeah yeah that's all we
wanna know in passion i'm not sure
if it is here but i think
i need to know i think
caption would also be do i make
you horny baby yeah yes yeah it
would be fun yeah and then it's
like oh yeah i sometimes like like
i would like someone to put a
caption of themselves and it's like super
sex and like my brothers on this
site too it's like your brothers looking
at this picture of you and your
fucking yeah china suit genus yeah so
she's
isn't it odd took your family scrolls
and also sees yeah why did i
find that complicated i it's for me
with friends yeah right we know people
know when i say yes or whatever
like oh well hello well oh and
i call them up and i say
well hello
i don't know if you realize oh
i saw your picture i always want
to and i wanted to say i
like it when i didn't think a
heartwood suffices i know you so i
know i say i really liked that
sexy picture you posted i know you
you probably can't pick up right now
you might be worked but i just
want to say i saw that pic
sure i really like to
i thought i thought you looked amazing
i just wanted to say hey it's
paul of topics i looked amazing your
bikini
amazing and i think i read some
article where they vets like you did
i think i did i am not
sure though nowhere they caught up with
a guy like they figured out who
a guy was who was constantly posting
on women's profiles like hey show me
your bud or whatever like that they
like figured out who he was and
went to his work or something i
i
show them their books you want to
see this would just backfire he likes
it it's literally bathtime i do i
sometimes do have a conundrum with someone
that i don't know that well but
i'm friendly with aha when they post
like a hot picture it's like do
i like this example
i'll see people liking stuff ago oh
okay lol nasty yeah yeah a little
nasty it does feel that way it
feels like if i like this i'm
sending some kind of message of yeah
send more it's send more nudes it's
weird because it is just supportive like
you know sorry i mispronounced foods i
meant to say sad news
but what i wrote edu dsu you
understood that i meant to write what
would but then you send me a
box full of nugs and i don't
want to deal with all these kitty
detox they're nuts they're fake peanuts yeah
i knew ds
this is big oddballs your dog gets
castrated you know they have nuts nuts
yeah sure we all know they need
big balls i don't know we'll give
him fake balls yeah you can buy
fake their calls new implants you can
buy for your dog that's yeah yeah
why why do they call noodles it's
pretty great because
new testicles exactly when the new testament
but there any u t i c
l e s so it's like part
neuter part testicles dad i'm being whipped
wow catwoman caterwaul will not i did
a video where she whipped off for
americans in a row and everybody clapped
and cheered do you think that was
pretty cool what is this recall what
does that for is it just the
feeling that for who is she married
when she was catwoman batman no in
real life i know are you talking
about we know michelle pfeiffer david e
kelley yes i i recently learned that
i was listening to cameron manheim read
it longhand on legal pad yeah i
did maybe that's why we that's how
you would write to every to all
my information i get it now that
you're explaining it magic legal pad and
writing appears on it every
i wanna know more about that what
does that mean he writes out scripts
in longhand on a legal pad oh
okay i thought he said that somebody's
triggered it okay to transcribe it like
reads it aloud and then someone else
has to type it or does someone
look at the page and type while
they're looking at the page good question
cameron manheim was on rosie o'donnell's podcast
and she had a great story about
being cast real
really you're done a lot of podcast
i listen to it almost weekly and
then has really been on cameron's podcast
yet this cameron well i don't think
she does but she loves games learn
that but she would had a great
stir up being cast on um whatever
the show with david was ostensibly legal
bobby i'm not going to tell it
all here
i really don't wanna hear it and
you're interested in anything good episode he
came to the networks like i have
a new show it's called barely legal
these people are almost lawyers they just
graduated must be called barely legal what
i thought was interesting he's married to
michelle pfeiffer i'm like whoa power couple
rolling yeah oh oh by the way
i was walking the other day speaking
podcast people having podcasts which we were
ever if you're talking about anyone you're
speaking about people having podcasts i just
thought
i just got into the
rice
i just got into the doctor and
they did the tiny taps on my
eye what the fuck are you talking
about you know like that does the
oh like oh my test it's what
does it test the eye strength or
something like them to just tiny taps
i think we've been over this and
we know what the blogger talking know
it it you can't it's they're imperceptible
oh yeah other than a vague that
no no
it's a little thing they put by
your eye and goes yeah yeah and
it's like uniquely on a new test
because they actually got rid of the
glaucoma tests okay we're used to look
at us you know everyone knows half
of i yeah how far are people
buying your air right that's the guy
i told you anyway so i got
the tiny taps i was walking to
and
are you warning so horny please just
cut to the already park and i
like the picture so i was walking
into the supermarket to grab a cup
that's not normal for you it was
right next to the ida okay and
i was behind these two women and
they were walking dogs and they were
like and one was like oh by
the way i was wondering if we
should do a podcast together
whoa you should turn running on na
i was like oh get out of
my space and other one was like
yeah sure yeah you gotta be a
little more excited and i know of
voice than that no premise by the
way they never talked about the poker
hey it was supposed to do both
walk dogs oh there is no it
was not like
the walkout supermarket that's our podcast it
was not a podcast about like hey
i was thinking we should do a
podcast about this or whatever it was
just purely like we need to have
a podcast it was like a business
decision yeah and she was like because
i was thinking about someone that i
might want to be in business with
for years and years and and you
came to mind it was like i'm
sorry for the wrong reasons people go
to these
weird workshops and they're told to do
things and then they end up having
business minded goals with their friends groin
set but listen you're telling me you
know i thought about people you've never
thought like i wish i like who
can i go into business with for
years and years years because like what
i i think like when i meet
someone yeah so like i kind of
do this thing like my brain first
goes like are they my friend
i go numerous top setup yeah can
you go into business like years or
years in your yeah and then i
really think about that and sometimes it's
the essences to know but even that
will determine whether i get the coffee
i remember that was when i when
janey were getting serious about each other
well during yeah starting with the podcast
we've been married for ten years yeah
when you guys see if hawkins is
when you kind of like like we're
busy now huh yeah yeah get it
now yeah so i went out here's
another story and these are slight stories
i'm hoping they are true
maybelline's to all now i have to
begin here's another channel so like we're
already talking from that why no we
don't need another one i can't say
this is not a smother one no
see this is not a story it
doesn't even qualify as a story so
i don't write wow
don't wanna say it and then you
guys go like why did you bother
with but then you actually did start
off by saying here's a story yeah
this is the greatest story oh so
i go to albertsons and i'm i'm
behind this this woman who honestly thinks
the grocery store honestly is probably somebody's
house probably my age it seems harder
some ways is wearing like really shy
short shorts and dark dark sunglasses and
seems like really harder machine i think
even from from everybody loves me was
the alberts and feels ray issue you
have less time than everyone issues this
i had to take a civil water
deal raymond um she was the spokesperson
for hours
for a bit um so so she
lingers out there it's kind of a
member
enjoying overseas because of me for i
became your sword because you saw me
in the commercial isn't that so
so i'm behind this woman in line
and there's someone in front of her
no this one is wrecked to shit
so that's how we know it's time
yeah it's yeah exactly he's three people
so she makes room for me on
the conveyor are nice i put my
stuff down i asked why was she
moved up or her her stuff and
like she had any layers for adults
the only way that i could describe
it as like adult lunchables okay it
was like pre-packaged meals don't tribbles
i've done chips because the lunchables is
for clearly for kids and then there's
done triples because adults adults hardly ever
have one right we skip because look
we're trying to save calories come back
where we can't we do breakfast we
do dinner we might have a little
bit of protein in the middle what
does that launch bay nice t-bones just
a nice big
a sick dancer tableside if we're lucky
if you got time to like jay
got time to punch if i got
talking about the money i got time
to get the state dire
so she do not my favorite work
loose gnostic diane so she loses love
okay go ahead she looks at what
i put down and one of the
things i put down are these salad
kits right there like basically pre-packaged salad
that has the dressing and the stuff
in em right it was like lego
yeah cum yeah like glue wood sticks
with what sticks
two things with sticks and woods ticks
what was the word i'm yes it's
one of the tongue depressor was that
popsicle sticks popsicle sticks you know tongue
depressor before popsicles i'm more a doctor
than a kid
and that about you
florae more of a doctor than a
kid if applications spectrums your kids in
a diagram year because you could never
be a doctor yeah i'm like a
doctor might say you're more doctor than
kid if i if i had applied
myself i could be a doctor sure
if i if i'd done it and
went through medical school and like been
smart and although we're not talking to
you here read your
kipling we're talking about what did happen
okay today was yeah if you good
to go to medical school and you'd
be good at it and it'd be
it'd be quick and easy i mean
how quick it'd be done in like
an hour it would cost nine hundred
dollars and you can do it and
yeah yeah i'll do yeah and then
you'd be good as a doctor the
rest of your life and you'd like
it and you'd be happy would like
to learn basic
surgery medicine well you know how like
anytime you're watching one of the like
the last of us or something oh
yeah everyone's like sewing people up but
they don't know how to do that
in real life yeah okay so she
looks at she looks at the salad
kits and she goes are those good
and we're having a conversation yeah so
it's turned into a conversation and i
say look look chaotic neutral mayor
gotcha and so i very friendly i
say oh yeah there
pretty good day she goes so i
would just put my own dressing on
it i go oh no they have
dressing in the pack i tend to
add chicken to my you know blah
blah blah and this was an albertsons
brand product or is the ceo every
every supermarket okay karen simpler ever these
types of macarons um so we have
wondering if she was kinda like i've
never seen that brand or like
oh shit remember sally chance okay you
simply understand yourself i need simply understand
yourself she's so this oh well sadly
was surprising for the standing what i
said so they're dressing yeah good plan
king
so we have a fairly long conversation
about the salad kits where and she
is hell she's zula made way for
me and and and acknowledged i'm behind
her so the the woman in front
of me finally gets her not the
woman in front of the woman in
front of her finally gets her stuff
packaged so confused
and she was patricia he i think
sample or whatever the teller was patricia
heaton it was miles teller okay patricia
heaton was miles teller is a teller
where you just need to call them
tell her you love her yeah that
was two miles so there we go
tell her about over
ah okay so then the woman in
front of her like pais aha and
zen that's important and then she looks
at me and she looks at me
and she goes ah are you gonna
pay why and i go i'm sorry
she goes oh
wait is it my turn to pay
and i go how do you mean
she goes will you you can't take
your food without paying and i say
like she goes aren't you don't you
need to pay for your food and
i go oh no i'm behind you
and you were clearly standing behind her
and she goes and but this is
the reason i tell the story she
goes
ah here we go ah and i
i took a demand she gets into
these situations a lot i took it
to mean like here it comes here
comes alzheimer's you know like or oh
here here comes like my another example
of me losing my mind i felt
bad whoa
i took it a different way you
thought it was like here we go
we're gonna throw another person who won't
pay for my food am i paying
this time as what you said micah
was the aren't you supposed to pay
my forward to the tim robertson that
was funny that isn't amazing thing chamber
do you have a bunch of three
days right
you haven't seen i haven't seen oh
my god please read and crispy
yesterday but today go to the next
guy but okay if take
ah thanks we like to watch it
today yeah yeah honestly get the joke
the news i mean that's to me
it's one of the largest makes me
laugh so hard like figure i've ever
gotten so surprised like i'm like cracking
up like it's just you don't get
to watch many things make you laugh
like that it's true that's very true
so far
that's very true so you thought i
should have paid for should i have
been nice no never no i think
he's saying confusion was i like the
two things i liked the gambit of
being in front of someone yeah and
then turn it maybe if you the
the deal is if you just have
a couple of things first behind you
as a bunch of stuff yeah if
you turn around and say aren't you
gonna pay yeah
or like taking up the little rubber
thing yeah i mean like we're together
yeah just so i got to but
also you strike up a long conversation
with them yeah about their other item
and then hope you raise them a
little bit like oh oh what a
smart idea yesterday i put the dressing
in the bowl or how does it
oh do you put the same liking
in the
does the chasing go on top of
the salad or like do you just
slow the bag
drifting in here
alright we have to disagree
yeah
and we're back oh my god um
but those are the two things exist
ah those are the two things that
happen to me you big stud to
get you to pay for like her
two items oh oh my items fall
into your pile oh no oh no
my club far from gere oh my
god those crazy apparently totals like ten
bugs i swear i least my
half was that's the thing about items
now is like only lying about items
recent item news
no but remember the thing is i
wanna know you'd be at the supermarket
so might of two items it would
be like here's a couple of bucks
now it's ten bucks per over sanders
ten dollars so it's like why would
you ever offer to pay anything for
anybody i forgot about reverse flash was
he was just a flash with a
yellow ca yeah with red boots and
said he could also
run fast he had the same powers
he he would have to run backwards
oh no
why would why wasn't this thing he
was really slow yeah slower than normal
how does that help
could you don't dodge you could indulge
your doll anything here we go let's
name thing hopefully dodgeball is named airway
go a cup i indulged
hey sure here here's a cup right
here alright can you adults yeah i
can tell you can you dodge it
just me can you dodge i'm it's
right here dodgy dodge there and get
indulged it wow incredible you like my
doll doll style
i adults before i do it it's
not bad thank you although i feel
like it's tipping people off to the
fact that you're going to indulge like
i don't always have to do it
so you are you doing false flag
dodges yeah all the time you're just
yelling dolls and the not dodging yeah
and credit theaters oh not in crowded
theatres yeah what about you
yelling fire in a theater that's not
right that has like ten people in
it that's cool i think it's allowed
of course yeah it's just the stampede
factor it is the stampede factor that's
what they're worried about so if it's
if it's under capacity and it's ten
people can get out fine but yeah
why why isn't capacity ok here's capacity
in theaters should be low
enough to where someone yells fire people
get out safely yeah all theaters should
have
gonna say fifty seats and ten ppm
max can i say speaking of theatre
yeah i saw the little mermaid oh
and wait in the ocean yes fish
barney as your harpoon matter thank god
or speaking in theatre so little mermaid
in the ocean i saw her and
she's swimming and daughter umm i loved
it pitchfork
seen it i know well i'm not
as well okay well neither my name
but here you are more doctor than
kid well in this instance i was
more kid but i loved it and
um it was the halle bailey is
so wonderful as long i mean it
was just right i love that movie
so much growing up so i was
really excited to see it and she
she is so earnest and sweet and
has a great voice and cheek i
got chills some of the songs i
clapped after clapping the c h r
clapped i clapped my ass
everyone's stood up and clapped their essence
sticky
yeah
okay category what's the noise
it's the little mermaid i never heard
of it quite like that weirdest thing
happened after every song
yeah
ah
yeah it's honestly really cute but but
i would say for kids a little
scary yeah oh sorry told me and
this is a spoiler for what for
the little mermaid okay but but because
this is at the end of the
movie okay but i mean well the
men know what hap yeah it's the
same it's the same story stories yeah
it was like an unintentional jump scare
wait what is part they she's sailing
off with prince whatever eric and then
when those prints poseidon's face appears in
the ocean no
and apparently it was like king triton
king triton excuse yeah yeah wow same
guy ridiculous to say beside it's hobby
airport bar damn i know when my
wife's crushes wow and really know is
it is that a free pass situation
and requesting that you want allow you
shall go to the movies with her
and let her
c m yeah his hair's floater all
hot and bothered yeah you like javier
bardem what about one made of water
ah yeah let her see okay let
her see that guy i want to
find this because somebody sent it but
i don't remember the i don't remember
the thought that i had during that
part you don't remember the hut that
you thought i don't remember having a
jump scared remember things
you were there um and whoa what
are you trying what are you trying
to find and trying to fly i
have video of the plugin plug it
in because somebody sent it to plug
it in again
oh my someone sent you a video
okay a little background they found the
end people send videos to paul all
the time he's what we call the
video guy they centers my po box
and i convert them and i put
them on my phone and thank you
by the way everybody for sending me
your videos i love them all ah
there's even some that are mean about
me and i still love to love
them you left them yeah much people
ah they say mean things about me
um and they ah they like laugh
in my face is this the one
yeah that's it can you can you
she's so fun once you get closer
and omondi went do do do do
do do happy new year
okay okay here we go video of
the endings media or you'll try to
love this part one place this was
like a lin manuel song they put
in one place
okay
let me see
with what does this video wow this
is from the actual movie because there
were some hunks in there yeah the
mermaids are a what
what a multicultural group
they're from all over i love it
even if it is woke ah
kit to it get to it bitch
ma da da dah someone made this
video like tape the screen
that doesn't scare me that the scary
either
i was like dubbed
but once you say it's like good
doi really good to me it's like
don't deliver good doing it whatever i
thought was that i thought it was
that his face appears in the water
oh maybe it does that later good
toy to toy looks ridiculous just while
you're used to him by now i
gotta say this looks like the famous
movie ever made
oh ah you don't chat logs okay
no way it's honestly is really well
done and i was so happy i
thought i'd suddenly end of the movie
you just showed us well that's not
shocking i thought it was yeah that
was really oversold too that was not
scaring know i thought that um it
was weird doing good doi doi yeah
sure i did
like the show good it's the best
live action disney so far i thought
this one kind of walked the line
of the animals being one of my
walking stick that was a great remake
what about pinocchio pinocchio i haven't seen
but it hurts my good but no
but pinocchio isn't a remake i heard
you heard that no no the other
pinocchio is the new the gear yourself
you know what that's what i'm saying
is to now that one is one
is a disney remake and one is
not i can't leave so many were
happening at the same time what's going
on everybody's lost their damn mind wow
everyone needs to fuckin take a chill
pill for one second everyone take a
chill pill plea i loved it and
i and melissa mccarthy was great and
it was really fun the end how
much did you pay
to see it yeah eleven dollars so
much would you pay my i paid
eleven dollars because my friend is a
stubs member and we went to a
matinee and our school is she she
got all the tickets she got in
for free and then you guys split
the free well if your stubs member
i think we i guess we'll discount
your free movies for life yeah we
got a discount from it for life
so who's you pay there was that
it's a one time fee there was
that thing though for a while where
you could go to as many as
you wanted that's something different that's moviepass
moviepass i want i was right i
missed that but i missed the window
to like two for free or something
stops anyway the whole reason i know
this is because i signed my parents
up for it i buy
eat them both really expensive subscriptions and
they end up march of twenty twenty
wow
and then they're like that's my donation
to keep theaters oh yes and then
had a long email chain trying to
convince them not to go no no
trying to get the company to defer
yea yeah like you're not open way
they were like oh that sucks yeah
anyway call me on em dor yeah
buyer buyer beware
buyer rare bear buyer brb bear buyer
kevin forney y'all hey cough cough cardiologist
naming jobs jobs i wear my other
jobs
penis shrinks
that was just in my spare time
on my own just actually good
do you remember dr schrenker are you
old enough to know what's trigger it
was one of those saturday morning live
action shows like electra woman and dyna
girl exactly my dear boy and this
was about an evil scientist named brink
once you have to be evil ah
he was a madman
the name dr fauci anyway go ahead
oh god the theme song told us
he's a madman with an evil mind
and his songs don't like his henchmen
was billy barty oh okay good for
him and i guess he shrunk some
kids down to billy barty have one
i duda duda
you don't even sing it now
i like to say that if you
get there like did he have a
glass sigh yeah nothing i've ever heard
it's me who's the guy peter sellars
who had one a beautiful kitty fok
say i just learned that he had
won i thought he had a lazy
fracture on my body had a lazy
eye were watching a video then we
learned
in the video peter falk they had
a glass eye yeah right he told
some stories about it and yeah it
was pretty interesting yeah how did he
lose i don't know how he lost
it oh god he told the story
hold on toy story memory comes into
play was a lovely lady milk um
yeah three boys of his own i've
talked about a one about rose julia
is falling out of his sock
oh yes and he's and they just
popped it back yeah yeah oh yes
i can remember oh noes my eyes
and somewhere like puss in boots
now i know he does not not
sound like raul julia it's a good
point to good good point and what
do you have any taxi
okay something or fault lose i how
did oh boy because he had a
cancerous growth at age three age swing
his eye was removed and he was
given a glass eye wow i mean
it's amazing they were able to it's
amazing they were able to to get
it up i mean maybe these days
with modern surgery there would be better
ways to do it but at the
time
time that's what they did and he
grew up to be an incredible famous
actor one what a success to play
columbus yeah fourteen ninety two rex harrison
my fair lady fame also had one
i sammy davis junior sandy duncan yeah
sandy duncan and a glass eye glass
from the hogan family yeah yeah she's
tricking the church in the way she
was great
and that show that was like a
show that was a remake yep well
you know we've talked about torah this
valerie harper it was called salary mallory
yeah and she was like i want
more money and they're like five dollars
then it was valleys family know that
it was funny always get this wrong
hogan family starring jason bateman what if
i like to think though
they kind of eased you into it
he was like galleries family for a
little bit more whole extra fuck you
to valerie like you to know that
their last name is hogan and it's
like now we know it's the hogans
they were a good cast i watched
the children that we realize it was
jason bateman yeah good for him that's
it others oh by the way dad
by the way i thought the smartness
ah
doc is fun is good i enjoyed
it i enjoyed it you watch it
haven't seen it oh yeah i liked
it haven't um i liked their dynamic
like director sam oh yeah i did
his show yeah i like to show
um it's fun because he his his
interview show sam jones yeah is all
black and white and he then he
takes he's a photographer and he yeah
and then he takes photos and black
and white and really cool and then
he thing isn't like he did those
things too yeah yeah you know that
color i don't think so i think
i would want too late to tell
him i'd want to show him the
wizard of oz and see his reaction
talk wow because that part you part
that part though when the
when the men that they get all
dentals just start filming everything is super
when like the ten mans are talking
and he's like isaac able to talk
and there's a good while away when
he saw that that would blow his
mind if you saw that lie and
talking holy shit know but i thought
he did a good job with it
and i really liked watch i agree
really i would like to do something
like that with you guys ah
but i won't well no ah show
business is not interested
i simply made a video i think
wait if we all were famous oh
okay and lauren you're going to be
we're counting on you we're counting on
you you're gonna be like pulling us
along to break apps like get the
deal look you're already a level of
fame but we'll never so no one's
asked
seeing us to be on things alright
so i guess i'll just see if
i get crew wants to follow us
around yeah yes see if a crew
wants to follow us here's what i
think the crew needs to understand right
off the bat and we mainly don't
spend time together yeah so this would
be a show about this like a
series where you kind of see us
and our individualized theirs and then you
see how
it comes together on three mobile how
it plays out on the pod like
oh actually no paul was having a
really hard week and then he shows
like having a lot of fun when
he's with his friends right you know
also they're on tour when they do
it and they hang out oh no
it's great oh hey sweetly don't say
oh sounds like they sleep in the
same bed but with us
it would be we would do the
show and then say good night everyone
in the elevator yeah yeah that's not
hang out afterwards i'm not happy i'm
not getting in a suite
watching tv afterwards with you like it's
over i've waited what are you talking
about did they all they hang out
they hang out there they all get
us a hotel suite with three separate
rooms and all that and they'll hang
out in a film them all the
time and they have all their meals
together and they make fun of each
other for everything they eat great yeah
which i loved i would love to
make fun of you and what
you eat scott i would love to
make fun of you when you eat
but i just don't think i just
thought you don't have many thoughts about
food i just had a time and
i just like to be alone i
get this cracker make fun of this
i have a joke about one thing
that you eat and if you're not
eating that every time that i'm out
of modjeska thing i don't want to
waste it i don't wanna i don't
wanna like burn when you are eating
that oh he'll get you know you'll
know
she'll know y'all know you're eating it
yeah let me grab this plum anyway
it's not a shot
it's really going to tell him the
plumber we should have done a tour
doc when we went on tour i
know we have so much fun yeah
with our phones and put together and
just we give audience members our phones
and they watch it on yeah and
we say please bring me back after
he's wounded phone back we need our
phone back it's the one phone and
we all
i'll use it we are one jitterbug
we needed or we have to take
a break
and we're back hi i love you
let's call you've got an incredible email
during the break oh yeah so the
latest thing is i'm getting these spam
emails um that are from sloppy ccs
they're from and by the way that's
not us like they called themselves call
that they they want to be known
as that so i see this i
mean they they're not saying i'm a
slut but the way that they're communicating
is pretty slutty and there's no way
around that and no judgment on acting
like a slot man you said we
love sluts so please get out of
my inbox my bed so you go
oh my
mapa yeah
so the latest thing oh wait this
is not a bcc one oh no
oh no this is a bunch of
people who are a few letters off
from the beginning of my email address
yeah old school alright so they're just
dirty and it's like hey i just
got to town i'd love to meet
you or whatever oh come this one
is ah this is from stephanie
ah and she she is a m
i y a d to ny to
a gmail dot com and the opening
lines you want to get a hold
of her and yeah i was gonna
say you do but she sounds pretty
if you used to these questions i
would write to yeah ah the first
line is hey ha y y comma
more than a million periods then two
emoji's of like ah the girl with
pigtails okay then we then we we
i'm already horny we tabbed down a
bunch a lot of dead space and
then it gets to are you one
hundred percent gay let's try
that's now where i saw him going
ever since this is already a new
twist
then several periods several question marks same
to emoji's then yes dash dash dash
dash dash or dash dash dash dash
dash no question mark lips heart answer
me now forward slash forward slash forward
slash forward slash forward slash then phone
emoji one hundred one hun
did emoji ah exclamation mark or emoji
double x emoji has been checkmark emoji
to rose emojis so their socials to
rose emoji yeah
so that's what i've been getting every
few hours or so see if i
haven't since saturday see spams
vesuvio jabs his spouse what's the latest
thing of do you want to fuck
ugly girls like what is that me
personally is that about like who's that
appealing to people who are people feel
like attain attainable think yeah maybe make
girls feel better yeah i bet i
bet it's girls trying to say ugly
girls sending those emails yeah
trash blue pills trash blue pill huh
yeah that's the email address that's the
name of the person who touched it's
a great email update my name's trash
subjects have teaspoon triggers erection muscle gets
you a hard erection muscle harvard research
shows when you mix half teaspoon of
a few common kitchen spices and mix
it into your coffee dot dot dot
you'll
activate your body's hidden cock muscle and
ah the hidden one and and they
put all of your muscles are headed
to asterisk for the o and restore
those bulging german incised boehner's women beg
for arrow emoji swallow half because of
this i've never heard any sneeze
swallow half teaspoon of this to activate
your quote cock muscle gives you bigger
longer lasting boehner's reacher shit research shows
when this erection is firing on all
cylinders you'll get rock hard right form
in seconds no matter if you're twenty
or one hundred twenty yet if this
muscle is weak dr darwin between it
doesn't matter how
how many blue or yellow pills you
choke down dot dot dot your cock
will flop over like a dead fish
humiliating you and your partner
your partner to leave them out of
this still let a week willy ruin
your relationship man get the recipe here
and then there's no link there's no
link to so so are you supposed
to write back and go like hey
you the link is broken yeah i
could get the link but my my
wet willy is humiliating me right now
as well
my partner i also love when political
people go like they have such dramatic
subject lines it says lauren this is
bad yeah and it's about some i
love that show and like eat shit
i've also noticed a company that just
sends automated emails they now try to
personalize it so you'll open it like
instead of like yeah this comes
tony wants you to do this they'll
be like sarah from this company is
asking this and that's weird there's no
actual sarah i don't like there is
no sarah and i've tried to find
her i've never seen anyone named sarah
nope
they don't and it doesn't exist as
adam scott that limit doesn't exist here's
one from lilly shane
ah her sounds nice is ah s
shankar nine one three or four okay
bucko sounds real and she writes she
gets right to the point oh good
ah well the the subject line is
henri i need you to make time
for me tonight say yes daddy
and then she writes my ass is
your next focus ah
it turns you on so much doesn't
it it's round supple and bouncy why
don't we meet up for reals you
can take me from behind i am
not far and i'm quite sure we
have seen each other around let me
know i have a problem now let
me know i have a private apartment
where we can run a vu let
me know let me go m k
following
up um did you get my email
how i don't think i get any
of these i'm sure they're in your
spam maybe yeah why they're going right
to my inbox
i don't even know how to access
spam their e-mails like i think you're
gonna want to see this one let
me see that egg plant in between
your leg oh okay i've never been
into my spam folder i bet it's
begging for my touch isn't it but
you know the rules always a tit
for tat show me what i'm getting
and i'll show you my lets arrange
for a special time together just you
and me no drama
okay so i've never you don't want
drama i've never clicked on my spam
fake flat and all i have is
stuff from
twitter
icloud request you cloud requests oh yeah
we all wow manner about erections we
had this other one i just watched
a video data den that i will
never forget dot dot dot whatever you
do dot dot that don't show it
to your wife dot dot dot let
this be a surprise surprise of her
life i told ya go there and
trust me you'll
soon know what every woman's fantasy really
is and isn't what you think if
you're on my mailing list i'm suffering
from e d is mandatory watch that
video right away because the secret sauce
and everything's pop like bubble wrap ferment
getting so many erection emails it's signed
by me
name of the thing is me and
it's to mike
yeah and i wrote this and i
love this they say your erection will
pop like bubble yes
good i don't have any of these
in my in my spam folder and
sorry i'm sorry today i'm sorry i
don't know me for them too yeah
um alright so for a three cheer
if you send us one a little
game to play you can you can
write to us at threesome usa at
gmail dot com and if you're slip
mailer then send us some smell yeah
yeah we'll send say right to space
so if if you just write in
it this should not go to spam
it doesn't go to spam right yes
okay that's the worker okay yeah this
should not go expect
so we're gonna we're gonna do an
old fave
press khan fresco for old sir and
we're gonna text each other two of
us are going to text each other
ah celebrity and then a scandal that
the celebrities involved in and then the
other one of us is going to
conduct a press conference and we the
or to our reporters asking questions about
the scandal until they've ah the the
person conducting the press conference figures out
who the celebrity is what the scandalous
it's like that game where you stick
a fucking post a note on your
head in your butt
right i don't know that guy
are you talking about two different okay
things oh do you want to come
over and play it later okay daddy
doctor
so dick pop like bubble wrap so
paul and i will text future paul
why don't you check a top like
the twin towers why don't you text
a scandal and i will text you
a celebrity you talk to me the
celebrity and that's why just said handle
what but i'm saying you want the
celebrity name first oh
i see okay so i can come
up with the scandal okay so i'll
text you a celebrity to keep putting
my sunglasses on because it has to
be a celebrity that that laura knows
okay um
so i can't deal in the lab
and can't do linda lavin can't do
linda lavin um the first parts
i don't know who that is she
played alice on tv's alice and i
do know which is a i know
wow version of the movie alice doesn't
live here i've never directed by martin
scorsese they're essentially alice on brady bunch
no that would be
what was her name anne and get
it now ann
what what are we to rand the
lady who played alice on brady bunch
a and b davis and b davis
and be quick and jumped over the
candlestick that's right
ooh her once shame on her fool
her twice a fire it's too bad
for me three times look i'm not
doing any of this for me four
times come on guys please stop with
the booing will be five times okay
now you're just having fun for me
six times this is oh oh man
there's a comedian i can remember who
it is who did
id pretty much that bit where he
was essentially fool me once shame on
ah you fool me twice shame on
me and then he i forget how
high he went but it was like
now reverts back to me yeah it
was i i remember oh yeah really
really funny alright ready yeah lauren you're
gonna start this press conference okay hi
everyone
ah thank you so much for joining
us today we have um who are
you celebrity celebrity i'll ever use remember
i'm a celebrity you know oh i
thought was introducing so i think they're
just the the press pro your your
personal liberty i'm sorry yeah yeah why
are you shouting celebrity this obvious non
celeb i want i thought we could
play celebrity oh yeah that's a family
um thank you for coming obviously this
is a big deal what we have
going on here today it's not something
that we want to be talking about
but the same
time we need to address just get
ahead of it so whatever questions you
have we are going to allow them
is this going to affect his ah
educational shows at all um you know
what we're really hoping not he's he
didn't intend for any of this to
happen say think that what he said
just sounds very integrity intentional which
part of what was sorry yeah do
you think this is going to destroy
his credibility i see i think the
fans know his true his true soul
and history nature i mean he has
been doing this for such a long
time but i do i feel like
the fans are the ones who has
trust is like a slap in the
face to the fans for him to
say something like this right so i'm
not sure exactly which part you're speak
thing about because there are a couple
things he has apologized it was a
very brief statement it wasn't not not
a lot of fat on that half
of it was very contradictory to everything
we know about the world and then
the second half was just an insult
slab so you're saying bill nye said
the world is flat you idiots well
yes i mean i mean the second
part of what he said
you can try to paraphrase it now
but i we we have it on
we haven't on t i mean he
likened that condition
two the only want to say to
the status of the cup size of
so bill nye said the world is
as flat as like as joan rivers
tits joan rivers know someone more personal
to me yeah your wife's tits oh
my wife has loving large breasts she
doesn't love you guys
um this is about someone that ah
that ah i used to be very
intimate with those breasts your mom yes
so bill nye said the world is
flatter than your mom's chest yeah i
mean i got there you did pretty
good yeah are those door again alright
okay so who's i
well um
oh perfect and that was really weird
that person is zooming by okay um
that person was acting like a dog
with zombies
alright gonna text you yeah you're gonna
text me a celebrity i'll text you
a ah a scandal
and then paul is gonna run the
press conference and we're gonna have a
good time i'm sending you a celebrity
yeah do do do do do do
do do you like our whole music
part of the issue is i think
they thought we were going to be
done at a certain time and we've
gone over that time the audience know
we should know
i have been the girl should be
doing this podcast
remember three years ago so we'll do
one more and will as long as
lauren sends me the celebrity oh yeah
i'm trying she's trying really hard not
liking what i'm saying okay to do
that to be alive mo no thank
you dad a the okay
and i'll text you the scandal
um
here we go i'm having post-lunch crash
yeah well we only have one other
because we're this the last round know
i know i know let's get let's
let's have fun pi i'm just i'm
just i'm just you get it no
yeah guarding myself and i'm letting you
know right here we go so run
run
i'm the ah go ahead and start
okay ah thank you everyone for being
here obviously um you'll have questions and
i will answer those questions in the
best of my ability great um look
what did what did her the people
she works with think about this well
honestly um
obviously that an academy award winner doesn't
want to be associated with with this
kind of thing you know it well
what the person she works with oh
okay yeah she herself has not won
an academy award it wouldn't make any
sense for her to win one no
but because you asked a question because
i really wish all these people
that that she is on this show
with yeah academy award on a show
with with with these different women with
these different thoughts and it's like they're
all gonna have suddenly have outsized this
kind of ah this kind of activity
okay well look i mean ah they're
obviously a cast as a family and
they um
they all can be different people but
still it's working together something like that
i imagine that one of her cohosts
is going to have a problem with
with her eating that yeah well just
because i mean look we've all seen
a female trouble and divine human shit
so so so it's not worse than
that and that's what you're trying to
zach thanks that's pretty good maybe worse
because it's not ah because he
we tend to eat yeah and it's
and it's actually an human shit is
just gotta point alright let's let her
off
okay i mean i don't even know
how she got the meat honest is
it mean is it fit how did
she spirit herself or it it could
be that was someone fishermen caught or
well look look before we get into
all that i want to talk about
the the working relationship and how things
are on sept okay
a and of course the academy award
winner
he shows she she she did once
all women and anyway she'd all the
women she works with she's not gonna
like that she's very opinionated and they're
all very opinionated in different direction i
mean i think one of them might
there her political leanings might lean towards
where she doesn't care but look but
an arab majority get on tv
authorities speak about things if they there's
no way that they're gonna be able
to not talk about you know this
big talk about what's in the news
this is in the news now yes
they do and sometimes they accidentally are
the news and if joy bahar know
because if deceased
if barbara walters um
says something from beyond the grave she
didn't say something she
she said she said grace before she
ate this thing yeah yeah well i
mean that is a mitigating factor you're
right yes and just because it was
it was i mean i mean it's
just we we hate tuna the thing
she ate was was a former star
of a tv show itself yeah we
i mean the the show that has
the name that is the start of
describing someone giving someone the middle finger
yeah
flipper off yeah okay
ah if you classify dolphin as meat
then of course you're going to see
this in a certain negative light but
if you just classified often as fish
ah then it's not the big deal
is it i guess he's got barbara
walters eats dolphin live on camera live
on camera i mean she had a
reason to do it what was the
reason
she wanted people to see how fancy
she is all you guys say she
was hungry
i don't think that can be all
you gotta say she was hungry and
will walk away and will walk away
happy barbara was hungry there you go
alright well i mean like yeah i'm
like car do you want to grab
a bite i'm good but i tell
you what honey you're good why don't
you go nah
smell honey
ah yes but yeah home and family
in mendham naval
alright well i mean it isn't a
hoedown it's a country song there's a
weed whacker right outside the window yeah
yeah are you a weak boy never
knew we gotta we gotta really creepy
pasta um alright if you want to
write to us ah i don't know
call knows all this
tough i do you write your freedom
usa jim lamb commander out there send
us lounge rooms and reacher if you
want to call us it's hey you
claims eight if you want here ad-free
episodes go to cvb world or stitcher
premium and follow us on social media
at three dm usa also a few
on your ad-free episodes won't you
good to your mom here she gives
away for free
yeah got and if you want to
write to those sluts
i gave you some sun addresses already
i'll keep giving them to you if
they keep writing to me i will
will paid forward i'm gonna say well
if you get any lie to gain
send it to us and through the
mail
a line knee game isn't nah alright
we gotta go ah boeing doing a
show please god please god ah the
twenty eighth the twenty six august twenty
six come on board no the other
one too it is their time now
this time i believe it up p
lie please come july
ninth sunday july nine seven pm lodge
room in highland park please i beg
of you and then the portland show
and then portland when i'm getting show
august fourth and you can come to
that as well okay keep up people
we we people bite
uh