nah
ah
a
uh wow hiring yeah and stressful i
loved it i was a remix that
was the every time we've done the
theme song all layered on top of
each
other who who ah did that for
us it's on the board behind me
was by i am lum ahmed tom
l'm person is only as big as
alum yeah let's um instead of tom
tom yes oh i get it i'm
thinking it's time to sell a thing
or is it because there was a
candy shop in my town it was
a character whose
about this big there was a real
guy who was in the circus well
he was not he was he was
larger than a thumb but he called
himself tom thumb it was a real
guy i think i think it was
a story that became a guy took
that name oh okay the village yeah
ghoulish nature you'll go gaga who's done
shooting again and the sec
a tom thumb to g welcome to
the show i'm assuming that thumb is
very choose to um i'm laughing believe
i'm paul f tompkins i'm scott alderman
nan welcome to three da um oh
what a day what a day what
a day what did some b'elanna and
tom
film ever get together sargasso so i
don't think
there's like tumbleweed in tom thumb it
up with shared tmc i thought i
thought they were going to take smoothie
i thought they were together but they
were lina and tom thumb they should
be together shouldn't be just because they
look like you all racists don't they
don't look alike they're just totals each
other well they don't you don't factor
in height
lauren the adventures of serious question this
looks very modern i'm saying do they
get kevin airy chevron has put to
get they looked districts extremely cutting edge
chevron has put up a link to
something called the adventures of tom thumb
and thumbelina i can i stay thousand
to meet stumble in nineteen ninety year
are going to say do i care
about you care about because here as
a tall woman
you're like five six five ten amanda
and um i just posted a meme
and today you gotta be told the
five chicken i'm five eleven exactly i
mean you gotta see it it's not
funny
wow that's not gonna be chicken in
the corn and you'll get all excited
and i hope you people are still
donate you posted a meme idea can
you believe it yeah yeah oh by
the way hey we should say that
that ah brushy one string yes his
his kickstarter ends tomorrow yes so and
he's so close so-called go over the
top guy have to like you have
two okay who would have to it's
your moral impair i'm getting i'm getting
a jingle his okay are you gonna
do i'm gonna get a jingle we'll
play it on the show you are
oh good his music is really great
he's terrific and it's where we weep
on this show we played a very
isolated part of one song but he's
really terrific yeah oh yes um the
meme is it says why does this
make sense and then it show
shows a taller person shaking hands with
a shorter person and the teller person
is labelled five nine girls and the
shorter person is labelled five nine guys
i'm just like way shorter because it
is true in guys cause i know
they're lying oh they're aligner like the
way you're lying about your heels i'm
not wearing heels in the meme okay
name
you're not but that is you in
the mean it is me an old
means
i modeled for memes back in the
day when i couldn't make a buck
you're that's why we call you molina
yeah you know those people in the
meme about the guy looking back at
the at the girl passing and that
like they're real people right well they're
not drawings know somebody somebody wants a
great image yeah somebody throws post thrust
it ahead the thrust
when i say a pitch i got
frosted somebody somebody posted throw ship all
the other pictures that those people were
stock photos oh yes people were in
they made a little story yeah i
know someone who was stocked photo and
then she ended up in like a
can't ah a political campaign and get
like some oh really
boys don't pose for those stock photos
it's worse than porn lady how much
do you pay for that flew ladies
ladies it's worse than like yourselves i
could see myself totally doing it as
if i just moved to allay and
someone's like look you want to come
here and just like pose you get
five hundred bucks for the day po
and will ever use would have to
be someone you knew or could be
a stranger
one hey just come and pose i
don't know i got myself into many
situations although i've seen kate hudson as
a fucking frame filler picture that was
definitely like an old stock photos she'd
have to do i've not said it
was like i don't know maybe it
became public domain somehow or something oh
so whenever movies became public domain maybe
good they forgot to rin
sue the copy right we should call
the cops on the fringe store because
maybe the dollar store oh yeah hate
to see it droese you go like
well sir i prefer the ninety nine
cent store i don't like the dollar
store because once i had employment there
ah doing like a like setting up
a new
dollar store i forgot that the new
dollar store it was your fourth time
today
not even on air just hearing the
word new
triggers you are setting up a you
what do you mean we're setting up
a new back when i lived in
try to imagine what i meant guess
they'll put up some folding chairs out
what like yeah why would there be
folding chairs i don't know what do
you think happens to the dollar store
oh no you go in you talk
about you have a problem with alcohol
and you dre
in coffee you don't me you aren't
in dollar store yeah i'm pretty sure
i am the dollar store i had
a great time it really helped me
oh look i'm glad i'm not gonna
take that away from you there was
ah there was a storefront on south
street in philadelphia where i where i
used to live and i was between
jobs and ah they were like the
two firms to train two jobs
much like the film coming september to
your home and tv on netflix hey
way so ah it was me and
a bunch of other people in a
similar situation who were money meaning money
we were just like was there anyone
else joey thing we were doing ah
yeah now there's probably some peace
well that did it for the love
like they're like send all my paycheck
to charity i honestly would have fun
organizing the dollar so it was not
fun yeah so what did you do
and what did you like literally it
was an empty storefront and you put
in the aisles and all the racks
and stuff like that yeah wow that's
exactly what we did you sweep
no i didn't know it was pre
swept it was i think it was
also carpeted oh okay ooh gross and
so you so you did you have
to install stuff was it like ah
a drill situation it was not a
no i don't remember there being any
like heavy tools like that i think
it was maybe some screwdrivers like that
drills is heavy hammers his head
depends on the hammer you get a
little raw camel you crack on him
wrong but um really we guaranteed him
roger julia from obiano joma like it's
nolan's rock paul hi me nolan rock
paul way uncle blatt are you gonna
do a bunch of new characters on
tour i was just thinking about that
very thing yeah we're going
on tour next week by the way
yeah i feel like i got i
got some that are that are relatively
new that i can put in there
and then maybe some new ones along
the way oh boy i've been considering
it myself
it was to get together to talk
about this so so how many days
was this three i'm guessing three
i honestly don't remember why i remember
might have been one day i don't
know what if it was my mind
i might have done one day and
then left oh right that's yeah that
was your memo was my one and
out and that's my old imo i
did similarly i worked for the the
the mark taper you know ah organization
here in town which is a theater
what the mark taper forum they do
all the theater in town they have
like he got his theater he got
his screen name they do all the
theater they do all the theater have
you seen theater because march ever did
it because i've seen some theatre that
i don't think mark taper had a
name is where was it lyric hyperion
my
his fingers in a lot of pie
i honestly wouldn't know if you were
kidding but i did i worked at
the warehouse for a summer and we
had to do now for the listener
that's yeah w h e r no
not the not where the listener that's
w e r h o o no
jacoby well or look scott guarantees yeah
did you
easier is small we live a result
i like oh tower are you in
high school i was yeah i think
i was told my entire life taller
than everyone who you know are you
in sixth grade i i don't know
come on scott you know scott i
remember everywhere and look at have them
take a picture i remember that thing
the lines on the wall i remember
like getting higher and higher as i
grew older this is very poetic remember
that thing online like oh getting higher
and higher xy older it's pretty good
you're right it's like oh yeah it's
a good song makes me think neil
diamond yeah i think because i remember
them saying remember i remember the
the lens on the wall glands oh
i send you the chair tide and
the audience goes like
oh god
yeah looks like i don't remember when
i was like yeah this is as
tall as i get when i hope
to no i think it must have
been in high school because i was
i think i was as tall as
i was going to get in high
school they'll be funny if that was
a moment that people had where they're
like yeah this is as tall as
like i think this is it people
i didn't but i think it was
a thing where like i kept going
up in
you know guys like topped out and
stop buying longer pants this is it
this is paul but i wouldn't pre
buy my lawyers small and high school
i feel like i was the same
why would a leading question were you
small and raised or are you just
getting to a story about how your
smoke i was told i'm just wondering
because i know a lot of men
were very smb
all in high school and then they
got taught like later i was always
average i was always advertised i never
thought about my height until probably very
recently that i feel like i seem
when i see pictures with people that
i seem so much shorter than people
just with you know what it is
you don't i think it is about
anything like that with at least
east our situation is that we have
photographs taken all the time you have
to look at them yeah yeah and
like it makes you or like if
you're in a movie or doing something
that makes you think about yourself in
a way you never would have where
like i know i would never think
about how i look that much absent
usually it's just that piece of glass
in my bathroom yeah that old piece
of glass little
isa glass in the bathroom the very
finance got all that like an actual
all glass to see his reflection he's
a witch from a cartoon
but everything that's like changed how you
you wouldn't have thought about your height
even oh honestly yes i feel like
podcast photos specifically have you made me
feel bad well also your podcasts photos
specifically notorious hero genre yeah the ugliest
pictures ever taken i will throw down
right now the ladle any
dad then the artistry is lacking composition
i think having existed i think kevin
has a pretty good job because we
he'll get us into poses and and
we can look at them how were
the doughboys doing better pictures that's a
good question what do you say those
new one please
you've done nothing wrong um your song
and kevin around with special guest coming
up i saw that on the shed
you ain't god i'm so they have
their own podcasts nowadays they do weird
all the sub genres all the main
roads you can listen to it okay
you can listen to i'm not telling
you i'm telling the listener we know
that you won't listen
and support chevy for sta e paul
i have other things to do i
had to bring you into it for
me thanks please support me listen to
heaven and new songs podcast
were you always small or taller whatever
you're on whatever small lauren hassan was
little ah
at what point did you realize you
were a real string bean ah middle
school and twenty offering real beanpole dark
okay i got way too tall remembering
i was the tallest girl in sixth
grade and there's one other girl who
was tall with me and we were
five seven and then i shot up
to five ten my sister i reached
my max height
eight in sophomore year if that was
the same yes and you mate i
don't know i don't remember what are
you sixteen are you
it sounds like you're negotiating with me
but hey what are you six and
what are you what are you eighty
six one
i'm going lower i actually would not
mind being lower you wouldn't well as
it's hard acting like especially doing the
the comedy bang big tv show um
it's hard getting it's hard getting lined
up next to someone that you're settling
there are too many short men so
for me i feel it's it's interesting
whenever i rarely cast opposite a shorter
person
right and david nmu david spade he
assured me so rice you've there's a
lot of apple box work going on
when you're there my week yeah we
didn't use why are you sitting on
an apple box if you're already taller
than its perspective baby you know that
raiders lost her low rada that was
coming with apple the other person is
in the foreground and then your background
on an apple all right
apple boxes doesn't make any sense
ah okay well lauren you're sick of
it no i want to ask another
question about it but i okay afraid
you'll be noi no go ahead was
it a point of concern for you
that you wanted to be taller you
like worried about it as you were
growing like you want it you are
moving not that again because because i
felt like i was like
of average height i was like well
i wasn't like a short kid yeah
where like you know when you're in
school if you are if you if
you are known as a shortcut is
because you are definitely sure yeah right
and i was never that kid um
but i yeah i really never ever
i guess every once in a while
there would be you would have thought
of like oh i wish i was
a little bit you were like toddlers
the baller you were average meaning like
there was nothing to make fun of
you about oh no there's plenty to
make fun of me about not your
own people did i was not one
of them is it is has every
single person in the world nobody's like
loose guy right in the middle
the average man tim go back has
every single person move but i don't
have every single person made fun of
you in the question made fun of
has every single person been me like
you hear about all these models who
are like oh god i was made
fun of my entire high school career
and i never hear them say they
were made fun of i hear them
say i was a bit of a
gay yes all
that kind of stuff but they never
i've i don't think i've ever heard
a model say like oh people used
to pick on me or make fun
of me yeah i shouldn't have gone
we should we kids should do the
opposite and make fun of the beautiful
people absolutely cozy good if you're listening
to my tag kids listen to me
kids ma you will know the beauty
is
seriously though because they should be taken
down hogan said instead of and they
need to get personalities instead of finding
weaknesses in the in the people who
had already have weakness this is like
you're encouraging school shooters yeah oh no
it doesn't sound good god what a
bad time wherein yeah it's great totally
horrid
well yeah it's true i really know
poor everyone i hate going to the
movies yeah i feel scared kind of
the whole time yeah it's weird although
i saw a great movie what's movie
did you see on a time in
hollywood i said well you like it
i liked it i'm not a big
tarantino fan but i liked the performances
of the
the two main performances so much i
really enjoyed it but i felt like
there's a lot of stuff that could
have been cut out of it okay
i've i've never seen a quentin tarantino
film boy oil oh you'll see me
doing he got in at a good
time loved it and i wanted to
go on longer i truly was like
wow watch this forever watch this all
day wow um i thought it was
great i thought the acting was superb
i liked that it was a nonlinear
story i liked that it kind of
went on different places i liked that
it was sort of true and sort
of not i thought it was really
cool
cool and i also was like i
watch i realised though i watched so
much garbage yeah but it just felt
good to watch so many i was
like oh good movies that i wish
he would watch instead of oh hey
i wanna watch all of them i
feel like i'm like okay now i
need to have a renewed sense of
purpose it's like it's like when you
read a book when you're on vacation
and you're like
yeah like why am i reading the
internet all day like i know like
my job you'd want to read more
than one book a year yeah i've
been trying to read more and it
feels really good yeah yeah i made
myself my my wife janie and i
instituted a no phones in the bedroom
that's our world no phone zone no
find the bones is a much better
phone's home don't you think it's much
better it's much better rain
calms down it's much better and so
it's it's i have gone back to
reading at night and it's been i
think it's been almost a year and
it's been great so night and great
because even just that amount every day
you'll read books look pretty fast like
you don't feel like it's be reading
for hours yeah i'm a real guitar
in a bedroom and i'm like asleep
immediate oh good hello
la ah sorry da o scott it's
like the roper is asleep immediately
no i'm not i'm not like a
phone in the bedroom guy because i'm
i'm ah when i go in the
bedroom it's down to business sweeping so
i have the same business
to je
mike and i are watching some movie
marvel movie with um robert downey jr
everyone was in it it wasn't any
new here and it really went on
forever i have relived that is mostly
yeah yes i mean it was real
i know i don't know i don't
know this actor riding junior was in
this know i lose like every actor
was in it there i've ever heard
these things are so like there's impossible
i haven't seen the movie but knowing
about them is impossible didn't i avoided
it this is amazing i was like
what is this and then he put
ooh and then ever
every five minutes go what are they
doing who ventures and what comb rudd
isn't doing that i'm supposed to believe
that he is with friends were there
all i may get the serious and
i like and his friends with a
wall that was like i love robert
downey junior so my thought was okay
now i want to go to his
mtb and then i found like five
movies of his that i've heard of
but
never seen than i thought i'm gonna
have a thing yeah i pick a
person or like a phone number yeah
and then i watch like a couple
of their movies is that with the
cohen brothers because cool up had never
seen a lot of their films so
it was me paul rust ah paul's
wife leslie and leslie's paul
campbell campbell oh i haven't heard it
called filling the void um and i
think that was it or maybe someone
else but we were going to watch
three cohen brothers movies on saturdays and
go through their entire filmography right so
we we did the one where we
did blood simple you went an order
yeah we went in order so we
saw so set the first saturday we
saw blood simple though
we saw raising arizona and then we
saw miller's crossing right and so then
the next saturday we all came back
and we watched barton fink and then
we broke for lunch and cool op
had made some bbq beef like they
have in the movie yeah though and
and we had
we had french rolls and it was
and it was cooking all day and
it smelled delicious
paul rust was the first one to
go down into the kitchen to get
some and he got the french roll
and he sliced into it sliced his
entire handle
blood went everywhere all over my the
ceiling of the kitchen all over the
refrigerator and all into the barbecue be
oh my god and didn't make it
taste better or worse is delicious so
i've got all that boy you gotta
take you around his hand out in
there
and he did that thing he did
like a like an orange he did
that thing where it was like i'm
okay i'm okay oh i was like
hey man do you need to go
no no no i'm fine you know
and then i like looked at him
i was like hey buddy i'm taking
you the hospitals okay you know here
let me get your shoes on you
know because he's freaking out yeah trying
to go like i'm ok now
no no everything's fine yeah no and
then in retrospect it's like do that
serious like problem anytime blood is hitting
the ceiling yeah yeah you gotta go
to the hospital yeah but it was
so like we were so hungry yeah
that's sad we were so hungry and
then melling it all day and then
i took him to the hospital and
we were there for hours before he
got seen oh
oh man i'm just like holy can
someone please bring something to eat we're
so hungry and then we never revisited
any of the movies we never got
over in the finally set bag of
bugles please please give me a bag
of bugles but now you never finger
learn you'd never seen a edgar wright
movie until we yeah see baby driver
well you you watch one in anticipation
because you are invited
when we first was hot fuzz you
watch yeah yeah yeah he invited us
to see baby driver and in a
screening in new york when we were
there and so you watch that i
should know a little something before something
like that but yeah i liked it
i liked it i was reading some
um filmmaking ah like articles today and
thinking oh man it would be so
cool to do one of these like
because we have a screening room
in my office to which you've been
to yeah so sometimes we'll have people
over to just watch movies in the
middle of the day yeah sounds fun
um sounds fun i've i i've invited
every friend of mine yeah message received
okay it's done kevin said i've been
wow
what about using them yourself is definitely
use on cat leiria so watch without
utah this week on doughboys movie theater
popcorn
but yeah i really enjoy that so
yeah yeah we should let you die
i yeah yeah want to like put
on a little overwhelming invited to the
only reason she's been to watch the
first movie i don't want to over
look guess i've no interest in movies
you're in it this means yes in
some ways this oh wait i am
decibels but yeah you are
okay that's something people want to know
yeah you've told me i've been in
so many movies that i haven't been
in and i show up to that
i should do this that's why you
venture once upon a time in hollywood
as you're told me i was and
you waited two hours and forty minutes
and didn't yeah anyway it for the
bloopers at the end yeah i love
those bloopers you hate work but there
were no they're just once
mitchell oh no well i mean i
didn't wait around for the end you
hate bloopers in general no i love
bloopers okay let me tell you something
i not only love bloopers the best
bloopers news bloopers oh yes me yes
can i set this as a newspaper
saying again something people can't see but
i just want to show you so
i was just watching the
view today and it was a rerun
and i was barbara walters and my
mom's in town i threw the first
airline sentence y and the second place
was new every day babysitting your money
if i put it on with the
sun she'll be quiet yeah
oh hi trish e used to eight
i used to watch the view every
day and i actually kind of still
feel like i'd be good on it
but anyway would be good in the
conservative role yeah you begin in the
view there was there were these people
it was like some old clips from
july so no one was but somebody
speaking in the house the house what
do you call it
i said oh whatever said look at
this man he just like has his
tongue like what looping out like why
king psycho she showed us a picture
of a guy in a suit who's
just literally has his funny pictures oh
yeah like a psycho he's going like
little it's called obeys in court or
whatever you usually just a
a man of animals week learn what
do you know about our government three
legislative grantees okay what are they
oh shit um judiciary okay yeah right
yes um
so silent oh boy i know what
they are isn't legislative one of them
okay yes you got and then the
other one is what you know roller
you know those orders that sometimes you'll
say yes ah you know when ah
the dude upstairs mann executive yeah
ah look i'm not dumb in fact
i'm smart now
in the criminal justice system the people
represented by two equally important groups you
know what they are yeah um yeah
from law and order that's right i
should know it because i've heard that
enough time that's right the represented by
law and order i was that hit
no
crime and punishment it's ah the just
the judicial system and the police and
it's um ah the ah the police
lawyers what does a lawyer how they
say it wow we sound like fuck
nobodies because you can't think of it
when you have to like everyone out
there i want to give you a
quiz what's next
to delaware you don't fucking know anything
about geography that's all i'm saying it's
not there we're going to let's know
i don't know no one does no
i honestly don't know we don't know
where else this is what i'd tell
you about the tour i don't know
where we're going i don't know what's
happening i don't know who what where
when why i'm just going i'm just
showing up wherever my just gonna show
up and you're gonna have fun i'm
kind of excited i kinda like that
and although kevin is showing oh hey
go back hey go birthday shows sold
out babe oh yeah nice yeah i'm
sure i'm sure we're gonna have so
much fun you're not going to know
where you are we're gonna be in
rhode island i've ever eleven philadelphia come
on don't embarrass me the smallest state
i'm excited to go to providence
it's um yeah i've heard it so
pretty and i was just in rhode
island and loved it oh we're doing
robot i was there with arden marine
oh right come to um yeah yeah
home of little bow rice
you know you know you know
why do rappers want to have little
in front of their name isn't that
well i used to be yeah but
no but little bump and yeah i
know what you mean lil pump yeah
pub the woodpile oh chump
dude that was so funny in that
oh i'm sorry mike advert you bombed
we were at dinner whatever backstage making
up that character and we were laughing
so hard i think he's on backstage
what he was gonna do know and
it was it was different he was
like i'm gonna do i'm gonna be
a little little note no way we
were we were riffing on little bump
the one
the pump chump where are we yeah
in conversation then i was like hey
what are you going to do tonight
because i think i'm gonna do a
little pump it was brand new it
was brand-new yeah given i remember that
no so i remember that as well
and where where was that that was
through i think that was it the
ace no no it wasn't the this
oh okay lose the road for sure
it was there i think it was
australia i don't know guys anyway yeah
you're right but it doesn't matter who
cares who gives a shit we might
bombs get ready i'm ready that's the
fun of it you don't know look
that's the bar we just have to
clear that
at bar and then we're home for
each bar loader showing up i'm chump
oh okay can we play part of
that episode oh that's as low as
it can go ah now yeah the
screen behind me i'd never know what's
on i just turned around and saw
my sandy well maybe you shouldn't always
sit in front of the screen and
want me to be over there
you guys need to know one guy
wanna say like what if we all
if we sat in ojai russian tv
when you do you would you ever
in a restaurant sit on the same
side as your as your i haven't
done that mike loves to occasionally like
tulip loves to she's like really over
i'm getting in well
that's adore yeah it makes us get
in bitch
so he's already in it he's like
once you in it i know he
pushes me further maybe you started doing
an invisible bitch hey that's you i've
always thought this about me but he
could be insane
how's this chessboard that's going well ah
this podcast should be about just us
complaining about our significant complaining i'm not
complaining only you are what i'm complaining
about your significant others that's what i'm
talking about jamie i never do that
accept if we are meeting another couple
and then we'll sit there if we
get
they're ahead of them will sit there
and it makes me feel very weird
does it really just trying to tonight
it do you have a crick in
your neck you can turn yeah i'm
trying to swindle some people have some
insurance money
so you see me on bullock wearing
a neck brace always why aren't you
in these pictures we take
ah ah okay we need to take
a break we need to take a
break it wasn't bye bye
give us some of your advice here
so for instance i've nephew todd ozu
who's in love presumably or or actually
i let a big time crush okay
have you tried eating around
is that an we're back
that is a little bit of shit
that was sex third settle down no
one pump chump from london from brisbane
australia now church that was such a
weird show because it was in an
empty church and in the city hall
it says oh city hall it was
a church it was a big building
that separation of church and state it
felt like a giant australia cl
classroom like a bit with like you
know because well you were addressed to
a hot teacher yeah had to chat
i was dressed like one acdc guy
kids little velvet pantsuit to do
and when are you going to say
do you know the whole hiss yeah
that one acdc guy kid yes yes
your kiss
hi this is kiss for basic dc
and know how to tell you we
love our costumes every it's every kiss
makeup put on top of each other
it looks like a mess the government
is god and god is the government
don't get it twisted um you're saying
sister to dwell you know how you
know how there's that whole like hot
teacher stereotype for for women yeah prefer
for guys mean isn't the same for
is it the same for wit like
is there a similar kind of thing
of like yeah there's a hunky hunky
teacher you never saw raiders of the
lost ark yeah girls right girls right
on their eyelids and says i love
you oh all the time i think
it says i lo
view of that response and i feel
like you happen to give you an
idea yeah lauren who is the hottest
teacher your high school i will never
you'll never say why no my crushes
were not logical i would say they
weren't like everyone's favorite person i would
just like were they famous or were
they meaning peel my my teacher i
would just go
love my teacher and then they for
whatever reason but it wasn't like everyone
else did but um i i the
the book i just mentioned on throwing
shade we just popped into the end
up throwing shade and left scott here
for five years but the book three
women as this book that i just
read was like my kind of book
you it is very turning um it's
a book
look about this this woman out a
couple of women or that i'm in
five women this woman lisa today she
interviewed women for like many years about
their sex lives and then compiled this
book that is basically a narrative exploration
of these three different women's experiences and
it's all just about their sex lives
over the year yeah like i mean
it filters into their relationships and stuff
but it's
sure it's about like why just their
experiences that and how that shapes people
were they mad when they found out
it was a book like it's all
it's all in my best girlfriend all
the details have been um changed to
make it so like penises have been
turned into vaginas yeah that's right and
in one one whole storyline is about
a sixteen year old girl who has
a relationship
with her teacher and it's so interesting
really i'm so one of the women
one of the three women had a
relationship with her teacher when yes and
i'm not really spoiling anything to say
that she like goes to court like
years later oh wow so it comes
up very early in her story but
um then they play back like whatever
it happened and it's like it's cr
crazy because it's so interesting as i
feel like okay so i'm thirty three
now but when i was sixteen to
priest it would have been so that's
like your fantasy is that that person
would want to be with you right
like your teacher or whatever like i
think he actually likes me and like
you could you could leave a whole
fantasy around that but then when you
read it
as an older person it's like disgusting
like this man has a wife and
kids and he has this young girl
in his house when she's not there
and like it's like so gross i
can't even believe it and like you
and i'm just like this person is
so wrong to student these mentions she
was fourteen yeah it happened my school
i think i mentioned yeah we've talked
about and it is
bowie that's spanking pen it's exactly it's
exactly that that when you look at
it as a group you know what
i also feel that way about um
ah maybe because go yeah i'm disgusted
i'm going to tell you who's going
to cool off in court
years later she'll realize how fucked up
i was talking with somebody twenty at
this point maybe another twenty she'll finally
figure it out i was listening to
um twenty years yeah i was just
listening to the babies online
oh yeah what is yeah able to
drink no that's some big one just
really more able to sushi and a
man alone and they talk about ah
moral dilemmas and it's a miserable it's
one of my favorite shows but they've
had on they've had a couple of
people on because they they they have
a large idea that they talk about
but they always asked their guests do
you have a like a little idea
that you'd like to
discuss little moral dilemma you'd like to
discuss and a couple of times we've
had people that have said like yeah
i'm thinking about having an affair
on my latest yeah guest would say
yes yes yes yes are these amazing
open-hearted soul and i'd love to hear
all about that and their phone number
it's it's astonishing to me what's so
weird about it is how you say
that i think that human beings are
human beings you know
everyone's human if you get caught up
in something i understand you make mistakes
accidents happen brought up but if you're
at the point where saying like i'm
thinking about doing this you're yeah it's
like it's too chill yeah what one
of the one of the rationalization rationalizations
was you know life is short you
only go around once so if you're
feeling this thing you should act on
or whatever like that's fine
fucking terrible idea for society and also
like i don't know how you could
possibly say publicly i'm thinking about having
an affair yeah you're not doing it
yet your significant other will know yeah
because someone would tell them you said
that on the podcast you don't listen
to it what are you doing yeah
i mean i gotta also if you
feel that way about like if i'm
feeling away than i should act on
on it then you should never get
married you know because your whole thing
is do whatever you want at all
times yeah yeah never get married because
marriages and you ok here's my view
on marriage are you ready oh god
a lot of people are like see
how i let him do it a
lot of a lot of people you're
putting us in these tiny chairs but
okay pull down your pants no thank
you i thought you were
gonna make us sit here right where
your pupils um getting making it
so i've you know how people go
like oh well um i wasn't being
given what i needed anymore i guess
there there could be some validity to
that but i kind of feel like
marriage is more about it's such like
a crazy but if you get oh
you're if you're planning something well the
the most recent person everyone's the most
recent person was not in a
relationship so i guess they felt removed
from it like hey if this guy
wants to cheat then oh i can
do oh okay i understand saying that
more because it's like a little bit
low because i'm not your relationship that
it would be damaged by it it
would be someone else's so you can
say this is my dilemma and it's
not ruining my boyfriend's life by me
telling you this podcast may yeah i
mean it's not
not good but i'm saying yeah i
understand that more than a husband saying
yeah a little bit more yeah but
it it is also if you are
the person wasn't freezing so much like
it was a dilemma it's like will
i do this or won't i you
know what i mean which i don't
yeah i just feel like if you're
at that point
you can avoid it yeah you of
course you can and i feel like
even if even if the other i
don't know there even if you're not
in a relationship you still have to
consider this other person because because anything
you're hearing about that person you're getting
from this guy you know what i
mean yeah i'm so unhappy and this
and it's like i guess i'll take
your word
for it so let's have sex with
each other but okay keep it
keep going well i just think it's
like such a responsibility when like a
person decides to marry you you know
like a lot of people look at
it very selfishly of like oh am
i getting what i want out of
the marriage am i getting but it's
such like an incredible responsibility to know
that like that person's whole like reputation
and
their their happiness is like they've chosen
you to tie themselves up into that
you know what it means that it's
just such a like it just seems
you know because like when it comes
out oh she was being cheated on
or he was being cheated on it's
just like such a disruption of your
life that they don't deserve i think
that is true but i think if
you
are unhappy you should not be married
just no no no i'm not saying
that i'm just saying yeah cheating someone
for like lawyers are like you know
you're a lot of people hold a
lot of people see look at their
happiness is like it's marriages and equation
to them of like how happy is
the other person making me instead of
like and what am i bring how
happy am i making the other person
but also how happy am i in
j
general it's like look at your life
it's not like i owe my ass
i think it's i think it's unbelievably
selfish to say well i have no
choice but to have this affair this
is what i have to do yeah
in order to be happy i mean
there's a story like that in the
book as well i highly recommend this
book especially to um people who are
interested in women stories yeah let's me
not really
yeah that's what i figured i think
i think you should divorce if you're
going to have sex with someone else
divorce your spouse and then get back
together with them the next day
oh yeah yea that makes sense to
me that makes sense to me makes
it make sense to me i love
that idea actually for everyone i love
that idea why would i love is
that i give civically i love da
da da
oh do you love oh love that
idea how you were just checking your
watch but it was because it was
an email thing right now i want
to see what the date was oh
what day does it i don't know
because the hands recovering the date what
hands the hands of my watch oh
okay i understand now well there's nothing
there i think today's the third
eighteenth oh boy it is fun thank
you a rare timestamp for the audio
oh forty isn't august thirteenth behind the
ceo you know well please don't tell
you one cool speaking marriage co up
and i got married on the thirteenth
and my mom was like because we
were thinking about september eleventh
yeah forgot that
of what year two thousand one of
two know but we it was like
one of those days it was going
to show timber eleventh or september thirteenth
while we were married ah in ah
two thousand and eight so you would
have willingly chosen september eleventh zero anniversary
yeah because it has you never forget
yeah it had
to be around that time right and
i was just like what are you
going to do yeah so so i
was talking to my mom about it
and and we said oh no we
chose the thirteenth and she's like wow
some people think getting married on the
thirteenth is unlucky oh i'm like it's
better than september eleven yeah yeah i'm
here anniversaries on friday the thirteenth every
four years or more
and i guess but then my mom
i was talking to her about why
she got married when she got married
she got married on july third and
she was like well i always you
know i always grew up wanting to
be a june bride
and i was just really want to
be a june bride just it sounded
so great to me and then your
father was like well you know i
want to be a july groom
i i would be so insane he's
a real lie is that i understand
being a june bride but i hate
the concept of someone saying i want
to be a july groom
just you did but you hate the
idea of a man wanting anything yeah
yeah i'm just like yeah you get
married on the day she said my
men
i think my dad there was some
sort of like army not army but
national guard like discharged thing you know
whereas like i only have july third
shit and okay but my mom's reaction
to it was like so i thought
about it was like yeah that's good
enough it's almost june there we go
um yeah we've been really delighted when
you were born a day before their
anniversary they must have been various how
do you know
know that about me i know people's
birthday i don't know i know yours
is september six for the first time
there you go because you just said
it but now you know and me
but i'm not number twelve right that's
right oh no kevin i'm gonna make
a total wow she is i i'm
sure your birthday has been so posted
i'm sure it's been talked about ad
nauseum
kevin is frantically pointing to his mic
he wants to get onto me yeah
you wanna give me a hint i'll
give you know i want to make
a guess but keep in mind i
just said it like a half an
hour ago you did hulu oh august
twenty third yes i'll never forget oh
that's right yeah did you sit when
you were out of the room and
have a show that day i'm actually
so good yes i would have although
i was off my right yeah
oh my oh august twenty third august
cuddle i'll never forget i'll never forget
cut out anything i remember birthdays of
people i knew when i was little
i liked and really even i could
tell you like so many people from
my elementary school's birthdays darth vader um
no darth vader of a birthday i
don't give a shit
there might come a point where i
need to know that or do you
think that he was ever like the
empire's like huh okay everyone come on
he's like no i told ya want
them or don't want come into the
break room it's lord venus book
who got the cake signed the card
lord vader it's been such a pleasure
working with you i love your outfits
ah does he wash his outfits to
the guy who makes black anything but
basic
they should do that instead of roasting
people that should have character like birthday
celebrations and you can like wait instead
of roasts we should have better things
to do the celebrations of characters yeah
and someone says on stage as the
character that everyone does that kind of
thing it's like the opposite of historical
roasts were that that you take
famous characters celebrate or i feel like
roasts are are so i mean obviously
so mean yeah and i i have
a hard time well you know what
would be better as funerals are so
touching why don't we have like pre
funerals exactly where you want to show
you a funeral yeah tour yes please
oh so
so i would do i know where
we could explore so so it's what
i do over roasted peanut i had
a roast one time before i moved
to new york to think it was
a lot of fun jimmy pardo had
for his bachelor party and it was
fun to that makes sense i think
it is fun i think um i
would have a hard time writing things
for i think walking that line of
of being mean but everyone's somebody worried
about it some people were worried yeah
and jimmy was with somebody who was
worried about it right and by it
but it turned out everyone was really
fun and it was action it up
yeah yes even and there it was
even stuff that um although i got
various like you cry there was unexpected
stuff
like unexpected areas of ribbing that i
was like oh that's what people think
always people knew that about me like
man some i thought i'd kept that
secret yeah it was one he would
say otherwise a lot of a lot
of talks a lot to talk about
my anger ah i know about your
anger i thought i kept that a
secret
my anger is pretty good i think
it's cool i think it's good i
think it's i always think it's fun
when you get mad because you're saying
yeah yeah oh well you're not you
here's the thing you can never get
mad i agree i do not suffer
fools madly scary good but like i
like you i like when you go
off
as a king
off kink just like i will say
in your you didn't come to england
with us yea i didn't in ways
that you have a dough cookie i
don't know where i was i will
say i don't think i've told you
this probably oh i had my my
nasal surgery or some oh that's right
i couldn't fly i was really afraid
and i had one i had like
a deviated septum and i went with
laser
years and like and just like darth
vader i had one night where i
woke up and like i was like
had played knows i'm like i use
planning so much on your nose off
practically the over the tub and it
was just gushing in the eye this
big blood came out so it's log
of i was honestly really afraid because
i think that was like this the
clotting that was holding it all
whoa mama i just pulled out my
slow the blood is too scared to
fly because they read the news nova
pol i heard you yelling at someone
in the hotel in sheffield because i
think i had the hotel yeah and
you were like you were like screenings
really like well i think it was
bojack horace
mn thing or something i don't know
oh maybe you reading doing a table
read no no no no no no
no i might've hey man you had
to call in and do some of
those i i know you did have
to do some of those but it
didn't sound like that but mostly it
was a tie chase or lines on
bojack yeah
i want to be a horse man
with the i can't imagine what was
going on i would love to overhear
you guys when you think i can't
hear you i don't ah know if
you are mad at someone i would
love to be like up to a
wall i'd be mortified oh my god
i'm trying to think of i when
the last yeah i don't know if
i'd respect you or not like
i mean i'm saying make your privacy
like i don't know
if i heard you mad i would
know to respect you for sure but
i don't know if i would maybe
go on put on headphones or if
i would go cup to a wall
can i ask you this are you
a person or either of you a
person who will look in someone's medicine
cabinet if you go oh um i
know i know what i was looking
at i might go like really if
i want to do it it's
like the quietest thing that's ever happened
and i'll go like yeah and then
i'll be like what do i think
i'm gonna find here yeah just like
to see what products women use and
stuff like right right i just think
it's interesting like i'm not it's not
even like i'm trying to see their
pills right i'm not a doctor so
i wouldn't even know like what i
was looking at
like well we're just imagining just be
wall-to-wall news ever just like what is
this medicine cam rallies is medicine no
but isn't that usually for people like
look at oh my god they're on
antidepressant i don't know because it's never
been a thing that i've done i
assume that's what it is it drove
yeah right enough but i know people
that do it like you said
to snoop like for sure and so
now it's more like it might i
might think oh i could snoop right
now when you were babysitting would you
snoop throughout the entire house i would
stoop a little but i was always
afraid that they would know somehow or
that they had set up a trap
for me that i would not do
it like a hair across the drawer
yeah whatever like a bear trap yeah
sure the tiger bar like i
i would disturb something it would be
obvious that i had opened it right
i'm sure no one would care or
know and whatever i think i might
have done that when i was little
like when i was like a kid
going over somebody else's house yeah i've
in my memory it was we would
do it together yes i am the
friend i did go to my friend's
parents nightstands and i might have mentioned
this we found sperm aside in a
day
diaphragm it was like two things i
had no clue what they were did
your friend no no but i always
remembered it can i say i was
feeling like new it was i'll never
forget i was thinking about this the
other day about sperm aside is such
a sperm size for some reason i
made me remember that i was thinking
about this tuesday's execution but you know
my parents very religious and they wouldn't
have anything
too bad in the house but they
had i was thinking about this the
other day they had one book about
sex that was like christian and influence
informational whoa and it was up on
a high you know bookshelf shelf and
i remember ah jeff
have it had a lot of like
diet diagrams you know like this is
where shit goes but the one thing
that i remember racy book put your
shit in her shin one thing i
remember that was so funny from it
it shows was he was talking about
oral sex and it was like written
to women right and they're like yes
yes we all know the thought of
this disgust us um ah penis is
disgusting but here's how to get around
it and their advice was imagine that
it is it is a miniature version
of the husband that you love so
much that is discussions oh my
my god yeah ruins it putting it
into your mouth is like you loving
your husband so much and just imagine
like oh it'll like you know ah
i think most humans rather have your
husband would rather have a dick in
their mouth
then there's our husband that is in
it was same raisi like the gym
mental gymnastics that's the day had to
go through district instead of just saying
like suck some dick it's great to
be back you girl just figured out
imagine your husband loves vore and i
remember devoured by you my friend got
a book that was
like all about your changing body and
it was like cartoons um of like
puberty stuff and they showed even worse
than the real thing yeah yeah they
show it was a very seventies yeah
they showed um i remember this the
only thing i remember from it is
they showed three different women with different
colored hair on their heads and how
they're
and would correspond yeah the carpet would
match the drapes so it was truly
a chapter about carpi which is a
little picture within a page about pubic
hair oh because she's good like i
guess redheads redheads all have red tubes
but that's not true though i know
none of it's true know nothing about
sixers or myth i do hear does
didn't grow in your house now
if you care group o squares like
i think i got my cubes because
my insights are constantly achieved
i took a human sexuality classic college
come haha
come on or whether this wow from
the classic to when i was eighteen
i took a human sexuality and i
think it was just because someone was
like dude they show porn there i
was like that what a weirdos you're
like dude where's my porn how am
i ever gonna see this but it
was true these shows i wanna make
a trip to go see some boy
i gotta watch it with friends and
a teacher
the only things i remember because i
failed it because you didn't get it
because i just never did the homework
that i was i was like what
did tits look like like i don't
know what her tits look like like
a reverse champagne glass did you jog
off last night you failed
you failed your fire but you're buying
five from class yeah the way but
the only the only things i remember
from the class were tits they showed
a porn video and it was it
was very seventies ish
and then i remember the teacher talking
about when you say they showed a
porn video it was a poor yeah
it was not like an educational film
no it was well it wasn't like
i think it was one of those
halfway between things where it wasn't educational
but it wasn't like pure just like
fun porn it was just you know
like was it's op jones for the
object to be shown in a class
or whatever but like was the object
to arouse you because that's what i
think about porn yeah i don't i
don't remember it so study of human
sexuality
i don't remember but the other early
like they put it on to be
like and this is one way it
could go i yeah i think
i don't remember over ten sexual scenarios
this is one
the other thing he talks about was
he he talks about how um it's
possible that he goes yeah guys i
know you all want to have a
big dick but it's possible to have
too big of a dick because i
have a friend who has a twelve
inch penis and you know what he
does every time that he has sex
with someone and then he went over
the light switching turned it off he's
like because
if the lights are on they'll be
like i don't want any part of
that
this is
oh is it is it twelve inches
around yeah
oh women
say they don't want anything to do
i don't want any part of that
if i see that day one in
the other way i'm putting this editor
on this legal the hardiest segment whatever
done on the show i put on
that alright look we have on that
note do you have anything else you
want to say about sex lauren what
is it and where do i go
either way i where
my shit go okay well be right
wait oh you have some you wanna
say yes oh please do scott sorry
i just want to say that sex
is natural sex is fun but said
there's one caveat sex is best when
it's one on one i hated that
about songs in the eighties anytime they
assign about safe sex because i hate
that
i hate that just think about sex
you should hate aids instead i kinda
like it oh i knew it you
would you wouldn't you did and you
do and you always want to be
so contract will be right back
and ah back back back back back
back back wow
for a feature we call a three
cheer this one is investors inc
just like it's like monsters inc but
for investors yeah the game works a
little slow today these investors are monsters
are monsters early monsters under your bed
yes yeah one person acts as a
customer and presents a mundane issue they've
made up to two inventors the two
compete to propose the most outrageous invention
and contraption to solve the customer's prob
elam the customer buys the winning invention
okay i tricked yeah in tree any
ghee so who do you want to
be first alright i'll be the buyer
sure
hello yeah yes hi oh this like
hold on address scientists lounge oh my
god i got an eyeful i have
too many clothes on this swamp he
took all my clothes today on and
didn't realize i didn't have any so
yeah we could have say it's a
little bit early for you to walk
okay so i wasn't actually an accident
i'm literally five minutes late like
okay um can we help you yeah
put on some clothes i want to
do this thing again okay fine alright
okay i have an issue and i
was hoping to come down here to
inventors row and kinda talk to a
couple of inventors and see if there's
anything you can do for me well
yeah come to the right place
he knew something yes sleep um it's
eleven o'clock at night yeah well that's
the only time i have freely your
appointment supposed to be at eleven am
yeah really yeah you told our mess
that up guess what's already been invented
the clock and guess who invented it
charles t
peaberry charles t peaberry the inventor of
the clock and if you don't respect
that get the fuck out of the
clock is over fifty years old it's
a very useful invention now that just
so you know we are competing inventor
oh you are we do not work
together oh we're not even if we
wanted to tell us your idea will
each come up with an idea my
idea will be the winner okay mine
will win well
well you know how um you're walking
down the street just the other day
just the other day yeah we're any
day but you two are hitting it
off already i like this guy i
like the cut of your jib i
don't like this um did you know
the gym cutter was also invented by
charles db this guy sounds amazing it
takes a little bit of fiction
that's what you think the jib is
you have been highly almost time shin
nick gibb so i don't know what
i like getting a jib to college
so i was walking down the street
and there are too many of these
you know these scooters that you can
rent oh yes i do and they're
just more every day they're in my
way and i was trying to put
money in
in a meter the other day and
it was in the way and i
had to physically lifted out of the
way but there's just too many scooters
on the sidewalk these days okay and
they're a nuisance and i am tired
of having to go around them all
the time okay
one of the first one second yeah
however okay
what is your name tell him
do you not know his name i
just want to see what you i
want you to tell me what is
alright i don't like dance together my
name is charles taylor here oh my
god yes yeah you're the size of
so what if i am yeah so
the clock inventor have you invented anything
like your father has i haven't invented
anything like my father has i think
two things my own way oh okay
you gotta respect that thank you now
then are you okay and fine
are you really okay because you seem
upset i'm fine i just want to
end my there isn't don't call me
honey i don't i don't want your
your business out of three church and
out of three-tier happening going on that's
not the teacher activity all right sir
what is your name oh i was
never born with what you were never
born one yeah not even when you
were born no not even then at
the time that you would think i
would be i'm gonna call you adam
after the first man what a delightful
name yeah adam
let me paint a picture for you
oh is that what you're gonna do
i'm not sure i'm interested know with
words oh
like the other day when you went
to that meter men you had to
physically with your own hands i know
move that scooter out of the way
i'm just i'm retching thinking about it
what if you were able to command
that scooter to get out of the
way and it did it by itself
bed knobs and broomsticks whoa what i'm
propose
oozing is an invention that hacks the
computer system in the ah scooter by
means of a high-pitched squeaks remember that
thing from brookstone oh of course i
do remote controls my favorite thing i
squeeze to turn off the tv yes
why i'm adapting that principle
me to to these scooters now here's
the thing it's not always going to
get at the first time okay so
you gotta keep squeezing it and the
tweets are going to get higher or
lower depending on how much pressure you
give cheryl squeaker but i like squeezing
things but eventually if you like squeezing
things this is the image for you
wow okay well i haven't even had
a chance to pitch my
eventually you will you will stumble upon
the frequency of the scooter and cause
it to go zipping down the street
it just goes swimming down to the
end is it my responsibility once it
goes or is it just the scooter
why would it be if it hits
so i wouldn't be okay you didn't
rent that scooter right yeah there's fingerprints
are nowhere on it no you're not
even see
and you're not even you know touching
it wow and this venture is called
the scoot ah oh like mad at
it yes i love it but also
an expression of power ah i'm wrong
baffle you are the son of a
famous inventor as li yu u-m lout
t o r ooh i don't like
that okay well what do you have
honey oh my please don't talk to
me i will kick your nuts all
the way up into your neck
all the way down there from the
top of my head short journeys guys
very small fasting so my idea is
as thus
it is um actually ah a series
of gigantic big bins these bins are
bigger than a trash can and they
are on every corner in the city
really big yes and i want everyone
to throw the bird scooter into the
trash can were set looking receptacle
and it's just shaped like a trash
can like an ape like a big
yoder it's shaped like a scooter so
it has to fit in exactly because
a dumpster so a bunch can fit
in okay and it is a way
to get them off the streets so
the second you see when you you
have to have hulk like strength and
you throw it over into the the
um been okay well i do have
hulk like
gg strengths so that's not a problem
then i will have a series of
um unemployed folks who i will hire
and they will empty so they'll be
employed they will then be employed you
have to fire them then no i
will if they do a bad job
okay and then they will take the
um the skeeters out and they will
charge falling asleep what is happening here
i think it's eleven p m i'm
sorry why are you still at the
office because he knew he buried his
rolling over in his grave which he
invented he is a great i'm still
here because i thought i knew i
had an appointment today but you never
showed and i always wait until my
appointments show up really i don't go
home it's true she doesn't okay because
here
called and called doom i'm going through
a breakup do any definitely what is
called what does that mean on the
phone i don't know what that is
oh year is it for you
fourteen ninety two my dad explains that
my good buddy christopher columbus told me
that he told you that's the year
whose invention to you wanna buy well
did you get to the end of
yeah okay yeah sure it was trailed
off as she was falling asleep don't
want to tell you more about it
because you're so condescending you really are
adam to whom to her or to
both of you but but when you
come into her you condescend to me
as well wait you're using the word
whom is condescending even if
right really are you guys related or
are you married or oh my god
you have to have all the answers
i would like to know this before
i decide whose dubai where were the
same thursday are one
you're the same proud as outwork your
different facets of the same person stupid
when i was born out of parasitic
twin growing inside me that's her me
and guess what i grew up and
i'm actually not a parasite yeah it's
great now we're friends i have a
personality and everything but we do compete
with each other for inventions we we
just need someone
to be chosen because we have to
get to work you're going gonna get
to work on it right away i
thought you guys were flat out sleepy
think we're going to do we live
to invent all right well um i
have to say that i think it's
impractical to shape these bins like the
scooters themselves because even though it's bigger
than scooter it's not the most
convenient way of actually fitting things in
my house people know it's not a
trash compactor that's a good point she's
got you there alright i'll buy it
oh fuck i will you said that
she's got me said she got a
oh yeah but i'm it sounded like
to me like you can see it
the whole ring i saw you had
more stuff i can't help because we
have a close
relationship i her i know that he
didn't mean it like that and he
didn't want me to win that's what
i get for white writing
hey she's never gonna date you dude
no i know she's like toy guy
the same and seen we did it
we did it and now it is
super long well it doesn't have to
be true
this way robert remember une by the
way this is the second three cheaper
than yeah maybe but thanks for sending
this thanks uni okay um my turn
to be the customer okay fuck
just say god like that you have
to i'm coming in right but i
don't hello
i don't even oh hi hello new
jersey adventures that were scurrying about oh
it's bringing about mentions yes okay that
works for me to love inventions off
them i love making them i have
a mundane problem i need fixed nah
don't look don't look down on your
problems like that yeah maybe it's a
big problem okay here's what it is
it's okay
sure there are no one day problems
here sorry just mundane inventors
where the mundane is by the way
well i'm robert mundane yep and i'm
bobby mundane oh i will this is
so perfect that my problem is so
mundane oh that's okay because really one
day yeah we're the guys to do
it okay but we but we are
competing against each other we are competing
against each other and we hate each
it doesn't have to be long okay
but we
spend all our time together that's right
and so you know me and all
kinds of weather yeah my problem is
this it's raining outside did you notice
yes i did and you want this
to be long
i can't eat my tomatoes fast enough
oh i buy too many and i
haven't but i want to buy that
many because there's a sale but i
can't eat them fast enough then they
go smash oh hey bobby why don't
you go first alright well i have
an invention called the tube meadow wow
and what this is is okay the
average human mouth is one in diameter
three inches now one tomato
yeah i guess i shouldn't even be
answered yeah she's the one who's supposed
to answer i help robbers and it's
perfectly round the size we've made the
exact size of a tomato well what
if your mouth was three tomatoes wide
okay go on okay i have teamed
up with one of beverly hills is
top plastic sir
surgeons to widen your mouth so wide
that we can put the two meadow
into your mouth to meadow to premade
dough it i know it's a little
confusing because it actually fits three tomatoes
so a lot of people think it's
too meadow but it's actually two tomato
and they feel any tomatoes and just
schiff these tomatoes right into your mouth
mouth as long as the plastic surgeon
comes ah does his business approximately six
months before the two mayo's installed okay
and he's a sixteen six month lead
time six months lead time it's vacuum
technology you'll need to be hooked up
to a sort of a vacuum sealed
kind of situation
and you'll need to constantly be forcing
tomatoes into the tube i like what
you're talking about okay um and you
mister monday doctor whatever robert mundane i'm
a dunker of inventing he was it
was an honorary doctorate was still from
temple university i had to wear a
cap and gown yeah and delivers speed
i guess
who he was awarded that honorary doctorate
with it was on the same day
the temple owl oh
now them tomatoes we love them but
there's so many when you bite i
was exactly right i like what he
says on fair now just restate her
problem somebody might say this is the
beginning my pitch bombings sorry robert i
was very quiet during your pitch were
you suffer at one part i need
i need both of you
to shut up and i did one
of you to talk that's me of
the top one
imagine this use trying to solve your
problem of how to eat the tomatoes
before they go smoosh by buying smaller
tomatoes but you don't want that because
even though they're easier to eat and
they go faster you can't have that
slicing tomato experience yes exactly that's why
i've invented the less meadow it is
just the
the outside of the tomato so you
get tomato slices but you need more
on each sense but he said what
so you're going through channels like what
or salad so you don't do the
tomatoes like wildfire love the nothing's wasted
and you don't have any leftover and
how are you going to grow these
honey that's not my problem i'm the
guy who invents they're just invent i'm
not you throw shit out that doesn't
exist
pst and then say it exists wow
i didn't know we were allowed i
pay her tommy which is why you
know robert he's robert yes
a cursed me huh before youtube a
tomato wormhole i miss him
and then i'm stuck with your bullshit
idea when i wanted his to begin
with sorry okay gilly yeah that's me
in disguise okay now i am the
man hey
i was gone i don't want to
talk about it right now because i
truly don't want how it's going because
i know what you're actually getting at
when you stop knocking your boner under
the table it's not me i think
that's someone knocking their boner against the
door come in during your boner in
here ooh oh i'm old oh no
oh i can see oh hello old
timer how old are you oh say
maybe sixty sixty wonder if i'm so
all of seasons how are you still
walking i wonder if you might be
able to help me with the problem
i'm having even though it's quite mundane
were down for that i'm
actually a detective but i've been trying
to get into making stuff yeah and
i'm an inventor who wants to be
a detective and i've been grilling her
is that the right terminology yes he
puts me onto the grill closes the
tough and i burn baby boy i
invented it i don't know if i
mean say humans didn't know we want
to convention three we want to do
it so bad human grill for a
human girl
that's what i always say i'm trying
to branch out oh hey speaking of
branches that's my problem oh is that
what a coincidence
i live in a house where those
trees and bushes in the front of
it oh no and the trees and
bushes are very nice to look at
from the outside okay but from the
inside i can't see out on the
street because of them and so i
want the best of both worlds i
want my shrub reason trees and things
should look nice
type curb appeal but i also want
to have a clear view of the
street sure what do i do well
look i have the perfect solution for
you because i'm an inventor i'm not
just a detective you know i deal
with this button oh here thank you
i'm a person who actually does this
for a living okay i don't
don't sneak around taking pictures of people
cheating on their wives okay mad because
although i would love to god yeah
i caught makoto makoto and guess who
he was with who yes you're from
this town are you yes born and
raised
guess who he could've been with in
this town who would be so embarrassing
to be with the mayor her i
was with her and i got all
the pictures to prove it easy to
get those pictures oh that's what you
say you know what he didn't know
i was taking any of them so
how about that but my mundane problem
okay okay i've invented a solution for
this and the great thing is is
i've already
he invaded it so you can just
buy it today this is unfortunate for
me this is the half invisible shrub
that's right it's half invisible it's invisible
on one side so you can see
out into the street and it is
totally visible on the other side so
no one can see a two-way shrub
yeah to nature yeah it's a lot
like um you ever seen one of
those detective shows where they're interrogating someone
yeah this is why i said two-way
use a two-way yeah i thought i
said to no i said it you
said you said have them ring a
bell not ringing i say prove who
said it and it was our guest
oh okay look at that yes yeah
your mouth is moving your stick another
oh yeah i'm not very pleased to
be seen by anyone these are internal
use only no steal let me see
just
by me you may wonder how i
invented it now yeah ok never mind
alright what do you got my idea
is this
you paint leaves on your windows
sure they don't wanna see which side
of the window
okay look she's nine and better i
think you make it worse she's yeah
she's she's okay now
will you have you have you hire
three young men and they each hold
up leave wait i oh i'm forty
five you're afraid you're afraid of three
young men aren't you yeah yeah i
let you have them holding you so
oh they sell more paint on the
window honey i'm racing that honey okay
okay yeah three young men or is
about as old as you if you
put them to
gether and county and okay hindi and
yes king they are going to be
holding brushes i mean branches go off
queen okay
and we we stand and they will
be only out there holding them up
when you're not looking at the window
with second look up they will duck
down put the branches down you could
see everything from miles so you want
to do so this is not an
invention this is just hiring someone to
do something that was my you're telling
me that hiring people to do things
isn't an invention yeah yeah look
the phone was invented because people were
tired of hiring people to go deliver
messages to people it took forever thank
you toasty pick um by the way
my name is
by cousteau breadmaker two thousand and she's
a robot boy that she's a robot
that i taught how to be a
detective i felt my mind was made
up but that was interesting information that
might help you i invented her she's
a britain bread dough is what were
you again
bread toaster or breadmaker make bread maker
yes she was a breadmaker lucia became
santa you came to life so i
taught her how to be a detective
and then we had sex and she
took pictures of me well we did
it he calls it sex he don't
want to know what he did he
never took one human sexuality class he
had no idea what he was doing
they didn't need to never watch a
poor license
sorry my penis is twelve inches long
and i turn off the lights before
we do and i'm sorry it's one
inch wide
even even less shopping these had dimensions
no i'm sorry it's one centimeter wide
and twelve inches long my penis is
twelve inches long but it starts nine
inches inside oh god no that's your
that's your problem you should come in
with when it's not monday
alright well who you gonna pick who
you better the guy invented her oh
wow he thinks he's doing wordplay
it did seem like he thought that
i guess i gotta go to waste
rubber ya bingo even though i co-inventor
the name anyone can brand something yeah
we'll see what happens out of the
love i love love love it
you love the utah states
i was built to be supportive
oh look i did a good job
with her like we had a great
time today we're showing her look we
had a great time this is me
now this is me i'm out of
carolina me breadmaker
oh shit we gotta get back in
and this was fun it was just
fun we had a good time you'd
have a good time and i hope
everyone has a great week um i
hope i have two loris fiona upset
i think your weeks okay you think
it's okay or you hope it's okay
i think it's going to be okay
but you were talking to people that
are listening to this at the end
of the week yeah yeah
yes yes king your week was good
yes and that was your week that
should be the title and that was
your week and that was your week
that guy's title like oh listen i
want item i want to shout out
let's can we shut off some people
that send us thing yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah i wanna shout
out this was very nice chris carly
er ca r l i e r
shout-outs bore you
turn us off now i hope i'm
allowed to say his name he runs
the mat mondo mascots account on twitter
one of my favorite twitter accounts that
is just documenting various japanese mascots jet
and japan they have mascots for everything
and she posts pictures of them and
explains who they are and we've correspondent
on twitter many times i love the
account and he
sent us you're in love with him
janie if you're listening he wants to
have an affair of the heart ones
are the ones
um he sent us this ah this
bag of all kinds of mascot stuff
umm stickers and and little cowboy have
one thing you can have one thing
of course i mean it was addressed
to me but he does say i
heard on threesome you like to be
sent gifts yeah and yes send a
shit so let's why don't you go
through the bag
and pick a thing that you would
like there's all kinds of shit i
did take a lapel pin some motel
paid freak i wanted that lapel pin
i bet you did motherfucker
how about this guy you want this
key chains teaching
oh yes i'll take all of that
some chopping steady set key chain let
me see the key chain alright to
shout out um yes there was also
suicide yeah china stickers that's from a
manager or a person named dean dean
fett or is it says right today's
a dane dane day dan grzelcyk
when you're in the dane girl zone
and then we also received a beautiful
card and letter from celia and her
daughter clara thank you to everyone who
sends her thanks guys very sweet permeated
don't have to send us stuff when
you do it's nice and ah like
if we don't send us stuff we're
never going to talk about you on
but we love with our famous shout
out sexual you do you could just
send us your name
sms send us your names in the
mail and we'll say them on the
wow i love this shame because we
we did this already with rpm and
people just set to what did you
do we'd just like send us ah
just send us ah stuff like say
you want stickers and we got like
hundreds if not thousands of people we
know we're not giving them we're not
getting anything but
if you want your name said we're
giving you you have to maryland to
send us a letter and nothing else
and nothing else no letter just your
name but we love that you listen
to the show thank you for everyone
such nice things send us a meta
loss to us as soon as you
choose the sentence bibs at your gym
alright i'll hold that over the picture
we'll see next time bye
uh