sorry
three
oh and you get a boom sharpie
that sob be your red day you
most certainly are a redneck when is
he going to graduate too you are
a redneck does he know he's hedging
his bets i'm tired
sorry to give it y'all heads now
i'm just pouring yeah i'm going ra
rab day you're a redneck you're a
redneck oh quarter the redneck is he
still doing it i hope so to
me and you'll want i bet he
does like because he hosts a gay
never name him never never appear
i bet he does tomorrow cause i
bet he does like ah corporate shit
like that yeah i bet he does
like special engagement cat thing oh that's
like a good handful of okay here
and makes a billion dollars yeah yeah
exactly i like that private jets you
might not be a redneck if you're
doing that when do we get to
fly in a tragedy it um look
i phone on right i've known i've
flown a couple of i mean this
type or a char one time oh
is that what's the difference that's where
it's like you're not it's you don't
have the plane all your oh that
one person didn't own it no no
no's we were only us on there
we were with strangers okay yeah but
it was it was
i'm sure i've told this story before
no i mean i think this might
be the rare one that no i
told my sure you've told you it
was a new year's eve where somebody
said we should go to like a
new year
people just cheer they
aw
they hit the ball out with the
bible
happy new year that was a sham
equal year i got my funko bed
two fly balls deep um and you
were like hey it's the new year
let's get a helicopter
without someone eating you out of the
nile copyright by firing a baseball a
frozen rope right
um somebody said we should go to
las vegas and then we actually did
but it was not fun oh we
got on the plane and then we
got there we realised we can't get
into any hotel rooms and now it's
like oh you don't have a hotel
booked oh no honey wow i think
we did but that we couldn't get
in because it was too ur ho
they wouldn't let oh no
no so we had to wander around
the casino it was fucking misery i
hate then got it finally got out
of the room immediately got sick of
sick like i got like a bad
child elder something we were already married
and then i just stayed in the
room and then it was i'm going
oh what a great time great time
well my my experience was i was
flying for a babysitting job so it
wasn't is that on a private jet
yeah yeah it wasn't a jet right
it's a plane plane i mean there's
a difference right i don't know it
was a prop plane
i don't know what engine a p
j james private jet yeah yeah whatever
it was it was private and it
was cool to subpoena and this was
someone who hired you to babysit and
took a private jet somewhere yes to
to colorado so really the telluride i
don't know where we stay honest i
think i asked been i actually just
don't know
so the difference between you babysitting and
movie star was really there's no no
because i well there is more to
the story but you know i'm i'll
leave it i'm gonna leave it as
a mystery because ah but not to
us off but not too off me
yeah but yeah the pay wasn't there
ah you hear about the pennies guy
pennies from heaven sure he wanted to
see time fly yeah i know penny's
guy so they got the guy i
think he owns a an auto shop
and ah a where you can get
your car fixed for pennies where is
it
a worker of his who got fired
said hey you still owe me nine
hundred and ten dollars and oh so
the owner of the the shops know
what upset said
ah he gathered up all of the
pennies on the floor of the shop
nine hundred and ten hold one thousand
more second why were there so many
pennies on the fucking floor yeah i
don't know did anybody fountain my smile
and my theory yeah
and they were peanut shells and we
call them pennies my theory is that
anyone can deposit them he was crazy
he must have gone to the bank
to do this but he but he
said he gathered up all the past
so many years that have been left
on his floor dumped them on the
guy's law how many could that be
i know i'm lying if he did
that
and he dumped them on my lawn
i simply would go to the bank
and deposit that i would pick every
single penny i would pick up the
pennies and take them to the bank
well wait a minute how much do
you get coin star pie even to
babysit if you're on a private plane
um on a private plane you like
to take like nine is it is
it more than nine hundred and ten
dollars an hour because i think it
takes more than an hour to say
scoop those up ah on a p
j
when i was ok i would use
a copper magnet when i was getting
paid it's nowhere near that sound and
so if i took me one hour
to pick up nine hundred dollars i
would simply do that i was not
that long i wouldn't bend over once
to pick up hundred dollars
i don't know like nine hundred and
ten dollars in pennies if you can't
get that but let's say he said
it'll take an hour can you do
it will you do it wait it
will take an hour yeah or i
may only have an hour it will
take an hour and you can use
a shovel yeah
it's a solid hour of shoveling shoveling
pennies yeah shoveling hard weight heavy duty
no might not know what you don't
want nine hundred dollars will know i'm
thinking about can i physically do well
you can you say you can you
still don't want to an hour no
it's not that i don't want to
it's like i don't think i'll make
it no but we're safe
saying you can well and yeah okay
so it only took an hour and
absolutely can do it yeah i'll do
it
if those are the three hours you
were fighting it was funny because it's
like i'm thinking of my fucking back
yeah you're here to pay
yeah there's no question i used to
get the chiropractor if you were paid
nine hundred dollars but that guy got
their bad debts there goes all my
money if you were paid nine hundred
dollars an hour to do something it
was a regular job like shoveling pennies
would you do it because like doing
it once is like right gotta ya
know but i'm just saying there have
got to be easier ways to make
nice
nine hundred dollars in general this is
all i could think nobody know but
i know gao nine hundred to shovel
anything no no i'm saying his job
they're not so i think once it's
funny to settle on that as an
hourly rate
i get paid well dollars pays eight
fifty an hour what about nine hundred
oh my god but don't tell me
the other employees so you see what
i'm saying like just once you can
do anything for nine hundred dollars yeah
just once yeah just once you can
do anything thirty dollars but as a
regular job that sounds good out of
her for like
would you eat a seal for nine
hundred dollars she takes our oh right
just once and you can't do it
during nine hundreds and you can do
it it only takes an hour and
you could do it for nine hundred
but anyway so this guy the owner
of the shop left to left hey
that's to me what instagram of total
tissue instagram bot comments are like it
should be like five thousand dollars yeah
i mean it's like just once shovel
the pennies one hour you can do
it nine hundred and eight hundred you
want that gonna come in reply can
i do it
so he left a note that just
said fuck you i'm on top of
the pennies on top of the pennies
yeah bread and cheese and no fuck
you and so this led the guy
to weigh what did the note say
just okay
so it led to the guy complaining
you know to who will check you
know the better business bureau's something like
judith who who who settles worker disputes
on a chart but um not ah
but ah charlie fill ceo
which then led to the guy basically
getting investigated and him now a judge
much guy the the owner of the
shop okay now a judgment has come
down that he owes forty thousand dollars
to all of his employees or over
time ah fees and he never pay
so you just pay up and move
on but yeah and shut up yeah
yeah
but good everyone's getting what's theirs yeah
anybody's gonna pay them all in pennies
and they're gonna be like yeah daddy
got in i mean it is legal
tender was his okay so forty thousand
dollars an hour and you have one
hour to pick up forty thousand dollars
worth wow but you can do it
the way three thousand dollars one hour
i can do it yeah
you can do and i'll get the
forty thousand yeah i in pennies i'd
take him to coin star yes but
i'm taking houses closer from the coin
takes a percentage so i'm picking take
eight percent or something i'm not a
bank won't right yeah no well why
don't people go to a bank in
this they don't want to wait in
line i think i don't know if
you bring them no one ever went
to the bank for that i don't
think you can bring change you can
bring
change to a bank anymore a username
i don't think you can bring change
but i think they make you roll
it up you they make me roll
it yeah that's why i think you
already know the world made up already
thousand dollars rolling for me it's forty
shut off while you do pennies and
i'm gonna i usually don't do it
and i will do it and i
get forty thousand
that's right and coin star takes eight
and you must go to the coin
star alright i'll do it and the
coin sir is not at the supermarket
near you it's a couple neighborhoods forty
thousand dollars in pennies that's my whole
trunk probably you can do it okay
but i can't do it because because
here's the part that were kind of
not included so like yeah i can
i can shovel the pennies you're the
one who came up with the you
can do it but i'm
let's take it a step further because
yes i can show you can do
it entity and you can and it's
easy yeah but what about when i
put them in bags and to carry
them into the coin oh you can't
do that you can not try and
you have to pay like a kid
who's around so one of the bags
of pennies which could equal thousands is
going to him as his windbag you
are the other accountancy backs are huge
i can't lift the bags are huge
yeah did you hear about the other
penny story in the news which is
like a radio show some people with
their did you hear about the other
penny story there's this guy fell submarine
somebody threw a penny to make a
wish just remember there is the sari
greene story which by the way is
long over over time anyone's theory in
every sense of the word yes
they're all they're all okay yeah yeah
isn't that nice
cool you can tell the future now
and they're giving away all their money
yeah so the other penny stories they
someone found with their dead mothers something
found like bags and bags of pennies
up in the up in the attic
and they're trying to sell them off
site on scene i think it's like
six thousand dollars worth of pennies but
they're trying to sell it off whatever
like like what tens of thousands rare
my neighbor pennies my dad tried to
get me into coin collecting like penny
collecting and it's like so like fucking
boring and we would go to the
penny store and be like what about
this nineteen ten s yeah what about
that you know it's just oh yeah
wheat penny today's share this interesting factoid
there so there was this thing that
i kept seeing online
line that if you put a copper
penny into your vice with her asking
if you put a cabernet into a
lie down the you have two lips
and i beg your pardon to lips
okay to lip to lauer to our
petty in the built it keeps them
sticking straight up for weeks
now i'll tell you what i did
it and i did work the other
thing is that you also have to
poke you you can poke the pennies
with a needle in the stem it
is neal and skinny as a needle
and it stands upright okay okay hook
the penny and this is something florida
sue and heels with the pen they
will know poke the tulip the stem
i would need you just with a
needle i said penny where do you
get this needle huh you're selling kit
what's what if i needed first only
well you put it back so emergency
what have i tear a hole in
my elbow what i'm doing anyway that
i saw an update about the copper
penny situation and what the reason why
they always say copper penny is because
not all pennies or copper after nineteen
eighty
they're not copper anymore so i'm just
labouring but my pennies were old if
you have an old penny it works
yeah and by the way most my
pennies not recent really interesting interesting why
do you have penny i have changed
i use cash some are you inspecting
them well i'm what i am now
because i'm saying i only want i
i am now i only want these
good ones okay so i don't remember
for this commercial and i think it
was for nyquil or something barbara you
up yeah rile you up and she
finally goes i am now yeah so
drummer this commercial ah rays i can't
see raise the seat
can't reach the pedals lower the seat
no watch
these two different people or one person
so just you when people go in
the duck boat yeah oh my god
it was freaked forgot about that quote
it was it was it should be
the ship and i would have been
cooler in my mind is the duck
boat honestly i might go on one
of those tours this summer on real
just so you can say yeah hold
on a second let me yeah let
me dream this out no but there's
the one architecture
a tour in chicago is really good
roi it's sixty minutes on the river
but you've been you can do it
yeah you can do it and this
fan you can afford it and you
will and you can yeah if you
had a job and your job you
know those those game show tubes that
blow around the the daniels and all
the money yeah the booth yeah the
booth yeah
i think one of those for a
no you shut up sketch and it
was really fun they will get these
at a little kids thing i went
to recently like a little carnival oh
and they had these little papers swirling
around the guys were all grabbing really
q so my my question is if
most guy was cute when i was
in i don't know fun for i'll
show you okay there's a gif it's
fun for three minutes right but say
it was your job i was in
there for nye
thirty minutes and you can do it
did you get nine hundred would you
get
five hundred dollars let's say it was
your job and you got to keep
whatever you grab but you had to
do it forty hours a week
would it still be fun oh my
god i'd be so mad you got
to keep with it
i mean do they just keep pumping
dollar bills
i want the job she's the one
dollar or you feel no isis i
mean like throw hundreds in there everyone
is that your is that your pay
yeah that's your idea whatever you kept
fuck forty hours a week to forty
hours that's a good job though like
you know benefits like there would be
sometimes where you're like i just need
a break and you would not be
grabbing the money
me but it would feel like wasting
time and wasting your break you know
it ain't it'll take place in the
boot yeah and you'd just be sitting
there with
yeah time to leave the edge time
to grab like leslie on your phone
yeah you'll be on your phone okay
but but you'd be tempted just to
be like grab behind the air i
really like scrolling you could do whatever
you want just making a call
yeah i think if it was minimum
wage you get paid minimum wage no
matter what you do in there yes
you get it's like a waiter you
so you can sit home wage
you can sit the whole time if
you just were in a bad mood
right because people are looking at you
if you aren't you and people with
more people will yell at you if
you were late to work i know
everyone in a regular life no one
can see you you're just in a
dark room doing this the only light
is inside the booth right so you
can see the dollar's right and no
one's watching you and you end there
and you're sure you there
or no cameras and you're like why
is this happening they won't tell you
yeah you wanna get paid or not
job market is rough so you guys
are saying you both do it i
i would like to be in charge
of it so you just want to
yesterday and you want to be the
person who's ever yeah you'd want to
be manager i would never raise my
voice what's what's another weird job that
zookeeper zookeeper ah the jada delivery repairmen
to
wait so a delivery man repairmen yeah
oh yeah referred every man delivery repair
man what do you what are you
repairing deliveries boxes broken anything with tape
so you're repairing the boxes yep
what don't you get hey someone bringing
something in a bag i can fix
it put it in a box did
you ever get a styrofoam container mean
it doesn't squeak right to squeaky that's
quick enough hey how about that padding
that comes in sometimes things and you
can come up to ten you get
and sometimes you get melted in the
sink with the water that's cool
er well yeah yeah we're supposed to
be using styrofoam anymore like everyone while
it comes in a box that i
get oh man somebody putting peanuts and
now like are you happiness but like
you know no i find that's why
i like those dissolvable little things they
can put into the sink like in
my farmers dog for example i get
farmers dog in my farmers and it
comes with this bio de gr
edible multiple delicious styrene know what
and you put it in the sink
and they turn the water and it
goes away yeah i like this like
the raccoon trying to eat the cotton
candy used to clean it and it
disappears would you do a human zoo
for money collapse like a slaughter hi
fi i would like you sit in
the zoo yeah it's oh wait no
i would run one oh you just
want to be management yeah
zookeepers to humans your hunger for power
is actually kind of sickening and i'm
just gonna take care of things yeah
that one i'm gonna be one until
job it'll be weird to have a
human zookeeper at the human zoo yeah
that seems rather like this like a
slaughterhouse five things like sad actually zebra
in a uniform yeah holly like zebras
it's pretty funny
for his uniform is it's stripes no
that's a skin buddy that's his fucking
skin so it's like no it's light
and take it off and when he
goes musically a horse in jail you
dumb dumb
there's prisons where they still use that
uniform one horse i love a jail
this area so retro i love it
you'll love it bro do you think
the prisoners feel that way too like
ooh they got the throw batting yeah
i know that's a drip what about
the ones where they they die the
uniforms pink just had
a kingdom that fuckin guy no that's
it's in real life paddington two there
was a guy that did that in
real life was served them like ransom
bologna and all that was it in
texas i forget where oh in paris
don't say sweet error made by a
little bear yeah and then it ends
up being charming it's very charming and
paddington two not so much for your
life do you remember the the furor
when somebody don't feel her
oh yeah i remember remember
do you remember um ah when patting
into it a perfect rotten tomatoes score
yeah one hundred oh yeah and then
somebody gave it like four stars know
why did they have to do that
yeah exactly that's what anybody said penny
wasn't to some asshole yeah is a
fabulous film it really is really not
sponsored by him now and we can
b and i'd love to be in
paddington three but i think it's too
late yeah yeah just joy for you
yep
is there a unit i'm still in
the mix because they're a unit what
are you in it or unit i'm
pat out here you name it and
ah alright we have to sit back
okay
nah we're back we're back we watched
pennington one after we watch paddington two
because we'd never seen it ah huh
that's fucking great i mean great no
it's great i think i could do
of course is i think you watch
an order because i think you have
to watch an order because everything has
to escalate in a sequel and if
you watch it backwards you might go
like oh that was a little more
tang restraint we watched it front words
we didn't watch it backwards oh wow
sitting facing your back to the tv
next to each of us we were
yes while we were trying to oh
okay your homes they try to stick
chairs indiana jones and the and his
dad style and his dad style
it was just the dogs ne alas
what to say terrible father day but
all good drag up he shucked i
mean never stop sucking and he never
apologized i know you're talking about indiana
jones's dad i haven't seen it since
i get the new indiana jones is
coming out indian this week or possibly
next in indiana new and you haven't
revisited
did all three or four of them
okay you're right i'd need to do
this now yeah okay yeah yeah i'm
gonna watch them all i hate watch
the ah crystal skull since it came
out this pie is not getting shorter
hate watched her hain watched hate i
hate going to watch it together i
need to watch it again before this
what's the crystal skull it's scary
you're not going to like it oh
okay i'm too scared oh i mean
well do you know have you heard
of a skull this stuff that's underneath
like this part of your flesh i
don't have that women ah
just have so many little faces that
are delicate and feminine and our faces
are just all cartilage we don't far
we don't have bones
um yeah i gotta i gotta watch
it i mean it was terrible there
were a couple of parts i bet
i bet i would find it i
find that revisiting any movie like like
that kind of movie is always a
little better than i remember it being
yeah i guess because i'm prepared for
it this time although i watched ah
star trek first key
contact the other day and it was
worse than i remembered it oh man
i think that's i think that's considered
the best one it is i really
like it was it was a little
slight after i watched it because mainly
because i've been watching so many episodes
i thought was directed really well but
yes it just felt like frakes a
yeah frakes i don't know i mean
i've
ever watched star trek's can't um yes
i watched start chanting newcomers about it
no i haven't watched enough to not
be able to do that but i
just can't do that um you can't
do it or we on an episode
but you can do it or it
was you can do it that's a
yes we had to pay you nine
hundred dollars tony and i had you
and i was on your podcast yes
yay
yeah right well so think i might
have done alice wonderland i remember if
i did that but you did back
yeah yeah um so i've watched a
couple episodes um they are actually kind
of funny like the one was that
the baseball one that i watched with
you that's not my favorite episode foreshore
but i found it so weird that
i like couldn't believe your neelix person
right what does that mean
don't don't don't just say i'm something
there's a there's a character character like
voyager who is just an insanely unlikable
character yeah i love him
you're a ga or neelix tie yeah
nicole loves ga nicola those little jar
jar i would love to send we
loved we loved all my best i'd
love to see you in a jar
jar type role i would love you
i mean you're always in a ga
type or like i would like to
see a larger role in me was
that right you big fat dude
and yeah it probably looks like a
tail
like an avatar yeah i've never seen
their penises but ah yeah they will
they have braids that they stick into
the what oh an avatar they have
brains they sticking to white into a
hole that's how they sex that's how
these
i can't believe what i'm hearing there's
so much there's so many dumb concepts
in the avatar universe that really bothers
me that's what's so i don't have
any am or why why does the
hair create sperm
who said it did that and why
isn't it on their flyer in the
break going the whole wow the goes
in the hole or else it gets
the hose again
yeah avatar made silence of the lambs
silence of the levator or else it
gets the hose to get as a
thing that we say a lot in
my house i think we say a
lot here he's threatened any with it
no we just like say when you're
keeper and a wow we say it
very casually because anything begins with it
does this right we're talking about machinery
i think it does it is because
i mean like you guys have fun
what a great we do have fun
i got to say should we swap
houses for sweaty days let's wife swap
not wife swap but just how swamp
just how swab oh yeah i do
that right here
what thirty i don't know jesus
i don't know that's a long time
a long time to be away from
you it's a long time to be
in someone else's house and you're not
that far from your own yeah that
is annoying but you're not in another
place you can you can drive by
and say hi to your house can
i say we took a little weekend
trip to lake arrowhead wow there's day
and it was so delightful and
it was we realised it's our first
family trip without going to visit family
or more wow we got to like
just have a family trip and it
was so fun it's very nice holly
enjoy did you go in the lake
did she just look at the lake
did she hover a bow we we
none of us was not yet actually
actually did that yeah none of us
went into a lake
because it wasn't even like arrowhead you
can't go into it's private privately yeah
you have to like at all the
houses drive in la you can't just
win there but lake gregory is fifteen
minutes away and i guess you can
go to that but we decided but
like your right is the star of
the show they call it like arrowhead
you said you went to like i
did go there i logged it around
near a private plane
this i hate this look it's i
hate your trip it's beautiful i had
a great time the cabin was great
it was a bad taste in my
mouth okay were you on the lake
though the cabin could now oh because
it's private but it was um we
walked down and we were trying while
the shops are on the lake so
he was only like a couple restaurants
we were on the lake in those
moments oh yeah but then when we
were
we're we went on when you go
into a shop like bathing suit shop
put on a bathing suit and jump
right in the like look i probably
could i don't know i lied look
you know you can't do it i'd
be jumping right into a pile of
huge fish there like like two feet
long to ate the fish that were
fish swarming by the swarming oops i
say something they were sm
army warming they were all staring they
were right by the edge people were
feeding them with um real food if
you get and some food you think
so cagey about i didn't know it
was in the bag but his breadcrumbs
are some of the bag
and there were ducks and that they
were all swimming with the fish were
huge video tell me you don't know
what kind i don't diagnose fish was
it in stores or was it what
did this make the grid it's on
the grid it's an ice slide we'll
just see about this go to lake
arrowhead post you can see the the
big ass fish at the end that
sounds fun how long were you there
three hours three
three nights anyways really fantastic it was
really relaxing it does some i don't
often do things like that how do
you do do you need to bring
a lot of coochie mah we brought
so much shit and there was still
shit that we didn't have that where
you're like flickr i didn't bring like
collies bottlebrush cells like i'm going to
just wing that and then i was
like i really wish i had that
yeah but i know how much spf
this could a bottlebrush take-up it doesn't
but it's like i was in the
glove when i was putting in so
many things and and and it was
kind of being noticed by mike that
i was putting oh okay you're bringing
a lot of clothes for a few
days being that i'm like you have
it it's everything that we could need
and then i at a certain point
okay i'm not gonna bring my shampoo
i'll just use whatever they have i'm
not going to bring my best friend
asked me is this
your swarm of fish oh my god
what a disappointment there's like four was
a little more fearful more intense wasn't
i irl yeah yeah yeah yeah higher
out yeah i always a million five
nine i was warming the one fish
one fish to jump down the water
don't you come in here and then
another fish had this private
how about this one here how about
this one that's how big they are
bitch
let me see got me those her
ducks she looks she thinks look at
j show big they are it's anything
on the waters a fish i want
anyone corroborate i'm sorry but you're crazy
that that was the smallest fish i
don't mean to gaslight you because he's
saying ah and everywhere there are no
fish there uh
um okay whatever it was great time
that's so fun did you have a
nice father's day oh yeah it was
your first father's day ah yeah it
was good it was i mean she
could stand to be a little more
demonstrative yeah considering the day analogy now
okay so she wore a shirt at
one well honestly though here's what i
knew to tell you about how sharper
your
raising her so whatever she doesn't know
is on you so if you have
a rival honor about fall yeah yeah
yeah why didn't i do the yeah
yeah um another shirts were so cute
you both had jersey operates a shirt
was very adorable yeah it was good
we just went to i looked very
cordial together
yeah no we we she's been hammered
i was like an agreement that's good
for this i go yeah i think
that's sick of the graham please do
it for the gram with a click
of the grab um what are you
putting on your lips right now well
sort of bomb well i'm putting on
yeah or is it just magic mafia
or what would i call tca
she's
elevate your critics so the voices it
actually is putting that you're asked me
what i have to tell you what
i am putting on my website because
it's funny that you said what are
you putting on your lips right now
right
it's it's funny yes it's called the
bomb for nipples this is a oh
like breastfeed why are you doing this
because she wants to suck on nipples
interesting this is disgusting but it's a
really good lip balm your lips and
your nipples are not made of their
same know meters are two different meter
too
for me like ma oman i didn't
want to bring this up but you
said you said a specific question that
i had to but um yeah you
know what that was a specific question
why are you coming to say it's
like one hundred and isabel if any
lady out there is interested in fingered
by isabel ingrid and isabel
jesus christ
you all are discussing and we've ruined
paul there's even a shredder early episode
episodes to the point where you are
saying yolo yeah gusta yeah everything got
ruined yeah
planet we've created
this post covered post covered world is
supposed to true world even though coven
is still in the world it's true
but covered ruined our brains didn't it
yeah probably that was a world yeah
yeah as canio believe that happened that
we just cuckoo didn't do anything for
a couple years it's ah remember how
to look at directly yeah it is
remember how like wonderful it was when
you saw someone in person during that
yeah yeah like like we would be
so giddy to see each other now
yeah fuck now it's horrible
i've gone back to despising the human
race yeah good
anyways i don't i it's reciprocal i'm
not a massage therapist no great play
by moliere i'm an anthro yeah most
people anthropoid oh my god i had
i keep flashing i had the weirdest
dream and i think you guys were
both in it oh no where no
no it was good we went to
this
place as a big group of us
went to this place that's like are
you familiar with meow wolf yeah no
it's it's a really fun interactive kind
of installation art yeah the thing they
have one in is in in in
you like me to go on yeah
it's gonna say santa fe isn't santa
fe yes marfa texas ah ma
alpha i believe there's one in vegas
and one in maybe in colorado but
it's a real place to she flew
on the pga it's it's true
it's really cool and it's really fun
and really clever and interesting oh cool
and in the dream it was their
mystic but like times a million it
was like almost like you were taken
to another wild but it was very
like dark and kind of a black
lady aesthetic and it was very trippy
when were you felt like your own
hugs this was a dream that i
hugged
you miss that part of it
i'm giving you facts about meow wolf
and yet you're talking about a dream
because
you don't need to give me facts
about me oh he knows that i
was on the ass have you been
there oh oh you've just been sold
to to his co
just slow bush oh he's realised wow
but it was like i don't want
me to throw up i it's it's
one of those dreams where i want
to go back to that place
original joyfully made you throw up trying
to throw off right now i'm trying
oh it kind of does that
for me so what was what was
our p o v in this dream
we were having fun it was yeah
we're having fun it was kind of
eerie and kind of scary but it
was like i want i want to
get back into that dreamland yeah how
do i do it i love that
feeling we gotta do something like that
is that i mean what if you
are able to lucid dream which people
will go on and on and on
about i won't shut up are you
able to program where you're gonna go
before you go to sleep i that
would be great if you could like
set a program because that should still
my brain somewhere yeah you can probably
like you could i bet you could
focus on it as you're going to
bed and like it would actually help
you go to sleeps focus what do
i have to look at a penny
but yeah there's gotta be a copper
penny do you only remember the dream
i'm an eagle do you only remember
the dreams that you have right before
you wake up because that's er do
you
well good but haven't you had dreams
where you felt like they lasted all
night yeah the entire time you were
asleep like it feels like a really
long dream like a story that keeps
unfolding and with chapters with chapters with
verses there's a bible there and a
great preacher who's telling me that things
can be different yes
yes if you and i think you
might have died at a certain point
you know you revived you wait am
i did oh right now no what
if this was your heaven oh how
a little compliment us that would be
so sad you never see janie are
always just doing threesome
she hasn't died yet we haven't died
yet we know we're all dead does
everybody come here with a yeah everyone
we've ever talked about on the podcast
ends up here i went to a
concert last days yeah oh yeah what
was that love and rockets um they
were great and who is better rockets
probably get the edge
yeah i think they're pretty cool yeah
they're great um but ah so legitimately
one hundred percent of the crowd was
standing
and there were seats are there were
not seats there were seats but every
like a minute they came out everyone
just rose to their feet with venue
the ace where we perform many absolutely
are all stomping grounds that's right on
sand the whole time we do our
show we don't either
and i felt good i wish we
were i always feel kind of bad
for like standing up during a concert
because i'm tall and i go like
oh i wonder if it's okay but
i was on the aisle and
i think it's fine or whatever but
yeah people will everyone standing when you
get any religion and there's no way
i can see if yes i stand
how it goes that's the thing if
if if it's spotty i will always
sit right and i also have a
rule of concerts of like i don't
get mad at anyone for doing whatever
they want because we're all there yeah
absolutely you know absolutely so i've been
at concerts like
we went to john legend one swear
some people were yelling at teens for
like dancing during the show so i
think that's like a whole big sample
it makes sense to john legend show
now sit down what are you even
doing here this is for us but
so three songs in i get this
tap on my shoulder and
i turn around there's this like older
long-haired grey haired hippie going do you
mind moving over so i could see
and i i i i think to
myself what's going on i look behind
and he's sitting down he's the only
one in the higher class side yeah
and he's gonna able to see if
you move over and so i go
like like what he is that doesn't
make any sense it by the way
i was i was over a little
bit over like say the plane of
where i
should be because otherwise i need to
stand on a like bump for the
aisle which was bump for them which
was uncomfortable that you had your reasons
because what does that mean the boom
you know the but there's like a
little bump of like a separation between
the aisle and the where the seats
are does that make sense yeah where
the carpet is like rick carpenter yeah
now i got you
it was like a hard but yeah
if i were to stand here and
that now yeah you me but i
went okay sure and i'm i tried
to be accommodating i moved over um
and stood on the bump which is
uncomfortable oh um tough and then during
the two hit songs i suddenly
they get shoved and i look behind
me and this old hippie guy is
wildly maniacally dancing why
why from sitting down and being angry
that he could barely see to the
drugs kicked in i'd maybe be me
and i'm waiting for my shore and
then when it means i'm going to
hit you i'll tell you when i
get up but until then get out
of my way and he's just flailing
about
and like with no and so then
i was like with wild abandon with
wild abandon and i was like oh
why was i feeling bad about this
i just did what i wanted after
that because if you're gonna first of
all if you're going to be crazy
i will say this yeah i don't
like to stand at shows i don't
either but this was yeah it was
only ninety minutes but if everyone
stands you have to stand to see
and spit sometimes like depending on where
it is i might take a little
break and just sit down there and
my little cave sure i do that
and sometimes i sit on it i
sit on the seat that's up so
i'm like halfway yeah i'll do that
someday yeah yeah what i don't get
i don't i don't quite understand it
because i entered i guess i
stand the music moves you yeah to
stand if you're gonna seize the little
savage breast as well but i mean
people sound like now we're all just
standing we paid for these fucking chairs
yeah what now we're all gonna give
y'all internet to the show whereas if
you're just standing there listening to music
there's no especially for like a loud
rock show there's no
no i disagree yeah i get totally
disagree most of the time i sit
at a show i told yeah well
it's like but they they're they're bringing
the energy the the band is but
so when you do a show yeah
are you fine if it's a totally
silent crowd that is just sitting there
judging you
you want them to give you some
energy back yeah and they do and
there's something yeah we were doing and
they're sitting down
you are only exasperated but why doesn't
the band just want to hear us
laugh
why can't we just be so funny
she said and laughed old why did
i laugh whenever i would be dancing
yes what if comedy shows and rock
show swapped audiences thirty days for thirty
days you can do it confusing would
it be they place on da wow
never goes ah and then we're like
stupid jokes and they're like
well we already have that unfortunately that
does exist already alright we have to
take
amber back and guys what if we
listen to voicemails we have like so
many i love voicemail i don't like
when my voicemails claw now listen let
me tell you something we have a
phone number and we're allowed to because
we're all
grownups yeah i mean my mum said
it was okay and yeah and i
got my phone and and and it's
red and light up and it's like
oh grandma and i had my own
voicemail i mean
you know what else my family hates
it and i call them nine hundred
numbers and i learn about sex
what if you called nine hundred number
eighty it was like i'd like to
learn about tax whoa slow down we
don't know what what these terms mean
i do walk with my hoof oh
my god guys i'm getting a new
kind of spam email know that's like
hey
hey i really want to meet you
and then we can i can show
you my nudes and then we can
start going out or whatever and it's
like it's a billion different addresses it
just sending out bcc emails
gcc's it started
it's from slough dot com and they
send it all sluts or business like
a thousand people with a similar email
address to you you must be i
can't see any other email addresses that
because that's what used to happen right
yeah you would you'd see like but
i'll still get stuff like that where
it's like you went hey guys to
best buy and then you see that
it sends like anybody who's emails yeah
similar and now these people are like
we should do bcc
decent thing to do it's the least
you could do yeah but it's it's
so let me see i may have
one i can show you because it's
been happening since it started saturday
and it's been like twenty a day
since then i bet i have a
new one right i bet i bet
i have these in my inbox somewhere
slutty you mean i guess i guess
i kind of did save those slutty
my stone yeah here we go
ah this is from sarah buckingham and
heroin buckingham classy name if you want
to write to her it's s r
a j a s d six nine
who oh um and hey if you
put a sixty nine in your email
your down for whatever that's right and
at least sixty nine
this is afforded message and the subject
is i'm always wet thinking about you
always and this is a bcs i
went thinking like a murmur when thinking
or she's wet i'm always wet thinking
oh my god allow me to rep
allow me to wow me too but
so funny allow me to wrap my
bread yeah allow me to re
baghdad alone rigged whole lot it's like
you're gonna like it allow me to
wrap that juicy beef using my thick
bread
thick white bread
the least sexy horns in here
oh that sick bread oh yeah are
you already getting around pick makes me
say let's make your wildest dreams come
true and then main bowler i know
you want this so message me tonight
oh my god people respond to that
i guess it but yeah it works
i got this thing it's
crazy yeah yeah it's creamy to me
the one the the ones i think
the work are the ones like blackmailing
you the masturbating masturbating one and and
i have all your videos of what
you jerk off to send me two
hundred and fifty six dollars now bitcoin
yeah by the way i did watch
vanderpump rules this season and they
keep showing this clip of this guy
james who's an english guy on it
i don't watch that show okay he's
an english guy he's a d j
they all met being waiters and waitresses
out at a restaurant and he's a
d j now and sexy unique restaurant
pump yeah sir and so they keep
showing this clip from a previous reunion
show where he takes back his ex
i'd say oh he takes back the
night his ex fiance gives him back
her engagement ring clay any dose he
grabs it and goes that's a bitcoin
whoa
that's slang where to find that's a
bitcoin a bitcoin that happy and that's
our bitcoin did jaso he's done it
again and lhasa was a bitcoin ted
lasso is a bitcoin kind of ted
lhasa was a bitcoin with that show
b s poppy
miller if instead he's a soccer coach
more if he's if you are a
bit cohiba bitcoin instead of a soccer
coach yes it would be ten times
below and make more sense because everytime
he's talking to the team i'm like
what and if it was a bitcoin
and talking oh yeah yeah yeah thanks
to moore's yeah yes that bitcoin would
be so positive yeah okay
ah i do what the fuck i
just close play and listen if you
wanna if you want to call us
and you wanna ask our advice about
something or another reason that i don't
know that we're qualified to give any
advice so if you want ask us
advice sure you can call us at
hag claims eight
it's great alright let's hear from juliana
margulies yep i hope so do mine
ma lauren my name is juliana i
like something funny that i thought you
guys might enjoy on the most recent
episode paul says that he says had
claimed and unclaimed freight theme but in
my area it was always on claims
frais ou
and i work overnight on my lunch
i'm listening to the episode and i
thought i was in a hallway by
myself and i go head claims a
it turns out i was not alone
and i got to look pretty fun
wow love you guys thank you bye
yeah i love giuliana thank you giuliana
thank you for working overnights whatever that
may entail
hope you get nine hundred dollars yeah
it i hope you get to grow
money from your history and do it
yeah um but do you think those
people were those of the people who
saw her and never left she thought
she was alone well i guess she
just maybe she's saving the rest of
that for a different podcast she calls
into you tell them about the ghost
she saw i had just broken up
this yorkshire
cooling other podcasts yeah she brings you
like they'll care about this part okay
juliana i hope that's not the case
i had a dream two nights ago
that i was ah at someone's house
and i put on a belt and
like flew me into a chair and
i was like this is a haunted
belt and i was like trying to
tell on you're trying to tell ball
like i was like
the belt just carried me over here
it was like haunted this is haunted
and then people were really busy because
they were describing the menu of what
we're about to eat i think i
have a hunter
i think i have a hunted bell
because it keeps not fitting oh well
maybe it's like george clooney prank bell
it'll fit one day and then like
sixty days later it won't fit and
that's crazy but that was just frank's
right yeah making things smaller taking the
wardrobe in an inch every whim that
time to do that i don't know
i guess how
does the wardrobe and the fact is
they don't that so jillian is sunny
on juliana morales did like oh my
god i learned yeah thanks being george
clooney um i loved you in deep
rising or whatever the fuck it was
called oh shit she was negotiating okay
that's right um it sort of sounds
like chain of fools didn't yes i
think what she's saying
claim but slow it legit free made
with no ice what's yours exactly what's
your situation visualized conundrum but what's yours
by john le carr
why is ah unclaimed freight and hers
was claim fray and then she said
hag themes hey that's chain changing yeah
fools yeah so i'm using a different
but i think she's slightly different somebody
is allowed to dum dum da da
dum dum dum dum dum let's hear
another one
but thank you julian hello scott paul
lauren tis pick j here j i
listened to you guys while working i
work at a camp and it got
me wondering
you can camp oh well okay the
roughest it you've ever done oh great
question and i wonder why i wasn't
evening pleasant you know what is funny
jay and i like camping has come
up before camping has to come up
before just because just the amount of
time we've spent talking yeah last time
though you
we're in a tent that was like
on the ground how twenty years ago
so you were seventy
so now you're thirty seven
but i just was saying because we
were in lake arrowhead and we were
in the forest and i was little
creeped out by it at first because
it was so quiet but then i
liked it but i was like i
said to my you know what i
don't want to i don't ever have
to go camping just see her where
i never ever yeah yeah and then
he was like i don't like i'll
go with someone else like he's like
he's like i'd rather go with
it was so inside because it's just
like you know go with a friend
who's excited yeah i don't want to
do that i have tried a couple
times when i was young it's really
like maybe i could have a little
fun but i think i might get
a little too freaked out more than
even more than the discomfort more than
the discomfort i think it's the sort
of like laying in the middle of
the open that i don't like well
the animals are there they've had enough
with us yeah but the orchids are
rising there like there's animals that are
now in places that they wouldn't be
yeah ten years ago and now they're
just like openly walking around like who
gives a shit yeah there's not afraid
of anything know at all i don't
give a fuck they don't give a
fuck and then the ocean
it is now sharks are attacking boats
orcas are attacking boats yeah cats and
dogs living together
that's a big twinkie
but yeah the i have not camped
in that way since summer camp when
i was a child for me must
have been some sort of oh church
thing yeah well like you being in
a tent yeah because i like my
work camp but it was in the
cabin yeah yeah we had kept we
we had cabins and we would go
out one night and sleep outside
did you have no chance did you
ever like oh wait we have tits
we just slept sleeping bag no i
don't like that that's like a charlie
brown cartoon it's not you ever take
a ten out to your like backyard
i always wanted to but we have
not had we did not have that
sort of thing what sort of thing
a tent or evacuated not have a
chance we did have a backyard and
i always wanted a treehouse was really
the thing oh yeah
treehouse seem like even today when i
see it in something i don't think
i've ever seen one in real life
by the way like an actual in
a tree house yeah yeah yeah i
feel like casey wilson has one yeah
um my dad built a clubhouse for
us which was essentially in the we
called it the alley but just in
the side
the side yard that didn't lead out
to anything where he's far wouldn't shit
but he he built like a clubhouse
which we then you know the only
time we would ever get together was
just about figuring out who was president
who was vice president who's treasurer and
who was skyler president of my club
we've talked i've been the treasurer yeah
our clubhouse was the basement and the
secretary
we have the worst job because you
never had any money so the treasurer
never had to do any although there
i think there were talks about like
okay out of our allowance forgot about
the shrug i was the secretary like
chip in money for something for our
allowance let's give ten percent of it
every week and then we can do
something fun absolutely we would do that
attention to where it was like and
we did it a few times
it was like hey put ten percent
of your tips in here and we'll
all go to disneyland so cool they
were like disneyland trips and stuff like
that noise i was the secretary of
my school student council on fifth grade
wow i ran to make a speech
she voted secretary whoever wants to do
what you're basically just like i liked
writing things down i ran your you
in writing this entire time i know
i've been right
in mine everything we've been saying oh
my little piss pigs who want to
buy a book i ran for student
council president was a humiliating defeat oh
wow like it wasn't it was more
like later i was like why did
i do that i know i look
back and like that was a lot
of effort yeah i was on student
council though
which is i got my friend elected
to president like i was his campaign
manager short you are like his ah
whatever the fuck i can't figure the
guy's name ooh ooh carville carville yes
we see the campaign manager for probably
for clinton yeah i saw that movie
ha kind of show but
um but what i noticed was everyone
put so much effort into doing these
super long banners that they would decorate
with paint and yeah and you're i
never would go to them because they
weren't it was always just like okay
whatever like you would eventually yeah they're
too hungry and eventually your eye would
gloss over because ever
no one was doing them yeah so
all i did was i xerox hundreds
if not thousands of just if a
million sheets if not hundreds of millions
if not just sheets of paper that
said washington lincoln and then my friends
last name wow and wow staple those
is all over the school and it
was really eye popping and eyecatching and
everyone was like like paid attention to
it that's really interesting do you think
there are any student council are you
being sarcastic i was like what if
i knew it sounded like that what
if he really had achieved such heights
as you designed for him
and he was the first student council
president on mount rushmore
well he was expelled by adding a
fifth head believe he was expelled by
the end of the year will wow
p j wanted to know if like
if we camp yeah and would you
camp again i would i wouldn't i
we've we've talked about actually during covert
right before covert we had a whole
trip planned that you guys were supposed
to come to
in montana we were oh yeah where
we were going to and it was
sort of like glamping but you got
yeah yeah and so we just didn't
do it but it would still be
fun to do yeah i might do
it i mean i somewhere between i
think i could handle any glamping i
could definitely handle i would clamp i
wouldn't go i am har somewhere between
that and absolut
route like hiking you know wrapping it
kind of thing i would do if
there's something in-between riot and camping i
would do that that's what that's what
i'm like stamping i'm saying that
clamping damping because that's between c and
d alright well sos f e amping
pham ping ou know that's a little
about when i come to montana i'm
okay with vamping
alright let's hear another word day thank
you j p i came looking he
said his j j gina jeder and
pelley keep closing these keep closing the
window by the way as of this
recording i'm just back from philadelphia where
i met many people who identified themselves
this biggs and now it's the normalization
of it is making me uncomfortable
valley it's becoming real comfort yeah it
backfired um but i also want to
say to the people there were people
that waited after the second show on
saturday and i came out and i
was i was burdened by a bunch
of shit that i had to carry
and so i did not stay to
say hi but thank you all for
coming to the show and i'm sorry
i could not stop ah sounds fun
he's
a good guy folks
go back on the highway dylan here
and i know we all do that
call and cute name should be mister
peacock i'm curious if you could rename
each other what does call things scott
in lawrence names should be what does
scott think paul and
ointment should be and what does god
i was gonna forget that one understand
what he's ahead of me his pig
out
loved it yeah what do you think
our names should be
wow let's see you got blue hat
over here
god him i'm also wearing a blue
hatch and that's what i'm talking about
that's getting complicated for both she's like
blue hat
i could see scott's name being
richard richard y richard i could see
you being rich like richard the third
type or a poor reared know you'd
be deformed
in that scenario i was i would
be deformed you would literally be a
richard the third time gonna keep my
name
and lorin aha i can see laura
and being a diane oh you want
to see with that name yesterday and
i was thinking of a nice names
my first crush was dying wow and
i was thinking about steak next year's
steak diane
oh wait i thought it'd be i
don't know but i thought it'd be
a good before and after for wheel
of fortune steak diane keaton
do they guys i'm thinking about one
clue yeah maybe that's one for that
they can use it if anyone hears
this is so patchy jack is leaving
the wheel of fortune i know we
should do it the value of us
together probably gonna have ken jennings do
it
what does that other guy who likes
to allow those the jeopardy guy got
back in the mix and was like
yeah yeah jammer check everybody everybody let
me tell you it's takedown wait i
want to give you your names okay
but i'm like that is it's a
dish of pan-fried beefsteak with a sauce
made from sees the season pan juices
sounds good it was originally cooked tableside
so
sometimes flambeau aid and ah so i
must have had it and it looks
pretty good why do i buy my
if it if it used to be
served tableside i must have had yeah
no i'm reading ahead so i was
like right that i had this when
i was in london it was i
just saw somebody i saw a baker
the baker baker so yeah there's just
cooking so um
okay so your name your name okay
let me think if i didn't know
you and i was like oh there's
like i i like to think the
way
okay you would be just talking to
me you would be
hold on i'm working i'm working okay
ross as a help if i turn
around process yeah
philip philip o can see it was
okay and your name sir
is sam
exam come on you see that short
for samantha smith who remember that show
yeah i do samantha who um i
don't feel like i could be equal
to doctor you're really fighting against that
huh i'm not i'm not trying to
fight really bumping up against a hip
bumps me okay so then i'm gonna
say a new name for you okay
your name is dilip
okay this is good fill up until
yeah no up until you actually like
i can see myself with new guys
like bonk into each other when you're
calling our lie
how's our names
wait did you give i know you
didn't know yeah um
or val okay or
your
clapper pluto oh my god please to
meet yeah turn musical yeah it's it's
it's simple peto it's the sound of
like rain falling in a yoyo blubber
people
peto what do you think yeah i
love it or bow or vo or
villain mama veto yeah yeah and then
what would your name be oh i
have to give myself a name that
wasn't part of daniel okay i made
it part of the deal i like
to make deals
and dr poo
so you've gone to medical school asking
this doctor porn watcher
dr pimple popper oh okay can we
go
do you think there's someone a doctor
named dr pimple popper who's like that
told by your doctor people like see
that's my actual name
and not a doctor either the first
name is doctor yes i work at
the bank counter penny and watching people
put them in roles alright we do
have to go low we do so
remember tie claims eight if you would
like to send us a three-tier send
us soon do that on the next
episode send a steak diane by the
way yeah
like to send a steak diane in
dry ice do so yeah and um
i said oh my god well i
usually have served tableside coach name usually
it gets cooked tableside and so i
probably had it and if you'd like
xmas table go ahead yeah sounds a
little bit assembled
and so listen if you wanna send
us a thresher write to us at
threesome usa gmail dot com and send
us a fun game like a game
you and your dumb friends play love
and then lauren is threatening to put
this very underwhelming video of the fish
up on the freedom usa and i'll
be that's that's
where people can find three to view
it i'll be i wanna clarify the
listeners not dumb it's their friends who
are dumb yeah yes yes um i
want to say i have a show
coming up on august fourth dynasty typewriter
noise it's an improv show and i'm
i'm it's gonna be a fun big
fatty notes fun and funny cross because
i know that i'm gonna put together
a group
oop that's stupendous and my time a
terrible reason for no every time it's
really fun this time have even more
fun because there's gonna be more people
can be really fun whoa i want
to tell you something yeah sunday july
ninth where are we in history right
now you were before that where before
that variety tokyo where we're we're into
july
lie at this point no oh then
i don't want my show you can
still announce it oh it's fine it's
gonna save the date it's august fourth
of july ninth lodge room seven pm
variety tobia is going to be great
we have great guests fun line up
don't miss it and then august twenty
sixth portland
and we're at the aladdin theatre that
show has been selling well and i
have not done any promo for it
amazing xo oh so get those tickets
what's the eleven theater it's a wonderful
theatre in portland you have to like
rub anything to get in there yeah
yeah it's it's a lamp okay let's
pause was a little weird yes no
you have to go to this old
curiosity shop
shop on one of the shelves there
is um an ancient mystic lamp you
rub it and then there's a bouncer
that says what's the password and then
the genie tells you the password whispers
in your ear there's sometimes where you
get nervous and in the bowser's like
i'm fucking lets you got it and
then the genie shows you to your
seat oh nice i was like oh
she's kind of doing
a lot though because every single person
yes okay it doesn't take a while
to get in yes so plan is
forty eight hours early
um and then if you want to
hear look three visiting on the twos
every tuesday were yeah i'm releasing old
episodes right in the feed and then
if you want here at free episodes
go to cb world or ah stitcher
premium and that's gonna do it for
this episode loves it it loves her
it gets the hose again yeah
yeah guy
uh