three
yeah
oh middle doors and turn the lights
down low
yeah god i feel like when that
was happening on live on television yeah
the baby turned them scotty maybe we're
indoors american lifestyle no yes that you
and i were saying that to each
other a lot i feel like we
were bringing some bells anytime we always
eat another oh yeah yeah maybe what
i'm doing yes this is the overlooked
doors
i think it was almost like a
rick roll kind of thing yeah it
was trying oh i have something important
to tell yeah baby lock them doors
and turn the lights down low
ah you guys we got some gifts
oh you know do we want you
to the gym where we knew you
lauren united what i think that's before
we knew you when starting mccreary was
on american idol before you knew actually
write that to be before scotty mccreery
and after scotty mccreery be smc yes
big big
sucker on campus yeah big sucker man
campus do you know sucker my campus
big sucker mike does anyone come from
a region where they called lollipops suckers
yeah sometimes yeah but we didn't even
be only thing we didn't call it
we the closest game was the dumb
duns dumb
mdms dum dum suckers um i think
they advertise themselves as suckers on the
remain bank lollipops no bank because they're
banging loudly sometimes or those know it
but that's what they give you at
the bank
thumb dumps now they give you money
i know that i always got the
i always got the flat lollipop with
the bang hops safety pops with the
link above
safety paw high ac pops have a
loop for a sticks that you don't
hurt yourself and choke and like stab
the stick into your blood book have
a loop i've loved stared tello such
a turn around oh there's nothing on
this guy so one guy don't want
a time he turns around one five
mio euro scott i'm not gonna lie
shit every guy ever i look what's
right next to it a dum dum
all right i'll turn around here i
go oh okay it would have been
funny or kevin view i'd take it
into why are you not clicking on
them kevin you're just hovering over the
load and you got pissed a smarter
guy
why would you not want a loop
instead of a stick and you could
hold with your one thingy yeah safety
pops safety pops really have to yeah
brian saf t pop were that many
people puncturing themselves but i mean i
i have to say i never liked
the stick i didn't like
eating it i didn't like sticking it
down my tongue or in my throat
kicking it down my tongue down my
on my own why are you sticking
it down your throat you to deep
throat welcome to three of mine paul
f tompkins hi i'm scott harbin and
i'm lauren laccase
i understand we got some gifts we
got good people i mean it was
i didn't mean around people send us
some present i am excited and we
each got one this is for you
scott okay she learns passing out on
volo sees her beautiful little car say
given to us and labeled to each
of us when it's a picture of
a fox what does this fox say
what does
the fucks say alright we're all opening
it up i think i got these
are blank cards with really huge maybe
the artists and seven they sent sta
oh these are beautiful these are beautiful
my anniversary is coming up i'm just
gonna repurpose this so yeah nine eleven
o nine fifteen
you see it fine spray it fat
che de roget that's thank you for
che de roshi love your daughter marie
instagram and dock huh yeah they're wonderful
hearts thank you so much they look
hand painted they're wonderful thank you very
much this one's like a ice cream
cone but the ice cream is the
world so you
could eat the world like jimmy
it didn't mean jimmy do lazy girl
jimmy eat world jimmy do we do
eat jimmy dewey's world i have to
admit
lauren yeah you were telling me before
the show oh let's let me say
this i want to apologize you guys
mon mike
i was fifty minutes late to record
today five zero in case five zero
heard one five it up up up
up ah that's a lie huh
oh and i wanna play this right
i'm five and i'm very sorry i'm
very sorry budgie zero she also said
that they learned not having it it'll
be making i don't care i don't
want your apology and i'm going to
hear it i feel like we should
not do this do what have an
apology don't do the show
things seem bad like wow everything showing
ruined everything's good no laurence good getting
you know the vivid person is going
to make art of us and at
some well then why didn't they because
they're gonna do it later oh it
says links for lauren lucas fox for
paul f tompkins wolf fur
scott thank you for kooning airwolf oh
that's oh thank you for standing watch
a you demaci i hope jeff overcome
onto well
what were you saying i had a
story to tell well you were telling
me beforehand but you are you saying
that i had a story to tell
you would know if you have a
story to tell i do yeah it's
about ah about yesterday oh well hit
us with it do you mean the
movie oh and this artist also sent
us a book okay okay i'm done
now um ah
it's not about it's about yesterday the
movie no it's about a did you
see yesterday the movie because maybe you
would want to tell a story about
it if you saw it and because
my story might be about it and
i don't even know because i've never
seen it oh this is interesting yeah
let's see if okay yeah this is
generally shum hold on if there's a
movie you haven't seen any store you
tell could potentially be about it's true
so let's vote at the end of
our story whether it's about the movie
yesterday absolutely ok so yesterday i had
this experience of it she said yesterday
i leaning towards it made a hit
song that i had never heard of
i think she's doing it she's doing
it first time out of the box
it goes a little something like this
i'll never go to give you ah
doors in la
jacka damn you did oliver
enroll you been able to sleep by
the way congrats to brushy one string
yeah completing his cane start a heroin
was donated oh yeah i make a
confession i had i kept saying i
was going to sign up for the
for the ah jingle here and and
i kept mentioning like
said you did sign up for it
like i'm making no yeah for my
well like i said it like that
like it was a done deal yeah
yeah i couldn't get a deal together
now i kept like making reminders for
myself and they kept falling falling through
the cracks and then on monday after
it closed i was like fuck i
forgot to do it so can i
still do it yes you're actually accepting
i believe she'll accept
because he's going he's gone over the
top i guess i could elect up
listen to that myself you alright but
i want to donate i do it
i do want to know of course
but when i want us on his
pay yes and we want to thank
all of you if you are a
freedom listener and you would go to
russia because of us because you heard
him on our show or we recommended
that you're very grateful i thought it
was so
cool it felt so good that we
were all able to do it together
i really feel like my heart is
warmed like this guy wants to make
this thing and it was it wasn't
gaining traction fast enough and then a
lot of time and we just came
let's do it for scotty mccreery now
we've got metal doors and dirt and
dirt lane around boo
alright so i was gonna tell was
that i went to a workout like
i went to a place i'd never
been for an exercise class a gymnasium
it's a boutique pilati studio and i
don't want to name the place because
i don't want to drag them but
i also don't want to cross streets
though no but i also don't want
to but i also feel that the
name is really essential because it's a
huge part of the theme of the
place
oh well can you describe what the
like a sanctuary donald's play place yeah
it's a big place and really whenever
you thought you'd ever you want in
there okay it is a place that
is like can you describe the feeling
you get when you they want you
to think you're in europe oh okay
it's a european kind of and you're
oh okay yeah okay you're not got
it your nice continental it's trans yeah
beautiful yeah yeah you it's decorated okay
so i saw i use an ah
an app sometimes to work out in
different like studios you pay like a
monthly fee in the open and you
can just go into studios can you
okay and this is not bad for
them but can you
do you have to go in just
on one day or is it that
month you can go to this place
or zone know any you can go
to just go to any up to
three times depending on your oh interesting
this great it's great yeah i mean
i could say what it is should
i they don't spawn yeah what classpass
i really like it i used to
other cities but i'm traveling so i
can find a place to work out
there used to be in when i
was going to school in santa maria
there was
a gym that you could pay a
daily rate to like if you ever
went and i loved it and then
i went to when i when i
moved back here ah i went to
gold's gym and i was like couldn't
i do what they did over there
and they're like no because it's like
their whole business model is getting you
to pay for something you've never doing
right um so this place i've been
you said right
you are patronizing me i think i
just wanted you to stop talking oh
okay got it that's how it read
to me okay done
so i saw i've seen this place
pop up a handful of times and
it's new and it's like ah felt
like special compared to the other places
i go and i was like okay
i'm going to try this one today
let me tell you i mean it's
a commitment for me to try it
because it was like a forty minute
drive to forty manic in the morning
that's less than what paul
yeah really classical and the class is
fifty minutes which is how many minutes
you were like oh okay oh right
but that's a ninety minute commitment there
and then forty on the way back
yeah we're talking like an overdue already
laid back but it was like thirty
million it's two hours it's a lot
of good time credits just do an
exercise class when i could go somewhere
closer
so already i know i'm getting really
flush your heated about them already i'm
i'm like but i'm kinda excited yeah
hi to tell sir and i am
immediately upset because i immediately know i'm
in the wrong i should not be
here it's not meant for me mining
this analogy yes
should not be participating in this environment
the employees are wearing these uniforms which
i posted my instagram story which are
direct like a pink dress and a
pink barat a small hard hat who
caught it right you know like ah
it's like a fashion but i don't
even know your safety bray like it's
like like
attached to a headband or symbol making
a ball as well like thick little
nipple on the top was it a
boo it was a tit
and i was immediately like a horn
oh please like i really was like
this is so corny like i can't
spin or corny
that's one that's so corny it made
me horny don't be forlornly we're going
to borneo yeah it's pretty free um
and i really wish i was kind
of like a lord and then they're
like you know the places really like
szekely decked out where it's kind of
like ah it felt like a nice
hotel like it was trendy and had
like la
lamps like light fixtures are trying too
hard as that way you don't like
it but already i was like you're
trying way too hard i'm like i
also feel like no one here has
ever been to the country you're trying
to make it seem like you are
in right now and then all the
women came in oh hey yeah right
too they were not my my my
people
meaning the women taking the class yeah
and they were really um how are
they dressed they were always there matching
sets and all their you know they're
like matching broad top and the pants
like i own shit like that but
ok
but it's like not the point of
working out to me is not about
how i am yes it becomes clear
that it matters because we get into
the room that i meet the teacher
who gives me the limbus hanczyc i've
ever felt it's literally like it was
like i don't understand people shake hands
if they aren't going to put anything
into i don't you try anyway it
stayed that way yeah i think i
much prefer
that too the hard handshake that i've
been getting from people lately i like
where they're squeezing my hand and i'm
go out like literally like well there's
a middle ground but like i don't
like what a normal handshake it made
me feel like i'm like a a
woman going i'm a woman and she
was like i'm a real woman like
it was like yeah i'm definitely dainty
i'm gonna dainty the fuck out yeah
and so i didn't like
that and then i i didn't like
the conversation the women were having because
they were like one one was in
germany and then the other one was
like ah
germany is just like america like it's
like it's just like america with more
pretzels like you could be in washington
for all you know like it's just
like nature and she's like it's really
pretty like she's trying like makeup because
the other woman had just been there
oh yeah and it was like she's
basically negating yeah person going i went
to germany i loved it oh yeah
that sucks yeah and then we get
the exercise class and they start filming
them
rooms is this feeling you do traveling
from room to anteroom know is two
and then we get in the room
and they start instagramming while we wait
to start and it's just me three
women who are together and then some
other woman who like doesn't speak the
whole time it's probably more on my
page of how this sucks but they
were like filming like we're here we're
working i couldn't believe it i know
that everyone does
that on their stories but i've never
really watched someone go into it when
it's like you're in an environment where
this is unnatural yeah you've seen the
result of it yes yeah are they
all lifestyle influencers they might as well
be my style brand or whatever they
trying to yeah that's what i got
i thought they were like one girl
just got her mba so i was
like this she's doing something
but like but she was filming herself
working out in the mirror and i
was like why so then they're doing
that and then i'm definitely in the
background like grumble at a w n
b a w m b o i
said to you mba oh you did
i thought yeah because i said nva
correctly the letters are so no i
didn't scott didn't correct anyone the listener
i'm just telling you this i'm choosing
you i'm just saying
just your accusing me i don't like
it i'm sure i was like
i'm accusing you of being late
um okay and then they're filming me
i'm not therefore not filming no good
purpose but i'm definitely being caught in
batches small space and i'm not happy
looking so you're like a background artist
i did great background work and then
they were doing the class then this
woman starts filming herself in these big
mirrors they have that are definitely like
i kept hitting my foot on there
like first of all there's another thing
i'm too tar was so big you
kept hitting you it was an angle
it was like a gold framed mirror
at an angle leaned against the wall
and my machine was really close to
it and i'm tall which is also
they should have been taking into consideration
when they placed me there like it
was a whole thing
and i was too tall for the
machine which i've gone to many parties
classes and they will give you extends
and like different things that make the
machine work for you oh really yeah
i'm just but i kept not being
able to do things and the woman
like thought i was not capable and
i was like i'm too tall and
then she would be like not just
lean forward and i know my legs
can't go further whatever the teacher was
horrible then the woman starts filling yourself
in the mirror and the teach
here goes do you want me to
film you for you and it's like
easier that way i'll just like shoot
it for you and then the teacher
takes the phone goes and one two
three four she's continuing to lead the
class while filming filming somewhat everyone yeah
this woman's story or whatever this doesn't
feel like a serious workout it was
horrible i was so mad and i
almost left the second day
started filming before we started i almost
want you know what i'm just gonna
drive up my upcoming losses and leave
because i'm just so mad that i
was paid trip all the way here
and like i want to work out
so what have you ran home that
would have been worth it
but anyway really early i was so
l a and yeah i was sick
i don't i just can't imagine filming
myself when i work out because usually
i look like shit i don't want
to see myself on zero but um
and then i start working out you
hate being seen in wet clothes i
know you really love you yeah i
do scots thing
in a sense as long as i've
known when we go back along like
clothes are wet half the time god
just don't take pictures of me as
my clothes are wet will you please
tell me you can't tell
oh i have wet blindness
have you ever like witness that like
we all do stories and dumb shit
and that's fine whatever but like have
you ever witnessed it in a moment
like that where you were like oh
wow that was totally unnatural or like
it just came out of nowhere i
have and i am surprised that i
haven't actually i mean i've seen people
taking selfies and stuff but i haven't
seen anyone narrating themselves in that way
yeah and the y yeah yeah i
do think it's funny when you're driving
and the person behind you if you're
looking in the rearview mirror ah or
the person next year whatever is just
has a normal face and then suddenly
they get selfie face and they start
going oh yeah he wants we'll take
a stuffy and and then the minute
it clicks they there it just drops
yeah and they look so sad and
they just look like ooh god now
life it's sad but it's also like
a get it and i do all
the same shit but like there's something
about them and we feel really yuck
and then i also had a moment
the other day where this was like
a positive version of it where i
was driving up beachwood canyon where they
you could see the hollywood
i'm really well on a lot of
people take photos there it's filled with
people thinking you can get to the
hollywood sign from there so it's so
if you're walking along that street
tourists of various countries are constantly stopping
going excuse me excuse me how do
you get up to the sign yeah
and it doesn't go directly to that
but they i started crying because i
was so happy for all these people
taking a photo from the hollywood sign
and then i was like this is
just sweet like it's so nice they
came here they're posing with their friends
oh yeah i was cool so you're
a lunatic yeah i'm crazy i know
there's no rhyme or reason to how
my feelings about anything i used to
live on beachwood and people would get
in the middle of the street to
take pictures would i lived i can't
remember the address but for time james
back to kitty corner from each other
meow
really did you know each other yeah
we were dating what was the survey
it was so great hurry to keep
an eye on you use like oh
well you know i'm different now
um but it was yeah it was
great it was great we can watch
each other oh yeah that's cool and
when you're first dating can like go
home and like change clothes and exactly
jail take a free meal
this is what i deserve this i
almost i almost moved to v to
it what stopped you that scared of
the beach
oh that's what she's oh too many
people stopping me to ask about the
hollywood's way but you are gonna say
people take pictures in front of the
well because the street yeah curves around
it's dangerous it's extremely dangerous pretty busy
street yes it is and here we
go i'm too nice talking about any
particular street in twenty years even like
david spade post a lot of stories
of people
all in beverly hills getting in the
middle of the street take a picture
with palm trees like it's not even
like there's something you can see yeah
these nuts to get in the middle
of a busy street what you have
you have like when you go to
another country and i had a little
child too i had a child love
to do and do often course in
england i have this
if you have like other country invulnerability
own way yeah you know what i
mean where you go like well nothing's
gonna happen to me because it's like
almost the opposite of what might maybe
my mom would have where it's like
oh go out everything is scary yeah
such a coward show grade is so
spineless it's no um but you know
what i mean you have just sort
did this thing of like i'm on
vacation of course i'm going to die
in my home state yeah everyone everyone
knows that i'm on vacation yeah everyone
knows i'm on vacation nothing will happen
i'm going to die in in my
deathbed i would die in that all
states yes of course i'm not aid
an england diet yeah gotta be so
awful to die and like outside of
'em
yeah and your last breath sort of
non-american ah no just that your family
would have to deal with that it
sounds really complicated yeah yeah that's how
they fly you back on a plane
every problem okay yeah because me do
you get to fly back to play
and you reply with the luggage you
get to meet the pylon you get
to be
the parable of the pilot meets you
meet the parents yeah they put wings
on your rabbi on your corpse can
you milk me greg oh boy getting
your milky to be fuckers ing to
meet the little fuckers little fuckers and
you get today's joe black
is that was part of the meet
the fockers universe i would meet joe
black yeah if all the meat the
movies like meet the stupid they're on
the same university i'd like that yeah
that would be great yeah yeah by
the way we have to vote on
what on her story it's over right
that's right oh what do you ah
i've sucked know know whether it's part
of whether it was about the movie
yesterday
oh yeah okay oh lord did you
take your headphones off for yeah take
your headphones off i haven't seen the
movie yesterday oh okay but you know
when i say hi but i know
when did you see it yesterday i
feel like i know the synopsis of
the film yeah and what the story
that she told i don't think
lyons lines up exactly into one with
the movie there were some words that
were very similar she used the for
sure she used a those have to
be in the movie yeah so somewhere
in the trailer i think that part
of her story was definitely about the
movie where she said nah she's sunni
and i think it's i think it's
ah you know i think she dipped
in and out though because then
she would follow it up by saying
like jim and i don't think there
was a gym in the movie i
think it's parallel thinking that other stuff
i don't know he never wrote it
seemed like a rip off to me
it seemed like she was wow she
was we might have a hung jury
here
you know you see i'm gonna say
whip em out
imo whip em i'm gonna say hello
my name is whip em i was
gonna say that her story was not
about the movie yesterday
this is a tough one for me
because i've seen the movie
ah i watched every single minute of
it and i never dipped out to
go pee so i know pretty much
i could answer any question that you
have about the movie zero oil detail
you have zero questions good that works
out great but um i think that
when i saw
the movie it was about everything that
she talked about so yeah ok what
you're saying the movie was about her
story she was in it too but
you're not but but that's different than
her story being about the movie you
see yeah and come to think of
it i actually was just following her
around and watching her i don't see
a movie i think that's what you're
thinking yeah yeah guys guys hi are
you almost done lauren yes no i
think we're ready to vote oh hey
we are ready to vote okay i
haven't even voted yet i vote that
your story
was not about the movie yesterday i
concur it was not about the movie
yesterday imposed to be no okay it
doesn't matter either way does mary though
it doesn't you don't win anything better
there was anything i don't win anything
i don't lose anything but i do
not born to sing the blues about
anything literally nothing changes could you
do something for us though now that
we were so kind as to vote
on your story
maybe turn them law center and i'm
like oh that's what you want me
to do maybe i'll let him know
during the allies down low along a
northern voice imo
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back
we're back we're whereby what is the
region where people when they pronounce a
word ending an i n g they
make it like een insane like what
like time we were talking about um
you know ah whereas that i was
i was walking somewhere
what king phoenix i don't know sure
is there i think when i was
a kid i thought it was a
california thing because the first person i
remember being aware that did it was
john ritter on three's company c from
california i don't know anybody lived there
i assumed he was because i was
a child here
where is john ritter when you grew
up you put aside such childish things
i didn't realize he was from her
was born in burbank oh wow oh
that's right because his dad was tex
ritter oh i don't know that yeah
they're very shape famous acres a third
generation show biz wow i didn't realize
wow john ritter was wow
forth his middle name was john ritter
was one of the first celebrities that
i cried when they died like i
love you i felt really young i
loved for how long five hours no
no but it was so shocking and
horrible and then they um did a
really like a beautiful tribute to it
on the show that he was on
that time do you crying tears yeah
oh yeah he was on eight million
ways to say goodbye to my daughter
a simple rule has come on eight
million ways to god i gotta stop
you guys stop pulling it over pause
strings you gotta stop call the string
scott
you're right i'll stop pulling all the
strings i'm sorry guys why was i
pulling all those strings yeah you gotta
ask yourself now you got um but
tex tex ritter was a was a
cowboy singer yeah what okay well the
singer yeah reminiscent what were some of
the oh he's oh no oh ah
you beat me to it
um what what ok celebrity deaths that
have affected you the most yeah go
that's one oh my god phil hartman
was a big one oh yeah because
he was so grim and we were
at mister show when it when it
happens and so many people knew him
yeah and just that
circumstances of it were so oh it's
nothing but horrible yeah john candy was
another one i was really upset with
john candy for some reason i did
that one didn't affect me as much
as i've really liked him and love
sctv and all that for some reason
i was just like yeah princess diana
was a crazy one i think i
might have told this story before but
i got to meet her i don't
know his story
i might tell kevin you told me
i know the story i don't know
don't look at paws and bring a
ball don't look at polls we're just
looking for kevin but i feel like
we talked about it on a podcast
but it was not this yeah i
probably said it somewhere i can't maybe
i'm sponsored or something tell me tell
me tell me oh my where did
you meet her i met her right
near my house when i was ten
in show in chicago yes she came
to meet with the president of northwestern
university which is an evanston and she
happened to be stopping i don't even
know we knew she was gonna be
at a certain location so we all
like a swarm of probably twenty five
people however there i was ten or
eleven
and when you into princesses at the
time or the idea of princesses well
i definitely loved her and everyone at
the time everyone like thought she was
the coolest person i thought she was
the bomb dot com so cool and
i admired the world family and it
was like a big deal to go
so my friend and i went and
we waited outside and she came
around and shook everyone's hand and i
took pictures of her with a disposable
camera which i'm not in i have
the photos of her which is cool
yeah nobody amazing if i was in
the photo yeah how crazy without a
bin but so it's like no proof
that i was there but i always
remember what she wore and you could
even google it she was wearing a
mint green um like so you know
suit and skirt um you can put
in like northwestern university or your pictures
online of this no other people's pictures
oh but she wears charlotte northwestern stuff
but there she is bottom right there
there she is she is wearing a
mint green so what i want wrote
an article called why was it so
strange that i met princess diana is
this about me
is this about yesterday was clueless what
a weird that headline
and then it's peace when she when
she died i was at ye rustic
inn o erst there which is a
which is a dive bar in ah
in los feliz and i remember it
came with they had a tv in
the corner of the bar um what
was it called ye rustic oh yeah
yeah
yeah and when it came on the
news they interrupted whatever to say that
she died they were showing the news
in a bar no they were showing
whatever the tv show was interrupted oh
i see to show it on the
news you've got it does that make
sense they were saying they were showing
the news and they interrupted the news
already knew it's different we as different
news what if i was yeah we'll
be see eruv
apted nbc news guys what if i
was in one of these photos like
there's pictures of crowds oh are there
you are but it was like a
smaller crowd than that in my memory
but maybe you know it will be
fun yeah you eat ten year old
lauren is that you she's the same
height that zach you if honestly it's
possible there could be a picture of
that isn't there
it also could be you i mean
you're you're in this line somewhere oh
this is not to think about okay
i'm gonna research that later okay so
it comes on the tv this dude
at a table nearby jumps up falls
to his knees and says oh my
gago was joke or no oh he
was completely serious wow k and he
says he's said why is it always
the good ones wow i liked him
then he sat back down with his
friends and he was like anyway
yeah well pretty much because he instantly
he was like oh and dodi fayed
he's a good kid he's lebanese you
know ah then i hear i'm saying
there's gotta be like top three celebrity
deaths of all time he's already ranking
yeah yeah of like how surprising it
is or how like unfair it is
yeah wow that was a horrible death
though because so avoidable anything like that
other right yeah no extremely grim yeah
yeah happening i was in san luis
obispo when that happened and went kind
of went huh okay revisiting the richard
nixon presidential library of course us know
he's in yorba linda oh sure yeah
yeah some connection assembly obispo i don't
think so i'm going there soon for
the first time oh let me tell
you all about it louie so yeah
you can say either way oh i
don't know i've never said it out
like i said wow play wrong go
to gum alley
is that a male oh that's there
and spend thirty seconds in it okay
gum alley think it's it's an alley
where everyone just sticks their gum on
oh are you fucking kidding me ah
yeah is that no i'm not is
that a real guy we don't know
i'm looking forward to oh get that
off the screen that's fucking dumb going
there thinks oh no look at kidding
add to it you work
that's horrible you're gonna take gum off
of it and put it in your
mouth maybe put it's the best kind
bid what if the bottom of a
table was a wall are you going
to to in it are you going
to hearst castle what are you doing
are you going to madonna stay at
the madonna i'm not i'm seeing it
um well you know i hope it
i'm not gonna say when and where
i'm sorry i don't say it but
it's it
looks nice and i'm excited and someone
will show up just like you did
to princess diana yeah i think that
was legal or business or pleasure pleasure
my exposure let's let's talk offline all
about it i'll tell you all the
feels
have any recommendations i don't know anything
about that area i just kind of
have heard from oprah that it's the
happiest city on our who oprah was
the oprah winfrey yoga studios formerly known
as aura no shoots from her birthday
wrinkle in time a wrinkle in thai
brothers using a wrinkle in time
but i watched like some folk one
show or she time everyone was so
happy there huh
we'll find out why i think the
break the celebrity for one for me
one of the weirdest slurs or okay
so the first celebrity death where i
didn't feel like i mean yes it's
you remember adam and eve are still
alive and watching no able able died
he was yeah cain slew abel yes
ah forgive me sorry kane c
he slew him is that the past
tense of yes it is kingston labeled
king slew abel um on lucifer i
played cain and yeah oh that's right
i saw the able trapped in a
woman's body changes good right yeah please
watch episode of the sopranos like lee
won jae cool yeah he was always
such
a creep that no wonder he got
out yeah and it was like so
horny i'm horny man morning corny man
i'm a horny corny i'm going to
bologna yo man um the first death
celebrity death that were i didn't think
like well yeah of course there because
every celebrity death including john lennon even
though i love the beatles as a
kid they all seem so much older
than me yeah it's harder chat under
even though john lennon was forty wasn't
he that i just was like um
oh yeah old people die you know
so but then the first one that
i remember affecting me at all was
roy orbison because i'd gotten
really into roy orbison and i just
seen him play like a few weeks
earlier maybe and so that one was
was very shocking just like i was
just next to him because you thought
maybe we're gonna start friendships yeah i
tried i made the first move i
went to a show i just like
pretty woman
i walked on by
um lauren is now so not interested
she's back on her well it's almost
it's actually almost urgent because my mom
was about like buy tickets for our
show that we're doing in ah well
we could use it no no shy
trish trish i say hi to wear
every time i never hear any word
messengers yeah we'll find out and then
i come on don't be
withholding the next one that i felt
affected by cut to six years later
under death i hope i hope there's
ten of these and then cut to
they canceled barney
yeah so i'm just gonna talk about
this already does celebrity cancellation effectiveness um
byway is can sort of pin in
this motherfucker because speaking of cancellations that
affected yes
we're not far from the netflix building
yeah and there are stone row there
are people protesting the cancellation of the
oh a oh come on shut up
and i on the way here shut
up late as i was at the
stoplight i managed to carry a picket
sign i know i snapped i snapped
a photo i was up there
oh it that's good yeah i did
a counter protest oh wait mas go
away but cancel keep your kids or
follow what they want oh well i
saw one person with a sign she's
looking at her phone she's had a
sign over shoulder boulder head said save
the o a um hunger strike day
nine that's only affecting newsweek or this
doesn't make sense let go protest something
real you're going to spend your outsiders
so many things right now i mean
everything is ads already show being cancelled
his help us tell me hey thing
you go go to the big agencies
today five ga matches the protest something
real it's just a little the restaurants
are using beyond meets no brothels his
restaurants are using bow
this looks like a kobo later we
are we protesting them for using beyond
me is kelly huh
whoa
alright so the next celebrity death i
was affected by was the chick filet
cow
who's the one on the billboard father
lawrence chikezie these cows know kurt cobain
when i was twenty fourth's mainly because
i had it wasn't like john lennon
where he existed before i existed and
so as you know the one you
don't yeah and you didn't care about
it was someone exist after you've existed
yes
yeah and and we were you know
around the same age and height of
fame and end of and the fact
that that he did it himself to
all of that combined was just like
oh god you know i moved to
los angeles the day that they found
him whoa i heard the news on
the ramp and i'm like cause i
heard
it on the car rate hey man
to make room for you in a
hurry i was in the car and
i heard on the radio on the
way to the airport wow
yeah i was there i feel like
that that happened to you that we
were talking about in the car or
something on this tour i felt there
was some death or some big event
that happened right when you move you
got married maybe i'm mixing up it's
like right when you moved i feel
like yeah i don't remember i mean
i was a big event for the
rest of the world i was married
and everyone had to accept the fates
that's right and i was already married
to you sorry everybody but you're not
married to me i emerged as someone
who's married to me wow that really
worked up i feel like it was
a thing where did they find him
in the morning because i feel like
i was listening to k rock here
and kevin and bean and it was
everyone was very somber and then i'd
go kevin and b
yeah they were both somber and then
i went to work at olive garden
in cypress california where i was working
and um they would let us listen
to the radio in the kitchen and
they were just playing like continual ah
nirvana songs but ah the one time
that they were playing the radio in
the kitchen was the o j chase
went right by us
it was i oh yeah yeah so
we were likely when bias on the
ninety one freeway and so we were
listening like oh my god he's coming
he's gonna be can we see him
is he going to drive through the
kitchen yeah he's gonna murder all of
us as well wow who's next on
his spree um so lorne any celebrity
deaths that you were
um i told you a couple wuji
well you said princess di di so
it happened shortly after i met her
right and then um john ritter and
who else not sure um i feel
like those have been some of the
ones where i felt really it was
also i was like a little younger
and like realising what it same thing
is you that like someone could just
die or something right someone who's like
well genre yeah john ritter and in
princess di have the same thing where
it's like oh they could have lasted
another forty years yeah for young people
yeah yeah i my favorite actor was
peter o'toole and
when he died i had met him
once yeah it was a story about
signing i he he released an autobiography
that he was gonna do three um
three installments of and the first one
was about any notch
the first one was about his childhood
and when that came out i was
still living in philly and i went
instead of a long line to meet
him and have him sign the book
and
ah you know like after about ten
minutes they you know the bookstore people
came to tell everyone online he's getting
tired so he's not going to have
time to personalize all the books i
was like i gotta get this god
person with my fucking book yeah so
i at the time would occasionally do
an impression of him on stage ah
if my closer did not get
a laugh that i would do this
oppression because it was a big shouty
thing and it would oh yeah things
like anything where you shout or do
a pie or oh yeah exactly so
i wanted to get him it was
the impression was him reciting the itsy
bitsy spider and so i was like
i have to get part of that
have to get him right some of
that in this book
and so when i got up to
him in the line
i lied and said my father used
to do an impression of him he's
passed away but we were kids used
to do this pressure that always wow
and so he signed part of a
side like up comes the sun wow
alumni zion the best part to pick
that that was also the loudest part
oh wow impression assad up
it sounds so meaningful out of context
yeah yeah absolutely and then it got
printed in the newspaper the next day
they did a story because it was
the biggest signing in you know bright
but borders history or what was the
interview you for it they did not
interview me but they they are as
a section that said the the fans
ah
ah remarks were moving in their obvious
in their obvious sincerity and i was
like the third person quoted my father
used my father's did your father he
didn't go hey what the fuck is
is i don't know i don't know
if maybe he knows what was going
on yeah
dad you see that quote in the
paper for me oh let me check
this out yeah dad i used your
sympathetically death too that's my own aims
that's right you still have the book
oh yeah i still have it and
when he died i wrote i wrote
online posted online about meeting him and
you know all that i'm lying to
him and lying to him yeah no
i told i told the story and
then um a year later or a
couple of years later
janey texted me um oh no honey
peter o'toole died
and i was like oh no this
is terrible
and i was like it took me
hold on exactly like an hour i
was like wait wait didn't he only
right
and i looked up my own fucking
story i was like oh my i
wrote this hoy thing i have forgotten
that people have done what what wait
why did she text into you because
she saw some yeah this happens a
lot online which is where it's like
how i get that fucking cake boss
story oh yeah six every six months
someone goes kick boss was arrest yeah
yeah
twenty fourteen yeah right right so she
just read something about this hearing job
back in the loop like an obituary
got back in rope or something and
you're like am i making this up
yeah i'll be funny though if like
she was in her text drafts or
something she just like yeah oh i
never accept this year yeah but i
had the same i the same exact
feeling as i did when it first
happened right yeah it's everywhere isn't it
weird though that that's letting me also
it meant so much to you but
yet you forgot
not that he was even dead
gone and forgotten yeah yeah yeah what
does that mean it's not like he
was super active well yeah part of
your life he was not a big
part of my life we only met
the one time yeah and he died
well after we meeting yeah yeah and
well after him even doing any movie
roles or he had retired i think
he had done a cup
apple movie indie movies of and yeah
he wasn't spiderman was like venus he
was supposed to be the venus was
probably the last big movie that he
did venus was venus venus was a
um may december romance story where he
was the december oh sure may december
is pretty generous it's like the yeah
oh yeah yeah it's always like
feb yeah new year's eve oh right
am i right folks like you i
think it's more of ah yeah you're
right
alright look let's take a break
welcome back we're back in time for
a three cheer i think so this
one was sent in by ass derek
underscore martz it's called dead celebrities it's
right on track with what we're talking
about oh good fine chevron chevron good
boy what a good boy what does
it have synchronicity
how beautiful synchronously one like that how
beautiful each of you will be different
dead celebrities and from your conversation you
have to figure out who you are
without asking direct questions each of us
not you the listener yeah although you're
not being this age and overweight i
refuse to let them play do we
have to figure out who each ah
well i think we should each think
if we are and we talk to
each other
and then yeah and then if we
ever figure it out we say oh
this is a twist i thought that's
how i understood it so so what
i'm saying is like if we ever
figure out your princess di we say
okay princess di and and and then
i die yeah i like any show
yeah you're finally released early bouncer maybe
turn them
i always get the wrong baby lock
them doors and during any time lights
and lock them doors down low what
roads are ok so let's all take
a second to think of somebody okay
okay okay i'm okay got it can
only think of living by the way
we're not we're not going to do
it
impressions because that would give it away
yeah we're gonna talk like ourselves and
just give it away via wall question
i'll give it away get away get
away dow the conversation give me yours
and give it away give it away
give it away bow okay i'm writing
i'm not i'm not ah you're only
thinking of the live people i'm only
thinking of living celebrities and the people
that we mentioned already yeah i know
it's tough tough to do to think
of anyone who's dead i have mine
um ah ah there's a little gag
i learned i got okay
okay hey guy
nice to meet you guys so funny
that we're all here yeah what an
interesting situation i don't know i can't
remember if we've ever met before where
would we have met well don't ask
questions right i feel like no isn't
that what was not don't ask direct
questions but i don't even know what
that means that was a pretty direct
question where would we have met tell
me your biography really direct
i think it should be oh i
know who you are
tell somebody yourself hey how are you
tell me a little about yourself no
do you know you look you look
familiar i do i feel that i
look it kind of depends on how
old you are how familiar i look
right yeah well i am in my
forty so i'm gonna say okay i'm
barely fifty oh yeah i'm about i
don't want to say directly because i'm
a little older i don't wanna say
directly because i'm i'm just don't want
to share that okay i'm um you
know i'm like eighty five or ninety
or so so after you've passed or
that was held oh my god you
did
we're all dead aren't we sorry wait
are we heaven yes this is happening
okay okay knowing that i thought it
was a cloud themed club
so you're forty
i would say older the older than
that and you've written some books i
think i have i think i had
i bet i have yeah yeah i
might have a bio each site there
i would say ha but if i
benefit put on a book there's probably
a lot of pictures in there i
you just put out a book it
would have a lot
ought to do with my life story
and maybe an animal or two and
okay jane goodall know damn it
i tell you this place you have
if you have a book out you
can share that of a book yeah
we like to talk about books here
i don't really like to read all
that much ah have never been much
of a reader um
this is something that is known about
you yeah not growing up ah i
you know i my my proclivities lie
elsewhere
um i tell you this place is
not like jellies at all
chili's yeah julie's cafe no it's just
a place i liked okay quit complaining
frank sinatra oh okay okay known not
reader i doubt over okay well you
could catch daddy ever did you could
keep um guessing right yeah okay yeah
yeah um so
so do you have you i mean
there's a stage out there if you
want to go get on no no
no no you couldn't do that i
mean like i you know i'm i'm
accustomed to being in front of people
but not in that way oh okay
so you're non je cylinder you know
i assure him now make a speech
or two i mean i have but
it's not the main thrust of
what i do right yeah right i
liked i like to be outside or
any of your animals here by the
way oh did you bring animals i
did too definitely by now i'm very
interested in animals i have one animal
that's pretty unique as a pet really
yeah like a snail or oh it
has hair most people
don't have this as a pet is
a pot belly pig no
is it a dog no everyone has
that oh okay i'm frank sinatra i
don't know what normal people is true
your mobilized himself i never sang any
song about any dog so when you
can quote me on that jack me
yeah in one of your books about
oh i don't know i don't really
write a lot of books i just
mean i probably have a book and
there are definitely books written about me
a lot of books around about me
well do you want to get on
that stage then yeah i do it's
when i was born due oh okay
barbara streisand lady dog i've also alive
it's my true passion it's how i
connect being on stage yeah
how do you feel about being on
film like have something you enjoy i
like it i've done a little bit
of it i usually do it in
short spurts snuffing
how about you do you spend much
time on film no no no no
on camera shore but not on camera
really on like television interviews and stuff
i've been interviewed yeah but i've been
on television a lot on television oh
yeah but you've written books as well
what an interesting hire i don't quote
me on that i think i probably
okay i think feel like we got
off track with all this book talk
i want to ask if you have
anything to do with the news
no i've been ever interrupted the news
other news i personally have not interrupted
the news
i don't think i think i think
i was very important and i interrupted
the news at least with my death
really what about the your pet's death
i don't really know when that happened
and so i can't okay yeah so
after you were alive i don't know
what you're doing so what do you
pet an elephant yeah probably
and actions yes ah you are gonna
be him too
he should have said he owe me
no more times okay so michael you
and i were great friends down on
earth yeah that's right you guys were
the best yeah
me and bano jack and we sang
a song together jerry you might go
on stage but you'd only care for
it it's not your main thing you've
written books probably form on stage a
television act are you oh are you
an actor i don't think so radio
personality for you walter cronkite knows i
know you've never interrupted do i look
like walter cronk
kai don't say anything to me ah
you know i honestly don't know if
i interrupted the news but maybe when
i died some people got their news
interrupted i don't know and you're in
your forties or fifties yeah did you
like it when news was interrupted when
you were alive
i feel like that's a very direct
question i'm sorry i rescind
it doesn't get up in
i'm trying to learn more about you
man jackets are how about your wife
is she around i believe so yeah
and my daughter she's here and having
no oh okay i'm sorry around on
earth i should say oh okay really
my daughter ain't on job i'm proud
that my daughter is following in my
footsteps or youtube bite
eden wait he didn't die murray yeah
are you john rowe john mccain i'm
not john ritter i'm not john mccain
you're not in politics no not are
you a famous john doe not
so not hugh grant then anyway
remember when he was on jay leno
did you know so ally yeah it
was alive for that i was alive
for that sure it was a huge
deal of it when jay leno took
the lead in the late i won't
tell us a little more about yourself
well
like you i had a great affinity
for animals i would say
more so in my life
are you jane goodall no i'm not
mad are you wait or use that
crocodile god no gave steve irwin yes
ah really turn the table
that's a good one bhindi mindy in
the airways she's engaged
that's great wow that brings us to
the end of another feature you don't
play it again does my wartime okay
okay i gotta think somebody okay i
got somebody i gotta think somebody too
can we do
okay why don't we all wait unless
you really wanna do yours what why
don't we all do um movie characters
who died or is it oh died
in the mirror oh is too hard
might be too hard hey probably as
pious yeah okay i gotta think somebody
i like it though alright i like
it too but i feel like our
interests might not show up an hour
movie
the knowledge might not overlap right right
okay i got um i got mine
i got mine
i don't have mine yet alright i'm
hoping to get yours okay yeah should
we get started yeah everyone hey oh
hey oh funny oh
i don't do that you don't do
that i probably don't
i had a clue how hard i
do but you think i wouldn't huh
frank sinatra
i love this place i love i
love this place but i'm rather sure
about the music playing well i'd rather
music be a little more upbeat how
about you oh i love it loud
i love and loud loud music it's
not my style of music you know
maybe i'm too maybe i'm a little
older than this style of music i
love
i love the style of music and
i always imagined when i got up
here what would you call this style
of music rock and roll ruddy yeah
and i always imagine when i got
up here that i'd be on guitar
playing in the heavenly bans hurt cobain
know i'm who the fuck is that
oh you don't even know who that
is what weird
is that your guitar ah yeah when
you do it ah it's yeah what
do you mean the brown marks on
it yeah oh i don't i'm embarrassed
i don't wanna say did you set
it on fire yeah all right jimmy
wow
i give you some really okay yeah
um he's always the lead guitarist
dance
no one no guitar said he also
been able to supplant it also coolers
to be the guitar hoped yeah which
he was famous for yeah so anyway
how are you you you you like
music more upbeat i would like a
little happier i feel that's what people
want happy music huh
yeah happy music's cool heavy music is
nice i've had yeah some tragedy in
my life have you yeah but i've
had ups and downs you know what
i mean are you frank lloyd wright
no
because you know what happens you're happening
no what happened to him so he
this is what i was watching this
documentary on frank lloyd wright you are
scum jimi hendrix yeah and so i'm
watching this this story about how frank
lloyd wright he like builds his house
yeah and any he gets married and
he has kids and then very calmly
the doctor
ontario in the narrator says and then
tragedy struck i'm like oh i they
got rubella and all died or whatever
native american person that worked for him
set the entire house on fire and
when his wife and kids all
crashed out the windows and started crawling
out of them took an axe and
chop them all to pieces yeah what
you know i heard this from someone
else on a podcast once i've never
heard that but i've never heard from
jimi hendrix before this this this fellow
must be thrilling for you i won't
we were contemporary now let me play
this
it doesn't mean that much to me
who you are what that's really why
were you did you die before i
may find out huh alright yeah giant
black guide before you were oh yeah
what about me um did you die
before he was big deal no i
was around for jimmy you around from
yeah
wow which some would you think well
i thought it was you i thought
you were interesting but not your cup
of tea um certainly your rendition of
the national anthem oh is that you
you're a big pain are you a
patriot ooh yeah i think so but
it's certainly would have raised eyebrows of
my former
in-laws oh your former in-laws were not
from this country
no they raise that when you say
raise eyebrows meaning they did not like
you related to the kennedy family well
yes i was alright gerald januar no
carolyn olson know ah robert kennedy what
is this you're just saying jam are
you eating j f k doing junior
marilyn monroe oh my god
no marilyn monroe knows of course marilyn
disgusting no i'm not marilyn monroe how
dare you it's also related to okay
alright jackie yeah jackie oh i yeah
i would never thought you look great
by the way thank you very stylish
i remained so until the day i
died meanwhile i'm still do you know
who jackie o is ye
yes i did you know i actually
probably nineteen sixty did you know me
as jacqueline bouvier kennedy i might have
just started learning about you and then
i quickly died
okay so yeah no no because it's
the information
i always thought i would ahead a
chance to ships getting news
um and what and you and you
like peppy upbeat music did you i
think happy music i think just being
happy as one of the most important
things and you feel like you want
a chance with my husband no no
no not at all i'm joking i'm
with now you can you imagine a
hilarious those jokes are to me yeah
why do you joke like that all
the time no no
no i actually i'm not very very
nice sense of humor and i would
never engage in homosexual acts i'm sure
and um i wonder why she brought
that up
no i was married i was married
to my wife i actually valued um
someone a little more when i had
someone that i considered more my my
spouse oh okay cole porter know and
it wasn't human being and oh it
was michael j
jackson
i am one of the i create
i create really great memories for people
you're a you create really great memories
from oh wait are you norman rockwell
no are you ansell adams no
but you are married i yes but
you are creating great memories faced with
something else photographers what you're talking about
yeah but i create art you create
art really sorry a painter i don't
not really i would think pencil is
more what i would use
huh and um coloureds coloureds get older
we don't say that anymore jimi hendrix
i know you're from a different time
but colored the mark i don't know
what the thing are called but anyway
something magic markers no i didn't use
magic markers but but i do love
magic okay you seem really cool
i come mostly cool probably have a
couple of bad opinions i think maybe
you do and i think one of
those opinions
was that mice are not pests but
that there's supposed to be revered in
some special way well dizzy you me
oh rip off my moustache
and put your moustache back on
fun that was fine enjoyed it i
enjoyed yeah
this was a fun episode um i
look i loved it i loved this
episode
as far as episodes go i loved
it i feel like a little bit
of an expert connoisseur yeah this is
i love you know yeah about episodes
yeah i'm having one right now ooh
wow
hey we need to go to the
hospital ah alright well we'll see you
next time by the way we have
a live show alive threesome coming up
september nineteenth and toronto's yes for laughs
first rancho largest ever live shady last
ever yeah maybe so come see us
if you're in toronto and if you're
not a draw toh steve i'm not
come away us never come to see
us never come to
but even if we do a show
near you in the future yeah if
you don't live in china never come
to one of our we'll do a
show in new mexico we only want
people from toronto to that's right this
is your chance to prove that you
love us trees come see us and
please follow me on instagram lauren lucas
wow are you worried that your numbers
are slipping no i just wanted to
do this
alright we'll see you next time hi
uh