three
oh
ah mama mama mama mama mama mama
mama ma ma welcome to threesome he's
got an airing got to sing napoleon
songs
new mayor obama ma ma ma ma
ma ma ma ma is lawrence over
there and we didn't introduce ourselves or
each other last week it's silly i
know you're all confused if you don't
know what the fine here my name
is paul i'm the pizza place and
knees and i'm two guys you're five
guy
guys i wish i were five guys
hey guys i would that would be
fun i think wish i were five
people that would be fun to be
five people so yeah he did well
i'm a complicated guy complicated it's too
complicated um do you wish you out
of twin know i think i'd be
pretty cool i mean well i wish
for
in the same way i wish for
having like that i had a sister
because i feel like you don't have
a sister no damn like i would
like to see oh no
what i would like to know what
that what that person would be like
i think is what i'm wondering she
always wanted a sister too yeah it
seems nice all my friends have sisters
they're close and it's cool yeah yeah
but it could be the opposite way
totally anything can get in miami soon
why ninety percents
true but i i think about like
oh i'd be so interesting to see
like i love when i see my
friends siblings and like if they how
they look like or don't look alike
and then i wonder like oh if
i had a sister i wonder if
we would look like or what i'm
growing utilize your brother but wearing a
wig right okay actually it's nice yeah
my my best friend in high school
i had a brother who was one
year above him i feel like and
we would hang out all the time
they were so close i was just
like how does this happen i thought
that you hated everyone that you were
in forced to be in a house
with wow yeah i always envied that
to my my family or not we're
not like estranged but we're not we're
not straight when
pals in that way although my my
brothers i think do stuff together but
um like an exclude you or they
just because they live nearer nearer to
each other because of near interesting know
like why don't they invite me to
the movies
i'm just saying you can invite me
of course i can't go but i
always think what if i could the
dynamics between people who have a lot
of siblings like the ways some are
close in some aren't and um i
have a friend who has a sister
and a brother and she's not close
with the brother at all and he's
not really close with the family at
all but then she's close with close
with her sister
or do you ever see like the
home alone family and go oh i
wish i had that where it was
ten kids right kind of do think
that would be really cool i think
that'd be cooler as a parent like
i'm like oh they'd be really awesome
to like it seems like a nightmare
to me have all the oil yeah
it seems like i would want ten
kids but i like the idea of
like i liked the idea i just
think adoption is amazing i've talked about
that but i like
like the idea of hello my god
oh no no no especially on this
nice topic
we make a rule that if it's
a nice topic we can talk about
it again okay who is the adjudicator
of yvonne nice nah honey um i
like the idea of helping a lot
of children right well maybe becoming a
foster parents were so challenging yeah because
when i come and go and i
think that's so hard yeah i know
well you know around the kids go
up still you know ah close with
her sponsor family and these yes each
other and that's really nice that's a
really cool situation that she had like
a sponsor family worth i thought what
they did was so amazing um in
clubs documentary which i got a special
preview of but you're going to see
everyone in her movie when they won
the
the parent the sponsor parents start talking
about the fish yes what is it
that we're talking about fish the barney
miller spinoff yeah that's right the band
they just do it like it's a
very it's a very you know oh
they're horrible people think that you don't
often see in these situations where they
there's like a brief sidebar where they
talk about
but never had that kind of fish
before and it was very good i
really enjoyed it yeah they're so nice
well normal yeah yeah yeah i found
them very endearing yeah it was great
ah let me tell you something though
yeah grew up in a family with
six kids it was no picnic for
anybody yeah that's interesting was it what
were the challenges yeah well i think
that my mom was
was burn out you know and i
think that it's john parent fucking a
lot yeah i don't think i could
really handle loud she did she have
a job or was she yeah both
my parents worked really well word she
worked she she was the receptionist for
her brother's piano tuning company whoa so
he has yet a small business small
visit her brother had a small business
tuning pianos yeah and she would answer
the calls of like well okay play
me a c and then they'd play
a seed she goes nope we gotta
come in here and bring that piano
ah okay i think we have a
good handle on what your mom i
mean it's not far from that i
guess what were some of the worst
parts of being one of six and
how many bathrooms did you have in
how many bedrooms to jeff we had
i glommed onto your question even though
they're not related i'll take the second
question first and then i'll and
your question lauren okay we had three
bathrooms live for we island doing parents
or three floors to the house okay
oh rich so eight eight p
um yes eight people my mom had
it white five children and they had
one bathroom betwixt them all like god
yeah just hearing that all day yeah
we had we lived in ah we
lived in a my turn in a
duplex
we lived in a duplex in my
legs my cousins lived right next door
they had seven kids and the exact
right next door exact same house yeah
seven kids two two parents as well
so nine people over there and then
eight new eight and you ate in
your house eight in your house neither
none of their house yes and i'm
sorry but everyone's related it
is two and a half baths okay
okay um and everyone simply everyone was
related
and um the bedroom's it was in
people all related to houses three three
and a half bath that's the new
justice ten of us six seventeen people
all related to houses three and a
half baths find out what happens when
they stop being polite and start being
real and knocked down all the walls
and stare at each other
naked
i did have i had fed up
with my my cousin doreen we were
very close we went all through school
together and we at one point were
the same age yeah we're this image
and we tried to do a code
or your tap on the wall to
each other because our bedrooms shared a
wall wait so these these were attached
as a duplex oh suplex smart
fucker are you sad due to plaques
that now mean anything to you feckless
content oh my hey samantha bee oh
who's that samantha bit don't say feckless
said my huh
so we set up this this code
which was essentially to say thanks no
i'm just like imagining what the code
is what is it oh the code
was
basically it's not well thought out it
was one tap for every
for every letter of the alphabet yes
so when he say it was v
yeah exactly oh my god exactly we
didn't do this didn't last very long
and also i was using a hammer
to do the tab and i hammered
a hole in the wall ah great
that's what this and then i supposed
to do yeah and what how did
you explain the hole in the wall
i didn't know i hit it i
hit it with clothing what was in
the closet oh so oh okay okay
okay yeah i was like i imagined
you like hey your pajamas over it
every day
i dressed it up like a person
i love you my roommates it has
a mouth yeah shared a room we
yes we shared rooms for um in
various combinations over the years i always
exciting when you switch your with someone
else yes it was well what basically
what would happen just one person would
leave like so yeah yeah so as
people were growing up and moving out
of the house some some people would
be teenagers
and would need more space or something
with a wow or spi it was
like the older you got the more
likely you were to get more space
so right at one point i think
maybe two of my sisters were sharing
a room and one had a room
to herself on the third floor and
then no it wouldn't have been it
would have been maybe maybe they each
had their own bedroom the girls each
other own bedroom and then because i
remember there being a parish where know
where my brothers and i were all
in one room right i remember us
all being how many how many brothers
two two so three of you brothers
and sisters yes and then so four
bedrooms the girls all have their own
room and yes the the three brothers
were all together yes my parents had
their bedroom wow were they did it
they did it at least six times
why not seven oh there's only sixteen
um so one time just for practice
one time
how are we going to do this
have a little fun with that
position should be like yeah do it
someone times thick that is six that
is it sounds like song lyrics yeah
six headaches if fellows take my advice
love those position held fifty stock here's
how to have six kids find a
position started
one tyler learned from me
six that is
where was there a lot of fighting
oh yeah oh yeah yeah cool cool
like me
i played a hole-in-the-wall on him
are you physically fit or just scream
both yeah both yeah and my with
my older brother and i've i know
i've talked about this before but maybe
not on this show thinking get ready
cash banking alert my older brother was
so much bigger than me that it
was like what could i do you
know what you mean you just got
physical with us you just pin me
in then that was
it was no difference from the oldest
to the youngest we were my sister
well let's see who's the old were
all like it was first it was
the three girls in the three boys
miss really easy oldest yeah and um
we were all like roughly three years
apart okay so what was the show
then that would be eighteen will my
my sixteen year fifteen years older than
you yeah yeah no no less than
that but because twelve ish thirteen months
she's i think sixty two now and
i'm about to turn fifty right yeah
so okay so tall so maybe two
years in between all of you does
that reckless
interests my little brothers three years younger
than me okay and i blow okay
sir sorry sir i thought you were
the youngest so i ok so fifteen
is correct fifty so if i were
the youngest daughter got all that attention
and then we wanna number of many
that's right me is when there's only
two it's different yeah
yeah were you loren were you and
your brother pals growing up oh yeah
we got along i tagged along with
him a lot and tried to hang
out with him and his friends and
my mom would make him was your
kid sister have to be yeah i
really was that hey guys hey let's
play what i wanna do it everyone
i want my bees um but i
would like watching die
games smuggle yeah but she didn't die
at the way she didn't die i
don't know who died thomas joshua we've
we've talked about this makalu and i've
also said my girl two is one
of my favorite know spanking right um
and i was making hi ah mrs
santos speaking i know spanking comma i
we always got along we like to
watch tv together and um you know
hang so it was the shoe you
like to netflix and chill chill um
and yeah there's not much to say
about it but then he went to
yeah i'm sorry i'm just thinking we're
not interrogating joking about it i'm thinking
if there's anything interesting
i could add but not really um
when i remember him going to school
and like leaving or going to college
and i that period i i don't
i don't i think that was when
i got a little more like adult
in my life when he was he
was in college and how old was
ah he was three grades older than
me so i was like sars or
nobody older years because i my my
birthday but two and a half ish
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's
you know whatever route three about three
um but yeah ah that was cool
that was cool so you were your
sophomore in then you really came into
your own and you were like you
know what this is who i am
i'm my own person bernie you party
i've heard like you remember the first
time you ever drank alcohol though um
yes i um was well i guess
officially i probably did in high school
with like mike's hard lemonade though toby
whose yeah but i barely got drunk
i was dating my now and yes
to drink his hard lemonade
yeah now i drink his hard fudge
you switched midstream i think you say
something yes i was ah don't wanna
let that out on this show huh
um so it was you don't remember
the first first time though um not
really i so common it was well
there was never really a moment where
that was like crazy years but i
just i guess it was a little
exciting one time we got some likes
your lemonade we always drink that but
um it's good i wasn't really a
drinker
in in high school that wasn't so
i wasn't either yeah i it's funny
that the the the difference in age
in this manifesto in this way that
when i was in high school there
were no options like that it was
just beer and yeah that was it
this was like right before it on
the climb because i'm a little bit
younger than you yeah
when we drank wine coolers exactly yeah
zima the first time i remember it
wasn't i was doing standup when zima
came out because it was a big
standup sideline it was very exciting zima
has been used on agents marvel's agents
of shield sorry i meant it into
marvel's agents of shield as as of
in like a really funny way i
can't tell
whether it is a it is an
integration of product integration if so it's
very success way do remember when people
would ice people with smirnoff ice you
can drink it on terrace house they
were all these guys were drinking smirnoff
ice when i was like this is
so funny they're standing in a bar
as if it's a cool drink to
have i'm mainly talking yeah bar yeah
wow
i remember the when zuma came out
there was a comedian that we knew
named roger kaylor who was a an
impressionist and it was the only person
i saw do a great version of
william hurt and he and i remember
him handing her william hurt yeah he
did like dip the typical people than
you would expect william hurt is the
only person
you should ever listen to read the
polar express it's an old tape my
family i've said this for years his
voice is so great he ended the
impression by saying i have a great
neck
um but he became the spokesman for
zima when they looked when they launched
the drink he was like the guy
in the commercial sing because you were
like a little hat was this in
philly he no no he was not
a philly guy he he was the
national zima guy how did you know
him though how is he i knew
i'm from from from comedy meaning he
would pass through
philly you asked through okay it's like
a passthrough he did a pass through
um how cool it was very cool
how long did it last i wonder
it lasted a while they made a
big push for zima they really really
really come around i think i want
to try it again i don't feel
like i've had one ever hundred years
i think i think it'd be good
have you watched this is not related
have you watched the steve martin and
martin shorts
yeah yeah i really liked it okay
i saw them do a ah when
martin short's book came out ah when
you have a book coming out i
guess ah you do these their events
that you do around town where you
do readings of it or or yeah
or some stuff like there's no what
do you why are you acting like
this i don't know yeah i'm i'm
trying to i'm trying i'm trying to
say what it is to myself i'm
trying to figure it out but there's
like a knot in bookstores i mean
like in a theater there is like
l a times books or something puts
on the yeah yeah or something like
that but i can't remember what john
hodgman did one of those thought the
asap so i went to this one
where ah martin short had his book
come out and they're like oh see
if martin is going to host this
one and i was like well then
i'm going to go see this yeah
and and it was so funny because
it was basically steve martin knowing he
had to ask martin short questions and
then coming up with joe questions that
were all like jokes you know all
stuff like he would do on the
academy awards or whatever it would like
start off
like a question and then have a
zinger at the end you know when
he hosted the oscars it was i
remember being so funny yeah i remember
the jokes being really good and then
it never was good again the fosters
ever yeah well i feel like i
feel like the jokes are are the
one i remember zayn over and over
and over again the one i remember
his set
you still have things to say no
eat eat drink man woman
you want to say no no he
was talking about the movie eat drink
and not jack twenty four jack bauer
twenty four bixby eat drink man woman
got the joke that's the joke is
he was saying and the movie eat
drink man woman came out this year
or ah which is also what arnold
schwarzenegger said to maria shriver on their
first date
right well now you're just proving my
point okay
he was great though it was great
i also thought they had a missed
opportunity they should call it steve martin
short
ah maybe i just like wheel of
fortune too much
well yeah before and after yeah you
are both on your phone because now
we're trying to tape a show for
millennials talk about it's god don't worry
scott this is millport husky um paul
just said yes god is a big
baby and he's with a little husky
she's okay lauren is showing an instagram
i guess of a boy
maybe it's exactly what we're doing that
british babies think everyone needs to know
it's loading very slow does he have
a british accent like gugu
boy oh boy good guy wow
it's millie and rupert journey okay thanks
for that lauren well i'm loading so
i'm sorry there's like one of the
things that i love that you just
showed us a fat guy well i
don't think he'll make it yeah but
don't say who it is because like
yeah i'll show you a picture of
someone fat and then a dog
what we do we're doing beta i
could go baby fat guy dog baby
fact i doubt any fact i dug
yeah baby back i don't yeah to
be a feature where you have to
be given you to come up with
a baby and then a fat guy
or a dog's name and ok how
about i'll do it right now okay
okay albert dog
baby pet guy fat over and over
on
he's right he's right all right let
me think of one bastard
the fat guy
let me do why narrow chance
that guy that chance yeah okay here's
one
boss
baby yeah buffy alright i go
lip
backflip you from the far side yeah
that guy that's right back alright here's
here's the far side yeah isn't he
for the first time the far side
it's always the cartoon i forgot that
there was a band yeah spelled differently
yeah oh the far side p h
a r that's right z here's my
robert
that guy dog
or baby
robert b rob or robert dog
as a baby
becky was a dog hell well i
just picked a dog named robert yeah
i just picked a goddamn wrapper yeah
so that's how we play right i
look one okay santa claus so shit
wow this is the fucking tough one
it's a dog bitch
good name for a dog santa claus
it's a dogfish dave is a good
name for a dog yeah it's adobe
what's your dog's name it's a dog
binge i get asked many questions alright
we gotta take a break we'll be
right back
good good good good good good good
we're back we're back good good good
good good back after these messages rant
back do we have to say we're
back no we don't write well cause
it's not well i mean you know
they may have heard a thing and
then we want to say
no you're not still listening to that
thing and we're back it's of course
they're not what you mean well they're
not listening they know my different the
difference you know we might we it
might be us doing the ads but
still were when we do the ads
it's gonna be very accessible it's gonna
be good hello i would like to
i feel you about my very special
products
the lady of the house at home
i you the one that makes the
financial decisions you're also every yeah we
get yeah sorry oh i feel sorry
for the people listening to on stitcher
premium they're not gonna hear these awesome
ads we're gonna do it's so it
sucks you guys oh my god because
looks for you because they're forbidden to
listen to anyone does yeah ah term
plus terms a lot of pt
terms and burns terms of birds welcome
to terms and burns where we're talking
about turns and then we're burning each
other that's right so terms of service
do you agree to them no matter
what oh no i got a bird
yeah ah
oh guy i like when there are
videos of animals being patient with babies
yeah it's very we were like grabbing
yours my nephews were just visiting and
my pets were very patient with them
and i was very oh good that's
important i know it's nice it's you
don't want your baby
eaten by you know no you don't
read that your baby eating bad dough
and get rid of the dogs real
cry in the dark then you go
on trial for murder yeah the major
hit i was gonna ask you guys
a question yeah she's like hey do
you like grocery shopping at
and if and do you like to
go to a grocery store in a
different neighborhood than your only if you're
buy one and do all the shopping
or is it like you'd rather be
in your store where you know everything
is well i'll tell you i do
like grocery shopping
but i like to be at home
so you order your groceries
i meant when my neighbor a local
store oh my local likes to go
like to go to my grocer's freezer
yes i like to know where everything
is sometimes but i always like to
walk down every single io no matter
what of course we have there's a
grocery store chain small chain and we
moved from
a neighborhood where we went to this
one to a neighbourhood where we go
to another in the same chain but
everything is lightly lightly different and drives
you crazy fucking i feel like i
finally got a handle on it yeah
because i still go to both because
the one is near the usb and
so i'm there i end up there
a lot and um
it's just different enough to be maddening
yeah but i feel like i've finally
got a handle i like going to
different grocery stores to see the differences
and to see certain products that you
would never yeah get to see it's
what i used to like about going
to different record stores is like oh
shit they they ordered because once i
have round records so now once you
figure out like pop chips i don't
even know what at what age i
realized how stores worked of the people
who own the store order things and
the things are brought like i guess
what your journey with retails amazing because
i remember when you figured out you
could order a sandwich at a deli
yes like what
i was doing i was six yes
no but but here's what i mean
like i was once in a record
store and i assume i guess i
had just assumed like they had all
the records and if they didn't have
something because someone bought it right and
then and then i asked the store
hey do you have this album and
they're like no but we could order
it for you and
i was like what what does that
mean they're like yeah just tell me
where it is getting the serial number
on it and like well order it
and it'll be here for you and
a few weeks i was like how
did really and then it sort of
dawns on you like okay if you
go to the grocery store like all
ralph's don't have the exact same things
yeah they make decisions based on how
much space they have in the store
of like oh we're gonna
order that so i guess i would
i'm trying to say is i like
going to different stores to see like
oh shit i've never even heard of
this type of time or this type
of chip or whatever but at the
same time i don't really like i
find it very frustrating being in grocery
stores and trying to find stuff can
i tell you a secret i like
the lita cheese ooh and i noticed
that the one
garrisons that we used to go to
has velveeta cheese but the one we
go to hell doesn't have it yes
and it's really where like what a
snobby thing yeah go like oh no
we wouldn't have yeah well similarly when
i was going to subway all the
time um they're the ones
subway by my house had carrots had
shredded carrots and i would always add
it and then to a sandwich to
a sandwich yeah yeah because i was
just basically trying to go
what's wrong with carousel sandwich that's weird
is it's like having sprouts and yeah
nah no carrots yeah it's not it's
just added fiber what we can we
can you can say that all you
like but it's not normal yeah you've
never had carrots on a sandwich before
never and wouldn't ever do it i'm
not talking about whole carrots i'm talking
about shredded carrot oh okay
i know what you're talking about
this is not crazy yes it is
it is no it's not i'm gonna
do it to devon have it like
vegeta a little crazy this series have
carrots on their sandwiches all day have
to make don't have enough options what's
wrong with having carrots on it anyway
it's a sorry
adds varsha i don't like salad either
well that's now you are getting it
now here's the thing i'm talking to
to insane people no oh yeah and
saying two and ceremony normal weight so
i'm sorry if everyone in the room
screwed you yeah you're in a room
with a bunch of unseen only sends
you to be this time figure size
i'm visiting you on ms
like why everybody's so crazy is actually
going to hold well it's what i
was used to when i was in
the army i got back home and
i just that bed is too comfortable
for me sir yes sir
ah yes sir i don't i don't
like carrots unless they are like well
see now we're just talking about you
don't like carrots yeah that's right study
dies cares not yet been ranch yeah
i didn't mean hummus i put them
in a salad what i don't do
is put them on the sandwich i
don't put about a pizza
okay now that's weird if i don't
put it on a pizza why would
i put it in a sandwich where
you don't put them on i love
pepperoni sandwiches i don't put them in
popsicle but what about on the thai
chicken pizza from california pizza kitchen i
put them on yeah they're on pizza
there and it's good yeah wait character
and pizza there yeah there's
one exception now for the short on
the proves the rule
now for sandwiches it'll never be true
well my point was i went to
it i went to another subway and
i was like oh and i'll have
carrots in there like we don't have
carrots i was like because it's weird
and i got i was like what
but also always have carrots
anyway i'm gonna put this on my
book that i better put carrots on
a sandwich but careless shredding it saying
shred it here put shredded carrots on
a sandwich yes you know sweet okay
let it lick it let's get the
result
tts at the end of our show
if i dig around to said yes
would be the first option and this
job should be that's insane i know
but i didn't want to sway you
don't say because you're a good person
i'm trying to be real
oh and the votes are coming in
there thirteen votes i won't tell you
that
how long are the polls open twenty
four hours twenty four hours wow okay
well let's stop now and come back
twenty four only we can do that
in our democracy oh i wish it
was slightly flowers reference xy wave guy
was wanting for wow i have sexual
relations with wow
i did not have sexual relations with
that woman i did not have sexual
relations with that woman aw i do
not have this
well i shouldn't what the woman can
finish i mean i can finish and
finish can't finish kevin nash gonna have
sex orlando now good shit finish gonna
finish finish finish gonna finish good
finnish don't want to get a good
fish
we've gone and say awareness songs ever
actually when you really think oh robshaw
marie was knowingly weird it's so great
i remember my high school someone did
a dance performance to that i hope
you yes i was like rock me
amadeus lauren almost danced she basically held
and slightly when you were saying the
other day i play who is dead
but also you were sees the hand
on the hip and pointing up for
this and even the pointing upwards yeah
it's it's so they did a dance
routine to me i'm going well first
of all he was german but it
was on the movie amadeus
had been out to do this and
it was it was knowingly like that
was back at a time in music
where you intentionally made weird songs to
get attention oh well and also you
glommed onto a thing that was already
popular yeah like when neil diamond did
that e t song you turn on
i couldn't believe i when i heard
that song i was like
this is about eighty i got so
excited i was like she's just fucking
petty i couldn't believe when i found
out it was not it was not
just isolations yeah i thought it was
i was like so fucking cool does
somebody need a song about devise a
movie he did what he made he
wrote a song it was essentially about
eating turn on your heart lie d
i know that some shy
wherever you go let it make me
happy low fuller all the world zu
see that flame
lame to be like e t erez
isn't that that's got my juices flowing
i want to flow my juices to
my music machine if it here's honest
question if aliens came down to earth
and they looked like e t yeah
and fuck yeah
no honestly you're going no honestly like
it's like if you're compatible and you
could have children it wasn't used like
that
but eventually we worked eventually we would
breed with them wouldn't we know those
fingers yeah what do you mean why
would well sky
julie looked like a weird hairless monkey
also it's all about looks for you
yeah eighties fuckin cool you wouldn't you
wouldn't have sex with there's no okay
no one saying not cool here's very
cool you could still fuck him and
kiss the same time because his neck
rises that's true that's true are you
used to
fucking someone to not be able to
kiss them at the same dog when
i'm not gonna answer
my colors yeah um i think that
we would eventually breed with them anyway
why would you think that i don't
know like we'd miss some people would
be into it they're very comfy totally
free there's people on earth they won't
breed with other humans that look slightly
different yeah there's people who won't do
that but people will will you soon
i'm one of those people that want
to fuck and i don't think it's
arrest i don't think it's like i
don't thanks your direct i don't think
it's like an animal because with an
animal you can't gain consent it's not
an animal no but it can't talk
you didn't talk he could tell he'd
say vader saying so stephen hawking spoke
in brooklyn never have been able to
have sex is
what you're saying because he can't talk
he could talk before he could talk
oh so there's a cut-off if you
could talk at one time you can
have sex i do think yeah actually
my standby i think it's pretty safe
to show the person in the diving
bell and the butterfly who's blinking should
never have sex because we don't know
if if they're actually giving consent guess
if they blink that they want to
fuck that's my point e t can
press but speaking spell can take lucy
you wanna fall like when he wants
to stop imagine your executive somebody you
have to like look
them the whole time these are the
problems receive they blink these are the
problems with anyone who can't communicate verbally
not anyone
for all these people you are worried
about well who am i worried about
your worry about people won't fuck e
t
well i think it's i think it's
you know i don't think it's very
cool to just say i'm not gonna
fuck e t because he happens to
look different here's what's cool e t
here's what's not cool not fucking billion
amelia de jesus not cool i think
it would be interesting it would lead
to like you know like a new
a new breed of i don't know
if we're compatible even well that what
if you that's what i'm saying like
if eighties mom came over how to
vagina you realize this is mom
okay so the pieces yeah sure yours
friend or like a good age no
i'm saying like through through various yo
la vi planet his mom could be
the same age because yeah no rule
they also could be backwards like benjamin
button rule so but what i'm saying
is it's through a series of trial
and error
we find out that we're able to
have babies series of trial and error
i'm not saying that it you know
i don't know nature finds a way
or whatever before i'm so i'm sometimes
the same as arguing to fuck a
dog no because a dog cannot it
does not you know you don't know
whether dog likes it or not all
right so i'm eating okay
yeah put the moves on me
hey what's up ah sorry that i
poked you in your vagina
that's how you put the boots yeah
when i said what's up i woke
to the giant i was saying oh
just because i don't know that many
words well how does iti here's a
good question how does he communicate with
other eighties let oh well that's like
why is that a good question is
are do they
good question i have alien language i
can't remember the movie i don't remember
them saying anything to each other yeah
that's i don't remember the communique indicated
through like ten telling symbols i was
telling a nice well then well that
is when the hell come they didn't
know telekinesis telekinesis when you can move
no no no but remember when like
do you call it one of the
kids alesi yes
yeah when one of the kids was
feeling what e t felt and without
z will know like remember of impact
number they were so yeah yeah they
weren't sitting up because e t was
sick and that's why i'm saying he
doesn't have control because he only feels
with the kid feels well so then
so then what if vt is putting
his feelings into a human and
and and then you're having sex with
a human but it's like you're having
sex with eighteen as long as it's
like i'm having sex with i'm in
hell it was one of the words
that e t learned on earth you
learn wow phone home eliot yeah i'll
be right here which was a full
sentence is only done well and and
one can presume if he wasn't getting
sick and had to go back to
his own planet that he could have
learned you know several words and several
sentences although comps
really full of course i just wanted
to nail down what he what does
it yeah the fray you'd have to
use the phrase the pace you'd have
to like figure out exactly what exactly
what he wants to say with each
thing so if you're like safe word
you're like ok so if you say
ouch we're gonna stop what we're doing
if you say eliot i'm gonna keep
going harder
what if he's not fucking elliott
he's just fine finally if somebody if
i was having sex with someone they
call out someone else's name eliot that
would ruin it for now but if
he knows you're if it was a
go word
i don't know you feel good is
it would be distracting what if what
if the goal were to get out
of my head yeah alright maybe so
okay i just think like oh you
wish elliot was here we we never
got to see iti was naked but
we never got to really see down
there did we he never pulled up
as has never pulled his trunk because
he had a big gum he had
a big buck like it's true
this look it's true a big fleets
true covering whatever it was down there
yeah penis or pussy tougher area did
you know that albert that owls owls
have really long legs yeah i thought
they had just claws or whatever know
somebody there was a fly there's a
picture you can find online of i
don't know if it's all als or
just this one type of owl
weirdo but yeah it's just what weird
al now that you got it has
long legs were no does have long
does he put bind is okay yeah
what he can put him by his
neck that's part of his act
that sounds like a personal story because
he was like that is part of
ah ah i mean did on my
show at le yeah he used to
used to like play i feel like
he used to play accordion with his
foot behind his head
the wild crazy look up okay chevron
lookup shown al yankovic don't put weird
in there because we don't want to
add any judgment on it but
foot behind her leg behind head or
something like that okay i'm gonna look
up how long owl's legs are okay
what are you going to look up
take a break because i want to
be okay let's take a break we'll
be right back
we're back lauren how's that p even
gain a left hook pp toi toi
um do want to hear the results
of the poll yeah what do we
go okay have you put treaded carrots
on a sandwich a sandwich i'm i
hate typos um thirty one percent say
yes sixty nine percent say no how
many percents you know sixty nine awesome
guy branham says a hamas eventually sandwich
knees them ah someone says love me
some bond love me a bond me
a balmy yeah oh yeah bun me
the same bond me
hey all veggies will answer yes media
will say no on you but bon
me yes oh my god a tuna
sandwich was treaded cares is going to
be my last meal yes tuna sandwich
with shredded characters great o shredded carrots
on tuna is great no guys no
don't like carrots i told you are
the more ny the person i talked
to about this to me about carrot
no tuna sandwich carrots characters great great
great i haven't put them on i
want one right now got a sandwich
at a sprouts and it came with
carrots and it was terrible
fuck you i literally just finished eating
a steak sandwich with steak steak sandwich
sandwich suicide takes like thirty minutes so
good steak with carrots that's interesting so
there's less people going well probably with
other with lettuce and stuff like that
that would be weird if it was
just a stake in sukkur i remember
one time my sister made
was visiting her in california years before
i moved here ms my older sister
and ah she november older sisters that's
true scotch ny pay attention and think
oh yes they are sheep
yeah i'm painting but you're still looking
at she made tuna salad with ah
mustard in it oh i like mustard
mizuna salad too it'll whenever eat tuna
salad period i did not like yes
um gross yeah so you guys are
not people to talk to about sandwiches
you don't like tuna salad what is
uri
original is ah ah don't you guys
got ah what don't you like scott
you're so great yeah like everything no
i don't like watching a rock sandwich
i don't like peppers i don't like
cantaloupe peppers i think that was like
yeah there's something else um that i
don't like you don't like and i'm
trying to think oh i know what
it is we ought tomatoes now
i i like raw tomatoes on sandwiches
i don't like i don't like the
like the ones that are what am
i trying to say but cherry tomatoes
cherry tomatoes only church and i kept
telling him and half i don't like
to bite into like i don't find
it i like tomatoes and pastas a
lot i used to get like a
yeah tomato pasta and kevin cordell know
i used to get a yeah
i gotta go with cafeteria health needs
to make a really great just ava
dobbie pasta tomatoes so i loved it
wasn't good job did it was great
i made some good money it was
my last job before i turned pro
you got to be five of the
members of chicago yet um it was
cool yeah it was ours
yeah
what was the best job you've ever
had
i always liked babysitting i was like
my main way of making money before
i started making money acting and i
loved it because i liked to have
a personal connection with the family and
um watching kid grow up and i
oh and i liked because i could
change what we did every day i
didn't have to like do
the same thing every day so i
liked that so were you babysitting for
a number of years for the same
child and several days a week or
was it yeah depending on the family
but most for the most part i
would i wouldn't really be with someone
longer than a year but ah would
see them a few times a week
right um yeah and then some
we reconnect with later and like they're
like are they grown up now see
oh wow
um one of the girls is like
in high school now that was like
my one of my favorite girls to
babysit when i lived in new york
and she's just so cute and we
had the best time she was five
but it's so fun i would pick
up from school and then hang out
for a couple hours but um i
liked that kind of job
just zap monotonous yeah
i didn't like my job so i
think my the the job i enjoyed
the most when i think about it
i love tower i did a lot
of
i did a lot of retail jobs
and the one that was the most
fun was this place called in general
on south street it's not there anymore
and it was a ah it was
a weird store where they sold sort
of like novelties on the first floor
and then cool housewares on the second
floor like would be like
how this sounds yeah it was actually
it was actually kind of a neat
store kind of novelties like fake coup
there honestly there was stuff like it
was like spencer's gifts kind of novel
time does not not quite as crass
you know right as if there was
fake barf was their fake pee there
was no baby okapi know for drug
tests not even in the code
when you handed someone a sandwich
cup of noodle like it's like how's
like a paper top on it and
then compile it off and take it
into your drug test he can into
it yeah i mean it turns it
into fake pee no it's pee in
a cup and then you can use
it for your purposes i love that
and you're just like i'm just going
to have a cup of noodle while
i'm giving you my sample you don't
think that businesses will learn to recognize
the label
well that's why they give it a
fake label well it's called right if
you look closely it says cut p
noodle co e noodle and they're like
oh yeah sure just take that into
the like the one hitter that looks
like a cigarette
yeah i'm willing everyone i liked that
job because the people that i worked
with were a lot of fun it
was it was the it was the
most
where it was the job where there
there were the most people that were
like me like the same sensibility records
it was like yeah me we have
fun together yeah the year i worked
at marie calendar's we i i made
such great friends with everyone we hung
out every night together after work wow
you know we ate so much paw
we don't want honestly yeah that was
my very first rest
good job and i assumed all restaurant
jobs were like this and and i
came to realize just the managers were
insane or whatever but they would at
the end of the night they'd be
like okay who wants to take what
home and i would take home like
five pies and croissants and like all
the bakery stuff and and then when
i went to work at like baker's
square was and
other job that i had a few
years later and they would throw away
all pies that were left over and
into a dumpster that they would then
lock because of that is crazy yeah
you find out later it's like well
we can't give it away to to
you know organizations or the homeless people
because what if they get sick with
it then we're well deniable
for it and take it away to
me yeah so fora does the same
thing with um products where they'll throw
him out and then like lock the
dumpster because people would word right dumpster
dives to get all this amazing sure
that you could just cut off one
layer of and then it's like right
now cost seventy bucks you got it
for free so they'll they'll throw makeup
because it's just been there on the
shelves for two ln you like
people you can return anything to say
fora um there's like a rule that
you know questions yeah yeah you can
open it and use it in you're
like i don't like it which i
always forget to do because i buy
things and then they're wrong and i
would do that with shirts up for
certain jobs that if i had a
catering job or whatever they were like
oh you need a white shirt a
white button-up or whatever this is you
know when i had no money
i would go buy it where at
once return it and i remember returning
it wants to ross dress for less
than them going like well you obviously
wore this there's like a ring around
the collar i'm like well i tried
it on yeah i tried it on
the how to say the year yeah
right right
um but they started locking the dumpsters
there was like a whole thing go
find the ones that are still not
locked because you can get thousands of
dollars of makeup right yeah this because
people could get could get sick because
if someone used a mascara yeah okay
i always felt a thing hold on
a second if it's a fucking dumpster
your risk yeah it's it's trash
it's like how do you sue hey
i went in your trash can they
eat this food and i'm gonna sue
yeah yeah yeah and they started apparently
hiding where they dumped the stuff like
what oh nice brown russian like kind
of a thing jackie johnson has a
podcast called attribute makeup and so she
kind of went on like a hunt
trying to figure this out and
called before as analyze different things and
some of them like take their trash
like a whole different part of the
mall it's like you wouldn't wow sigh
yeah crazy yeah jackie cracks me up
she's she's the most texas person i've
ever yes hey guys we gotta do
a feature well okay we're in the
third act oh we have to do
a feature so we can repeat one
do you want to read
he won because we could do the
one or we already have repeat we're
already repeating if few luckily it was
a million years ago look in the
phone let's go to the phones let's
go to the phone line we want
to hear what you think
tex one for two and three for
yes
how's that a poll still doing lauren
are you or i'm looking up features
i was i was but i'm going
to look at the poll okay okay
let me read this description of a
game okay fellow thirty five votes the
percentage of the same still sixty nine
nice this is a game called cornell
ee uu is
parlor game created by jan cornell a
member of the metropolitan washington chapter of
mensa this game has been popular at
mensa gatherings for yeah well then it
will certainly be quite popular with us
and it has turned up at science
fiction conventions as well you don't say
quite a pedigree oh cornell e o
cornell it can be titled it can
be called a title association game like
word association only using titles such as
those of a book play movie or
song it's played by a group of
people you arrange themselves in a circle
with the non-playing judge or cornell master
standing in the center the cornell master
starts the game by zach going to
be chef
even you would have to be seven
and he's got to stand in the
center well you don't have to stab
the center so i'm standing on this
table like marinelli masters starts the game
you think he would break every stone
who's to say we were at a
popular ah theater in the area the
other night doing a show and i
said let you know i was back
backstage so let's take a picture in
the mirror and this particular backstage the
mirror is above a couch and so
we're trying to do it and wasn't
quite working i was like let's stand
on the couch anyway it's yeah so
so studies show let me tell you
the legs of that couch are tin
well
holding it up i mean i can't
believe that that eusebius couches broken yeah
well no i never said that we
want after we've we we instantly got
off it and then um i was
so you know people saying like i
knew that was going to happen and
then one of us said well i
had a feeling it was going to
have me because one of the legs
is made of samy
ant and it was just up on
blah so we we joined the one
remaining leg oh that's fine oh yeah
stuff is so cheap i don't understand
why you can't just put like a
nice couch back there and then it
won't get fucked up because it'll be
nice i think that everyone you mean
like like good quality yeah like give
it like this won't collapse and maybe
because of you
spend all them money and then someone
spills a beer on a day one
you're like well this is no longer
nice i spend all that money something
you could just pinch off well that's
i thought the the couch wiping when
they got those leatherette couches i think
that was the smart move like the
kind of city sunset are way nicer
all this stuff stop arguing i can't
hear about this game people need to
hear about this
yeah so the cornelia masters in the
center of the circle cornell e he's
tow car nilly starts the game by
pointing to one of the players saying
a title okay the point of two
player must continue the game by saying
a title himself which must connect to
the previous title in some way so
just having a word in common the
time machine time enough for love
common creator and author as with hamlet
or macbeth or an actor or producer
direct so what you're saying i'm already
bored with this wait wait when do
we get to say cornell e wait
what so it's like the movie title
game as you say a title and
then it has i have to say
something that yeah why
connected in some way either by a
word or by a person the other
part is why does there have to
be a cornell master who gives one
title and then points at someone and
then his out of it or does
the cornell master keep orchestrating this much
like falco orchestrated rock me amadeus let
me read on okay
um or the different groups of cornell
players can vary and exactly what kinds
of links are permissible so we can
decide okay what it needs to be
a notable regional variation is that some
gatherings such as the chicago area mensa
these fucking assholes
i'll come back hey welcome and i'm
usually not an acceptable linkage what if
we did movie whatever we did movie
titles but the or titles of anything
but the next title has to be
the very last word has to start
with the very last word that we
just did okay okay alright with there's
no kylie master anymore about ca
tonelli okay the next title has to
start with the last last word of
that previous and it could be a
song title it can be a movie
title it can be to be a
title of anything title of anything but
the last word has to be the
first word of the next title and
will go clockwise and lauren will start
how does that sound paul i think
that sounds good i think that obviously
like you don't have a limited time
to come up with a title um
i think we kevin can be the
cornell master and point was why do
we need a cornell yes or no
because he can he can move it
along timewise he can police the time
alright so what are we going in
a circle it's his quarterly i thought
we were just gonna go in a
circle
yeah and we would want to circle
alright so lorin go oh okay we'll
go clockwise slaughterhouse five
five easy pieces
pieces of
the heart nope
pieces of pieces of
pieces of pieces pieces of pieces i've
got one i don't go yeah i'm
gonna pass pieces of me which is
oh yes yeah oh
okay so you have me me so
horny
oh boy or oh you do okay
pass to you horny for horror oh
okay that's a podcast that's right okay
so you're turning out okay horror
movie oh i just realised we have
passes in this game yeah yeah only
huh
i just wondering when you were gonna
bring up that disguise say you guys
just kind of went along with once
okay let's start moving yes just started
that's hard does hard okay you you
start um
but are we starting over yeah well
okay yeah three men and a baby
baby boom boom there she was scary
political he
was
was the start to anything was there
it could be a question maybe oh
by the way pass ah
yeah about this if there's not a
you can rearrange the letters to create
something else so was a saw
and so then paul has to do
with it starts with saw because that's
the first and last word because they
saw those rewrites the letter rooney sassa
too
can i say it was not was
it's i mean it's a band i
think we should be able to allow
their name of something yeah okay so
then i'll say saw but then i
rearrange the list yeah so i'm gonna
rearrange the letters and say satu
a bus
okay too
two
i'm gonna just use the homonym ah
shing wong foo thanks for everything julie
newmar newmar newmar okay to wong foo
thanks for everything okay that's good yeah
that's more commonly it's more commonly known
as to wong foo thanks for everything
everything but the girl
girl talk it's a song title talking
heads
heads up seven up
up
for the downstroke
just drove me amadeus ah
um stroke
stroke stroke stroke stroke
mr scott stroke or the stroke thus
drugs yeah so i'm sorry you cannot
use it because it starts with the
pass oh wait pass stroke henry arranged
to iraq's
t t rocks t t rocks t
rocks iraq iraq
hey jay rock's that's what i was
trying to say oh you're saying oh
eighty raw huh he really does you
really does rock um deal one more
yeah go ahead paul you start okay
the empire strikes back back to the
future three
freedom oh so now three of them
you have to shoot sorts of three
dumb people town
town called malice i know it's a
college town called malice but afford me
this
malice speaking of a four
selim
salima
just pass back to me that's malice
of forethought
thought
imo you're out you can't do one
with thought thought i don't know what
about th ot that ho over there
kevin
kevin that over there huh tease our
little thoughts speaking of thoughts i had
a thought which is we need to
end yeah um guys i had five
minutes
a wait to see guy next week
and thanks for listening everyone we love
you love yay ny
ugh