sorry
oh
um secara by the same guy oh
yeah who needed help you didn't help
and we just passed him that was
oh yeah awareness carbine it was kinda
cruel huh
hong kong we almost got hit by
a mack truck and semi just got
on our ass and i yeah so
you say the word house gave me
a semi oh my guide oh circle
dirt and that's a harold and that
is where a herald is if you've
been wondering the high road and that's
a big coin and so
bitcoin com bitcoin herald everywhere i go
handing out bitcoins to everyone i know
here's a song that stuck in my
head and it's periodically stuck in my
head and i don't like it and
i have to purge it oh god
i have so many of those and
learn you heard me sing this earlier
you did
did i did it's a jingle for
i think a cracker that no longer
exists it might still exist i don't
know yeah but it goes like this
new bad or chatters sour dough bake
dryden delicious tasting better chatters the san
francisco style snack thin wow it sounds
really seventy s
sounds delicious i want to put it
at late eighties yeah yeah yeah and
it does sound delicious doesn't it windy
yeah when just having a big actually
reminds me of a song that was
an a real earworm in my house
yeah that my nephew made up
mac and cheese cheddar cheddar mac and
cheese better better whoa man you'll you
won't be able to stop singing i
swear to god oh man y'all won't
be able to something and i can
get cheddar cheese you're gonna be pretty
pebbles baby but you're gonna be singing
this mac and cheese chatter chatter mac
and cheese batter batter yeah okay yeah
i'll remember it's really annoying kasubi like
mac and cheese chan and chan and
makino
every you know you'll just start looking
into new versions yeah no one has
really taken up the offer that i
put out there of new version of
the oh no oh no so i
liked your version thank you let's hear
it but i think somebody should slap
some music on it and it should
be
here's my question you'll feel like you
have to make it on tik tok
just by itself or it can be
like stitched over as audio i think
it can be stitched overs owning a
one person did it and it's a
fan account for the two scared and
watch podcasts where they just laid my
audio acappella or acapulco is i heard
somebody say once
over um scene from jaws which was
funny so let's you know i was
like you didn't need to use a
qr code and so piss pigs
here you know audio his pigs unite
piss buys her this is your call
everyone out there buy one keyboard i'm
calling all piss pigs and the sound
of my voice even if ppp ppp
here goes yeah and you can use
this everyone's tired of the other one
yeah yeah what's this for by the
way this is for let's say you
want to post video or something is
going wrong and you know that someone
goes oh no oh no oh no
no no no no i don't but
go ahead guess
she's not spending much time online i
forgot i forgot a couple years god
is online for only six seconds a
day he literally goes oh he posts
my picture like morons picture ah the
two things i do ah so here
it goes you can hear it slap
some music onto this just slap it
on someone out there
who's good at this because you know
a lot of our piss pigs are
extremely talented musicians that's true the other
half are extremely untalented music but they're
really talented bankers what if we done
up bouncer was a piss pig oh
my gosh you had a blast on
tour right yeah you're in a tour
bus what else are you going to
appear to us you don't want to
talk to everyone all the time you
want to hear
some fun covers here in the back
of the van with the gear yeah
and no good bands listen to podcasts
say they should and should you'll need
to do but they should they should
because it's their duty they should all
right here we go and everybody quite
ooh oh ooh oh oh no no
no no oh
it's it's beautiful leaseback you're holding back
laughter no imagine like some strings on
the yeah do you mean no obo
rarely fun and obo oh it's a
bus and you put that over like
oh bo oh boo but not over
like a video of a cat that's
like about to jump into a pool
it doesn't know that it's there because
it got scared by raccoon or
you know yeah these are just one
of these things don't know yeah sure
just stuff like that that just something
that happens cats about the gem of
the police know it's there because you
got scared by raku he's just going
look just
anyway yeah commercials don't really have songs
anymore other than for drugs do you
do we still get the song um
yeah because they have they go like
oh zappa couldn't believe that yeah i
was sitting there going really but then
there's the geraghty in one which is
oh na na na na
the little pill with the big fat
says i present to you one less
one less one less one less yeah
i don't i thought that was majority
and it might not be oh damn
oh other commercials have used that too
yeah the oh it's magic yeah yeah
yeah like but what if you would
if you could keep any commercial from
using the same song that you did
if i really singer ah if i'm
the writer and owner of the song
oh oh it's magic every e-commerce every
commercial you want yeah sure you want
it have you thought about this i'll
just ah just cold calling program like
hearing your products or the oh bro
oh it's oh real till going concern
are they still show pow so either
champagne problems for some reason i really
was into the idea of prowl when
i was a kid the advertising worked
on me yeah oh right what was
the
i don't remember why it would work
or it was just like well when
it was tar i don't remember the
commercial was i just remember i liked
the name i liked the color yeah
i liked what it promised yeah and
of course pert you will get bouncing
nba plus per plus for me why
would anyone buy just peart if there
was pert plus yeah i mean come
on
wow did you ever get a big
mac because you could get lint get
triple chocolate to a big mac why
did you buy one hamburger would be
fifty five years so i really would
you marry your view of hamburgers hot
dogs fifty five comprising i remember avoiding
the shame of someone ah seeing that
i had shampoo and conditioner in one
one because i heard wow they went
how old are you i buy my
like early twenties yeah because then you're
like you recently learned that you're supposed
to have two yeah like oh girls
are gonna think i'm exactly because we're
all happier even taking showers oh no
but it's so guys so guide to
just your beds on the floor yeah
will you marry i'm billing conditioner
one
that on the floor yeah toilet with
a ring pants on the ground tub
with a ring yeah yeah it was
but i heard a woman shaming like
making fun starter dude and i was
like oh i bet you guys so
many guys have changed things from that
moment that is lear a woman
and say that they're they're from like
this guy had a fucking mattress on
the floor and he's gotta get a
bed getting every thought of it totally
gotta get a bit yeah
yeah my cat how hard is her
get one but mike had a one
on the floor mattress on the floor
why it's when when we started dating
really just a mattress still think it
was on interest on a box spring
or it was yeah yeah yeah but
it was worse
i mean yeah junior high and then
i made him get a home bed
i like picked it out and then
yeah and you picked on how important
box springs yeah like you had to
ah i mean i feel like i
still but but honestly can i just
say he was in his twenties and
yeah every guy that's true but i
know you still toys cradle robber
yeah wow hi u y la honey
yeah i had a futon for a
long oh that's really bad did joseph
that's worse than a message
not a bed did you also have
agree leather couch
that you couldn't sleep on because it's
light on i mean my friend was
somehow very deep but completely uncomfortable right
my like where my best friends in
college who was a bit older than
me let just a few years but
at that time made a big difference
but he had a futon that folded
down it was like on a metal
frame yeah again it couldn't be
show because it was his couch as
well as his bed right but he
was never starving for pushy
how many did he have how many
fish
i like john i think five right
now um yeah we should think everyone
who's ever had sex with us back
to your previous point you know what
yes let's get that out of the
way in the first segment i think
men should think and women should do
whatever they want to regarding that i
don't think women should thank everyone i
think women should thank us i don't
think so
i'd appreciate
i mean how about waiting for thinking
about if it was good if it
was good yeah if it was good
and if it's not good i'll i'll
take a lie man i should thank
everyone so then that's a lady so
everyone like you forever yeah i'll take
a lie probably making lie but okay
i knew to think i don't think
yeah i mean
i don't need it for every single
time she just needed for the aggregate
like the total i'm going to stay
out of it you can go try
to get those
if i did a high fidelity yeah
tracked down my old girlfriend you just
say all i want is a thank
you i want to say thank you
for having checked with me and and
you'd like to say ah so gross
so gross the idea of sales girls
girls girls girls so
um what's going on with you guys
since the last time we yeah home
yeah i need to know what's going
on at home now now lauren you've
ah oh well i have ah a
little bit of a story yeah i
wish my brother and sister-in-law and then
their two kids visited us recently oh
and no i made you know i
planned a lot of fun activities for
us so we went to la we
went to universal studios we did
mario we did super nintendo land oh
no here it goes on but i
got a lot of tips and i
can share them if anybody got all
the foyer have you been an intend
to land i have not heard it
was heard of a lot of sound
have you missed it it's like instagram
was just inundating me with intended land
i was shit i thought i heard
it was a lot a lot of
sound and fury signifying nothing
way to tell told by an idiot
yes okay i disagree it was really
fun wow that's my review of nintendo
land i just heard tale told by
an idiot i heard you had to
wait along like three wells so so
here's the tip this was like most
people here to do and ultimately people
told me that just the tip okay
and i was and i was trying
to avoid it but my nephews have
been talking about it for a long
time so they were really excited yeah
to go and i was like we
have to go to nintendo we have
to ride on the the rise thankfully
the most important thing at universal for
that thankfully our nephew did not care
one way or the let's get his
otherwise i mean it was my idea
initially because it was seemed easier than
disney which ultimately it was because i
usually take them disney don't buy it
so they took the fast one
so anyways we'd everyone said get get
the early pass so okay right off
the batter there for now right after
that the ticket to be the tickets
are based are not one solid price
it's every day they're there they vary
slightly so why pick a popular day
it's more expensive all come on and
then on universal dando
and you should be universal basic ticket
price it should be and then just
this springsteen suddenly thirty dollars me that
per person to get into early access
yes all right i'm going these tickets
are about to eat rival disneyland prices
yeah and there's not there's not much
to do yeah and then we get
there we
got everybody up at the crack of
dawn at the butt hah anyway so
at seven we were out of the
house by six thirty we were like
we were everybody oh how did holly
feel about it she was thanks or
my cousin her neck her cousins were
there so it's exciting though she's time
what does that and we can tell
aren't if your toddler's like it's six
thirty yes what i said about
wow meanwhile mine is like six thirty
am like pounding on the crib get
me get me to sleep in so
um we got there really early was
still dark ding dong hello we're here
for nintendo land but there was barely
anyone there and we got on the
ride the ride still was like a
forty minute wait still forty minutes when
you get there that ur
early and then the second we got
off the ride was one hundred sixty
minute wait yeah sh so we really
got to do it there's just we
also we also ate at the toadstool
cafe they pack so many people in
there and there's nothing to do so
they often wait for three hours now
i think now the toadstool cafe some
of the food might be poisonous is
that right yeah yeah yeah and some
might give you hallucinations yeah and you
have to rely
and onion soup makes yoni yeah wow
why were you oh did you was
it fun though it was a fun
ride it was really it was really
fun um it's very v are based
and like it you have to kind
of play a game with your eyes
and stuff just like bopping my head
all over the place i go idiot
i'm sure i but i did reach
the number of points that was
i told i had to reach some
and then what what did you get
i not turn i was saving those
fucking nothing oh by the way you
also buy the kids forty dollar wristband
yeah play all the games and the
and the section and you don't have
the wristband and can't play the games
and you're spending so much when they're
forty i was like why is it
forty this is crazy and it's useless
when you
leave the place it looks like mario
thing it's like that's cool but it's
not like the watch to be a
watch right i'll go to a public
park for free will look they they
they can and i'll feed the pigeons
i don't know if i always say
like we will do less next i'm
like oh i will do more i
went to a place where i could
have a million adventures it's called the
public librarian yeah right
yeah and mario's in there too yeah
there's a lot of books about mario
and we also had to beat fe
and that was really fucking ny ever
see the ocean do you we we
i try i wanna try to only
only when we go type carolina yeah
yeah i pass on yeah if i'm
on vacation activity the ocean but i
passed on the beach day this time
when my nephew was there but he
ended up waking up and not going
because he drank milk
shakes every day he was here and
didn't feel good that morning my guy
mini like more than one little chickadee
occasionally two a day does it do
you have a milkshake maker like you've
done in the blow he would he
would just get ice cream out of
the freezer and put it in a
glass and pour milk it well that's
not a milk shake that's good
give you a stomach ache
that's how we're different you blaming kids
are so funny like that was like
that's delicious he's done it does sound
delicious to me i mean to be
blended up a little bit ice cream
and milk yeah thanks yeah there's nothing
else and resolved goddamn kids trying to
tell me hey i know but we
had a great time it was always
happening so fun
to see the kids altogether did you
go to the waterworld stunt spectacular or
not but they did get to ride
jurassic which is only like a five
minute wait because everyone was at mario
land the new jurassic i have not
been on i have any old one
i loved yeah are you in the
new one um my picture is in
the movie but i oh yes but
i'm not in the right but i
did feel a little dorky stay
ending right outside of it waiting for
them to come out waiting to be
recognized i was just felt a little
bit like i should move from the
sign but but then you're trying to
see them come out of the ride
because they they go on a water
party yeah and so my picture of
them yeah which was funny yes and
did and no one noticed you um
one person did but it was for
another movie oh and then they asked
me if i knew adam sandler
so they named their son after him
i have to go
ah so that we named your our
daughter the wrong missy
ah um well that's a lot of
fun so you had a good a
good visit it was so nice i
appreciate the effort you know it takes
a lot to fly with the gauge
the shariah yeah sure to us
um yeah we had a good time
with the nephew ah he went to
raging waters without us i feel like
i'm too old for raging waters even
though what did he go with he
went with ah cool club sister oh
okay it sounds like he like got
on a bus yeah yeah it's san
demus old hobo bindle
but i've but i am too old
to go on probably raging waters wow
i don't think we're gonna have we're
gonna have fun there i doubt i
will just a bunch of water soil
and water slides oh it's a water
park is a waterpark i've been there
so many times i love it oh
really and i just feel like i
was kind of like i just don't
think i can do it i i
could i feel like
i could do it if i somehow
had the park ulta myself yeah that's
how i felt too hey when i
think about being rented rented out just
you know you don't wanna stand in
line with kids
just ya
yes too if i was rich that's
what i would do yeah yeah those
are for school and and rents ranging
instead of water it would be chuckled
but that is honestly it's not that
much different than how billionaires are i
was thinking about that today like all
the shit that they don't do that
would be beneficial it's so annoying it's
like i'm going to build rockets it
was already well awesome if i had
a
billion dollars to find a billion dollars
i would rent raging waters well sure
that would be one oh my what's
like thousand dollars and you're done my
one luxury thing like it has to
be more than a thousand i'm sure
it is it's gotta be at least
i wonder how much for one day
my eleven hundred dollars it's no it's
gotta be i'd say twenty thousand right
oh wow i've been on a waterslide
since i was a kid who give
me guglielmi but i one thing i
remember about them and i'm i assume
a place like raging waters is better
than my local you know little pool
open pool with water water slides kind
of thing that i would go to
as a kid that wasn't a water
park it was a place with slides
right
but those ridges in the slide like
so yeah and a slice you can
measure like your bag is in the
sly you know yeah dabbler the next
all the tubes that's the falling i
have in my body when i go
yeah yeah think of that and hopefully
there's enough water but if if suddenly
it's dry then you'll come you're like
a skateboard going over a sidewalk exam
exactly paul and if you step on
a back crack you bake your mother
my back i'll go into that some
other crack break your mother's neck back
pussy that can happen it can happen
and will you if you do a
real nasty fall you can bring them
all at once step on my mother
back you when you step on your
mother's back freak my pussy
alright we have to take a break
and we're back and i don't i
don't see any i looked up renting
raging waters and all i see are
locker rentals well how much does that
cost
well because it's run a locker reggie
water yeah that's five dollars that's good
we should do that jimmy could do
that lately i'm looking for storage space
right now i feel like
yeah it must be kind of hard
with going to a waterpark with the
phone these days we were like i
want to view it but like i
go on the ride but then i
get my phone to somebody will i
go oh i guess phones are waterproof
what what basically all iphones are waterproof
now is that true sort of pity
they did the okay phone jack the
they do it yeah put it in
the toilet that's why they did the
headphone jack the way they did it
square rectangle because i can't get into
square rectangle waterland ra circles like water
goes around because like no tub
like well only like some weird tab
but most tubs don't have like a
rectangular around is round yeah the hole
is round yeah do sometimes a little
rectangular just imagine some fancy modern bullshit
that has ah you know rectangular iranian
you probably have it yeah i got
all i have a rectangular dream
hey the street has them yeah you
know what i mean yeah it stays
dad's area down there yeah pennywise yes
where he lives it the clone have
you seen him
no what's what's zionism bank yeah oh
yeah she looks good yes those epic
face
i've seen pound foolish what's that is
pennywise other other shop oh out you
guys got me and that wasn't riley
fucking god no it wasn't it was
not right but you want to know
what's happening with me and oh yeah
yeah what's happening with you at home
nothing really hey
guys do during the hurricane to hit
you hard a great question we spent
the entire day watching and pump room
as hurricanes intended it was kind of
exciting it's in the way if you
don't know california was hit by its
first tropical storm it was scary and
it's scary what happened in certain areas
but once we sort of realised it
wasn't going to be that crazy in
our area yeah you could just enjoy
a rainy day a little bit because
we never get rain like that so
you're kind of an animal being called
l a d j i'm not saying
we needed it or something it was
it was very weird and it was
scary and there was an earthquake in
the middle bit but while you ain't
were able to huddle up with your
family or
loved one and watch a movie we
all we live in three separate areas
the three of us we don't live
together we don't live together and not
anymore everybody thick no yes dvd yeah
you still have two guys one mattress
oh boy we started the show yeah
he had a double king-sized mattress on
the floor yeah boat so we live
in three totally separate
areas and even rely feel like we
have three different experiences yeah so paul
huh
because there's two things the rain level
and your way hitting the floor so
paul how is your rain level rain
level was in the morning when it
was supposed to be you know you're
i thought i'm gonna wake up to
torrential downpour and it was a soundless
drizzle right and janie was on high
alert all day frozen
around she was like what if we
have to get on the roof wow
what happened i don't think it's gonna
happen yeah but i think we'll have
plenty of warning yeah if that should
yeah once you get one inch you
can start to think about that yeah
yeah but we are close to the
river yeah yeah um but it was
i did not i didn't think anything
was going to happen but it is
like because there's so much talk about
it and of course the news love
to do it we weren't watching news
all day but we were getting alerts
and shit like that and so we
were kind of like janie more so
than i was but sort of like
is this going to be bad what's
like waiting for the
vacation that is going to be bad
and then it was just a rainy
day um which i did once i
kind of settled into nothing yeah but
we had some tree damage that was
pretty crazy yeah we're gonna get to
you okay so so paul water-level not
not anything different than a normal rainy
rainy day not really no i have
not yet looked in the garage where
we do have a leak oh no
that's gonna be a drag not to
look in that garage it's hard to
leave your jew scans it's gonna make
it's gonna bomb ya it's like i
know it's in there i know there's
bunch of water against that wall yeah
okay now i really have to go
look at it right now so that
i can do yeah now learn your
water level um it was raining hard
i've heard that you have some tree
damage and we have tree damage so
true damage there was a point when
i was just kind of putting around
the house and i saw spending caught
my eye in the window and i
thought oh it's been almost flew at
the window but then i looked up
and there was nothing out there and
then puttering yeah what's putting nothing it's
another thing
okay and then if you a little
bit later i realized that it was
actually a huge tree branch that had
fallen and it was on the ground
but i didn't notice it when i
looked on tight pants yeah on the
ground right german roads and then throughout
the day big huge branches were falling
and they all fell right into the
path so it wasn't dangerous right like
none of them were now like above
the house or anything like that oh
i don't know that i'm aware of
and but everyone was like why is
this happening to you because it's not
that windy yeah and then um my
landscape person came to clean it up
today thankfully and because huge they're like
they're like six feet long yeah
you sent pictures and they were like
i'd say six feet long yeah yeah
they were huge branches and really heavy
and um he said that i have
to trim the trees and he's gonna
do it more often i'm not gonna
do it um because they're really heavy
old burn but this this is really
interesting tree that has a lot of
flour like it's like flowery leaves and
it's always filled with bees like at
this time
of year there's hundreds of bees in
the morning it's like xo you just
hear like the whole yard is humming
with bees because short dick to flower
i was a little bit okay with
losing a lot of low-hanging parts out
with be that's right girl um even
though it's a shady spot i'm and
now i can see that there's other
branches
bending and snapping so he's gonna come
get excuse it gets dangerous if it
bans if it's dangerous yeah if it
breaks it's on the ground yeah but
you know the good thing is the
bees probably weren't in there because of
the rain and they all got away
oh thank god i know debbie's no
one is going to rain there like
see later they probably hide a little
bit yeah hide
aid men so well how is your
unit smaller ring could really fuck you
up yeah probably like one drop you
could drown boiling you could drown everywhere
we go i'm sure you could oh
we were if you
yeah we were being attacked by dragonflies
the other day and i was attacked
we were in the pool and they
just words like constantly i think they
were trying to figure out how to
get above the fence because you know
how they fly pretty low to the
ground and they just worked they somehow
got in then were like how the
fuck do we get out and they're
just working around us we were like
it's like ah what's that word
for catch twenty two
what are those things that fly in
film people go drones drones drones which
is another thing when they term for
bees so true bestie yeah there are
these were drones yeah it's awesome and
they're just your winnings there'll be inter
queens and they slay yes bees you
slay
babies just such a thing as a
queen bean um like like mr bean
like a black bean yeah yeah oh
you're both are always kind of being
a queen bean garbanzo like i'm thinking
of like if there's a in every
can of beans there's one there's one
clean queen bee it's the one who
knows it's the most important should do
that because it's like any other beans
protected cracker jacks
so fun and they got so popular
because of the priors yeah so far
you would buy more beans if you
like were able to get the queen
bee you know what i think is
fair to say cracker jacks none of
peanuts mix it up yeah that's why
they say at the ballgame buy me
some peanuts and cracker jacks because i
know the cracker jacks not have enough
pie
i got one last time i had
a craft yeah not that long ago
really i had recently but i'm like
you know all these toys are just
they're just tattoos and stickers now yeah
give me a toy they need to
refresh give me a bugle yeah put
us in charge of the cracker jacks
i said i want rollers okay put
us in charge of em you'll have
roller skates inside of the bottom of
the box at
and your sales will go through the
roof and so did you drown during
the hurricane so our our rain level
was practically nothing and then i think
i was texting you like we're not
getting anything and then at a certain
point it came down kinda hard and
for about maybe an hour and i
was at it honestly hot rained harder
earlier in the year oh my god
yeah like the bro that was insane
i had yeah so many weeks
so that was disappointing but then the
earthquake happened and paul what was your
earthquake experience my name is greg experience
was janie isn't a chair i am
on a couch she's not on that
roofie we feel she's dying on the
roof but she's poised she's standing on
the climb she's standing on there going
is that all you got
we use this said that tada
yeah
so we we feel the house shaking
and then we of course we even
though we know one of us will
look at the other say an earthquake
yeah because of course it could be
a weather related thing where it's like
your house is blowing down oh marsh
gas why are you trying you calling
me that why
ah a weather balloon um and so
it's like one of those ones where
it was it was kind of rolling
for a while really and you're thinking
what do we do now i certainly
don't want to move i don't think
i've ever moved properly during one no
i mean i live i've never done
the right thing to be used to
say go
onto the doorway and now i think
now they say don't go into don't
come in the doorway but i used
to get under a table yes yes
that's for nato's yeah um i oh
wait what did the alert say because
the alert was lured dealer was like
a funny to me there's like shake
drop and rolling grab your ass kissing
goodbye
um i feel like my response with
earthquake always is i just am sitting
there going come along just gonna go
lift your head up a little bit
and go like and then it was
the same thing i need to pay
to do and then right at the
point where i start to get worried
like it's still going it stops and
then i but then i always reflect
on i don't know what to do
here's what the emergency alert said earthquake
detected drop cover hold on protect yourself
usbs shake alert drop cover hold of
island pretend those are really helping me
know drop sure but sure half cover
with what
what mike arms yeah i guess yes
this was supposed to fold my arms
like i'm gonna get up and fold
my arms right now and shake my
head to go ah earthquake secondly better
to have broken early post technically better
to have broken arms and broken head
and so yeah it's definitely better to
have a broken arm that a broken
head yeah let's play put your arms
i don't think that's technical yeah i
think that's a fact absolutely it's better
to end here i was during the
earthquake dear it's better to be alive
than dead i guess i do i
was napping and i didn't know you
know about it but my phone was
doing a lot of vibrate
thing and it was like me cause
i didn't put it on sleep mode
and it was like going crazy and
then there was a a week a
lot of vibrate and then a lot
of one long room where i was
i was one of those alerts about
the flooding oh yeah and then like
when i woke up and saw fifty
texts for her lying they do feel
that and i was like no i
didn't and i don't think we would
have i don't think mike didn't feel
it like did i feel
but thank you for me would you
like to feel these urkel
grandma always texts me
we didn't feel it at all paul
saying earthquake was the only on a
text chain was the only indication that
we had an earthquake yeah yeah yeah
and i'm glad to bring you that
news yeah it's great i love to
get news like that yes so we
had a very quiet day the concert
was going into her quick oh yeah
we're having fun that's how this funny
however once the ah the cars
ncert we were going to that night
got postponed very very thankfully because at
the hollywood bowl there like rain or
shine that's crazy but you can't bring
umbrella's what is the other thing rain
or shine your shop bringing bringing in
there and a bunch of fuckin poncho
who who aren't you she is worth
that i honestly can't think of anybody
that i would want it that we
were
with it to sit there in a
fucking raincoat or whatever at this stage
in life i'm not doing that i
would say if i was taught anyone
i will say and it started ringing
during it when i did bonnaroo maybe
they let us they they put us
in these vp sections for just to
see bunch of people and we saw
tom petty and start raining in the
middle of tom petty and it was
but it wasn't
like hard so it was fun yeah
but ah and it let it you
know stopped about to do twenty minutes
in do you think that's what killed
it that times doing this culture in
the race lifting fell timing got rain
fell and he died his wound was
i was five years before he actually
it was a body yeah after that
no yeah
why didn't they keep using him how
are you going he knows that
yeah yeah why did the body double
have to die
because he'd just like beggar belief build
the body double it was just too
long it was just too long it
was like a leaf barred believe what
beggared belief yeah it beggared belief beggared
belief so people were not straight not
continuing to believe it i'm just trying
to understand this phrase it's like cured
but it's like you're laying over
keyless playing with the devil my god
with the dough i think they didn't
know what it was double
oh beautiful him to our mighty lord
the devil oh someone is what if
imagine if the devil was real if
he was here i would have to
laugh he'd be like i'm just read
hi if i'm naked to read i
have a tale ever drawn with clothes
xs do you like my my session
beard e i'm gonna get you you're
gonna have a bad time with me
i'm tempting you to do things why
don't you steal that candy bar
when you eat that candy bar oh
yeah i we saw friends when we
were in south carolina shout out to
my friend elise din and then then
then then then
nah nah nah nah do so you
no one told you to have friends
should know so you so here's so
here's been tapped so you so you
so you say
look here
ah
huh okay so snow can we do
it the other day was j last
was going to be this way but
um yeah more songs you have cloud
cover clapping i agree there's a bunch
i do oh like what come on
you know
this under pressure getting a medal will
have claps no i don't mean just
having claps i mean that specific cloud
under pressure but you should've said so
now i'm tripping out a whole fantasy
so like we didn't start the fire
would be like noooo babe babe babe
babe blip blip blip
blueprint paper yeah i'm trying to have
another one but i can't but i
know there are more it's it's it
is astonishing how many people have done
updated versions of we didn't start the
fire or personalized versions of we didn't
start i don't know what the personalized
i know fall out boy just did
the new yes the nouveau italy i
didn't notice there are if you go
to youtube there are
many many versions of we didn't start
the fire where people either updated it
or they have made it about like
their graduating class or it's fun they
get married and you know the men
like that idea we were like i
would date you like the idea but
we did not hate you said thank
you for the sex
yeah we went on a date i'm
doing it god did you hear my
line you should thank you for the
sex
we went to the cineplex yeah so
thanks for the sex you go to
the set of like this guy yea
you had dipping in and i had
raise in nets but just like full
sex going to the cineplex
checks yeah so he writes a few
bets yeah i guess pity sex out
of that
many thanks many thanks we would do
this and then say you thank you
for the sex
that's x is x two different types
is it bad checks and checks pity
sex
it takes good
and you think we've caught the sun
i can't say what next
nothing like a
historical
and then aladdin
what the heck's
ah wait what
some specs oh so sanjay had we
had lunch with friends that their home
and our friend lease made us this
shimmied like a gumbo and she made
this mate of this amazing cornbread that
was like the best run around and
then for dessert she made this peanut
butter mousse cake that was delicious
wow sounds so good my wife that's
okay go my way that's my kind
of dessert she had some leftover um
hershey's bars i left over yeah because
the recipe called for it and you'll
like you you shave ah like you
chocolate on top of the thing right
and so yeah hershey bar class
like hershey bar okay like with little
squares yeah i mean sure rectangle heard
of it the little rectangles you'll write
like my my my dream apologize yeah
like your train and so there was
some leftover and she gave she would
give the ah she gave the liver
to her husband who ate the rest
of the hershey bar
and then she said
you know like one time i started
him just like eating just like a
whole hershey bar like a whole thing
and she's like this is very strange
yeah it's like why they sell them
she said who is a whole candy
bar and i was like i oh
yeah most people you're looking at who
has two thumbs and he's one
yeah that you can be bad especially
place fairly they're very thin chocolate it's
yeah it's you know it's not like
a dark thick dark chocolate or something
you'd have a particular kind of dark
although i have to say it's like
one percent cao yeah it's like only
if i buy my real chocolate oh
growing up you would you know like
how much did they cost maybe twenty
five thirty cents something like that i
thought were going to say dollars and
i was like what sometimes you being
one hundred and fifty dollars for you
know but but you would save up
allowance and stuff i still think about
like how crazy it is to that
you would eat a whole one they're
so giant and you're so little
for a kid to eat for kids
eat you know what any horrible like
how little are you that it's so
giant you have to be very smart
shippers aren't huge hershey bars are kind
of shit bars are huge
will ever so what do you think
slim and petite
shanda what has more mass a three
musketeers bar or a hershey bar um
oh well like yes of course fluffy
marshmallow i guess i would say with
um i would say her she has
more mass it feels like in my
mind the hershey bar is heavier than
the three that's how i feel but
i want away
this yeah i've had a real phase
with three musketeers in fifth grade that
was like i want that all the
time plus dr pepper now that is
not newgate but it is whipped i'm
so whipped maybe to whipped nugget it's
like a mark almost a marshmallow e
center what are your classic new git
candy bars nuggets sneakers has a new
git ranks does have just a layer
of newgate three musketeers has newgate okay
so we're already seeing that i have
well i was looking up your answer
so don't chime in
ah well my feeling wow we went
too far by we had sex big
checks and everybody does everybody do the
flex
solo play um
okay the weight of a hershey's candy
bar bad checks wait bad checks wait
wait to see bad chick right wait
wait wait bad checks wait no wait
wait i bad checks bags anyway will
it what did you do it so
you sleep sang jokes so you got
to know way way way way way
way
bad checks with eighty six hit me
in the solar blood
wait wait
dicks ever vs x yeah remember ballistic
expert vs sever um okay so the
weight of a hershey's this is oh
yeah graphs this is with almond pieces
that standard bar one shoe with almonds
if that changes the weight i know
changes the look of it too and
the taste
i know i think they're i think
they're both the exact same okay like
yeah that's weird it's not possible weight
is one point five five ounces one
point five five ellen payne five i
don't see it now you must go
to each of her chiba three musketeers
one point three
five nine two no so what's upset
that's community believe so so technically you're
eating more with the three musketeers but
it doesn't feel like it to me
no it doesn't it doesn't it doesn't
because it's fluffier yeah one hundred percent
what were your go to candy bars
when you were a kid
three musketeers with my mouth tears was
a bad phase but i read i
loved mom m and them snickers to
an eminent yeah yeah butter twix aw
oh wait wait wait wait and then
with my brother and now moody and
then with the invention of the take
five everything really took off for me
sure
sure sure sure how about you ah
i was oh we just been pickups
sorry i recently had take five ice
cream jimmies oh and jenny yok by
jenny's daddy's next love jesus crushing it
guys hey my screen jesus slaying like
a badass okay i want that slick
grown i you know i like
jenny isn't sending me like boxes of
ice cream like they do with a
lot of people what's going on with
chinese days they're not sending us boxes
of ice cream for free don't you
get boxes like oh honey yeah i
got one bottle from them but i
want boxes and box i've never gotten
any and i feel jealous i will
say that i have gotten two boxes
there you go jenny's i want my
second box and then i want
a lot of boxes after that but
what about lauren's first box jenny's ginny
i want lawrence first box ah this
is working out oh we we wait
wait wait wait wait we gotta take
a break but do do it one
more time i want i want i
know that your song oh okay bad
checks hello
bad checks lazy sags hit me on
the solar plant takes me to the
cineplex thank me for this
or will be
and we're back and paul you at
a you have a three-tier i do
have is it through xiaomo rent it
is holy shame magic can't believe i
obviously can't this is one speaking of
singing oh la la la we haven't
done this in a
a while ah only didn't once and
i believe that we only did it
what else to say oh this is
a thresher that is called
i have bad tunes for you okay
i have bad tunes for you this
is where one person comes up with
some bad news that has to be
delivered okay another person comes up with
a song that everybody knows
and the ah and the remaining person
has to deliver the bad news to
the tune of janis that's okay vaguely
remember this i vaguely remember this and
i'm gonna say right now we didn't
start fires off the table damn here
that's the only time we can think
of right now
who would like to be the first
deliverer of the musical bad news oh
shy one lauren yes scott would you
prefer to come up with the song
or with the bad news ah i'll
come up with the bad news alright
are you going i shall come up
and checks me or tell me right
now yeah
your texture because i think that's fun
yeah i think that's fun for the
listener checks the bad news i'll text
the bad new objects the song o
k and your name by the way
so i can find it in my
text i think you have me saved
as bitch i hain
okay i am texting the bad news
okay to lauren and she has received
the bad news and not all i
have texted song song and is delivered
quietly
okay who am i telling it to
both of those ideologies hey we're one
person hey hey guy
hello
um i'm really glad i caught you
before you're about to head to work
i'm thinking maybe yeah thank you i'm
thinking maybe you should stay home i
don't know if he should be conducting
a train with the news oh but
i can
ford who stay home while i just
don't want you to be in charge
of conducting a train with the news
mobile but but but but but but
that's my life's work choo choo well
let me just try to tell you
what happened maybe it'd be softer in
a song
i have news for you i'm going
to share i'm going to share i'm
going to share i have some news
very i'm going to share ah i'll
tell you know your uncle was riding
on a roller coaster
her he went down and ah
he jumped out to try to stop
it with his arm because he wanted
to be like superman and the roller
coaster ran over him it broke his
clavicle in three spots in three
three spots it broke his clavicle and
their spots and though rez says biden
yeah
how do you feel to jews as
you go oh don't choose you
okay we get it yeah yeah alright
great i like it okay i'll go
next okay all right so paul you're
gonna text me the thing that's wrong
yeah and i'll send you the song
this is exciting this is too exciting
almost
i almost don't want to do this
because it's too exciting
yeah let's quit
you guys are the most silent textures
oh my gosh the song has been
set the song is sent i have
received the song and now i got
to receive that bad news that i'm
gonna deliver to the tune dead lawrence
sent me lee if you can if
i
a dare do it which i think
i just wow delivered
okay
hi guys hi your one okay yeah
that's right i'm molly
well um
you don't know who i am who
are you i'm the local anchorman from
the new
that's right that is what a local
anchorman is from and
when i'm not on camera i go
around delivering news wow two people do
do they pay you
this is a case if if you
like the job that i did you
can tip me afterwards ooh we'll see
so i have some news for you
do you
oh i'd like to deliver it for
me yes i like that
well one thing i don't get to
do on the news is i don't
get to sing because songs are copyrighted
and on the news you can't i
don't care that you're tommy lee jones
impression yeah yes pretty good pretty good
thank you what a year and again
okay
i don't care it's perfectly you do
the face do yeah credible i know
okay third time's not as good yeah
alright well i'm gonna sing you this
news and i hope that afterwards if
you find it in your heart
give me a few bucks you know
let's hear pads hot pants you heard
me
last night you occur cake and one
of you left the oven on then
it caught fire and it burned your
house to the ground but that's not
the bad
bad news there's more to calm your
baseball card czar gone yes that's right
go house burn right down to the
studs yeah baseball cards are gone no
what happened upset with my choice is
gone oh noes i'm upset i have
exam oh boy i'm alive on my
own oh no split in to do
that's my backside i'm going to bring
evil upon the world oh and
my cardigan know what's worse guy oh
god oh god
alright now it goes to payload comes
to me out on jody i'm gonna
take some news
i'm texting the song
i've texted and then the song great
song
ooh i saw that that was the
ah by the way the first song
ever slow dance too
that's really yeah oh time after time
not the song you just texted no
um
yeah that's the first thing i ever
slow dance to and ah and there
was a lot of like oh how
far how low can my hands go
here oh and you know what
the butt
you went all the way down i
went all the way down you are
given the green light i didn't go
all the way down to the shoes
be funny that's how low you want
to go
touch the back of your foot your
heels
in the zoo over the zoo okay
ready okay
hi there
hey i'm sorry to wait i had
to tell you something but i love
you oh that's very nice okay okay
don't don't don't come up we're worried
about what homeboy come on thanks i
want way work yeah
i want to have some extra fifty
okay this is
this actually reinforces my respect this actually
actually reinforces my decision um i have
some bad news for you know i
want good do i know and that's
what i want to give you but
i can't
oh my goodness yeah right goodness good
news you can't do a one person
chance it's ridiculous i yes did it
they look like
yeah i know high speed yeah i
mean i know i know i say
mitchell because i'm freddy krueger but i
am your boss and i need you
to stop calling me that o e
um guess king h
i have seen let's imagine isn't i
think the only way i can deliver
it and not burst into tears is
by delivering it in song
well ok here we go
damn employees
i've gathered you here today to tell
you about this they call your job
and now it's not gonna be what
you thought it was gonna be
because your job is different now
because in this company
you're on your own meaning you fight
because you know that child
the one that came in here the
other day with a job application
well he got your job
it's always this life
you know we're ready whoa
only doing that writing this book i
can't think of how i yeah i
can't make to take of like the
melody of the lyrics zoom zoom better
do you liddy the bell do lady
z angel ben de la de da
da
do you really oh no i don't
don't don't don't do yeah why don't
you put that down yeah i don't
know why i didn't do it i
do think let's go crazy we'd be
better if printed started by saying dear
employees
yeah they've talked about this thing called
job
huh well i'm sorry i feel like
i let down the three i was
very high like a joy that way
that was if i could have gone
into the leery have would have to
know but that's what made it really
funny i thought it was funny or
christian because it still counts as the
song it is young well guys could
have would have should have
if you would like to send us
a three-tier wanted to write to us
at three-time usa gmail dot com you
can follow us on the socials three
m usa and if you'd like to
call us it was a voicemail you
can call it hag claims eight it's
great and if you like your ad
free versions of this show
why don't you go to cbc world
com which i call hell
um yeah and then follow us ah
at social media at three am usa
yeah so that's great oh also follow
us on social media three the usa
no no no hold on
um shows if you missed the super
ego show at dynasty where we did
ulysses improvised ulysses um it's archived identity
typewriter dot com yeah watch it there
um also sunday no sunday september tenth
me nicole parker the two hosts of
the neighborhood
listen that's right i'm excluding brett for
these purposes good um we will be
doing our two-person variety show at lodge
room in highland park not a lot
of variety only two people
there's more than two people wow a
weary because there's a full band o
a lot of variety they count as
people a lot of er i've never
thought musicians count sb and they're all
different heights okay yeah yeah yeah like
someone's for one yeah they go from
four one two i wanna say seven
three okay good yeah
and they're all standing in oregon size
order one of them might be a
tuba
they are a touma with goog yeah
yeah i did think that was a
person yeah i do but look also
ah october fourteen scary months scary very
scary month but here's something that's not
scary a fun show yeah variety topi
alive at the bell house in brooklyn
early shows sold out late show
those are moving so make sure you
get them tickets this is gonna be
fun to different show from friday to
saturday so make a weekend of it
why don't you do that why don't
you do that that sounds like fun
it is to new york in october
yeah oh what a loud i'm in
new yo yeah that was beautiful crazy
i was lucky
pity sex right spot jimmy graham to
see what shows i'm doing and that's
my update yeah there you go yeah
um that's great thank good-bye ah
uh