three
oh
um
oh um
ah three to oh what have you
said um that lowry you were trying
to figure huh
ah but if that was your curse
and you had to because it which
made you
you couldn't do anything about and you
couldn't tell people that you were cursed
by a whale
who you never can have you guys
run into any witches a gentleman doesn't
what did you have have you run
into any witches and all of your
travels yeah yeah you haven't
broomsticks of course a cursed yours that
like is that like a chore for
them is that like we've got don't
be naive carries when they have to
yes if you do what you love
you never work a day in your
life they love cursing people
welcome to threesome and point of order
we should mention we are not in
the backyard
like what to do with zuma zoom
zoom zoom in the boom
we're over zoom dude due to weather
concerns just shake your rump
um and also one thing we should
mention about last week's episode that was
done in the backyard is that if
you know what i mean many of
you have asked us why their last
music playing during the last i don't
know twenty minutes of it that is
because my neighbor um it was a
weekend and my neighbor
was out by the pool and just
started blasting ah music and i am
scott's neighbor full disclosure that's right yes
fallen i lived next to your pool
i went from scott's yard to my
yard turn my music up as loud
as possible then came back to the
show so there's like a little pause
in there where you can't hear paul
and that's what he was doing that
and saying lord laughs
this year music that loud yeah probably
yeah no one cared like no no
usually no one cares but the other
thing you the other thing i wanted
to say is that when we sent
the ah episode to our producer josh
who's now on the assume with us
he's usually not in the backyard with
secretly spying on us he told
us weird he told us no one
would hear it and it wouldn't be
a problem
and then every comment was like i'm
really distracted because i'm literally singing along
to ceo while they've played yeah oh
josh is on k now josh somebody
comes on camera and watch no no
no no no no no he wants
to defend himself get off discount hear
us into the nights
so apologies for that but i hope
you enjoyed the music oh we didn't
clear the license for it although i'm
sure that we have ah what they
have in sports where they have a
license where if something you know is
er the news if you hear music
in the background of something if you
hear music on the news it's fine
so you're telling they're just reporting on
sia that i could go in stand
behind a news reporter and blast my
recording of a song yes and then
they would be like it's in yeah
i think actually weirdly enough i think
that is that is it happens with
it
saturday night live is they have that
that particular licence ah where they can
play songs much like the news does
and that hey just like pretend that
the musical guest is someone they just
wandered in say much like the news
does is if this is a common
practice at the news does on like
this a football game yeah they know
they have they have a special license
you know how during football oh i'm
going to just play a little bit
of celebration by kool and the gang
under this next report during the during
the football game when cheerleaders are dancing
oh go on you're so interested all
it takes is cheerleader so honestly when
the cheerleaders come out that's when my
dick gets heard
the dallas obviously cowboy cheerleaders come out
paul
remember when josie and ameri remember winners
remember when the dallas cowboy cheerleaders were
a big thing they would be on
the love boat and honest lord and
take a breath loren loren they real
this was a 'em out they really
were they were treated like a single
celebrity
made like guested on a bunch of
shows but other teams had cheerleaders right
yeah but shit on the love boat
yeah the dallas cowboy cheerleaders were over
it was all excited where i guess
i guess america just all decided they
were the hottest cheerleaders or something and
they they had a good p r
person or something like that but they
they they were the most famous cheer
leaders in the world at the time
they were the only ones with matching
outfits of the other leaders they just
brother clothes from home they were like
grateful dead's he leave or sweatpants
i feel like cheerleaders you know you
find out that they get paid like
thirty bucks a game or so yeah
rude and it's just like what are
we doing everything all became famous will
all have dualism the razzie gave the
famous
she was for the l a rams
was it touch i i thought she
was likely a laker girl yeah that's
pretty crazy
what the les paul anfield all time
paula abdul the end she was follow
up dual the whole time but like
sushi took over mask of laker girl
and revealed it was paula abdul the
whole show is like just a cheerleader
and everyone was like we're all cheerleaders
and then she was like i actually
have a lot more skills and i'll
be really famous and then they all
didn't believe it and then i can
also barely sing yes so
wife well now she's mass dancer isn't
she who are the who are the
cheerleaders who have become famous i think
tony toni basil and paula abdul and
has added so who the woman who
sings hey mickey you're so fine yeah
she was a choreographer and that's why
her video is just a cheer videos
exactly right
so she was she was a choreographer
who did like talking heads videos and
stuff like that and then she spun
it off much like she was the
pro paula abdul she was paula before
paula was a thing vpa
i think dr joe biden she was
a true leader who became famous
you guys like her valentine's day decorations
so no no what were they like
they were sweet well first of all
something where i thought they were photoshopped
when i first saw it i didn't
understand what i was looking at she
put big hearts on the like of
various sizes and pinks and reds on
the way it goes large small yeah
and they said three sizes big lunch
so no mediums
where were they on the white house
yeah white house lawn yeah for valentine's
day why not just put a giant
heart over the white house yeah you're
right you're right
but no but it's like oh you
didn't like it it yeah it was
so
it was a place of it's a
workplace why would you have isn't it
a place of worship um it i
got scored i feel like it was
corny yeah i mean um i feel
like yeah it's ok for old people
to be corny you know what i
mean but when i saw the picture
it look
looked bad
look good and i think what it
was was that the hearts had no
dimension to them so they yeah no
dimension they were just very look little
cartoons like it was weird and then
but what i let you talk they
should have been realistic heart's ventricles position
i've had they should have had some
some sort of depth to the the
paint of them
or something but they looked like they
were just clip art or something looks
very homemade bow but i thought this
is really sweet and we need this
can you i mean i get i
get i totally get that feeling of
like a little creaminess is welcome yeah
right it's you know i don't know
but it also see
seems like such a um ah putting
a band-aid on a gunshot well of
course because it's like whoa whoa what
are you supposed to do paul i
don't know but she also was seen
at the bakery on her instagram getting
sweets for her and joe for the
valentine's day celebration i hope she got
him an ice cream cookie he lie
loves ice cream he does love like
my phones i think i think anyone's
celebrating valentine's day with like a celebration
you know i mean it's like you're
not in you're not in fifth grade
anymore oh wow
shots fire we don't usually go out
to dinner well sure but that's that's
like a a thing that you do
with your loved one it's not a
thing where you decorate your house you
know and go hey everyone we're celebrating
valentine's day together hey you know what
i like first of all i didn't
decorate for valentine's day but it's not
beneath me
i would happily do it last tree
sure i actually have thought about getting
valentine's tree because i have my halloween
tree now and i have two christmas
trees and one of my christmas trees
is pink and i thought well i
could put it in the front window
and put hearts all over it and
make it valentine's tree christian do that
but maybe i will next year course
they didn't do that of course i
did that would be insane
but i will next year when i've
legitimately gone mad what are they going
to put it up february fifteenth yeah
i'm just like what of it
calabi come at me it's a christmas
tree anyway
no rules you don't even know it's
a christmas tree idiot fucking idiots
scott do you you don't give cool
up little the hearts and things oh
yeah maybe i don't know flowers are
are coming we're we're taping this right
before valentine's day but it'll come out
right now so that is what that
is though you're getting her flowers you
would go to dinner know what i'm
saying thereto i'm saying it's not as
though like like
ah work i'm saying this is a
workplace if you were to go to
work and your boss had decorated everything
with like pink hearts everywhere and and
heart sounds really lowers yes
and they were hanging from the ceiling
from strings and stuff like that you'd
start to be like okay i'm trying
to work here right like i'm not
in love with any of you people
ah well what have your books i
love with all of you
i want to start
a quadruple be my valentine's um i
actually think i liked that but i'm
i'm a dork i don't know i
think it's like cute well the white
house is not just a place of
business they do live there and put
these out on the law and for
the public yeah but celebrated in in
steel reserve
this is it's like tang like thrashing
through a mobile this is a lot
for a movie this is a good
plot for a movie like ah what
does just follow did what our butler
movie what's fallen olympus has fallen olympus
yes so for the fourth one or
whatever they're up to now suddenly the
secret service can't get to the president
because of all men
valentine's day decorations i could not believe
how many of those movies they had
made yeah there's like theme at least
three
it happened to the white house it
happened to ten downing street right or
was it the ho yeah yeah palace
and then it happened on a boat
the royal boat
the president the the premier's boat of
canada do you know what we're talking
about lauryn you you look like you
mentally are checking out yeah no i
don't know what's going on do you
know those gerard butler movies nevermind do
you know your butler is yes i
do okay everyone knows a drug book
isn't good butlers
um is he in first of all
i do know who he is but
is he in
that movie with um hold on because
i'm mixing up a bunch of people
okay it's called well that part i
don't know but there's more
it's a movie where p s i
love you
and it's um hilary swank and her
husband did i spell pi ss i
love you piss i love you scott
hillary swings husband dies and then she
gets all these chad lowe um
and she used to come into my
restaurant oh not a movie what which
one cafe cardinale now who cares who
cares me marie calendar's no name marie
calendar i to do want a list
of my restaurants yeah girlfriends okay started
no started out huh
started at ah ah we were not
waiting marie calendar's
whittier marie calendar's worked there for a
year
ah moved on to hoard oh po
folks po folks oh no yes right
across the street from medieval times medieval
thai adjacent to the hollywood wax museum
medieval times is so dependent on you
not being able to see the food
food
i've only been there once too dark
did you go to the pirate restaurant
with us that's over by medieval times
now no okay that was i think
paul rust and neil campbell and my
cassidy and i've never been to either
let me tell you a story about
the pirate restaurants a secondhand story ou
from ah my rear friend nicole parker
who's bit of a pirate she stole
my heart
um wow she was on you know
she was on mad tv and they
organized an outing the cast organized an
outing to go to this pirate restaurant
and they were all going to get
in like a van together you know
they rented some you know whatever we
bought a van down by the river
yeah
we bought
and the last person to arrive at
ah ah the van to go to
the restaurant was ike baron holtz who
shut off and already he's much showed
up in a in a full airline
pirate pilot's uniform carrot like dragging a
lie
it'll suitcase my area some case
it's solely so that he could get
to the door of the bus that
everybody was waiting for him and say
oh hi rit
wow yeah that's yeah that's fun
yeah that's fun
that was the reaction of everyone in
the bus did he make that's what
did he make the costume department do
that for him or did he rent
time it sounds i think he rented
it on it's own okay so that's
ok so giving the costume department more
work to do that's probably not the
right move especially if they're not invited
to this pirate restaurant yeah if you
have like the set department build your
house
i should do that
that's not a bad hey since you're
building stuff anyway like building a house
up to code hey only do it
with three walls yeah flats it's just
the inside of the house looks good
looks go when you're in it okay
so you'd then what what happened after
that oh okay well poe folks already
calendars po folks the back of po
folks are marie calendar's whittier if you
don't end up at another marie calendar's
gonna be mad well they're seeing some
very important to matt gourley so i'm
more an l even though there's no
other laurence
um po folks the the back of
po folks was a giant um sort
of catering place called california catering so
they i worked for both of those
simultaneously um yeah jobs at once then
i went to ah but de da
de da second
but bethany on it if the southern
front of poe folks was po folks
the back of p folks was california
catering yeah so did they have two
separate storefronts like if you went to
a back of po folks would it
be like you are walking separate interests
yeah so so poe folks so segregated
if you've never brave of you to
admit that if you've never been to
a po folks i don't even know
if there's still any around now it's
not only never been to never heard
of yeah it's it's a southern themed
restaurants that lean leans heavily into the
southern part of it to where we
had to approach every table and ask
them if they wanted to belly washer
instead of a drink
nasty yeah i've never heard that in
my fucking well
you're from philadelphia
yeah but you live next door to
the rocky statue like that are you
fine so i'm from philadelphia philadelphia you
don't like it come to my office
right i just saw a tweet that
references that and yet i still don't
know what's going oh they it just
happened maybe an hour ago um but
belly washers yeah belly washing you have
to say howdy
like from deadwood or some shit howdy
howdy this is like oh belly washer
yeah it was you had to every
table yet to say how do you
can offer your daily work or youtube
and if you didn't and we we
would constantly be sort of like scanning
the room to see if a manager
was around or and if they weren't
you'd say hey can i get you
something to
drink um but they also had a
trucker got out air
i think i was reprimanded for not
saying belly washer one point they also
had secret shopper i want to reprimand
you for saying it now okay go
ahead it's kid mason jar problem yes
cam spain but they added ah ah
an electric train going around the entire
restaurants a giant place it was like
the south would have
yeah but it it was giant because
um it was one of those tourists
you know medieval times kind of tourist
places um next to the wax museum
and all that where they were just
expecting a giant amount of people in
every day and usually they got it
it's closed so be fair
but so is a giant restaurant with
all this southern kitsch all over the
walls you know like ah stop signs
yeah no there were there were signs
everywhere it was just like i was
at the southern this sounds so half-assed
it's making me mad yeah this whole
line fried okra and hushpuppies and all
all this kind of southern shirt so
but in the back they have this
like beautiful tree lines ah outdoor place
where where they would host you to
host weddings and parties of any sort
to be you would
but they they would use the same
kitchen from poe folks so so that
was sort of a separate business that
was owned by the same people but
where you like i'd dress up in
you know not a tuxedo but ah
you know the the parks don't
the taxi don't
but you know the party down like
bow tie and white shirt and all
that stuff no party gown at first
party gowns or my party gown everyone
gets your party gowns on who wants
a belly washer and ride on the
train but they use the same kitchen
so you would essentially get like a
little more upscale versions or the or
the po folks menu
that was the best stuff you know
same food but make it better
um so after that then i went
to college and the and i worked
a bigger square in college ah yeah
and baker square as opposed as opposed
to marie calendar's where they let us
take home full pies and cakes and
whatever they have left and karen whittier
yes a bigger square was the first
restaurant i'd ever worked at where they
made you throw away all the food
right anyway the dumpster lock-on dumpster locks
yeah that's so discuss
damn bait it's what they say because
if any homeless person were to eat
any food and get sick they would
be able to sue them for millions
of dollars actually which is what i
have people are dying to do all
the time right sane um what city
was baker squaring that was in santa
maria california and they work baker square
santa maria
yes i think square summary think i've
ever heard of santa maria california whereas
that central california over by um by
the way i should say on last
week's episode i saw indecent proposal at
the azusa six it was at the
royal grand a six so don't want
to do that get a lot of
kind of freedom regrets
i lived in azusa later arroyo grande's
by santa maria is by pismo beach
oh now see as a bugs bunny
fan i know exactly where that by
the way next to pismo beach is
this town called ah guadalupe and my
teacher and it's just the shittiest town
right and it's
it's it's it's so just boring and
gross and um and you would never
go into guadalupe whenever you lived in
santa maria um but my teacher was
at a different college down here maria
you do not going to go it's
just crazy that you can just like
fuck up a whole town and it
just sucks
that like sucks there's nothing to do
there's nothing that you would look for
there's just no restaurants and stuff but
anyway my ah i remember my teacher
down here in orange county once like
picked it on a map because it
sounded beautiful and there was no why
did you go there just like it
sounds gorgeous guadalupe
just the name just even had a
crush on someone named guadalupe is like
sounds maybe she's there
um so yeah baker square i worked
there and i also worked at dean
witter with bill murray's brother um simultaneously
what dean witter dean witter which is
an investment firm restaurants only sorry sorry
sorry sir i don't wanna hear about
your life as a corporate shill with
bill murray's brother you don't want to
hear me was it joel
it was not ah no joseph was
in lynn licensed to drive no no
no he's an actor is not does
that mean he couldn't have worked at
dino true true but but this this
this one was like one of the
top people at dean witter so like
he that was his career essentially he
does come from a family of like
eleven kids are so yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah and only half of them are
actors right and so i would constantly
be looking at him for bill murray
signs of like always acting like bill
murray like his laugh or smile in
utah and you'd kind of go oh
he said that like the sides
but that was where i learned how
to fax something and so i was
able to put that on my resume
we're getting far afield
next restaurant i learned how to fax
um as a kid because my dad
had a fax machine and i would
fax my aunt at her work at
the court she worked at actually talked
to the mayor's office in indiana at
that point and i would send her
faxes and then she'd send me really
legit faxes from the mayor's office and
they were really funny and i have
milestone what do you mean what
why are you so yours may well
mine were a child right right messages
and then i would send it to
her and then she would write back
with the mayor's letterhead and then it
would be like something about the front
message from the mayor and then consider
yeah
it is illegal to eat your vegetables
yeah what i got new ordinance yeah
i had a fax machine in the
in the i want to say and
like the late nineties like faxing was
a thing that um
audition times since yeah yeah yeah yeah
you have to facts like your sides
your your well yeah yeah yeah yeah
it was you sides you would have
to do your your picture and resume
sometimes yes some people were only reachable
by fax it was such a stupid
short-lived thing that the idea of at
least some great importance on the idea
of someone having their fax machine
and then like one one end is
a person who's like sending their headshot
through and then the
the first thing getting in there like
oh like it just sucks
you just described the process of the
facts
ah yes one of facts was going
to send you this okay great
it sucks
like it comes through all shitty quality
and you're like yea that's what he
looks like oh my mom this isn't
me faxes from her job when i
lived out here she would sound like
a big font you know nice message
to me it was very small that's
cute we also
oh by the way lauren lived through
beepers which my roommate had a b
i did have a beeper oh you
had a paper i had a beeper
in the high school when some people
had cell phones but i had a
pager that you would i might have
told this story before but
you could was a doctor yes so
i was doctor knows
and i'd have to go to work
hey there it was like you could
call and you would leave a message
with an operator and then the operator
would type out the message to me
on my beeper so it had like
a little text on it oh but
it was always wrong and it always
made no sense like i don't know
if it was an automated thing that
was typing it or if the person
just kind of type whatever they heard
and they didn't try to make it
make sense but it
always made no sense and then you
have to figure out who it was
from and then try to call them
back and i really loved it though
i thought it was really cool and
it was maroon clear
adam levine if he were a scientologist
alright i'll see you guys later
my i i my my roommate had
one and he was always pulling the
car over so he could find a
payphone how the person is just like
ever that important now oh god wait
it was at the restaurant roundup no
no i have way more okay so
so they way more yeah
so then ah olive garden in cypress
california that's horrors that's the one that
i didn't have a car so i
had to figure out the bus schedule
and um take two different buses i
would have to take but i would
have to walk to the bus station
about ah maybe a quarter of a
mile take a bus to beach boulevard
hard than wait around for another bus
and the worst is when your first
bus arrives and you see the second
bus leaving yeah yeah from the second
you're always like running after him and
they won't stop well that reminds story
um my friend laura wilcox and i
used to do what we still do
to person and prop together i'm gox
yes
i am
a long time ago we were going
to um a an all-female comedy festival
in austin texas and i think this
was probably two thousand and ten or
something and we were really broke and
so we shared hotel room and we
bought like peanut butter and bread and
we were basically eating like just whatever
from our hotel we would never go
out to eat but i did
have a twenty five dollar gift card
to applebees that was given to me
at some point and so we were
like okay we're going to find an
apple this will be the trail after
yeah yeah we're gonna go to applebee's
and we took multiple buses i was
it was so far away we took
like a buzz i mean it was
it was really fun like we have
like agree it was a hilarious time
but it was just kind of funny
we
i took a bus really far and
then we walked along a highway for
a long time like in grass like
today go there and it was like
just the middle of nowhere and then
we had like a shitty meal and
you know of course still had to
pay ten dollars on top of it
or whatever we're like annoyed by that
and then take the bus all the
way back and it was just the
time i used to do the
the ah the comedy club in austin
cap city which i closed down and
i guess is reopening um but they
used to put you up at this
terrible hotel and the reason they put
you up at the hotel was it
was close to the comedy club which
is where you spend the least amount
of time while you're there it's like
you're at the comedy club for ninety
minutes
and then the rest of the time
you're just in the middle of nowhere
yeah um and i remember how hard
it was to get around without a
car um you would you would often
be what if if you were walking
anything it would be grasped by the
side of the highway yeah just to
go get lunch or something at a
denny's well that's that seems
like an austin specific memory because it's
quite a few south by southwest walking
along the highway yeah good is that
just an austin that's how you have
to get everywhere i don't know i
think it's just because it's so spread
out i guess yeah and like there's
concentrated areas where stuff is going on
but if you're not one of those
areas you're just fucked up this hotel
it was a best western that i
guess at
some point they they busted a prostitution
ring that was happening there um i
i was in a room with a
probably my smoke
and i swear in my face i
got destroyed destroyed my face so i
said or did toward my face
that's what that's what you want when
you hire right to my face put
your telling my face that i became
a super villain um i smoked at
the time and so i was in
a smoking room and the guy who
is in there one one time the
guy that was another week before me
was a cigar smoker and the stench
of cigars
it was it was so unbearable and
there was like
like burns in the bedding like in
the comforter there would be cigarette and
cigar tarn it's hard to believe that
smoking hotels were a thing man i
still don't plan it's it's wild yeah
so i heard about snakes on a
plane once would you here monday to
friday plane
native friday
yeah i get it i get
very good i got to um so
do you ever miss smoking a lot
never do i enjoy rooms you'd miss
smoking a lot or a little
i never miss it i never eat
it i once i was done i
was done and i'm so sometimes i
have anxiety dreams where i'm smoking hoof
and i'll i'll i won't realize i'm
smoking until after i've started smoking and
then i'm like oh no what am
i doing oh no my streak yeah
yeah yeah i feel like real shame
about it in the dream i would
imagine if you're if you're in the
program that you would have stress dreams
about drinking as well yeah what shares
anything like that where you're trying not
to do something or he or something
has changed in your life and you
have a nightmare about it being how
it used to be or something but
um i still am dreaming about this
particular house by the way calls
ainge back an earlier episode i've had
several dreams oh yeah yea though the
stands made up right yeah well there's
three different houses that i that i
dream about all the time and i've
made them all up it's always fucking
weird you need to go get help
yeah well why don't you help me
oh i agree i drew my child
huh yeah i want to ask a
question that book about not smoking yes
i'm sorry i'm like bill nye honest
i
i almost want to read it but
i don't smoke but i'm like what
does it fucking say that works so
wow i'll tell you i'll tell you
what it is is that it's it's
very it uses almost hypnosis techniques in
a way it's very repetitive um but
what it really did for me was
early on like early on in the
book it got me to admit it
gets you to admit that you don't
enjoy it that you don't enjoy it
yeah yeah that's really what sally was
like you know you says didn't you
say that it says it says don't
stop smoking until the end of the
book but you read the first chapter
and were like i just don't want
to do
this anymore no no no i did
stop smoking before i finished the book
but it but they do tell you
don't don't don't try to stop smoking
and read the book was still smoke
while you read the book and then
gradually like the urge fades away it's
it's it's remarkable i recommended it somebody
before people ask me it is called
the easy way
way to stop smoking by allen carr
um and i have ah i've recommended
it to so many people and it
works it works like a charm for
most people i got to say and
i and for me i i had
it on my coffee table for a
year before i read it
yeah and then once i did i
was like that was it do you
wish you you would have read it
earlier in the year or do you
think that you were just in the
right oh my i wish yeah i
think it was that ah i had
to get to the point where like
when i first got the book i
think it was that i know this
is not good for me and i
shouldn't do it anymore
but i wasn't yet intellectually yes but
i wasn't either the fatigue point of
it where it's like i don't like
this but i don't know how to
stop doing it yeah and the book
the book really just kind of laid
it all out in a very logical
way that in a logical way that
also so really zeroed in on your
emotions about it and
so you are it's like sort of
admitting you're just you're just admitting something
to yourself and then it all like
falls away do you are you bummed
that you don't look cool anymore
that's my one regret that's why sometimes
late at night janie sleep i'll hold
up a pencil and looking mirror and
i'm smoking sort of the silhouette maybe
sweetly can you stand in front of
a bright window and yeah that's right
she's like why do you have all
these golf pencils and i'm like don't
worry about it
okay look we have to take a
break but when we come back i'll
finish restaurant roundup
okay we're back and apologized during the
break we're discussing whether it should be
restaurant roundup or restaurant ramble because he
believes that around it would be over
by now but ah you are clearly
rambling and just to be clear during
the break my opinion was never requested
ah also to me even clearer the
break
was two seconds long that's right but
i prefer to get this on mike
um what do you what do you
think it is a ramble
i think it's um the restaurant roundup
ramble i'd like to hear about all
of your you guys jobs at some
only had like two but yeah i'll
tell you all about them i won't
say but every family babysat for oh
it was babysitter then i was in
movies
ah
i also worked at a coffee shop
for a day a day like a
couple days and i worked at a
dock for you know a week a
dog i'm doing well definitely told you
this story when i worked at the
boat tourist place on navy pier in
chicago and shout about boat tours yeah
shout about both doors are great
yeah i had to be like
evening boat tours thirty minutes on the
lake sixty minutes on the river
why the river twice as much time
because we want you to get back
textural tour of the chicago river okay
no you snapped right back then i
actually would like to go i'd like
to go to know it's really fun
i think excuse me have it
what the fuck did you have this
problem is why you only worked on
the dock for a week no but
i always have this problem has gotten
too nervous talking about the shores um
i highly recommend if you go to
chicago to go on the architectural boat
tour there's a handful of them and
it's so cool because the architecture along
the river is really beautiful and they
explain everything and it's it's
really fun i love stuff like that
i love being on a boat and
i love seeing a a city that
way we did ah janie and i
are we took an anniversary trip to
ah polly just like emily and we
did a boat tour on the san
jose and it was ah it was
a bj
beautiful beautiful afternoon it was wonderful well
i we talked about this on the
tube and i got a mercy infection
in my leg and i almost couldn't
walk yeah jim mirza yeah demurs i
didn't yeah we talked about this on
the tour but when the first time
i went to england coupe had to
sort of convince me to take that
bus tour
or around england's because i was like
bus tour that sounds stupid and it
just will take ah it just gave
him it gave you such a good
ah you know the city so big
that it really made me go oh
i see where everything is what the
different parts of it so i recommended
it to my canford when we went
to england on the tour and he
really loved it too so
anyway and then you got right ahead
aircraft flowers not to go off track
about these restaurants or if we are
constantly trying to take things from mike
today why don't you leave us alone
as anyone in the james bond martini
restaurant and hated all the martinis yes
he is charlie likes his vod straight
vodka that tours
started with talking about how he likes
martinis now then him complaining about every
my team ever got me because he
had martinis at a party at like
a backyard party and we figured out
all it was was just straight vodka
into a glass yeah with an olive
or something maybe be but but i
don't think he had any ah what
what do you put martinis again you
the vermouth i don't think he added
vermont he was because anytime he had
any martini after that with vermouth he
go ooh what is that that's that
was so funny because in the habit
of australia yeah we went to that
weird restaurant you can hear about all
of these that's true yes honored for
your roundup to around issues where
speaking around us though restaurant roundup row
row row ravel so that we left
off in the olive garden where i
i listened off i listened to the
o j chase in the in the
freezer where it was i was just
like oh i know and he drove
by ah on his ah in his
chase you saw i didn't see but
he drove on the ninety one freeway
which saw it was like how crazy
you'd be sitting there listening to it
on the car
goes by like
he's the guy from the radio
it's also where i believe i heard
about kurt cobain dine dying um i'm
not sure but i do remember thing
because i played them because they played
k rock in the kitchen and i
remember the day he died just it
was just constant nirvana songs that day
who do you think is the next
celebrity who's going to murder someone more
on your sound just got so
so much clearer oh i brought the
mic to my mouth oh that's like
doing anything the headphone mic is she's
reporting on that one yeah oh i
see i don't have a plugged into
the computer but i have thought about
this and i it's just more of
a hassle free internet i don't i
don't do it but um i guess
i should understood this tech roundup
okay
yeah but i was close to my
my my little mouth and you can
hear everything your enemies closer
to your little mouth
i keep this close to my little
mouth i keep my enemies closer to
my little about well we were talking
about a certain celebrity who there were
rumors about um them having murdered someone
and and someone we know and and
someone paul is intimately familiar with said
that would be crazy and i had
to bring up oj simpson that how
crazy it
was that he did and it made
everyone kind of go oh yeah you're
right i guess i guess a well-known
celebrity could be a murderer i know
we do what i would really love
right there head was routinely battered by
their job do you think that's what
it was it could contribute to that
i mean like that that o j
um made an america doc
have you seen that if you've seen
that no yeah i don't think i
read a lot of the books oh
and it was so that doc is
so good it's so well done and
it gives you a real history of
yeah racism in los angeles right and
it's it's it really explains it not
explained but it it sort of illustrates
how was the line from the rodney
king oh from further back than that
yeah oh sure the watson further back
than that yeah like everything that built
up to ah what could have caused
o j
to be um ah kind of not
in a good frame of mind yeah
i have to say the jeffrey toobin
and people you know condemn him for
being a famous masturbator but his books
about the o j book is great
and his patty hearst book is really
good i mean
heard that there was stuff in the
patty hearst book that like the whole
fact of of daryl gates how he
rose to prominence and the and the
fact that when they shot up the
patty hearst hide out it was on
live television that was the first time
that had ever happened um that they
had ever broadcast live on the on
tv like a police thing like that
which led to
chases and all that kinda stuff but
those those books are if you can
look past the fact that every other
sentence he was jerking it they're they're
really really i'll move down from that
very quickly didn't we well his author
photos his penis if we also didn't
know
i feel like it would be fun
and i don't mean for any of
the people involved but i always like
a good trial on tv like when
you're tuning in to see the trial
and i would like one of those
but it feels like right now it's
not really a time for a jury
and all that stuff i mean regardless
ignoring impeachment i don't care about that
i didn't even think about that how
they are how
handling jury duty well because i've gotten
jury duty and started my yeah and
we both never had to go
and i'm sorry
cut out all my coughing um even
enjoy lee but we both we both
didn't have to go like we had
to check in online every night and
we didn't go and i was like
i'm sure today i'm sharing ny having
us come i'm sure they say like
oh we've made it safe or whatever
and it's hear anything about it that's
but i trust store i wouldn't try
just it but i thought it was
more like they are just going we
have to go through the system of
asking people to come you have to
say you're gonna go and then you
want to go and then you get
off the hook for a year well
maybe it's an everyone goes to jail
it might be a zoo trial though
too i don't know zoom trial yeah
mary kate olsen was getting divorced on
zoom nice right
yeah that was weird to see screencaps
of someone's divorce i didn't feel appropriate
that they know that who was doing
that i don't know
someone someone who was like reporting on
it or something was like i got
to watch this today click this seems
weirdly yeah i don't know why there
would be anyone that was outside of
that proceeding that would be watching much
less anyone in the proceeding saying i'm
going to take a sneaky little screencap
yeah oh my god imagine if you
were we
watching that and then you did the
screenshot and i went to church
and what has to immediately go who
did that i don't like maybe i've
talked about this but i don't like
the fact that nine one one calls
are public so any time a celebrity
calls nine one one yeah they it
winds up on tmc the next day
like it's so worse one of the
worst moments of their own life so
like
that's in your head when you're calling
nine one one of like i've got
to sound appropriately like either composed or
not composed or yeah usually people are
i don't think you're supposed to have
a sociopathic thought about how you're supposed
to but
but it can get in i wonder
if real red flag life has ever
gotten in anyone's head where they're like
okay you call because i can't because
they'll release this or something oh i
don't know not i mean does seem
like in an emergency situation you can't
be thinking like that i would if
you did oh i love person than
you are thinking like that and you
go here i've
sound composed but not composed know but
that's how i feel is is it
shouldn't even be an issue for people
like it shouldn't even pop in anyone's
head well yeah channels yeah we don't
we haven't established that it does it
does this is who do you mean
it does speak have you called one
one
every day every day what time is
it i think like an emergency tmc
is is they have no morals and
they don't care no and they just
discussed go deep into whatever it takes
to get any information it's it's in
their name their lack of their lack
of ethics and you know what i
mean it's just like what is tmc
i'm thirty zone yeah it's like we'll
get as close to you as we're
allowed together that well no thirty mile
zone refers to the um it refers
to the filming area filming area the
zone yeah but does that mean the
filming area ah it's you know how
um when you has this real yeah
it is so yeah everyone
because of it but it's remember when
we were making them between two ferns
movie like the furthest yeah places that
we would go that's like within a
thirty mile zone is where all of
the um all of the union stuff
ah like if you film within that
zone then we don't have to pay
extra for travel all this kind of
stuff
so there are these like weird little
towns that are right on the edge
of the zone which is like as
far out as you can go before
you have to start paying everyone extra
so that's so they call the thirty
mile zone is essentially tmc is covering
this thirty mile zone of like where
celebrities are
so pretty gross yeah it's gross yeah
um do you remember having to call
the time by the way paul morris
day yeah i remember that yeah and
they would say hold a mirror up
to the phone and i was like
okay i would do it then there'll
be a silence and then they would
say okay you can hang out nobody
do it wasn't like this in philadelphia
fia where you could while it was
ringing you could hear the other people
calling
what okay so so this was it
and i don't know whether it was
california specific but when you call the
the time which was you had to
call i think it was like something
like two two two one two three
four or or any or no it
was maybe it was five five five
and then the last four numbers
you could call any of the last
four numbers and they and it would
still work and it would ring bring
bring bring bring and just anyone pick
up and you would hear at the
tone the time will be six forty
eight and thirty seconds be but while
it was ringing anyone else who was
calling at the same time would be
saying hi hi can you hear me
and you go you could hear them
and when i was like twelve and
thirteen basically what you would do is
you would shout your number over it
and then try to get you talking
up try to get like girls your
age to call you and then have
have like we're in
converse yeah weird conversations where we're line
phones try to make dates this is
the tom sawyer island of phone lines
i this sound what day does it
you're calling the time you're calling to
find out what time it is yeah
okay i do know that from full
house and i hate to bring up
full house gaffe well that's the other
thing that we have to bring we
we have to talk about this but
i i'm full house ah d j
wears the same outfit as the teacher
on the first day of school and
it's humiliating and then everyone thinks he's
starting loser buddy and see yeah that's
really funny price yeah i've never seen
an episode of oil that's absolutely but
everybody's sad and then she goes
into the phone booth of the lunch
room and she just pretends that she's
on the phone and she's just calling
the time for like the whole time
now that's where you know you never
had to do that because by the
time that you are cognizant of the
time everyone over their cell phones
um i just think there were clocks
yeah i just don't know everyone had
clocks what i guess to call the
time so you could get set the
current time to set your clock yeah
yeah so so i never had to
set check probably even in to the
two thousands i think my parents gave
me a clock that automatically
set itself to the the world clock
or something like that they called the
most accurate clock ever and then none
of that stuff within a few years
they were all out of business because
cell phones have times that were exact
thing to the atomic clock yeah yeah
so you had you had to call
the time but but you could hear
whoever else was calling the time and
so kids my age that it got
around of like oh yeah well i
called i call the time and someone
this girl shouted her number out and
i called and i made a date
with her and all this little trap
this is psychotic and yes so like
you might the idea of just calling
someone blindly and being like let's go
out and like yeah no it's crazy
and my and my parents saw
forbade me you like i told my
parents like oh well look what you
can do on the time they're like
don't do that and and well yeah
i gave my address to somebody on
instant messenger on aol when i was
um a kid because we were talking
in we were like let's be pen
pals and then i was like man
i got a pin pill online she's
like oh my god never do ah
you're looking trash
alright now we gotta pause the restaurant
roundup rambo for just a second yeah
and we can get into we can
address the counter of wicked t d
rogers am a first of all just
have to issue an apology i am
humiliated i am devastated i am known
honestly i am known for knowing theme
songs i have
played games online you can watch me
guess theme songs just with the spoken
word i know that the fact that
i
one such as you one such as
i haven't
conflate the family matters and full house
themes on our last steps point where
i actually said people often mix up
these two theme songs and that one
was full house i my face is
so red i could just bury my
head in the sand and i really
am so sorry terrible estrogens around scott
i know
i'm so sorry for everyone i hurt
and i'm really sorry for everyone who
is confused and you know and i
think paul even said that was failing
matters and i said no one yeah
so grounds him i don't accept your
apology oh paul how did you feel
honestly i was prepared for that no
it's okay i accept lawrence apology and
may i further say that i am
proud
proud of myself for putting the family
matters theme song over the full house
opening credits and posting on instagram when
i saw that i was filled with
joy because i thought this this team's
got my back fucking haters half of
the team has your play up sky
you're only a third fuck the hater
i'm i'm hopefully half of it
we share half of our coin you
guys yeah oh man
that sucks okay i gotta continue to
rush around opera it's never gonna like
so how many fuckin restaurants so then
i moved to azusa the aforementioned d'souza
and i ah my manager at all
of garden recommended me to the glendale
olive garden where i worked for three
days for
first of all i had to take
the most insane test i've ever taken
to work at a restaurant where they
out hostile look like
no they asked me the ingredients olive
growing a garden the ingredients of the
pasta every like you had to know
every single thing about every dish which
now when you was just beginning peoples
spaghetti meatballs okay next now that everyone
has won his garfield favorite food lasagna
oh
now that everyone has food allergies it
actually makes a lot of sense that
you would have to know every but
but for most of my jobs it's
just been like oh i'll ask the
cook and you come back and they
know you know but you had to
know the ingredients of every single fanatical
county breaking my balls law and it
was the longest restaurant with with a
patio
and he was super long like a
train car whatever and then your section
which is the most insane way i've
ever worked at a restaurant instead of
having you know six tables next to
each other you would be stacked on
top
that is crazy you to climb up
like jakob love cricket team stuff
no they they they in order to
make it because i guess some a
lot of people liked you know being
on the patio or whatever they and
that's the most popular so they're trying
to be fair so they divvied up
where you would get one table in
every single part of the restaurant and
so you'd had to run around the
entire restaurant trying to check on your
tables and it was just
it was crazy so i already was
was fed up by this place and
then there was a guy who was
ah ah eighteen and he would follow
around this older woman who was like
sixty five or whatever um and tell
her about every weird al yankovic song
and what he was parodying and what
the what his parody was
was anyway whew these were these were
waiters these are waiters oh yeah huh
so the soul was an it was
an eighteen year old guy and sixty
five year old woman yeah we're both
servers at this rate they were both
servers and and he was just following
her during the entire shift and saying
like i'm trying to think of one
but like like a like a surgeon
like oh
you know how madonna does like a
virgin well weird al yankovic would do
like a surgeon and then he told
her every lyric that was a parody
and stuff and she just kept going
with that sounds funny and then were
you like i'm going to be fringed
them someday but yeah and everyone was
like shut up and you're like no
really i'm really i'm going to be
friends with um so then the the
final nail
in the coffin was um the guy
here yes i died
no no there was there was a
group of people my age who were
all friends and they invited me to
go to islands over in burbank after
a shift and one of the one
of the ah women like ah made
kind of a full court press trying
to trying to like make out with
me at island floors
sixty five years since she was like
you sound funny dear um
dear no but dear i to fuck
but she ah but it made it
pretty apparent that if i were to
return to this restaurant
i would have to deal with this
and tell her like oh hey i'm
not interested and instead i quit after
three days of work at at this
olive garden right well okay and ah
my coward's way out
it was there a woman at every
one of these jobs who wanted to
fuck you
yeah no i will a bigger square
i was i was the person who
like befriend of this kind of looks
like sixty year old woman and so
we became friends there and so we
had a nice relationship there but um
i don't think so
um there wasn't no i'm trying to
say the bigger squared no one was
my age it was all like over
older women who worked there that's um
so okay so i went from there
than i than i immediately went to
chinch in i worked there and then
i went to came immediately and whenever
you really want to change it whenever
you started a new job were you
nervous on
first day
i mean yeah i think everyone kind
of is although i was i was
a pretty good waiter in fact i
got poached from chin chin to cafe
cordell because the owner of cafe cardale
was in chin chin and was basically
like hey i never do this but
you're like one of the best waiters
i've ever had so if you want
to come over to my restaurants you
which is just like an insane thing
like how how are waiters really differing
that much you know but he was
just like you have a job if
you want it's god you're being very
modest but you are the best waiter
and i wanted to fuck you will
you please come to change i'm sorry
five your very funny to hear
um so how many is that that's
how nobody is counted once
how many stories are how many restaurants
these are all the plays you know
i mean this is my resume and
you use these are my restaurants that's
how you got your job right direction
between two ferns you showed them your
resume
it was the best waiter at the
whole graphic ordeal keep all your day
jobs on your resume
that would be a good bit for
like can everything you've ever done every
job you've ever had oh manifestation i
forgot that was my first job i
was gonna say god it's not what
i went to your restaurant it was
a yacht place you pulled that out
at the last second it's gonna say
oh i can't i can't wait to
nail him with this the christian yogurt
place yeah and sea
station mad station where my my yogurt
my parents church friends did them a
favor by giving me a job and
then i think i was a terrible
employee and gotten fired after six well
i like the team for the job
of them by the time you were
at cafe cardio and you were the
best waiter they'd ever had so it
took all that time and all
grubbs to really figure out your way
although i will say cafe ordeal the
owner the owners ah mom who who
worked there she reprimanded me for not
marrying the catch ups and they're gonna
say not marry her daughter i was
like oh hey i'm making my debut
succeed in this
this company you'll marry my ugly dude
and i and i explained to her
that it was not part of my
side work i like told her oh
no that's the other waiters like we
all divvy up the sidewalk and then
for the rest of the time i
worked there she would give me a
disappointing look and say remember to marry
the catch ups today
oh dear it was like it's not
my fucking job
i'll pray for you that you remember
to marry the catch ups why is
there ketchup at a yogurt place oh
that was a manifestation that was cafe
cordell sorry manifestation was yogurt and then
christian greeting cards christian greeting cards and
and like it was a christian half
christian first order god
pictures santa claus saying it
um it was half christian bookstore and
i don't think we ever sold any
of the christian books it was a
failed business yeah it it it disappeared
shortly after i have got fired have
told them that i needed to cut
my hours back from twenty to five
that happened to me that happened to
me at one of my first jobs
when i was in high school like
i got a job at this ah
pizza place was called rsos minimum called
rizzo rsos and um i was reserved
from greece yeah it was greasy pizza
it was it was rizzo from grease
and rachel rizzo they teamed up
um and i was i started out
as a i as a bus boy
um and i remember another guy from
my from my class work there in
the kitchen and was like yeah you
know you keep ah keep moving up
and eventually you can work in here
and as he's saying this i noticed
all the idiots like birds birds
yeah because like okay but then i
got cast in a school play and
i was like i need to have
all this time off and what i
was i was that was my mind
i was casting the play when i
was at the time off i was
asked for was absurd and the guy
like pretty much laughed in my face
you can't work here like this you
asking for
you're asking for like one day on
that's not the way that yeah i
think i asked i was like well
we we rehearse until five every day
and this place is only open until
seven i'm like so i work from
five to seven and the guy and
the owner was like well i want
to talk to you anyway because you're
not working out
oh
because i think i gave someone ah
i didn't check the styrofoam cup that
i put the yogurt in they were
all upside down on top of each
other year and someone someone came back
and said there are like spiders and
cobwebs
yeah and my point is that's the
sickest thing i've ever heard my point
is don't have a dirty ass styrofoam
cup laying around restaurant you like how
many bites did they take before they
realised that the base of it was
spiders i don't know yeah i'd sob
webs that's how to use a cobweb
i also hated cleaning windows i was
like where i was like really clean
the glass windows that's part of our
duties and sweetie huh can i will
tell you a story about cleaning windows
when i worked to tower video on
the sunset strip oh yes i remember
these days we had to clean the
um there were a big glass doors
rs um and we had to clean
those and one time i was cleaning
them and ah the actress amanda plummer
ah who was shocking i had a
dream lydia ah she was there with
somebody else and so there there her
friend was browsing and she was outside
smoking a cigarette
and as i was watching the door
the glass door she said do you
clean your windows at home and i
said ah no i don't she said
huh
and then when i was done i
was going back in she went spanking
clean wow just you yeah
oh my god what an amazing celebrity
story i loved her one time i
was working there and you were ballantine
i of course i did
by the way great
here you go man one time i
was working there and out the window
i saw diane keaton walk up the
street in full like diane keaton drag
with like that and the gloves and
everything great yeah and it was one
of the most exciting things it was
wild like you i it's you know
you just instantly know who it is
yeah and
that was like like a lot of
famous people came in all the time
but the but that was like seeing
somebody from mythology you know what i
mean it was really wild but that
just in my brain yeah it was
really cool were you guys friends at
that time you i knew we were
just starting to know each other i
say yeah because one did you did
you work there in your third ninety
five or nine
eighty four did you start or wow
i got to know each other in
ninety five i think it was ninety
five i think it was ok five
yeah you know yes stories about it
i think i've visited you i worked
there for about a year and then
um i got fired ever taking video
tapes right yes for taking them
ah what's that laura you stole oh
i did yes for a long time
for a long time yeah so like
still video but
anything i said anything i was like
the least bit interested in i'd be
like because i was so bitter at
that job i longest i ever worked
anywhere and i was really burn out
working day jobs because i had gone
from um you know doing standup and
philly doing open mics to finally being
able to support myself doing standup
then i moved out here and i
had a kind of start all over
again from scratch yeah and so it
was an affront to you to have
to work a day job yes it
was an insult
and i couldn't i i did not
have the ah the psychological tools to
cope with my situation in life and
so i decided to take it out
on the company and i stole like
videos and i'd like i feel guilty
about it as i remember you talking
about it like you felt guilty that
you had all these videos i mean
you were like oh okay look
look at my collection but also like
go no i did not feel guilty
about until i got caught and then
i write i had like the most
profound shame i've ever felt in my
life when i got called into that
office and right the they realized really
taken a lot of stuff or they
know they had no idea they they
only i think i just got caught
the one time and the
and so the manager said how long
has this been going on and i
said i've done it a few today
i lied even then um but i
had to return a bunch of videos
that i had stolen did you like
the ones that you didn't even like
all that much oh yeah i feel
i filled a bag as if that
was yeah that verso embarrassing always more
fighting
i was humiliated humiliation and because i
because i knew i was wrong like
as soon as as soon as it
was and i talk about i've talked
about this in my stand-up but as
soon as as soon as i was
confronted with it it all washed over
me like oh yeah i shouldn't have
been there's no justification for this like
right yeah i should not have been
doing this and this is this is
profound shame
while speaking in profound shame i'm ashamed
we have to take a break but
when we come back we'll have a
three-day i hate when you drag those
cbp segways i mean just read our
shit on this area like that so
much um we'll be right back
okay we're back and it's time for
three-term and lauryn has picked it okay
this one is called rhyme time it's
submitted by eric from chicago one person
the fish thinks of two words that
rhyme they then give the players two
synonyms for those words the players must
then deter
than what the original rhyming words are
whoever wins gets to be the rhymer
next so for example let's say i
gave you the words furniture tale it's
your job to figure out what the
two rhyming words are you can ask
me for him so sofa gopher
no because goofus have taken and the
answer air player fable you can get
pretty clever with the synonyms once you
get going but it helps to start
with something easier so you can ask
as many questions ask for hints and
all that kind of stuff okay so
i'll kick it off i got one
right yeah i want ray ago and
this is an easy one well it
it was off to dove right into
it oh deedee ah feline chapeau cat
that's right you guys did it i
proud of lee did it okay
um oh here let me think of
one
ah ok
um
okay how do i say this
um um i'm trying okay hold on
i say more than one word because
some some things i'm thinking of don't
have one like a one-word synonym can
you do a two word synonym camp
yeah i don't know what you mean
but yeah ok so here's why and
here's how i think you can sure
okay okay sleep space that's what i
mean
oh yeah spaces sleep space um top
top yeah bedhead yeah oh
how about um
dog speech rest area bark park
yeah barking parkings what i was thinking
but yeah oh yeah rush area parking
i mean what what else is that
what is a synonym for parking i
was trying to think of that like
well it's like synonyms for like car
slot
oh man have you seen her car
slot oh
that's not funny dear
that's not clever dear
okay me i get yeah yeah yeah
yeah
um
okay okay i like where i'm going
okay i'm going i like where i'm
going
ah
wolf prey slumber
wolf prey slumber sheep sleep you got
it okay here's my
you're just thinking about yours not trying
to guess his
yeah
ah okay ah
pale fear
white right right yeah yes
wow scheme sucks ass ah
wow wow wow i thought it'd be
really fun oh um
ah
rectangular follicles square hair
is this fuss suck
this is fun
i'm laughing but ah okay i'm gonna
try and cope with one that's like
really hard it's my turn laura god
dammit she's just admitting she's not gonna
be listening to you oh
oh okay i won't even think about
my okay ah okay well what do
you think about why
um
argyle timepiece
patter plaid
swatch watch no um check clock
does those rhyme
buck clock
sock clock yeah oh see i helped
i helped okay
you don't want lauren here as good
as your word you were not thinking
of yours yeah have to think about
it um
i got one if you if you
know i got really want to try
um
okay
potato seed
potatoes
that was the christian bookstore i worked
at
the power of of the potato see
oh wait i thought potato seed was
the first part of it yeah it's
just potatoes seeds oh oh i don't
know if yeah just ah
so bud yeah oh wait oh seed
oh god i gotta go to bed
but okay here's my real estate betting
from piano man
real estate betting yeah house sheets
um
betting or bedding bed ah da da
da da ding okay
double d
okay
loft soft
no
shoot okay do i give you another
costume house house pillow house
um website
head
domain
this is related to my previous clue
the guy just keeps saying don't tell
me please
domaine dovey
um like link-up the previous words were
ok real estate website zillow pillow yea
alright here we go we've turned the
corner on our having fun
um
a
sickly
tickly
a doc
um
sickly ah diversion
ailing flailing
yeah failing diversion
sickly diversion
flu askew
ah new clue no clue yeah um
ah a ailing um
fun activity
sickly ailing diversion past time but no
nothing rise with pastime facetime facetime pastime
ah barking ferris wheel
um
ache
achy breaky
is that right yeah he is i
know okay
hobbled um limb pimp
ah guys got the pimp limp
ah what was the last cool i
gave a fun time or no it
wasn't volatility maybe fun um yeah um
so i'm gonna say a hobbled ah
um
ah children's pastime oh hopscotch swap scotch
hopscotch
would you say lauren sway play
um
well hobbled is someone cuts off your
foot right then what happens necessarily
sickly been way
lame game yeah oh i'm gay i'm
okay
um get it
um okay
giggle no pickle pickle ah
um
illuminate joy
ooh you googling it no
um
illuminate joy lighting
why eating
illuminate lighting
joy okay how about joy my flappy
happy flappy happy no it's not floppy
happy
okay and that puts me back at
square one um and give us another
one i can't think of it okay
um
on turkish
and turkish on turkish
on turkish what does turkish make you
think luffy taffy know that laugh a
taffy
you bet i live i'd have a
turkish dominate o de lion yes light
delight yes yay
yea we did it i'll wait i
still have one to go what
um
ah
big bear big bear presentation
ah grizzly paisley trip pip
aspen ski
aspen ah ah revelation
not revelation aspen presentation is good or
aspen ah display
snow show
very close yeah i'll just give it
to you it was snow place showcase
what
what no why not we were never
going to get snow snowflake you came
right next to it and you nuzzled
up against this no play was sweet
no wings here with an actual word
that people know yes
the wheel of fortune would accept it
under their runtime rules so play showcase
under their arrived they would accept the
puzzle that they made yes there are
judges for all of their puzzles ah
it's a bipartisan board and we've shown
the of the tribunal and we're ready
to play wheel
well guys that said thank you so
much us that way i won't say
it was fun but it was i
won't say it was fun but it
was a time had by all i've
met the whole episode are you guys
talking about that as well your company
sorry about the game no no i
was just talking about franny lets see
franny she's going to break my zoom
get the fuck off that right i'm
going to break matzo you curse
candy oh that's my dog high dog
friendly she's very cute umm guys thank
you so much we we hope to
be back in the backyard um by
the way i live next door to
sia that's why that we want to
swing um without music wouldn't be
the law heard under her way i
couldn't think ah
audible i can think of the word
auto heard under her wig audible bottle
oh well that's a good one save
that
see ya wouldn't wanna be ya well
we will be back in the yard
next time i'm sure i'm sure but
thank you for listening um don't forget
that we are stay ah oh my
god don't forget americans three m usa
and we are tomcat on twitter three
of us via twitter and instagram and
like and subscribe us on itunes
rns are i don't know what i
don't know yeah the wherever it works
christian right if you can rate us
rate us ah leave a review date
i'd ever heard us if you can
date davis i dare you to that's
challenge that's the challenge we're all married
if you if we all go out
one night a week if you can
manage today any of us we all
go out to a
bar one night a week and if
you incite love to us next to
somebody check wedding rings
but you have to date all three
of us at the same time that's
right if you can manage it we
all have to want to date you
and we're not a couple together no
no we will each
okay alright we'll see you next week
bye bye everybody e