three
no
ah threesome three notes with the fur
cracks without the fur somewhere crux everyone's
looking at her you sadie shows nobody
no zozo is o o's
guys it's summer crock season this is
not an app this is actually the
start of the show it is summer
crock season and if your feet aren't
in some crux and they're not comfortable
umm ahmed johnson crocs and they're not
comfortable if your feet aren't in some
crux there no oh i was just
not an ad i gotta stress this
is the actual show this is the
show and we're showing you if you
don't have crocs right now you need
them right now and there is no
discount code
just buy them just go buy a
thing that's not paying us to tell
you this and enjoy in fact crux
is ignoring us very hard much like
our giblets that says ignore ignore his
advice yeah you know what i need
to i need to really try to
get in touch with crocs because i
feel like we just like a movie
star would be able to get in
touch
with crocs i'll put somebody on we'll
see what happens
i'll start with an instagram story and
we'll see what happens yes ah by
the way welcome to threesome i'm scott
arvin i'm lauren laccase okay i'm paul
f tompkins he's wearing a pee on
his hats that stands for paul no
it doesn't it stands for phillies the
philadelphia phillies the baseball team are
you happy though that your name starts
with p because this guy's say
it's a little secret little bonus for
me yeah do you have another hat
that says f and then another one
that says t and you could wear
um around the same time like a
lunatic like a looney
three loony three headed lunatic
i can have one bill in the
front two bills on the side yes
and then take them off subsequently p
f d s
you're always screaming your name right i'm
never
this is what here's what i like
about doing the show it gives me
a breakthrough screen when my name for
an hour but only one hour so
it's back to work guys i hate
to bust in here with a topic
but i have some some news whoa
since the last episode yes i forgot
i forgot to slam this in the
last episode meanwhile okay so it didn't
happen in between
the episodes because we told no it
didn't two we took two hours and
fifteen minutes or so in between the
previous episode in the last episode is
gonna be two hours and scott needed
an extra fifteen minutes for some reason
we didn't ask question he had to
drink milk from a bottle
what's your what's your goddamn topic last
night jamie and i went to a
restaurant wow yes wow we went to
it we had a double date with
friends we're all fully waxed we went
to this restaurant off where xt all
we were awfully vast huh
that slows backs dripping in the stuff
is drink we were cut we were
soaking wet with vaccine and um so
this restaurant that we used to go
to all the time ah their staff
was all that i know which one
i went to after a star is
born when you couldn't get ye to
start a strange that snow a different
one
you were refused entry into a star
is born i was refused entry i
have a youngest can josh bleep it
out if i say it yeah who
cares the mother fuckin
that restaurant that starts with an a
that's like italian food no that's the
one scott was talking about well go
there
he's good i can't wait to go
back blah blah long thing i said
we know leave red we um we
shall we went and had ah a
night dining in at a restaurant i
was wondering how it was going to
feel it did not feel weird you
know what i mean it actually result
it was very refreshing it's like just
feels normal we were inside we were
shocked we did you have to wear
masks the entire time we do not
draw mass the staff were also wearing
masks um and they still have a
lot of their tables taken out um
so there's a lot of space between
other patrons for twenty there's a lot
of space between other patron
ns and ovid droplets stay around no
tae bo hue and we had a
lovely time and i was but it
did not feel it didn't feel strange
to me it felt immediately familiar and
you know like oh yeah this is
what life is like how is your
covered by the way
i mean i was more other people's
problem than mine now
they're you know they they opened up
some restaurants on robertson i was gonna
see if you want to go paul
um but ah did you know i
love robertson yeah but all the restaurants
on robertson they opened up for outdoor
they're like putting in like every restaurant
is out on the street and stuff
that yeah closing down the street and
all that wow out on the street
ah
um but yeah i want to go
out on history i don't want to
go out in the day i'll like
i can eat a bad bottle voting
or we go no raw wow
a drink guy do you really yeah
oh we gotta wow what a singing
star like mr eddie grant mister eddie
grant who also did the same for
romancing stones the star
now mit media baja lord strawberry night
and every day
um lauren showing her teeth right now
which means i think she started progression
yeah yeah she tell you to stay
away um no but here's the thing
yeah so that felt very normal to
me to not feel like how did
we lose again and there's there's a
sort of meme that i'll admit i've
laughed at some of this sometimes but
the idea of
that we don't know how to we're
not going to know how to be
around each other again he was like
no we are i mean because also
we've been talking to people through our
fucking computers and you've seen people in
distanced hangs and stuff like that i
think i feel like a loser within
ten minutes yeah i feel like it's
a very small sliver of people who
absolut
really are not talking to anyone have
not talked anyway for a year also
it's just like you know driving i've
barely driven this year i have maybe
like you know fifty miles on my
car this year but get me out
there within two minutes and i'm like
slamming on the horn and getting going
saying get the fuck out of the
way like it all just comes back
to drive
thanks but i do feel rusty every
time i get in the car
but you're the tin man yeah i
feel free when i get in the
car i feel like that's when it
feels the most normal because you have
the most power over life and death
well i mean cause i don't have
my mask on and i can have
my windows down my music it feels
like a normal experience yeah well will
the three of us will have to
get together at some point but
it's inevitable i guess yeah
i know we're seeing each other you
guys are like some of the only
people i've really seen in besan yeah
but you still stay away i didn't
get well yeah you didn't get to
come bless
we didn't started recording with our usual
ten minute hugs
lauren have you been part of an
improv group that that is that touchy-feely
where you like huh you're not around
yourself up that way yeah so yeah
i definitely been part of a lot
of improv teams over the years and
there's varying degrees of ah loopy loopy
sort of stuff going on beforehand you
know what i mean it's very filter
like i feel like when i was
in chicago that was even more the
case because you were in chicago when
but like i feel like the energy
around improv there was even more like
this is everything kind of thing yay
and paul rust ah reminded me on
when he was on bang bang the
other week that when he and neil
campbell did the live show oh yeah
show us yes that um i i
he came backstage before the show and
caught them stretching before the show and
then i guess in my intro i
made fun of them for stretching before
show was just like you know you
get into comedy so you don't have
to stretch you know yeah i mean
i think some of those things are
nice just to like feel like you're
focused and are about to do something
well also if you're gonna do so
some physical if you're gonna move around
yeah but um i think there was
i did a lot more corny things
and i'm willing to do now
just what corner things are you willing
to do now what can we get
you to do right now right now
i just look like a chicken okay
nah see it um i it was
more that i feel like now like
you know you spend so many years
were horsing for probably like doing ember
weekly improv practice and then for each
team that you're on and then at
a certain point you kind of go
i think we're good enough to not
do that anymore yeah and then that
feels amazing and then you're like why
would i ever sit around like boo
bop boo to look just like yeah
now i feel i kind of feel
that way too that that because ah
you know i've got into improv relatively
late but there are some some people
in the seventies when i was in
myself when you yes and you've been
aged
backwards ever say yes bb benji bucks
so um but thank you pause so
i was part of benjamin buttons you
just had a really nice but it
everyone's like yeah the aging thing but
like i mean have you seen the
movie when he does have a nice
but at one point wow
yeah
old so um some groups i've noticed
that some people ah it people that
i don't improvise with often or have
only like improvise with one time are
people that tend to do warm up
so they want to do like a
little scenes before a show or something
and this is people they maybe it's
because of the
presence of me because they all know
each other but i always get the
impression like oh no they do this
before every show whereas i don't i
don't do that because i first of
all i never learned those were right
but also can't learn them anymore yeah
but also knows july to your baby
but i just wanted to escalate
yeah but it's not like like there's
some two legs
to learn it learning
but things like vocal exercises i think
still have a use no matter how
long you've been doing a thing um
whether it's singing or acting if you
do like your tongue twisters and shit
like that like i get that to
to to make sure that you're you're
limber you know with your with your
mouth on stage and the singing of
course you got to lose
listen up your make your your throws
in tune i mean you are making
me think that like there are moments
where like you're with a team and
you haven't seen each other in a
while and then like you're kind of
on different pages where like it would
be helpful to center yourself yeah and
kind of like check-in and go like
cheerios rice krispies
first way you got jumped into the
proud boys did they did they say
that or that's fairly that's like ah
one of the initiation things as you
have to name a bunch of cereals
while guys are beating the shit out
oh yeah why would anyone out i
found that i that i need to
say if i'm i'm
about to have a really uncomfortable conversation
with someone i need to say the
words out loud for the first time
before i talked to them because you
know how you know how like that's
why cool up stop touching my stuff
by which and then you and my
bedroom door coolum i want to watch
tv my show tonight
no but you know how how you
know that's why you go to therapy
so you can say stuff out loud
for the first time because if you
don't you keep it inside or whatever
but um you know the whole thing
is if it's never even mentioned able
it's manageable you know what i mean
like like a lot of a lot
of people who have really bad problems
just like internalize everything right so
so but i found that i need
to if i'm about to have an
uncomfortable conversation with someone where i need
to like you know lower the boom
and i'm not great at confrontation you
know what i mean i need to
like practicing it out loud because if
i don't the first time i say
it out loud will be like filled
with emotion you know so you are
like those scenes in movies
that i do not like where somebody
is
practicing a big speech in the mirror
not in the mirror i just need
to like literally say you're fired no
no no say different your your wires
well i think that's helpful too because
sometimes if i just think about something
that i wanna say i like forget
all my points by the time i'm
actually having the conversation yeah like if
you like on the few instances where
i've had to fire a manager for
instance you know what i mean and
and i've been with them for a
long time yeah
you know if i were to just
say what i was feeling off the
top of my head it would get
like very emotionally yeah you know what
i mean and so and i wouldn't
even be able to say like i'm
firing
i'm just going like i love you
so much
so i just need to like say
the say my points out loud ahead
of time so i can do them
sort of like without emotion anyway that's
that's me but in terms of what
is you that's so you yeah lets
you in a nutshell about me what
do you know about you all about
me and eve now i'm steve i'm
so
sorry
i love how people use that made
up story about adam and eve to
prove that it was adam and eve
not adam and steve well it could
have been anything yeah i mean it's
like oh no it was like fish
legs that turn into monkey legs and
then we're here that's what it was
fisticuffs
on friday wasn't anything to do with
those people but i mean not ah
but it's like if you believe that
then you believe what are you going
to do
either you know i love my love
me you know i mean your merry
way and thus you oh my god
huh
i tried to watch that movie i
don't know if we've talked about this
before right after watching the document hatton
know but we've made before the documentary
i tried to watch an enhanced presence
and he's like he's just bored after
let it go i try i tried
to watch it after like all that
that stuff happened when it originally happened
when we were all hearing about it
and it's it's absolutely insane like you
i watched the first twenty minutes that
movie i was like this is just
custody yeah i think i only saw
that movie when i was in high
school
which is just a weird perspective on
it because i'm like yeah next you'll
experience i think you're gonna watch that
movie and be like oh that's how
what it was like in the late
seventy s you know what i mean
what does it though i get it
will in new york yeah i guess
you know and only kind of go
like well okay that's isn't it interesting
how things are
different like you don't watch it going
like oh wow
that's crazy because now it could not
happen you just kind of watch it
going like oh and nineteen seventy nine
yeah that's what that's why it's not
golden
wow i don't even a good question
we didn't get age of consent until
nineteen ninety nine yeah weird lincoln park
came out with their album they're like
we gotta get age of consent going
on so age of consent laws started
in the eighteen hundreds yes were you
fact checking me lauren i'm actually just
wanting to know
and eighteen thirty the age of consent
for marriage was raised eighteen years old
for males and sixteen females premier okay
um that's so gross it's crazy that
people got married when they were fourteen
it's crazy that people still get married
therefore that's so crazy that people get
married i'll just reduce it down to
this it's an archaic institution it means
nothing
today was especially about land article about
how we might live to two hundred
watts when us maybe i mean they
they say like our lifespan keeps doubling
and at some point we're gonna get
to be two hundred but i was
thinking yeah but we all look like
fucking shit at sixty year whatever it's
not good to go to two hundred
that
is going to be nasty i mean
look like shit at sixty anymore i
think it looks like shit at one
hundred but like shore ninety i'll tell
you their faces bup bup bup sigh
when you look back on loving like
people back thirty years
i feel like people looked much older
younger even just in like no people
are looking younger at their when they're
older now but i just why why
did we start talking about this about
we don't have a reason for anything
i know no one i own this
whole age come up but anyway i
don't know would you want an age
of concert oh wait you can oh
that's why would anyone get meh
married at twenty if you're gonna live
to be two hundred i think i'd
want to be lived at two hundred
so i could feel like a vampire
if i need to use if i
had a new life and i lived
to two hundred i would get married
at like one fifty yeah ooh seems
reasonable
you know but like like i if
people start living to two hundred do
you think the whole conception of marriage
will start to go away i mean
especially with like alimony and stuff like
can you imagine getting marrying melinda gates
for like one hundred years yeah can
you imagine getting married at twenty divorcing
thirty twenty and having to pay alimony
for the next one hundred and seventy
years i mean i'm sure we know
by now but i am curious how
much money melinda gates is going to
get all man because they got me
in the box
they've been together since before he was
rich right yeah
they they were just too poor people
who are selling malaria together and then
he said figure out ways to get
around
yeah
how can we track everyone on earth
we got a trick i'm somehow well
i'll admit a serum it is crazy
like i clicked on a tweet about
them divorcing and i read some comments
underneath it which i shouldn't do but
it was all like
like these people finally getting what is
coming to them and finally satan
is is getting it's come up and
and like i'm like because they're getting
a divorce i think it's probably fine
like what are they saying must be
okay harrassed well first of all they
think they like they're focusing on the
wrong thing like everyone kind of i
feel like has agreed at a certain
point that getting divorced is a good
thing so it's like he's probably have
being the time of his life oh
man what if he ends up on
raya yeah he's gonna be all hooking
up with young comedians okay can we
talk about the ben affleck on riot
thing i was just gonna say yeah
yeah yeah let's dish okay this is
okay this song called three dish three
days
just a memoir called three dish where
we talk about tiktok yeah and only
tick tock
but um so if you don't know
what happens some woman on tiktok so
put out a tick tock saying that
she was thinking about the time that
ben affleck um and she matched on
raya and she unmatched thinking he was
fake and then he sent her a
message and then she sent her an
instagram instagram
yeah an app yes a video message
and then join match me thence me
and that but then she played it
she played this private message i just
felt mortified for him i thought that
was mortifying i agree i mean and
you know it was for her because
he said her name and and she
had a very specific name and he
put a lot into it he put
a lot and he put alive he
was really sure
honestly was flirting in the videos yeah
it was supposed to be hot and
i felt concerned about it and i
felt kind of i felt so i
felt like i was too personal like
i just knew too much i don't
think that should be allowed
well i think if someone sends you
a video that's the whole thing right
i mean it's just like how does
anyone die thankfully i was done with
dating before all of this stuff was
invented but it's i sound incredibly old
but i but yeah just how how
could anyone ever especially if you're famous
how could you ever say like okay
i'm gonna send
i feel like i would just retreat
into a cocoon and never date anyone
ever again i said yeah it does
seem really hard i think about that
a lot like people that are that
level of fame that but it's also
like well you gotta factor that in
when you do things you know what
i mean like i've been like wasn't
you do armageddon you gotta factor in
that
at some point someone's gonna buy less
likely factor but if you're if you're
ben affleck who
oh hi guy know i'm still here
we absolutely should let it go but
um if you are if you are
that famous like ok let's see ben
affleck isn't famous and he still did
that same message right like and it
was just like why did you unfriend
me or whatever or why
did you match me um you would
goofy me i don't mean like shoot
a lot it's a lot weirder if
you're not famous i mean just feeling
is only trying to save me i
have to prove it's me because no
one would think it was me but
then it's like that's so vulnerable and
then that's embarrassing but i'm also like
hey why
don't you match back with them you
know i mean like i don't know
yeah exactly look he's walked around spilling
dunkin donuts everywhere he goes i'm interested
i'm like he's the duncan tony dang
oh man he know what did we
think about him in jail getting back
together i don't know i mean if
this woman you know did that to
him i can only assume that he
went
back into jails loving embrace to comfort
him jail loves getting engaged ceo loves
loves thing more she's going to do
it five times yeah yeah has she
ever taken the plunge and well yeah
she got me yeah marc anthony wright
marc anthony not mark antony oh who
am i thinking oh he's like an
old guy sweepstakes
here
well pardon me that that's my frame
of reference instead of our tiny yeah
oh my god i remember one time
seeing gwyneth paltrow on the oscars referred
to anthony hopkins does anthony hopkins because
that's how people pronounce it over there
and it's like come on lady that
should be as embarrassing as ben affleck
sending that video absolutely
one hundred percent we should bring it
back bring back that video but i
just hate who will listen the culture
yeah i feel like they did let's
see why not let's say they did
but i think you know how it's
we were talking on the last episode
about consent yes to consents to ah
consent to record of a phone thing
yeah remember their centre record a phone
thing from last pieces get hard at
thirteen and shouldn't jack bauer he twenty
four big kids shouldn't it be illegal
to post someone's video message at some
point especially if they're famous yeah i
don't know what now with cameo i'm
like it's like that
cameo yeah now be loud and word
backs heard it job birthday and yeah
fran wants to sell they would kelly
yeah like if it was cameo and
they sang your messages
yeah no i think if you are
on camera you have to sing everything
like a cameo yeah wow tell me
lance nowhere no no jaw high school
graduation annual fail and good
um yeah but ben affleck i've i
you know i read some people talking
about it and they're all like what
a creep and i was just like
man i feel bad for him out
of and i feel i feel like
she shouldn't have done that yeah i
know what you mean i don't i
don't think it was well laura what
do you say it was it was
it creepy or was it just like
okay dude
well to me it was a little
creepy i felt unsettled by the video
itself yeah but i also understood definitely
by how turned on your i feel
like i feel like it definitely did
not come off the way he intended
it to come know and she's much
younger than him so that's also part
of what makes it yeah weird like
you're like why is he doing this
like yeah so why did he find
me on another app which is like
kind of a difficult thing to do
if you don't have the last name
of the person it's like there's just
like a lot about it that feels
kind of how over the top really
well but it's a little bit that's
what you're listening oh it's so difficult
to find but it's okay maybe not
difficult but same but it's invasive to
then send a message like the person
unmatched yo so then it you're assuming
it's because you are but it was
but
oh but you're assuming the match because
they don't know that it's you and
that was true she said it was
true she said that's why she did
it yeah she said yeah unmatched him
because she didn't think it was the
real ben affleck okay well so he
guessed right but i'm still seeing what's
happened to him all the time there's
something a little creepy about it that
being said i still think like i
would be delighted that happened like i
don't think like would be
i think it's this that i'm seeing
it as internet crash yeah because it
becomes hilarious when to take because when
you when you are in possession of
ah of something like that it has
value to give you like internet fame
for one day and she did yeah
and she she made us all laugh
at ben affleck for one day great
and we'll ever see her again
oh don't pay to shoes i may
see her on ronnie guys i'm gonna
match with her rye very soon i
was on my friends riot and saw
some celebrities on there i think i've
talked about this but that was pretty
interesting i mean it's it's a whole
different little world on that app but
that's part of why you would think
it was ben affleck because it's ah
an approved yes prob
access and people have to get approved
to get on it and a lot
of people like are rejected from it
so yeah i don't know well that's
yeah i mean can anyone apply to
get on that site so when it
was first went my friend who is
honored was first talking about it it
was all just celebrities and then they
expanded it to like influencers or people
who are artiste
istick oh sure you know i so
like people who are in the arts
you know like they had to expand
in order to have like more hot
young girls have ben affleck would go
after yeah yeah
i don't know
hey lauren you have something to say
yeah oh ya know
nothing alright let's go a break then
okay alright bye
we're back i have a question because
earlier before we started recording paul so
that he took a nap and he
said that he only takes naps on
top of the sheets what are you
the girl who outed ben affleck
here's the video
hey that's me but you said naps
are not for getting under the covers
and i disagree well does she drive
by our house where we have a
sign on the lawn that says in
this house we have on top of
the covers and that's all it says
um yeah we i don't know why
we here's what we here's our here's
our arrangement okay on the bed we
have your top sheet you have a
five hundred eighty baby duvet or comforter
we have five hundred beanie babies they're
all the princess diana yeah it's good
then we also have we also have
a blanket
that is like a sort of pho
furry blanket that is folded at the
foot of the bed that we pull
up at night sometimes you will sleep
on top of the duvet for a
nap you'll sleep on top of the
dovey under that fuzzy blander that fuzzy
that sounds comfortable it is it's really
nice i think a nap i can
do it on
the couch with no blankets that usually
it just at some point my brain
shuts down it goes you need to
be asleep right now and we'll just
like fall asleep wherever i am so
that'll be on the couch sometimes and
i can do it without a blanket
but there's nothing better than an app
where you just like it's basically just
going back to bed but for only
an eighth of the time that's the
thing because
i have to really make a play
i have to really put myself into
the headspace of i'm gonna fall asleep
because otherwise i feel like i should
get up and do something even if
i'm really really tired real snoozing i
have to emi sound machine i turned
on my sound machine i put on
my the rain gets a mask sometime
anyway but i'm asking around just loud
as hell
and then i fall asleep for me
it's like if i'm at that point
where i have to take a nap
i'm very tired and so it's i
the the only thing i have to
do really is to stop looking at
my phone and just lay there and
let my mind go and then i'll
fall asleep but i always set an
alarm i don't like because i don't
it's not good to everybody yeah
and it's not good to take naps
for too long like there's a certain
amount of time that's like i think
over a half hours too long really
i'm gonna yeah really like like an
hour because i think i have about
it takes me a while to wind
down mentally and then because i don't
i never you know i've never liked
naps my whole life is so only
recently that i feel like and they
past few years and these two kind
of yes oh yeah um i i
will do twenty minutes is what i
shoot for wow you should do three
times that i can't man i can't
i can't because that's what happens you
wake up and like oh we're more
yeah a little dog
big long beard
there's there's too much happening in my
house ah in terms of dogs barking
or people ringing the doorbell or what
have you that i need the sound
machine on the other because if it
if suddenly i finally drift off to
sleep and three minutes later i hear
the dogs barking at someone who's come
to the door it just is inferior
that like oh i was just leaves
those dogs they make me angry yeah
um does your dog above the law
and does your dog bark a lot
i'm only when someone's at the door
okay and then she goes fucking nuts
and check
they also stout i'm it when i'm
walking them and we see the mail
person or an amazon delivery person drive
up they know they know the sound
of their car or some wow and
so they bark at that like usually
they don't bark at anyone on the
street but if it is like an
amazon person drives up to someone's house
they'll
go nuts because they just know that
that is that person that comes to
our house all the time what do
they care yeah and that's what i'm
saying that's why i say to george
i'm like georgia we look what he's
pretty smart though nothing's but i mean
here's the thing nothing bad ever happens
come on remember this dogs like what
happened oh he's the person who
takes care of you open the door
got a package and closed the door
z and shot up but we don't
know with molly we don't know what
happened in her first year when she
was just ah a trash dog down
in mexico who slept outside should we
match you get her
through whitney cummings i think had a
hookup and got us this dog and
yeah lived outside in mexico and and
basically like fended for herself so we
but just saying that's okay i mean
it's like ingrained in them maybe or
something because with georgia it's like no
one has ever come to the door
and been a problem so what but
my friends sorry my friends had a
dog that they adopted
anytime you said the word abogado the
dog would go and say wow but
doesn't that mean lawyer yeah it's lawyer
bad
and i was like she and so
my friend told me i was like
really and she said and the next
time i was over there she said
watch and she just went abigail and
the dog started barking like crazy wow
just remember what happened the first time
i wonder why i don't know how
they i don't remember how they learned
that huh
but it was definitely a trial and
error thing of like what made the
dog the old do this
that is weird
you must erase that knowledge from your
brain it's not it's observing you maybe
i've never seen it and i never
well come on life's long enough it
was like to be two hundred michael
richardson who just him
no one else no one else because
one man show like mark twain
lauren how many michael richards movies have
you seen let's see
yeah the game the geese nodded the
game michael douglas
one of michael douglas had played kramer
on seinfeld oh michael richards was that
wait who's michael richards kramer from jaipur
oh i just googled i mean looks
so different i was like who is
that so different than michael douglas yes
used it to his advantage so how
many movies of his i've seen is
seinfeld one long movie yep
seventy one
would you yeah you've already been around
for a long time yeah it's gotta
be younger he was way older than
everybody else in the cast yeah he
was on the tv show fridays it
was eight seventy one no fucking chance
fuck gee you shut your fucking mouth
it was me he's actually seven okay
he's not that much younger dance
i'm surprised i didn't realize that they
were that much older i guess what
does michael douglas had to enter as
kramer and do the slide and sort
of like stopping i would love it
i bet he'd be okay at it
because he's a good actor writer is
the only good at his thing
i mean he's not a chameleon although
he did play liberace in that one
movie oh he was grand he was
in fatal attraction yeah i recently watched
a while character study yeah it's the
same guy though in almost all cases
yeah he's very he's very much who
he is but i enjoy watching him
yeah but he's he's one of those
people and maybe we talked about this
before
where he is like i feel like
in the eighties he was considered like
really hot but it's also like yeah
you'd see him in like you know
doing like ninety minutes pop up and
scripts where that people would write where
they're like young girls talking about like
oh well if only he looked like
michael douglas and you go right yeah
two year old is writing this i
love that shit i'm like gold standard
of hot man i guess but let's
google michael douglas young maybe i'm wrong
i'm talking about i mean in this
streets of san francisco and everything use
like sort of a heartthrob i would
choose handsome yeah yeah he's actually he's
bay comedy okay by mcgill fan
and my predators are my findings michael
douglas is gay because i like my
whole life he's been old yeah that's
the thing is like it's surprising when
someone who your whole life has been
old you realize you see a picture
of them from ten years before you
you know knew who they were and
they're like gorges or like katherine hepburn
was always like that for me
cause oh yeah in the eighties she
was always like hey i'm katherine hepburn
yeah and then you see her like
in the thirties and you're like dash
of dead bang but she aged really
well like her face is like you
know when you look at her i
don't know that's that to me is
i don't i know i'm
not that she'll still looks great she's
and considering she's dead yeah when you
go to work grave and digger ups
can i ask a possibly rude question
what happened to shelley duvall oh i
don't really know but she's on hard
times right yeah did you watch her
on hard things she just read that
are you just saying things that sound
like songs
cold-blooded hard times that's what i was
trying to say okay cold blooded hard
times um shelley duvall i just read
that interview here yeah it's from paul
because he took off it's for me
you're welcome
oh you're oh i took my headphones
momentarily and they were ah you could
hear the sound coming from the headphones
into the microphone lord is still confused
um i actually was looking at chelsea
she you know she kind of went
she kind of went a little nuts
though and there was like a video
interview with her and she yeah i
don't know it's it's kind of algae
listen to my own time yeah she
lives in ah in the middle of
nowhere and people kind of leave her
alone and and you know it's that
because ah yeah she's i was watching
pa
pie the other night and she's so
she's so amazing and those old movies
yeah she's ah and you know what
i have to confess
anytime i watched something like i've been
watching the next generation or you know
all this all the old star treks
or whatever and an actual come up
that i recognize i'll go on their
wikipedia page and see what they're up
to lately and if anyone is divorced
i get sad
but like i don't know i don't
know what it is about them but
when i see like she got married
in nineteen ninety one they were divorced
in nineteen ninety five i go oh
it seems to me that doesn't do
anything because i guess i've been divorced
but i feel like it's just like
oh cool i just knew oh i
don't i feel really bad for especially
if they never remarried like they got
divorced at ninety in ninety five and
yeah married it's like i wonder about
that but i feel like it's what's
worse when you see like their spouse
died or something and they're like yeah
that's very sad i do think a
lot of people that get divorced don't
get remarried like they i think i've
there's many people i've known who are
like yeah marriage is not for me
i realised like right that wasn't something
i wanted to do um you know
i i've know a lot of people
that have gotten divorced and remarried but
i think i feel like you know
just as men
me that never did again because their
their marriage their initial marriage was like
it was not in their nature to
be in a relationship like that and
then they they unfortunately found out the
hard way and so did their spouse
um you know my starter marriage um
with cool up is
ah almost over displays going great but
um i don't know i don't know
what it is and i know it's
irrational but when i look up someone's
wikipedia page and i see a divorce
or even someone who's been married five
times or something like that i go
like oh i wish them happiness they're
they're entertaining me on my video screen
right now and i wish them happiness
in their lives but should write to
them yeah i should say hey sorry
she
assigned to my ben affleck style damn
sorry you got divorced in nineteen ninety
four are you okay hey joe lykken
barry it's me
sardi has been done
chill like and barry ah so good
oh good from l a la familia
lores course we all remember her love
her yeah it's very funny seeing people
i don't even know what i'm gonna
say never mind it's very chilling people
going
just just try to play it funny
seeing people all these people are so
like jill ikenberry who were so like
in our consciousness in you know when
there were so few tv shows on
the air and then they were popular
for those seven years or something and
you just know who they are for
the rest of your life yeah
yeah we've never done anything since yeah
that's super weird it's not like henry
winkler who keeps like reinventing himself in
being on these like new cool shows
every ten years or whatever you know
true that and he is a wonderful
man yeah he's very kind yes he
ah i he was on comedy bang
dang ah and did a great job
as he was pushing a thing of
books i can't remember why but he
was really funny in it and really
great to work with him and just
a lifetime dream to work with the
fonds same as when i did like
these improv shows with with robin williams
same kind of thing of like you
know i just told them both like
growing up how much they meant to
me and from work and mindy and
happy days and so it was really
great to work with him for that
you know for hours on bang bang
and then i happened to see him
crying five months i haven't seen me
crying like no five months later so
he officiated
a wedding i went to and um
i caught up with him after the
wedding and i said hey mr winkler
i know you probably don't remember me
but hey mr winkler oh yeah right
want to dance with my baby balm
and it's any says to me he
says to me
scott comedy bang bang it premieres on
may thirteenth and i'm so excited oh
so many it was like okay what
a nice word yeah
that's really you louis mo nice i
was like oh mr winkler turn the
record on anyway food on i wanna
yeah even you
yeah
one of the nicest one of the
nicest guys one of the nicest guys
absolutely lorena g madam yes um your
air ma'am i got the force so
yeah it was my starter marriage i
mere ah i met him um i
think i met him at u c
b but he knew me from some
thing maybe
b he had just seen i remember
one of which think it wasn't he
was really nice and he was he
was just like he went out of
his way to give me a compliment
which was very nice because people that
you admire doing that is like so
memorable yeah and he doesn't have to
do that at all and um that
so i met him very briefly and
i think i auditioned
audition for something his son was creating
his see the next generation yeah i
was to play the female funds it
was turned on it's head huh
you're going to be upside down the
entire day yeah but i wanna be
female mc
yeah mozzie feminazi sorry
a femi nazi yeah that's a terrible
term that people use to anyone who's
a feminist you never heard that before
oh oh no i have you know
it's so weird i i of course
i've heard that but i then thought
immediately of oscar hours because for the
family view femme bots but i don't
know
did you know that align between the
modern feminazi is very thin
as the poet say but you know
that femme bots were originally a thing
that were on the six million dollar
man i assumed that kind of thing
yeah um oh no relation it would
probably be the seven million dollar man
now oh yeah i probably you know
i saw that movie when i was
a kid though i don't think i
probably got ninety percent of the acts
lol jokes like i only you know
i got the jokes where it was
like he's backing up the you know
he's gonna run them over previous his
and yes this fruit is his dick
that kind of thing just walking down
the stairs behind a couch that kind
of thing i don't think that femme
bots were necessarily a reference to the
six million dollar man because the femme
bots in austin
in powers were a very specific thing
and in six million and six million
and they they didn't make any other
reference to the six million dollar man
which why would they it was not
it was yeah part of that genre
that just he wasn't spoofing six million
dollar man no they just they just
stole that name either stole the name
or came up with it independently because
they they weren't oh parallels
thinking huh yeah yeah here we go
and it's and it's not pair of
parallel and its you know the seventy
s vs the ninety this is what
i'm saying the seven was first so
it was a time traveler though
stoically he came up with it first
no because he was he was frozen
before this big six million dollar man
premiered yeah that's what i'm saying so
he didn't come up with it first
okay right yeah i just remember that
part of it you don't remember him
being frozen not really it was probably
a scary movie for you when you
were a kid right yeah i'm still
good idea i'm breaking the rules ooh
do you gotta be cold you gotta
be cold yeah yeah yeah
wow i got my files yeah alright
we need to take a break we'll
be right back by
and we're back and back and it
is time for a reacher this is
called may i take your order boy
this is just already for someone who
has listened to restaurant roundup like the
two of you this is
just prime material and you consider myself
a listener through demo for oils
um i like restaurant roundup i don't
like the other stuff i don't like
three three like restaurant router this is
some bizarre maybe its own podcast and
every week scott should list all their
us we'll do our dot ah
submitted by brad
i'll basically oh oh brad paisley pays
median the accidental racist
oh that's what was that song he
did with it was called know your
racist know was l l cool j
you know you're accidentally racist know nelly
did a country song with someone really
yeah nelly is one of the first
people to do like a country like
team-up um anyway i can't remember what
it was maybe at some point
josh may put it in the chat
but who knows um okay so here's
what freeway sign gwyneth paltrow dated yeah
i declined critical research that one i
didn't research that nor did i comment
i was over zoom and sometimes lauren
you can tell when she's in research
mode or right now i'm just staring
this was admitted by brad albrecht to
customers attempt to befuddle their server with
an increasingly elaborate meal order so basically
two people are eating at a restaurant
one person's the server after the introductions
we begin the the people eating begin
with a straightforward restaurant order which the
server has to repeat back
flawlessly then we jump into chump change
the order and make it even more
complicated the server has to repeat it
back flawlessly and it continues on until
the server does not repeat it back
flawlessly enough
the end scott i'm sorry to break
in here i'm just being told that
nilly teamed up with florida georgia line
on cruz parentheses remix and parentheses wow
also he had that country grammar
okay he did okay so
yeah agreed
agreed so do you want to start
with taking the orders out since you
have some restaurant experience so we yeah
show us how it's done let me
show off for you guys okay um
alright here we go timer oh sorry
sorry whatever no time okay can we
talk about this when we get home
i want to talk about it here
here are just guys like hi have
you dined here before no no sir
first time i know i haven't i've
never been here before i also have
never been here and i never would
come here are basically would come here
either but they were open and they
had a reservation available right well um
this is a building ah
ah essentially made up you can fast
forward right wow oh okay yeah yeah
so it's thomas
okay great now what is that oh
god if i have to explain thomas
one more time small plates my dear
boy i think he got through it
pretty quickly okay so so sorry hello
second honey small-size food but since i
moved yeah honey i can't do this
area this man you saw the sign
the trivial restaurant in
the world sorry later excuse me i'm
bitching at my husband my name is
joel joel i'm sorry i'm trying to
bitch my husband hey joel could you
give us a second you want space
yeah but i will just stand here
but just give a second don't sink
please
we are the singing waiters though they're
you know we're gonna be singing who
we'll get your taco what
joel we can fight later the malini
mishra bit later joel we're ready to
take your ready for you to take
our order we actually were ready for
you to be ready for us okay
we we kind of spitball it okay
so i'm just remember it i don't
need to write it down so oh
great yeah um i can have some
i can have i'm gonna have some
of the truffle fries and i'm going
to have them put on t
op of a pizza that pizza is
going to have olives on epi medium
size and i want the truffle fries
to be cut in a criss cross
pattern and laid across the pizza on
top you know it's supposed to start
as pretty simple right
ah this is the simple restaurants just
ah you saw the sign i'll scratch
that then i'll start with twenty one
rasheda you just want to shout okay
i can do that you and i
will have the bruschetta ah to start
okay yeah are you talking about the
what she just ordered the exact same
thing i don't know what she said
but i said bruschetta which is the
correct way to pronounce two orders of
boucher no so excuse me i need
more scatter i ordered rasheda it's one
order bershad i want under one hundred
percent okay one would overshadow one order
bruschetta i can do that alright great
alright we're gonna share the taco pizza
oh okay
and we're gonna do it upside down
i want the flippy flop option okay
sure and i have could i have
mine half flipping flop okay do you
do you meaning half of the pizza
to be flipping flopped because you're sharing
this thing so yes we're getting into
belongs to getting to taco pizza up
upside down style she's getting the flipping
flop i want mine have flipping flop
we don't really like the same things
usually okay for each other i'll cut
it in half and then your half
can be flipping flop is that what
you want i just look he wants
his have to be half flippy flop
yes okay alright so it's basically ah
you want one order of the brush
ah bruschetta than the taco pizza to
share with one half of it half
filippi flops all right and the other
half upside down
and also want flippy fluff fluffs
basically three-quarters or liberty flaw c you
want you want a quarter of it
flipping flop but the other corner the
corner was flipping flopped one quarter regular
was your first day is it your
first day being a human being now
as you suck at it yeah she
was seventy nine
and i'm eighty one i bet you
thought we were younger
why would she i want our younger
joel i know joel i want to
go zero okay coke zero for the
lady joel i would like a glass
of the scotch java lee would you
say the scotch scotch or yachvili scotto
di ave this wine here sculpture diablo
the sketchy diablo okay so we have
one order
ghetto one order rasheda a taco pizza
three quarters of which has been flipping
flops and we want one coke zero
and a scott show de volley sketches
yachvili deanna lee deontay i was a
napkin that has a z bread drawn
on it drawn on it by the
show
f for by a great artist it
can't be one in the same we
have three chefs that are great artists
but yes three of our other chefs
are poor artists i i you know
like to nevada chef is great artists
okay great
can i also get that wine ah
poured into an ice cube tray i
don't want frozen before he asked me
but just porting to an ice cube
tray has keys still in it no
law
poured in the ice cube tray and
just chew half in each individual compartment
and should be a six cube tray
a six cube tray but you only
want the import into half of each
of the cubes i want them half
full each of these the equipment should
be apple cubes
i mean if that's how you remember
my grade remember yeah okay so one
order bershad i want odor bruschetta taco
pizza three thousand i was and i
haven't won a sundae for dessert with
two bananas in the split well i
only want oh okay great anything for
dessert for you we can order it
now yes i want a flan with
cinnamon straws
and cinnamon spoons and a cinnamon knife
okay so one hundred percent i want
to order a bruschetta taco pizza three
quarters of which have been flip-flopped than
we want a coke zero we want
a glass of the sketch oh deana
lee ah you want that poured into
a six ice cube tray half full
on each of the
cubes we want a sunday with two
bananas that have been split oh and
we also want a flaw flan with
ah cinnamon spoon cinnamon for consignment knife
i would also like with desert a
sangha with ah a jolt cola portion
for dick
ik okay great anything after darling do
you want any for tea for repartee
for anything like that i would like
a scotch on the rocks large large
how large the size of a large
soft-drink okay so twelve ounces is er
sixteen sixty order we talked in big
cope size sixty
four ounce sixteen ounces of scotch on
the rocks okay that actually sounds good
to me so cancel my thangka the
sangha jolt cola with the jolt cola
and i will have a venti scotch
on the rocks okay
how many ounces do you want that
vente vente vente oh okay which means
twenty right yes my ticket goes twenty
it does that's why they call it
that i believe yeah i know yeah
i know i'm saying oh my god
smiling fondly which was at home you're
like a father figure to me yeah
no no yeah exactly i think you're
adorable okay so one order shout one
or bruschetta a taco pizza three-quarters of
which have been flip-flopped ah then ah
oh then you want a oh yeah
yeah you want the ah oh shit
you want the bottle or you want
to share in the sum of don
schiavone
yeah you want to burn him to
the poured into the six ice cube
tray half full and you want goddamn
ah what do you want to drink
you want
you very wise a coke zero is
that right and then ah for dessert
you want the sunday with the two
bananas that have been split by a
little and you want the flan with
the cinnamon spoon fork and knife and
you want cinnamon straw x zeman straw
off for organ spoon and spoon for
cans
spoon knife and then ah ma'am you
want sixteen ounces of scotch on the
rocks and sir you want the venti
twenty ounces of scotch on the rocks
anything else i changed my mind i
want to go back to my original
after dinner drink order okay so you
want the ah it was the it
was the ah sanko with the joe
cola poured into it no
i'm gonna go back now actually i
found that sounds discuss twenty twenty ounces
yes of scotch on the rocks yes
great alright and i don't want anything
except for the basho oh okay that
makes it easier so one order bruschetta
when we get the check you haven't
ordered any you haven't perfect zero you
know you don't want to make money
i there's no money are you going
to tip me at least well no
you ever implore you out
the fat little teapot
hey you're short and stout
alright get the fuck out yeah that's
a restaurant name by the way
okay
again
that was good god good work it
was okay and is it alright yes
lauren would you like to be the
winner say like okay
i think we're going to have very
successful business meeting i really do believe
that our business will be complete by
the end of this meal yeah whiskey
smash yes you know you've got us
in a business chose to do you
do who were just mining business toast
as we have no drinks i'm so
sorry about that i would love to
get you a drink sometimes with important
things i have to practice doing them
before i do them of course what
does the drink you want ah can
we just order everything all the ways
our entire nine course meal or
are you from where we are from
i was raised in the ditch outside
this restaurant
oh
wait a minute are you our sister
no probably not
a lot of people think i'm a
mexican trash dog
alright here we go i would like
ah dram bowie neat dram berlitz yes
and i would like ah
half an order of cornbread
danbury neets have noted of cornbread and
i would like the fried chicken with
all of the skin taken off okay
john bird needs half of con buds
fed chickens or the skin taken off
yep look also
i'd like the damn un nabi think
i'd like a sweaty male for a
drink i'd like i'd like to get
as an appetizer i'd like to get
the crocodile and i think for an
entree i'll have what does this say
here the the coconut explosive owning um
in
can i get that jacket though with
extra milk so i have here a
drag very neat half out of combat
um thud sudan with the skin fish
la ooh you got it elsewhere other
now um hold on i can get
there
we believe in you if that makes
any dev believe in it any ditch
person i believe in um hold on
i can't tell you your game from
the ditch you'll make something of yourself
i can't remember the last two things
he said well there was i had
an appetizer do you remember what the
appetizer was oh the crocodile of course
yeah hours yeah there's my entree it's
a special item that you serve here
it's a special item they explosion yoni
my go
expose you and a with se yes
no no it just happened
extra milk now to be fair these
were not the most simple orders to
start you off with okay try on
your menu and you're a ditch person
john but john barren it's um have
a lot of combat chicken the skin
off ah swelling now um a cuckoo
oh and a kogelo suppose the only
extra milk yes you've got a deer
yes yes yeah and you want to
change yeah why change a little something
ah perfectly okay i tend to put
the order and yet i want the
dram buoy on the rocks if that's
okay yeah i want one and a
half orders of cornbread
id ah the fried chicken is good
but then ah what i would prefer
is if i could get the pasta
fazul soup ah without any meat ah
and without any oil if that's ok
so you want to drown any online
rock sioux answers here my dear i
wandered off the raw
i didn't say neat so gen barry
you did you guys really so you
want to gen no i said so
you want to gender on the rocks
no but
you are a liar we've got everyone
that you're not a gutter person or
you drag looks
one and a half others a con
blood um
the skin taken off of anyone pasta
fazul with no meat and something else
yeah something else taken out and no
nude i'm very allergic to oh oh
i oh yes then black gold texas
tea we can change also
yeah instead of instead of the rescue
deal can i get a extend of
this ready now can i get sleep
in sleepy nail and i'd also like
instead of the crocodile yeah i'm gonna
have the eye of ah two newt
ah which is ah looks to be
a tune-up
and ah sunny so rusty when sleepy
now and i have lots of news
yes a guy also have his chicken
skin and with good weight well done
with the coconut expose yoni could you
make sure with the extra milk that
it is ah one and one point
five percent coconut milk
yes
would you repeat everything back to us
honey look onto to have a tandoori
on the rocks you're going to have
one and a half orders of of
columbo you want to have chicken with
the skin taken off the side because
i'm gonna get to that later i
don't have
no oil and no meat and you're
going to have a sleepy nail you're
going to have the
um i have to newt and you're
going to have the coconuts expose yoni
with one and a half extra teaspoons
of milk
and that's close but it's very close
one point five percent milk and also
i think you forgot something that you
specifically says you would put a saturday
yeah and chicken skin just
oh we're we're very forgetful of vogue
desert oh it's about dessert we actually
don't have that yeah i'm gonna need
you to go across the streets to
your dessert store also use something you
don't know what we consider desert you
only just met us okay i rather
like something several
yes i'd like a sleeve of ritz
crackers and i'd like them coated with
olive oil make sure my friend doesn't
get any because he's very allergic to
oil and the olive oil should be
extra extra virgin and it should have
a picture of a lady on the
bottle yes and i want a pie
a pot pie turned upside down with
every other carrot taken out to voice
what happened are you all right i
cleared my throat and i am able
to talk like this now last year
did checks it
i'm not from the ditch what you
lied i know i'm a liar like
she is her business venture this is
so upsetting i coin you i quit
and go before you quit tell us
what we ordered sleeve of ritz with
olive oil just go the whole thing
that's the game
yeah on the rocks ah when the
hell is a club of chicken with
no skin loma fried chicken and the
scheme of possible rule no meat no
oil and you're gonna have a sleepy
nail you're gonna have a
newt yeah you're gonna have chicken skin
from his and you're gonna have coconut
explosives on me with one of the
one point five um percent milk you're
going to have a sleeve of wit
crackers dipped in the olive oil when
so um percent
top pay shipped over what
what about my carrots i can't eat
any carrots you must take every other
carrot out i count a girl
ah everybody wins everyone my god that's
exhausting
you want to be the waiter i'm
ready talking like that is the biggest
problem yeah that was okay
hey um oh hi me know i
was saying i was saying hi to
my do you need a moment should
i come back i mean i don't
know honey what do you what do
ya mean i don't really need a
under no we don't we're fine is
everything okay
i just just to tell you tonight
i was talking to the waiter zebra
okay i'm ok i'm i'm worried about
way you tell me well just wait
i don't have anyone to tell you
know you're worried about your memos that
was awesome meanwhile i'm saying well wait
till he takes our order are you
listening you're gonna tell me yes if
he gets if he promised me if
he gets our order correct will you
tell me what's been on your
mind obviously something's been on your mind
for the past week and yeah i
don't know whether to be excited or
concerned or concerned as the concern really
concerned be very concerned remember the fly
hey dude stay out of this i'm
sorry i apologize this is between my
girlfriend who i guess is gonna break
up with me or something in my
life oh no a person that let's
just
it's worse than that oh okay i'm
ready to order okay alright well what
can i get you welcome to slabs
i might have this sloppy hampi um
on the sloppy happy but i want
it to have no cheese i want
um dipping sauce on the side okay
and you sir i'd like the eighth
of the pound
sloppy junior
wow
with extra pickles ah and ah fried
onions on the side ah and ketchup
and mustard mixed up into one thing
i don't know what you would call
it like ketch turd or ramekin ram
oh no i don't mean the container
but i'll take it in a plastic
ic container if that's i'll i'll take
that to go okay but everything else
will be here so a sloppy happy
no cheese with ketchup on the side
dipping sauce on the song dipping sauce
on the side forgive me forgive me
cats are amazing check sent know i
consider are you from the ditch i'm
just i tried to forget about it
but yeah my grandparents are from
the ditch she's tried to lose it
because she thinks she's better than it
comes out whenever i say dipping sauce
so slappy happy with no cheese dipping
sauce on the side and you sir
wanted these sloppy
the eighth of the town sloppy junior
aces does levy junior and you wanted
ah onion rings and no no fried
onions on the side friday onions on
the side and you want to do
a ketchup and mustard mix together to
go to go yeah and extra pickles
and extra pickles instance okay sorry
goals boy that will be terrible yeah
can i get the fries dipped in
chocolate and can i have the um
milkshake that has the aura on the
bottom and the peanut butter on top
okay and you sir deserve can i
get the boots semi desert oh i'm
sorry it is a dessert as well
so i thought but it is a
drink i see it's a drink yeah
could i get the boots with the
fur shake the one that looks like
the boots with the fur what is
in that
oh everything it's a suicide everything in
the restaurant everything in the restaurant chairs
i mean the whole deal i guess
i could not order the other stuff
i ordered that i'll just have the
boots with the fur shake because that
is everything okay so budget for shake
for you and you wanted to have
these sloppy happy no cheese dipping sauce
on the side
side you wanted the fries dipped in
chocolate and you wanted the um the
shake that has the oil in the
bottom of the peanut butter on top
yeah and i wanted to get um
i know if you guys still have
it from the secret menu but it's
the elephant um burger where it has
sort of like those elephant knees as
the
the um top and bottom and the
meat is the elephant's face and it's
all real and it was killed by
donald trump junior
oh you're ordering for her what a
charming old fashioned gesture not for long
i'm just point you to the same
she's looking at the menu it's the
same thing alright a user could you
add the optional car wash onto my
meal and ah have that done yeah
i'd like the detail ah so
detailed with the vacuum i'll definitely to
the end two coats of wax and
can i get the rachel haircut and
i'm also going to get a pair
of prescription glasses that are like mr
magoo yeah and also i think that
i need probably twenty milligrams of vitamin
d and zinc was followed
any of this honestly cuz yeah he's
not reading any of you repeat that
back to sleep yes i'd be happy
too so so far we have slappy
happy with no cheese dipping sauce on
the side we have one suicide um
sure but that's called the
yes you know it
the the shake called the
buddhists refer to show called the witcher
the phone about his burger i know
he had to debate like this because
the fur is everything um is this
what you're gonna tell me why you
never listened to me
please don't interrupt and then you will
have the fries dipped in chocolate milkshake
that's the oriole in the bottom and
the peanut butter on top ah you
want your car washed detailed with vacuuming
two coats of wax you want the
rachel haircut and the secret elephant burger
that's
it's made of the burgers the maid
of the elephants knees and it's face
and it's trunk is that correct
and killed yeah and killed by donald
trump junior yes right yes i plan
on your chivalry sir and then also
my my medication i need the oh
yes you need fifty milligrams of twenty
milligrams vitamin d fifty milligrams of twenty
twenty vitamin d
very good anything else can you scrap
the vitamin d actually now that i
think about i have plenty of that
i had a lot of that beforehand
and just so you just want the
twenty milligrams then yeah could i get
the um i realised i don't have
a car to get deep to get
you the car wash
when did you last see arrows whenever
you're talking about yeah could you order
me like a new prius okay ah
probably two thousand and eleven year so
not a new one not a no
no just to use prius can can
you make sure that it has the
sticker on the that gets you into
the carpool lanes
yes and then wash that with the
same you know the same thing that
i said earlier yes okay and anything
else few meme i want to have
you deliver bad news to him oh
so let's see if i have everything
here you would like a slappy happy
no cheese dip
the sauce on the side ah you
will have the boots with the first
shake which is everything suicide um you
also would like ah you want the
tracy the milkshake with the ori on
the bottom and the peanut butter on
the toe you didn't say well you
want that ah and then you were
would like the carwash french fries for
common french i can't believe it now
i mentioned the french fries dipped in
the chocolate okay okay and then you
will have the carwash with the detailing
and that bouvier twenty eleven welser that
will be a twenty eleven prius with
the sticker that gets you in the
carpool lane ah
you would like to wax though two
coats of wax of course vacuuming i
believe i mentioned the vacuuming um and
i've been doing this a long time
sir
don't worry don't worry i'll take care
of you i'm seventy eight hundred years
old wow yes wow yes i'm the
oldest profession that's right that's right you
happy now that i'm this old yes
um and then let's see you wanted
the ah rachel haircut with the secret
ah elephant burger from the secret menu
that open burger of course is made
of the elephants nice face and trunk
and it is killed by donald trump
junior um and you want to just
the twenty milligrams you no longer wear
that fit like fifty milligrams oh i
didn't want any of that no milligrams
no milligrams of nothing yeah but i
think he wants you to do something
and you want me to deliver some
bad news would you like to do
that now or later right now is
good you can tell him that i
hired you to kill him i'm so
sorry to inform you sir but i've
been hired to kill you by her
oh not like this like this
and seeing
but using silent john yes i'm a
deadly yeah he's reached over and choked
him twice yeah yeah i choke too
oh i didn't know you choked me
oh darth vader vader whoa you're theater
oh right huh later bam la better
bad lamb
had a job
well that was fun it's actually very
mentally taxing it is i'm exhausted and
sleep but it was very fun i
want
for one hour under the covers yeah
you to lauren under the covers i
might do that i might do that
or am i just stare you know
maybe we'll do a second nap
live it up maybe something's wrong with
me
we'll find you just now on the
next episode yeah um yeah see you
next time remember to get those threesome
giblets and put them on your crocs
which i guess crocs is not interested
in sponsoring us for some wow yes
get out of rocks we don't love
ya krug rocks i thank you all
for listening rate and subscribe and review
and all that stuff we
adore you oh my boo
ugh