nah
oh
ah
um hi everyone oh pathetic music psychopathic
music forgot that's what we do he
went three two one i went ah
and then you guys shouted three okay
neil armstrong and then i pretended to
forget to make you feel better oh
that was nice she forgot the second
one get me i forgot the second
one and then she
maybe the same thing i mounted her
which was i forgot i remember bill
cosby wait i forgot remember look i
do remember that goes on how to
have sex oh right thing huh
love the rig affable dig was noah
who forgot what was noah i forgot
what's wrong what's it humid i forgot
what fatale birds from cosby show no
it's from one of his record albums
i memorize like all of his routines
and i think i even did one
in church once where
i did like programme where did one
in church why would you do that
you've gotta have been tragedy you were
like speaking in tongues remember when the
inches click on your mouth you're like
jim bottom lip never leave jesus dad
is great give us zeigler geek shop
som shall go for slight knee fun
impressions out the window now i know
it's so bad just to talk about
michael jackson yanks we always love to
yeah what's to love speaking about this
man can you believe the radio still
play i'm like i really know or
remember how erin a previous episode i
said i was saying that i can
enjoy a person's work oh even though
they're bad people and then i honored
on an even more recent episode i
said i heard a michael jackson song
and i couldn't enjoy it yeah back
to enjoying a bagel bar
three round out out brief candle you
powered it you hear you once you're
buying what's your personal record of not
being able to enjoy michael jackson's song
what it was that one one how
long how long did you go i
it was probably it was probably like
a good week or two and my
song was it i believe it was
don't stop til you get enough for
something yeah and i was
like you're trash i'm rash
jackson is cancelled come on i have
so many good memories plus years of
us hearing about it but finally interesting
documentary i thought you know what i've
really believe this and i think it's
over i believed it before i believed
it when he died i believed it
if we need don't know another person
with cancer
good point well this isn't the first
posthumous cancelling oh i wonder we can't
be there must be no issues alive
just this could all blow up but
also never really have kids life yeah
i want to be canceled just to
see didn't dame judi dench just say
ah today that i'm councilman hello i
i'd like to be cancelled renewing me
and yeah to me yes ah um
no she said like we can still
enjoy kevin spacey and harvey issues like
what are we going to never watch
a harvey weinstein movie again he made
so many great movies like that's a
tricky one because it's like his name
is on something hugo neck the card
co
comes up at the brain beginning then
you forget until it comes back up
at the end and then you move
a little ne but what bir my
is like he didn't make those films
like yeah he didn't have a hand
in the creative he may be gave
a note maybe do you think he
enjoyed the movies that he made i
don't when i'm such i'm searched
just pig like he was like that's
good if other people enjoyed the mystery
more for six in this oh are
they having sex she looks like she
wants to do it and i understand
that why does she give him money
for the hat when she could just
have sex with him
movies mrs livingston buys a hatch universal
that was beautiful maggie smith bill nighy
not the real me no it's not
okay we're selling yeah thank you yeah
yeah good actor i actually would like
to sell this movie oh okay so
bill nye who else ah let's see
colin firth
oh like he was in there darn
how many hats do the adrian anson
jessica is the only one who buys
she wants to buy a hat but
she wants very poor i will she
store this is spoiled well i need
to know if i'm gonna make yeah
this is a legitimate linwood idea commit
to this on the mic okay do
it off make your will turn them
off thank you
she um she robbed a bank why
to get a hat how much is
it she doesn't she doesn't jam much
things cost really so she doesn't she
robot store i don't i don't i
can't think of the characters in idiots
i feel i want the audience to
judge the hat still the hat not
the base oil by hash
not one of those baby are you
doing hey cup in the bush this
strange pitchman you guys doing bill cosby
yes we're doing bill cosby
the right fit for ah for you
were talking about the hat i couldn't
get a signal in the parking garage
and cancelled small
and click were back on and click
and click and click that's what i
think of what i think of cat
on a hot tin roof and click
click you know you know how he
keeps talking about have you ever seen
it i've never seen it who's the
dude with the cast who's the dude
with brick castle are you yelling to
so brick brickley entire this is a
phone we don't know
a guy named brick he talks about
the whole time about how like he
needs to drink enough until he finally
hears the click and that's when he
can relax you know it's mean death
that no no it's not death it's
like being shit face it's it's finally
i'm shit faced enough where he doesn't
care worried like everything like finally feels
like he yeah so so he just
like he spends the whole time going
to click the
click click you know arguing about the
click and then finally towards the end
of the thing he drinks a thing
he goes
the click areas yeah so stupid i
think that's what happened after about or
are you touch one in five years
during atoms since i saw are you
you're not talking about clicks during adam
sandler oh no and i'm not talking
about the kanye west click song either
i saw ten seconds of click the
adam sandler movies really what happens
in it it makes a speech and
drink color of his face oh with
a remote why did you only watch
ten seconds like to be different i
was literally walking through where it was
closer to movie theater yeah it was
a revival house it was the new
beverly they were showing ah fistful of
dollars in
well i thought his new comedy special
was really funny it was great i
haven't seen it but you know what
i saw ah murder mystery the movie
with j yeah imagine that i fuck
i can't believe how much i left
you know it's insane so it really
caught me but i was watching it
when i was visiting my family recently
and my brother was like oh that
murder mystery movie it's like choose your
own adventure and you always
is it like the baylor study said
that he just assumed do it well
he got mixed up somehow because he
thinks all movies are choose your own
adventure he's controlling the belief it has
dreams like he's a wire yeah well
he said that he's like i think
it is and he's like well no
i don't know i think it is
and then we were watching it and
i was like nothing's happening and it's
like so disappointing because the whole time
i was
thinking i'm going to eventually get to
like choose yeah a thing i liked
it though i didn't see that beyonce
twitter thread yeah i got inspired but
only if the fired you know the
beyonce three oh okay so it's this
thread where it was like your beyonce
assistant for a day do you do
this or that and don't get fired
so like if you choose the wrong
thing it leads you to it it's
like basically one of those
like quizzes where you follow a map
you know right but i didn't i
didn't i guess i'd never realised you
could do that on twitter it was
very it was very clever yeah it's
very clever i got so far away
wait how do they how does it
like this you know how you thread
tweets yes so if you choose one
on the thread then it's reply will
tell you okay you did the wrong
thing your
you're you've been fired or if you
choose the right thing then it's reply
will send you off on to another
thread i would just cheat yeah allow
would you cheat and as bonsai twitter
wanna try to do it right now
is that towering buy it from jack
hashtag paul or add paul
here my aip somebody want to get
rid of the nazis i wanna get
rid of everybody that was young me
on there okay here's my i'm enough
at last here's my opinion of twitter
yeah it would be great if you
just took out the people being able
to talk to each other here's what
i want here's what i want on
twitter and instagram no talking back no
likes or read
tweets this is also mike
lies is what you require of me
because yeah no talking back no likes
survey tweets don't be thirsty
yeah and that's in the kitchen as
well
i don't keep any liquids in the
house you re tweet to me on
the way away but he shouldn't be
thirsty yes
stand from the kitchens okay and i
also want no one to see it
and i also want instagram to have
no likes no put re posts and
i want no one to see it
so i want private picture you want
a photo album i want to die
in a photo album and i want
to interact with nobody
how how can we make this happen
for you don't you kind of wish
they would just delete all of it
over i honestly wish the entire internet
sometimes would be deleted because i see
you know just it's it's very it's
just so crazy how like brainwash i
don't know i'm sounding like a conspiracy
theorist here oh but i just this
i
just like you know when you look
at how weirdly um outright like a
lot of video game people are and
it's just like like want everyone to
just start over and go like like
i like things you know the star
wars fans are crazy now and the
video game fans are crazy now and
everyone is crazy like i i think
i'm always crazy
but now they can talk no i
don't think we were crazy like i
think i also think that it's never
had my outlet it's not so much
that there are certain people that really
are unstable right but i think that
it's just easy to do it's easy
to get outraged about stuff and it's
easy to judge it's easy to get
matter about a thing that you know
when we were mad about something we
would never go like
so listen to me other than like
a friend oh no no no you
certainly wouldn't talk to someone the way
people talk to each other sometimes i
will look at you know ryan johnson
the star wars director so sometimes i
look at his replies and i cannot
fathom being a person who waits around
eagerly for him to tweet anything so
i can call him a piece of
shit yes it's like that's there
lives yes so lame and it's just
such a waste of everything it'd be
very cool if there was a period
of time i think we're like some
news outlet deleted comments from the thing
like maybe the new york times writing
i think everything should everything should be
everybody should be comment doesn't help yes
yeah why do i need to read
an article that someone researched and then
read what some dumb ass thinks about
yeah i don't want to know it's
also the same
same fights over and over and over
again well don't even get me mommy
daddy oh don't even give a sorgi
any story on it sorted i had
it with and this and this is
my i will take some culpability in
this because i made a comment about
louis c k and then man i
got so many people that are
are searching his name and trying either
searching or it gets where he gets
we get there whatever you know but
it's people that what's so crazy to
me is it's a guy who admitted
he did this horrible stuff and then
he and then he went away and
then he's like i'm just gonna come
back now and it's like all i'm
doing is making a joke about him
being a creep and people
like but now it's like people are
like fuck yeah he got consent or
i've even seen people use the word
allegations and it's like he said it
happened it's not an allegation like stare
is like what do you care no
you won't you like him he's doing
great but you should be happy i
think it's interesting you were getting that
too because i i've seen a few
female comedians
reading about him getting like such hateful
responses back i'm just a little bit
glad that it's going both ways oh
yeah oh but i believe me but
it's so nuts to see no one
certainly rag me but yeah yeah but
did it happen i think there is
no look i'm not i'm not counting
now i will say that there's a
there is good with the inner
ynet i get you know i don't
know there's there's so many cool pitfalls
there are like some of our fans
like ah i was just ah what's
emily war do you guys know her
like she's so supportive hello out there
hey yeah she came to cluster family
yes i saw her and she's so
supportive in like you know that so
i what i did if like a
couple of years ago i
think is i just deleted anything well
first of all this is i did
this before i deleted all my twitter
posts but i was just like i
am now only going to write positive
things on the internet like i was
just like what who cares about first
of all every single person wants to
be snarky the snarky ist and the
the most clever
and the you know and no matter
what their scalability or skill level at
it you know like like you look
at everyone saying sir this is an
arby's like they're the first person to
ever make that joke or whatever but
everyone wants to be the funniest so
i was just like who gives a
shit if i don't like a tv
show and i want to make a
crack about it i'm just going to
put positive things out there on the
inch
fernet and so and then i deleted
all my twitter posts but yes like
i was saying my we're all just
trash but also i was thinking i
one thing i do is i mute
your trackers they were just right well
it's like it's it doesn't i don't
need to have a record from two
thousand and eight to now of all
the dumb things i've thought and said
like it's just not necessary and i
don't need someone to go
you know i looked back to them
and there it's not even funny like
they don't even touch me funny i'm
sure it's just like i'm bored i'm
yeah when twitter wasn't like a joke
site yeah right it was just like
hey my a one thousand yeah i'm
bored now yeah yeah but i muted
like a bunch of words a bunch
of like really hateful words yeah
yes so that i never see any
tweet that's at me or anyone with
like the word comment or like you
know just that's a hateful word well
no why do you worship it
but like i just feel like it
weeds out probably a lot of negative
things that could be seen and i
could probably add like twenty more words
that and have a better time yeah
oh yeah it's great i just can't
fathom like treating people the way people
treat each other it's just i feel
like i have fallen prey to it
of making snarky comments about things
yz or expressing myself in that way
are also professional comedians yeah but you
have loved to do it but i
am i found myself being susceptible to
that sort of twitter attitude you know
what i mean and i've stopped myself
so many times like in the midst
of composing some dumb joke i'm like
right who needs this i don't think
that
used to be fun to like live
tweet the oscars or whatever back when
it was only like five thousand people
or whatever looking at what you said
and it was fine and those people
are like stop you're flooding my feeds
right yeah yeah but now it's like
now why be another person who's trying
to be funnier than whatever people were
trying ads
i think we've passed the point where
being funny on twitter like leads to
something i think there like a few
years ago people were getting jobs from
that i don't really feel like that's
still as much of a thing where
they're like finding new writers know or
twitter figures only rob delaney shelby farrell
and maybe oh show me yeah they're
like people who like king and queen
yeah a few people like popped it
huh yeah sure but that was still
like five years yeah exactly that was
a time where like people were kind
of being plugged for that and now
it's such a like hey i do
like i like the i honestly haven't
gotten to the point where i turn
off comments on instagram yet like you
have paul but i i um i
still like posting something funny and seeing
people like go haha
that was funny or like yeah good
to see you on here whatever it's
just everything that comes with it is
so yeah i honestly i i'm so
happy that i turned off those comments
yeah let's talk about that talk about
because now it's commonly if anybody comments
it's pulse com it's talk about it's
people paul's comments talk about
i was trying to find talk about
pop music and i finally found a
talk about his comments it's like it's
the mixture of commons that i get
now from people that i either know
really well or just kind of know
from work or whatever are a mixture
of people saying nice sincere things or
a funny thing
that you know like either they they
what a funny thing that the picture
made them think of right or if
they add on a joke to it
it's funny you know right and it's
it's fewer comments it's like it's less
noise and it's really enjoyable and that's
why that's why i'm saying twitter which
should be is like the only people
who can comment to your the people
that you follow
then how fun would it be yeah
well that's what i that's what i
have done is on twitter that they
can come but i don't see it
oh i see but if i if
i go looking for it which i
often do that's like oh yeah i
see that's my moments of borders more
secure iasi yeah it's a curiosity killed
my dear boy well i'm not
yeah i thought i'd be saved
it's so like anyway i'm sorry that
we're complaining social media so much so
much complain so much i know a
huge part of our lives that's part
of the problem like i also am
like what's going on like i want
to know what's going on in the
world and i know that's the now
that's the excuse people use for twitter
of like you
no i just wanna know i wanna
be like one of the first people
to know if michael jackson dies right
but you know i went to my
plan worked i was like at a
very low point with it where i
was really frustrated and i literally was
had my finger over the delete your
account button yeah and delete your account
anyway
funny if
if it goes away than two minutes
later i see the lever right i
was working for the center i was
wearing someone could use my name and
like make an account oh yeah you
just gotta keep your account but i
just see yeah power just delete the
app wait how are you doing with
your password horrible horribly horribly i
if you haven't heard this episode they
they each have a timer on their
phone of how they can only use
the internet for an hour in order
to keep each other better and instagram
and we keep each other's passwords but
we both gave each other the password
eventually and and now i just bypass
it all day long and i told
him last night you have to reset
it i am out of i'm i'm
out of capacity yeah
yeah and it makes me feel nauseous
like i think i'll look at it
for so long that i'd be like
i hate life i'm feel bad and
i'm like this isn't healthy at all
and it's not even i can point
to what i'm looking at that's making
me do that just the feeling of
it all like so our podcast our
podcasts the same thing what do you
mean like i don't know do people
or should people not listen to these
wow what am i saying you know
first of all yeah what are you
saying it's very different because this is
a full conversation someone just posting a
picture of themselves like basically naked or
something and then going okay so then
i saw that and then and then
it's like some
it'll be alright people i know who
okay and then there's like people posting
like you know negative things or bragging
things or whatever and i just go
remember it's like yeah it's just too
much okay what do you have a
whole hive a question oh earlier did
you do an impression of dana carvey
doing impression reaches yes it's good yeah
good show i wanted to make sure
oh yeah that's very meh oh yeah
that's great well yogurt lot of impressions
on this episode we got last
that's why we're doing regis that's true
you know and those are number one
and deal with them all and more
every other time
this is maybe the view as we
were at are you doing anything lower
and that makes you happy recently yeah
let me think about it what makes
me happy hey wouldn't you do up
in san francisco after what i do
yeah because we just didn't show up
in san francisco and and i left
right after the show to go home
but you stay the night right yeah
and i wait what were you on
because they it
wasn't a footwork and get out early
enough after our show corinne told me
that no she did not overnight she
won't be able to make it did
carinthia overnight flight were you on what
time so it was to burbank maybe
yeah are you going for a bank
or ignoring me i don't know she
didn't go but she said you want
to stay sunday night not saturday i
didn't want to stay any night i
didn't want it to oh
you fly in sunday and leave sunday
yeah i don't know okay well this
conversation off me i've ran into korean
at the grocery store what what was
she buying but just to defend terrain
in the vegetable section frozen the produce
produce i want to defend kuranda there
are hundred of the bus and just
say i'm sure i miscommunicate something but
but i go with to leave okay
all i ever heard
was that you wanted to stay sunday
night i was alone and bored i
want to do so i after the
show i went shopping um and and
sounds boring well i like going over
there woman you'd be doing that oh
yes i must and then i ah
went back to hotel and then i
decided to go get dinner at a
place near the hotel and i ended
up really talking to people
i mean it was not my yeah
okay so not how i operate okay
i don't go to a place and
then meet new people and chat with
them i don't want to do that
but this happened so you so what
i heard from your social media so
this is your fault that i know
is that someone ate some of your
dessert but i bet you did not
say how the conversation started okay
hey so i was i was seated
at the bar um at the restaurant
and i was between two men
not ideal though their chair that was
available drums on it so i've heard
the two men there before you said
yeah and they're not together and i
sat between us so you thought
and the one to my left was
with another guy and then i was
like ordering food and he kept leaning
over and being like what did you
get you know that kind of thing
like hey did you get a sense
that he and the other guy were
together or did you get a sense
that he was chatting you up it
it it didn't it didn't strike me
either way it just seemed like he
was definitely wanting to talk
talk to me i don't know that
he was hitting on me i have
a bad sense for that too i've
been hitting hitting on you for like
thirty pm so it's okay i think
when i started this podcast so you
would fall in love with me okay
while it's failing so scott i'm sorry
i really thought i was gonna work
so you were yeah we came up
with this plan while playing basketball
okay so the man to my left
i didn't i didn't feel sexual necessarily
but it also didn't feel like not
he didn't feel it didn't seem like
he was gay as my i didn't
feel i didn't get the vibe that
he was dating the manic something they
were colleagues okay and our friends sure
but they were both wearing like business
clothes and i was like they just
yeah friends don't do it yeah
and he had braces and address for
friendship which i just think is a
great detail wade so yeah yeah he's
the guy the other guy the no
one was speaking to me okay he
had braithwaite he was really confident man
was with braces on his teeth or
his legs ah legs good question and
he way we were saying but he
so he was yeah he was not
one of the business
cute guys he was he whoa okay
has two faces guys friend to talk
to yes news guys thought they were
coworkers or something sure race face mother
physio had enough of him yes he
was going why did you get and
then i was like smart green shoot
every act is good and i was
like is it good it gets great
then he didn't order that i thought
he was like debating like
like you want to know he just
wants an open then he leans over
and says a couple you know he
says something else to me like warming
the pizza yeah whatever but i was
like fully texting somebody in leagues where
you eat the foods yeah i was
like not i was going like huh
you know but then turning back it
was being nice but not oh we
know welcoming and then i thought
because it got so out of control
then um he said then i ordered
no then ok what's going on you're
right up to that guy right on
i sort of i-pad thing that's like
standing up like a little tablet and
he wasn't in ipos like microsoft's okay
face it was a tablet so he
goes he kind of like commiserates with
me a little bit about the guy
talking
oh okay but i but he but
that's his angle now and i'm commiserating
with you yeah guy's terrible i thought
he was gay but i wasn't sure
and then i was kinda like okay
like trying to just like be on
my phone i decide i have a
drink and have another drink then i
decide to order dessert i get these
italian doughnuts and
i was asking the bartender like what
they are really wanting to understand cause
i don't know if i really wanted
it and whatever and it's like it's
donut hole by explaining to us what
donut holes that are basically like there's
more i know i know jack i
don't know and it comes with a
bourbon carhauler dipping sauce oh scott sounds
good but you need to know about
so the brain a little domes some
embraces man leans over to me
a nice face
i got it okay do an impression
like you said so they said hey
listen show oh yes anyone shows you
gotcha those donut charger would you get
a struck your cello he talks about
how those centrally good he's shown he's
a really cool guy and i was
like yeah yeah i was like totally
you should
i don't i don't think i said
you should have what i think i'd
say it was just but i was
a little tipsy but i was like
yeah they're great i don't know you
just conversation yeah then he says a
little bit later he turns to me
and goes and give you advice
no you're doing and then i said
what and he said i'll give you
a bite and he was saying of
whatever he ordered some zero are you
sure yeah he's as dick but i
think he meant the cake and then
i said i'll give you a bite
of my dick
how would you like to do like
my day but like i say
so i was like oh what's the
difference ha dog would be it would
be the the tip right and the
sandwich would be lowered to five sandwich
side don't buy the sandwich oh well
you mustn't a sandwiches square not always
fun me i can't believe you flew
out right that i would have totally
just i'm sorry
yeah what time was your flight wait
a minute to finish the story no
no no it was it was it
got delayed though but it ended up
flying out at eight but it was
it was at seven o any good
magazines who cares nuts that i stayed
overnight for no reason i was right
i was really frustrated by it not
against korean or anybody that was like
oh i think i'm speaking my mind
it was full so it might
yeah i've gotten it about a long
time and maybe she said there was
nothing available listener i know you're with
me okay so
the desserts come out oh you're annoying
i io everyone here is annoying that's
part of this ah that's right it's
big did desserts come ah braces guy
tells me so he deserved at the
same time yeah and so does his
friend and they get two different things
and he's going i just love sweets
i could eat sweets all day the
first thing i want to have is
sweet
then i go i want to visit
then i said because he had kind
of talked about having a bite okay
and there was this whole bite conversation
give you buy so i said i
got a couple of these donuts there
are way too many there was no
way i'd finish them and their donuts
you could just take one so i
said yeah do you want one then
at that point they both get very
oh no we could never about the
doughnuts
we're colleagues and i said
not friends truly i'm not going to
finish them i just eat this whole
pizza i'm like there's no way i'm
gonna like i only eat round things
yeah and he takes one fine fine
but he takes it with a fork
even better i'm like don't try yes
love this question to you but then
he's like can i dip it
and then i was like you gotta
lick it before you i say go
for it because so far this point
it's a straight doughnut that i have
not touched anything else touching the this
the same and he you've you've had
your germs in there presumably haven't got
one yet you haven't even had one
oh this is awful he's before me
he does it he dips it fine
it takes about
then the guy to my right starts
like we're like komisarek of minis like
oh my but i was like wow
i was like we got really close
just know what's happening like yeah i
was kind of like going with it
yeah then i'm talking to that guy
then brace face comes back and double
dips hips this mother the butch and
joan not not not if not the
other end of it were yeah you
could say my mom managed aw
falls into the sky zoo which is
now contaminated forever and then it doesn't
then he can't get it out and
he's like trying to get in i
was like why just his fingers and
i was like we've lost control i
don't dip ever again from this point
forward anyway like the sauce anyways fine
then i'm then the guy next to
me is like to give them better
review really
why don't like bourbon but then the
guy is like the guy to my
right gets real involved with me and
then we're talking for like forty minutes
forty minutes you talked to this guy
and this is the time but it's
probably forty minutes come in three who
knows was it a good conversation it
was fine there was some things about
it that i thought were good
okay robot he mentioned and looking yeah
he basically knew i was an actor
so i've got started which was also
part of the problem because then it's
like it's hard to get away yeah
he's i tried to shut down but
that didn't really work alright robot he's
like i he asked why i'm here
that i told my power i told
him all about comedy bang bang he
loved the oh wow oh i'm into
the story now
and they want to invest i told
about this show and what we just
did a great show you should take
it to shark tank and i'll tell
you this and he he oh mr
wonderful saying he actually had some improv
background and he started telling me about
it but he actually didn't know what
he was talking about so i was
happy because it wasn't just someone who's
talking out of their ass completely or
like i took a class
once at a work event yeah so
he saw me about his improv stuff
and then he tells me he's a
magician he's also a musician he also
knows jeff tweedy son and was going
to send me a ah bootleg cd
of a jeff tweedy so it was
never released i would have had to
email him for that so i didn't
feel comfortable doing that because anyway yeah
the relationship too much
yeah um but i wanted that so
if someone wants to send that to
airwolf you also have the right you
know who this guy is from all
of these clues i have hardware yeah
tweety son and you're listening um he
was nice though but then at some
point he mentioned a girlfriend and then
i was like oh and oh the
other problem was and this was the
big thing okay he kept grabbing me
oh
oh so many times he grabbed me
at my hip oh i have to
be on my arm to make a
point you know he'd be like yeah
ripping he grind okra my side not
a thing that people do know and
i really and i was really like
wow but i part of it is
like because i was like having a
few drinks and feeling pretty happy yeah
i was like wow i didn't
so i'm not in a mental city
oh hey man i just heard the
click yeah i was honestly i had
heard the noise clerk i was feeling
it and i was like i was
already in my mind in my hotel
room watching tv like how your friend's
gonna be great when i get other
friend i barely knew who i sat
next to at a dinner and she
would shove me every single time she
talked to me
i was getting so mad about it
to be like no in shove me
and she goes no i think are
the people who tap you anytime they
want to yeah yeah two oh god
yeah fuckin guy do that and i
i and i finally said to him
hey you know i can hear you
like when you when you're talking i
don't have you don't have shit in
my you don't have to have me
every
time then of course it became a
funny joke and he did a wood
oh wait what's the end of the
story what a brave face do did
he try to get honestly try to
give you the card or wow it
was it pretty much wrapped up because
they they left before me i hope
so and um
yeah i don't know i really don't
know i guess it just ended with
him dipping and dropping them going like
alright man alright later bro but yeah
you drop any later i give me
a bite of this dessert needs to
give me his friends desert oh and
i really had to say no a
lot yeah because it was also like
a cake and i was like first
of all i was full like there
was a lot happening but yes like
i don't want to
do this yeah yeah you're like sort
of like dessert menasha trois i know
it was so it was so shocking
though do you guys end up talking
to people when you go like if
you were in awe at a buy
have to be in a really good
mood i think that was it i
was like yeah but here's the thing
also is that it is so rare
for anyone to just strike up a
conversation with a
a man who's by himself yeah and
chinese told me so many stories oh
like oh my god you should read
the one i had tried to read
a book somewhere like fra but this
this i think i've been asked also
what are you reading what is it
about whatever and it's like i'm sorry
but that's not what i'm reading the
book for any car to show or
what i'm reading yeah
yes i'm reading the book so i
can read the book right and you
should have brought a book why don't
you like this book i'm reading yeah
hardly ever happens i'll tell you the
title vn that's all you get it
hardly ever happens man i will say
on the flight back that you missed
um there's a woman next to me
and i sat down and gave her
a polite hello as in like this
will be our last
interaction and then i sat down and
she turns to me and she's drumming
her fingers the entire time and then
she goes oh sheila e yes she's
of you to i heard this story
she turns to me because i hope
this thing flies yeah i'm like okay
i put on headphones hands
what a thing monday yeah oh no
i speaking of talking to people that
you don't know yes i was at
the gymnasium ah recently i've been exercising
good for you i need to get
back into it now that i finally
finished the movie by the way lawrence
and the movie we haven't talked about
it
that's the only thing i can say
about who else is in the movie
the less said the better um but
ah but now that i'm finished i
can finally get back into the sup
i'm glad to hear that you have
yes it's been it's been very good
i got past the the first garden
or two or the harder like that's
the guard i will not renew that
membership
guardian australia people yeah every turret i
go to a gym um there's a
small gym in my neighborhood has everything
i need it's great just you know
sides of beef yeah but you've got
it's got the the box where i
sit in it with just my head
sticking out and then i turn the
heat up
yes some kids always turn it up
to danger i asked them not to
do this but it's like yeah so
i was i was on the elliptical
machine and i get a text from
our old friend marilyn rice coke oh
good she says a friend of mine
is at the gym he's he's a
fan of yours he wants to say
hello oh that's psychotic right absolutely like
i said okay i'm gonna act mean
to him
so he comes up to me and
i'm like i as soon as i
heard he was he was there i
started like fucking go free because you
know you're being watched yes and so
he comes up to me i just
see this guy in my peripheral and
i feel like he's there for one
second and i turn him go what
and he said okay he turned his
turn walking i'm like i'm so sorry
i've just look at my daughter maybe
my taxes say it was gonna be
barry told me he liked it i
know he didn't like it yeah and
i don't blame him i felt bad
yeah it would scare me he would
if we had a nice little chat
but i could tell like this was
not this
not ready for getting back well yeah
good for him sometimes big dog got
a bark
alright look we need to take a
break we'll be right back
we're back hi we're back at her
daddy we're back woman i'm telling you
we're back ah this woman is in
charge i'm in carried now this woman
wants to make as much as the
men yeah speaking of well you probably
make more way more than us oh
good you're in but he's not on
the show though we actually do get
paid more than learned this weird isn't
it strange and it was our decision
we decided that basketball courts yeah they've
been doing it longer and they get
more we were shooting hoops b c
news were like hey bro what have
learned fell in love with me and
i got paid
for it this is getting weird like
for the first time finally i knew
we'd get there i knew we'd get
weird out a therapist say that to
me one time what was being weird
i knew we would get to this
point today really yeah i think that
what point do you were you crying
oh she was like hey she was
like today
paul's gonna break
i'm gonna get him i respected it
i respected it well what was it
a buildup of several sessions or was
it you'd came in hot on this
session it was about it was about
a guy
i gave it a hot rat i
was like i've got problems but i've
got to talk about is that a
new red jacket it it it it
is it looks nice thank you i
was like feels new it feels button
on it's making you uncomfortable this discussion
know i know trying to change a
sudden i know you don't believe in
therapy actually do nicely
facebook
now there's a super ego button oh
and i was gonna say i that's
how i know these guys because of
the internet well i didn't tell we
met i mean i know we're on
ten tangents and yeah it was my
fault but yeah how do you do
how many times how often do you
cry in therapy or did you when
you were going here so um i
haven't i haven't gone in probably
two years but i'm looking for it
because you solve all your problems but
then i developed a new wow no
i think i'm aware i don't know
that will help you but i'm going
to i'm going to supernatural therapist oh
let's go um i want to go
to some i mean i i'm doing
well but i would like to go
somebody who's um closer to where i
live yeah purposes very what's your address
my address is one two three apple
both apple tree way it is annoying
to drive far my therapist is is
not totally inconvenient if i'm coming from
somewhere else but the way home is
always convenient isn't always a bad traffic
time because going back the wrong way
yeah and then i feel like oh
i just like got so you know
get everything out
there now i'm in traffic for an
hour yeah yeah i want to be
home immediately yeah so getting about all
this so to sleep i do inner
therapy which is i have arguments with
myself in my head works he works
like a charm thank you absolutely that's
all about eighty cry or in your
life even an ally of therapy in
life i don't think
i cried that often but you know
what's funny i was thinking about this
the other day because i was listening
to a podcast called hysteria which i
really enjoy which is hosted by erin
ryan that host voice you do like
yeah that would i
oh yeah
but she it's a great it's a
great podcast and um it's ah it's
all women panelists and um they were
talking about crying and how often you
cry and i know that for women
you know it can there's there's a
way that women talk about crying in
the the release that it gives and
how they
feel after they cry and i realized
i don't know if i ever feel
better after i cry do you want
to i don't know that i ever
feel like i got that out you
know and now i feel better after
saying something that i've been internalizing but
first yeah mucho but i know for
sure i feel better after crying just
i mean it's definitely a release you
know it's like it
i make sure right well i'm gonna
to say it but if i could
say without crying i would prefer it
see i say things yeah i say
things while i cry i'm on the
other end of oh okay you cry
while you say things i say things
like oh that's interesting you're like oh
hey
like gift giving directions or ah look
at ah oh my bow the coconut
that's directions sort of the arguments you
have with yourself how do you get
there up both looking
that's interesting i mean i cry probably
like a couple times a week at
least like with in terms of like
tearing up but not like sobbing but
i get choked up over sentimental thing
media me too i get yeah grind
crying out of sadness or frustrating yeah
crying out of sadness or frustration as
my head one once yes every cup
i had one recently and that and
i was like oh my god this
has gotten serious like as i it's
it's hardly in terms of like you
know just personal life or whatever it
hardly ever gets to that point with
me but i was just like ooh
boy i feel bad about this one
yeah yeah yeah yeah well it's good
to cry i mean i do it
it's interesting though i like no one's
ever articulated like that about like
like not cry as often typically as
women that like you might feel better
like using your like communication to get
out your feelings that might be give
the release that the emotionalism wrong would
give a woman i here's what i
think is that and this is just
off the top of my head that
i think that because when because
men are allowed to express themselves more
freely in various ways and they're allowed
to have negative emotions that but some
that men are not allowed to express
themselves in certain way well but they're
allowed to express things they're allowed to
express things like if you're angry if
you're frustrated or whatever and women who
dug out a bark well look bigger
look up bark
litterbug women ah they are not encouraged
i don't get to girl um they're
not encouraged to to indulge those emotions
yeah and i think that it's the
only thing i can relate to as
being when i was a kid as
a middle child i was frustrated all
the time that i felt like this
person
is being listened to this person's being
listened to i'm not being listened to
or i'm not being taken seriously and
drove me fucking crazy because you feel
like i got i have no one
in this world that will hear me
and see me as as a person
you know and so that's i remember
crying a lot as a kid out
of sheer frustration like you're new
not listening to me right this is
the this is what happened to me
this is the way it is whatever
you know it's a lot of if
you're met with i don't care who
started it and it's like it's really
important that you know who started hitting
yeah like that's a big part of
what's happening right now yeah you know
and your experience as a kid is
like if he's always loved to start
it but never gets in trouble than
what is the yeah
exactly yeah when you're a parent i
wonder and all the way when you're
a parent you're a parent although away
from your first cigarette to your last
die much jumping around the room i
truly wonder snapping
little take delivery that you do they're
both jumping around the room i wonder
if because i wonder if if when
you become a parent you will start
to just go like i don't care
who started or whether it will be
important because that was what was important
when i was a kid well i
think i think nowadays mm
more people are focused on really listening
to kids like i think across the
board like of course there are always
parents like that who are paying attention
in that way but like it feels
more um appreciated on the internet at
least for you to be like well
what happened and how do you feel
about yeah we also interesting is is
because the the arguments that my brother
and i were in
as a kid it was always like
well he started it but i bet
there actually is a start to it
before that like if you dig even
deeper you can go well yeah but
the reason that the person that everyone
agrees started it did it is because
you actually started it with like some
sort of passive aggressive thing or something
i don't know any yeah i mean
but that's good to figure out if
you actually
like want to like i don't know
help your kids right rooney was ugly
i think if you're gonna make passive
aggressive comments and you're gonna react violently
you can't coexist it is funny that
people of
certain like modern generations that had old
school parents are now so afraid of
being those guys they're gonna do it
that's why it's not like i don't
fucking blame them but like the pendulum
swinging so hard yeah like i don't
wanna be like my mom yay yeah
i was like every other generation is
like that you're never gonna escape it
though like i feel like i understand
the desire
fire to say i'm not going to
scar my kids i'm not gonna have
i'm not gonna give them a reason
to resent me it's like what's gonna
yeah they'll find a way yeah i
think if i were a parent of
two kids like lifelines away your friends
think yes drezner as my friend i
would further the family the movie i
would maybe like
make my kids if they were arguing
a lot i would force them to
have a rule of like anytime you
get into an argument and make me
mediate we're going to end it with
you guys having to do a full-on
like lip kiss for sixty seconds after
so you're demented
that is still but you know you're
gonna you're gonna have a hug each
other how to lip can go nowhere
for sixty seconds because living i've ever
know it's not because you won't be
able to stop laughing during it because
it's so ridiculous so wouldn't even touch
my brother when i was growing up
like wouldn't even hug what is someone
heard about that yeah you are
those kids would be gone yeah you're
anytime we fight and they would stop
fighting because they would know that they
have to hug each other and have
each other
okay but i hear your dad i
will say scary it's funny you're scary
with how twisted you are i would
say make them make kissy noises at
each other yeah yeah so like this
and blow kisses to each other that's
the ashes actually that any better grabbed
each other by the hip and say
okay now once we've solved this argument
you guys have to make up by
blowing funny canal to each dealer that's
funny yeah i do like that where
you're like oh yeah let's just say
i love you make out
i don't know i circle i'm back
to the media it's sort of like
wow wow what changed i think you're
actually really gross
actually yeah i never really thought about
it when you say actually you mean
like i hate to be an act
guy but actually you're really gross you're
sick and then you twisted man you
twisted paul you're never having children just
go nope
monologue please um i was gonna get
my letting i didn't hear you i
didn't finish the episode i got exposed
to important theater but i wasn't a
sperm cast ma who's to say the
name look i gotta say my hockey
is an improviser who has a podcast
about her journey to become a parent
by herself
and so it's every episode is she's
either interviewing people to be sperm donors
or she's literally interviewing people to do
it or she is interviewing haven't gotten
the call while i know why take
the note she doesn't want kids to
kiss each other ah and or she
interviews just friends like that you think
is john's shouldn't
it was just genetically that's odd
ah anyway you and janie were on
together just talk about your choice to
not have children mister you have to
leave a cupful when you leave or
what i was not invited to be
a dono okay no there i didn't
want to say everything about it but
i was a little insulted journey from
where i am and i feel it's
fair to talk about because yeah
she is a podcast talk about she
got paul's picnics talk about and then
she miscarried yeah and then ah so
in the episode you were on i
think she was currently pregnant but yeah
so it's only it was not long
after we recorded that yeah she miscarried
yeah but fasten she's sharing all of
this because like it's such a personal
journey yeah but i'm
sure it's it's demystifying for a lot
of people and i'm sure it's very
um empathetic for a lot of people
who are in similar similar similar path
but yeah we ah you know janie
and i got married both kind of
on the fence about it and then
we just tipped over and to know
like as it was
just like was there ever a conversation
where you're like
i gotta admit something i'm no no
it wasn't because we we didn't we
didn't talk about it talk about dude
it's not dude levels rose
you've never used screamed at us okay
i'm not ah sell ice cream to
you in a comedy way that was
it was really funny greatest woven through
mystery it was great i deserve it
i laughed just as much listening back
to it yeah allow me in life
when it was happening umm we ah
we would pee
periodically talk about it but it was
always like
take a look how's baby here dewey
hey when in rome hey i'm in
rome bib around babe yeah we frequently
discuss it but um it would it
was always a very brief discussion and
we just both were kind of on
the same page like i don't think
so it's so great to be on
the same page yeah
either way yeah absolutely i mean you
have to and and it's i think
we were i think we lucked out
in that neither one of us went
through a like a ah ah change
of hardware it's like this is suddenly
very we need to do that and
the other person didn't want to do
it you know which would have been
right open heart i know that's really
hard really hard for people when they're
just suddenly like hey by the way
i remember that thing we were on
the same page about yeah that's huge
and yeah changing yeah but it's like
we've love kids and i it it's
just a tradeoff it's like life is
a series of trade-offs and and you
know there's certain things that by not
having kids we get to live a
certain way that we
really love and it's not just all
about like being able to leave somewhere
at a moment's notice it's also about
our lives at home and what that's
like and you know i think that
if we had kids i think we
would do an okay job i don't
know i think she would be better
than i would be right and i
know i feel like i yeah i
really owe for she would
do better than yeah you want to
present she'd that's not any better than
jail huh that's probably true just probably
drew um but yeah i was a
star when i think of myself when
i think of myself as ah as
a as a parent to a child
it really i get so anxious um
about how i would be and and
how ah i just feel like i
would let that kid down you know
that's i don't know i sort of
i worry that i'm because i like
just kind of being by myself you
know i worry that i'm gonna be
like this where you got married like
no i mean like being a club
but i but i worry learn
like yeah but now i worried that
i would be like a kids love
you in the morning and then like
see later see you at night you
know which is not that bad bunny
dad's like that yeah i'm good day
okay okay i i have the feeling
that you would be very interested in
your child's life yeah maybe yeah i
probably would yeah you would
yeah you'd be surprised how interesting or
that you know what maybe it's like
once they would be like a certain
age you see them as they almost
appear and then you'd be so happy
well i mean here is like i
mean have what they achieved in their
lives they are gonna be low achievers
they're like dead like there goes children
do you say appear
appear so you would talk to them
like their peers yes i thought they
would appear to you like operate yeah
they're holograms you come you can buy
those we've okay japan we know you've
been
um we i know we've talked about
this before but i up i feel
like what i really want with the
way i am now because i have
all this leftover love that i could
not give a child right is that
i want to be the the father
of adult children yeah i want to
be proud of like my younger friend
rice yeah and a very
colonel way how old how old is
too old for that for in like
how well is there a cut off
like a thirty because i'd be realistic
that you yeah parenting but like people
people young people that i know in
their twenties and stuff like that i've
i do i tend to go on
to take trying towards graduation pictures with
them and yeah no i do i
want them to give me presents for
father
i will give me some nephews tons
yeah i'm a great uncle but isn't
that great then you get to like
have those kids be people that you
can but you don't live here they
don't live here and ah it's funny
because we all we all might my
sister started having kids when i was
still young
young so they don't really feel like
my nieces in the right because you
weren't in a position of i'm an
uncle yeah know what that means yeah
yeah you were in like your twenties
or whatever oh no wait i'm so
at the latest like i was in
my teens when we started out oh
and your uncle oh yeah how old
is your oldest nephew or niece and
how young zionist ah oldest is in
his thirties and the young
youngest annual stem tenure with the thirty
um
no back as a kid
with say allergy um the youngest is
in college oh that's okay and then
you're saying the thirty year olds are
what they're having kids their great great
uncle yeah wow i love being an
aunt to think it's fun yeah my
nephews are coming to visit and i'm
taking them to disneyland and way where
are you gone friday
i will not be there good you
god goes to star wars land you
know i don't guys get overrun with
you're going to go to stoners like
oh i'll talk to you off mike
okay tell me some tips ah look
we need to take a break while
i tell her these tips will be
right back
hey welcome back why we just decided
to do something insane
you know we always have a feature
at the end of the show and
you know this and it's a thriller
know this we've never tried to hide
it from any we have no what
are we trying to obfuscate this no
of course not we're not trying to
office gate of space my favorite film
who have found god hung off the
space was a friend since we've in
office space um so we were just
talking about the beyonce choose your own
adventure twitter thing and chevron over here
said hey what if we play that
as the three-term and we thought well
that's not going to be good not
only has not gonna be good like
nah wouldn't be prudent so but but
i said
you know what i would play one
about your life chevron and then i
said wait a minute that's a good
idea chevron why don't you just pretend
you've hired us and give us choices
of what you want us to do
all day i'm really excited one is
right and one is wrong in your
mind and if we pick the and
and and one of us we we
choose what we're gonna do and then
you you say what's right and whoever
he was right because to continue to
continue and we all have to write
it down right we have to write
it down okay great so ah so
chevy why do we have to write
it down well because we have to
be okay we have to be on
we'll be honest okay wow really gonna
pour it doesn't matter if we're we
don't know the answer until he says
oh we're gonna so
gotta go we can all choose something
we don't know if it's being right
okay well then he has to be
honest yeah yeah he has to be
honest we can lie especially hey he's
done he but he won't be honest
you're saying you don't want him to
just have me win because he hates
you both yeah hey me he doesn't
kevin like it's huge stating sky i
just said it makes me feel better
is a nice one
this is a show become you guys
don't like me episode i like you
scott i love you alright ah ah
loves you and that's enough for voting
wow
that's right yes i'll have to love
you for both of us
are you always nagging me to make
me fall in love with you again
i'm like
hey okay already know it kinda okay
so yeah it's basically starts in the
morning yay so when you've hired us
all as you're waking up and you're
for postpaid your girlfriend you need for
any three corners a halo okay hello
everyone
oh work started
ah
he's awake but i get in there
the boss is away he just said
hello everyone
i've been staring at him for six
hours waiting for the weekend ah i
have things like he's got it in
his room either yeah there's loudspeakers hello
i think you know intercom he just
says he wakes up so perfectly says
hello everyone just heard to safely on
the other room
we sleep with our ears okay boss
boss we're here we're here yes hi
oscar mori love you we love you
suck a lot to have good dreams
boss thank you everyone um so i
need help rather buying a car or
you guys have to go to the
mall where do you need help rather
buying a car help buying a car
or we to go to
car okay i'd like to help you
buy the car i'd like to go
to the mall
i'd like to go to the mall
okay well you actually have to go
by the car oh we say we
got eliminate we got fired i might
be able to get our jobs back
later in the thread why did you
hire us that's part of this oh
i have to explain um well the
mall's close today i shouldn't know
nah we would have known mostly lows
unser j we should have knows a
trick is it christmas the car dealerships
open seventies okay good luck the entire
mall is closed but current car dealership
always open on christmas
that's big carbine day that's right yeah
because big bows yeah that's at the
mall like somedays i'll open up a
christmas president will be like thirty thousand
dollars is like what am i going
to buy if you get fired um
on the new boss and then we'll
rotate oh okay so because you know
we're gonna continue for that yeah
okay so we're at the car dealership
and the options are a convertible or
a motorcycle
you know a boss i think i
know what you want yeah
you want a convertible yeah i do
yeah oh yeah i'm gonna feel the
wind a new beautiful thicker
okay so now they're arguing that you
are you're you're trying to get the
price better that's right um lower yes
lower better lower bettors higher to me
that's why are you selling us the
car
go okay so this is the card
this is johnny carson so what are
the options for your young friend here
your assistant how much you charging for
this car oh so i'm giving the
two options yeah you saw you see
me either do a um a two
year lease with option to buy
or you can outright buy it right
now
i think you should do the lease
because you're gonna get tired of this
card you're gonna want something flashier in
a couple of years come out on
the new model i can't have you
can't be driving around some scaled fuckin
convertible it looks like scott's my assistant
now oh wow i've always wanted to
see this far too okay
you have fired actually means i'm the
new boss kevin you can be one
of my assistants okay okay that's nice
i mean hello everyone
oh she's ready
good morning sat up to morning boss
time for breakfast now do i want
a banana on the go or a
sit down pancake breakfast
oh boss you're so busy i think
you just want a banana on the
go plus it has all that potassium
i think you're sick of always having
to have a banana on the go
because you're so busy and you actually
want someone to make you a sit
down pancake breakfast after being shamed in
japan about your banana peel you're sticking
to a sit down breakfast wow you're
both fired and scott yes i've always
wanted to say this for you i'm
very busy and i have to go
that's why ate the banana in japan
so
okay alright we're in the car yes
we know you're driving maybe
that's my roadrunner impression by the way
do you like it now do i
have to get to my audition oh
okay
should we run lines in the car
while you're driving or should we get
there a little early and i'll sit
in the car i'm working by myself
while you pace around the block
this is so obvious but of course
we need to get there early so
you can do it by yourself well
i tired myself out i guess basing
around the block you're still iron i
knew it rabbit shit
sure what what i strive i'm sorry
really embarrassing
i crushed it it only took two
minutes i'm back in the car now
we need to run errands
lauren is loving this being my last
your options are we go to target
and you put me in the cart
and push it around the
or you drop me at home and
you go to target by yourself with
my list
as much as i know you would
love being pushed around the store and
saying we we we as i do
it i know you have a lot
of stuff you want to do at
home and you want to not be
around me all that much so i'm
just going to drop you off at
home it's so you're killing it
you've dropped me at home
you go to target it's a little
bit later in the day cut too
it's dinner time the options are
skipped over lunch oh wait that's lunch
that's like the options are um you
get me chick fillet through the drive
thru um or you have um me
you set me up with a meeting
with someone you think i should meet
and why
and um and it's someone you think
is important but you don't really explain
and you and it's like just go
meet with them and we have to
have a fancy yeah it says either
chick-fil-a or this maze
shows either chick layers or being in
sane person i'll pick the chick filet
ah
and it's because you pick it up
so they don't know that i'm going
there because yeah so you're like yes
and you're not photographed doing it i
am yes exactly exactly which know all
that
this is going so well okay
the next thing it has to happen
in the day as um
i needed to take my dog to
get a haircut do i want her
ears trim short or long
well ah
being as your dog wow if only
i knew the breed
huge from my assistant being being your
dog is the breed that it is
you obviously want to keep it up
that years long you're fired
yeah for them shorter and they often
keep them longer and it makes me
annoyed okay well you got lastly on
tal is the is the boss hello
everyone he's awake he's like he's quick
swick why is he wearing nothing i
have to do all my number but
i do well he went to bed
wearing clothes now he's naked
sleep walks and i take my pajamas
off i can hear you sorry hello
i have to do all my things
that i do but first close
now do i want you to dress
me in a fine italian suit or
do i want to walk out there
in my pajamas
i would say you're gonna wanna wear
the fine italian suit you always look
so great every day why would you
want to look like you're phoning it
in
the suit yeah same i think that
ah you're a big fan of downton
abbey and you love how ah all
those people are addressed by manservant so
i'm gonna go with the suit as
well you're all fired wow want you
putting clothes on me i'd rather go
out in my pajamas
wow okay i was one yeah and
i know hell
a little later bash the is what
i needed scott you're the boss
hello everyone
he's he's awake this morning good morning
morning boss guys do you think i
should run twenty miles or should i
lay in bed jerking it in front
of you guys bar
i think you should lay in bed
jerking it i want to know what
goes down
and i think you don't want to
run twenty miles if we're being honest
you'd rather lay in bed and jerk
off
i'm going to give two straight yeah
you should run twenty miles akio your
fire oh if you wait to do
it a message we haven't care to
be fighting about watch him jerk off
it's a lose lose
what are you gonna pick i really
need me
oh and say hey i need someone
here just didn't have the same story
as me you can stay in bed
and do what you please alright here
i go okay cut to the next
so no
is a lunch okay so alright the
wait that was right duh and you
just rubbed your dick again so cheap
just need someone to watch me jerk
off and that's it for me alright
guys time to do my other things
i'm going to do all day and
i still have to assistance um i
i found out last night when i
um park my car that's the one
of the lights was on it said
that i need to have it checked
shine does not pay attention to it
or ah should ah i uber somewhere
and you take the car into the
to the place
i think you should uber it's just
safer i want to make sure that
you don't get harmed and i want
to take care of all the things
that are kind of tedious like getting
the car fixed i think you should
uber and i highly recommend bringing some
headphones because i know you love avoiding
conversation and i'll take care of it
as well learn you're fired showing your
hires
he suggested the headphones i i so
pick the right no i wasn't i
wasn't gonna pick uber because i don't
like the uber but then he suggested
the headphones and i was like oh
you're right they true to what we
believe well i doubt i would have
fired you both because i was like
i don't want to uber but the
sign kevin continues go on
alright i've just uber to work seven
hello are you at the car dealership
yes i'm here
where are you
i'm at work he's omniscient what's going
on with it kevin just hears his
voices what's up with that what's up
with that like it's kind of an
are you at the car dealership would
have gotten i need you we've got
cover would be helpful know are you
don't know what oh do you know
what's a cubit okay next problem alright
what's going on with the light weight
you're supposed to just actually have it
yeah i'm just having a conversation with
him before i get to what's going
on with the light you left the
lights on so there's issues with the
battery but they're fixing it now
oh okay do i want you to
okay do i want you to come
back leave the car there and come
back and um feed me um my
meal by hand um because my hand
kind of hurts right now and i
don't want to pick up a fork
or should you just stay there and
make sure that this actually gets done
correctly
um well i know you don't you
don't want to eat your own food
you'd rather have someone feed you and
i feel like you're just going to
send me back to the car dealership
anyway
so i'll i'll feed you
get over here my big boy wow
okay wow he continues on a little
higher i'm done i'm done i'm done
to your mouse
he's just stepping with banshee just like
tilt your head to toe
oh that was so good
just be an associate
yeah he's missing just mash bananas yeah
going yes i think this is ah
yee oh no the police have just
called cool i've spent murdered oh whoa
do i want to find the killer
electrics myself or do
i want to let the police handle
this
um i feel like you you really
like the police
so you want them to take care
of it
that's why because you really liked them
who gave you the idea that i
liked the police fuck the police and
fuck you you're fired wow kevin now's
your chance some you've always wanted to
say yeah say by the way if
you say this to be for real
you're fired
i'll see you tomorrow okay thank you
it's me oh yeah just the ultimate
test that's the ultimate test i fired
him but he's gonna show tomorrow really
mean no yeah and that was good
that was fun it was fun we
found a new feature my was my
i was unclear when i was the
boss was i clear know there was
an instruction i think that was actually
the biggest pr
elam for you is that as a
boss you're not clear about what you
want and that's where they all got
we all lost our jobs were like
cleric yeah
it was supposed to be a choice
of either you personally dressing me i
got that orla okay i didn't get
it oh okay see i wasn't clear
but i but i thought that you
wanted that you seriously don't want anyone
personally addressing you oh my god what
have you i always think when you
see that in some old movie or
downton abbey or whatever yeah it's the
weirdest fucking oh man well that was
a thing you always come in late
in the press oil family you always
come in late in the process in
in downton abbey though so like it's
a little better where i go although
it would be cool because you're always
there on the finishing touches every jacket
yeah yeah lots and i had to
have a girl dress me because i
was wearing period clothes from back in
the day yeah and i had so
many layers that were really heavy
like a buttress and like all these
different things and boots that had like
a bustle bustle i mean what's a
buttress it's such like a bridge some
feeling like i was wearing a bridge
when you gotta go see this movie
bustle but you know i'm like boots
that had to be like link cool
and like they were buttons off the
side and it was um i mean
it was fine but it was it
was really uncomfortable
anything else are like zipping you in
as tight as you can possibly take
in language oh my god i think
it would have been so you didn't
like the person dressing you know i
liked her she replies no i don't
mean that you don't like the situation
oh yeah no i feel like it's
really offered by would never been able
to get into the closed by myself
what if they weren't nice comfortable clothes
that someone was putting on you know
that's weird
i'm slipping me into sweatpants like a
baby i hate i would love to
see a downton abbey type thing they
just lay on the their legs out
with gym shorts yeah alright we gotta
go this was fine this is fine
what a blast enjoying fun what a
blast i enjoyed it seem right see
you guys next week wow we love
you we love you yes yeah
ton
ugh