three
ah
three yeah um guy here guy who's
whispering i was doing here whenever i
wanted and i don't even remember i
was doing like a scary ghost whisper
great here's my you are whispering to
a ghost and trying to get it
to adjust its actions yeah like stop
stop haunting us
quit scaring everybody just you a question
yeah oh yeah please oh lauren depends
on who you are talking to you
because you looked away from both of
us i'm talking about you shit okay
maybe talking in the audience of my
name is lauren and what are you
here to say that your name is
paul and your name is scott okay
and we're rapping in a whole new
way
all this pressure to wrap it a
whole new way but the whole new
way is just we talk freestyle okay
yeah you don't think rappers cigarette wrappers
sit around thinking like what's a whole
new way to rap who's they wonder
i i had a little tiny burp
in the the first time night oh
so it sounds like you're broke you
don't think rappers like i got emotional
talking about
iris robbers i want to ask when
you have a task that needs to
be accomplished in your home such as
paperwork or you know cleaning something organizing
are you a procrastinator or do you
get right down to business
oof like the minutes it's like if
you're like oh i got her yeah
i just remembered i have to do
that thing and they're like i'll just
sit right now how would you go
like i'm a procrastinator i'll do it
two minutes before it's supposed to be
done no matter what it is yeah
i have found that i will do
household tasks that need to be done
as a way of procrastinate
eating doing other things i do that
as wow interesting day when i feel
one thing that i feel is that
i will let paperwork i'll just put
it to the signing i'll deal with
that later and then when i go
to deal with it like a month
later it's one took one second yeah
what a paper what what paperwork are
you doing constantly i get lawsuits like
like phil's are like ah i got
like a thing about my insurance that
i just got a phone call falling
because like go ahead and deal with
it which is why i'm thinking about
this now yeah but i set it
into my pile of things to deal
with and then i was like oh
right i'm late on like dues payments
for sag writers guild stuff like that
i'm lucky i don't work so i
don't have dues
need to remember
i feel like i've been forcibly retired
you gotta pay some guild dues toe
yeah yeah well the normal i just
mean like the whole like the dga
keeps emailing me reminder you know whatever
it is two point five percent of
your of your salary you gotta pay
a debt this boy yeah not a
problem for me
two point five percent of your salary
whatever you're doing remember what they're doing
you know how duck that w ga
it's like two point five percent isn't
it well i don't know because for
me it's always like what's the minimum
to stay in the guild and it's
like sixty bucks or something right i've
made any money from writing but they
they made they ah put me into
a mary
data status writers guild that means it's
like you're not we know you're not
doing anything but you still get to
be here yeah can i complain about
writer's guild insurance please wow i've been
dying for this and the listeners want
it to so
i've been worrying for the writer's skill
or i've been a member of the
writers guild for now twenty proud member
proud member i was a meme or
i've twice been in it for twenty
five years
and and remember for twenty twenty and
i love that a certain boy they
wrote to me and said you have
now qualified for insurance fraud status yeah
yeah you know because thing right so
i the back of my mind had
been like oh wow no matter what
happens at least i have me and
my family have this insurance right yeah
so then covert happens everything is shut
down i don't write for two years
right they write and go by the
way we're kicking you off your insurance
and i go i thought i had
it for life they're like no that's
when you retire ah but but you
have to actively retire and say i'm
not working like you would it that
at that point yes still that's what
they meant so and i'm like but
wait a minute aren't you supposed to
protect the writers like co-write happened it's
a pandemic and ever no one's working
they're like no more insurance by
that's cool we have a bad bad
system i'm here to talk about it
because i don't want to talk all
about that i like a lot of
research i wanna say everything i learned
our insurance has sag and it's like
the weirdness of in order to maintain
this insurance for your health ah you
have to work
and guess what working is not up
to you right and if you are
not sacred you cannot work if you
get did you get kids like they've
talked about changing all this kind of
stuff yeah like you should just get
if you remember you just get your
insurance yeah yeah no matter what you
make one year what you don't like
you have to make thirty thousand dollars
a year or something yeah i get
it why
isn't when covert happened really something i
don't know how the right insurance over
the writers guild is gonna yeah yeah
and i was like this consistently no
matter what was going on now we
usually write something right here right right
yeah what it is for so i'm
curious when when sag like well i
feel like at the beginning of covert
and they were like yeah we don't
have any we don't have any more
any because ah some members needed some
surgeries and so that's all the money
like that you gotta be fucking kidding
me well this is a problem for
people who don't work in show business
too when you tie insurance to employment
yes then you get a bunch of
unhappy people were like i can't quit
quit my job because then i'm out
of insurance and then i you know
it's just like let's just
make oil anyway i do have to
make twenty five thousand nine hundred and
fifty dollars just get saginaw i know
what you're saying out there why don't
i just like guessed right on s
and l for a week yeah just
it'll just get done you know but
like just do just do a little
pop onto a show guys let's just
and and this is a radical thing
i'm saying maybe but
let's just do medicare for all bass
everyone just gets insurance yes everyone just
gets the hell the same it makes
no i know that yes we have
the best healthcare system in the world
or the best doctors in the world
because they're competing against each other whatever
but there's gotta be a better way
i don't want the government coming between
me or my doctor i want to
go to my doc
after that's assigned to me it's either
church said it already is so complicated
anyway sorry sorry sorry great start grey
star that we're all depressed about it's
not what i was trying to get
going with my questions were you what
was your passion neater or you're a
good guy i'm a craft yeah i'm
procrastinating about medical stuff right now yeah
because i just don't sometimes it's annoying
to deal with this stuff you mean
like you wanna go get something checked
or i have to there's procedures that
i have to do just from like
i have to get a colonoscopy which
i have not done yet to take
measured i do that myself to see
every from the base of the vaults
yeah i stand next to the wall
in the kitchen
they said the door fit two little
pencil barks
that's just because yeah lie down on
the goodbye
you delete your body with six friday
yeah well that's just the crown molding
yeah yeah those are the baseball all
yours fit is a baseboard skinny as
an iceberg
as you can see i'm the a
spaceport oh my god but yeah i
have to what else do you have
to i have to get my thyroid
checked oh yeah um and i'm just
i'm supposed to be making these appointments
and i just haven't done it you
know it's really hard to do and
i also feel like in l a
it's very hard to get a doctor's
point with but you could see you
in november like yeah you so far
away yeah
well it's crazy but sometimes i'll turn
that down like even my dermatologist like
they're like we can see you next
to me and i'm like that's psychotic
and then i'm like oh go somewhere
else iconic i'll go somewhere else and
then do you have a psychosis next
may rolls around i haven't done it
yet i'm like yeah but had the
appointment tomorrow if i just kept it
on the counter to just my new
thing is i will take whatever they
give me
cancel it up and thank you yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah way to
go yeah that's the way to go
yeah when i asked this regardless you
know yeah i do like when you
go into the the doctor the tooth
doctor what do they call notice
that later and they make the automatic
appointment for you when you have and
they're just like and i always just
go yep i'll take it and then
and i usually doing march six new
nokia i'm like i don't i don't
fucking know but then it rolls around
and i'm never doing it i schedule
whatever around fires of hours yeah it's
good to say i'm just going like
yeah let me talk
to you a month beforehand and then
they're like we don't have anything anymore
oh wanna keep my options open yeah
maybe i'll get to ride a roller
coaster that day it's true a man
that would be so great do you
like roller coasters i haven't done with
boats and roller coasters oh i'm definitely
telling with roller coasters you love boats
i love ball not all roller coasters
out by the way
i want my big thunder mountain any
day oh no disneyland roller coaster rollercoaster
yeah no notes i'd probably do that
i don't know if i'd go hold
onto your hats and glasses i did
um it was a great time but
i don't really want to go on
up to topsy turvy roller coaster and
i don't want to i don't like
a little duluth there as i think
we have gotten into that in-depth fishing
a lover i know
i will and i know i'll be
on boats many more times about a
blister did a loop de loop i
think they'd be like not on a
track on like a water loop de
loop yeah i do i'll be so
happy cynical
would you ever watch her ski i
don't see that in my future i
used to when i was reply hazy
try again have you done it no
i never have i don't think she
when i was it doesn't appeal to
me it was super fun you used
to do it yeah but i thought
that the other day i was like
oh i'll never do it again there
are certain i was talking to a
friend of mine and she
like she'll never ski again i was
like yeah i mean it's just like
at a certain point no desire to
ski it's like you don't want to
sonny bono it you know and die
yeah just things are just too fuckin
thanks for putting too fine a point
on it to precarious to do ever
again applying and i like being me
a little
very house years oh i heard their
version of the bills bills bills today
it was good oh i think i
have heard that yeah i haven't
automobiles the audacity it's called writing to
say automobile automobiles in a song yeah
can you pay him and have it
be good it's good maybe we could
chill
i think i think i told you
guys this that we janie and i
rented a boat when you were in
south carolina yes we did we did
i want to do it again i
want to do like and how choppy
though is is it like the ocean
or you know what knows the river
that's probably lonely but it leads into
the ocean because i'll say when we
went to we went to italy recently
we went to venice well the yeah
the great thing about flying into venice
it's so fun is you you touch
down at the airport and then you
instead of taking a taxi to the
hotel you have to take a water
taxi fun which is very very fun
and didn't feel choppy to me they're
going fast enough where it's like they're
just skimming over the big choppy stuff
right and it's short enough for whatever
it was like twenty
minutes or whatever then i was like
that's fine i'll go i'll do that
again um but then we rented a
boat and man just twenty minutes into
it i was like i'm more sick
than i've been in forever i were
doing like you put your finger on
your lips and then the big cheeks
yeah chipmunk morph so
yeah i think it's cool off and
i were both like well we don't
need to ever do a boat again
you're gonna end up on boats again
and you're not gonna have much to
say about it because waterworld is coming
true oh it's custom joe boats come
into your life you have no control
you're like oh don't come in here
live because they do you're gonna be
like where's the lighting something that's
i'd have had to do that on
boats multiple times i go to someone's
wedding and like the rehearsal things on
a boat and then it's like this
and you just say i'm trying to
stay sharp boat in appear whatever we're
taking like a nice option on t
little airy nice old jaunty thing around
like ah ah ah very calm water
or whatever i don't mind that okay
but you're saying that i'm gonna go
on
in a big storm united sea boat
at some point in my life in
the future um tyler henry the medium
told me that he saw that for
you wow
you asked him about friends he brought
it up oh wow do you mean
to me he did what did he
say i don't think you want to
hear and you guys tell me now
did he mentioned me did he mention
me
yankees follows yeah he said your friend
named paul i'm getting that no i'm
no he said oh she'll let you
go but her name ho do you
have any says he likes snickers bars
and i said i'm not sure and
he said well he's gonna end up
in a stinkers eating contest eating contest
wow how can anyone eat but he's
gonna happen anytime
time in the next fifty years
probably sooner than fifty
the last thing i do before i
die you die because of you deathbed
before i go let me show just
snicker some throw you would do challenge
me you do because you already know
i'm dying and i'm like i i'm
throwing down the gauntlet you know what
homes people have like used their death
moment when they're very old or like
you know like a very old
person where the death feels like i've
had my time and this is like
appropriate to be like do a bit
like how many times i've gotta jump
out this bill maintain yeah yeah yeah
but where's my oscar wilde obviously he
did either that wallpaper goes or i
do
to say back with the whole job
for those last words what a guy
i believe they were yes love it
love it i mean it's hilarious what
was jaclyn how long i've mentioned on
another show what was jacques lemans tombstone
it says like um women now it
like starring in this or something like
and it just blamed yeah let me
look it up it was it
his or was it somebody's know it
was jack lemmon yes um jacques lemans
tombstone it says oh yeah jack lemmon
in yeah and then the ground
jack that's i love it you like
you come up with like funny ideas
funny ideas and then people go like
well no no you have fans around
the world are gonna want to see
you tuesday they want to be serious
it's a somber event your family members
but he committed i think some background
i do too yeah that seems like
a great use you know we have
all these stones taking up space eventually
we won't
enough room for cemeteries and things like
cemetery use the cemetery space but we
still got it due to a joke
let's let's make affordable housing instead of
cemeteries and let's just burn everybody and
there's that many secretaries i mean forest
lawn there's like three here in the
area forest lawn is huge for shines
yeah i mean the hollywood cemeteries
is fine like let's leave it to
that one in every town hey they
each get one of the most famous
people all only the famous people in
every town yeah they can be born
there or have lived there so hollywood
cemetery an easier more exclusive and new
york where they have some mosieh listers
yeah too many randoms yeah you have
to find find the good ones um
in new york i love the cemeteries
that are really old and just like
tucked between all the buildings just like
the ones you see on the way
there like you know like those one
time the acts like oh right yeah
i'll be like just like all the
really old yeah those are interesting they're
interesting we need to have them i
always i think there should be some
element of history that's history
but it's all history but you know
i like in an old church you'll
see like i like brave searches in
manhattan as well and there's so old
that the grandma first dust
oh they that even the inscription has
worn away and it's just like this
green moscow oh yeah right and it's
like what are we doing now that
feels weird it's also interesting it just
feels like hocus pocus or something but
i think like don't you think it
should be but i think we don't
want years after but you're putting the
ground they recite along that's not long
yeah but you know that if they
took out the cemeteries in manhattan they
would just build some ugly condo like
know what you need you need at
least a building that's going to be
like historically interesting or like or what
i'm saying what if they didn't just
build an ugly condo they built like
a beautiful condo yeah of course i
want to work the homeless i'm not
i'm not arguing against that
that i'm just saying but i also
think we can do that in general
yeah i don't think that you're you're
a nimby what's that not in my
backyard oh god no i'm saying like
how about just anywhere where there's a
building they just do that anywhere there's
a building vibrating i honestly launched this
un what do we do we are
using no one to sit
sport and housed know that part i
but you're saying anywhere there's a building
you like anywhere you can build a
new building could be one of those
so why do we want to want
help what do you call it affordable
housing oh yeah okay what how did
we get aware which building you say
turned down um a tear down for
what oh there's so many ugly buildings
that way i mean what's the first
building the us building so this is
good because it it inspires or gives
incentive to people who own buildings to
make them look nice yeah i think
here i have a very different argument
of about building things and i wouldn't
manhattan which i think has a lot
more historical like the aisle about value
but
here i think that architecture is um
ninety percent really bad and from like
nineteen sixty or nineteen ninety and it's
like really ugly and frightening of architecture
yeah historical value and los angeles when
i'm visiting my sister here in nineteen
eighty four we've heard this yes no
we don't no i mean we've heard
about a story i'm just putting into
perspective for me
which story do you think they to
oh no no i'm just saying that
we've heard about this trip yeah just
probably a new it's three am legend
yeah but i've visited place sister she
lived in redondo beach and the night
inspired you to live here it seems
it did names like yeah must have
been cool you said that to lumina
leg and nineteen eighty four of you
came here and were like this looks
like a pretty cool place no
no in fact the opposite because i
was raised back east where we are
encouraged to have a healthy ah hatred
of a place we've never been yeah
for sure and what's your point um
we saw i think we went to
we go to what we see out
what is the alley where they have
sundays it's it's santi alley where they
have why it's deep they have like
a little east alex almost like it's
like a little old mexican i know
you're trying to get anything kind of
just makes
it's like a little mexican town along
a street in downtown yeah oh it's
ah olvera street a vera stream yeah
and so the famously this try with
sandy lane sandy lee famously the street
to i had any name a major
ah
tejano music festival on the ny cool
up and i got married yeah we
were supposed to be married outside yes
yes had to move it inside because
loud blaring yes when we were i
remember when jane and i were pulling
up to that and we heard the
music were like what's oh this is
yeah wait do you think you'll be
able to hear it now we moved
everything inside and cool ups cry
crying because we planned everything and then
it turned out so much better because
she's great she got to make an
entrance for that giant circular staircase it
was beautiful i never yeah it was
great there's just so much better it's
why they say when one door closes
but closing you have to go inside
you have to get in there um
ah so so they had ah like
ah ah an adult
obi um it might not have been
olvera street might have been another part
of town okay describing because i've been
there so many times they had this
is all i remember was i had
like an adobe with like tara street
with like a plaque that explained it
that no that is it yeah yeah
and i was reading a plaque and
went this build a bode wrong ah
i love when you're dumb and my
sister shut me down oh yeah well
good i'm glad there was a sibling
there to show you row skid me
but we learned so much about adobe
but probably because it's doba oh sorry
for do you mean photoshop
no we learned about it because it's
a culture it's regional so much about
adobe acrobat there probably wasn't any call
to learn about adobe when you're in
philly right no i never i'd never
heard or seen that word but i
learned all about it in chicago's one
adobe you learn about what about adobe
xd is it plural adobe adobe
lie in books you know will learn
about different oh yeah a historical you
pretend to read just like talk facts
and one of them was a dubai's
yeah we didn't have books in my
school i'm sorry oh it was the
oral tradition
we can't fire in the middle of
scenes and make really over they would
t c r g a whiz in
the elder with tom
um speaking of adobe um i feel
like it never remembers a password to
save it's life and that each little
branch of adobe you have to have
a different password for he's still on
it i don't really have time to
use it for the docusign there's a
lot of things i did for rose
city emphasise absolutely sick
of passwords
by you do you know they say
for everything what is it oscar wilde
said no part of password you're tired
of life yeah i heard oh your
wild head here a wild man so
many websites too many websites let's start
let's start twenty was reading the blog
and i don't need a login for
every store i buy something from online
i don't know it's stopped doing this
we should be able to delete old
websites from the web like if you
go to let's say you stumble upon
a website older than five and you're
like no one has been on this
for years because like i get to
tell me weed comes through yeah yeah
but then there are the thirty six
humble weed those olds like eight bit
websites that are still around for something
like the what was the one one
video game that stay
still is there i can't remember but
it's like oh my god it's still
there and i just try to wipe
away um let's make graveyards on the
internet instead of in real life digital
graveyard gonna have like eight tbl to
when you had an old website yeah
after dinner
kicker daughter
back manner you can sit there and
grieve and then get back that ghost
comes up and there'd be like arlington
cemetery would be there where like special
honors you know this on this website
only people who have died in battle
about this tomb of the unknown soldier
what a waste of space there's nobody
in there not know how hard you
don't know who it is you know
somewhere somebody in there you don't know
that
you think it's really one guy and
they're like we don't always yeah they
should do a dna test out
he's part collie
no and then the mom gets mad
at the dad
here we go again here we go
again yeah this is all happened before
oh ma ho tomei too you could
do oh my tomb i like i
like a womb to tomb to to
sperm sperm to which they had it
why did your girl we had to
change that in the high school version
would you change it to births earth
maybe or something like
that i can't remember what yeah stormed
a worm that feels that feels intense
because what wounded to make sense but
oh because worms are eating you yeah
yeah i'm a warm you might get
more use out come the dirt it's
so funny like yeah when you're spur
i started out his fur homework see
i believe life begins at sperm
not even if it ever mingles with
there you go okay you owe the
cinema owner and you must not spill
your seed on the ground that's right
what was that about why is god
getting involved in that kind of business
because he had to see it it's
gross like this guy just stay standing
and someday yield because like look i
gotta watch everything and half the population
all days jerky
this good this due to own in
because spill your seat on the ground
so this guy is like just standing
out in the desert jerking off well
okay so that's the other thing they've
interpreted that interpreted that to mean anytime
you have sex it's got to be
inside a woman yeah that's their excuse
that's their excuse to say like
gay people shouldn't be gay and all
this kinda stuff because sex is only
you i've not heard that i've that's
how it was interpreted at my church
growing up really were like you shouldn't
masturbate because that's wasting your sperm yeah
we ended you can't be gay because
that whole relationship is wasting your sperm
i e spilling it upon the ground
ah the purpose of sex is to
probe
create right and to do it inside
a house a bedroom so you know
you know what what you're still spreading
this information to people who might not
have heard that and i saw i'm
worried i didn't even the church kind
of just not even acknowledge those things
have ever been said and just move
on you know damien no i never
have known
that and i don't want and i
think you didn't want to know that
i think it's just so stupid that
i can't really deal with it you
know and i feel like my life
was better before i knew that did
you even know about that bible verse
ah yeah i've heard it ah mike
talk to my dream start when he
smelly noisy
wound
he's right
alright let's take a break
and we're back no i am i'm
here yay yeah wow yea yea remember
oh yeah is he still doing a
little john yeah he has a new
um home renovation show not to give
you the reality oh what but it
says little john wants to do what
that's what it's called and it's a
show where he does innovations i love
it i haven't watched i have one
of my ddr but he was an
absolute delight on the company aiming i'm
only going watch it in something against
little john i don't watch these kind
of shows i will only watch it
if you renovated school and put soda
in the drinking fountains yeah that sounds
like it would work really well it's
never been done yeah i can't
believe we've talked about this so long
i know whatever leaves soda fountain i
tell you it's true to when i
was in grade school i think we
had an assignment or something of like
you have to write an essay assassin's
of
sanders years
choose to accept
they had to say that every single
time they gave out homework like i
don't choose you know no thanks um
so i think the i think this
is not me running for office i
think the assignment was okay if you
were running goes from family circus
ah
i think the assignment was right write
a paragraph about what you would promise
to do in the school or something
like that i don't know what but
i wrote maybe it was i will
get to work
video was running for office i don't
know why the rest of the story
makes sense if i was ready for
office but i wrote student office um
so i wrote thanks
i'm trying to be the youngest mayor
be the city comptroller i heard that
that was that that was pronounced controller
that the p som stroller come true
anyway so i wrote a big essay
a big long thing about how when
i'm elected
i'm going to make sure that when
you go to the drinking fountain because
there's two side-by-side right you will think
you're having tits that are just
i'm writing this you're grabbing oh it's
like i'm in the musical chicago i
love your honey but they're so spread
out there's this party that happened there's
this part in chicago where a woman
is talking about her husband that she
killed how he would work on her
like he was working on carburetors and
and so i'm mining twisting these cars
that's stupid anyway
so i wrote let me guess chicago
was written by a man
you can tell when you watch that
play
starring all women practically in one man
that is written by a man that
actually does dan okay tics like carburetors
these nazi it's like carburetors she's complaining
she's complaining that her husband a mechanic
yeah yeah it's like ivory within work
on her body instead of dewey
king foreplay can i just say it
was written by two men and the
music of my man no
everyone wait what that's why i was
putting all this ink on me doesn't
matter you do know but all of
that
yes it's a headphone jack i don't
know that somebody's like i'm gonna get
me hundred a week it is like
a prank that you note it is
i bet it was inside there oh
i thought it was like asking this
one i was like i kaleidoscopes and
then you pull it away and you
got a whole black i mean i
thought it was like hilarious a true
asshole doesn't wash true asshole sets up
a prank
that he will never get to see
yeah he just knows it's out there
breaking away at least the impractical jokers
you know they're watching
those guys so anyway so i wrote
i wrote this essay about
when i'm when i'm school president this
case i'll make sure that when you
go to the drinking fountain if someone
is already there drinking something and you
turn on the other one it doesn't
make the flow yeah while you're drinking
i'm embarrassing you know you came to
dim yeah it's like yeah still happens
at the airport doing
who's your cat to water funds at
the same time at the airport what
lunatics or even dry out okay or
hold on a second guys yeah you
and who is there's the there's the
water bottle filler yeah and the waterfowl
next to it yeah and if you
use one the water pressure on the
other one goes down i'm so sorry
to hear that well this was
very ooh this was the topic of
conversation this is the topic of conversation
when i was called into the principal's
office holy fucking shit and explained to
me by the principal about why that
wasn't possible because the fountains are white
only yes because they had just recently
changed over
they're like we can't fix these now
but they oh thank you kevin he's
given me some wipes good shoving thank
you shea we love you um disinfecting
wipes and he was like ah he
was like well these are about everything
like at the beginning of the pandemic
oh everything here is not a brand
name like i'm looking at the hand
sanitizer that's like
from france and it's like germs be
gone they're just called disinfecting wipes like
all of us back in stores now
you can go get the brand name
show gavin like i don't believe that
jon stewart
i think these are just left over
from the start of the pandemic that's
i'm saying is this is starting i'm
saying that's what i am saying no
but i'm saying oh no no it's
left over from the beginning why does
the airwolf go to the fucking store
and get some of the real shit
that actually works you're well on your
door you're gonna loaf of bread container
milk a stick of butter your lowest
rated show we have demand
ah so anyway he excited to me
i think actually the office ladies would
be thrilled to see a real brand
of hand sanitizer here when you don't
think they like germs because
terms be gone sure by the way
it's not begun like one word it's
two different worlds gone the g is
very large and then it says herbs
be on and then supposed to line
up with the g jones herbs beyond
the g is very large with snoop
dog's follow up song to enough but
achieving gmt one but this has
and it is ethyl alcohol sixty five
percent w slash www i don't think
these are good when they use the
same gyfer two different words it's way
they didn't have enough money to get
to jeez it's so cheap yeah yeah
sure ghibli's called d'oeuvres be gone
huh
just a rapper doe gel this falco
paloma guys mike my hands are relatively
clean at this point so i'm so
looking at your pinky that's what robert
rock
yeah well it took a lot of
wipes so i'm on my third wipe
right now and i didn't even take
a lot of wipes um anyway have
you guys ever been called into the
principal's office is robert yes dead
yeah right yes great i want to
say i'm great thank you i hadn't
called it yeah i mean have i
told my epic story i don't know
i have a story as well it's
not epic should i go for yours
ah i went my brother my older
brother i went to the same grade
school and i guess he had
incurred the ire of our ah principal
sister ah sister close with her name
oh fuck was ah damn i can
see her shield like she was earned
to you saying god damn tuesday from
now i can see her in the
corner right now
she um ah she was a short
woman she's a short king older woman
she's she's manager king um and she
had um shot glasses via these huge
booming and editor lets get that item
mustache and i was going oh shit
not have had this for years it's
like a thick it was like a
thick musty american
i'm like a man like a man's
mustache like like paul's like it was
a thick mustache and i was going
like oh is it weird that i
housing just realising i was looking in
the mirror going oh i think i
should have gotten rid of oh i
think this support my look but i
get shouldn't be it was no which
is gonna cost me work please don't
do that yeah um
and so she was a mean lady
just your miriam that was her name
and um
i was in fourth grade and so
this one already did not like me
right because enforced i had a reputation
because brother she hated the family so
that's so dear yes so brother was
causing a ruckus my older brother and
i don't even know what he did
that she'd been here but here's where
this is why he may not have
done anything yeah um
but i was ah in fourth grade
we were having some sort of gym
period in the classroom where we had
to like move the desks and stuff
because it was raining outside maybe there's
maybe we had a sub we substitute
teacher oh that's what sub means
a bit of a submarine when an
unsold sandwich that was teaching us and
um i was wearing a ah ah
clip-on tie my uniform tie oh it
was a uniform oh you just chose
your like i was already in the
pile of tompkins just guts
good article
so i i probably i'll go i
was like a class clown and i'm
sure i did something else that this
teacher was annoyed by whatever a sub
but yeah so good defense yeah you're
not going to be there tomato yeah
exactly sweetie pie
oh you're making this day hell for
this so i i remember that i
took my tie off and after we
moved the desks and i i like
tossed it on my desk and at
some point we were all getting out
of hand and the principal came in
and said like what's going on here
and this sub sub get ah get
word to the principle of like you've
gotta get in here i don't i
don't honestly i don't remember if if
that's what happened right or if we
were all just so fucking nuts
which i think is probably whatever and
so the the principal came in and
and so the sub is like they're
doing this doing that he was throwing
things pointing at me right because i
tell my boss oh yeah oh that's
so stupid and so she made me
the principal made me stand in her
office like the outer room of her
office
as for the rest of the day
stan i just stand there stand in
the yard or office now of the
day yeah keep doing it so it
was standing part of the punishment or
they just did yes sandy was part
of the punishment like i just stand
there and stand a little more easier
but that would be a worse punishment
right i remember having to stand outside
the classroom
right like getting in trouble at having
seen outside the classroom nowadays zu hei
luft after two minutes it would be
like you don't gotta give me a
chair it is funny like the only
thing that you worry about then is
oh my if my parents find out
about this i'll be in trouble right
yeah um but if this is just
a punishment that stays in here where
i stand on between you and me
yeah great yeah
i'm not mad at all
or am i missing out on here
and i know i don't my parents
found out about that and it's like
one of those things right you you're
a kid and you're you're telling your
parent i didn't do anything wrong and
i think the assumption is that you're
like yeah yeah your your kids right
is they're trying to weasel out one
hundred percent of they're lying no matter
what they said yeah yeah
yeah yeah i think everyone knows that
yeah um when i was little here
we go here's the epic story how
do we have time for this it's
an essay i might have told it
before alright well which will stop you
at any point but the principles involved
but i didn't go to the principal's
office but um i was in second
grade and i haven't teacher who
it was a witch and she was
very very mean like the hat and
everything she might as well prescribe took
off on a broom afterwards i wish
i would've i would've assumed i would
have assumed i rode a broom unless
i saw her sitting in her car
smoking cigarettes every day oh no that's
brutal but she was very mean and
my brother had
had her and she was also very
mean to him and did your brother
say like oh no because it was
family lore know he's older owe his
family laura that she was mean and
made him cry because he wrote a
to backwards once and she was shut
off on him and so i was
fine i was really afraid of her
god damn why would and i
it's like snuck eight and i went
into her class which i had her
for math and she was really mean
and math was hard and whatever it
was she just a math teacher would
yeah she's checking grade we did switch
teachers it wasn't we didn't always do
i don't know why but anyway never
did that um oh we switch teachers
every year now every year we would
do reading teacher i had my o
oh i see yeah would know but
it was password that that is i
was thinking about that the other day
it's so crazy that teachers have to
be good at all subjects through elementary
school they gotta be good at reading
the book that's only going to be
good at gemeinde but no i mean
like i was taught fractions be affected
yeah the book yeah well i chef
so my class
yes we had to do an assignment
where i remember the day like it's
clearly teachers man yeah of course it
will it was me i'm getting around
it's teachers have magical powers that's our
bed and i had to get we
ought to come and and go draw
on the base of baseboard of the
wall or like you know some like
marker that she had put a marker
of how
call our pet hotel our parents were
what laying down what and i just
remember being like so confused my dad
is six five so i put the
i put i'm eight at the time
yes i put the marker wait wait
tall i put the marker halfway down
the wall who knows it might have
even been accurate no matter how
far i went because whatever she thought
she saw she thought it was insane
and she made me feel like i
was absolutely so wrong and crazy and
bad gaslighting you yeah and i cried
and i went home and i told
my mom what happened i cried and
that she made me cry and all
this stuff because i'm i'm already knew
that she made my brother cry and
i'm sure countless their children should
i mean he she went and talked
to the principal about it and then
the principal told the teacher how you
can't you know this that's not thinking
and then i was in reading class
upstairs and i got up someone told
me i had to go down to
her room and downstairs in the basement
and talk to her in the middle
until i knew something bad was happening
and i remember dragging
my feet and i saw the janitor
in the hall who is a really
nice guy and i knew the one
that taught you to play chess
no but i didn't know him like
my whole life and to tell you
if i ever would any time i'd
be near the school he remembered me
a huge really nice guy he passed
away like two years ago as well
so um but he ah i saw
him and he kind of was he
was like sweeping some in the hall
and kind of gave me a look
and i was like really i remember
this i just remember it so clearly
because i was so nervous and he
gave me the look
like i like going to going into
the teachers around like i was like
i was kind of like know when
like i remember like walking on the
stairs really slow and then i got
a room and it was it was
also like another world because like the
other class was in there like oh
so this is what hap holmes oh
after hours yeah it was weird and
then she brought me whatever task it's
dark don't you ever tell your mother
either i made you cry what the
fuck you should told tell your mother
that while my mom knows i don't
know i told mom that then but
oh definitely i definitely told her later
that's insanity yes that's the behavior of
a lunatic it's so weird i mean
teachers can either be like the one
of the most positive forces in your
life or they can be
absolute fucking yeah but it's but my
teacher who was my reading teacher who
i was like in the other classes
was the sweetest woman ever she was
so nice and she worked at barnes
noble in the summer and she was
such a nice lady and i always
love to see her there and then
she'd give me a hug she's probably
still doing that this makes sense now
why you don't know any numbers yeah
i know i
just remembered that our ah school janitor
when i was in grade school his
name was george and then we got
a new priest that was in charge
of the priests really
head by new pastor yeah and um
he came with a dog german shepherd
whose name was george so then we
had to start calling the janitor a
different name what he said he called
a dog a different name well the
done with dogs is not going to
learn another guy on board
or
here's my original pick up on it
so he said we could call him
bud oh that's nice yeah he took
to it alright but i'm sure wouldn't
like having my name change because there's
a dog named lauren which by the
way oprah has a dog named lauren
rowe oprah comes around here i'll enjoy
whatever he says by the way we're
letting oprah on three of them if
she wants so one of the few
it's not mary holland who have we
said oprah ah paid changed david yes
yeah because that it might be other
one there was a condition on mary
holland like if she were the last
person on earth know if it was
like the last year not bad but
still doing the podcast for the last
four people on yeah we do because
we love are married to listen to
honestly i think it would be glad
if persona chan or tn she wouldn't
want to be a guest it gives
us a reason to just to listen
right gives us a reason to make
it oh well if we're not podcasting
what are we how's remember bud once
played the harmonica over the loudspeaker oh
how did i i can't remember why
it was like well there was some
days in school
where it would be like you gotta
go to school but we're not gonna
do anything to yeah we're just gonna
fuck around yeah there should be more
days like it's crazy that you have
to go for nine months five days
a week and teachers have to fill
all that time yeah yeah that's so
there's a lot to learn when you're
brand new to earth i was talking
to someone who used to be a
teacher
you might go welcome to earth by
somebody punching him in the face
as someone who used to be a
teacher and i was i was bringing
that up like that's a lot of
pressure to be on for eight hours
of the day
and and do it do it different
thing five days a week yeah for
the entire year on stein he was
like i loved it i was like
a performer i was out there well
somebody chose like green like valuable mantic
know like some teachers are really good
like that that where they keep really
interesting and they're like funnier and just
and i guess once you figure it
out the first year you can refill
yeah exactly realize that as
like the older i got whatever like
oh they just do it again like
i've said this a million times like
it's not hardware i mean it is
hard oh you think teachers should be
paid less i was gonna say what
i meant by that was the punchline
our splitting side intimidated by it's not
intimidate me a ruler said
yeah but you have multiple classes a
day doing the same thing in high
school true try that i'm remembering two
more times i was called into the
principal in high school oh and then
i got a story for ya oh
i remembered why i had to stand
in the hallway that time oh so
i don't i don't remember what it
was but i i was forced to
apologize to my tenth grade history teacher
called zhukov
hey jerk no i don't know i
said something sarcastic or something and and
she told the principal the principal called
my parents my parents were like you're
gonna go in and apologize publicly to
her tomorrow hopefully like in front of
the class or whatever and so i
had to do that which is just
like let me do it privately yeah
yeah and let me not do it
at all
about that i mean are you cool
with the kids hearing the great thing
that i did that develop this moga
miracle so then the other thing was
i used to do i used to
do the trivia question in the announcements
every day of course huh
and if you know this this is
is a lot of senses crazy that
we allow picking up dude did you
pick out what the question was yes
so what it was was when i
was a senior in high school um
by the way i was only there
for three classes in the morning that
i went to the art school afterwards
but somehow because i was interested in
broadcasting they let me do the trick
a question and i forgot what the
prize was but every single class if
someone knew the answer there could only
be one per class they would run
as fast as they could out of
their classroom to get to be the
first person to wear his fun where
we did the announcements and then that
should be what jeopardy is if they
said what
and they were correct they got the
whole class got a prize or whatever
every single day i love that and
they have example stuff and doing it
because people were like running and hurting
them scores and each other i'm pushing
me away and stuff like that love
to see it sounds fun i like
that let's go back to high school
just for that but i guess for
that just to do that in the
morning and you would have to
do it at at seven am right
fine i get up you know early
i like to go back to high
school do all the plays again because
i think much oh yeah i could
kill me i like russia's i'd like
to do the actual classes and then
yeah um oh i was gonna say
so i was called into the principal's
because ouch to retail be right yeah
um because i did the i did
the trivia question of what was the
name of the girl who kicked the
bucket in the recent poltergeist three kick
the bamiyan died i said kick the
bucket oh they were anyway it was
too soon hashtag too soon because she
died
i'd like the week before so i'll
read the real person yeah the real
version yeah but it's already turned to
industry that movie she died oh no
no no she oh like what was
the name of the girl who kicked
the bucket in the recently released poltergeist
oh what a horrible question is preventatives
pretty bad but they were really mad
i said you also public apollo
they were really mad i said kick
the bucket yeah and it was treating
the cavalierly right so i got called
into the principal and they were like
you are going to read an apology
on the announcements tomorrow and i was
like fine i was like okay and
then i wrote the most sarcastic like
flowery apology and delay
livered it very archly and insincerely and
they were very upset that they allowed
me to do that and they they
didn't like look at it beforehand no
they looked ahead and read okay like
oh okay yeah i mean i am
souls
never shoot it says it was something
he was so it was something like
a situation like this should never be
you know so like duh and they
were and they were so mad about
how i delivered it that they kicked
me off the announcements oh is it
worth it skye know i like doing
bill maher
or after nine eleven i said that
you don't want me to be like
bill maher after nine eleven when this
what is your see i was like
did have you watched dc cab
alright so seventh grade seventh grade i
have the teacher sister millennia
also honey i love that name to
beautiful name beautiful um yes that weird
that's the only other time i've heard
that name yeah i'm great millennials two
of the best um also i was
remembering the only time we had these
desks which were um like
usually you have the flat desk and
you put your books like underneath on
the little ah shell for what really
we have the kind of like the
chaplet this is the only time we
had those everybody was like a chair
with ah it was like wow chair
or even the part under the the
flat of the salad bowl like you
slide your yeah we those where you
yeah we had those but this is
the only time i had the desk
that you opened it up
and it was like a bowl that
you put your stella that you like
glue don't put your glue in the
um it's probably a generational thing ah
in the pencil holder you probably didn't
have goo nose i just feel like
i don't know that pencil doing yoga
but you put the special cost a
nickel weekend unfortunately the bright green turquoise
blue clear elmer's that was like very
nineties cool put it in your pencil
holder part then you close your desk
then later you can peel it out
and it's a big gel oh no
that sounds like fun though i was
done sounds so she thought to do
that yeah we should arm right now
so i'm
there's i'm there in seventh grade and
the teacher sister milan she's walking down
the aisle talking about whatever she and
i already had a problem she also
didn't like my brother because my brother
was always hiding a book on his
lap during the hide his boner
i'm i'm literally asked how re o
to read he's reading a book oh
my argument school member everyone i discovered
quote unquote kurt vonnegut when i was
in high school like i thought every
book was so amazing and i was
i remember reading in chemistry like i
had in my last breakfast of champions
i was like this is the best
thing ever i remember ignoring my teacher
it was so amazing it's the best
you sound like a grand faloon to
be rescued cats cradle the book instead
of learning about something else is like
just it's great like that's i think
oh yeah you should get ah you
should get a pass for if you're
like expanding your mind in it yeah
like this is still a book yeah
it's
this is still a boot so she
pre doesn't like me she came here
and to be honest i probably gave
a reason not to to be honest
you don't like yourself oh my god
oh sorry i'm the last person to
do that so um one point she's
going up and down the aisles and
she's ah i who knows what she's
fucking talking
about to make my little friends laugh
i'm mining with a pen staffer in
the guys
guess whatever you say it i love
it sheaf this i did go in
the hole no i went quickly in
the hole
i like jabbed her
and like the world fucking stop she
wheeled around on me i can see
her faces clear as day like she
was like this can't have happened just
now yeah and she looked at me
and she went
get out and i went outside i
just stood outside for the rest of
the day and the day that's the
day and then when this when everyone
else was leaving they all left and
she came out and said come in
here
and she sat
she sat at her desk and i
sat at a desk in front of
her and she said never do that
again and that was it oh she
never said it like i didn't have
to tell she forgive you i mean
i know you don't have none and
again like yeah you yeah out of
your mind yeah
i think maybe it was too hard
for her to even complain to someone
i don't know like this kid pokes
me but he's stuck me in the
ass or the pit i'm a nun
yeah what is going on yeah i
remember one time we had we had
er a funny this isn't eleventh grade
i think we had our funny english
teacher who is really old that we
we really liked and she was funny
yes but she was so old and
she was stern but also thought we
were all funny or whatever and i
remember like we dared my friend to
go make out with pencil sharpener take
off his pants and pencil sharpener is
under
nowhere
we did it
with the pencil services right next to
her dad's yeah we're all just like
laughing so hard and she did like
a triple take
and she's she's like get back there
and she like started laughing i was
like get back there and put your
pants on and we what we all
laughed and she laughed it was a
great book i love when when it's
a great moment yeah absolutely speaking of
a great moment we gotta go
and we're back
you know i hi jack lemmon i
wasn't sleep and john lennon have very
similar names yeah almost to the point
where john lennon should have been in
the odd couple yes paul mccartney and
work out their differences that way and
then the beatles
would be back together and everything would
be cool let's do a three-tier that
was kind of cheesy alfredo can we
go bhuj lee to jitterbug yeah by
special request of laurin we're going to
do jitterbug great so as we all
remember jitterbug is the game where we
sing the beginning of the song
wake me up before you go-go by
wham
and very swift jitterbug
oh we did jitterbug
jitterbug
and then we just fill in with
another word anything fits the syllables anything
that fits the rhythm jitterbug okay who's
started me well we're gonna say jitterbug
three tugs that's yes and then who
goes yeah hugo okay
jitterbug
masonry
strawberry
air supply
mccartney
the count mccartney mccartney
does it is it because the middle
syllable jersey yeah it's gotta be it's
gotta be i think the syllables have
to hit the same jitterbug that's how
i say paul but i say found
their agents just
yeah
we gotta we gotta do it okay
right who's doing it isn't i'll start
okay
jitterbug
jet about
j bag
broadway show
madison
area
aspirin
garbage stripe
astronaut
morocco cool baseball bat
baseball team
juliet
turn around
romeo
but as
ah and we gave you moroccan spanish
morocco
alright i'll start this time
yeah
gender
i never know if i get wow
jitterbug i can never do ready
jitterbug
jitterbug oh
oh okay
scott's fingers i'm laughing i'm my wow
canvas yelp this much my fingers have
all frozen okay don't you mock me
chef and i see him in there
behind the glass she a little klopp's
okay
jitterbug sounds
jayda bag
j bag
run til that
office depot a wanton office you deeper
oh d
depot a fist you both this philosophy
had the chance fifty feet of kill
us if you get the chance
yeah the chess jesus fits you oh
okay no new round scott started zooming
around we have to get to like
ten
jitterbug
plug shader bike
yeah like
disinfect dupes
dirty rag
lightning bug lightning muck lightning crash
oh man wow are the man
are you thinking of portugal the man
of powder all growed up out of
man out or the man because he
got up and leaving
powder was a teenage boy was he
don't know how well to teenage boy
that was because he was younger than
man yeah i'm sorry yeah he was
eighteen years old enough to vote and
buy cigarettes and get in the army
oh my god huh wow that looks
like a great way to wrap it
up that's right yeah that's a fun
one thanks everyone so much obviously call
us
that haha im poo and leave a
message and follow us on twitter i
mean ah i mean ah to the
truth social as it makes twitter tram
at three m usa and write to
us to freedom usa gmail dot com
and if you want to hear the
ulcer do we ever look at that
email i never look kevin looks at
it i guess
if you wanna hear the full archives
of all of our past one hundred
or so shows as well as listen
to ad-free episodes of this show listen
at stitcher premium or at cb world
dot com dat corn dat corn maybe
world debt corn
hey
uh