i'm sending you a secret message
oh i've received it and i dislike
what i read hey secret
oh yeah louder anyway oh yeah yeah
we're doing an ama ooh yeah yeah
ms laureen lampu my name is scotty
lamp kill me this ball lee lamp
yes and this is three
freedom lap kay hazel and i'm here
to say i'm happy to be in
the studio today oh my name is
lorna cowan dubai i am happy to
be in the studio today
king of the co re na ra
no puck huh
i know that he that actor was
allergic to are nearly always not killed
him no way because the woman's going
sober and playing off of that fucking
hell he was allergic to hair in
general buddy option but the option buddy
show any option buddy play option your
fire because you couldn't hang with the
show repeat well well well can i
just say we're back in
airwolf it's i've been here in years
and this is the inevitable comedown episode
the second one we're taping today now
for slum i might have more to
say this time whoa she's hit i
might not that bathroom here yeah well
i went wouldn't pissed in it and
it has that quality that that is
so superior or the better also before
before we start
what'd she said i'm gonna save this
story for but she started with you
know that bathroom here as if as
if we've never been like yeah we're
we're here now there's one there's one
bathroom and there's one toilet and that's
all it is okay but it's it's
it's a more it's what i call
a worst fear bathroom what does that
mean because and i call it that
right now and i just made that
up i coined the term but oh
the now everyone's saying and
everyone's talking about it and they can't
stop but the toilet is so far
from the door yeah if anyone were
to open the door they couldn't slant
yeah you can't tell a quick shutting
there's no keeping your eye on it
to make sure cause you can't tell
if the lock works or not right
it was just yell no and then
it also says no plea in all
red letters please do
not flush a million exclamation points like
to wash the the switch points or
after the word flush and then it
says tampons this that oh no also
i'm not supposed to flush
so you didn't i didn't know a
lot of these i don't know if
you guys noticed a lot to see
that through the door i know i
screamed it and this place is soundproofed
and this is my like yeah is
my bathroom stand up but like a
lot of you guys showed is through
no news probably haven't noticed because you're
not women but in a lot of
bathrooms are having the same bathroom but
they're having lot of fun with
at the women's tampon flushing saturday are
what are they saying sillier like there'll
be a sign that has like a
dog and it says like do not
flush and then it tells like aura
tampons like you know the dog make
sure the tulsa don't challenge it's like
get your attention isn't this got my
attention call is this stuff like that
time of the month will don't flush
it we know
the way you're not supposed to flush
tampons anywhere not just in certain buildings
it's actually very better supposed to keep
them it's just to keep them in
a box for your ever telling the
story about the girl i went to
middle school with and there was a
rumor that she kept her used pads
and a drawer oh tell us about
now is very whoa you already did
i told it was a true i
don't know
no but i know who it was
if you are that girl please get
a hold of us at least three
of us age like i don't stand
to shave your bags and writing that
year had your period dealing family to
know or something you maybe if you're
carrying and throw out later or what
have you wanted just keep them for
research yeah to see what how does
the blood change my luteal phase
and maybe you'll say is remember when
i went through that menstrual phase that
was so weird two years of my
life whenever i did it whatever your
man sees my mentors is red
ah right p like a fun robot
my robot demo buffer
my betsy's is red uterine wall shedding
ah alert alert
exterminate exterminate
ah lauren tells another story from when
you were young okay please let it
evolve tampons i'm not wearing ease on
tonight yeah this one is pretty crazy
yeah
there was a rumour rumour has it
i might tell us before but don't
remember if i had this is this
is a feature on the show it's
rumor has it yeah album rumors by
the mask
mask and this was a rumor that
basically this kid had sex with this
alert can mean essentially we were in
middle school so yeah and what middle
school is is harold six to seven
or sixty you could be anywhere from
twelve to forty eighty three yeah if
if
like the christmas song from one to
ninety two ah anyway so when it
because this is a gross story okay
i'm right i'm right here that when
she replied because it was a remembering
sir
they didn't know what was happening they
put band aids on her vagina and
then the other part of the rumor
was that
wow lots huh
kids are insane what kids are so
fucking it's
that's stuff that the dead film putting
the band oh hey huh it's really
sad that i don't know you forget
that that those things that happen in
school it affected somebody like you know
to be the object of a rumor
why do my god i know stark
okay so i remember when i was
in middle school i was dating this
woman no you weren't and and i
remember she came to my church one
sunday night right yeah then she had
a best friend and we were all
friends right like the three of us
but i was seeing seeing this woman
sure and then one day i got
two new moment it's not because she's
a woman now yeah but it feels
weird to say it was it's but
you were a kid and yeah kid
girlfriend okay so we were thirteen or
fourteen i used to love those books
can grow a friendship girlfriend yeah i'll
just pretend i was the kid girlfriend
i still love the kid detectives well
instead you rode off into the sunset
so her i got to their skin
to mother i got to school one
morning and the girl i was seeing
like just shot me the dirtiest look
and wouldn't talk to me i was
like in the morning in the morning
can you believe this early header sangha
yet to live on this all night
so i was like what's going on
in it
took like all that all day for
her to finally say like you spread
this rumor about me blowing you in
the church parking lot oil yeah yeah
yea hot cima and i was like
i did not do this i don't
know what you're talking about and it
finally like after we follow
do it and then the rule
yeah yeah in the theater
and da da da um and we
finally trace it back to her best
friend
who ah so called who said that
i was who said that i told
her that and then she finally admitted
that she spread it because she was
jealous that that this this woman was
spending so much time with winnie yes
wow look at you're trying to paint
you as a black girl was so
jealous of the other girl
i got to date scott that she's
nice and this is just me bragging
yeah
no but but thirteen year olds why
do you why do you creep why
do you hear people start rumor i
know it's a while to actually come
up with a lie and just say
like somebody did that about that story
that i told and it's just so
insane it's insane i mean it but
it also happens with adults with like
celebrities but i don't feel like it
happens i feel like
pulling it out like your victory years
you know yeah but i feel like
like a social group that's always couched
like i heard this yeah but who's
the person who starts i think a
lot of times rumors that are like
that not that one not the hamster
the ah when i was i think
i had started by the well know
i'm gonna talk and i think that's
how
what happened was that started hello when
i heard the verbal thing is a
sexual fetish game and then someone said
gerbil looks a lot like the word
gear put it in there and then
it was telephone this theory is where
we're both things got in where someone
heard that person say wow gerba looks
a lot like the word gear like
richard gear and then the next
person heard it are like he just
heard announce a gerbil
your book gerbils huh but the next
person heard horrible the previous person say
richard dear in this group journal story
herbal is a terrible story this but
this i'm fascinated by this that somehow
because gear and gerbil share letter the
first three letters that they would both
make it into
altona i'm fascinated by seahorses but zoom
in on one of those puppies i'm
fascinated by hamsters hamsters which einstein sir
why am i doing this it's twice
why you'd live like why i can't
imagine being you i simply can't em
at a time like this it stinks
it's it's more you the critics oh
remember the critics yeah
hey we all remember something that doesn't
usually have it yeah hey wow like
that show yeah i want to rewatch
it i guess it has it's fans
for sure yeah there's there's a cult
following for the critique yeah yeah love
it or leave it's
yeah guest yeah yeah it was jon
lovitz upset his name's not love it's
no i'm saying it was jon lovett
subsists yeah i love it's well john
lovett apostrophe yes i'm saying was john
lovitz with a z upset that i'm
sure he was yeah because sure i
don't know
dude stole his thunder i'm sure he
was going to say i don't think
that he was
you can't say that because i'm sure
letting you know who's man lyle lovett
yeah that's the way the cookie crumbles
what if i love it how to
podcast and then like he talked about
julia roberts marriage first episode and then
he's like oh motor stuff wow love
it has he red eyes somebody doesn't
have to continue
it's like if only julia roberts would
be on this show and say why
she divorced me his podcast is where
he reads old issues of people magazine
from when he was in them with
julia roberts yeah his recap podcast or
not fuck it huh sophomore boy boss
wang is a tough room sometimes you
just say stuff
boy is that true judson going to
three of them sometimes you just take
stuff sometimes you don't vote earlier do
you remember me into it got me
down because sometimes i'll be like my
fam sometimes you don't bonk but that
would cut it out too sometimes you
feel like sometimes you know why would
this crime
when they not say it sometime because
they would show it because that is
an offensive term yeah and say we're
way ahead but most just sucked when
everyone started calling testicles nuts back in
the seventy i was shocked when people
call testicles in ways they waited as
long as they could seventy six rounds
like let's just do it oh wait
they call them that because they're like
walnuts i think so
but there hasn't i think so there
hasn't been a new term for testicles
in a long time voice like guys
i feel like we ran out of
stuff in the eighties or whatever like
let's figure one out there's gotta be
right today i'll just turn to talking
about them no i'm not calling a
little spheres little spheres what about marbles
i think that's
already been done right that's fair mortals
very selling a bag of marbles is
like a really different thing bag of
marbles oh bag a marble my bag
of whatever to marble what are the
big ones that are like yeah what
do you shoot my bag of shooters
let's do that let's call them shooters
let's call them my bag of shooter
confusing because the penis is sort of
the shooter
of that area well okay he's got
oh gun hey paula has got a
point fuck yeah i find is it
too confusing my bag of shooters it's
so bad oh me back shooters i
love it bag she i love you
lie all of it yeah okay i'm
julie robertson the situation
is bad but she famously doesn't love
him anymore what if she does oh
that he's the one that got away
yeah and she's just like you never
call me back
that's why people are broken you never
use like my phone was disconnected one
day this is julie roberts right no
that's wow that's i love oh well
that totally disconnect mahfouz this committee oh
my goodness i was shopping yolo tags
we have to move on from all
of it because why it didn't work
oh lawyer me was great we loved
it other new chick
back to that nature balls i know
that do i think we should go
to something random alright what are you
waiting on rand that paul wants to
talk about oh come on you're the
one who wanted to move on now
you throw it onto favorite gold spring
in front of you right now
probably this one
ah you guys are so gay
i have really bad hygiene oh yeah
right guys it was coffee cup huh
broken coffee after i leave it but
i've never seen that does he name
himself after you've never seen that you've
gotta come on scott machine for special
orders and see if you know yeah
you know the ending so ah if
spoilers for anyone who has not seen
this okay movie with a great grader
that's right yeah great cast oh you're
talking about particular yeah you may know
him from my favorite spicy disease
drum it's called usual suspects no unusual
suspects is pardon me the usual suspects
called huge sus usos yeah this movie's
totally sus and it turns out you
know ah kevin spacey's playing that he's
been a terror gated targeted by ah
who the what's his name oh chazz
palminteri
mcgarry a bronx tale yeah a and
ah and he was giving all these
details blah blah blah about this this
caper that that he and a bunch
of people were involved in and then
they let him go because he's been
talking about this dude keyser sosa who
is behind it all yeah huh andy
this guy's name is normal or something
what normal
it was good
yeah it's close his name is verbal
kim toe right yeah okay horrible sounds
like um what earnest went to jail
for thirty people irl firm hey vern
and so hey kemp turn a verb
so weaver no main verb a verb
tampa
so it turns out after they let
him go chazz palminteri starts looking around
his office and he realizes all the
details and historical names and everything have
come from things that he's just lost
items in the room it's basically a
rip off of the brady bunch yeah
why what happened to match joe george
george glass so it's
yes george i haven't lifted his name
is george glass george glass is about
to come
um issue is that we do you
know i'm old enough that i watched
that show in prime time wow i
remember it was that it was a
big deal i was a little kid
and me and my cousins would gather
together to watch it you oliver
all of your cousin we added a
cousin later because we were losing ratings
yeah the family was not doing well
i remember watching a certain episode of
happy days and i would watch before
that shuts your named i would watch
five ninety eight i would watch happy
days reruns just to watch a thing
yeah absolutely
yes so but i remember but i
remember there was an episode where joni
was going to pose naked for playboy
or something like that some photogs an
episode here mine yeah and i remember
i watched it when she was talking
to me saying snapchat i do this
so i watch it when it came
out and then when the rerun came
on i started watching it and i
remember did i talk about this show
before you block but i can't remember
the entity so my so my dad
walked in oh right before the whole
nude part came on and he was
like isn't this a rerun why are
you watching it again and i was
like i always would watch the reruns
and then suddenly
he got to the posing nude party
goes i see why you're watching this
again you know your creep why why
do people want to humiliate children then
you started a rumor that you were
created yeah and that i blew him
oh yeah it was like it wasn't
the church parking lot that is said
it was in the church second yeah
wrong yes i defy you god
yeah man there were so many weirdos
of that church though no fucking kid
yeah oh boy
yeah alright hey alright sloppy but that's
what happens when bodies start slapping doing
the wild thing thank you okay body
starts slapping yeah anyone ever say uncomfortably
anyone ever say boff or was that
just used yeah oh yeah off as
you bought it i think i heard
people say
golf i only know it from when
they really about the f word on
television and eighties film and they put
him off right away they would bleep
and put into words you know they
would just talk over it
sleep it and then after go ball
did you boff her did you off
did you you say back okay did
you wait with my guys passes when
you say did you i say boff
yeah
think yeah did did you bob her
into offer did you love her you
do her
okay and now when i say oh
my god you totally say buffed oh
my god you totally maf oh my
god you totally oh my god
and when i say what's like to
pay
i like to like yeah what show
is this
malfunctioning robot wants to have feeling what's
it like to love
did you love her
just get stuck
she imagined like if they had to
do it where guy had to press
a button every time you really go
me to do alive yeah fuck you
we're gonna do it alive what's your
job honey i pressed the off button
i have to first of all i
have to guess i'm a bb operator
when it's happening you get a sense
for these
and i was his wife who didn't
know but yeah well thank you for
finally asking
go honey and go to the bar
forty yeah
do you above where do you buff
okay look wow okay
huh
look we gotta take a break
we'll be right back
we're back we're back sail away sail
away sail away local flow or noco
you know i say yeah i can't
go out i know orinoco flow is
in town
yeah
or no coneflower read my article exterminated
my menstrual blood is red i sang
and yet at my at my aunt's
wedding that must have been you just
stayed away yeah true star hey you
have if anyone has any reason why
these guys lily and ya
and grabs his shooters seconds and
shooter sick like michael jackson g o
no i saying ah on your shore
i'm sure you did with ah with
her ways and everyone cried she make
it sound like almost enya or you're
sure you can you can either say
by actual like in your shore and
you're sure yeah oh yeah i think
so like oliver
titles are stuff that people go like
then you know flow is that her
name or is that yeah so entitle
yeah but it was a request it
was by request will of course from
my aunt yeah not from the crowd
not like the fans
well you voted and your account
this ania song was the song on
your shore on your shine yeah i
remember it behind i go i'm it
was something to the effect of like
a boat metaphor of two boats coming
to get i don't know i don't
remember i feel that how you're saying
it all right here i'm gonna find
it thank you
i'm gonna find it in you're gonna
be sorry you ever asked i sang
at a wedding one time i had
to sing this was at the request
of the bride and groom when a
man loves a woman when one man
loves one womb and yeah they were
very christian dhaka ah it went fine
but i had never really paid attention
to
all lyrics of that song before and
it's a grim zone for a wedding
the hennessy was playing before never said
it wasn't you
okay here we go huh la la
la show isn't environmental sounds or something
i don't know whether this is the
videos video starts on the ocean
this is what you say i haven't
heard this i've not heard the song
since i signed this how you sounded
is that her or is it the
covers that's her scott on your show
it's humorous that you saying this yeah
i know discuss very sensitive i sang
it in this actual case i'm saying
you're going oh hey
yeah so you grab your shooter said
tuesday
good sick it's taking off i think
that's good i don't want to be
like
oh better grab my shooters you go
auntie too much
yeah there's do you mind if i
grab my shooters something that they have
to do there's something i have to
do i very much want to perform
the song for yeah oh wait
yeah
why is it so awful
oh shoot okay so this is the
eighties it was eighty nine yeah and
she was like a yuppie at this
point she's she was a hippie on
her first marriage where we're talking about
yeah no i would never talk about
it anyone she's like bruno keep and
his name out you may know my
aunt got married a tongo bowden yeah
no
can i tell you that i can't
remember how any of those songs go
except bruno know even now when i
forget how it goes oh i only
can remember that one and i don't
know why
my always a hippie i remember being
cited as a hippie my aunt was
a hippie i remember being seven and
she got married on a cliff to
a dude with super long hair oh
thank jesus stuff and i remember like
peering getting to the edge of the
cliff and like looking over it and
everyone he was down there was down
and she's like seeing me in fourteen
years
irs using me um and then she
was a yuppie in the eighties and
she got married to a like a
finance guy i think also with long
hair and no he was famously had
the larry david horseshoe
you know like the gordon gekkos slick
bang had it shaved into his head
he was a famously because he's a
guy who had the diet coke press
to his bald head when he fainted
at the altar
oh my
what a nightmare maybe again full strength
coach dollars already know you think please
no wedding day for the caffeine urgent
smell ah
but then then in the nineties she
was into line dancing she got into
country oh she married some other country
duties their third one yeah there's a
third and then i think maybe she
went on to fight like that like
total shift i love it i love
it when you like you everyone should
change their personality every decade i love
total shift by ania do you remember
she dashed been comedy festival i do
i want a couple
years i went many years as bumped
by dave chappelle huh whoa get in
line um i ah i was there
one year and i don't think it
was my first year their birthday
sierra
like the awesome company festival um i
was i was asked by e entertainment
television why they were doing a lot
of stuff at the festival and they
said we want to like have you
like out on the street doing stuff
with people and blah blah blah and
it was so illustrate
de da de da de it was
so sloppily produced there was no like
plan or anything it literally was just
talk to people whatever we're gonna go
into this bar where they do country
line dance there have been so many
times in my life where i'm suddenly
doing something like that oh why is
it on me to figure out what
this is there's also nothing i hate
more than man on the street no
i don't stop i hate
so uncomfortable especially if you're the man
yeah because it's always dog they always
will now but oh always like now
go up to them and ask them
it's like no there should be a
producer that yeah this up yeah exactly
um so i it was so awkward
and uncomfortable and then i remember i
got back from the festival and i
called the person that had booked me
to do it
and i was like oh yeah um
when do i get paid for this
and i asked just like that oh
no and this person started yelling at
me yelling at you it was like
what we'd never agree to pay but
you said you were na and i
was like oh they were like waiting
for that fight like oh yeah and
it was like so
so not a fight yeah you just
taught like you were getting paid and
yeah you weren't like oh okay you
have to be paid to be on
camera i think so yeah i think
it's the law
but i don't know if they i
don't think they used any of my
stuff because it was just like it
was bad right it was bad but
oh so it was one disaster it
was so bad he was yelling at
you for that rather than the payment
thing the yeller was a woman seattle
was just a one old yeller was
a woman and it wasn't actually new
it was a woman did you say
she or did i just make that
up because i remember
like but you do make things up
a lot i love to do aroma
has it rumour has a rebecca rumor
has it you got more rumors let's
see look at all these rooms rumor
you remember if there were any rumors
that we don't have here care where
there rumors about neighbors that you remember
like oh that house the person who
lives in that house i've told
about the one yes i know the
hell christmas card oh the late well
the lady who came by your house
right that's the same person yeah although
my mom did tell me i told
that story wrong yeah oh true listen
to it and she was like no
no that's not what happened um but
going to mess it up again if
i don't revisit that again yeah she
actually said god bless you um so
you were
way off no yeah i don't remember
i told something wrong about that but
it's better the way you told you
i love it yeah fuck the truth
i thought it was fantastic and fascinating
yeah the story that i constructed i
thought was very interesting and i thought
it was quite true
um i remember once i was working
outside my house and the garage was
open and we had a big ladder
and i was like doing something on
the ladder and the neighbor came over
and said hey does your dad want
to sell that ladder and climbing out
of the witches and i was like
i don't know only the witches the
old one
i'm no no ref no let's like
this like it's like when the girl
the chin in this which coach you
want to put the kitty like it's
kind of like trying to get you
to come back here to say your
last one to see my snake and
then the kids like ooh but it's
like why were they talking to you
when you're on the ladder it just
feels very yeah what if you are
in the letter and somebody said hey
have you ever fallen off a ladder
while you're about to ever hold a
lap lander yeah exactly yeah kick kick
so i yeah i yeah ah fifth
day's up
so i went to so i went
to my dad share a bug which
i love but i can't wait to
read it by the way it was
when she turned fifty molly shannon oh
yes it was great i used to
i waited on her wants attention oh
she's the sweetest after she was on
us allergies did she say anything to
you about wanting to be a girlfriend
ah yeah i'm assuming that's where the
story is leading we do
she's um so i so i went
to my dad i said because i
said i would i said all asked
my dad i went to my dad
and said hey here's good as your
word yeah of course today the neighbor
wants to buy the ladder and my
dad was like yeah well anything's for
sale for the right price you know
you kind of set something like that
and i just kind of took that
at face value even
a woman's maiden head smells like you
can get a ladder yeah store yeah
well this is before home depot was
where they're definitely for sale you don't
have to ask yeah well how'd you
daggett one oh good question i don't
know i think he made it out
of steel he didn't see what somebody
else's driveway like
there's wild ladder america waves around yeah
as needed so do you think they
would bring us together as a nation
if they will all have one ladder
and we had to share it if
there was one home ladder yes like
professional people i need to do like
a week and a half i think
we need one per neighborhood i think
one in the yeah he is naib
yeah i agree yeah it's also a
waste to have so meh
the ladders with the environment the landfills
are full of ladders yeah the way
people get some easter but then they
don't want to keep ours so that's
how you get our land choking on
ladders sea turtles are climbing up and
gagging
oh the little fish climb up the
ladder then they're in the air yeah
yeah and the king back down so
nice like stamping so i went back
out i started working in the attic
he couldn't get up seriously in our
imaginary story that we told us episode
of it anyways
and then the neighbor came by and
goes hey did you ask your dad
about the ladder and i said yeah
he said ah that anything's for sale
for the right price and he was
okay well i mean what's the right
price how much does he want and
then my dad heard me talking to
him and he came out and my
neighbor was like so i hear you're
interested in selling the ladder for the
right price and my dad had to
be like oh aha
i just have that as a joke
huh
idiot such a wheeler dealer yeah he's
like no i don't want to sell
this ladder this is my important ladder
it's our families letters family ladder you
dare to come into my house where
my children sleep my stake our lives
on that ladder
as you've seen did you have an
attic growing up though i had an
attic and i used to climb up
that ladder and spend the whole day
reading books up there we did not
have an addict but i was big
on climbing on the out on the
roof of oh yes which when i
think about now is very dangerous very
dangerous my brother and i used to
do that and jump off the roof
onto our onto our ah backyard grass
oh ours are
roof was too high to jump from
all those ours but high enough to
fall from and die yeah oh no
we had to work up there a
lot but i used there was one
so you could in the back room
back bedroom of the house you could
climb out onto this sort of flat
part home but then when i would
i would climb up then onto the
slow
nope the slanted part of the route
huh
which was ah you know shingled so
the shingles you could give you like
a little bit of purchase yeah you
know little bit attraction a little bit
attraction um but it was when i
think about now like i should not
have been doing that no yeah yeah
why would you go out there just
to look at the stars yeah see
how they shine for you it just
felt cool i would make wishes of
course of course yeah
yeah on shooting ones or just all
of them all like everyone just to
care for the ibhs friendly odds you
remember where she made his kid on
a star didn't come true handle i
hope a pretty lady falls in love
with me i'm sure i made that
wish for sure true i hope an
attractive woman will fall in love with
me as eight years old ah in
thirty
eighty five years or now i'll take
it like in blank check when the
woman kisses the little kid um ooh
what yeah what blank checks like jack
podcast the film blanks yeah somebody gets
caught her on the stairs a little
there's a little boy and what's blank
check against that's melanie griffith one no
this is it's like a disney movie
and this kid gets um he gets
a blank check because he gets hit
by a guy who got awake and
then the guy gives a big check
just in time to stop he doesn't
realize
he's gonna go and then the kid
was like fill this up for whatever
thing yeah for whatever bike is worth
whatever you fucking by his work types
in the computer and makes it was
cheque worth dont line whoa that he
buys everything in the world whoa dang
just actually not a bad idea and
there's gonna be coming after him and
the reason it's like tough situate people
like who want the million dollars for
themself
elves are people that the original guy
sent after care i don't care or
or just like other bands there's support
there's fans of the movie he details
i'm forgetting and then at the end
there's like a bad lady oh no
but she's like tough and they go
on a date and then like she's
tough about and they think that it's
like he thinks it's like a thing
and then at the end she like
kisses him on the lip
lips and he's a whoa i tend
into and he's like it's awesome like
it's a good moment and i'm like
this is a sick sick very sick
individual woman who had to do that
poor thing i know we've talked about
it before all for money but they
shouldn't make like a sql too big
with elizabeth
perkins n tom hanks yeah completely agree
with it where they make they did
make that one um with um what's
that little girl's name he did it
with them hold on it's called what's
the movie called anybody you know i'm
talking about
little little no no no what i'm
steward little i'm saying same characters the
reverse situation in that one and the
woman becomes young yes i yeah yes
what i want is them playing their
same characters and then they meet again
oh i love that right yeah and
then but but the aging will be
off he would be younger than her
but he would be younger than her
he's has to be twenty years younger
than her twenty years yeah because he's
he's thirteen he's yeah thirteen then he
becomes thirty three erwin c this is
a problem with your colin hanks then
oh okay great solved
elizabeth perkins from us from barry yeah
comes that she's in barry now yes
i know i'm wiring larry at me
because i will need to break that
i love her i get all my
entertainment news from all dawkins she's a
fantastic actress elusive i love her i
love when she shows up in something
to show yeah right yeah she's great
well i tell you about when my
dad like ah he called me this
is after i started working in hollywood
semi-regularly and he called me he goes
hey can i take you to lunch
and you said anything's ah for sale
right right right price yeah but i
thought it was a serious thing i
was like yeah
my mind first went to oh shit
what what did i do how old
are you probably thirty five i was
like oh what did i do what
am i in trouble for then it
was like oh no is something wrong
so he's like we can meet in
the middle because he was coming from
orange county and i'm up in the
valley i think at the time he's
like we'll meet at that denny's la
like you know where the one one
first starts or whatever so you're thinking
this is really bleak yeah so like
oh no we need to find the
five dollar x less peter nice place
he takes me to lunchtime the whole
time i'm like oh fay la la
stampa di di di midi ou do
yeah my window over my hey yeah
so i'm like what's going on and
he and he just wanted to pitch
me ah ah an idea no no
which was it's about a dad who
has a terrible son
no he's like so you know how
like tv reunions are all kind of
big right now i think there should
be a happy days for union but
you know ron howard he's such a
successful drama director he should direct it
as a drama and i was like
dad i don't know ron hours
and i don't know how to get
this tune yeah i'm sure they've already
thought about these kind of things i
would watch that though i don't know
much about that now little did you
know that i would work with ron
howard a few years later and get
to know him did you pitch him
the idea i never pitched him that
are you fucking kidding me i mean
you know tell him that i should
have told
him because they actually still are doing
those reunions yeah they won't stop although
the boss is gone or more the
boss yo it's the boss tom bosley
dad right yeah yeah
carefully you know your tonight
i did did you think about brian
bosworth
you still with us right bosworth hated
eighty what do you think hey it
guesses laura brian bosworth what about him
is he still with us the boss
is that exactly is he still with
us or not he was a football
i don't know who it is football
but he famously has blond spiky hair
on spy gear i believe he was
in a movie he started a movie
one yes
yes i think with only a title
ice cold i think it was ice
cold wasn't i answer yes we do
alive and he's fifty seven he's alive
he's lie and what was his movie
ice cold that's the answer we really
want stone cold stone null definitely story
stone
phone called the flintstones man i wonder
if they saw the movie stone cold
in the flintstones and they wouldn't have
to change the title i bet they
did
they're like hey were you going to
the new brian rocks worth movie stone
cold no
oh okay let's say midi
beatty i guess we need to take
a break and oh i hit my
elbow oh no that's a good reason
for radar hillary to go to the
nurse yeah gotta go to the airwolf
nurse oh let's call my parents
give me medication alright we'll be right
back
alright we're back everybody okay we're back
we're so bad right now so and
i'm so excited because we're doing the
game that i have three justin twice
a p hasn't gotten back to us
yet is called a p we're waiting
to hear amy e why didn't you
get back to us in between these
episodes we take back to back it
doesn't have a name in fact this
game but it can be why don't
we naming bad shooters if you can
game it you can name it yeah
the game is one person thinks in
their mind when
isn't going to call one person in
there my celebrity and also like two
people know all the other two questions
scott about what the celebrity would be
if they were nothing like what kind
of candy are you what kind of
shoe or yeah and then you have
to guess who it is based on
that those clues yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah so it's called
celebrity style and when we guess you
get it they'll tell you if you're
right or wrong and does that that
takes up more question and then are
we good yeah but doesn't really mean
good because it doesn't really matter like
if you're going like what makes us
whole you owe me you owe me
you just kind of i mean we
should but something yeah okay we're just
getting wanting it's more about the experiences
yeah about
winning yeah yes so who wants to
think of the celebrity first obviously you
do oh right i i usually didn't
use stars in your eyes you said
they're just like us okay let me
think oh you've thought of the perfect
nurse oh my god lauren his smiley
lovely lauren smiles when she thinks of
a celebrity g fr
rounds the entire episode but then when
she thinks of a celebrity she suddenly
smiled like happy play lights came on
in the room i remember one time
laura was smiling and i said who
is it and she went we learn
it
ok she's got it one second oh
certainly one for sure i think gone
to different people in my head cause
i'm just not sure oh huh let's
sleep funding the park george never seen
it oh it's so good you got
ever heard it okay gotta rent the
the pbx the great performances i can
do that yeah
it's on itunes i i can do
a few paul out of anyone should
i will do yeah you please do
oh wait sometime died right yeah no
shame wow okay yeah so you are
only into people who are so i
only like to watch stuff where i
have a chance to tell the creator
what i thought of it okay so
okay mzuzu from it's a wonderful life
just say
a past never say okay okay i'm
ready she's the last person i don't
know i wonder that about wizard of
oz sometimes like is the last person
who ever worked on that film finally
did have we kept track of that
like we kept track of like civil
war we also kept track of like
the munchkins and everything for a while
oh yeah sure yeah okay you gotta
talk like who's the last grip i'm
ready yeah
the last the last grip the lash
grip i'm alright so we these are
not yes or no no you can
you're asking a question of what i
would be if i was something got
in the kind of thing if you
were a rug what kind of rug
would you be i would be um
like a sort of shag rug maybe
with like a palm tree design or
some
this is robin williams would be austin
powers
who played shaggy ah what's the name
more question what's his name from ah
the scooby-doo from the euler it wasn't
no um alright if you were a
by the way i made it it
wasn't me shaggy joke on the comedy
bang bang anniversary episode that blew by
good and i felt betrayed
i haven't listened to it i have
c l z because i feel like
i sort of remember
if you are an automobile what type
of automobile which would be i would
be like a tan up like ah
oldsmobile um yeah olds okay and what
kind of carpet again shag shaggy like
like i sort of pink shag rug
with like palm
a tree design or something yeah maybe
that's shag rug would just something sort
of like that yeah okay if you
were a college sweatshirt what college would
be on it um
it would be possibly i would be
like ah sarah lawrence ah
is it crazy if i just guess
you just guess
florence henderson
no
what the fuck of whom me you
know yeah you're guessing you fucking way
we're both a magnus what my guess
was worse way worse than that gus
matthew lillard is worse than florence henderson
in every conceivable terms of how wrong
you are and also just as a
person i worked with my good girl
she's fantastic
he's no florence henderson you see him
in twin peaks he's amazing no keep
going no if you were if you
weren't and it's
good game if you fucking play it
ask more than you should get worried
alcohol what kind of alcohol would you
be i would be um i'd be
a late night glasses schnapps
this is obviously a drinker glory i
mean she knows her alcohol i don't
even know what that is but i
think it's ah um if you are
a sport what sport would you be
um i don't care about sports i
wouldn't be a sport i might be
i might be lovely
so is the idea that the person
the celebrity is choosing to be these
things yeah okay alright so that's what
i think wow i mean that's how
i okay okay it just wants to
give you the idea of who that
is ok cool for supremacy with the
rules okay go ahead
alright like for example we did around
where it was like i was reese
witherspoon like what kind of sheer i'm
like a high heel what kind of
can't hear you imo rainbow pack a
skittles you know it's like you kind
of give the energy of them yes
i get that but but the sports
thing you could have divided the energy
of the person sports chose not to
sport is competitive ah ah they're all
competitive their sports tv watching or something
and say she wouldn't it's like i
can't gee i say he you said
she did yes that's what i said
that you say no as a jew
mike i my heaven cannot write i'm
ending this
zest this is a disaster he lonely
so i look salvage well okay shut
up no but that's the key part
is that you're not asking any ah
when i did you said no um
that's not true keep going i like
how you hung this up by denying
the category and then you tried to
make it our fault for not asking
question come on
if you were a a it's my
turn asshole
if you were a shoe what you
would do be sensible pump with a
half inch heel
ah aerosols brand or something yeah comfortable
if you were ah ah some sort
of creature in a haunted house maze
what creature would you be great question
i would be um someone who pops
out and pushes you in
tatyana ali no
and oud no but you're in the
right field great field of acting people
okay if you were a crop in
a farmer's field what would you be
a tall stalk of corn oh okay
yeah if you were a a type
of landline telephone what would you be
an eighties foe
phone that's like cream colored with one
of those big rubbery like things on
the back if you were a kitchen
utensil what would you be wow it
was nice yeah how do you like
it yeah two in a row you
think i don't keep checking datings yes
you tend i just let pie and
have to good pie a knife to
cut pie if you are a knife
to cut pie how
sharp would you really sharp the sharpest
knife in the business gwyneth paltrow no
book
let's say you wanna wear a sensible
heel i don't know you'd said a
whole bunch of the other dumb shit
that i thought was her okay if
you were a jade egg
um if you were a spice in
the spice rack what spice would you
be like something really spicy like chili
peppers that's pretty spicy if you if
you were a person who is walking
around universal studios and was approached by
jay leno to appear on his hilarious
segment jaywalking what question would he ask
you
he would ask um the question he
would ask is about something to do
with ronald reagan and is this nancy
reagan
if you were jay leno delivering his
monologue on the night show and he
said here's something what would that something
be it would have to do with
a fist bite if you were
janet reno no luck um if you
were although i was close right she's
told physically okay she's my eighties right
now she's more nineties um if you
were a character in back to the
future who would you be here
somebody's grandma somebody's grandma i don't think
anyone i think called famously in that
movie everyone says by the way my
grandmother's dead yeah i think it's um
everytime they're introduced for lloyd's girlfriend and
the part where he's as old as
he could be married steam version know
i don't know i don't recall that
care i feel like i have another
guess
yeah
are you penny marshall no
are you betting on you're in the
right zone are you penny lover that
lionel richie sang huh so you will
not walk on speed around
you can't just say speed round and
make us go faster what color are
you calling colorways that like erase dark
blue
yeah like ah
um if you were a section in
ikea what section would you be um
ah ah comfortable ah you chair that
matches a couch that's not a section
that's an item but okay i'll tell
each section coach section good good good
good or patio furniture if you were
ssl
liberty who had to be patty bea
arthur
ah okay yes we got it again
do it again yeah because i want
it i want to show you how
fun it can be when it's good
you when you're the person in charge
no i just mean that one was
a bust but we'll try to get
sucked it sucked yeah thank someone and
maybe a little sure and i think
we'll see an apology
who do who do you want to
be the person with the celebrity who
do i want yeah you want paul
okay i'm the person with the celebrity
yeah paul pick a pick a celebrity
and smile when you do okay
do what it helps if we said
if the person was living or dead
yeah to narrow down okay this person
is unfortunately dead oh no now about
to think of the celebrity yeah oh
hey why wipe work backwards like that
green think of no i have it
i smile you have oh gotta go
together yeah yeah i was instructing my
brain to think of them
um ok okay you're both on your
phones yeah not a good start i'm
looking at dead janey texted us janie
sorry kind of cat are you
he has a half years looking at
him it doesn't matter nicer kind of
blue shirt or you i'm gonna say
like a ah i love you guys
are throwing me
i'm kinda ripped body are you i'm
gonna sue
ah okay
a like a like a knit wool
hat okay okay what kind of dinosaur
would you be
yeah um i'm gonna say like the
ah the the the one that just
eats leaves from dressing park will kind
of house are you
i'm like a cabin like a nice
sturdy cabin okay what ah a nick
offerman no okay what um sport in
the olympics would you be shh
it wasn't the person's elaborate proposal person's
death oh right oh you fucked up
okay well yeah didn't the government know
it's been saying i shouldn't have guessed
this is where we find out or
breaking entertainment news what was it without
auto loading
yeah kind of olympic sport would you
mean um
i'm a sport guy
no none i wouldn't be any ah
yawning at our own game
i feel like um
like track and field like like yeah
okay running right um if you were
a door what kind of door would
you be how many types of doors
or like you just kind of like
maybe a small mouse door i'd be
i'd be like ah a wooden a
wooden door like on a craftsmen are
some like like a oak
oak door yeah if you were a
boat that would match the cabin if
you were a book in the library
what book would you be
oh heavens maybe um a book of
maps some sort of ah atlas
charles atlas for a nature guide nature
guy
are you guessing nature guy yes let's
be still alive shit what kind of
animal would you be kind of domesticated
animals
dated um i think like ah like
a yellow lab okay you're very classic
man yeah if you were redford
you know life yeah yeah unfortunately if
you were a day that someone went
to the zoo what date on the
calendar would you be oh an actual
date yeah
um i'm gonna say may third interesting
interesting you're fucking with the game i'm
dealing with yeah don't fuck with game
fuck with the player if you were
um if you were an attitude kind
of attitude would you
positive oh are you abraham lincoln
damn it are you are you an
ag chairman sometimes
when you're not dead you're an actor
yeah sometimes i would describe the system
possible i'm sorry to everyone
um are for
when how gosh okay if you were
a if you were a sitcom what
succumb would you be
ah there was one called out of
the blue yeah what was that it
was about an angel living on earth
played by jimmy breslin jim not jimmy
jimmy brogan jimmy bruins first crowd work
okay interesting out of the blue and
angels sitcom oh do i know who
you are yeah okay it would be
terrible if someone
this person was mentioned not long ago
on this very
tom busby tom bosley
brian buzzer neither of them
if you were okay this is going
to crack it yup and yeah i
believe it if you were a member
of the showtime lakers which one would
you be i fortunately have not kept
up with that chain if you had
a name what would it be john
denver oh rocky mountain high
huh
using rocket man on high rocket man
nah hey let's go visit rocket man
on high heat in the church rocket
rocket man we pray that you will
deliver us from moore's it's cold as
hell this game is hard because it
could be anyone in the world maybe
maybe we don't have the group mind
for it because wild horses was zip
zap zap yeah but you also probably
only think
of a very narrow group of oh
yeah we can only think of people
who've been in one direction
no you know what i mean like
you all have fuss oh yeah we're
like similar barrios reese witherspoon yeah yeah
yeah i think my cat famous categories
probably have to be narrowed that's that's
kind of what i was saying at
the beginning was like should we pick
a more ubiquitous person and when to
listen yeah um yeah john number was
not one no fence although if i'd
asked if he was a football team
alright
you could have said the mouse denver
broncos and that would have been so
fuck you would remount and have huh
colorado oh right wow hi rocky man
and we did it again everybody did
you get guest john denver out there
everyone did you guess did you guess
john denver did
just doesn't he wasn't mentioned on this
episode he's mentioned on the previous one
does your rocky mountain huh i still
vote i did not see this episode
know i know you okay just just
to be clear but i wonder if
people were thinking who was mentioned who
was mentioned did you guess john denver
who let us know if you didn't
know in the comments on instagram on
the three-time papers
i'd be lying there's a space for
comments underneath this podcast just put it
right there yeah don't say i guess
john denver just say i guessed it
i guess it will know what you're
talking about yes and we'll find your
comment no matter where it is in
the world we see when you're sleeping
and we know when you're awake that's
right ah booty booty booty booty everywhere
do you moody
nah hey i'm sorry i pushed for
that game
uh