dan
damn
shit
a three-day oh right that was my
memory we did it by memory we
should always did acapella i did it
by men and by madmen yeah
what does met ansel yeah all i
know is that the theme song deodorant
deodorant oh okay i just know die
men and are they still around i
hope so god i hope so i
met and we wanna hear from you
man we want you to sponsor us
i really love diary products have abandoned
us my guy yeah crocs really bailed
dude
dude where did they go your killer
croc croc you're telling me you didn't
see a one thousand percent spike in
your sales after we did your ad
i think everyone was just happy that
it happened and no one was no
one but they were like yay cracks
did i have i feel a sense
of completion but i'm not buying those
shoes yeah i might as well say
i know where you got honey scott
and you're a little bit quieter you
are a little quiet oh dear turn
out makeup buddy remember when i asked
you can hear me
okay yeah we could hear you but
it wasn't as loud as once we
all start talking over each other okay
is this slightly past the freedom test
yeah let's hear it what okay how's
this that's better that's better it's better
yeah i mean i could turn all
the way up then it was peaking
on my on my zoom recorder speak
we
we don't want that do you want
but but i want you to be
able to hear me we can hear
you much better now okay all right
great um anyway say something no yeah
do you have anything to say well
i'll just say really quickly see later
i did get mike ah valentine's present
what did you really
one of the things that got him
was a new pair of crocs wo
because no new para cross this he
have an existing pair of crocs he
does he loves oh okay he goes
to the pool a lot to swim
um not just to look at girls'
bathing suits i'm sure that's a side
effect of but he he has cr
roxy where has he ever come back
home wet yeah actually every time but
only get rid of a whole area
yeah like hey oh yeah the general
radius so dicker around the area of
my decal oh my god this piece
and that's one of the things you
got him yeah
yeah and what's the other thing you
got him
and the other thing i got him
actually is baby foot dinamo baby foot
i beg you that sammy hagar fremantle
no that's his that's it's it's island
in though right maybe what i um
i have heard of baby foot yeah
so i don't know what this thing
basically you do scott is you put
this there's this gel and it comes
in these plastic bags and you put
your feet into the bags and you'd
like tape them up and tape them
close and you put your feet in
them
for like forty five minutes or something
and then when you take them off
it looks like nothing happened but over
the course of two weeks your skin
will peel off on your feet revealing
the baby slayer of your foot so
soft so supple all the bad is
gone okay this you have a foot
fetish this sounds nice it was for
dramatic gift
way how do you see your skin
peeling off yeah peel it off you
shouldn't grab it yourself they say don't
heal yourself because even though you'll really
want to paul you really want to
because you they say that yeah i
really want to it's gonna it says
like in like there's there's really powerful
really really really watching you've got you're
dying to your you gotta do it
you just gotta do it
but you can't do it because we
shouldn't do it because it basically kind
of messes up the process a little
bit because you start to appeal email
to the point where it's yeah you
you peel it to the old to
lessen baby to an embryo yeah it's
bad it goes back in time it
becomes a zygote this sounds like jackass
forever and ever well wait wait
wait wait for silly if you can
do it with your feet why can't
you do it everywhere like can't you
do with your face um i'm not
avoiding arms you know the thing is
what about baby feet is that it
says don't use it if you're pregnant
or breast-feeding only things i'm like i
wonder what's going on with baby jumps
and so to me i would just
put it on my feet because it's
like that seems pretty low
no stakes and it works out really
well anything above the ankles though you
wouldn't you wouldn't dare i'm not covered
in calluses anywhere else i would say
what about your ashy elbows all my
my ass is complete as a callous
you want cow is probably true all
our asses are kind of callous asses
are calluses because they're
you know that's gonna be the title
i did better now
or dallas forbid it
you just see it tight this thing
this machine was made of the same
stuff as the plan b pill
that sums sums up in there i
don't know acids are basically like the
nature's chair as are nature's candy
candy you millennials
well that's a very sweet valentine's day
gift no it's not yeah she's gonna
like it he's like oh you want
lean to give him some like chocolates
and arose like uvc he's gonna like
these pres i was struck list i
was shocked that's it arose what are
you getting for your chosen family mean
yeah for valentine's day the rest of
my challenge signs your gal
sometimes your palletized um i'm not getting
anywhere well i sent valentines to my
whole family i sent valentines with with
holly's picture in there yeah yeah i
have this this this mini polaroid printer
called mini instax it's like very small
about the size of a phone and
you can send pictures from your phone
and print them out a little polaroid
aids and it's really cute and so
i and you can write on them
and it was like the size of
a polaroid picture like a thin mini
one right but it's most powerful rancher
it okay so you you converts your
your pictures that are in your phone
into little polaroids yeah although other books
i'm talking it's very cute so i
taped that into the little valentine's and
madison we've talked about
so many companies that could be sponsoring
this right hey no luck every all
of these things come on guy this
is at least what are you guys
getting as marketing jesus christ what are
you getting your honey's for valentine's day
now my gift my nose how romantic
but i think it is um
i'm going out on a limb and
getting nothing me too what kind of
fuckin limb are you guys on get
it together we're going allow is no
ah well we got we have so
many flowers around here we don't need
anymore so you're going away like we're
going away yeah that's cool but coop's
planned at all oh okay you should
get something
dinner or something it's just crazy tomorrow
i'd have to get it together so
quickly um i think you can and
i think you should something that would
be there when you arrive i think
you have done it who would have
well can where you're going is there
like postmates or grocery delivery and will
you need roads
because you are a pager with doc
brown you could order a little cake
all a little cake patty cake baker's
man yeah okay give me some ideas
because like ideally it would be something
the hotel would provide and oh let's
see mexico mask
yeah that's great
hotel children abide well you could you
hear a massage at the hotel i
don't think we have time wait she
she she planned everything out or oh
okay oh yeah occurs when you could
get you could fuck her
um you see if we have time
for that anyway have a spare three
minutes yeah white boy one today and
your birthday that's the title point point
we boise is an acceptable title i
think you could get well you should
get her a card and write her
a nice message
why yeah you're right just got on
with you don't do it fuck
yeah don't get our day in solidarity
on this we've been together too long
it's not meaningless to have gotten higher
of course getting each other stuff for
value like we do every year yes
paul yoni anything real no we don't
really observe it um and i and
listen i've checked with her so many
times like you don't really you don't
care about this right she goes no
and i'm like does she secretly and
she's just lying here's what i think
you should do
i it's not hard okay just twenty
years
because she says she doesn't care it's
it's just gonna be a fun surprise
you just go get her a bouquet
of flowers but then he has to
do it every year we'd hasn't announced
attention to that every year two things
one time she did one time want
to go out for valentine's day and
we went out to dinner to one
of our favorite restaurants and it sucked
because valentine's day going out about times
is the word yes which i tried
to tell her but she didn't seem
to understand it's valentine's week by the
way on freedom so yeah we're okay
i know you know days after valentine's
day but this is a big week
for the podcast yeah um as everyone
knows
find you find your threesome on valentine
so she's men do not believe valentine's
day however these are podcast play valentine
yeah exactly yeah what part of valentine's
day um so after that she was
fully on board with like yeah that
sucked and we can't do that again
right wrong we we need six months
after chris
tmus to wind down from oh yes
we need six months after christmas i
mean we've done this holidays no drilling
and i know look i just think
i just think it's so easy i
told my guy i said i valentines
is coming up like about ten days
ago i was like just you know
it's almost valentine's because he never knows
what the day is or what the
date is going on you know i
said it
just see what's coming up so i
do want something and i it's not
hard it's not fucking hard i want
flowers i like chocolate you go to
the fucking grocery store giving flowers and
chocolates i'd be like that's awesome it's
not hard i'm not doing that orrin
this reminds you hate this why are
you using i will tell you exactly
why i hate it because it i
want what valentine's day is to me
is the memory and it's not it's
not like a vivid memory anymore but
the memory of all the valentine's day
days when i was not with someone
and desperately wanted to be with someone
and it was just like
a reminder of your alone no one
loves you and when i think about
it i think there's so many other
people that are experiencing that even though
i have somebody now it's it's a
shitty holiday because it's there's a lot
of people that are lonely and and
you know want love and they don't
have it right yeah true i just
think it sucks and i i i'm
reminded of all the valid
tynes day where i days where i
broke up with my girlfriend a week
before so i wouldn't have to buy
them something sure of course
can i say all this talk of
flowers reminds me of a jingle that
i used to hear on the radio
and philadelphia many many years ago and
that is i think it's like in
my head anytime i hear the word
flowers yeah did yeah in my hey
j na j anger hoover law howlers
jagger what a movie um and the
hey here's the part that i remember
okay is that the idea was why
you can buy flowers for yourself was
the theme of the jingle oh i
can't remember what florist it was it
was a it was a like there's
a whole untapped market of lonely people
out there exactly later of course ah
used in the analytic eye in ten
gay kente days
yeah i'm gonna let you have sex
with ten other men
and then i'll break up now
i'll lose him at that point you
get ten realign man mondays
they can go for a breakup with
you i'm so ah
in in the movie how to lose
how to lose a guy in ten
days hallelujah hi guys hey guys a
t guy louis guy in ten days
hallelujah
father god we pray hallelujah guys good
gaze um he is an advertising executive
and the campaign that he comes up
with for women to buy diamonds for
themselves is and i quote frost yourself
ah here's the jingle here's the part
of the jingle that i remember
so treat yourself to a bouquet of
flowers pick up some flowers you really
started high
does it i know but like the
end of united a bit any key
and you've felt such a high-water like
today
huh okay
because he wanted to do a right
sky yes that's i have think you
are on the exact pitch he did
it yes i do i have a
good i have a good i have
a good memory for these things okay
i don't know okay i want a
side-by-side comparing
i wish i could find this fucking
jingle yeah was question scott yeah cool
op is planning a whole valentine's excursion
and now how in your mind is
that he sounds like he doesn't probably
guess okay so because sometimes we catch
it sometimes we take turns doing this
stuff like when we were able to
leave the house on our anniversary
irie we yeah it became like too
much of a thing where like we
both had to celebrate an anniversary every
year so i owe so we were
like okay let's switch off planning something
so maybe this is the valentine's year
she plans and then i do something
i can't remember what we did last
year but um but you know i
mean maybe it's the switch or last
year you did not think
she's sick
you do nothing um no that's great
i do i do do flowers occasionally
but will be out of town so
it's like no no that's fair enough
and i know you've given you've gotten
your flowers money time and and paul
i'm just saying thank you this could
just be cute you know to just
show up with a little bouquet i
just think i knew it nothing like
that little bouquet
tails looking like a penguin crying ice
cubes
surrogate it well lauren i think it's
nice that you guys observe it but
you don't care i forge course she
doesn't care but by what i think
it's your personality the lauren i love
holidays yellow holiday love holidays your mind
is constantly whenever you see something like
a product you think you think of
the person in your life that
i would like that and you file
it away i was wondering where this
is going that's yeah and yeah you
know what i mean and i think
that's true my mind is that vitamix
yeah
my mind is more like
always think for yourself ah
oh my god but not everyone you're
you're like yeah you're like my my
sister-in-law she's very much like that too
but not pretend it's just not everyone
thinks that way like i'm just trying
to keep it together man na and
i know i know i know i
look janey and i are hanging by
a thread and so i don't think
this is going to do
do it so yeah everything's in such
peril that pays not gonna turn it
around yeah i think it would actually
hurt more than help yeah because she's
gonna go oh you think i'm fucking
around and say you don't pay attention
i don't like valentine's day i already
told you that and by the way
paul took janey to jackass forever
on that i wish yeah i love
that um it was it was really
fun um janey this was her first
experience with jackass of any sort why
yes she'd never seen any of us
love the show she was not i
would not say she was an enthusiastic
fan i think i don't think it's
i don't think now is the time
i'm to be introduced i think i
was saying oh yeah this one is
a little too a little more extreme
than the others didn't certain aspects of
it so it's like it's like we
we paul and i have seen previous
ones and were like charmed by it
are won over by it and now
for this one to be someone's first
ah it would be yeah it would
be a little weird yeah i think
but she started off kind of laughing
at you know but as it went
on she was laughing less and less
there were things that she just could
not look at like anything with bugs
anything with you know obama it's whatever
kind of went off on them did
you see that peter was upset early
peter pan heat a pan with
he came from neverland and he said
you fucking ass you guys gotta grow
up at some point i'm being chased
by alligator now this yeah you you
call yourselves jackass i mean you got
that right j nano dye your hair
huh
he went back
he his hair like a bell no
he just die well what's weird in
the movie is he dies it's for
some scenes and and is let it
go gray for other scenes so here's
what i had heard last night because
i was curious about that too umm
is that they started filming than they
had stopped for the pandemic and then
during quarantine he grows hair out and
he's like hey i actually like
this i'm going to stop dyeing my
hair and so ah he did yeah
and you know what it looks good
i to see that i want to
see what his hair looks like can
i you shouldn't go see jackass forever
see the first scene with his hair
and then walk out that's all i
want
ah so you so you you're saying
peta has an issue
zun issue that's a real tragedy um
oh i like you but the gray
hair yeah i think it's what i'm
seeing here i mean i i i'm
not he's good looking man of everything
that peta does ah yeah yeah people
who care about animals peta but i
do find the guy that their animal
guy
a very suspect that he's willing to
fuckin try to all these animals to
do these guys it does seem weird
i ah yeah they basically just said
that there were a lot of animals
being um you know tortured even including
spiders they're like they they they provoked
the biter sanders mine until an attack
or something yeah that's fine yeah but
they got mad
you know i mean i'm spiders in
my opinion are two seconds away from
being dead by my hands and if
i you know so it's like i
agree with that even the town tula
sure yeah you're when you're gonna you're
gonna squash him with a paper or
something a paper roll of newspaper meddling
ball oh my god if i thought
rancho la who i wouldn't be happy
you now i've told you i
saw torrential in person one time on
the side of fryman canyon on the
hill whoa that was where i see
valentino
that's crazy
i missed something when clubs um when
our nephew came out from minnesota one
year he
looked up all of the
animals in california like all of the
all of the like lizard alien snakes
and stuff that he wanted to see
while he was out and that's so
cute and he and he looked up
ongoing counseling yeah
and he was like okay i have
this list i have this checklist um
where can we see these and in
my head i'm like i don't fucking
know with a zoo dickhead
so he i was like that's around
my house i was like let's go
in like let's go on a hike
up in the up in the hills
and maybe we'll see some there and
he was like you know and we
went on this hike and he was
actively not enjoying being on the hike
because of course not family yeah that
wasn't enjoyable to him but but then
also mad
mads that i couldn't just point out
oh there's that there's that hey
it's finally like it isn't came out
and he entered wasn't looking at it
and it scampered away yeah you missed
a lizard so he never saw anything
i don't think he ever thought well
i think maybe you saw one thing
at one point and we checked off
the list but he fully used to
be funny to them online
fully expected to come to california and
just like go to different places and
see yeah he thought it's gonna be
a fuckin richard scary books you have
jobs or running cars i mean i
think it's adorable we get it we
get last week it was last year
i think or the year before where
there was a ton of lizards and
i thought i was the only one
ah i thought it was just happening
like i was just noticing them more
yeah but then somebody else i think
on twitter or like somebody that i
know is like have there just been
way more lizards around than usual so
and then they're i don't know but
then they're not around anymore was that
janie on twitter
oh rye someone
meanwhile paul's living in elizabeth someone in
my house that's me looking at a
lizard
but i love him i didn't did
i say i this is the thing
that i do around the house i
don't do this anywhere else but around
the house i do this if i
walk into the yard or something and
i see um any kind of living
creature i will say hello to it
yeah that's q thank you we we
we have the we have the coyotes
are are too cool up by the
way it's taken to chasing the coyotes
and run whores see him as of
course she has she was wearing like
one real issue and i was out
for ah ah ah jaunt yeah and
it would been jotting lately i was
jotting a little
a bit just to kind of get
moving um and there was a coyote
mere feet away from me and i
didn't get startled but you know it
just walked away she's running at them
now she well we we get we've
been getting a lot like i think
i've made are coming after the talks
about this but they they they've been
in our yard a lot so they
like travel noire yeah here it is
i don't mean oh okay they traveled
through our yard from the back and
then go out driving through our yard
yeah and we catch the moscow front
and kissed him on the cameras and
they'll it'll be in the middle of
the afternoon cameras made and we don't
have turned noon we no longer let
our dogs out on cash
you can't cannot you must not so
but then then our neighbor came over
like i guess or the one of
our neighbors is this very elderly woman
so someone on her behalf came over
and and said a lot of the
coyotes are jumping over our fence into
her yard and then just like laying
there all afternoon
no and there were like is there
any way you can raise your fence
up so they can't get over and
so we we measured the fence and
it's like five and a half feet
but the tallest you can have it
is six so we're like we're not
going to spend thousands of dollars to
raise and they can jump over six
we have a six feet foot fence
jumped all the time some
spikes on it or some you know
like we're alright no angles at the
top it's like a movie dangerous but
like like like spikes with other coyotes
hands on them yes exactly really send
a michigan and one george george w
bush mask yeah like game of thrones
there's no one death for you here
what are they afraid of and get
a big plastic version of one of
those like you do an owl
you know it's like you put like
deer piss all over the place you'd
think we did do the deer piss
dad did not did not do anything
right i may not like deer piss
maybe they're scared of dear i thought
saying was weird isn't go and get
it yeah yeah i don't know no
dearer slightly bigger maybe they're scared of
him but we did put like flats
bigger than fucking deal writes
sly sly slow we put the flashing
lights that are that looked like analyze
around the house ooh we have some
whimsy the sense of scene that feels
terrifying that was four days ago we
haven't seen him since so maybe maybe
it's working there you go i want
satellite so that's we actually the lights
to lie lie
yeah hey what what is that from
what is if it's like kanye west
wow sorry yea yea you're forgiven yay
it seems like cool guy um
more i hear about him hey how
about coda nominated for an oscar love
that film
do you get there are we on
a morning radio show
florida entertainment news noted yeah never at
oscar because i thought because we all
like hey no i don't know it
somehow led me behind yay than code
yellow and yea coda short kona twenty
yeah i don't know what got me
down what was it twenty twelve twenty
twenty twelve was it kona coney coney
coney hola is
coffee right is a kind of paul's
famous punchline yes
that ironic bit dad went too far
but yeah cota conversation going nominated for
best picture also the the father in
and nominated for supremacy his video where
he will or he got nominated you
know it is yeah go check it
out what's really shocking he got up
and fell backwards over his chair and
he was filming it oh no it's
funny
that's adorable yeah he was terrific he's
yeah and marlee matlin is great she's
fantastic she's tasker and eighties and i
used to wait yes she did for
children of a lesser god i used
to wait on her tower video backend
yeah yes yes yeah any memories of
what she got i ri
remember she came back with i think
it was little nicky
and she returned and said this movie
was awful wow
wow don't know what to tell you
marley
i i'll make the films that just
rank maybe the voice doesn't translate into
the subtitles shit yeah it was really
funny
i mean if you don't get a
little picky voice it all fall i'm
usually high but you can tell what
he's doing when you see it yeah
i see it's a idea sure i
think he'd get enough of an idea
to say i don't like this
i don't think i've seen that one
that's the scott hasn't seen that's we
talked about it a lot coming up
i believe on last last friday's episode
was that a it was a bomb
that movie yeah it was his first
one where he was like paid a
lot of money and then bombed right
but then he he he has like
his company has like a formula right
where it's like now know yeah
they know that comes with it they
know that if ah where what is
keeping formula for ten by the way
i know come on it's been so
they got to foreign and they stopped
working on it i mean they worked
so hard first four hundred and eight
but they have a formula where it's
like this this is how much money
it's going to cost and this is
how
much money it's going to make and
it works every time oh i'm sure
yeah i mean how much did they
pay you to do the wrong missy
you can't trick me into this one
yeah it's all based on actress if
we guess if we guess when you
say yes oh yeah break you are
a freak scott
you bring very freaky today i'm so
freaky not going to take you home
to mother
what was it what's the one she's
on the what is it the kinda
girl you read about in newsweek magazine
newsweek magazine that's right i won't say
time for sleep in the one in
the super super freak but they say
that that kind of like arena wow
news agency
in newsweek that's my that's my thing
why would a week of news and
sometimes like maybe teach you about hierarchy
she is not how like high class
or newsworthy she is she was she
used me excuse me she is a
super freak and if you think that's
not newsworthy i don't know what to
tell you well maybe he's taught it's
in the in
the sort of context he was talking
about she's a very sexy girl the
kind of einstein so scary i do
i do do that what's so paul
has a late breaking update but is
it that girl is pretty wild now
the girl's a super freak the kind
of girl you read about in the
new wave
magazine makes a long for asics dad
is it makes sense kind of girl
you read about in reader's digest why
don't we all go around and name
our favorite new wave magazines start with
lorin lorin my favorite new wave magazine
is bop good scott
pob
mine's open
yeah class three great new wave magazines
rarely stuff i love that that's like
the the private dancer misunderstanding that i
had where it was deutschmarks or dollars
american express will do nicely thank you
i always heard as ten sam sa
da la
wow he's really good one of the
chief you also accepted american express for
a dime
i carried my penny candy yeah i'll
grind on you give me a dime
what that song's about private dancer i
danced for money i believe had an
understanding with your private dancer where you
couldn't tell she said deutsche marks are
dollars yeah and because she was singing
it and i'm like just say it
but wait is it about someone grinding
on someone or just someone who's like
hey come over and dance around like
ballet style for me yeah that's what
it is that's that's what i choose
to plead oh you're so so wholesome
you were miserable we just are scott
you can't change do you remember paul
when the song erotic city came out
and how prince's erotic city did you
ever know it was played on kiss
fm here and it was shocking to
me because i might know it if
i heard it but i deliriously these
are the lyrics we can fuck until
the
dawn making love till cherry's gone boo
tilled til it's gone yeah hope still
there we try
yeah kinda like dimon kind of keep
going but okay so the plausible deniability
is prince says he's saying we can
funk until the dawn of course it
does not sound like you're saying funk
it just sounds like and by the
way
the very next line is making love
till cherry's gone right do they didn't
cherry one radio which songs on the
radio they bleep funk so no so
so it lasted maybe two full weeks
and by the way i'm i'm fourteen
and horny when i'm hearing you are
i'm just going crazy
yeah it's like but either way i
never told you guys i'm fourteen and
horny
oh yeah i meant that right now
i'm forty nine horny sluts etc to
me i'm fourteen and horny
yeah well we never talked about this
he's fourteen and horny but eleven
they call him the horny fourteen year
old you read about him in newsweek
but now we're relating your view him
law
so they they played it for like
a good two weeks um unedited on
kiss fm top forty radio and they
must have gotten so many complaints but
this was prince at the height of
his powers that they had to play
it because he was a hit so
they then did it like a mix
where they took out that one line
and like
like did did a backwards thing they'd
never believed it or whatever but it
was just it was crazy to me
that they thought they could get away
with it for awhile and they do
think who do you think knocked i
know yeah i hate marks probably only
with someone's mom yeah
my parents when they saw in the
columbia record club that i ordered prince's
purple rain they put a stop to
it
that is yeah they're like no we
are not gonna record in the house
same as saw when i said i've
watched a money python movie at my
friend's house they're like he's a dirty
old man oh dear oh mom and
pop no
i don't think carefully is loyalty you're
not listening to prince
lauren would know yeah lorne did your
parents ever say you couldn't watch her
listen to anytime i mention this once
i bought ah i went to barnes
and noble with my dad and i
bought um what is that book but
alas dallas oh my you podcast dallas
yeah and my my mom saw it
and she said wow hey next you
i was like a nine or something
but it's like it's exactly for you
know but i mean i was too
little to even know about drugs and
nine that's you gotta you gotta tell
em early but i can read that
phony i think i still read it
though because then i was really
the intrigue of course well ours in
the attic that was the one that
i always that everyone dies yes yes
when i was a kid yeah that
was a big deal oh yeah never
read that all my female relatives my
cousins and all that all loved they
well i don't know if they loved
it but they talked about it because
it was it was they were trapped
in an attic because that what it
was
yes it was it was kids who
were among a lady where we were
yeah it was raising these kids and
she trapped them in the attic so
it wasn't like an ambush traps in
the attic no it was not an
frankly we're not hiding they just weren't
allowed out okay and then they they
were and then they they were so
they were growing up they had to
grow up this way and they were
so horny that there's so
together yeah they were the only people
they ever saw i don't know if
we can try to justify what happened
in the book i mean if you're
that horny what if one of them
had been gay okay you are fourteen
and then the other ones like are
you fucking kidding
i'm trapped in the attic with you
sorry doesn't do it for me
um that would be a bad situation
to be trapped in an attic i
believe that would be bad as well
but there's an upside to it yeah
thing is nothing is completely terrible yeah
i mean the pandemic is sort of
a flowers in the attic situation for
a lot of people true and i
had sex with my siblings
we live in the same place you
guys are sick lauren you know you
love it
i was allowed pretty much to read
anything that was what was so strange
was i was able to read stephen
king books i was able to i
rem remember reading the omen when i
was like eight oh they didn't just
they just didn't want you looking at
things or listening to things you could
imagine whatever you want yeah yeah i
don't i don't know what it was
and they read stephen king books
and it was fine weird yeah the
the rural symbol a little blurred from
time to time was blurred lines it
was total word crimes situation but yeah
weird crimes um ah sweet lauren when
you read um go ask alice were
you what was it like for you
were you like oh my god this
true story
i loved i loved anything sort of
crazy like that like i read when
i was in like i was probably
ten when i read gaskets and i
read um so you live forever by
judy blume right what's the what's the
deal now one what happens why don't
you there's talk a lot of talk
about penis yeah oh yeah there's a
lot of talk
my penis is that the one where
it's like we must we must we
must increase our bust no i would
think that's from our either god it's
me margaret okay maybe not but but
ah forever it was like her first
sort of gloat grown up now oh
right right this was very adult and
it was about a girl who has
sex with demand shit and they go
skiing or something i don't really remember
all the details chosen
man and then they go skiing maybe
they only have slurs and then his
penis was named something like henry or
harry or something fucking your knee and
i remember that really well and um
except for the part that i don't
remember anything about it but i just
remember being like wow this is crazy
that i'm reading about this and
ah that was always pretty exciting i
feel like i feel like now with
the internet that kind of thing doesn't
really happen as much anymore that you're
excited about an elicit book right yeah
google anything you want i read mouse
the other day and oh that one
was banned yeah my teacher got very
upset at me
so you in co-op role-playing banned books
yeah she was my teacher i read
mouse in front of her i think
i theorised about a race very critically
and i got in trouble
okay we do your branding take a
break
okay let's let's talk about on the
other side of this okay but let's
ban books yeah
and we're back on your your you
had a list of banned books books
you wanted to ban yeah i got
a lot of stuff to say the
bible no but i matthew mark luke
john this banning books debate it's like
why do we live in the past
it is
is crazy how everything just happens over
and over again it's let's ban future
books is that what you're saying oh
yeah we should ban topics from being
written about that was to have this
problem why don't we make up books
that contain all the things that people
are afraid they contain and then we
say it's bad yeah and let's weed
the three of us write a book
that has everything we don't write
the memories of these committees though we
like shit yes so we can burn
it no wheat we create ah campaign
a psychological campaign where people think this
is a real book assad it's a
psy op it's a psychological operation gay
or be a psychedelic operation you know
and i'm i'm already writing yeah i'm
sorry we've already written it lauren and
i have written this book oh yeah
i'm tripping balls so so we're gonna
we're gonna keep a copy for ourselves
right there so we know what we
will tell burn and ban all the
other copies aren't in ban the ones
that we wrote are good and exude
exactly so an air bnb yeah
i have an air bnb that's all
banned books it's like the blind forbidden
air bnb i went to early kids
can rent it i went to an
air bnb speaking of airbnbs and books
ah thank you for justifying it where
the owner had filled it every every
shelf everywhere
air had taschen books everywhere oh my
wow they're so expensive and egil he
just that's why they had to airbnb
be the house well okay can't pay
for these books i believe on another
show i said whose house it was
but whose christian audio jays house right
who's that um he's a guy who
who ruined ed hardy right yeah
hardy and and his air bnb well
he was one of his houses right
and just for the record everyone knows
tacos taschen books everyone knows that is
it means like those huge books are
books like yeah i know people i
know you know but i'm saying maybe
i'm sorry everybody that whatever notation books
are like art books that are that
are big and very exp
pensive um and so so ah the
the caretaker of the place said oh
yeah christian used to just go to
the taschen store but at the grove
and just get like one of everything
and here's what's so uncreative and stupid
it's very stupid although i'm jealous what
i love about giving the storm what
i love about that store at the
grove is that it's really
early part of the farmers' market so
like yeah still smelled the fish of
the farmers market yeah now you turn
that corner and then there's this like
open-air stall of taschen books it's it's
so incongruous with where it is that's
why a lot of the same weird
but you know i just i don't
i don't like the idea of just
having a collection just being
i'll just take all of those it's
like so like he never opened one
he doesn't care oh well we are
and i don't know earlier books you
know anyway they're picture books yeah yeah
i don't think we ever even opened
one while we were there no and
i actually have a couple of never
open that were given you know it's
kind of like once to my house
is filled with them i've never opened
them i don't know you're talking to
me i live in the tensions i
have
to go look and see what they
are but one is like um i
can't tell you ah oh yeah i
could look at my my picture money's
picture dicks yeah well it's kind of
like actually it was a thing that
like mike's agent would like give him
ah these big books everyone's soil so
that's cool yeah it's a nice gift
but ah
there's just really every job next time
hey how about you stop that's anytime
my agent giving christmas gift it's like
hey how about a job instead yeah
why do you direct this energy for
buying books towards pitching me to people
it's not their job oh is it
all they can do negotiate the deal
exactly this
agents only can negotiate deals and managers
can only give you advice about what
you should be doing yourself badly this
is exactly right
yeah what's up with that what's up
with that ooh ee i love that
sketch so much now i think i've
mentioned this before but they they so
it's called what up with that but
they seeing what what's now what up
with that that should be the whole
premise of an episode i'm just always
wondering why when
did it change and why lena name
kenan thompson is very changed me and
when did they know it is very
financially one team since i was a
wee child i was going think kenan
and kel show and all that so
forth all that i thought kell was
very funny and good burger which i
saw for the first time last summer
for in this ah ce
subsequently five more times yeah because oh
welcome to good burger
wow well good burger home of a
good burger take your order yeah so
good never seen it never seen it
i don't remember the plot at all
it's fun i like it it's no
coda
yeah i remember once on twitter i
wanted to i was asking people to
show me pictures of fun shaped cars
yes i remember that and then a
lot i was a big day for
me when you did that it was
fun because there were a lot of
that i were not i was not
aware of but so many people sent
the goodbye
her car and it's like it's too
much car it's not accurate you need
it to be a basically a strawberry
on wheels yeah you needed to be
like the oscar meyer wiener yeah that's
i mean that's the classic one right
the gold standard yeah how many times
have you seen the wienermobile i've seen
it probably three times always setting yeah
always exciting to travel around doing i've
never seen it in person but i
do know someone who used to work
on the wienermobile wow work on it
friend of mine mechanic she was yeah
they had doing better up to and
she put in the
the oil slick and the smoke the
smoke screen of the machine guns yeah
changing my place yeah no she was
like one of the one of the
big team of people that drove it
and would they would go around to
different yeah what did they do why
or where are they going i still
don't know they're not saying they're not
giving away hotdogs are they
i don't know if they're giving them
away or selling them probably giving them
away but they're like they're just brand
ambassadors they they really it's like it's
like a program that you do out
of out of college i think kindness
of your heart
it's a philanthropic over it as h
h just drive around throwing out dog
out the window i mean i it
is so exciting to see it i
wish i could see it today well
where where does it originate from and
maybe we should go there in the
morning and stick it out and then
follow it around yeah i don't know
why we recorded an episode i'm i'm
i don't
i believe it originates in los angeles
i think it's been somewhere else yo
we're gonna to fly there but yeah
if we want to do this right
i love things like that because it
feels like it has been fly there
decades and decades of joy with just
the same idea yeah yeah it's so
simple and my friend the last time
was in town she went and visited
with somebody else to wanting to see
it and she was she like was
talking to the crew and like said
something that they realized oh she used
to work on this thing because it's
like there's a lot of the same
protocols but ya model name on the
wiener yeah hotdog name yeah you have
to have a hot dog based name
moyo that well but that doesn't have
ah how do you get sick it's
like a pun on your name that
is somehow connected to hotdog either huh
a dog or condo mouse how do
we do this so well you'd be
like pickle fried tompkins or like something
like that yeah scott would be i've
obviously got dog obviously okay the noisy
little lauren would be
this is our lauren button
lauren okay fun kids let's think of
the things that are associated with hotdogs
buns
pass religious relished your unconscious catch up
none of that sounds like lauren lab
ketchup you have a lap cat job
but buckeye navy chicago dog no maybe
yeah think so no i think i'm
sorry sorry i'll check her boyfriend i'm
sorry too
do you mean a texture right now
and ask yeah yeah okay good lord
be called chicago you're this close with
the winner will be oh yeah and
she's a winner birdman mobile whoa you're
on change it just texture can lauren
be chicago dog don't text her no
explanation and see see if she won
well i want to be hotdog bun
kiss i think that's better
can you believe that dick butkus got
away with having his name either if
he wanted it to be
time machine right now
what did you as a child i
was like that's i mean that's just
beyond the pale well we had ah
a politician in evanston named dick durbin
and during was also a term for
blow jobs right i don't know if
that came after knowing his name during
was it i've never i don't think
i've ever heard or yeah i don't
know if that
so maybe maybe people will tell me
that's not a thing and that was
disturbing named it after dick durbin he's
eighty a senator or congressman yeah i
don't know what to do this weekend
i was up to a little dick
durbin
der beek a shot she served him
it's like it's like grab ass don't
know i don't want i don't want
you being here just do it about
your dick durbin yeah i honestly i
legitimately thought you were yelling janie ripen
yeah but you were so good at
acting it and you looked off to
the side like you wanted here you're
like i don't see anyone in here
be quiet on podcasting
there are people like dick turpin and
that makes me feel like dad i
think i'd like to do on as
on a zoom a professional zoom is
if somebody has a dog in the
background that's barking i will turn off
and yell at my imaginary dog
so just oh yes and you hear
the dog and i'll go quiet why
by the way i love the genre
of video of little kids coming in
and disturbing people broadcasting live with the
acquisition zoom so we absolute best it
happened you just have the genre it
should happen all the time it should
to be a reliable thing that we
all celebrate instead of someone getting embarrassed
but i love when they get embarrassed
too but it brings everyone down to
earth you know it's a you you
think you're so special on the news
while it comes your kid talking about
how they just pooped up
i love it so much
is the best the best one is
it the okay the one i'm thinking
of where the where the nanny came
in and got the kid yeah well
like some yeah that was his wife
yeah thank oh sorry paul but like
she was trying to know what happened
she's trying to duck out of the
way and all that kind of stuff
that was that's the gold standard that's
part is that little girl mm
marching in there like the way she
walks in it's like she does like
a little here we go it's so
good i love it and it's in
the fucking baby
i really think it'd have a good
wonderful time that i mean there's so
many levels to that video yeah it's
so good that was the highlight of
quarantine i think but anytime it just
even a different little kid comes in
i still love it yeah log or
anything like that i only like it
when it's one girl and she goes
into different peoples yeah yeah yeah she's
dead right
she's a ghost that's right stand your
ground
she went to the wrong house so
don't you love that story of that
kid who are the lady who texted
the kid about thanksgiving but it was
the wrong number and then he's yeah
oh yeah all the time and i
wish yes me there's still close they
didn't ever like the sixth year in
a row i love it it's the
you know and then her husband died
and the kid was like er he's
not a kid anymore he's a grown
man but he was like
you know posting about that too is
because hey developed a strong connection yeah
yeah it's very nice i wish i
had that kind of connection with anyone
anyone at all isn't that hard that
you don't texted or not just you
know text cool ups you what happens
oh no thanks to we got this
big weekend coming i'll see ya we're
doing an awe
all phones weekend where we are just
on our phones the whole time can
you tell us we are going
yeah because we'll have already been there
yeah you'll be gone yeah ah we're
going to the senate as valley and
doing some wine tasting and horseback riding
yeah that's np like the cover of
a romance novel yes oh my gosh
guys yes long mane flowing grew up
my hair the horse will be shy
shirtless and young mane flowing but the
horse will be wearing pants i hope
so
nice i know i do want to
join us know yeah i know i
got this before he was going to
go i'm trying to put in the
context for the listener sure that we
did we did a wine tasting one
time and anytime you step outside of
los angeles to other parts of california
you are despise
sized and so we were at this
place in one of the i don't
remember if it was napa sensing has
someplace like that and we were at
the little bar of the wine tasting
and with were with other people in
the woman who ran the ah the
vineyard was asking people where they were
from and these people said you know
they said
colorado and she's oh yeah that's so
lovely you know i used to spend
a lot of time there and blah
blah blah and then sit down and
say hi um coors and she asked
us where we were from and we
said los angeles and she went oh
and then did not speak to us
for the rest of the time we
were there what yes people
they hate us they hate us know
that yeah that oh they love it
when we put out things like our
big hollywood blockbusters yeah example or just
right lousy oh they love osmosis jones
but they don't like the the people
who make it wow
oh they love all about steve but
they don't want to know that you're
all about the beating heart yeah
absolutely absolutely anyone really have oh they
love absolutely productions but they don't want
to know the people who are absolutely
human oh my god the ending of
nathan for you was so good yeah
oh my word the ending of nathan
for you how did it end i
don't think we killed him
where where that guy a little girl
interrupted highwire he was like he made
it out you know i'm talking about
yeah i do i don't so kinda
why did you watch it ball i
can't describe it all i was just
watching like instead of hearing us dumb
asses talking about i can't i don't
explain it it's like it's so funny
as
unfold i would just ruin it
i'm okay with you ruining it but
for everyone yeah everyone's seen it who's
going to see it i can't i
don't think we'll get even one more
watch from lauren just casually mentioning it
it will all right i don't want
to be watched a lot if you've
never seen nathan for you and what
lauren said enticed you to watch it
for the vet
the first time we want to hear
from you can i just take what
i shed so the gas station episode
is one of the best oh i
can remember that one that's the coupon
coupon for free gas episode i don't
think i saw that i got sick
so good roofer oh funny man no
don't ruin it i wanna watch it
well you should watch how
two john wilson
because he produces it i oh how
really good i watched the first season
i just have i was able to
say i haven't watched the second season
seasons go one with that naked guy
in the first season was insane you'll
love jackass then our guys forever if
you like dicks go see jackass forever
or watch porn even if you just
like balls oh my god my friend
posted this um
is this tik tok video though like
tick tock trend it's a dick tuck
it's a triple t it's a dick
dock grand it's a tiktok trend i
asked where you were i didn't understand
what was happening so i'm not turning
myself to be some saint but i
didn't understand what was happening when i
watched this video and and he posted
it being like oh this really got
me out and and then i was
like what is happening i can't figure
out why this is funny so what
it is is you hear it's just
clips of people playing this one sound
clip and then they see if the
person next to them turns to look
because of the sound that they're hearing
and it's a little musical sting and
then if the person looks they go
oh good and if
they don't look like who and then
i figured out from someone else commenting
that it's ah the beginning of porn
like a lot of porn videos start
with the same musical sting and so
if the person looks it's like they
think that you're either watching porn or
basically leading the way watch porn like
this what is what the bid or
whatever and so it's like people
i like getting to see seeing if
their brother will like turn and go
oh or something like is it as
recognizable is like the netflix jumped on
i think it is if you watch
porn is it that yeah is it
that don't don't it goes like steal
that from porn
it's like you're hoping nobody would see
me i can't i can't i can't
do it in freshman
is it like law and order don't
don't ah and thinking gung gung air
and let me say good vale and
that's the to me that is the
best part of the loan or theme
yeah that's a good here okay tick
tock audio trend attempts to catch people
who watch pornhub also begin play the
sound
hold on but then if you're doing
it then you also watch porn
so then it goes into de la
liga who we couldn't hear it but
we can learn we couldn't hear any
it's that it's drums
okay i don't know okay okay alright
but my feeling is if someone's playing
a sound next to me i'm gonna
look yeah but yeah any sound i
answer depends of the look on your
face if you if you turn right
for people like you why are you
watching porn then they go you will
ex porn a got you got you
i got you see a man who
just seems confusing
now i watch porn but i don't
masturbate so i think that makes me
kind of a cool guy i want
but i do i just do like
interpretive dances to it
i'm sure you're like the dialogue as
well as the music whatever happens happens
is there do they still do do
they still do dialogue in porn like
how why was that really like you
used to rent a porn and you'd
be like god there's so much story
in this day they still have that
problem i would say
cheers i'll bet here's the ideal porn
what do you think of this hey
likes fuck it's too likely of a
person you see like ah one hot
person in a home doorbell rings yeah
open nice home a nice home another
habit it doesn't have to be nice
another hot person comes into the room
they look at each other they slow
only take off their clothes that yes
so you can build up to it
for sure sure then they once they're
completely nude they look at each other
and nod and it's turned but they
just do it yeah yeah i think
gabe ross said he he on a
podcast but he yeah like john davis
john amos yeah you like
so porn with a story but ah
oh minority oh yeah i mean maybe
it does it for some people do
vacuuming is really nice already report that
he might be in the minority but
the ah what of minority report was
all about catching people before they masturbate
i want i want along with ah
decided under the water just like they
sit up suddenly oh the only power
they have is they know what somebody's
going we have a red ball ah
we got on fairly oh i want
i want porn with alias actors doing
an incredible scene well that's the thing
what
if what if there were a list
actors and then they stepped out and
had body doubles for the porn part
that's fine yeah no okay so you
will see a doctor sorry sir alias
doctors yes dustin hoffman meryl streep
alright let's take a break we'll be
right back
and we're back where so bad time
to play some people were thinking we
weren't back and i was like that's
the wisdom of a fool they will
before we get into the feature i
have an update why oh boy this
story friend has written back oh my
god oh my god my wing mobile
pilot friend
my hotdog friend has read wiener is
my code bank she says great question
oh no i oh here's what i
wrote to yeah what did you write
could lauren be chicago dog or lauren
bunkhouse with no no you know whatever
she immediately knew what i was talking
about a great question chicago dog seems
too far from her true thank you
you ma dogar was why i ruled
that way okay and here's what you
have to know is that there's so
much pun stuff going on with the
wienermobile
she says lauren bun kiss however really
cuts the mustard oh wow oh wow
she told me when i was like
always she remembered um so many um
so many so much of the little
things they had to say
they're all like hotdog buns it was
fucking wild love absolutely love ketchup is
like you're on your period as what
i thought too i don't want to
say it and but how is that
like drawing yeah how does what i
paid through my white jeans i have
lap cat chups
that's what happens ah okay
now it's time to play raichur paul
oh no pickle pickle what else ankle
fried pickle tompkins pickle fried top pickle
and fries tom pickle fried tub pimple
pickle fried temple chump triple triple scott
dorman okay yeah
this is called remaining game is called
thank you for attending my ted talk
thank you for attending my tedtalk who's
sent this adam
the first man wow
that's one player loads up wikipedia and
goes to a random page now we
are doing that via wiki roulette dot
ceo they can refresh a few times
until a page of an appropriate length
comes up they have sixty seconds to
read the article then they must give
a ted talk on the subject while
the other two players are encouraged to
ask questions
can you click blink and something came
up i've included you send us the
link in the it's in the chat
my dear boy linkage in the chat
i'm gonna do it on my phone
ah yeah i got one
okay so you want to crush shit
you can refresh it if you want
a different one or no no i
mean it's it's short so do you
want me to read it ah yeah
okay i'm going okay i'm gonna time
time hold on i'm not looking at
it i'm not looking at it i'm
not looking right just wait wait wait
wait wait wait okay i gotta get
my clock okay make sure there's not
on lap i won't ever okay and
ready set go
you have seconds to read the wikipedia
page on this point i will be
searching for something for myself that seems
to be appropriate length sixty seconds is
kind of a long time but i
guess that's good you gotta really soak
it up so now we who's who's
doing scott is doing it so we'll
talk yeah so i've been just talking
talking talking okay
i'm more oh i haven't interesting one
here that look curious to read about
um have you gotten your you're worried
about him yeah yeah to me just
like it doesn't sit in the stuff
with cool that does not sound good
while all the ways that they fight
all the time in scream and how
she was screaming dakota because surely want
to take it out on scott yeah
yeah that's exactly what he has twenty
seconds left
this is so crazy waiting for him
to do this
you can't go on near me when
i say this is so crazy waiting
for him to do this i'm going
out of my mind this is so
crazy why does time reading okay
guys
thank you for coming to my ted
talk i'm here to talk about what
you say we're welcome to it
you're welcome for coming to my tedtalk
um okay i'm here to talk about
the ohio state university press okay okay
you ohio state okay now it looks
like you're just reading it does i'm
looking right at you guys okay the
ohio state university propose rise
okay yeah ohio's has the ohio state
university press is the university press at
ohio state
ah ah and we all know the
university press is a is a ah
a printing press that um is on
college that published colleges at colleges that
publishes scholarly works and this one has
been around since nineteen fifty seven and
has published over one
a book and a lot more than
that but but i know they've published
at least one i think somewhere in
the twenty thousand range um and um
it's run currently by someone named mr
sanfilippo um and ah it put out
a book recently ah
a few years back called how to
how to do something to a slave
i can't remember what it was how
to make a slave okay what it
was yeah and um and that one
the ah yes you have a question
yes so it's a university press with
a publish collegiate works or they publish
scholarly work certainly i don't know whether
they are published by by teachers who
write them or well i don't know
who writes these things to be quite
honest yes paul yeah oh and the
gentleman who is now running the press
or sanfilippo yes mister simply because um
where when did he become ah the
gentleman that runs the i was seven
years ago or there abouts
it's okay and his first name is
um i wanna say
mr okay alright yeah i did hear
that correctly yeah now there they also
have an offshoot print ah called let
tino latino something okay where they specialize
in latino books and that's very very
popular so it's because it's called le
chinos something because that that it's about
everything yeah like i feel like calling
something latino here's where you go so
right there you go to ohio state
university press and it's offshoot and china
are chinos yeah i ohio you know
is a state run you know you
know that i don't see that part
of the ted talk you're just although
this is part of my talk okay
so how is part of the state
and ohio is a state it is
a state yeah and there are many
cities in ohio cleveland the rest so
you're just filling in in some time
now yeah this isn't about the university
i feel like we've yeah we've strayed
away from the i'm telling you everything
i was able to retain from this
iss
and this is your ted talk sir
um so do you have any more
questions about this that i can yeah
why did you do a ted talk
about this i was forced to at
gunpoint
well they've kidnapped my wife and oh
no who did this um it's ah
did you ever see diehard yeah yeah
actually just did for the first time
it's my favorite christmas movie huh are
you doing are you doing dialogue for
ah for new to some newcomers diehard
and we just watched i heard every
episode
um no they ah it was ted
it was ted did it he needs
more people to do talks yeah fuck
well actually i'm being held at gunpoint
right now and he wants me to
do one so you want to do
i have to kind of study up
so can somebody okay yeah do you
have any more questions so i'm sure
right no no you study up you
study up okay you said i lost
interest i'm sorry time but do you
like books in general
you're happy but i like the idea
of grew on you a bit so
you like this i liked i mean
they did quite honestly they wouldn't have
to ignore excuse me sir i've i
have to time this lady for today
alright yeah are you ready yeah three
two one
so you don't have any more questions
not not about that but i've just
personal questions okay yeah hit me how
how tall am i
a personal to you yeah i try
to be a person story no personal
questions about me personally that's surprising but
i'll roll that um your ah you're
between four feet tall and twenty feet
tall i would say yeah yeah yeah
okay great um when am i going
to die somewhere between
tween thirty seconds from now and one
thousand years
i think that feels right to me
yeah um
could god make a rock so heavy
that he's like why did i do
this yeah of course he's got you
can do anything
anything
yeah anything can he make a plane
take off before it landed oh wait
ty okay i was at an idea
that i should just say oh when
i can't send you my thing because
it won't be a link never mind
i going to send it to you
so that you could look at it
while i talk about it that's okay
we'll just hear what you say okay
so here's what i'm gonna tell you
i closed the window and like yeah
my eyes don't need to know um
the queen tense blah oh thank you
for coming to my ted talk oh
yeah
wow when it's keen to today about
the quintessence block now the quintessence block
was the first storefront in golden colorado
to be added to the national historic
buildings registry the ambiance an entire block
or just one store on it's a
storefront ah it's so it's key
called acquaintance blog and i can't get
into why that is which i will
it's not time for questions yet um
well excuse the fuck out of me
this isn't golden colorado and in ninety
ninety four they added the acquaintance block
to ah the registry of national historic
buildings and this this was the first
one in golden to be
added now in nineteen eleven this man
mr acquaintance which he was pleased to
make your
i like when they're funny
p he ah he opened up this
so this set of three stores that
were a brick and mortar storefront they
had a blonde blonde break in the
back and a sort of red brick
in the front and he sounds like
ah some women i know yeah yeah
i'm with you so what he did
was he made
one ah for his realty business and
then he also had one for his
brother's business when he was a lawyer
and then there was another one as
well and he would get people to
stay at oh wait i remember was
castle rock i would think so something
is a hotel overlooking this area because
he wanted to build this up into
a sort of shopping area and these
people
would take they'd come to take rides
with donkeys burros as listed in like
on donkeys are with and with them
they would ride them around because it
was ah colorado you know mountainous area
they would switch dog roxy yeah and
then he would develop their photos while
they went on a ride so he
had a whole business and they
this was nineteen eleven this was a
long long time ago over a hundred
years ago my dear boys and hey
that is all i really know so
i guess as far as i got
but he did would mean this as
far as you
you're the expert why i got it
being the expert i thought i don't
know if you should have done this
talk look i'm being held a component
and it's long time so some are
kind of going we're it will be
cool we'll be cool the queensland boq
any questions with acquaintance block yeah what
was his first name
quaint this quaint and yeah and easy
really i think it was to rachel
acquaintance
yes yes oh wow marriage by marriage
by marriage and um a castle rock
is that any relation to stephen king
yeah is it scary stephen king was
inspired by it because um just acquaintance
often when he would be developing these
photos that people with their photos they
would find that they were
there was ghosts in them okay and
of course in the arose in the
in the in the border pictures in
the pictures of the photos show um
and rules and i mean the shining
is set in colorado so yeah obviously
there's a connection there um when one
of the other buildings that are legally
the landmark buildings so i wasn't able
when i'm when becoming an expert i
wasn't able to click to a different
page to read about that but i
can tell you right now i'm a
little curious no that's okay no i
want oh no i wanna know i
wanna thank you national register of historic
places know is going to be too
many i can't even
figured this was a nomination process no
i feel you're losing us yeah yeah
i'm i'm bored bored as shit so
why should she not care as stated
by john h sprinkle junior deputy director
of the federal preservation institute mister sprinkle
junior sprinkles junior
um why did you hear my this
um why should we care because this
is such a you know sometimes we
think about big buildings like the you
know eiffel tower and every day meaning
yeah piazza and we like to think
about these little buildings that really matter
when they call it something funny they
called it the spud nut or something
yeah um does it lean too
looking at the page now now am
they called it the spud spud nut
shop but i did remember sputnik the
spud nut shop why would they i
mean who names something the spud nut
shop look it's ninety ninety four things
were coming back nineteen ninety four hour
yeah wows who's holding you at gunpoint
ted ted again jesus she's in your
zoom well why didn't they call ted
to ten again
paul is holding you a company because
kenneth brown all that's holding you at
gunpoint oh my god i have to
i have to do a ted talk
ma'am why were you why are you
even oh well somebody to meet yeah
ah i don't press lap yes sir
are you doing it wow yeah okay
well i'm going to find the clock
and do it um okay so while
he studies go ahead um i'm gonna
ask you questions so why how why
did you get interested in this so
i was always so interested in acquaintance
block because have you ever been there
have you oh and i just knew
i had a dream about it actually
before you even knew it existed yeah
exactly i saw this beautiful brick brick
and mortar shop and it had three
little store friends and i thought this
is special what i'm seeing here special
they need to make this something that
everyone knows about on the list so
when you looked it up how were
you dreamed about this place how were
you able to look it up like
so i don't think i could enter
anything
into google from a dream that would
make a subject come up a great
question sir i drew a picture what
i saw and then i uploaded to
google images and then it looked exactly
like this oh so it came up
yeah praise you so you're that good
of an artist yeah i really really
am going to draw you yeah it's
because he's easy oh my god
god look at why why am i
wearing why am i shirtless and wearing
firemen's because that's what you're wearing right
now we know where you are
i do the jungle baby you came
to a ted talk in fire suspenders
good time
hi welcome to my ted talk thank
you so much i'd like to talk
to you about a song by the
scottish singer songwriter eddi reader it's a
song entitled joke parentheses i'm laughing close
parentheses wow i'm already laughing at just
him talking about it
it's a great joke it it reached
number forty two on the charts it
was the second single off of the
album
that was named something yeah and it
was written by boo hewerdine
you're reading this who i never died
boo hewerdine i any reader probably and
a third person um boo hewerdine released
his own version of the song on
an album called
baptist something
baptist the word baptist was in it
okay and the critical reception
was not the best it was it
was called by the trouser press a
song that was sardonic these are direct
quotes sardonic and that it quote seethes
with disdain and quote is that a
bad review because there are certain songs
that would have both of those qualities
that would get good reviews well it's
a bad review because those are negative
things well okay but like if i
listen to you know a punk song
or a nirvana song or something like
they're they're talking about negative things excuse
me who do you think it was
more who do you think knows more
about the tone of trouser press me
are you me no it's because it's
smart
talk oh how do you spell eddie
by the way e d d i
how you sound teddy t e d
d i want is he holding you
at gunpoint right now yes so is
it teddy d i y ted d
i y because like her idea to
yourself because you do it yourself that's
right
well um what banded eddie reader sing
for before she went solo that's interesting
um in my research there was not
another band named but it's entirely possible
that you're doing with your doing a
whole ted talk about this woman's song
that you don't even know yeah saying
for a different about the
the song the the whatever band she
may or may not have sung for
in the past has no bearing on
her single her solo single that was
the number two track off her album
but don't have a great name the
far more success as the singer of
this band than she did in her
solo career what band you're talking about
fairground attraction fairground attraction did fine i'm
sure i'm
sure they're all very nice people but
we're talking about eddie readers song writer
joke right eddie vetter hey hey sir
should you be up there doing the
ted talk maybe i shot about they
shouldn't because yeah what do you know
about the song joke parentheses i'm laughing
close parentheses other than what i've told
you which is that it went to
number forty two on the billboard chart
it's i can tell you trouser press
gave it a good review saying it
was sardonic it was a poor it
was a terrible this is the critical
reception they're being critical and they are
saying it's sardonic and it's one can
be critical while giving it a good
criticism and a good review
cats do not listen dude do i
call me to word my god do
i come to wear a huge hook
and tell you who value trouser press
that was the band eddie reader was
in before oh it was i'm hugh
k talk you can talk h u
g h k y t okay sir
i want to know what this lady
next to me is looking out on
her phone madam is there something you
share with the right topic
what is that it's a cartoon of
something it's a cartoon it's a pile
of tibbits there's ladies lucky jib while
you're giving a ted talk how does
that make you feel this is enraging
and i'm leaving
kill kill you and your family ted
can shoot p the face i don't
care this is so disrespectful i can't
even imagine why i agreed to do
this
guy ah
i paid attention for a long time
about a subject not interested in
um good stuff i was ah ah
i'll get over it i'll give you
some tibbets guy i'm i'm good thank
you you're good on the deepest front
yeah i'm all i'm all set well
especially with crocs doesn't give us more
crocs they didn't send us a jew
it's all saying no they didn't assure
didn't
maybe they maybe someone was talking to
them and they weren't looking them up
online fast enough to stop laura's red
faced and embarrassed no i'm not paul
is you sure yes for real
why you hear someone say furious furious
as puzzle bad pulse basil legitimate i
had
zimbardo hurt i feel like yes my
feelings my feelings are hurt it's trawl
i'm really sorry i hurt your feelings
i was right yes a little bit
thinking about gibbins i thought i could
get away with it
yes that's a beautiful apology one that
i haven't no choice but to accept
more i'm really sorry like that i
thought i could get away with it
yeah i did what god would have
done that if i thought you'd notice
i wish we had promoted our show
paul in the last episode but i
guess people could still get it right
i mean maybe it won't even happen
oh you're mad he's that mad oh
wow
you want to hear about this song
that you memorized a fact about and
you're mad i didn't listen it wasn't
your personal story no was my personal
story but i'm fuckin b o i
can't believe be able to explain it
i would not happy i did yeah
you're a have you got caught well
i'm deadly i have gone huh
i gotta wait five more minutes i
didn't ah
you could have waited one more minute
i'm sorry please forgive me i forgive
you i look i'm the middle child
of three dim and i understand this
is just the way it goes
it's just the way it goes it's
not the way it goes the old
that just lower your goals is loren
the oldest
a young meaning of of our relationship
i'm i'm the big sister no i'm
the i think you're the big no
i think scott's the baby i'm the
baby because i'm a little rascal yeah
paul you're the you're the worst thing
is we already buy stuff or wives
on valentine's day i'm trying to boss
you around not gonna work
ah sorry i feel really bad i'm
gonna power and so chow it's okay
i just had to give you a
hard time about it yeah and he
didn't and i felt it and i
won't do it you smelled it and
i can't wait ah to do our
show i'm looking forward to so much
and it will be archived so as
you're hearing this you can look it
up online dynasty typewriter dot
com you can find all of our
past improv shows of course to be
very interesting because we're gonna be in
person with no one in the audience
got you know that we're going to
be disengaged yeah there'll be no one
there and weird kind of can't wait
i think i really know what they
say because just because no one wants
to go right yeah we sell tickets
and no one bought on it's mortifying
and then the theater was like we're
giving up
we'll just we'll just live stream shaming
you guys people will watch on their
computers hey and then that was a
lie too
well it sounds fun i'm gonna i'm
gonna one of my life for you
why would you hear flying trip like
for one second i was like is
he really going to say he's gonna
watch the show he never would
you never been alright guys we did
and no and that hurts me and
that hurts paul scott and that will
tell you actually doing something wrong and
just now i have to apologize like
you know i apologize the yacht yeah
it's got not being interested in anything
that we do is not it doesn't
hurt me anymore come on
my heart goes i just my hardest
calzone baby foot i i i top
out having to listen to comedy stuff
at a certain point yeah after you
get the famous people that you suck
up to sure and then no room
for getting no famous people on my
show anymore well then
they're all doing conan instead what do
you get it's i well there you
go you know i'm gonna say like
hey can we get this person on
the show and they go no he's
too busy and then i sees ancona
and the very next day come on
i'm sorry and the guest zone cone
and the very new guys do do
apologizing me i don't think so i
think ah i wanna just say one
more time though i just wish i
hadn't shown you the gibbins because i
feel like that really showed how a
show
i think i feel like the it
was so what an embarrassing thing that
you were looking that's why it was
funny and that they're very early mortifying
the way yeah yeah there really girly
group like it's like hello kitty jim
get some adult jib it's it's it's
it's it's a hot tip action amazon
he had a bag of one hundred
giblets for fifteen dollars hundred
why don't i just throw fifteen dollars
in the trash trash yeah you could
do that why don't i write every
every eighty seconds i've been doing they
should mail those right to a landfill
well look guys just so small they
won't make a difference i i had
fun on this show lauren i'm gonna
deflect your trying to make me culpable
in any of your blame here and
i'm not gonna accept any of that
but um i had fun on the
show with both of you i had
a great time in paul i meant
every
every other time when i was listening
to every word you said it's because
i cared so much and just in
the three try i i waned do
you know when i got week i
hear you and i apologize and i
would never do i will never do
that again they look the siren song
i know that's not true but the
siren song of our phones is very
loud i understand i understand
the room i showed up frozen um
but what i can say is is
if you guys want to subscribe to
this show please do and if you
want to listen to ad-free versions of
every episode you can go to stitcher
premium or you can go to cb
world dot com or just stay right
here yeah whatever you freakin want you
want
here no ads just listen this episode
you are all yours ah alright everybody
we love you three team usa at
gmail dot com if you wanna send
us some three cheers ah three m
usa on twitter and instagram um and
check out what's going on everywhere around
you move closer to you world my
friend take a little bit of time
move closer to you world my friend
and you'll see
hi how are you saying earlier but
but wow still going pick up some
flour
alright we'll see you next time by
ah
uh