right
three
oh yeah it's i told you to
clear out these christmas candy stops we
have asked you a million times southern
comfort jars i'm supposed to chomp into
this and get alcohol charges their actual
southern comfort these did you see jars
because it's like a it's like a
box like obama so i said jars
oh my god i drank half a
jar of wine
oh my heck
okay it's chocolate you have to bite
this now you have to buy this
i don't like
it's ten am you have to bite
the i pre know my gosh why
did you run rapid because once this
no one lost your mind in the
morning saying nobody you don't have to
wrap everything that's in front of you
yeah whatever i'm just curious okay i'm
curious dance cheerful joy alright whatever you
want me to bite into it really
yeah and you want me to report
back as watson said i would like
you to keep talking we talk about
curious george and have a frank discussion
okay first of all it's introduce ourselves
my name's scott my name is also
scott and i'm also lauren
okay then i'm paul okay curious george
actually because i've been reading some of
his texts sure his texts hey thanks
to his touch tasting your secret tex
his sacred texts what's going on in
there just tastes like alcohol well i
just like going on in there i
beat her mouth i bit the neck
off the bottom of the jar rather
than the juice come out no juice
yet hold on ooh
yeah you got to drink the juice
you gotta drink the juice shelby
still haven't seen it guys i actually
do wanna show it thanks for being
here jews shelby steele magnolia yeah we're
right fried green tomatoes and i haven't
seen fried green tomatoes oh you should
do scholars oh no we are oh
i only do one movie on your
show and it's once a year you've
never asked me to do scott isn't
saying he's drinking alcohol out of chocolate
right now just as a maniac he's
out of his shot why are you
doing that i think i mean everything
tastes like but it doesn't have the
bite of it so i think it's
just flavor yeah that's nasty and horrid
well you want me to do it
i'm glad you did i just think
why do these exist who wants to
flavor of alcohol without the fun drunks
drunks just want the flavor well if
they want a fun drunks drunks in
the in the former alc drugs in
the former no i'm sure there are
many sober people who enjoy drones in
the form of alcohol anyways curious george
i one thing i really dislike about
the books and i'm i'm he's too
curious he's just always getting into everything
sobbing
by curious he might see i was
like one thing he's not curious about
me george is very heteronormative he's obsessed
with being straight years cetera are two
genders he's the last page of every
curious george book he goes oh as
always when is the straight pride parade
was that the title of this week's
episode no no absolutely no nah oh
and just for the record i now
pick the titles so yes oh my
god that's right i have so much
power new regime the the the george
books start in a way that bothers
me it will just say
here's george's friend like this is george's
friend of mine when yellow hair like
who's george like they jump and in
a way that they don't set up
ga is a curious monkey he lived
with his best friend the man with
the yellow hat i'm like they'll just
be like the man with yellow hat
said hey george ended up i'm like
who are we where are we what's
going on here's what i say okay
i think is dynamic
storytelling you do you think because you
are saying who's george yeah and you're
curious oh like oh that's with cherries
and the title reflects you not me
so we got so we just understood
now so now i relate to george
yeah because i'm curious you're like what
the fuck is going on with this
book yes i'm like who's the mouth
yellow hat and what's his sexuality i
do
you wonder why you never you never
see him with a partner he seems
gay but you know he's at work
working they lived together i just read
the whole thing rihanna valentine's party at
their house all the neighborhood kids i
for some reason i thought the man
with yellow hat was a zookeeper you
know he's an explorer as anywhere he
found george and he took him back
to america shit which is right oh
i remember this i don't know it's
been fifty years later there's running ticker
text there's like one tax to where
where where you are and helps the
woman bake a cake the woman who
she hit a woman and i fucking
know but there was sexual tension with
the man in the hat and the
woman was like they're gonna finish it
down because she lost george felt uncomfortable
left the room george makes it crazy
master saw some things he shouldn't have
seen and the woman's necklace gets baked
into the cake of course george's eating
the cake when he
shouldn't be finds the necklace so it's
kind of like wow and then the
mailto hat had a bunch of cake
too and he also has a bunch
of k he he eats a bunch
of cake and maybe salvage a bunch
like a jar full they've either got
to thinking like a mason jar that
shows that actually does sound great if
there's any company out there sponsoring
podcast that does mason jars full of
cake in a jar a lot of
people do that where you have to
break the jar
god you smash the jar you get
that special jar you get down on
all fours you start biting until everybody
walk the dinosaur oh my god i
used to love that song why the
dog get down on all farms in
the subject matter about walking dead i
love you because when i was five
i went to disney world and we
went to the parade
aid and the dinosaurs from the show
were in the parade singing and dancing
from the show dinosaurs yeah what what
a great time yeah oh my ghost
two things happened at once now gather
together it wasn't on purpose i thought
oh i think it was an accident
was like a laboratory so that was
their song no they spilled the song
onto a tv
oh and that's funny
well there was hot let's just all
say otherwise was held with the dinosaurs
you you have a history of liking
reptiles you this turtle this teenage mutant
ninja turtle legal angelo i was attracted
to kermit i was attracted to
but they all looked alike right so
it was it was the voice and
the personality that guy attracted to green
you should have evolved well about oscar
the grouch he's so rude and it's
so ha he's real alpha and the
green eminem is the horny one so
i guess i'll make sense yeah remember
how that was a thing yeah i
mean not just recently like i feel
like when we were children yeah remember
during our eminem's taste-test episode we all
got horny when we well we did
yeah we
did some off like fucking
but with the eminem
with imams like what's so good about
it is that each color does something
else you will take when you eat
a bunch of them you get a
little horny but then you get a
lil smart you get a little like
there's other things that happened yeah feat
to blue and you get depressed brown
is smarter
sound is smart there's the title and
they should never have gotten rid of
tan let me yeah it was a
nice option it was because he's like
i don't want to brown i mean
i want a brown one but i
don't get that brown was so dark
yeah it's you know what you mean
like let's let's just lighten it up
what would you ever when there was
the competition to choose the new color
you call it
losing you you would send in a
paint chip call though do you want
pantone door pissed yeah like this is
our domain why do they pick a
color every year who cares if nothing
else
see you're just waiting for it every
yeah all they're doing is giving out
little cards with colors on there like
look the sears color is jade and
it's like we don't do anything with
that information how often do you paint
your house every day yeah same same
every every day the entire exterior iowa
okay i'm dying i've a few things
ok well first of all i would
love to paint the house a different
color but it seems like such a
gigantic undertaking and if you don't do
it i know but it has to
be if you are a real man
yeah that's true if he'd get out
there on your fucking ladder and just
do it you'd fucking do it yeah
you could do it and probably think
that would make me start smoking again
yeah you find you hate moto z
if i see you outside like a
white tank and gonna call it by
it's old name yeah yeah and your
interest pants anyway no i'm wearing it
right now you're wearing like gabardine slacks
no bill
i love that i love that and
then you have a cigarette dress shoes
your your bought your jar of alcohol
is like strewn on the floor next
to other ground i don't have like
a can of bud or something okay
well you do you're holding a bud
can but you already drink what other
way you drink colt for invention idea
cole forty
invention idea just came to this was
but it's something else just three came
to me a thing you put around
your beer cam that can hold your
cigarette it's like a circular thing you
put around your beer can and it
has like a little container or a
little slit for your cigarettes so that
so that you can pay you describing
an ashtray around to beer can not
an ashtray necessarily but something
that will help because you know how
when you're painting and you're holding a
beer yeah if you have a cigarette
you gotta hold it in your mouth
the entire time well yes but that
that is a skill that's the canal
so kinda low what if you wanted
to just put it in this little
thing that's attached to your beer then
you could just go okay but but
so is it it's it's it's horizontal
alongside the beer i don't know what
direction it's in
campbell yeah five degree angle okay when
i smoked i used to love just
holding the cigarette in my mouth it's
cool i thought i thought smoking is
not cool smoking is not always nice
it's if there was a period where
it was i look at it now
and i think it's i can't i'm
i i came out so far on
the other side that i look at
it it looks
so no matter who it is i
think it's crazy little gracie anyway even
if it's like really hot person yeah
wow yeah yes you really believe that
especially yeah like mary-kate or ashley olsen
oh my god
we're actually all four yeah not indoor
and or yeah that's right isn't it
weird okay and dor right right but
then they also have n door it's
like what are we doing yes you
think when is your indoor coming this
this question might start star wars takes
place mainly endorse have you ever noticed
that i only notice
it was a big deal when they
went outside for the first time and
they all like died because they couldn't
breathe
shows joy alex
even in space
there's like oh wow there's no atmosphere
on this planet they are in space
we like everything
did you blow your mind whoa and
there were thought of it like that
have a couple jars cause i'm like
a little ball in the sky can
i talk about yeah everybody walked a
dinosaur and what it makes me think
of every time yes yes first of
all i have not heard that song
i think since it was out so
who wrote that was it was not
um i thought it was done my
cavemen and dinosaurs i honestly like you
i thought it was a formed by
cavemen actual gay man dinosaur that's who
i saw perform it and i felt
like it made sense to you so
performance way cavemen to yeah i got
like a boom boom i forgot about
that part well this is every case
or you make by queen latifah
oh thanks from the ice age dawn
of the dinosaur huh oh wow we
did it recently
anyway i did play a little bit
this is a remix of that song
or remake a remake yes very different
from a remix this isn't really to
write using queen latifah is out there
just remixing songs and zarina
i don't know what she does when
she's officer equalizer movie i'm sorry we
want to hear the chorus
get on the floor everybody wanted that
data so get on the floor and
then assigned out so um good years
ago when i was starting out and
stand up comedy i did a show
in god what was it it was
like ocean the body mary
solyndra you did a show in a
bind by bob this is a classic
do you remember how classes were we
were convinced that was an urban legend
right i still am know is it
real they showed the clip while somewhat
yeah they they got receipts some like
big hours know what you're talking yeah
okay the newlywed game ah
ah supposedly and now paul says it's
always a crazy place to make the
craziest place you've made opium strangest place
to be but in the butt bob
the puppet who said who's in it
a woman said it and she did
not say bob she just said in
the button
that's nice that's honestly that's like how
every family feud answer is
family feud has gotten so filthy and
it's like freeways like it's like families
watching you can't kiss people anymore but
we're gonna make it discussing like there
was one answer that was like where's
like what's the man's fear part of
woman it was like dairy pillows you'd
like
i would set the episode we were
i think so yeah i don't know
if that's that was the question but
yeah gary pill um so i was
doing the show i was the mc
of the show and the headliner was
this dude i won't say okay um
but he he was just like a
hacky club dude but
his big closer was i think this
was his closer
he would get somebody up out of
the audience to do um some sort
of dance too
walk the dinosaur and under what pretense
if you don't mind me asking i
don't remember how he got into it
i'm imagining him saying hey i want
someone from the crowd to come up
and dance to walk the dinosaur yeah
i'm sure it started with like a
guy you know that song walked a
dinosaur and everyone was like yes yeah
we all know we know what i'd
love it it's a queen latifah rebeck
it's a current song that we're enjoying
and so um he would always get
it like an attractive woman out of
the audience to do this with him
and how how are there why are
attractive women going to standup shows i
don't know you should um they should
be out there having sex thing we
just stand up you think women with
each having sex instead of continuing laughing
well here's a here's the thing
one night this was like this like
a three night gig a weekend gig
and one night the the woman that
got out of the crowd ah he
convinced to go back to the hotel
with him i don't think that's uncommon
know it's not so this is the
whole reason he's doing it yeah exactly
yeah and so if it happened one
of the three nights when
you were with him that's usually his
ratio thirty three percent of the time
i would think so yeah he'll find
someone to come back to zotto and
so um i remember he we were
supposed to be sharing a room and
then when he got this woman to
come back with him he said we're
gonna go in this room if my
wife calls ah
tell her whatever you're telling the story
i don't know i haven't heard anything
ever in my life yes i haven't
heard it i want only exclusively news
stories on this meaning you've never told
anyone in the world well i have
a new star oh that's tough and
people fucking when i was staying in
san francisco whoa okay back to where
yeah
paul was up there too so i
was annoyed like oh i have to
like this guy's just assuming a guy
go ahead and lie to my wife
for me well for life i've tried
somebody say something hits me to not
tell somebody i would not pick up
the phone if i was in that
position but as they were going to
the other room
she like took off her top like
in the hallway ready for it she
was ready for it she's probably drunk
out of her mind i hope she
was not hope she was sober and
gave consent yeah me too hope so
too and then the i was in
the other room with one of the
waitresses real
all the stories getting a little bit
higher i was wondering if you brought
anyone will she wanted to hang out
really she just wanted to talk about
this comedian from philly that we both
knew that she thought they had a
thing and then she was discovering that
they did not have a thing to
a boring night for you it sucked
yeah yeah because you did you think
something might be happy
of course i well i didn't i
was like show i was you want
to go back to your place at
like two am yes i was not
reading this properly when it was like
nothing was going to happen like she
was not she really just wanted to
gather intel on this obvious other comedian
that you knew but i was kind
of yeah right i knew from around
the scene right but i he was
like one of those guys who
is like not funny but he was
handsome and so tough he would like
bang all over the ears are burning
yeah
like you want to be and i
wanna do either i want to tell
her yeah i neither have any um
but it was that that kind of
thing where when i look back at
it now of course nothing was gonna
happen but at that age oh yeah
i was keeping hope alive yeah oh
yeah definitely yeah those those are where
all the time those are we're all
the time
or all the time at the in
that age so is the is the
image of her with her shirt off
walking towards the bedroom door just imprinted
in your mind that is imprinted on
my mind him on stage ah doing
the dinosaur thing with a young woman
and like laughing as she messes up
and all that that's imprinted in my
mind what dance would he make them
do
do all i can remember the only
thing i can remember was a a
sort of mimed like a ah think
it's like what happens in the video
yeah right i can't remember the video
at all yeah but making your hand
into dinosaurs of the end of the
year are your forearm i know but
i feel like your your hand is
the jaw of the dinosaur
not the actual but i don't know
maybe this is the eyes and then
you think there's an invisible head around
there's you're insane you're just gonna bone
structure within skeletal just because you've forgot
that dinosaurs actually did have flesh you
know we don't know you don't know
that they had feather lot of times
dead feathers so we we we think
they had the leathery
skip that feather no one goes the
most direct they were just skeletons yes
exactly let's see why are we hypothesized
having layers to them oh they're proud
salad the bones they were that's when
you see skeletons on halloween they're not
former bodies they are just their skeletal
record that way you imagine giving birth
to
i don't know that that's i don't
like you but it learns mine but
it goes away
i don't like this without all the
noise the dial phone noises
no it's yeah yeah yeah hey tucker
spaces exist
okay going to take a break yeah
okay this is the original
we got the video
like a lack of the entire band
just saying boom shaka laka boom sort
of embarrassingly
i was forced to do this for
the song like family photo style yeah
because it's very like child song this
shower child but at the same time
doing a lot of things at this
time were the style was just kind
of extreme in this way that feels
like it's for kids but it's not
my future so bright after shapes
my future sobriety really i have to
worship him as she's right right because
i got my eye poked out there
in a drunk driving
okay okay this niqab came over but
you will that's what happened to sammy
davis junior yes does that he was
he lost his eye in a car
accident because the the kind of car
that he was driving had this sort
of order during the day in the
center of the steering wheel o ano
okay went through his abc's whore that's
why you
ah like a pen in the center
of your steering wheel yeah knife yeah
don't put like a big curtain rod
in there yeah that can hurt fugal
the snack sure google the instrument i'd
be that would just crumble if you're
a beaut you think it wouldn't go
in your eye be fully literate euro
okay fair enough there are
any hard lauren a bugle will obliterate
i already gave in
i just feel like you're not taking
this seriously i really am it's actually
scary how serious oh no oh no
are you kind of identity now and
it's all i want to talk too
far we turned her into a bugle
hard person up you're not a bugle
hard personnel ordeals at the hardest thing
on earth
you know second harvest apologizing oh wow
yeah but you gotta do it because
that people really like that people love
apology my god they love it they're
fucking horny for them they're horny rune
god who's gonna apologize to me today
how many do you receive in a
year would you say apology for yeah
it seems like maybe for one a
season yeah sure seasonal when you get
a really exciting time oh i'm sorry
let's say when you get a very
nice apology out of nowhere that's a
very nice thing it is very nice
yeah that happened to my wife recently
and you apologize to her yeah for
the past twelve years away
it happened to her
um yeah it was it was very
unexpected i was of course filled it
in the whole story but it was
we both remarked it was a really
good appeal i had the same thing
happen to me oh excuse me and
it was unexpected and it was a
very good apology and there was no
but you also did this er yeah
no like i'm still
mad about that none of that yeah
i was like this make me feel
better upside than it allowed me to
apologize yeah and i felt good about
it you know what and it's a
good apology unlike reality recap yeah tom
sandoval oh okay okay so i really
only know him from special forces you
want special forces in office
ten instead of standard banner pumped yeah
i love special forces i actually get
watching that instead of roles well i
mean they're they're very special forces and
it's the world's topic is not watch
yeah so it's kind of like you
think i'm not going to watch the
world's how's this time i guess if
there was a show called forces a
tough test yeah
it would be like a tough test
let's make these forces a little bit
more special let's make the test the
toughest testing so yeah i mean you
know he was on that show and
he was so ah i rowley oh
he's the worst i just i couldn't
his whole deal his home his haw
voice is like dance hit i was
really shy
shocked by his whole look vibe demeanors
the duty of the moustache um i'm
trying to think i you oh really
i thought it was mustaches less maybe
maybe he doesn't have because they show
some clips oh yeah because it was
kind of like um what's that singer
from queen for freddie mercury wasn't it
kind of like a long thick mustache
lohan
i mean it it wasn't he had
a good mustache but it was not
like there's not like a biker oh
it wasn't gay biker he or even
a regular bike it wasn't like al
pacino in cruising oh no he was
he was a guy without it he
was only guy without
well they knew he was undercover most
mustaches of all time so he made
an apology for obviously for anyone who
doesn't know he cheated on his girlfriend
with another cast member yeah the show
in under all of our noses for
years and years yes yes yes yeah
well not for years and years but
what he probably cheated with other people
for years i mean you gotta assume
with randolph's
it's tough you know but it is
it this show we we watched it
last night ah ginny and i and
and it is ah i was really
a heavy episode and it's become like
a more of a psychological study than
like a fun reality show yeah it
was their world like genuinely tense moments
it was very surprising
i mean it makes sense though i
feel like the stuff that went down
at that point was so real
i don't know about the earlier seasons
but here's his earlier seasons just felt
like a reality show you know anything
i was like messi being messi yeah
here's his apology style though it's like
hey i just wanted to check in
with you like that's not an apology
he will when he says i'm sorry
it's always i'm sorry but i'm sorry
but you know it was just a
tough time and this is something that
yeah so what about what about this
because well what about what you did
to me yeah exactly because that's always
gonna everyone around him is always saying
like you just need to just sit
here and take it yeah exactly that's
what everyone gets the exact same advice
just like i'm doing that already anyway
you're trying to do that by doing
toughest test he was like i deserve
this you go on another
ality yeah i get paid i know
my guys spaces in the physical punishment
of the challan more attention i deserve
this they were times when i couldn't
i couldn't believe how weak he was
and i'm not saying i would be
good i'm just like hey lit on
that list up this ball jo jo
siwa did amazingly well there was a
point where i believe tom was having
a really hard time carrying a person
or a big bag or something because
you didn't show joe was and then
gioia was doing it i was like
a big bag and he was a
person i think she was going to
want her back
back it was an empty bag but
it was just big as well the
big bag full of bricks loaf of
bread watch kitchen nightmares never i don't
like nightmares oh i always tears up
to go when it's really no hate
em i'm starving i can i love
to scream so we not even the
fridge coordinator we've two things about gordon
ramsay okay too okay
look
we've been waiting for this it's the
third episode of our new season there's
a new department lord has been talking
forever about two things she's wanted to
say about gorgeous is laura this like
initial it's lawrence two things she wants
to say about gordon ramsay and doe
one i think he's like an amazing
chef and how would you know have
you ever eaten anything he's cooked no
batch noble we've learned from him learned
what that he's an amazing shots to
master things in their night and about
scrambling eggs we started doing it like
when it was really great wow how
what are his techniques to scramble these
e put them in a pan using
no he used a pot he used
to pot he cracked them into a
pot okay how big medium
so tom sandoval could not lift it
yeah and it was full of was
whipping and then he puts in butter
and then he put in chrome fresh
and he also put ooni i mean
i didn't do all this shit what
did you do you just put it
on a pie and it was but
we just ordered them no actually restaurant
i think i think my chrome pressures
start with trying to cook now
i don't wanna get into that but
anyway well this has been a big
thread you've talked about how you know
what you're not hooking well no i
do want to get into and then
i'm very excited about it but i
don't want to um that's a whole
separate topic you don't want to have
a husband who's like a woman
isn't the idea wonderful
could be the shit number to um
number will hold i was you i
gotta get back to it so we
need you know paul knows they turned
out great but the number one is
still looking on it stays on the
show he's so he walks already set
number one he's a great chart of
number one this is my three you
can pay to lambie but i might
have number one the time
al is he's a great she's great
and then here's number record number two
but the thought comes and you wanted
more time for this i just i'm
trying to make i'm fighting for you
has listened i'm reclaiming my time sir
i'm reclaiming my time listeners can't see
my chart so wanted to make it
clear oh okay all right well we
gonna see it either it is
is invisible so number two
he he will come into these restaurants
that are gross they're nightmare he has
the best he has the best phrases
and so we love to say but
our own kitchen
this
it's okay to say
ah
ah try to do something in the
space it's like two scholars
i hear the lord
a little jiggle so well
this place isn't
ah i know here's what i send
me i've had this thought flashed in
my mind that years from now when
your children are grown that a sweet
thing to tell them would be that
you laughed so much oh that's so
nice oh because
it really is true what you like
your partner giggly is true as sweet
and then the third thing about whatever
his name is is it a bonus
thing this is no this was the
main number two but then the thing
i just said became a module it
was the thing that the dust chopping
was really part you were trying to
tie one and two together but there's
no lauren come
three things so your if it was
going to be one thing it was
going to be we think he's a
great chef but he has these great
phrases no it was and he does
this thing okay and the next one
is that at the end of the
episode he read he sort of recaps
like what happened to the camera by
himself outside of the restaurant standing outside
like encase
you didn't watch it he just kind
of like here's what i did here's
what we didn't hear just how you
feel for them and here's like what
like hopefully they have to do to
make this work and then we'll come
back to like here's six months later
we'll see what happens they have to
add he will look around we've deduced
okay
that his cue cards are on the
ground because he's like we're looking over
here and he looks down over here
and he's like he's he looks at
the camera and he's like and then
they had it's you know so many
pots and pans and then they suddenly
he's like adding something else he's like
yeah he's not he's a he's a
downward thinker you know how like when
some people think they think up to
the right or whatever well so
posted about this and we were like
oh my god other people are noticing
this then we watch the master class
he's looking down at that table there's
nothing on it when he's talking he
is a downward downward thinker hold on
wow hold on a sec because he's
looking down and saying stuff as if
it's referencing notes but there's nothing there
i don't mean to sound all tinfoil
hat okay
but maybe before the masterclass he saw
that people were onto him oh he
was like this is this ice i
gotta memorize this shit and remember to
look down yeah so he's looking up
and thinking yeah i gotta remember to
look down and then he looks down
it's just remember look i just feel
like they could help him in the
sky because when he's looking down it
looks
so distracting lots of things is they
say that you can tell if someone's
lying if they're not when they're remembering
something if they're like looking up into
i believe it's the left because then
they're like pretending that's when you see
your imagination is you have to go
up to the left like look in
your imagination it's like when people actually
lie when people are trying to remember
something it was to the right
when people are really trying to remember
something they look up and to one
direction they look to one direction i
always look in one direction and you
know what i still think harry's going
to get back together with i think
he will eventually i mean justin got
back together with n seeing that tray
and think and think and think
was it an apostrophe n semi was
star and sink maybe even it could
be possible i don't know let me
look i want to look at like
when you're thinking or when you're lying
why were the backstreet boys the backstory
look well they were all born in
alleys in dumpsters you know what asked
and answered yeah
did not know that they were all
dumpster baby yeah one of them was
a toilet baby i was gonna say
moved him to a dumpster because yeah
you embarrassed jaycee she's a saint michel
it's a myth he was born in
a sink actually it's a myth
but that's the thing is like all
the backstreet boys they were born in
six
okay i know this is a myth
that people i didn't know i was
pregnant but i looked at the sake
there was a baby it was debunked
debunked but michelle a university of michigan
study found when participants lied they maintained
eye contact seventy percent of the time
i do think that's actually more accurate
because like you're trying to be like
i like i'm being yeah right okay
i'm not blinking or and i have
nothing
be afraid of i'm just looking i'm
looking at you normally yeah with my
eyes wide open that is that's the
other guy when i read the book
homicide um like holen life on the
streets i don't know if it had
a colon in the book but i
believe it's just smaller lettering under homicide
i don't think there was any life
on the street in the book i
think it's just called homicide i could
be wrong but ah
hope you are at like i was
probably wrong about instinct not having an
apostrophe but um actually you know the
wikipedia page for instinct has just the
end in the sink next to each
other like it's oh we're right in
the snow or possibly because i'm working
on a project connected to it so
how likely are you in and sync
now yeah i'm doing all the dancing
just the dancing yeah are you doing
block the
dinosaur dance um yeah we are working
on that but i was supposed to
shoot yeah wow okay um what am
i gonna say no breaking breaking breaking
news the there is an asterisk in
front of the asterisk and why us
one word though i mean yeah astros
an s y n c
yes i was just heading to i
said gaseous anti stamps i see
so in sync is who it's this
case you say do i've been watching
so much old footage i'm doing a
project with lance bass and danielle fishel
oak okay okay we believe you and
so i've been why are you going
to use icons i don't believe that
you believe me and i'm lying
the old footage is so amazing when
you go back and look at all
their wardrobes i just will do you
just stop talking i'm eating like nurturing
their houses yeah god and then you
gotta know your stuff i'm actually pleasure
there it's okay so it's justin timberlake
justin timberlake joey vast joey let me
try and risk kirkpatrick
ic okay that i'm out
you almost had it and one more
jacey lamps jacey shazam jason alright backstreet
boys don't know ah carter nine vince
cost our neck or card agent carter
agent carter yeah all the carter nick
carter they should to have a band
together they should all the carter hayley
attwell hey carter still alive jimmy
sophia i don't think i know everyone
saw sandy single
nick kevin bryan
that's where i'm that's yeah if i
saw them maybe i can i don't
know anyone's last name other than nick
de paulo kevin kevin james
bryan cranston yes and then one more
so j o e a mclean a
journey howie der rohe how jj mclean
hollywood ended a bit try and go
oh it's a jay benzo age amanda
heaven richardson okay so so the one
thing i learned on from the
a book homicide is that ah guilty
people when they bring them into the
interrogation room they always fall asleep oh
and this is according to cops yes
okay
liars policy guilty people when they get
interrogation they always fall asleep well i
know somebody who when they were caught
doing something like cotton and i know
this story they fainted but it was
pretty easy to like what you've done
oh my feeling is like falling asleep
is like a sort of
of tactics like i'm not even here
i can't do about this you can't
wake me up it's rude but i
also trying to use and you can't
give me longer than twenty four hours
i sleep for twenty four hours yeah
dammit he fell asleep i have a
friend who used to interview celebrities for
like e and stuff and she would
get very sleepy like in exchange for
ecstasy the first one interview celebrity yeah
just john tesh
you would get once you get nervous
about certain people should get really sleepy
yeah so that's what that's what i
think they were trying to say is
like these people are so nervous about
being caught that they tend to fall
asleep like it's a it's a
i don't know that's so great i'm
like i was watching caught my adrenalin
would be higher than it's ever been
they also tell a very funny story
about how they would use the copier
machine as a lie detector supposedly where
they would put in the third piece
of paper ah the the first piece
of paper when you're loading the paper
yeah it would be blank
the second piece of paper would be
blank and then they'd load a third
piece of paper that would say lie
and they would ask they go okay
we have randomly we have a lookout
we we have a lie detector here
and they would ask a question like
what's your name the person entity would
press the button and a blank piece
of paper would come out like a
where do you live they would say
a blank piece of paper would come
out did you kill that person no
i didn't pr
yes the button lie i think oh
well we got you and then they
would confess i'm like yeah well so
far so far sober stayed true i
maybe it did say true and i'm
misremembering this has been like that was
blank by noted cup lover david simon
and it was called homicide colon a
year on the killing streets a year
on the killing
streets yes i wow does show that's
too long maybe a little afraid i
don't want it but i don't think
it was about two hours on the
killing streets i'll spend a good hour
and a half of the costs really
love him yeah have you i would
like to spend a year i mean
if i can nightmare american nightmare
due to duty away from me why
did you that i don't know about
elizabeth lambs was talking about on her
podcast i say why are you bringing
things up that you haven't even was
always talking about it but you don't
know what it is it's a documentary
about something really scary a documentary about
something scary huh and i was gonna
watch it last night i texted her
should i watch this she's always talking
about it because
to be well i'm like well my
goes to sleep so it was like
i can watch this alone or will
i freak out and she was like
i would say watch during the day
but then i was curious if you
watched it but i know jamie likes
i'm sure she's watching okay like stuff
like that i mean i thought we
would leave that in the old place
let me like stuff like that let
me settle exchange like stuff like that
did
it want to mention oh when we
all went to high dimension yeah right
we should do a disney day where
we record from disneyland yeah that would
be so fun i did a podcast
from digital so any time you did
a podcast from that did did did
did disneyland yeah don't be scared
this was this today's podcast called walking
with michelle i was fishing with michelle
that was the theme song i bet
it was and i by michelle balloon
atlanta com yeah oh yeah when that
song came philly i thought it was
old like a seventy song why the
way it sounds
and then i learned it also the
way your brain is young you receive
that information when i heard it i
was like this is like a cool
retro song and then it was new
okay so the idea was we're going
to go there we were gonna record
a podcast from she was going to
go various places and record a podcast
with guest right and so the first
one was disneyland and this was me
and her produce
sir matt belknap whom you might know
from never not funny yes and this
is this is early podcasting data silent
killer
that's right because he has a silent
k on his name that's why that's
great so i call him cholesterol sometimes
well that's fun decidedly killer i thought
hypertension was the silent killer i think
there's a lot of silent killers too
many so many don't announce like oh
yeah like talk to us guys so
yeah we recorded this on a sunday
morning perfect sunday
morning day after i went to a
friend's wedding ooh bad timing bad timing
and then we discovered that the reason
we were doing it we had to
be a disneyland at ten a m
was that he thought there would be
ah less traffic and fewer people there
so how that works
it's absolutely not how that works there's
less traffic and fewer people at like
seven pm yeah yeah digital and it
turns out is very popular i think
people with children who wake up early
will go there in the morning yeah
and i was hung over as hell
yeah i this is what i do
in this situation i call dizzy
bomb
that's when you do enter them they
close the whole place and you can't
use people should leave but unless you
let a few fits in okay there's
a bomb that is set to go
off around two pm
we have sick break right
and we're back and it's time for
three cheer i know this is so
exciting i shall part of the show
where we play the game i'll play
your game yes we are we are
are we doing gathering sorcery or or
it's something like that yeah because this
is three
these are submitted by you huh time
yes so don't blame us yeah and
the theme song was submitted by michael
jackson he submitted it for our approval
and we said you know what turn
listen to something different for your own
album oh scott you didn't finish drinking
your alcohol i drank everything in i
don't want to eat the chocolate you
don't have to drive go ahead
um okay this was submitted by robert
cub okay oh it had i know
he's just a baby bears just a
baby bear has no title but my
tiger but then are ah other things
it comes okay matt exxon's new server
met ex producer maddox i hate that
guy he we can fight
only say benedict arnold yep
he we left he just stays where
he is it did benedict arnold do
anything that bad there we're still talking
about benedict i i saw something recently
that led me to believe that i
guess certain people think that he was
framed or he was trying to do
something good certain people yeah i think
i know who you're talking about
let me guess they don't like the
company pfizer ah um i love last
names kennedy pfizer had a commercial during
the super bowl that was so bad
and it was like it was to
the tune of don't stop me now
ah by queen oh yeah eventually you
actually go to rancor they just did
like like moving lips it's like that
face tune thing or whatever it's just
moving lips on paintings and busts and
sculptures and shit like that good shit
it looked so bad though the the
cgr was the animation was so bad
so bad i had to spend so
much money getting it on
you know but the whole thing was
like we're the future of science we've
always been at the forefront of science
like this sox
if this is how good your drugs
are yeah yeah
i always feel like i could write
great commercials if only i was given
the i've always felt that about youtube
yeah but i only man you do
that you should be in it i
know youtube could write great cover i
think if i wanted to if you
put his mind when you read a
jingle songs should just be commercial like
which yeah like expert will but you
know what a lot of them were
know the song you want to live
really really hero with your wit and
which is that part of focus focus
too was fun that's good good time
so if the width version it's an
accusation as opposed to the original version
it's like i am a bit i'm
of which okay look we gotta do
this i'm not a witch i'm you
remember that
no
ah what was her name o'donnell i
thank rosie know if only speaking of
hating houses rosie o'donnell it was this
young woman who's actually running for president
remember that movie east of eden where
she's where she's dressed like a likens
dont domineer i remember robin dominique i
remember seeing and hearing here i saw
it at the city
oh store like all the telugu do
you want to see in this stuff
rosie o'donnell and dan ackroyd but um
he wears dominatrix i believe so yeah
and then and then i watch this
there's ah there's a like a sub
on this island they go to i
haven't seen it so right so there's
some green and um dom sub relationship
while there they everyone goes to this
either like
anywhere under cover cop yeah they're undercover
cops okay but they're all dressed like
this and there's there's a sub who
comes in and goes i will do
anything you command mistress she also paint
my house the one of the oldest
jokes i'm gonna watch that yeah it's
as old as in the bud bop
i'm just even older which is by
the way from sea of love
the movie sea of love the alley
you know the epigenome movie they're they're
two characters are telling the story as
if it's an it's an old joke
yeah that turns out to be true
as we learned from paul f tompkins
know the newlywed game thing yeah the
newlywed game thing you know it's still
sea of love you can't just put
this is where it's like you can't
just use some old street joke
and call yourself a scriptwriter like write
your own joke
don't so when you see of luck
i don't know but the killer i
believe the killer the killer steals a
job killer steals easy he's a bad
guy there reveals a joke there's the
fifth okay look this is matt x
producer says maybe this could be called
reality bites why matt we don't
it doesn't make any sense for what
i know though maybe oh sorry realty
bites there we go you know worse
well it's not actually me oh no
it's actually no no right now it's
perfect i'll call it reality bites realty
bites okay for this game one person
to realtor and then the other two
are a potential couple trying to buy
the house
ah what a potential couple yeah it's
a well they want pages per day
just like sam and diane
canopy working i'm like going okay okay
open house there's a fun thing to
do on a first date yeah house
yeah i think i mixed up the
words it's potential buyers of the house
i think so i figured it out
here's here's how we should go out
you just une you ah neither of
us are going to text you this
problem you just come up with the
problem for the house is that okay
oh i
have to guess the problem is you
and and will try to figure out
what the chromecast with the problem we
were all going to try to figure
it out
i don't know i know it's real
you know you you i know what
the i don't know what the problem
is the words on the page no
because we're changing it so one person
doesn't just sit there i see her
i sort of feel like it makes
more sense for the the the real
church or not no okay it's like
in the way these games go okay
so i'll text i'll text learn what
the problem is
what do you want oni why don't
i don't get why me knowing like
tell me what's happening i am the
realtor i have to guess what this
guy gets guys hey we're going to
hint at it yeah okay yeah thanks
okay so i'm gonna text lauren what
a problem is and we're gonna be
if you're new to the show we
play these three cheers that are variations
on five different and and sometimes the
piece
all who submit them don't exactly incorporate
all three of us into the things
so we have to change the reds
rude um i are people trying to
push me out of the show
the fans
okay i have texted lauren the issue
exciting and we are going to hint
around the issue not okay yeah rabbit
put it in my memory read it
hi come on in oh that there
is open you don't i know but
i just wanted to see if it
works it's a nice yeah hardy door
this is a good door this is
good i just want thick because want
to make sure if i were in
a hurry door well it's good for
a very party yesterday i was going
to say thank great for parties i
love this so this is beautiful thank
you do a little bit about the
home yes it
it has done me to like don't
just tell me i don't know and
and well you a couple of you're
almost a couple of potential companies to
work out the way i'm the breadwinner
so i think you should speak directly
to me okay we see here's our
situation we wanted to live together yeah
but we don't know whether whether we
want a date or not so we
feel like if we get a house
that's big enough maybe it has upstairs
downstairs
there's kind of thing like you think
the one part could be his or
her mind and if it doesn't work
out the way you'd just have a
good place to live that sounds terrific
we can find a similar situation oh
really what's your situation ship i'm stalking
stuff
that i think is gonna come around
okay right sure they will become those
lives in your house ah so i
live in their house in the walls
oh god it oh like a bad
ronald situation my name is robin t
here like you've been very good to
hear everything that they're doing everything they're
doing well that's good because you'd see
a lot of insight into what kind
of stuff they want to talk about
also
i surprised him with gifts you know
them intimately at this point so you
know whether you like them or where
do you leave the gifts i leave
them in the walls which is not
working great yeah yeah especially if it's
food do you ever say like have
this pie through the wall i do
heathrow at all i'm very very quiet
because i don't want to scare them
right so
so what i'll do is like when
this person gets in bed i will
be behind the the head of the
bed and wall and i'll just be
like
today have a sound mission thing while
they're sleeping they do but it broke
a while ago so i have to
imitate the sound oh okay so they
don't know it's broken they turned on
and oh my gosh ronald i love
to give you good refuge please call
me to give you a huge commission
on
this house because you just seem great
i would love to tip you on
top of the commission i like the
sound of this well let's talk about
the house yeah so you like upstairs
and downstairs it has two upstairs is
okay cool how's that where you make
all three stories are exactly so you
go upstairs and then you can go
upstairs again that's so fun and you
can also go back downstairs twice that's
so
fine yeah hey yeah how many times
can you do it in one day
it doesn't have a slip and slide
ready okay is it can you install
a fireman's pole do you think and
between all these i can't but you
can i'm sorry i'm like to sell
the house and i asked a question
i'm sorry what was your question or
your stam
i was just gonna i was wondering
how many times do you can go
up and down the stairs you can
it's unlimited okay you can go up
and down the stairs as many times
so we pay it that's part of
the mortgage we're paying for unlimited stare
usage yes ah um it has crown
moldings or a way to discount it
if we don't ever want to go
upstairs i can talk to the seller
yeah well there's something i saw no
i just want to be a little
but i think we should just tell
him yeah we were poking around outside
kind of peering through windows okay and
we saw i think what's a huge
problem it's definitely a problem i i
i don't so well
i think i know what you're talking
about i hope so i mean it's
huge i would say it's affecting the
whole thing right but look at it
as i know that it seems like
a problem from the outside looking in
but i think it would be worse
when we're inside it's an opportunity to
what to to do something
that you've never done a house before
a swim i don't think it's yes
that's one thing okay but i one
thing you pretend to go fishing yeah
i don't think that any fish could
survive doesn't seem sample that's why i
said pretend okay that's a good point
did he pretend to know but imagine
if you don't you don't call me
that yet what do you want me
to call you
avery dr avery i know you have
your p h d
have a last name too
plans every was your thoughts are two
it's my first name but what's your
last name wonderful first day belonged every
below the doctor avery belong
what's your name i'm sorry
this name peanuts
what's your last name no that's my
that is my last your last name
is tina yeah mr mr peanuts yank
mister mr peanuts mister mr peanuts yeah
his first name is mister mister mister
peanuts dr belong
i know that it seems like
that area in the house is maybe
toxic and dangerous yeah yeah it's i
mean you know i noticed and it
seems deep it's incredibly deep i'm just
worried that i could catch some sort
of disease yeah i mean it's it's
fine for most of the house ravenously
the you know i don't expect it
to be funny
hst necessarily but i mean i think
it should be dealt with i do
is there anyway to drain it i
wouldn't do that because i think the
fuller it gets the more you can
take advantage of it i'm just worried
it's going to seep stuff and voters
get some work to do think maybe
i can donate it to science yeah
think i mean that's up to you
i think you can i think you
can it's good for tracing circles where
did it all come from this is
what i'm pre tracing circles know about
it means it doesn't know if it's
not even know what that means tracy
said well it's a realtor's term oh
we're not real here i can't there's
no way i could explain there's
not a term for it a realty
circle is like realty bucks so there's
no way there's no way to describe
it without talking about it without without
being a realtor exactly mr mr peanuts
gets it yeah i um i actually
get it too i'm a woman in
stem but you but the the the
you could just put the cover on
it it has a special cover
you could put on okay okay you
see sort of like a waterbed feeling
at that point maybe we'd forget what
it was underneath that yes exactly and
i'm helping you out honestly because i
i can live like this i mean
it doesn't if we just never went
down there it would be fine but
sure but i would enjoy things down
there yeah
eventually we want to you can store
things
like what what what what do you
need storing and i'll tell you if
you can do it a childhood momentos
yeah put him in there but they're
gonna be jimmy ruin they're gonna be
red and
and and soaking wet
red and soaking wet yeah i mean
i guess i could store my old
pads down there yeah i guess that
would be why you keeping your old
tags well because i like to remember
do you have your first one i
sort of just check every month to
be like and how did that compare
last month you know and so she's
like is it ever different i yeah
really what's the what's the variation on
it um sometimes to have your flow
right right i think you can make
a wonderful wall piece out of those
like radio station put them in the
de kooning if i'm thinking of yeah
person i shouldn't put them in the
basement no don't put them in the
basement and you were looking through the
basement window yeah yeah i would say
that
um you you can use this in
an emergency situation like if i'm flying
anita transmitters yes if you're the correct
type which what what your blood type
adds z negatives she's kinda she's an
anomaly the universal diffuser and what's yours
i'm zed
oh the england and canada universe reviews
for u k yeah um all right
so look a lot of houses are
not gonna have an amount of blood
this substantial i mean it's so it's
to sustain so i mean there's no
such thing in in home-buying there's no
such thing as too much blood look
just tell
us the truth why is waistband filled
with blood why is the beta filled
with blood before he got here at
a bloody nose to sell came from
you i was picking my nose okay
and started okay don't you know you
can pick your friends and you can
pick your nose but you can't pick
your friend's nose yeah that's why it
wasn't doing okay you might think because
your your fingers in my nose right
now well you're my friend
i thought we were friends oh wait
you really think relation mister mister paris
so much good ronald what's a high
school things get around like donald has
that unique ryan mcdonald i'm not the
bad one who sells hamburgers
okay well i think we should just
take it you guys have a history
how much is it oh it's good
question how much this house are you
ready for this now di di di
di di di di one dollar and
one billion
bad ex like it what's a billion
sense it must be how much is
one billion pennies
ten million dollars yeah million dollars one
dollar for a bloody basement
okay the house with two upstairs i
want that i want that one that
i want the basement can we keep
the blood of course you can't you
want it back no i'm packing your
head oh i can't take it back
but okay oh oh it's a matter
better out than in type oh god
this can't go
back in okay for can't go back
in okay yeah
well thank you so much thanks so
much we obviously have a lot to
talk about what we do and it's
where do we sign and were that's
what i'm saying we have a lot
to talk about where do we oh
yeah why we should ask him oh
that's right yeah why are we just
gonna wear a couple yes your trouble
and we're throttle now
i'm right here who is living in
the basement me and i mean it's
an upgrade from our guys it is
going to be swimming in blood i'm
going to sleep in a canoe
this makes sense they already had this
planned out yes i did so what
do we just walk into your trap
yeah you like i love it it's
beautiful trap think you can mill you
you put an eight i'll put two
yeah that seems fair dude a dollars
yeah times million
damn it fuck those guys this fucking
doctor over here fucking doctor all right
that's it we did it we did
that was fun right thank you matt
the final time will ever refer to
you on mike but thank you robert
cub for submit huh i'm trying to
remember this story that there was um
a i bet people calling someone who
did ask that once who was a
showrunner and he talked about his childhood
pictures know so much he would put
those boogers in the lamp shade and
all over the room
that and then one day picked so
much it started going crazy bleeding and
this whole family was like freaking out
until you put the blood on the
election i think he'd go to the
hospital it was like a whole thing
oh it was about just about how
much you bitches know i did a
podcast once i can't i can't even
discuss it it makes me sick to
my stomach oh say it's
i learned that pregnancy right yeah i
say the row she wants to yeah
last thing she wants to eat vehicles
oils pike yeah
ah talk to me about the taste
of hair say yeah alright well texted
to you because i honestly can i
will gag if i say oh am
i gonna throw up i don't fucking
know
okay here's what you need to know
if you want to write to us
and suggest one of these games or
you want to write a feature you
gotta send it to na na
a jingle send it to us at
threesome usa at gmail dot com nailed
it and then if you want to
leave us by the way so you've
heard the first of these about a
week and a half ago we're doing
our three medium episodes
first-time they were mentioning them here this
is a special proper show but every
other week we're putting out three meme
episodes where we're answering your voicemail resume
this is ah you can get him
at cb world through you knew as
well as apple podcast premium and if
you want to this is huge news
freemium
remember how people could call us and
leave these voicemails and they had to
call a special number had claimed eight
we do not have that number we
lost we lost the number but when
we gain the number was a website
hag claims eight dot com where people
can leave us voice
males what a website was the voicemail
website yes so go to hag claims
eight dot com the number eight the
number eight had claims eight dot com
okay just voicemails and will answer some
better three new episode does seem better
website seems more official it seems better
anybody can have a fuckin phone number
i know what i mean and angry
i mean we'd have to figure out
how to check
yeah i kinda figured if they spell
out the number eight will redirect i'd
have to buy two websites
right and then teach them into fish
who am i going to teach out
of everyone knows how to fish these
days yes true well what's complicated it's
like archaic expression but no it was
yeah back in the day when they
made up that expression because she uses
names we fish she was whoever was
like how do you do this now
everyone fishes
yeah it's like it doesn't make sense
anymore but we still say oh the
first kind of fish must have been
so annoyed like now i gotta show
you another one it's like i just
figured this shit out i can't you
show him after i showed you
so ah leave us these voicemails at
hag claims eight darkly because these voicemail
he's whatever you gonna say those come
out every other wednesday and then um
are three visiting on the two episodes
are still coming out these are our
old episodes that are behind the classic
classy ah so that's that's all of
the business here at three m
that's all we got so we got
forty i don't know what more you
want we just hope you have a
great day or night depending on when
you're listening to the sound okay or
if you're sleeping because some people put
on podcast to sleep which is still
screaming that losing whatever happened to me
i know
i
bye