three
ooh thank you
just no
ah
welcome to three am
you say whoa did you see somebody's
boop boop do you see
it's use
so much boop and we're not leaving
till we get to the bottom of
this it's going to be a chilly
day today today today oh welcome to
three now come to fix a silly
day we're goofing around as lawrence water
ball ball says your warsaw mo ma
out of a bow i take a
squishy nerve
soccer ball i get it okay good
and this ring it out over your
mouth is sopping heavy as hell it's
billion pounds and it is changing shape
did you ever
b j ever be in a pool
yeah and get and get the i
saw that did you see who said
boo boo get the nerf ball stopping
whitman hit someone in the face with
it and it's really bad actually didn't
do oh that's really mean that's terrible
yeah i mean it's cool i'm i'm
not saying i did it exclusively i'm
saying when it doesn't seem
to be a thing everyone who ever
did that loose know i flip this
over this hourglass then you flipped it
back and i wanna know why well
i thought that we would flip it
in order to time how we were
doing in the episode but i suddenly
afflicted too early so i was like
you know it's like five minutes and
they will yeah so every five minutes
flip back and then at the end
will know how many five minutes ago
yeah that makes
thank you
you know it's definitely an hour i'd
say are these are these inherently an
hour
it depends on how much sounding sanders
extrinsically yeah
that one looks like an hour to
there looks like
feels like smells like sounds
i think there are hourglass size that
are a day and there are some
that i'm in today
don't you think would that be from
the ones from the board games for
a minute dude
so you'll be ooh i'm like glass
there's to be an arc she tugs
at the twenty four times that there's
to be an hour bus it's just
one grain of sand but it's on
a time release thing where after an
hour the the platform that it's just
drops out and it just one was
like on ellen's game of games
huh
okay no table games we've talked about
this eight times heavily who's allen's gaming
who do you call far because this
is shadow oh yeah you've told me
they don't i asked you at least
twice on this program you know i
was allen i generated
you see i didn't say poop
you said though i did not say
boo boo my god
oh alan game of games
he's also producing a new show starring
dex and christian oh thank god and
they are doing games with families i
think it or something the mason family
it's done and i saw one episode
of the manson family makes you the
adams family look like the the sly
the family stone the walton family wow
um i had a friend who was
on a game show years ago congratulations
po
now we're having a pretty one and
there's this person was i don't have
friends that aren't on tv that's probably
true right it probably didn't say poop
i didn't say boop she might my
friend andy savage from the thrilling adventure
yes i've met her on a game
show she was on a game show
this is years ago and she was
eliminated at one point and she fell
through a fucking trapdoor wait a minute
is show shocking we've we've we've must
have talked about no because we didn't
talk
how about this because i i dated
a woman who was on that very
same game show i believe what show
was it i think it was called
trapdoor i don't know if it was
it was it was on game show
network you're lying i'm lying boop boop
and and they've i we haven't talked
about this because it was crazy you
dated a girl we talked with for
sure twenty year
years ago that dog yeah yeah yeah
and we i should hope so you
fill out the entire time yeah
but it was it was a thing
where they fall through the floor and
they and they just fall think of
the hidden temple is nickelodeon show you
guys wouldn't get it fuck it wow
you know i wouldn't because these are
wheat dairy here likely don't because you
spoke
anyway because anyone if i can't hear
women
i'm auditory processing issues wherever you're a
little bit i get here
but yeah the only fall like four
feet yeah but pretty far it is
far or maybe two have you ever
done a trustful they fall into a
shopping cart and it hurts and then
they're on supermarket sweep and leslie jones
is pushing around and she's suffering because
they can't because she doesn't show pushes
everyone know
wait have you guys ever when i've
where i just asked
ah look i need you guys to
keep track of what i'm saying because
i do it
have you ever done a trust fall
oh and no i'm not going to
suggest we do one i think we're
never doing i would never try that
seems like something that you do when
you're in elementary we didn't high school
we had a stand up on this
like really toll storage thing that was
like normally for five feet tall and
stand up on it and then everyone
would put their hands interlock
looking like in two rows yeah it
seems any more trustful back i know
it seems to danger that was my
class called adventure ed and we were
we had a wall like a rock
climbing wall my school and you could
climb you'd climb the wall which was
really scary and then we wanna know
each other and just something yeah it
was all like okay i'm belay play
on ladoga yeah
i learned all that i beg your
pardon and we had a um there
was a i forgot about this there
was a like ah what do you
call it obstacle course in the sky
heaven
the solar system
very much over that pluto there was
a very old museum this was my
adventure and class was and were you
but did you say adventure ed yes
there's a very tall gymnasium and i
suppose everybody got a trophy it's is
is this guy's deal
there's a very tall gene all young
leo like a rock climbing class then
you would do these trust exercises because
it was part of getting used to
like climbing on the wall sounds like
a rich person's high school but it's
it's public school weight but this is
also separately in every other neighborhood the
only school in town in a real
estate deal was going down baby but
it's a separable in town there's a
big lawn
talking
lower and only paul is talking only
high school was it was this separate
was his trustful separate from the one
where you got on office equipment and
fell down ah yeah in the same
class but we then would there was
a exercise we'd go up on this
opposite course i was hanging from the
ceiling yeah so it was like rope
steps you know yeah blatter high
getting off the ground or you know
pretty i'm not gonna read it that's
that's summer camp too we were twelve
feet lita twelve feet up in the
yeah like it was stretched between trees
and stuff yeah yeah and then you
had to do it blindfolded know is
a partner guiding you from below telling
you oh this is not legal yeah
i'm sorry to inform you
i've been crying and then on my
camping trip when when we went rock
climbing which was horrible for me i
hated it so much but the camping
trip is alex wood to build our
own tent with our little team of
friends from scratch um i don't run
cheerio no real champ but something happened
to mine there was like a storm
and mine was called santi town to
begin with because we messed it up
so much
then it was pouring rain and i
slept in the truck the teachers truck
um with the show
yeah all his arms are after it
was just ohio boy
remember ha
there were there were piles of logs
there's something in his truck bed and
i got in there with to my
friends and we slept on the woods
soaking wet all night because we had
gotten rained out of our tent and
everyone else this town was fine they
could sleep in it but oh wait
so you were sleeping on top of
the wood but under what truck top
there was okay it was i was
covered it was the back of a
truck but it wasn't a truck i
got empty human bessemer yeah okay got
it anyhow bedtimes bedtime end did you
have to to rock climb the next
day or had you already collapsed that
was it was only one night i
believe did you answer did you see
a group
she's adding these business is yes are
these imposed i'm listening back to the
episode now and i'm hearing oops yeah
but i'm not hearing them when we're
talking meanie there and we've all we've
all been asking we've all answered the
knocks because no one said that i've
said whenever i said to have you
did you say boop it's me when
i'm listening to it recorded lady yes
yes we said we would
those in person
wait okay my school didn't have anything
like that because we were just simple
country folk but we did have the
parachute and boy when the parish came
out that's a great way to do
with it again you put one of
those red bouncy balls on it and
then you'd play some everyway around holding
a little p
nice at the parachutes keep it open
then you bounce a ball keep it
up in there or or and you're
a little did you play this game
where you would stop pointing at me
where you would flap the parachute and
then switch spots like some people yes
yeah where people go wrong right yay
go to their site
fun why don't we do that then
we should bring a three person parachute
nice haircut i already said he got
to her company thanks i see it's
nice i don't know but it looks
nice you did say it wasn't ok
thanks so i thought she walked in
and just said you got a haircut
that doesn't want imply that it's nice
or or anyone
oh okay so that's the way you're
gonna go so i took it and
what you did like it just wanting
your nicer heard what i wanted to
hear it's actually a really good haircut
oh where do new personal styling at
differently style it that way from now
on okay she does it all you
get is the one time it works
buddy
it's working for the listener up here
you can see the picture hell yeah
just in fact pause this right now
take a look at this picture we're
listening back anyway so why don't you
pause
did you say did you say boo
i mean i said pause i heard
you say as i was saying pause
the episode i heard a boop and
i thought you said oh okay no
it wasn't so anyway is there a
problem with my muffins are you guys
gonna fit ahead outfit long mike now
you you've run three muffins for four
people i thought it was josh
i already ate one inside o three
muffins for nine people mailed him and
said he could ever meet about him
ah i would love that though oh
you can email muffins hey why don't
we start playing mafia on facebook again
mafia do you play farmville no i
never did farmville mafia or something like
zombies i think i did oh my
god that's sucked it got very irritating
very quickly i think i did it
for you know a second and then
the there were too many alerts
or better exactly
i got very irritating wet very very
dare we go
the new yorker says
yeah coming in at number eleven and
three you know they don't write they
usually don't write bad reviews for podcasts
have you noticed that because there's there's
so many are so many that they're
trying to elevate you know ones that
don't get a lot and i think
everyone's good at winning don't happen back
in the day they used to get
bad reviews like when they would review
it every week
v club and yeah yeah yeah but
nowadays you can't get better reviews i
would love to see a bad three
drummer yeah i would love to see
that tightly wound i choose
that's true never look at that stuff
i was like okay i'm just saying
hey so wait i had half of
the remarkable i thought i was being
kind yeah because i thought you brought
three muffins for four people and i
was like so lorna eat the other
half of that one or or i
don't know how we were going to
do but i was right into it
you ripped i ripped it and i
was like are you okay thank you
so much i'll have that in-between things
great if you know what i mean
i just wanted to make sure they
didn't taste like um but no they
didn't i mean they taste like a
bud if a but tasted like a
beautiful delicious chocolate chip muffin which sometimes
does
yeah just like ass to me
yeah yeah you're correct so lauren why
are you town so much okay well
we had were taping this at three
of the morning when we bickmore up
from the airport and we started recording
right away they went out of town
for two weeks to do a movie
in georgia your movie star and then
i did another movie in georgia
georgia marie yeah move are you in
a marvel movie when you do a
short film are you daredevil or no
i'm not i don't know that i
can say what it is only because
i don't know what if there's a
rule oh i do know i signed
an nda for one of them and
they're doing a prostitute and check me
um yeah so do not resuscitate the
movie i had to sign a do
not resuscitate because i'm in this
designed to make life choices yeah yeah
if i get hurt please do not
resuscitate me but my first trip with
holly was the first one for two
weeks to georgia how did you like
it um she did really well hello
i'm your friend yeah she's like this
little tiny little fresh
and that moved into my house she's
so small
she is she the smallest roommate you've
ever had yeah yeah what's your smallest
roommate some six foot bible
my smallest roommate of all time okay
all my other spots roommate was named
amy how small machine ah she's probably
five two should we do roommate roundup
was around oh yeah oh this incredible
stuff
across these never die roommate round roommate
round up i had roommates of course
of course it was the smallest before
we get into the roundup well maybe
we should go through them one at
a time and then we can going
way back the sewing go through them
one at a time and then we
say who was the smallest at the
end at the end yeah like i'm
not going to be able to remember
like the
the audience decide who they think yes
why everybody right away we describe this
that gave mine away so you're out
alright um did you have any other
roommates i had a lot of remain
well let's should we should we go
around the circle and do the first
roommate and then the second roommate of
each person oh yeah this could be
a long game let me we did
all right now are we counting siblings
no
no not killing once you move out
or we can't already canting roma a
candy aisle we can take already counting
romantic relationships yes okay alright okay yeah
because that's that's okay just might be
a a great deal of information we
should we all do first roommate yeah
yes okay paul first roommate her name
is lori her name was larry ooh
she was a showgirl is this the
older woman from the bats in the
belfry yes
because that's correct who is that refreshing
meeting an older woman this is my
first year and second yeah you guys
had sex in the wrong mature you
never made that shirt we never made
the shirt we guys yeah it's a
shirt we call yeah but you never
made the shirt together which is like
when you both get one shirt and
we made sure one big show and
i made a shirt thing in there
good it up
we never saw made the shirt you
know what i mean
that's getting our best shot voting
you only feel really lucky to work
in the pic yeah i love clothes
did you say boo i never i
don't think i've ever said in your
life in my life yeah well i
haven't either yeah alright so first one
was laurie from hats in the belfry
she was i was from hudson debelle
fridge and she did she there she
hailed from developers she was from a
place called the last wound up which
which was a windup toy store tv
show this really guys just like it
is centric with thousands like you're both
characters on pushing daisies and i'm not
sure if you're on
i work at the last wound dabble
and i work at hats in the
belfry only yarn bunny philadelphia's specialty stores
those were the two on the same
street by the way well that's too
much i wrote the same street they're
on the same street oh my god
just a few blocks from each did
you guys meet on the street just
about to be illustrate measures manager
i saw her on the street i'd
never done something like this before see
or like you are making my tongue
roll my eyes bug out the top
of my head flew off of streamers
came out i've done her signs in
my eyes yeah yeah baby
you need a covert sex recovery
yeah
yeah it's nice and wet door
fasting i have paper towels here i'm
like fleming to one the other night
i thought i had a cold for
like
with twenty minutes twenty minutes something like
that and i was first i thought
oh i feel a cold coming on
then i was like is this breakthrough
kofoed i don't know why you always
gotta think and then you remember you
smoke for thirty years
thirty come on forty twenty oh god
i don't know i don't know where
you started when i was ten years
old yeah maybe i thought i had
covered the other day but it was
because i had been screaming all day
oh and the movie looks like okay
holly yeah gotta say i fucking used
something very sweet on a text thread
ed what did i say you said
that you love you paul
i'm in love
exposing me it's very sweet for instance
hello friend that's sweet but it's a
problem um ah you said that you
miss hollywood she's asleep i oh wow
are you sexy without me that thing
that being said i am speaking to
a sleep consultant next week to try
to get her to sleep through the
night because everyone i know and the
baby sleeps twelve hours and this is
not how we're operating i feel like
that's rare and they're all doing it
or that annoying know i think they'd
like done the sleep training thing a
little bit right yeah that was kind
of avoiding this i didn't
oh how i felt about it but
now i feel pretty good about it
what's the what's what is the sleep
training thing basically won't be hired somebody
that my friend used for us who
she talks to on the phone everyday
kind of says like do this try
this bubble lot and then until it
all works um and it's and there's
also books for this stuff and i
started reading the books and i was
like it's not anyone to share yeah
yeah that's the plan we make
read the book but what it was
was i was gonna do it from
the book but then i thought i
feel like it's so specific to each
baby like what what we're doing throughout
the day how i'm doing this i
would like to talk to somebody so
they could say oh stop doing that
thing or whatever why don't you buy
one that is addressed to holly that's
yeah yeah yeah yeah exercise is she
on the peloton she'd you know what
and i was gonna buy a used
ton and they sold it somebody else
was so fucking pissed you wanna buy
mine used you don't want for new
price and i'll buy a new one
this way are you saying things are
you saying that the way i styled
my hair before you didn't like it
um no i'm saying no really nice
this is really nice no i don't
know i'm struck by it yeah i
went to chuck to i'm i'm in
love with
ah but anyways this women will just
basically what you have to do is
like it's a whole i mean i
don't know what her exact rules are
but from other friends i've heard like
you put them in and they cry
then you go into script and then
you leave and then you come back
and say you have to say so
like you're kind of script like saying
the same two things and says you
have to memorize your lines yeah yeah
look
eventually i'm kinda started doing a little
bit it's kind of working sometimes but
she doesn't really nap much so anyway
i was born she naps like thirty
minutes at a time and what i
hear is they could be going like
couple hours at a time several times
a day i usually have going down
every hour or two for thirty minutes
noting i have babies love naps is
what they live for and this is
why you
hire a sleep consultant because it's not
working out dang she does want to
sleep she just like gets upset when
i leave and then it's a whole
thing she misses you when she's asleep
yeah aw it's very sweet paul tell
us about this woman yeah heather ah
this was usar on the street wherever
it had this real heather's my first
remain ah she's
just know each other is your frame
broken so i smiled i am so
tight i have to say i am
very tired oh because the only situation
i've been up since five thirty and
i tried to sleep when she was
sleeping and only last thirty minutes each
time and i think i'm the same
sleep schedule as you are you do
you like having sympathetic sleep will go
down
without even rear sleeping sync'd up are
you where we live and die thirty
i wake up and fall asleep whenever
you do okay so you're getting porcelain
simplify this just whenever you're awake i'm
awake kindly
with my fitbit i get zero steps
but i do know that i sleep
very poorly so i'm getting a lot
of information from sleep very poorly i
way i stayed up too late and
woke up too early okay well it's
just that simple it's bad it's about
if i did that too but i
was able to get back as the
beatles one said get back to where
you want spoon
oh learns she put her hands up
as if she was being robbed get
a load of this get back
yeah
back to where you want below have
you watched that documentary i have all
of it love yeah great okay loved
it great i'll check it out absolutely
love it i'll get around to that
when i'm just watching dexter eissa who's
when i realized i was the monster
i loved x maybe i'm not the
most relatable so you met this woman
i saw her walking up the stream
a roundup is taking for fucking ever
well you have the street maybe we
just do one on this ep i
think so i was very struck by
her those what what ah an attractive
young woman she turns into the store
and you've never done that before yeah
it was my first time that was
my sexual awakening
wow my jose jojo seventeen years old
is puberty but didn't know the outcry
center and you said will you let
me move in with you yeah sounds
like coloring that's you anyway yes can
i make lots of money
so so she walked into the store
and went out to the theme song
to share ah is it probably i
don't watch right oh yeah it was
from it was from beauty and the
geek hey you've got the looks i
got brains let's make lots of money
on reality don't go but they do
donate during zhan hu is i do
i remember that show but what route
how did they make nerds day hot
i know and then one day fuck
and if they weighed why guess if
you stayed a couple you got money
or some bullshit or then do the
challenges and all sorts of stuff because
that's how many actually stay together though
none have aller au yeah i started
dealing
earnest hots with nerds it's unbelievable it's
star crossed lovers and have good tv
man where any of the nerds like
i just didn't like the huts of
course you know that's the force that's
true because sometimes hot people are so
stupid and fucking annoying i know but
you overlook that because you want sex
i don't know what you're talking about
yeah did mr e
participate in the show who is that
the the the pickup artist or was
that a different show military mystery oh
ah that though you really usually pronounced
it mr dodgy i've never heard said
aloud i'm just responding to how it's
written mr e had a big hat
and he told me to wear big
he was talking and he said you
must put talk
now that was
i forgot what show i was so
you went up dallas game the game
the game ah yes based on the
book based on the book precious so
i
haven't hurt myself
based on the precious it's pushed ah
remember hearing that
they say little push by sapphire but
i like bass
isn't much precious which is based on
the novel sapphires the photo now
i was with my friend john lanka
love we were in that we were
in the process of dropping out of
time
you want to say it all the
where are you how are you in
the process of dropping out you were
you like we were like we were
going to fewer and fewer classes and
just hanging out together and not going
can you stop jangling that
i'm sorry it's a it's a very
attractive piece it's a wishbone bottle you
love that i know i do love
it i'm gonna try to think about
wearing know i apologize i'm gonna take
away
so yeah boop then did you
i never mind i didn't hear it
either never oh yeah i didn't hear
it so i saw my friend john
and i were walking down the street
and i said let's go in the
store let's go into this story that's
such a funny now i'd like to
see what's going on and here i
don't even know what the store was
at that point because we still walking
towards it sure oh meaning you didn't
know what this the the signs
yep didn't know what size so you
just saw a store and you thought
you'd go in it i saw a
pretty lady and i did oh i'm
going for sure okay so you you
were like hey what if we went
into this store exactly played a real
right right right yeah i told i
would do that and so i walked
in she was my little
shoes
i mean i mean i did walk
into stores but no but i'd be
like i wouldn't allow my pre nineteen
years old i'm gonna pretend i'm doing
something so she used behind like a
big wound up jack in the box
just behind the counter oh okay and
um i started talking to her what
if you saw her and then you
went into that store and then you're
she's nowhere to be found
then you wound up the jack-in-the-box and
she popped out just like ah yeah
what if that huh
i saw you looking at me what
would i that would you know when
you have sex in the shirt weather
or not we would have shared it
um you always need the shirt so
i started talking to her yet come
without this shit
in the process of talking to her
i broke a toy i was on
the counter oh no what are you
doing my neck started to get stiff
so i am popping it you're punching
the air yeah l this guy's nuts
i'm crazy i'm my dad is my
he's like don quixote
tilting at windmills residents spanish class which
i feel like is she challenging we'll
see and i can't imagine anything you've
had eleven days ah a book in
spanish central ponza it was hard i
spent oh yeah what's windmill in spanish
you think i know
he came up so many times in
the book and now it did um
he's always going to that windmill he's
always going inside on being like check
out this the square footage in this
i can power my nike with this
i was on the bachelorette i'd fucking
hear yeah that's one thing that you
can think of when you think of
windmill is all i know
is did they come up a lot
on now there's just only fucked four
times in one windmill and the dad
did one and that yeah and the
guy's dad was like yeah that's my
boy he was like yeah son that's
so nasty to care about your kid
o reporting for duty
oh my god and how did you
convince all linda to be your wife
as you are really lost we so
while i was talking to her i
broke this toy that was over the
counter and she said progress toilet
sorry i'm going through the ships through
a hard book that's what i study
i use your bathroom
emergency she started talking to
part of your plan was a functioning
toilet and the wind so straightforward i
was the stores four inches long this
guy swagger
one two
it's one of those two i'd have
to hold down for a long time
and you don't know that the first
time you flush it oh nothing goes
down and then you wait for it
to refill
so don't you hate that so nears
it's like the right flush anyway i
hit so um oh god it's funny
we focus focus choice she was making
cloudy to give reviews to our own
bits
want to talk about that enough yeah
they don't talk about it enough
i shared desert about a discourse about
it do you think it is not
just there should be nobody's articulating what
happens when you flush an old toilet
it sort of pulls one piece toilet
paper down but not your shit and
then you don't see the way they're
so good you're waiting to stand up
to me wrong in front of a
fucking guy
oh me oh okay i end up
now this is your first five and
you're and you're waiting for it to
go down yeah and everyone knew
wow need everything is what happened this
is someone's house
like a standard would maybe you have
a metaphor i'm getting to set up
huh okay it's just like when when
um oh no
i wanna hear this i would actually
like to see this thing
no forget it i don't get nothing
oh so bright and isaiah i would
do this so i broke this item
on the counter she made fun of
me in a very funny way taught
it was very hot you piece of
shit it was very yeah it was
just that funny hey you piece of
shit and so um i went back
i went back in
or again i think few days later
a week later something like that and
i asked her out on a date
wow when she say she said yes
and where did you go to the
day how did you move in together
we went to okay what order should
i
do my verse my first we what
was your question where do you go
i can't remember the name of the
place it was someplace on south street
where we both weren't didn't have a
funny name no no you didn't go
eat it like um two in the
pan is worth one in the cup
or something
what do they serve there
only path to in the past or
the one in the cup um um
um ah now why did i agree
to this oh god i'm so terrible
is daddy oh my god do i
still get my ten dollars
you wish why did my friends make
me
um i mean so it was a
restaurant it was restaurant we ate on
a patio is called marie calendar's know
if only take forty oh my god
there's goats she shuffled off this mortal
coil after every calendar last day we
ever saw lord i just know as
much spit my water out why didn't
you it's your house because i don't
want to
my own house huh i do it
in yours fuck
so um scott just say boo scott
did you just say boo let me
check
no ooh yeah well is that is
like testing my mouth out to see
like oh let me check
any notes let me check i say
that oh bungee and the first date
oh shit while were you thinking i
don't want to shit later i'm gonna
eat just this one thing yeah i
had a salad
so a so so i don't remember
what we ate there's a million years
ago my parents remember with aid and
they're on their first day what else
do they have to remember marry her
that's true why you only remember if
you marry someone yeah um the first
time judy and i had did i
knew exactly what we well because it
became important because you're i do know
where we were cool update where do
eat sushi and tap a restaurant worthy
sushi waiters tap dance oh are you
just gonna say that it's a joke
and the truth that is the
true no that's really stupid i know
they've been closed they've been closed a
long time so yeah it's it's a
sushi place they tell me door we
still go into the ocean like
all the
although it the sea
we still go in there all the
time because it's right next to the
comic bookstore but didn't know it's rockin
sushi so it remains sushi huh that
mike and i ate at a burger
place in silverlake that's now closed johnny
rockets called ah ha or something um
ha ha the band it was good
it will yeah so so so this
whole my first roommate by the way
so this remains isn't good i have
like ten we have earned the same
take forever we counted romantic relationships that
was that was the first time i
lived with a stranger how exciting though
move out of your parents houseman suddenly
you're living with some old broad well
first she had a roommate who we
did not like each other oh so
that was your chats could have been
your first ways right well i stayed
over her place more and more and
then attacking my roommate was annoy
a who's the word technically talking roommates
which means you had two people be
your first roommate
i don't know i don't think so
because i didn't live there we eventually
made it together when when when harumi
was oh okay okay so that person
does not count as a roommate oh
my god that was a close one
that would have been scary but she
was kind of person where she making
it very clear like get the fuck
out of here
yeah pretty much one time she one
time she and i were alone in
the apartment and i was washing the
dishes because i was very paranoid about
being there alone and just like hanging
out or whatever things like watching tv
biden yeah yeah my undershirt so here
like do here so sure are you
sure you're just hanging out i was
just hanging out either way she'd give
me a key
and so either i was with her
or she had just laid out his
shame i was the roommate i'd hate
this too yeah of course just some
guy yeah some brando yes me though
i know
oh my god no she did not
like me and that made me not
like her yeah which seems her yeah
and that is fair she so i'm
washing the dishes she goes look
i don't like you and you don't
like huh i don't think i've ever
had that convo with anyone like why
isn't it then why are we talking
about it like what is the bible
but yeah was her solution was down
to like let's just be polite to
each other it's like i thought that's
what he's willing to write for you
opened your yeah maybe she was just
hating the tension so much of the
situation that she was like let's just
acknowledge that it's bad and that way
we can all just i would respect
more if she was like look i
don't like you you don't like me
so let's fix this let's hug that
wouldn't feel that would have been nice
yeah don't pick let's talk let's drop
it or she pulled out the big
shirt oh well you'd have to go
in
i'd have to it's just what it
is so she she trapped me by
the way if people don't know yeah
so she she went by she fell
by the wayside did she stay at
that place and your girlfriend moved in
with you i think she moved out
first and then my girlfriend i got
a different place okay and how long
were you roommates this will be the
last piece of information we need we
were
we're roommates for one year one calendar
year and you broke up and your
anniversary
yeah on the restaurant that surprised
alright well that's a great first roommate
your anniversary did you celebrate it or
and then break up
i don't remember what your anniversary would
have been it would have been the
anniversary of you living together not your
anniversary of ways we let me go
whenever you celebrated an anniversary and then
gone this isn't working actually know what
we did not live together we we
were together for about a year and
we lived together for a little less
than oh okay this is different so
you were to
gather for about a year media broke
up before the anniversary meaning you didn't
want to buy her an anniversary gift
and so you broke up with her
scott you've figured me out wow was
cheapskate your your eyes and you're small
there's been thrift i'm thrifty yeah any
relationship it's cheaper yeah and i did
yeah many times
yeah that was that was the apartment
where i famously tree we had like
a loft bedroom oh yeah you're famous
for this this is just i mean
la cite your netflix question yes this
is and so i'll just do the
special forbidden grape there was a light
light switch for the upstairs bedroom and
there's a light switch for the hd
downstairs hallway and so i was going
to turn them off and on simultaneously
because you were scared of the dark
terrified yeah and that has not changed
yes please don't turn the lights out
and yeah but how often do you
run up or down stairs in your
alone or in pairs
like you get scared at your house
and like run around a corner or
something
ah
lori go to sleep
don't just take a look now thought
to happen during weekend carry a segment
now i'm saying when i was little
i would get scared of the basement
and so like run up the stairs
because like things were gonna definitely gonna
grab my ankles as i was wrong
haha yeah every once in awhile at
my own home i will have a
moment of ooh i've just been like
what if there is a ghost and
i'm like did you see boot no
yeah she said ooh i heard her
say i think i said ooh so
wait so you turn these lights on
and i touched both switches at the
same time yeah and completed the circuit
between oh no what was it like
really real and i was like frozen
they're like ooh you were electrocuted like
cartoon way way you can see my
sky this happened
because i was touching these two switches
at the same time we so i
was nowadays you could probably still get
the probably you could do it yeah
but back then yeah they didn't dan
figured out light switches yet i mean
technically i don't know i could not
tell you the exact physics of that
or what i yeah but do you
but can't i won't wow you have
to earn it
please will you believe i'm using that
for freedoms anniversary yeah remember what we
first ate
when did we first eat on there
for show ah well we have a
record of it so that's right yeah
let's really talk about eaten since yeah
that's right that's the record the record
submitted to the library of congress but
that was a great first roommate thanks
because we have to take a break
and then we'll get to and nice
first room like expiring segments a roommate
special roommate around up and i hope
they're not
listening oh they are okay are you
still in touch with her i'm not
she came to a show of mine
in philly a handful you're like two
thousand and seven two thousand and six
something like that i she and her
husband came i was blown away i
hadn't seen her in so she didn't
tell you she was coming i know
john toshack out there in the front
row kind of like seconded up
she of course already ma'am you be
gorgeous
she i was doing a signing after
the show like merc signing oh and
she came up and she was like
my tisch she came out
this one to sign my sender to
first fifth
my sister wires you make it alright
we're gonna take a break
good thing a very will be a
bit
we're back
whoa we're back and now it's time
for more of a rooming re round
well maybe early something else ie should
it be a song i thought it
was definitely a song i thought was
inspired by restaurant roundup so my recap
really recap restaurant race roundup roommates reminiscent
review from a rv
view do we want to burn review
my review because we're not reviewing them
know made reminiscent reminiscence and then it
goes like this roommate reminiscence roommate reminiscence
roommate reminiscence ruminate on that
wonderful beautiful like lodge of my first
really was at college now i lived
in the dorms for one year this
was before you were a babysitter know
i've been a baby since i was
twelve oh okay before you were a
movie star yes it was in college
as a college student babysitter but the
bar when you break the toilet ah
so day one wow okay anyway i
moved into the dorms at depaul university
dormitory i lived in university hall of
one cares funny that you vader would
have a great friend who is depaul
you demand
um and i was randomly assigned to
roommate and this is this person could
you could you request one if you
knew people more and i you know
what i i didn't i had a
guy friend who was a close friend
at the time he went to the
same school but i don't think i
had any one of our friends
i could have lived with but i
remember thinking about other people i knew
who did that at different schools like
they're not going to branch out like
i had this idea that it was
good tuesday was a stranger however looking
nice huh
that would've been really cool to live
with a friend and have a great
time yeah um and just know who
they are and not hello the other
side of that is it could have
maybe damaged the friendship yeah yeah oh
yeah you'll see why it's to my
roommate roll okay fudge here while my
first one so then her name was
heather and she was ah nice girl
from where was she from i
i wanna say minnesota so minnesota in
the silver spoon little blue moon men
on the moon neil armstrong buzz aldrin
we lived in a very small room
it was smaller than the room we're
in now definitely probably half the size
maybe well i mean oh no it
was a really small recorder i had
a loft bed with desk under it
and she had her bed with a
desk next to it and could you
pick or pick what loft i paid
i paid to have a lot better
actually because because i wanted to maximize
my space yeah yeah sure so i
can have a chair so it was
extra thatcher and i had a low
mini-fridge um yeah and i share them
any friendships at all for you we
must have shared it gotta hope so
i can't imagine that but that makes
a mini fridge and even more mini
fridge yeah it does when you're sharing
it we had a microwave on top
of that when you have a mini
fridge and they called that order it's
appropriate for it in the dorm they
had is like a sweet but it's
not really it was just that two
rooms were next to each other and
they shared a bathroom so everyone had
like everyone had to share a bathroom
with two others two other people so
for the people yeah this is for
girls nude and one bathroom we know
we're never knew together
and i don't you know i am
the first day i met the two
other girls and we were getting along
fine and then they asked me if
i was going to church and i
said no and then we never really
talked to go no no no yeah
it was it a religious school or
while deploy is a catholic school but
i
yeah i don't subscribe my mom went
to paul it was just like ah
okay so they they thought everyone there
was going to be religious and then
you come in and you're and i'm
a heathen right but i don't think
not it was but yeah i know
a famous so is it related you
know like the three of them yeah
i sold my soul and yeah yes
because they live a godly life and
lauren lives here and yeah town of
pedophiles and see
and right it's true but um ah
they were all very nice though but
we just didn't connect and then heather
was my roommate and she was also
very nice but she had her best
friend who she chose not to live
she chose not to live with her
why did she say i don't remember
why they didn't live together but i
knew they regretted it very quickly because
oh they always turned out non stop
and then it
was like i was just like in
the room yeah you'd want me to
not be there of course and i
would weird at at a certain point
could you say like we could just
switch it never crossed my mind you
know i didn't understand how anything worked
i was my first time doing anything
what if you'd gone up to heather's
friend and said look you don't like
me i don't like you lie i
should have switched to be with roommates
with whoever she
that would have been way better um
excuse me but she was like obsessed
with going to like cubs games and
the the to chicago shit and i
dish didn't care about any of that
and i was doing my improv life
with my old older friends you know
all my twenty seven year old mm
male friends who are weird and wanting
to date girls yeah totally weird and
you know great but they're telling you
how cool you are you're actually really
good
i was no do you think that
you would never know you were eighteen
when you're very you're very you're like
an old soul so so disgusting but
anyways i she ah you know it
was one of those things where we
just never really bonded and there was
one night where um we got a
note on our door and i was
so
someone had tug i think they gave
us people were giving out awards like
someone just made them up and it
was like cleanest room or something okay
and we got that oh you guys
got cleanup listeners i was braced for
the worst yeah no but i was
really stoned or some shit i came
home like i was no i was
really stoned and she didn't know that
the tombstone
was told she didn't know and i
was like i was extremely stoned and
this we got this note put on
the door and then i open the
door and we saw it and i
couldn't stop laughing so that was the
funniest thing for cleaning through yeah because
did you know this was happening know
anyways i got random note on the
door sir you win clean israel okay
it's like really
alright i would like to know like
that newer say so note to say
but then she started laughing when we
both concepts but that was like a
one positive memory i have the time
we both wish laughing really hard at
how weird it was that's the bomb
the last time i know that that's
happened that's the absolute best thing in
the world yeah you got a note
yeah when you can't
stop laughing at stuff when when you
and someone else cannot stop laughing and
you just keep like reignited about it's
the best and she came to see
an improv show with her with her
friend and they are both like um
supportive more know that we're both like
cool or like you're trying to be
hot going to the bars like they
they live that lifestyle is very yeah
there it was where they would do
their makeup for you
yeah yeah half before going out yeah
i can get way and you only
do it three born twenty yeah no
but they would get like it's fucking
hammered from my memory okay um and
i will give a stone go do
my own thing now that was a
different life but she would be around
people who are really drunk is really
different you know and i never really
cared for drinking that much and they
they would just get wasted don't yawn
and
and ah what was i going to
say oh yeah yeah improv show and
then i was like i solidified my
status as a weird person dude i
mean yeah they did the yellow dildo
factory april hi i don't think they
did but i think it was ah
than a just saw my life a
little more it was too much but
now i wonder if they see you
in
cancerous and go like oh that makes
sense yeah she actually i googled her
like a couple of years ago and
she was married and lives she was
in the news because her murdering someone
or wedding her in her wedding happen
like this number toledo or something like
a weather event no dirtiest room and
they know you got married and it
was a torrential downpour oh wow like
a news story because it was interesting
this wedding was ruined but also interesting
and she lives in a lane and
wow you guys should get together you
should be room
aids now how does seem that is
gonna circle yeah she's perfectly nice we
just never spoke again after we ah
you know no you should be roommates
this don't look in your eye like
this is a good idea is what
if what if what if though you
guys oh good we're joking about but
no this is not a bad idea
for a television show you put a
law
off but over you put a celebrity
you may emily with their first roommate
how is that good for a week
for a week that's a horrid idea
i think it's not for week i
think it's for you don't know how
long it's going to be it turns
out it's a week so to me
it could be like opening three hundred
no amount of changes based on how
you perform
i'm in the games that you don't
realize you're playing okay so you can
yeah you can get out of there
earlier if you if you do everything
you know this is a good idea
for show this is a really good
idea this is a good idea for
a show do you say okay so
we didn't so so it's been five
minutes fun it was empty for like
an hour okay nah it's another five
minutes here we go
hi i've been watching the the real
worlds reunion route oh i watched that
okay finished shit that what was that
on the new york one or that
it's terminal but yeah are they eating
all of them it's if we ever
people know they're doing every season oh
they also say i was just starting
lie got up first one i just
started watching the second season with yeah
delay i don't really remember and it's
making me depressed because it's making me
realize that human being you are essentially
don't change well the first one i
thought that was kind of a nice
take away almost like how some of
them were still how they were there
was something kind of nice well what's
nice about it with the firm
first season is is that their spirit
hasn't been broken by the world or
whatever like yeah it's like oh wow
there's still fun or whatever but everyone
in the second season they always fought
and they kicked out people in it
they're exactly the same and having the
same argument damage it's likely you can
go by that though i think people
i think people can change if they
want to change but did you think
and you yelled at twenty years ago
you'd still want to yell at them
oh yeah you know like i know
like people say i didn't get along
with like that i'm like i say
i don't think i'd still act the
way i did but i would still
probably like why i don't think i'm
gonna get along with them right now
right i mean i'd be nice but
i'm saying it's like yeah you wouldn't
want to strike me a friendship so
mean to me it's the thing though
i would thing
if that if we did this show
together which we should just show that
we're doing know the show show where
we know the show where we live
with her oh wait we're doing yes
we're all doing really well finally i
thought it was other people producing here
for winter mean we have to get
to this because what i'm trying what
i'm trying to say is we've barely
spent time on yours lauren i know
what i'm
trying to say is is that i
think the stakes would be lower because
when you live with someone when you're
eighteen or twenty or whatever it's like
everything is so important and like what's
it feels like the stakes would be
lower but then i watched the real
world thing and everyone is fighting immediately
and so it's like this major tv
the same rally and it was like
they
they were on tv together and they
had a lot of their life most
of these people are raised because they
were on that show together yeah exactly
there they were put on tv at
a young age first to remain but
there's my first was i was twenty
years old i went up to theatre
school and it was my friend bryan
we were friends in college we'd been
friends
for two years at that point it
at cypress college in the theater jarant
and ah we he got he got
accepted into the theater program and they
really wanted me to go and i
just sort of let it slide and
was like yeah yeah i don't know
and then i forget what changed
are you thinking you were going to
do at that point i don't not
theater no i knew i was gonna
do theater but i didn't know if
i want to go up to the
school was there to the school so
yeah to the great big school mr
unique
with a big rock wall um but
like a hobo song for the rock
wall and big jim nato i'm really
leaning on all
da da da down da bug pic
yeah but they they accepted him and
then pigment class the fact that he
was going to make me go like
oh that would be cool to to
go up there with him we could
be roommates okay and then they called
me and were like hey you know
they really they they thought they had
a full class but they
they really want want you to come
and someone just dropped out and they
really would like you to to to
be there so i was like ok
i'll go ahead and do it laughing
about ladybugs picnic
so he he and i decided to
be roommates and i remember my dad
drove us up with all of our
stuff in his red pickup truck and
i was in the cab my books
flying out the back
ah no doctor fate number thirty
i was in the cab and bryan
was was in the actual bed of
the pickup trying to do on a
four hour line even have like those
little one one this is nineteen ninety
i mean everyone he just drive in
a separate car he didn't i don't
rely on one one one else could
i don't think i had a car
i don't think he had a car
but he sat for four hours in
a truck bed yeah if you can
believe me guys like that and it
was legal back then yeah on yeah
just being in the back with all
of this stuff like free wine sounds
like god damn so we were we
we got a two bedroom apartment and
i shared one
huh
we shared a bedroom the other bedroom
was just gym well yeah so the
only bit i didn't i think i
didn't know what the time that you
could buy just like a cheap bed
or whatever like that so the only
bed i had was the bed that
i was sleeping on at the time
which was a big sofa bed pull
out which is incredibly heavy and yeah
and so at lee
east it's super comfortable it's terrible so
and it wasn't comfortable and so we
put it in my room and then
attending anyway so uptick and wide when
you put it out it filled up
the entire room so i was like
so i just ended up sleeping on
the couch in the living room you
can just fold up your own thing
into a couch to sleep on it
no i didn't plus i think i
was depressed because i was like yeah
yeah yeah that's like going to sleep
yeah that sounds depressing i was in
the school where everyone hated me he
and i were getting along you because
because i see why hey yeah everyone
hated the teachers i mean oh even
worse um and and so and so
i think i was depressed in my
and my friend and i were fighting
all the time and ah so
so he ended up just going like
fuck this moving out and that was
my first roommate was be lasted two
months yeah really well
a roommate what does it reminiscence you
remember the song ruby ram and nuisance
roommate ram sneeze vanessa wow rumi dicks
i want to know toby to ruminate
on that exact book something like that
ruminate on that but he's a great
guy and he's become friends again
then after yes i think i mean
we we don't you know keep in
touch really but i believe he's out
there in texas and probably still ah
yeah yeah no i not sure i
believe i was on zoom with all
those people recently i think he was
on mentioning that yeah i think he
was hunting or maybe he wasn't but
i can't remember buddy but he's occasionally
written me i'll believe anything
go to
listen if you are on that zoom
let us know if you run that
zoom please let us know we have
to take a break this has been
a great guy anyone who was on
that zoom i want to know more
about the zoom for sure this has
been a great roommate roommate thinks i
gotta say yeah like three great roommates
if you had to live with her
for a week huh
would you
if i had to die
which i would do
yeah outside i wouldn't kill myself i
try to make it work for me
i can't do whatever you hated or
so much yeah i think brian i
could live together for a week it
would be great so is that the
question at the end of every remain
could you live with them again yeah
yeah yeah could you get with everyone
for a week i mean sure because
she's just some girl i don't know
well she lives out here in l
a you probably have a lot in
ca
common we i'd be fine living in
a shared space with her for a
week i'm sure as big as the
place that you originally lived all that
oh that's done that could you live
again with those because i could because
it was a nice big two bedroom
apart i would not be happy in
the small space okay i would not
be happy i don't want to share
that space with
anyone and you share the bathroom again
with some other strangers with the same
two girls they only come to the
bathroom really wanting to time their own
house they're always in there and you
want i should look them up if
i could figure out their names that
would be one thing
i know doing team of one of
the i know i have the first
name of bone marry julian sarah
but it didn't put into google i'll
figure this out putting putting julie and
sarah roommates julian sarah my my old
roommate sort of
julian sarah i shared about him with
them yep alright i don't remember ever
like crossing paths almost like wheat in
my memory it's like watching stream able
to utilize the separately and it never
interrupted each other i don't know if
that's true and alright we'll go to
a break and we'll figure this out
we'll be right back memory boot
and we're back and it's time for
a three cheer oh boy paul a
three church god i know you love
it and lauren i know you love
it too when you're not on your
phone but whatever on there whatever when
you're up for you turn on the
two
right then i was doing something to
help you ah three cheers everyone loves
them we love them the most because
you email him some tissues by the
way
do you mean she really bad know
i can make it through the end
of the episode i give
hey my trough
and this time we're going to do
a reacher that we haven't done before
and everybody's going to have fun oh
my god i want to have fun
i'm excited for the first time in
my life i want to have imax
i wanna know why
this is a mammy list
submitted by adam silca don't we can't
talk over the names adam basilica sucking
it's like a boob
now that time i heard somebody say
i'm a soccer boot swear i heard
some sledding just been imposed
oh buddy did that this is submitted
by adam basilica boop editors called wedding
planners one player approaches the other two
who are competing wedding planners we're not
gonna approach each other we're sitting here
approach though big mistake and yeah actually
approach the first player tells them both
the theme of their web
thing and the other two take turns
pitching on theme ideas example if it's
a pirate themed wedding the bride and
groom have to walk the plank great
that's great alright and then and then
the person picks which one they like
i guess
whatever okay let's do it like for
somebody like like like wedding plans so
they don't pick the one they like
we we have to the wedding planners
have to take turns i just wonder
why it's competing with wedding planners if
there's not going to be the result
of a competition well for sure good
someone says i pick you game over
yeah game over man yeah
okay i'll be the customer okay whoa
wait i'll be the i'm should it
just be a team of wedding planners
and then we we pitch ideas rather
than okay we could do need to
be a competition three cheers don't need
to be a competition actually yeah that
is one of the main roles of
teachers they don't need to be competent
we would need someone to suggest a
theme unless one of us just suggested
a theme
i think what i think one will
come whoa one of us will run
in an approach and approach nova so
one of us will have to run
around the block a couple of times
to really couple of times just to
be method about to work up a
lather that sounds good
alright who is the person getting married
ah scott scott and we're the wedding
planner okay but i thought you said
we're all wedding planners no not at
the same time you just have no
sense of what's that oh i see
it's a team i yes it's a
team i'm also for what you said
when you think we should all play
simple games cat games okay um brave
brave and raven are
and it's here thank you landry let's
do it let's remember what we said
of the mirror to each other we
got this okay hello hi wayman and
landry hi you must be lan no
brave no i can't handicap all the
time i'm braving
your prime land during those last row
and we want to make you the
best wedding of your dreams and all
you need is a themes i need
a someone to get married to as
well no you don't have that you
don't want go that far forward yeah
right no yeah i don't have anyone
to get here but i pick the
date what date it is august
second so you have twenty twenty nine
yeah okay have you really what did
i just fucking say okay hey can
i tell you something check me
this is oh
just because i was gonna protect landry
you're standing in my way
listen let's let's all take a step
saying
major stuff that's on go to the
movies i love okay yeah that's the
same here lead is nah nah but
i want to play to my wedding
as my bride walks down the aisle
okay so so definitely do that will
well download that from youtube okay
we have a youtube still exist in
twenty twenty nine oh i can't imagine
a wood not that long youtube bread
so okay yes give us the theme
this is great it helps us a
lot noah's ark noah's are no other
biblical i look we haven't done a
biblical in such a long time well
the first one we did was virgin
mary read was the virgin mary getting
married
no because i got knocked up and
yeah she wanted to pretending she didn't
have sex with yeah she wanted to
make it like it was a shotgun
wedding reception law but anyhoo so what's
okay so you want to deal with
a theme of doors nora's arc nor
this arc so it's nora ephron marry
a girl named nora as we nora
f
from theme i like the ark two
by two of all the characters of
nora ephron movies that's right too dang
keaton's to alec baldwin let's go let's
go let's go so what movie is
that you're talking um i think that's
a smart person they might be wow
yeah right you're right oh sorry but
we're gonna have to make sure that
no nancy meyers characters are in this
way i have to go
to a different wedding planner none taken
no no no and i never will
make that mistake again in this moment
here's what's going to happen okay
the wedding nora ephron picture this nor
efron is the efficient yes yeah make
it happen huh really i am i
thought she had oh okay like the
tupac yes it'll be two pilots nor
are we actually gonna be more like
when kanye had kim kardashian's father and
whoa i was actually i would prefer
it was him know okay we can
do that
can he mentioned puppies
he mentioned a couple times as many
tv missions this plus okay good then
i think you're gonna be very happy
so he kind of has to say
that very stretch his new thing the
way his mouth moves his new thing
when when he was alive he never
mentioned pcs as far as i can
remember now he's known for saying p
now he's known skechers so the thoughtful
to have the dad cps the hologram
of yeah you're gonna bring someone back
to life with the dead and this
is what i'm talking about
so the hologram robert duffy any tokay
if you pc that's right and the
site quote unquote make pcs
oh thank you okay so robert cardassian
what's the setting though because the setting
behind him is yes levels of an
old boat yeah with troughs of hay
yeah on every level and every human
eats out of the troughs exactly so
you basically push everyone's face into them
and say whatever isn't there some of
them
have animal poop in them okay because
animals don't know what they're doing right
okay so horse backup to a trough
and let a big shit drop in
it so it's just kinda general like
oh i was gonna eat that just
wow my little grains i was going
to eat just the wedding party get
it's own trough or it's just luck
of the draw if you get no
if you want the season the troops
up to you if you want the
wedding party get their own trough they
get a feces free trial
and no one will put your face
into and what's great about this is
it goes from the wedding to the
reception immediately you got a burner well
because the troughs are right behind you
and it's abode it's not that big
yes i mean big enough to contain
two of every isn't an actual voter
we're having this on the water itself
it's actually what it really is
i'm gonna be really honest with you
but please can we just be totally
honest from this point because i feel
like it's weird that i've come in
here and you guys are like yeah
i'm sorry i'm going to one of
us always tells the truth one of
us always lies i'm always like ladbrokes
i wish she was doing i'm looking
at you and i can't lie because
i see your budget i see your
budget very low you pass that piece
of paper over
her to us and said look at
this it was one hundred dollar bill
here's what's going to happen and then
written underneath it said i'll give you
half of this so we're gonna get
fifty bucks to do it so what's
one call a lot of favors i'm
calling a lot of lot of numbers
right one of my favorites from someone
i know who works in set tech
and he's going to make the setting
decoration i'm gonna make our arc but
it's flat it's very truman show
oh ask it's just a flat front
of an arc it's gonna look three
d when you look through the windows
of it it's gonna look like it
continues to hook it doesn't at all
so this isn't really even a boat
it's i'm going to have your family
hanging on with handles behind each window
to look through on the boat okay
i'm gonna say relax look like you're
standing on something but they're going to
be hanging with their arms they don't
like to be told relax
how is it possible for me i
don't think so says fans or not
they're not franky says fans at all
frankie unfortunately does not say relax yes
so they they kind of have a
thing about us relax they'll get upset
yeah they have a thing about that
so i can you just figure out
something else for them to say we
want to work you there oh well
i thought it was a problem they
have
on something i said to this and
they're saying it i'm saying it to
them because i want to need them
to relax landry's frank in the scenario
okay no they don't they leave you
says relax they don't like any words
i do accessing them oh i definitely
r e l a c k s
perfect
okay it's a group that works with
your okay and oh i wanna say
about this one and only tom lennon
i gotta say who me yeah you're
rich i've never i mean what i
do okay you get a big kick
big king how big is this cake
this is the big part because for
me if i got a bit of
a sweet-tooth if i don't leave this
wedding say she
what's your wife's name nora well i
have no idea at this point no
old nora will call her nora but
she can change it to norris that's
important for the day
it's very important that cake is going
to be made of styrofoam and you
won't want to eat it but the
frosting will be real so you can
look at before i kick it exactly
so here's the thing it's a huge
huge styrofoam cake covered in real frosting
you make a big show of it
you and your lovely jar you're not
tom i'm not sure i drove a
tesla but
it's an old one but were you
wearing brown uniform i would say it's
tope already wearing those shorts it's it's
summer tough okay so it's not somebody
to protect somewhere maybe in australia from
from from you're from australia yeah that's
true so ah you you you and
your wife nor i make a big
a show of lick of like scooping
up a big boys care he can
see she's your friend anyway
my first roommate film crews filming you
that says comedy central on the side
that i can tell you okay so
it's just a quitting so
i should say something else now like
heroku who knows anymore yeah oh check
cache anyway so ah you you since
i brought it up no you sound
more like you know i
we're trying to help you so you
scoop a big handful of frosting off
you'll lick it and you say this
is for everyone in just a few
minutes and then the styrofoam cake is
wheeled away and everyone forgets about it
oh okay i love that this is
good not allowed is it how does
it end the apple you know oh
you guys versus sexual or
wow you hadn't been in peace ever
said i love you i've never said
it back we've been friends for years
but just lying here
education way we should be your wedding
so that's a good idea this is
too cheap though oh really what what's
your wedding gotta be well maybe i
can try it for years we just
never knew it was to each other
you got
let me slip this piece of paper
just the same piece of paper i
swear to you that's right get out
of here yeah okay bye
oh and that game with little thing
i call boop and you did say
buddhist that time okay so the other
ones were those weren't real oh boy
did we do it on time but
yeah i think that yeah josh said
yeah he didn't say anything wow
i think we did it guys think
we did it that i was wrong
think we did it that was fun
tastic i don't know how we're gonna
do another one because this is the
last episode of all time yeah you
just you didn't think we could do
another one i take you at your
thirteen coffee we've always said if any
of us never wants to do this
again we'd stop immediately we uses vague
wording has been
yeah i'm out
alright thanks for this oh wait guys
you gotta hear our outros yeah gotta
hear all the sounds through team usa
instagram we have a new intern follow
us on intern ta call is funny
answer zuk huh
yeah man have an intern by this
point i'm still interviewing people and it's
not going well we do need what
time of the year is it as
people are hearing this december
what do we do need christmas presents
the biggest me so go get the
three-day month cpp world dot com it's
know and also stitcher premium payments no
ads here it's free it's fine and
the ads are fun i think it's
december sixteenth is you okay christmas is
coming christmas the geese are getting you
know let's just say they're not skinny
oh we don't say
that anymore we don't comment on cases
appearance anymore okay we just need them
but the geese are hot these are
our god games huh yeah those geese
bread with tuesdays
um so yeah we might have a
christmas we might have a christmas enter
to oh okay christmas i am i
know i need to dive interviewed a
couple people who are kind of christmassy
and i'm just not sure okay they're
not christmassy enough or chinese m de
jingle all the way and i just
don't know if they all they've jiggled
yeah way okay there's a lot of
tests and an interview
steps yeah right i can't get into
it here because then the next people
will be prepared if that's right exactly
yeah you gotta catch em underworld check
us out over there on instagram freedom
usa subscribe to this show listen to
it wherever you can rate and review
yeah and if you want to submit
a three cheer right to hide yourself
from first of that yeah rodgers said
go fuck yourself dot com
go air and turn dot com three
dm usa at gmail dot com yeah
we love america we love them and
that's the one thing i don't know
if we talked about it in this
episode enough but we love america so
much i think we've been downplaying it
i think we need to uplay it
we love america wow fashion maybe to
love america but with the lovelies
um yeah
josh did you see boob
a