three
oh frida welcome to three are we
gonna sing freedom know why why because
for some reason there's a lag when
we sing along huh if you listen
back to the episodes you'd know but
you are fucking what i know it
was just scolding me because i had
my arms crossed and i was a
little tie
tired seeming and he said demon
i say come on and cross your
arms we're about to record three do
it have fun i said i'll do
it when we do it so now
you know i'm having fun you are
frowning so that's one of these guys
who makes you go to escape rooms
every weekend yeah i'm sorry alone and
he insisted you have a great time
and tell them that you had a
great time after yeah well it's
just polite to tell everyone at the
escape room they had a wonderful time
i would like to tell people to
do that
yeah wow guys do you want to
go to escape from this weekend though
yeah
yes it's habit i don't like those
one how about robin room okay where
you don't escape from you break you
try to get into it right yeah
i did wasn't that sort of like
an escape room where you're in one
room and you're trying to break into
getting outside picture that shut up shop
and i want to hear some a
bag of dicks but me too
lips
yeah what's not good run the jewels
um i ok ah i'll take you
and then i wanna hear lauren story
okay okay the break-in room you see
like a little family inside living room
with a little family hello
out of room and how small is
a family is it like you look
through like a pole then you see
like in this little box like a
diorama it's like there's a family in
there this is stupid it's regular sized
people inside a gigantic room that makes
them look tao is an optical illusion
like santa jones boulder yeah it's like
the indiana jones pan am i looking
at it from from above
so it's like no you're peeping in
through the window like a real creep
but i'm the same size as them
yes but you don't think that you
are is it like a porthole situation
where it's gonna sake your regular there
look i think i'm regular yeah turns
out i'm actually a giant they're far
away the room and there here's what
it is they're far away the big
room their regular sized bay looks small
yeah i think i'm normal size but
i'm a junior john you're a giant
they are also giants ever day this
i think they're they're giants the same
size as you a giant but they
think they're little as in littler than
humans eighth they know that upside they
know they know their regular size but
they're pretending that they think that they're
fools
being you and the room is pretending
it's a big room but really it's
a small room full of mirror and
wake up how did you do i'm
scared i was able to solve the
riddle congratulate was it what was it
i think it was ah two times
pi you're right you win the big
prize
lauren tell me your story please i
beg of you i went to an
escape room with a bunch of friends
this was this was probably three years
ago so they're not friends with you
anymore
not all myself and some of them
never got out some couldn't get um
i just well first of all my
friend mary holland is a huge fan
of escape rooms and she goes often
and often
so two times all regularly i would
not have guessed that but i can
see he has a spreadsheet of the
rooms and what the deal is she
shares it with people who are interested
she loves me she returns to decide
this on a podcast so it's not
it's not snitching just telling her she
returns to the same ones all the
time she i don't think so i
think she goes to new ones
all time because what's the spreadsheet of
then all of the different ones in
law that she's been to and yeah
like if it was good or oh
i saying yeah okay i don't know
i've never seen it i don't know
what the scale of how things but
you said she would share it with
anyone who's interested i'm not
she knows i'm interested i saw i
went to one with her this was
before her obsession with them but she
did i think organize this outing with
like ten people and it was um
downtown l a and we were like
in it was like a fake theater
and like then like you know suddenly
were trapped inside wasn't ah it was
a fake theater it was like a
back stage was like a green room
of dressing room of theater and okay
all these props and different things i
just couldn't give myself up to it
enough i think like i'm too competitive
without the skill like it's like there's
like all the things don't line up
for me like you're competitive without the
skills i want to win every game
yeah i want to
when i really want to win but
i don't really know how to do
an escape room and i don't really
care to solve puzzles that much and
so i'm like anxious about how i'm
losing but i have no way to
help and i don't really want to
pretend i'm really trapped here on that
i care because i just don't really
want to and i get that that's
not fun but that's just
what the deal is i don't can
i ask you yeah are other people
like pretending they're trapped and the stakes
are high for everyone i write and
i i just don't have the stakes
i'm kind of like what didn't you
spend money to get in yeah well
there's the stake i mean ultimately ultimately
the stakes are you have to solve
the puzzles in a certain amount of
time yes and i feel
all the pressure of that everyone's happy
we i don't remember actually how it
ended
yeah he was happy we beat it
but i don't remember if we did
i really did i don't beat it
do you just go the same thing
happens you get out of the room
yeah why would anyone want beside and
said it beat us there's there's ah
that's emasculating i think some if not
all of them there's a percentage they
give you the percentage of how well
you did yeah okay and so it's
like if the sooner you get out
the more
x yeah level yeah i just i
like that she likes it i think
it's very fun that she likes it
i just shit competitive yeah i think
so yeah i always think if this
is your thing like you'd have to
be like yeah i think she always
she loves puzzles but you're competitive you're
not competing with the other people necessarily
isn't it supposed to be like a
team and a team you're competing against
against
coggins yourself mortals and god yeah you're
company gets mortals and god i don't
even want to say i think it's
i don't think it's dumb i don't
think it's fine i like that everyone
likes your thing i just don't wanna
be like what do you what do
you like what do you like don't
know why you're wearing a shirt that
says tokyo is my favorite city in
the world you better than this one
yeah why don't you fucking move there
i can't focus speak the language what
can you say in japanese um i
can say this is there's not much
i can say i got though thank
you sam hey um
shall we say or something it's like
what you're saying like walk into restaurant
maybe it means about cover something i
can say i can't say much but
mike is learning japanese and he's got
a lot down easy really yeah how
is he learning it with an app
that really yeah well which one like
duolingo and then also ah he uses
like books and things like like workbooks
cover he gets like graphic novel
oils that are like oh like manga
and stuff like that yeah there are
some that are made for um p
like for i think for children in
japan that like like basic like it's
like a ah this panda runs a
cafe and then like all these things
that happen in the cafe and so
it's like a way for people to
learn the language easily because it's giving
people a crazy idea of what japan
is like because
as well the pan is don't run
the cafe right there for being pet
exactly you got opana cafe and then
they call on the play yeah he's
talking you could go talk to him
all things i can answer no he's
not and here we only have panda
express's yeah we're americans you know you
just want binds and look at a
pan look at ouya one pan to
me
jt is not on my watch would
you do that no i wouldn't eat
anything of any endangered species is it
where you draw the line endangered species
let's say danger let's say their own
endanger know like dogs there's plenty of
dogs oh i wouldn't eat a dog
why not because it's disgusting what do
you why because only chickens are good
to eat and only
cows and i only want to slit
the throat of a pig
you don't want to slit a dog's
throat nope just a smart little pig
if you grew up on a farm
could do you think that you have
it in you to like kill the
things that you would have if i
grew up on the farm i would
but i don't i don't like saying
if you wanted to slit a pig's
throat do you think you would do
it how to tell a different upbringing
with you that all the time as
a child and was totally normalized you
would think that was fine if you
had different feelings than you do would
you feel differently yeah
do you feel bad at all about
eating meat i do sometimes um sometimes
i feel i love it but it
is the problem too i tried to
be vegan for like a week i
was like i'm bored i'm bored bored
i don't feel bad about it weirdly
i don't know why and i think
if i try to eat vegan as
much as i can there
so many options in la that i
feel better when i do but i
don't mind throwing a little bit chicken
in something i have a turkey sandwich
everyone let's come on
reading veal i'm trying to i bounced
out in other ways i don't i
don't use plastic straws xylo i don't
use plastic bags i use my baghouz
i'd like to there's your japanese
oh beggar i tried
i can't speak japanese if you say
op before anything it makes it sound
japanese huh
just put ou at the end of
anything but somebody tawny newsome told me
that that actually does help in japan
is that racist is you well it's
yeah way i'm sorry you know saying
huh
ooh like if you if you adopt
like oh like days which seems like
a ridiculous accent that actually work oh
because they're like you're from another country
you're not american yeah oh yeah what
point is like imitating someone's sort of
tone of speech when is it racist
like if you go to that's a
question because
and here's here's a question ah maybe
we'll cut it out
wow
i mean anything by this and i'm
genuinely wondering i enjoyed doing voices and
like trying to imitate people and if
i was telling a story about going
to spawn the my woman who massage
me was saying very funny things and
she had an accent and i was
doing the accent and i'm like how
is that bad i'm like it's like
if i did it if i said
it an american accent i'm not even
trying to tell the story
with what happened like i'm not i'm
not making fun of how she talks
or saying it's bad or wrong right
i'm saying i think sound like the
same way if i talked a little
kid i might be like oh okay
you know it's like it's just kind
of impersonating to give the thanks some
of the some of the issue is
that especially in the eighties used
being someone's dialect used to be a
way to say they are stupid and
they are less than i was like
oh yeah that's what makes them crazy
yeah oh hahaha they can't speak english
the way we can and it's sort
of been conflated with people who just
like to do accents in the peter
sellars way you know of like oh
and put on
brown face well yeah but but in
the in the sense of like oh
i'm really interested in becoming this specific
person or like the specificity i think
is one like she was being very
funny and like the things she's saying
she's making fun of me and stuff
so it's like to me that makes
the story funnier to tell it how
it was happening i it it i
think it's
like if you if the the source
of your amusement comes solely from this
person trying to speak english yeah that's
yeah that's the problem i never when
i would think right because also if
you travel anywhere else in the world
and you try to talk you sound
very unaired
located yes because you cannot say anything
i just tried to say a word
in japanese i don't think i did
a price on horrible member speaks japanese
think i selling an idiot so like
that's you can't you have to respect
people come to this country and like
our oh my god alignment not you
have to paul i'll tell you will
not do it but i always think
it's so crazy when people like that
the argument of like speaking lose something
it's like the first one is a
very hard language to learn it's very
complicated it's so like even just like
trying does does mike i want to
ask you does he read the japanese
character yeah in this okay yeah i
know i know and he's been he's
not too far
but he can't there's like a there's
you you learned in two different ways
basically he can read this and understand
what the sounds are but not know
ah you know it's like it's there's
like ah there's sounds associated with the
care with the characters and so it's
like syllables a lot of times and
then probably also not sometimes i don't
know enough because i haven't been like
watching him do it but then there
are some points where so he'll know
this character means the sound and these
sounds together mean this word but i
also think there's there's a new ah
another wrinkle to it which i learned
i saw a play the other day
that talked about it with tones yeah
there's several rounds that there's a casual
tone
and like is that in japanese as
well yeah yeah so so like tone
one is ah and tone two is
like ah until three is like huh
and if you say the same word
in different tones it means different things
yeah like i have ah i know
i got that wrong no no no
i know we're trying to like pieces
ceo actual
all nine but it's just interesting like
thinking about that and being like so
these people from that country know this
really intricate like the sting yeah it's
like knowing some sort of like you
know trigonometry or something yeah instead of
language and then we're like complicated and
they don't use pronouns in the same
way they'll just they have like they
they don't make a sentence in the
se
same way we do so like the
idea that someone is supposed to come
here and then understand all of the
intricacies of english which are really complicated
and not like any other language for
the most part and really like have
really weird rules and weird way that's
not based on any of the romance
languages or anything like that yeah like
expecting people to be able to master
that like even just like wait and
height are basically spelled the same but
are completely yeah them exactly yeah just
like the whole i before e except
after c but except on the watching
world yeah yeah yeah none of it
makes me ill enough to bleed all
of three
that's really difficult to understand for a
lot of people but it's like they
gotta know
um oh
one time i went to the montreal
comedy festival juice bar yeah yes i've
been there and i've just career that's
how i said i
just poirier and i'm just here to
rear
i'm just here to rear we're here
we already use yeah we're having a
lot of fun huh
oh right huh just for laughs and
juice career and can't see it at
all is how you say it in
french and doesn't mean the same thing
like is there even an expression just
for laughs you know how like that's
an english expression how you see it
just believe nobody you know what i
mean like a here in america it's
like hey i did it just for
laughs that's like an american expression when
you
translated exactly are people like what the
fuck outta yeah just for laughs yeah
it's like it the closest and french
is like i've betrayed my country yeah
why laughing why did you do this
but jail alchemy wednesday so they had
i you know been there for years
many years in a row and and
they changed hotels at one point and
so the in the new hotel there
was a it was ah attached to
like a shopping center so there was
a food court and i had just
gotten off the plane and checked in
and and first
they were doing this for a while
like every year because it's festival is
huge and montreal i don't think they
have room service there either well at
this they used to they used to
they used to and then um they
were doing this thing where because it
was such a big festival and all
everyone for the connected with festival stay
at this hotel they
the hotel staff would go on strike
oh right oh yeah this was like
three years in a row they did
this knowing the busiest yeah yeah i
was there during the right so the
first year eve the first year that
they did the strike i was like
i got a waste well that is
striking his name i left for france
yeah to win so i went down
to this food court
rt to get something to eat and
cross the picket line
yes you don't really care about jeff
you eat you are crossing the picket
there was no picket line by the
way oh yeah that yeah they're just
gone yeah i don't know yeah i'm
not sure why i feel like i
ordered the when it happened i ordered
room service and then it never came
what's going on and they said although
oh right we should have told you
this yeah we should yes exactly
like oh yeah here's the explanation why
this was never going to happen but
i acted like it was going to
so i went to the food court
and everything was in french yeah and
i it was the weirdest you start
to panic i've been nitration tell where
it's slow stupid holy shit what do
i it's you know who are they
author speaking layers everyone who speaks english
and french and that's why i also
feel inferior when i go there because
they'll be speaking in french oh yeah
they're geniuses there's like oh yeah can
talk with you like what some have
been americans yes well it's just unfair
it's unfair that we're so stupid here
in america is a piece of shit
i felt so ignorant and so pr
eventually honestly so wrong that um we
don't teach a secondary language in elementary
school yeah you can go in your
promissory label formats you need it when
you're a baby beyonce and that's why
you know ah if we have a
child we're gonna make sure our nanny
speaks you know several different languages
and only if
well my ira my nephew is ah
bilingual because he was raised in elgi
germany q
get you through it
he was raised in germany and he
ah from an early age when he
was like a weirdo he was like
a toddler like a real dad
he asked me to cut off his
penis trying to surface
the classic german
oh here is a drunk weird also
i just want to show your american
explain here explain the genesis of that
because it's something that you hear about
it did one guy want that to
happen is that it's a common thing
i keep hearing like there was a
guy on the equivalent of craigslist in
germany maybe it is crazy maybe
yeah i think it went with a
k yeah yeah okay craigslist he took
out an ad oh i think i
remember that looking for someone to do
this and someone took them up on
it and then there was a trial
where the guy would think they'd be
boiled down to like well isn't it
if did he die did he tell
you lose all the oh yeah is
it
murder what he died i i believe
the gentleman died yes because he just
from cutting off a penis out of
his dick or um a day from
bleeding out of his decoy is because
these races watch v p fell out
of a pp fell out of the
pie hello rod are all his pd
fell out
you could allay what jack jack what
did he cut off the pitas and
then just pee and semen fell out
of the hole i hate you so
loud yeah it just was like i'm
honestly ron paul's like what four hours
later i draw the line no it's
just like a water gel water balloon
breaking just like
um my cousins speak lithuanian my lithuanian
side and my dad speaks with william
but he didn't teach it to us
when we were kids which of your
societies lithuania your identify society my society
said society she's assigned studio and i
understand him not doing because my mom
doesn't speak lithuanian and whenever i like
my other relatives married people who also
spoke with nanos more in the household
or your mom and dad both between
you know now my mom is greek
greek oh that's um but i like
um and thinking i ah
and feel like oh it's been so
cool if i had learned that as
a kid because i would have two
languages and then that already opens you
up to learning a third lithuanian based
on another layer of its closely it
sounds like i don't i'm probably only
wrong with this but like to me
it sounds like polish or like it
has more in that realm right right
um so yeah you could have learn
earned one of those languages yeah ah
it's too late now too late now
i took spanish for seven years and
seven in high school which seven from
like sixth through twelfth but it's not
enough do you how fluent are you
i can't understand ah i can read
and like understand a good amount of
spanish like if i saw like a
bill
lord i know what it says or
like someone by the way chevron tried
to just fool a phone and he
threw it at him and i um
i can like if i'm overhearing something
i can like pick up pieces oh
they're talking about what time they're going
to do something or whatever but it's
like i wouldn't if the conversation gets
more complicated wow working as a waiter
for ten years i became
and and i had taken three years
spanish but i became relatively like able
to have a conversation yeah or understand
what they were talking about you know
um but it's not something where if
i went to mexico i would be
able to know when i'd feel really
self-conscious if i were trying i did
go to mexico and i was like
really afraid use my spanish because i
just don't want to sound dumb and
that's another thing too it's like when
you
think of people coming here who actually
have studied but they're just uncomfortable or
afraid trustee right yeah there's probably a
lot of that too do you think
people then this is sort of my
original question with languages do you think
people in other countries appreciate when people
are trying like i found this when
i go to mexico are or when
i was in costa
rica like people appreciate you trying to
sound trite trying to like almost i
feel like i'm sort of doing an
impression like like but they appreciate and
they like it yeah they're always like
they always laugh and they always like
it yeah it's a smile on their
face and sometimes they'll cut to the
chase and talking english to give you
a break but right i think like
when i
went to france there was a i
had an interaction that was like i
was with somebody who was kind of
refusing to do that and like it
was the person like the woman who
was working at the shop was like
hating it right and then like refusing
to do what to try this to
try oh okay i don't even like
ordering that's what you hear like when
i went to france too i heard
heard that that's that if you don't
try people are angry at you and
that's not but that wasn't my experience
i witnessed that but i really when
i was doing it myself i usually
try or like even it's like it's
it's it is hard to do but
that's also part of what makes traveling
so great as i was saying son
i was talking to my ah
puppy owe it to the attention
at first clear my throat but then
i did so
for me it made me laugh but
yeah that's what i would resort especially
winding down i look here you're going
yeah there's something yeah
point of order
so well you did jay went to
paris and i would i would try
to at least say hello in french
first to like sort of like yeah
good example look i'm gonna i'm gonna
say this so i'm trying to me
one book i'm trying to be played
but i this is as far as
i can go yeah this interaction but
like i remember
we're going like mosher elfie
just think about this people don't in
america we do not expect we expect
people to say hello you if you're
in a store you'd be up for
a foreign person's not gonna walk in
and say hello in their foreign language
huh we're winning we walk into other
countries and go hello hi yeah just
walk in and like lasers like there
is a part of what i've shown
like to me was
is that the presumption of of just
like we're american we know english the
most important thing right so you should
speak so here we keep like a
french person doesn't walk into a store
in american go bonjour did ah sorry
yeah yeah just in their language just
because that's what they are yeah we
we do that so rudely yeah so
let's say i didn't want this right
yeah right yeah and and but i
there was this coffee shop around the
corner from us and we would you
know fresh-made
so you had milk milk and lemonade
and then you went around like we
had in the place where we were
staying had two servings of milk one
serving of lemon right yeah like yoda
was fudge
i love the milk what if there
was a restaurant that just remember those
three things that was on the german
name and you had to order it
all what i really needed some well
you'd have to go around the corner
yes or no and it was it
was around the corner yeah and you
ordered around the corridor like when you
go on the e and then you
ordered there and then they communicate through
a walkie talkie i guess now
no clue
or the internet probably sounds good i
always going oh also ah i get
some fudge with that yeah around the
corner
so go there in the morning to
get a coffee and pastries sure and
i would ah checks out
you've read my life my pleasure yeah
no yeah so i would order ah
ah the palm too shallow ah and
then i was never prepared for follow-up
questions yeah that was yeah so it
always be ah bez you play ah
do panchkula
and then they would speak back to
something about wow milk you want but
i don't feel like oh no but
i found everyone very friendly there after
ok because i was trying to go
up so that there as well in
in restaurants i would be like on
my phone looking up what words men
and stuff in the end then the
waiter would see i'd go oh no
let me speak english for you and
tell you you
you know like i found everyone very
like accommodating i agree that was just
one notion and the person i was
with was not being right and great
we were we were someone was rude
to us in one place where there
for a week and only one place
with somebody ruthless one in this bar
and um it was empty and we
a friend of mine told me you
gotta go to this bar it's great
and it was totally empty and so
we went up to the bartender and
said i you are you open and
the guy was like yeah like we
had wild yeah yeah one thing like
okay that's where but what was so
terrible was it was called the american
bar ah okay very likely it was
like a bait and switch can i
just say died
coy bride one like that as well
where buddy was closed and they were
mad at us for trying to come
in oh it was very weird okay
what's the phone before okay before the
break when we got chevy and what
did you show in la he locked
your phone logged on locked bro were
on lock here on what do we
got you always just a bit of
trivia or something chevy trivia this is
far
following armin may always arm and may
was pointless already he can't read he
there were so great as there's a
pronunciation key for the name and i
can't read the pronunciation key like no
idea how supposed to say that you
don't know i'm sat down e means
he's a german shuai
he is a deep she was a
german his his birthday was september and
december first what are we talking about
hover december was away going to tell
you we're talking about the penis guy
oh yeah okay i'll shut now i
use a german computer repair technician who
achieved international notoriety for killing and eating
a voluntary victim whom he had fought
for
found via the internet after he and
the victim jointly attempted to eat the
victim's severed penis because they were going
to eat it together in a conversation
where they had armin killed his victim
and proceeded to eat a large amount
of his flesh because of ex oh
he is also known as the rotten
bird cannibal or der metzger meister
the rotten burt cannibal rotten bergh o
roddenberry rot like i said with a
real rotten borough that's i think what
you call a seventeen is the rotting
berkeley ca ranbir once a penis has
an attached shiny anymore it's colorado is
also known as the master butchers and
you're gonna be a whole thing about
learning a bobbitt oh i hope so
oh i hope
so she's doing a tribute and i
think yeah alright we need to go
to break a concert okay we'll come
right back okay bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye we love you poor
thing about lorena bobbitt
we are back what do you want
to know la lane ababa why do
you think they're doing something with her
maybe something lifetime them together doing like
a show or something yeah tell me
jordan peele's interview with her now that's
what it was yeah jordan peele's producing
it that's what it is it's like
the lorena bobbitt files are so high
i'm curious like how did it feel
kind of curious i guess i want
to hear her talk about that do
you like to chop it do you
fantasize about that you know right oh
god chevron's like it's a doc series
jordan peele and amazon are making a
lorraine ababa documentary series umm umm fmm
four part documentary series about the virginia
woman who made headlines after she cut
off the penis of husband john wayne
bobbitt with a kitchen knife in ninety
three and threw it out a car
window that's the funny part did you
throughout the whole yeah hey just like
she was taking she decided okay we
are like you know what i don't
need this i just want to go
far she wanted to go far away
from him she was physical
ali and thermally abused abused by him
and he also cheated on her she
says um play a little peel said
she said peele says here's why jordan
peele wants to make this when we
hear the name bobbitt we think of
one of the most sensational incidents to
ever we can catapulted into a full
blown media spectacle with this project lorena
has a platform to tell her
truth as well as engaged in critical
conversation about gender dynamics abuse and her
demand for justice this is lorraine a
story and we're honored to help her
tell it okay wow i'm in i
don't fantasize about that i don't think
that's interesting or cool she actually did
ask me that
ah you think this is going on
something like oh actually i don't fantasize
about that
not really often i don't i do
know people who think that's like really
like oh that's like the ultimate i
just it was like a common thing
in eighties movies and stuff like yeah
we want you to shut up wrong
you know cut your nuts off yeah
maybe rodney dangerfield saying hey boy showed
up on kitchen nook so that's okay
yeah it wasn't teeing you up for
your thank you i appreciate it who
else you want me to do right
into it like this leary
hey everybody ford trucks cut your nuts
off dennis miller that's jackie i thought
a chance you just start with if
not dennis miller does larry you told
me no no what's around you start
with before wow hey r i don't
know i was trying to do rosie
o'donnell to be i was trying to
do okay i have
i had this what a reveal i
have a i have a thing in
my mind of surah shady residental you
know what's that movie where she and
and dan ackroyd are undercover at the
sex east of eden east of eden
okay so i'm on the v h
s cover with like her like bondage
gear yeah yeah yeah so i just
always remember walking past said blockbuster every
week from hola and it
looks hilarious i looked close i never
saw it i just have an impression
of one of the lines and there
was like a servant coming up to
rosie o'donnell saying i'll do anything for
you madam she's like paint my house
oh that's an old joke yeah so
i just and it's garry marshall jam
isn't it he yes and he and
penny marshall appear in the movie as
a married kobe row is as well
oh maybe that's the one i'm thinking
of oh okay oh well sick anyhow
sick and fucking grow are you do
you have a fondness for the movie
hocus pocus i love it i've never
seen it shit every year i don't
think i don't think it'll appeal to
you i think it's because a generation
young child yeah i think you had
to watch it when you were a
kid or it doesn't do anything like
i've shown to people who did not
see it as a kid and they're
just like okay
like it just it is it is
a nostalgic thing i feel like we've
talked about it on my show about
the male reboot hook is broken
it's just being broken for focus and
notice
broke as before hocus
i never focus
what does that boat facebook raucous you're
in the crook and the
congratulations you're in the red crocus know
what is supposed to be here in
the rear beer before liquor never sicker
signature familiar in the clear okay that
there was some poker in the front
liquor in the rear there's so many
funny what are you teaching me
i never thought there would ever be
a podcast where you said both if
there's grass on the field play ball
oh he's saying no you you need
to say that
if it can bleed it can bring
fifty i said it's old enough to
old enough to what you said is
horrible i said old debate doors grass
on the field play ball that's very
similar to what paul's that yeah foul
he didn't say it was in your
head you want to say it's the
same fucking dad why are you staying
related baseball related so you're saying if
who got a bald pussy you can't
play ball old enough to sit at
the table old enough to eat well
but oh like the thanksgiving grownup stable
yeah exactly yeah that's what it means
i can't do this with you guys
while since your last episode judah
ah leave me here i'm not i'm
not going anywhere don't worry what did
you hear that oh god not the
problem here hey hey wait am i
the problem here
i don't know him the problem here
it's a problem i the market dip
problem here but the book
that's sure that's ah
so every one of our shirts has
today that's a but i'm back that's
so sure that's for sure dogs that
just are the jerk
i'll check member twenty four he became
such a great catch phrases are things
we kick clear yes they're all from
thing yeah we've never said an original
thought were dumb and um i'm the
fat jew well yeah i can reveal
it now by the way that's a
reference to someone on the internet yeah
you're not you were saying i'm with
a fat jew i was to z
fetch
ok cool but you are like an
i'm the the dumb one or some
would you like command the fat jew
of the that's what it sounds like
oh it's a joke and better if
it was a fat jew like he's
not v fatu he's just a i
think it was two e's in thee
i would like to think about the
fat jew and i of course i'm
saying at the fat jew the yes
twitter and
instagram personality of in quotes because it's
a meme um i don't know if
i'm impressed or inspired or neither i
think um mean collectors don't have much
chin
brain for introducing respect or interest
full movie the meme collector merchant ivory
film so gorgeous i you know i
love a meme as much as the
next person but i want to be
passed to me from a friend don't
even account that's how i get my
meat from friends friends my family i
don't need to subscribe to one meme
person if a friend passes me a
friend's meme i'm inhabit
a memes will eventually stop or i
mean a meme is just a place
your heart makes it's a meme
but i mean it means zona draw
a very dear friend of mine was
like it's a meme in the earliest
days like it's pronounced yeah yeah it's
pronounced meme i know but no but
not the way we use it but
yeah who gives a shit because we
all say it now yeah we like
and it's more fun to say meme
than ma'am ma'am isn't stupid way to
say it it's stupid because
it's not short for like memory write
short for like memetic something isn't it
rare yeah yeah and so when any
eyes yeah what does the actual
yeah short for remembered projector memorize put
him on this he effected them he's
my doctor my doctor my guy no
my have to go on tv and
spread it
i noticed that dr pepper for him
didn't notice you to diagnose or just
hey why did i you go on
tv and spread your notice me yeah
what is this if this was bad
what if that was his wife like
wow i got dough i got horrid
spread reddit for you to notice me
i love memes and their founders if
you gotta
it's speaking to hook his brokers if
you could have one magic power of
the traditional magic powers that which is
how are they are the witch's hat
okay so slight in visibility they're flying
on a broom flying well yeah okay
rahm tak lam specific cackling that's one
of their magical powers casting spells
cooking in oil but casting spells we
got to get more specific because that's
too jackass loss if excels okay that's
good casting love spells that's probably what
i'm turning people into things i would
want to cast a love spell making
things would always know i made that
person look million would that be great
if like what you could make like
someone
terrible fall in love with someone great
why would i want to do that
oh no
it's great yeah i don't know i
would like to wonder you would put
your love in the world
like you don't want to terrible people
to fall in love they'll just be
terrible but isn't the great person falling
over the unlucky ter here saying like
kellyanne conway and her husband you know
which one is great which was terrible
but let's for history to decide but
they obviously disagree doesn't do he's like
a lawyer guy here's my question you
don't pick my thread that's not a
question
that's a command i thought it was
for everyone no here's my question
okay so famous person not just a
like not actor necessarily famous couple or
person who's who would you love to
be a fly on the wall like
whose house would you love to be
oh the curious madam yes madam and
husband curie
isn't madame curie marie curie yeah madame
andre yeah like when you say for
husbands who would yeah so what about
the women when you say fly on
the wall you mean like using your
hundreds of eyes to like to watch
you whatever on their food and then
eat it no it's yeah to just
be able to hear like how the
relationship works so no we're not talking
about like hey you're
tying the wall to watch them have
sex together you do whatever you want
but the real thing is part of
the relationship get to learn how the
relationship functions on all levels right and
you you die in twenty four hours
or no you are a u k
it's you right you're in your you
oh yeah i'm invisible you're when you're
invisible for a week and wait am
i just am i just invite
visible i love good days in bed
this year there were like they could
bump into me you know you're invisible
you're zero part of the wall and
you had moved around the house and
be on all the walls and be
anywhere and you so i'm i'm like
i'm i'm shaped like a war omniscient
you can see and understand where you
why are you blinking slowly at me
and my shoe
shaped like a well know this is
what i'm you already owe and just
sort of
she got here square build that wall
yeah um what am i sort of
like an apparition that's just like you're
just you're just a pair of you're
just like god you can see the
house and right right right and i
get to see how their relationship works
because probably the fucking watching gets boring
doctor looks for a way
week ooh thank you for watching and
gets boring i tell you i would
not get bored watching people fuck for
one week if i
need to toast banana you're talking about
maybe zero if it's like try yeah
that's true it's like so so so
it's really more about like hey i
want to go see how wow today
really like each other well yeah yeah
yeah something you know trump maligned be
so interesting to watch i'm like how
do they interact i don't think i
ever like see each other they might
not i kind of feel that way
but then they'd be an answer to
the question too they didn't even see
each other like
and if they're not together are you
seeing anything so i probably wouldn't pick
them because i also hate him so
i probably pick someone like i wanna
know you're gonna pick up before i
say mine okay um this is actually
tough because i don't want to deny
the premise but i'm trying to think
like i'm wondering if i'd be that
interested if there's any couple that dynamic
i'm that interesting
yeah like like there's there's the the
couples who might read more people that
i know rather than to say yeah
i think ult i think the question
i really wanna ask is that you
know oh okay well i was gonna
say in celebrities there's the the the
people who are like um delightful i
would imagine like ryan gosling and eva
mendez you know it's like oh i
would go like to
watch them have fun together probably they
might not and then they might not
them that would be bad but but
but then they're you're right there the
couples where you're like how the fuck
does that work yeah or like i
do think that happens more in real
life because you're like you're around people
and they're like oh it's so interesting
i wonder what their dynamic is like
when they're alone right and that would
be more interesting but i i think
just to be able to answer the
question we'd have to think about okay
a i guess if it was someone
i knew i guess it would be
you in my
okay like i said
you and paul and your house together
oh wait nobody knows about that ah
everyone knows about the tunnel between right
that would be you know a secret
home in the middle relatively far away
and by the way we when we
were shooting bazillion there was a home
we shot in it has a tunnel
underneath it too
another home where you ever want no
yeah yeah over like kind of like
chan offload few wow why would they
want that yeah it was like a
bomb shelter i can't i can't remember
exactly why it was scary but we
live like him can you imagine if
someone broke a if you work had
that tunnel on in europe just really
rich person people are trying to get
your jewels and this one
in your house your rubies is real
be sitting here working bags and use
one broken your house and your baghouz
egu know kyle richards from real housewives
had her whole house robbed with all
her birkin bags those are each worth
like ten grand or more and the
laundry jewelry and oh they're versus their
purses or bags okay their purses
is right there made it was i
was i was like ah shit they're
made from real said when you said
birkin bags i was like why would
any bag i was thinking of grocery
know their persons and they're really expensive
i still think that's very nice too
it's dumb but it's it makes more
sense today they're collectible yeah that's why
she's called der birkin bag the imagine
you had that that that tunney
lol and you were going to escape
and then you got trapped in the
tunnel and the person started coming toward
you oh like there's a gate like
someone had put down the yeah you
couldn't get a damn entertain and then
like have you thought about your exit
strategy from your home should intruders yeah
i think well it's stuff all the
time i feel like i think about
that wherever i am i just brought
it up to cool up and she
had not thought about it i was
like
oh no really here's what it is
we go downstairs like yojana first i
laid it all you make a slinky
sound
throw open the sash
you're like up you stay upstairs i
run away i get out i was
like oh wait were we talking about
it when you go away
you're gonna grow i thought we were
talking about it when we were in
palm springs but probably because i feel
like because janie is very rare aware
of that yeah well cool i brought
up something she's like well we gotta
we we have to ah what was
your team our keys hires or something
right well i was talking about like
someone break in that at that point
i thought we switched it over but
ah but she was like
well then we have to we have
to start leaving our keys because our
plan is like you go downstairs to
the downstairs exit and then and then
leave and she was like well then
we have to start leaving our car
keys downstairs at night and i was
like why she's like because that way
we can get into our cars and
drive away i was like we'll just
run away
just like walk down the street or
go to our next door neighbor because
you're talking about a situation where you
just have to immediately get out of
the yeah yeah where you're like oh
shit someone who's broken in we look
at my bank bags my birkin bags
quick to the tunnel but so what
is your escape strategy not telling all
you people guys you have ditch work
imagine where i live and
no no no no no wait so
no no no no you i'm sorry
no no i won't be sharing me
no no unless you have already so
no windows and no doors i got
the window i got the door depending
on there's always my way
ah on mansion reference yeah i doing
okay wait at the haunted mansion at
disney land there's this moment where you're
all crowded into a room telling this
for the people who don't go there
all the time like us freaks iran
i mean when i moved here i
was amazed that people were always at
disneyland i was like this is not
normal this is
not no one does this but it's
right because because when you live far
away it's like a big thing johnson
and ten years yeah it's it it's
a hassle but anyways there's a part
of haunted mansion where you go in
and then you're in this room that's
all no windows no doors and they
say it's because they close everything off
in weird when you're in this like
little section of area and then they
say
so there's always my way out and
they show a hanging skeleton at the
top and flags on himself in order
to escape this right he had to
do he's gone to heaven or hell
john depending if it's good or bad
part well because he hung himself he
he went to help my story is
just that when i went there with
erin whitehead she screamed when the puck
was on purpose oh she's
oh and then i went there again
without her and i did it and
it was i was like oh i
think i'm gonna do it i wanna
do the screen whenever and then i
did it and people were like so
like what and then like this little
kid was like was that part of
it like they were like doing not
impressed didn't work yeah you are too
theatrical yeah i was like
ah when aaron did it was like
it was like a realist it was
more like a startled scream like wow
or something and you were like huh
yeah but but i still felt excited
about can i tell you something i
have been to the haunted mansion a
couple times i've heard you make that
reference many times sure i know
never knew what i knew as a
reference to the haunted mansion but it
did not sound familiar to me at
all and this tale about the skeleton
i never saw this you never saw
this i only know look up to
you yeah do you have neck problems
i do have neck problems so you
probably didn't look up because like what
happens is they the there's a lightning
fly
flash and the suddenly the ceiling which
had had been ah solid up to
that point it's right is now see
through and you see someone hanging there
really high up really high up i
gotta go now now you gotta go
now and you gotta and right at
them moment just look up ah i
remember seeing a little rascals ah i
didn't movie that way
in case people don't know little rascals
there you saw a little rascals movie
where this this guy this man had
he he leaves the dock he goes
to the doctors you've got a stiff
neck yeah the doctor says you have
to like essentially have to like keep
looking up what horrible advice or his
hope for his neck is just i
can't remember for a reason right yeah
look down yeah so
so he's walking around he's walking around
like looking up at one point he's
waiting for a traffic light and so
he's just looking up and so all
these other people like passers-by start looking
up to see what he's looking at
and then like they keep cutting back
to it over the course of the
short this i don't remember if this
if his story ever intersects with a
little bit of titular rascals
but it's a really funny gag because
he masses this huge crowd around him
now he can't move because right all
these people are crowd around looking up
into the sky right well that's human
nature for you isn't it that's cute
arrangements very nice own judgment should i
showed film that we'd like to present
two thousand another nigel film wow
gentle gentle gay if you do jimmy
stewart oh hi y'all building and loan
you've talked me where you're talking ah
you're an old maid you do it
paul you do it you're that's the
i love that film i think it's
a building and ninety nine percent
perfect film and that one percent where
he's like mary mary you're an old
may it doesn't say you're an old
maid does doesn't know she just isn't
old man he doesn't say because someone
says old maid i someone says solids
thirty minutes that are really boring in
that movie oh shut up
on the other hand i saw a
white christmas for the first time a
couple of years ago and i really
liked the one where like they're they're
putting on the show reminds me of
you who actor and that cosby your
dow danny kaye i go oh yeah
i was like oh so funny you
could be like him if i had
any talent ah if only i wanted
you to be i just wanted to
be like i wanted to be jim
amy stewart when i was young jimmy
stewart when he was young is like
the hottest guy he's adorable yeah it
he's rushed me to learn how republican
he was like late in life i
didn't know about that but back then
but back then it was fine that's
not like you know now why did
yes even republican when i was in
high
my school is very different than what
it is yeah for sure it's very
bad now
sorry to all of our republican luxury
and a huge fanbase of trump supporters
who just hate when we talk shit
about trump i don't believe it there's
a few slides
i won't tell me if you are
it was very surprising over the last
year to find out some of the
views of the people that follow my
work which i don't think i would
have found out about um the year
before i think they're right because we
are emboldened feel then yeah they are
bolted yes it's like yeah we talk
about this now how come you have
you
feel the need to have black people
on your show like oh okay yeah
i got a little bit disturbed virtue
signaling people are really stupid take away
your stupid my mouse bladen that's not
from high bar my mouse blades from
when i do it it's stores somewhat
yeah wonderful speaking of almost perfect films
though ninety nine percent prefer films i
think i think that way about back
to the future to where i've been
i'm i don't mean back to the
future too i mean back to the
future as well where like it's such
a perfect back to the future also
perfect film other than his happy ending
is he has a new truck
it's like ah yeah his his happy
ending is like his parents are now
not fuck ups and they're rich and
he goes into the garage and there's
a there's a brand new truck forgot
that and there's like you hear like
really soft to end he's like
yeah i got a new truck dude
dude dude dude distributors do do do
do do do so sewers did you
know that michael j fox was not
originally in that film yes eric stoltz
shot for six weeks then michael j
fox was shooting family ties at the
same time and he was like basically
doing it
oh all night long well they yeah
they thought that he was they originally
wanted him a copy he was he
was shooting family ties men got family
ties in them and you shouted over
there anyway we need to take a
break we'll be right back
lauren what i said was tumbled to
save him oh ya well it's it's
unbelievable all my life i used to
think it was tumbling to shake tae
bo da du mali desert toya mo
ya da da da so well oh
ha na ta melita sediba ya
jumbo da bana oh hey we gonna
have a parte din ho na ho
na i don't own law lord what
happened did i loved it i loved
it i'm sorry that we're singing a
song that's i just didn't know that
part enough
to try him in yeah what is
the what's your song that you want
to sing will be quiet while you
doing i'm taking my time to stop
your vegetable isn't it weird that both
of those songs came out right at
the same time like within a year
of each other
that's what does the name of that
song again it's ah you wanna be
starting something wanna be starting something he
does say your vegetables vegetable yeah i
everyone everyone's time using my every time
you see a vegetable on a plate
at dinner you should that should pop
in your head well know your vegetable
you're a vegetable what's new i mean
yeah give me
ah see no ma for a year
at a very particular mood today i
had over and i'm enjoying because i
just did a few recordings yeah tv
right before so i've been talking a
lot today yeah and i think it
i mean my downwind right now right
downwind thing sing a song down on
alexa singular sophisticates on it'll give ya
suggestion of a word
and they'll inspire any word cracker crackers
you don't know where you come from
on don't know why you can turn
around and tag band of you know
never momentum
a like me like palmer shana sabes
following me everything
yeah
da roda wow lee flores doing a
long chair again where she oh no
my profanity and yes ah here and
ah i love you like a little
sailor dance and uncle cracker i love
you
is that what you thought was going
to happen that you were the word
was going to lead you to a
band name no i didn't i thought
you were a drummer but i'd be
assuming terrain was opere yeah i love
that moment brain i love it i
would open brain so let's all do
okay giving giving giving award this is
the feature no no okay well let's
let's take a break and when we
come back hey no we
why don't we let's do we'll just
do one then we'll come back word
association songs okay we'll do a feat
right okay um this one's for what
you have something to say chevron shut
up chevron go ahead what are you
pointing at nearly took a word no
we're taking times oh we always take
cool we already took to this is
you never think back
the second break no we did come
back with yes because i take a
break we left there was a moment's
pause sorry zhang record i came back
and said tom bailey jay city mo
yeah that was that was that was
a good break that was coming back
did none of this gets cut out
by the way this all station no
yes
okay paul yeah but your suggestion is
tree now paul has already established that
this is tough for him i say
oh yeah we
that's okay just open your mind up
this most tree oh christmas tree how
lovely aw lie brand jazz is you
came to say huh nah nay
you came in and so far only
christmas tree went so far oh christmas
tree oh christmas tree i want to
say my e city
i can't believe you guys ruined ruined
moe tannenbaum reminded me of my favorite
song was dismissed find out who gave
christmas find out who gay guys find
out who game alright now you want
and then we'll do a real feature
alright scott are you ready alright i'm
right your song word is
crunch crunch that's what i said asshole
correct
i got pac man fever
driving me crazy pac man v well
okay what are the lyrics know that
i'm well i'm okay what are the
inky and blinky
okay i'm going to seem that what
are the lyrics it's buck it's buckman
and garcia sang it that's right ah
not to be confused with the jump
of the saddlebag saying the curly curly
shuffle oh my god lab idea for
a game okay so where are this
is a feature it's time for it's
time for us to play teacher spin
off that game okay and it's um
this is like laverne and shirley yes
this
is a little prematurely family members um
this game is c s i miami
the commercial jingles game and how it
works is one person sings a jingle
the next person things until we run
out of jingles and we don't have
to zoom all the way through once
you know one you have to it's
a real jingle or yeah for a
real commercial from tb okay
and to end it can be about
anything yeah just we all have to
know them or the can we count
local commercials it can be local i'll
just have to kill okay shot a
real i'm i'll start okay give me
a break give me a break break
me off these ah kit kat bar
give me a break danny i'm like
right properties that kit kat bar keys
keys keys keys on an eyes keys
keys keys keys keys along
a zone man
a zona da da da da big
money at menards call for action greenwood
seven five three one to go see
cal go see cal if you want
a new truck go see cow touch
the field of
cotton the fabric of law because speak
hymns with hey what's that one that
i see all the time oh hey
two three hundred and ah like chicken
tonight like chicken chennai eight one eight
eight
a no well it's like so it's
the other one it's the other ones
you have no time for this um
loving it nah got a passion for
fashion and you've got a great thing
for saving take the wheel of your
automobile swing on down to
two ideal the best part of waking
up is folgers and ya baba baba
baba baba baba baba baba baba huh
is that a commercial for whoa ababa
ababa we kill it and no way
to-day know whoa baby
what's one that i love nowadays when
i don't know we won we won
we ran out what's the one that
i i'm that's it's been on my
mind the entire time i love it
i wish they would send me one
current yeah it's like they're dancing to
to bring amp amp amp amp amp
amp amp amp amp amp amp drop
the mic bump bump bump away
bamboo dropped them back away
yes having love i hate it i
love it so much i there here's
the problem with it there's part where
the music drops out and a guy
is just singing going away yeah and
then it starts back up bamp bamp
pepper and i'm like i could tape
it off the tv and have a
clean you know recording of it except
there's that guy doing it so i
wish
shh the company would just send me
like a clean recording of the entire
thing company was just send you my
my mother god rest her soul do
you think that she she loves with
guy she know she was an atheist
so she's roasting in hell wait even
if she's not how it works you're
not if you don't believe in god
you can still and don't believe in
it it's not there though there is
no
no way to enter the kingdom of
heaven except believing in jesus christ here's
the thing there's no cleanup there's no
hell if you don't believe in it
if you do believe there i wish
that's the way it worked lauren but
i don't think the rule i think
she's with thor now an odin oh
wouldn't that be nice she's with the
all father i just keep the highest
target commercial which nfc want to say
yeah sure um there's a target commercial
that just uses a popular song right
now but then it gets stuck in
my head forever what is it
why don't you tell me man oh
don't think i'm lonely
just a little anything i don't know
that commercial or that song i'm glad
you it's should for yeah she was
the thirteenth singer or something that that
tried to turn that into a song
like hey people who wrote it had
the bead and the function whatever and
that they they stay centered to like
more famous people and none of them
could like crack it oh and
yeah i'll go with mama
yeah he's like well i think that
ah murray you're an old married obama
is like why don't you refer me
in the middle why don't you just
meet me in the middle or you
gonna say when your mother did what
she loved the movie midnight run with
charles grodin robert jr she loved that
movie but she
she my mother hated to foul language
oh yes the movie has plenty of
oh yeah and she star-rated just for
language yeah she's searched forever for a
version of the movie for like a
tv yeah yeah like on v h
s right she just wanted to have
like a clean version i had a
friend who would who
would like have videotapes of movies you
didn't know and and then read dub
them like like like in a vcr
vcr thing and then bleep out all
curse words himself so that he could
watch it around his parents how do
we do with time
i know like who you who gives
us tell your parents to fly who
gives a con
all the mummies were like you beeping
there was he saying in himself have
you ever done the we had to
do this we had to do this
on the mister show movie where we
had to record the safe for tv
version oh i always love and why
hundreds of it like wearing like you
buffed her in the bathroom yeah well
we we were off we were doing
it like which i think is more
disgust because as a kid i was
like well that's offing we were trying
to do it like surrealist where the
things wouldn't make sense anymore like mickey
mickey chinese dentists stuff you know yeah
and then i ended up seeing it
on kcp which is a station here
once and it was it was just
so bizarre to watch that version that
we recorded like what would an example
be what i just said
said oh okay well i'm
certainly lost though i think that was
based on like do the right thing
the tv version of that instead of
saying like your mother fucking some things
that it was like mickey mickey chinese
saying what did you do in your
thing i think we were using stuff
oh like like stuff it didn't even
make sense anymore almost you know like
monday to friday plane yeah
does that from ah snakes snakes on
a plane yeah there are snakes on
this monday to friday plaque is that
the lead guy and there will be
blood what's the monday to friday plane
i'm monday to friday plane and i
drink your heart he'll drink your milkshake
mary you're an old maid
bert i've got blood in my mouth
oh boy i tell ya i've got
blood in my mouth is that what
it is no mouse bleeding it isn't
bleed
oh i've got a low mouthful book
i tell you my lips bleeding drink
my blood and gore straws shaking all
style jaw blood in your mouth i've
cut off your penis and now i
have blood in my mouth while i
eat thanks come on he's my friend
think i always knew daniel day-lewis yeah
yeah yeah there's no plain view both
what's doing character do you think if
if if you would have done whatever
his name is and i just said
it was his name daniel day-lewis daniel
day lewis if he doing research for
that movie it's a character who cut
off someone's penis why would he cut
off someone's penis needed he had to
know he would i think he would
exchange text messages
about penis cutting off yeah that's what
he did when he was playing lincoln
was that he would send text messages
in character to sally field
it's like how would lincoln have proposed
that silliest thing i've ever heard yeah
well you so silly guy yeah i
love silly silly that's what people don't
get when they watch his movies he's
silly yeah i say do and see
how silly he's he's just always cracking
jokes he's like oh look at me
i'm lincoln was like what what gifts
would link it sends
right now with stickers butlin can put
on this text chain really fun look
guys we gotta wrap it up we
gotta we gotta yeah we don't wanna
we got ah y love you i
love you wanna say one more song
yeah yeah can we give you a
word yeah okay
what about us
lauren later figure one never knows i
was not thinking of the singer pink
but what about us what about us
all the time sad yeah they have
so
oh wow what the bo unhappy i've
i've that to get the right ton
what is the finger austrade the nose
for people put everything right here here
ever done in my life i don't
know why i did that for about
oh how about pink column one hand
that was my faint beeping that
it's the one that is that the
heiress oh it's you know janelle janelle
monae oh i think that awful picks
yeah pink is my favorite color that
sucks so bad a he's a pussy
were knocking on bravo i hung out
on bobo what is that about i
you know what i honestly don't always
a female
equivalent to suck it on chilly
alright we'll see you next time bye
a