three
oh hello everyone
welcome to three and we very very
quietly sang along with that song as
beds in sucks right we're on beds
in socks oh that's inside we're having
a slumber party episode leiria we are
in her party through in the afternoon
yep we're in st paul minnesota yeah
we're in a hotel room oh my
god
god so many things have happened here
do you want to complain yeah i
do okay so let's get our cleveland
right off yeah play the jinx i
mean we were we are we're in
this ah perfectly fine hotel but as
often happens in hotels there's some sort
of wedding party family reunion who knows
what the wedding as they
they are taking over the entire restaurant
tonight oh that's right yes yes yes
and i saw somebody get restaurant the
restaurant downstairs no
i wouldn't eat at that sports bar
actually have stayed at this hotel before
that restaurant is not bad today
and should have gone there the only
complaint i had about the chop salad
was actually delicious and had good ingredients
as they didn't chop it oh i
didn't issue this morning i ventured out
because i was like i don't want
sports bar food right now and i
went to a coffee shop and i
had the shittiest avocado toast
anyone's ever made fuck up off a
coach i don't know but it was
so gross and i sat outside and
i was eating it and then i
go outside yeah i don't know oh
yea when i when i went outside
because inside there were three men and
i was like an baby or a
little lady and they were having a
conversation and they go well in the
third act will
i'm in fucking saint paul oh wait
you already play bitch oh and i
go outside sound good though sounded so
good i oh my god yeah and
then i went outside and start eating
it and it was so bad i
ate half of it and then i
want this taste like shit i said
out loud and then i looked up
and the woman had been staring at
me since before i started talking clearly
like she was like ms
id stare you said it out loud
to yourself this taste
close with that's bad that's bad avocado
you know what i gotta take this
out loud just deflection shit this has
gotta be verbal
okay so then what happened you had
this child keeping you up all night
so not
guy each morning zoo mature ny child
be loaded in the hallway um there
was so there's this little girl and
i did not we we did a
show last night then we went out
for family dinner afterwards for my birthday
or lauren's birthday which by the way
is over i know no special treatment
oh yeah i'm
glad
and er we had a we had
a very nice time but we're all
i speak for everybody when laura and
i were both up we keep track
of each other online yeah we're both
up quite late yeah and then i
just feel the morning and i walked
to the dam as you fell to
the floor
like pressure
i crumpled in a book my foot
like oh can't wait
um it was me screaming this morning
this family ah right across the hall
from me has kept their door open
with the little the swing lock you
know that bar took in in the
purpose of this is to get air
nodes so people because they're all staying
here oh so people coming and going
out yeah and this little girl is
yelling so
so loudly and i thought they were
in the hallway i thought they were
maybe i heard it too and i
thought they were maybe like leaving their
room you know how like they're like
lingering when people leave their hotel rooms
they don't think about the other people
sleeping they just like hey i'm done
with this place let me as loud
as fuck yeah nothing else exists yeah
and no one's there but no they
were hanging out
out super loud and for a really
long time and i realized this is
allowed there because i realized they weren't
in the hallway they just have that
door open a crack and it's that
much it's makes that much bracket yeah
i for some reason i was able
to sleep through it even though i
heard it the entire time but it
is it has been kind of non-stop
incl
eluding mere seconds before we started this
podcast the little kid was screaming and
paul i went to jump look jumped
to his feet i thought oh hey
leper amanda choice in the air for
seconds yeah like floating wait ran over
to the door i thought to reprimand
the wicked child
old but i just don't like see
i i wanted to see if they
were out in the hallway right and
then i opened the door and it
was just you know the usually see
the doors just propped open a little
crack and the
yeah and then paul screamed very loudly
at the hollywood yeah maybe yeah
wow it felt pretty consider getting up
in your nightgown and cap and going
over roy
yeah but i didn't have a stub
of candle
so i couldn't i couldn't find my
way though what's stopping anyone
victoria nike cap
yeah oh my
who calls so loud
go down to the market you know
that goose hanging in the window is
good for hours i do no matter
what if i hit her up to
guides me i hate them i hate
them hate them so i'm very very
tired i mean they're gonna be doing
this tomorrow you know they're gonna be
doing this tomorrow yeah but at least
we have to get up early tomorrow
well i mean we aren't wow come
on scott let me have this coast
ten thirty ten thirty yeah but an
eight am shout party
when we have to leave at ten
thirty s a little early true true
i don't want an atm shout party
the reason we're in st paul is
none of your business so back off
maybe you didn't see my mud flaps
hear somebody say holding two guns in
your truck nuts then and of course
my truck nuts
learn was that all you want to
complain about zero avocado toast fucking sucked
and also so lady was staring at
you oh yeah she was staring me
but she's just like sitting out there
as well by the way let me
tell you what my patio situation was
it was a bunch of timolol all
go around the okay because bunch of
tables and chairs tables enjoy around tables
and chairs
oh tied together with like boats and
hoes from ah stepbrother soups stews soups
stews oh that's right they were um
just all like locked together with like
you know like a bike chain kind
of like big law cables so that
knows like you weren't supposed to be
like they were only setup and they
weren't really nicole pillow
well tell us do not use
we're we're how to use we're in
kevin puts one under his head one
between his legs one under his but
i want under his feet that's obviously
and one is brown and kevin ryan's
room yeah yeah that is why i'm
like oh we're gonna have an in
ryan's room all day on the beds
all of the chairs were
we're like lock together and as i
walked out there saw sky's gray skies
huh
hey
nah three i shouldn't sit out here
but i also don't want to turn
around and go back in because i
came out here and it's fine and
i sat there across from this woman
who was kind of eating one of
the other locked up tables and chairs
chairs tables chin she really was staring
at me by the time i guess
i mean i didn't say it
loudly that i thought this tastes like
shit but also it was only five
dollars and i mean there i went
back and forth
this day slash yeah that's true you
talk to yourself when you're out and
i talked to myself i spent twenty
years talking myself down at that sports
bar because you say well i've had
just terrible service at the past two
hotels restaurants we've had because i'm usually
the only one in there and you
never get worse service than when you're
the only person because they've decided to
just leave and do
yeah it takes a long time our
times yeah so i just was kind
of sitting there and every and by
the way every other employee just staring
at me from the the cooks slouch
to the bus boy's father was st
paul other hearings oh they were just
like st century stairs like because i'm
looking around the room trying to get
figure out where my person is
you've lost your love if you like
yeah
person i was just like well service
here sucks out loud
well y'all do area me yeah i'll
tell you i don't think i do
it out and about but i do
it at home a lot yeah i
will i'll say it will just be
random things that i will need to
yeah yeah it's pretty funny when you
think about it yeah like to say
i'll just like do something at home
and sail out that didn't work
after they haven't talked for hours i
also like when you when you're when
you're married that tricks the other person
into thinking they're trying to talk to
you because you haven't been talking and
then suddenly they're talking and it's like
why oh yeah i'm not talking to
you you just like every day so
many conversations i once got caught complaining
about
janie
oh after i was like in some
cranky mood she asked me to do
something
and it was like something she asked
me to do already or i care
what the situation was but whatever it
was i was like
like undermine like fucking jesus christ and
then she heard me she was like
are you cussing me out and i
was like
a
a little bit that was
and was that were you persona non
grata after that we are separated
you're here to find your person
we actually say that to each other
you're but sometimes you're my person oh
yeah yeah every common thing on reality
tv now yeah oh no is it
really yeah i just i wanna find
my person oh that ruined it for
one night we don't watch reality tv
is so damning for you that's why
it was it's organic for you and
it's normal yeah i thought you said
satanic for you i panic for you
i say ten panic for you it
addict panic as soups stews soups and
stews so those are your only complaints
i got more ya
i have to say this is a
nicer room than the one ah directly
next to it where i reside where
there's a huge dark stain on the
ceiling oh no really from when you
came on this yeah
power coven did you yeah and did
you hear scott moaning let's write
yeah that was yeah tell roof next
to jimmy pardo in san francisco and
i was sick we were up there
for sketch fest sick and that's sick
dude i just i said to him
when i saw him that evening i
was like do you hear me in
the room he's like yeah every two
seconds coughing
it's just like geez yeah it sounds
like him but you know what i
mean it's like that's why you usually
don't want to get adjoining rooms when
you're travelling yeah you want to be
a stranger who yesterday expensive if it
was one of you guys i'd be
so mad but i love that it's
this person that i don't know right
well the good part is you could
have walked over on keefe shut the
fuck up i was so close so
many
i was kind of i even though
i slept through it i was a
little like excuse me people are trying
to sleep in here like what's the
nice way to do it is there
a nice way really overweight emasculated with
your glasses on and you go i'm
i live here and i have to
go to work the night shift and
i have to speak
a mother is ill i flew in
to do a surgery and i need
to get my sleep and comedic surgery
re mine for lash i think
i heard something yeah i heard some
like damn we will go out to
take my word confrontation i want y'all
yeah i think i think the best
thing we could do is say i
am recording a podcast in this room
and if you do not respect that
if you do then you don't understand
the arts
comedy tragedy you hear component revolutionized everything
thanks to daddy conan by the way
i did last record this honey yeah
but your will
conan will you let us record another
one please
that i might cut this but how
about when conan have those finance
what conan there were those bananas and
the airwolf like kitchen and it said
conan's bananas not touch and i was
like why do you need to ten
minutes
wow one but did you did you
see him he eats all ten banana
yeah it's nuts i wondered who made
that decision to be like like that
we got to label the guy with
the cigarettes or oh it's like that
i pictured it like the hot dog
eating competition and just like swallow him
whole you give him any water
rose doing it with appeals anyway
those hotdog eating contest where they dipped
like okay so one i didn't really
know anything about them until i went
well i don't but i want to
talk about them and i have opinions
okay i know less than you and
i want to scream my opinions but
i once went with a bunch of
people somewhere ah ze maar bag when
ya um jackson hole wyoming
my friends dick cheney but on fourth
of july and one person we were
with who i won't name baltimore yeah
now lately he watches it every year
and like made us all watch all
the watches what a weird magical vote
to go to this show
yeah that's just for the cipher snape
oh service names like wow part-time but
he have we talked about pottermore did
you figure out where you're what school
yeah yeah i'm a hufflepuff haha make
sense yeah in cool up is two
and she was very happy about slither
in your slithering that thanks
that absolutely tracks but yes they they
it's this one dude johnny something and
he johnny voldemort yeah johnny voldemort he
wins all the time i think you
don't pronounce the t at the end
is something that someone's told me oh
fuck all the way i know i
know i know but i'm just saving
all of you ever read it
potter book i read the first one
and i did not like it didn't
like why didn't you like it i
thought it was i thought it was
unimaginatively and um so you think magic
is real and almost yeah actually yeah
no and i come for you i
thought like there was stuff in it
that was just not i get it
it was for a a
lower age than i was led to
believe i was led to believe like
this is a this is a book
for kids but it's really for all
ages because it's so fun and everything
and i didn't get how it was
fun for adults from the first book
and i saw the first movie felt
the same way while the movies terrible
since then i've watched ah a number
of the
there they are they're right i've watched
they're claiming it so they only talk
when i talk i've watched a number
of the movies and the movies like
the story gets better as it goes
on and it gets more you know
interesting as it goes third movies great
yeah but um i you know it's
like things like just like the
the the jelly beans that are different
flavors like that kind of shit why
did they sell them and they taste
like poo and yeah something i was
taking that's what you were eating just
morning i go yeah pilgrim burger can't
whom buggers jellybeans and i thought it
was have a co two yeah i'm
very badly oh my god chose yeah
i did she's like shit they put
weird tomatoes on it by the way
i don't know what tomatoes on avocado
know if they don't if you order
avocado toast and it doesn't say tomatoes
are on this then
what are they doing i agree i
was the star of the show and
it doesn't need help from tomato it
doesn't need anything i've gotten into like
full on debates on stage with wild
horses regarding harry potter i know you
have and so it is a hot
button issue from roofs are you pro
or con i don't give a crap
but yeah alright huge fan
and so then we will get into
things where i'm like who cares then
she's like it's the best that she'll
read reread it over and over again
but i read it when i was
in eighth grade and i was like
that's good then i'm like i'm thirteen
like it was like i truly like
there is a party where it's like
this i was a child i enjoyed
them i remembered all of them i
didn't read the last one at that
point i was
it's like it was like later in
high school and i was i kept
starting being like i don't care yeah
and i don't care about the movies
i don't remember which one's which and
i don't care if you like it
and i don't care if i don't
like it dude i mean yeah oh
no here's dough says
but i get i get like um
i don't even dislike it no i
don't know it it's one of those
things where it's such a huge pop
culture thing that a lot of people
talk about that sometimes it gets frustrating
to just hear it constantly right yeah
you know i kind of feel that
way about
the simpsons like i liked the simpsons
when it was wow you know the
team yeah i watched it when it
was first on and then through you
know a good chunk of years yeah
and then i just stop watching it
you know it was ah it was
so dear to my heart because i
love mac greetings comics yeah that
jeff and all that yeah so when
life in hell and so when i
heard he was making a tv shows
like what and then it was you
know with all these like comedians that
i really liked and and writers and
stuff so it was like it really
shaped a lot of my sense of
humor up until up until i remember
like the episode that was terrible or
i was like
ohne oh my god simpsons made a
bad episode i couldn't believe it it
was like the x-files episode and then
it took such like a downhill turn
for me tour i can't watch it
ever again here's what i think is
a big difference for me is that
i watched in in it's original airings
and i didn't watch in syndication because
of how old i am yeah
i it was just a tv show
to me and it was like i
understand you have a different relationship to
shows that are on like after school
shows that you can watch over and
over and over again because it's always
on and for me it was not
that way so it was like appointment
television that i would watch sure it
came on yes but now it's like
people people reference
the simpsons all the time sampson and
it it it sort of ruined the
simpsons for me you know what i
mean like i'm just sick of seeing
what other stuff has like the fans
have ruined excuse me have ruined to
foster brooks oh and other things that
the fans ruin foster brooks's lauren no
foss
our brooks fans ruined him for me
is that you know who that is
yeah he's a foster brooks was this
comedian from this his heyday was the
seventies i guess probably sixty seven that
a little redhead kid
who are you thinking
oh mike wendy i'm going to find
out oh okay keep going long stock
or using of ah oh shit was
a mason reese yes it was amazing
race mason reese was a cute little
kid who was an advertising campaigns for
something like oh yeah but he's an
adorable little red-haired bright kid sort of
like seth green theirs
yeah there's some really fucked around the
world and for that i think you
heard a fucked up story well i
didn't know the less yeah the really
boys are coming for that we could
child that week i gotta remember this
like i remember this but anyways okay
so i'm looking at foster brook foster
brooks was a comedian whose whole shtick
was being a drunk guy i've seen
him on stuff with
yes ok yeah and he would do
this and it was it was funny
like he did a funny drunk voice
you know huh it was basically legged
joe joe guy trying to get through
a story with like hiccups and burps
stuff like that it was really funny
then after after being drunk fell out
of fashion
been like that wasn't a thing you
could do anymore
i remember he had to do a
p essay about drunk driving driving oh
yeah mothers against drunk driving she showed
a clip of him and then they
showed him on voice know they should
come in shouldn't be driving and then
they showed clinton then like that that
clip pulled into a little square and
then it was him and in the
president saying hi foster brooks oh it's
not funny to be drunk driving
don't do it okay okay i'm looking
up mason reason he's still alive and
um has a young model girlfriend sure
in june he was on some show
man dating model half his age denies
being a sugar daddy so pretty fascinating
sure get not a sugar daddy i
will be going down a hole with
this later i merely
dating a woman half my age for
everything i do she's paying for me
how do you like that
i spent all my commercial money
is that what masonry itself yeah these
very good i mean doesn't that name
sound like that's what he was saying
certainly i may soon reach mason reese
well this has been freedom
yes ever be a sugar daddy
what what can what constitutes sugar daddy
in your mind you like you and
paper and someone who's like twenty and
yet you pay for everything for her
and like she doesn't really necessarily do
anything for you besides are you looking
for sure
okay so she never has to talk
to you look at you yeah you
really mean meaning that like all you
do is go over and have sex
and then we've yeah then you like
give her like really expensive purses and
stuff
so you're considering it
is that what you're asking sure why
not show she's hot what was that
movie ah wherever the the women robbed
everybody widows yeah widows yeah what does
i did there was rubbish around everybody
just the duty with the
babe in therapy they have a sugar
daddy relationship that seems seems wonderful and
never cdns wonderful it seems wonderful
happy no one's getting hurt okay it
seems a wonderful i'm very
i'm very happy for them it seems
wonderful are there any like growing up
or there what did any of your
friends sort of hope for that kind
of relationship like talk know be so
great if i could find someone who
paid for everything no i don't really
most of my friends are not of
that kind of mindset oh la de
dah
i'm serious i do really that's a
specific kind of person who would want
to not do anything and have someone
pay for everything i could i can
i can understand that having someone else
pay for everything part of it but
they're not doing anything part well that
should be taken care of yes i
get that idea wow i wanna i
wanna be swaddled every night
i mean it'd be great early have
somebody just like be really really rich
and that happens to be who you're
dating but i feel like seeking out
a person who's rich and only dating
them because of that is rice that's
why i think ah you you need
to hide your bank account statements yeah
for all your effort you started
forever forever from yourself if everyone's never
met you i don't know how much
money i have on that i know
i'll never know i'll find out if
i don't have any i just i
have to for you of course it
was actually for a number of years
you know right like i did i
when i was working on mister show
i would just put the the checks
in the bank and then
never look at the balance and then
just withdraw anytime i wanted money and
then i remember the day i got
my last check i put it in
and i think like ah the banquet
no i think i think um like
a week later i i withdrew and
my balance was zero i looked at
my balancing and i was overdrawn was
like oh shit i should have saved
some of this money wow you really
put any check-in and then drawing the
exact amount out
but i'd lean put on my money
for awhile because i i had i
didn't pay taxes for
ever because you don't believe him i
don't believe technically there's no law that
says yeah hey tax evasion is way
um because i had i always have
like menial jobs and no one noticed
like i also i also did not
know how to do stuff you know
any mean i think a lot of
people just don't know what's going yeah
yeah there's no one like
gg says you have to do it
you just start to figure out that
you're supposed to be doing it yeah
it's a thing you hear other people
talk about yeah and then after a
while the government says now we need
to talk yeah but i and i
so it took me a little bit
to get it all straightened out and
then now i'm good with all that
stuff but
all the all the sort of like
what you would think of is like
sort of homesick kind of yeah life
skills they had to learn them all
the hardware was growing up taking home
ek was like that's girl stuff and
yet so many of those like life
skill kind of things but mk was
in my school just like making pies
and shit like weed even so i
just like baked and
stuff yeah like i would like it
was clad right i think we didn't
have that as a class i would
like to have learned how to sew
i would like to learn how to
i like to understand taxes and so
i don't i feel like i'm just
like what honestly they should be teaching
kids how to pay bills and pay
taxes and stuff like that yeah and
also and what it means if you
don't because like you when you examine
like i've had a moment where like
my i like my autopay stopped working
on some bill and like my credit
score dipped and it's like group dam
like i'm like that's a really crazy
thing that should be explained i mean
i knew that dogecoin gore's answer with
with the fact that they market credit
cards to eighteen year olds i'm like
i knew this girl who like i
ruined my credit with like five credit
cards rarely when i was eighteen oh
my parents were really like not they
were very clear about that but i
knew someone guess as an adult who's
like in her twenties who told my
friend like oh i can buy you
a bunch of stuff at coles buy
you a bunch of yeah because i
just got it
credit card there and she doesn't like
but the money be paid back somehow
well he could buy her a bunch
of stuff i didn't have a credit
card till i was in my thirties
oh wow
i um i guess i had my
twenty i got a checking account i
didn't have a bank account till i
was in my twenties wow like i
just didn't know how to do stuff
when you put in your pocket i
just savings account i remember at our
local bank that might my mom would
take me to and you had to
write everything in the in the book
like yeah not a book and you
had to write it you know
like every withdrawal and everything
um but but yeah like my parents
never taught me anything of that kind
of stuff but then they would get
mad when i didn't know it yeah
you know fucking like one it makes
my blood boil sky my parents i
want to yell at um for you
on the phone all right here
just wanna take your word listen up
take your rainbows shut your mouth you
could just yell like if a kid
across the hall it's alright we have
to take a break
i'm back we're back we are back
bless you lorin thank you my souls
will stay inside
we did it foster brooks also was
a guy who parted his beard
wow today we're in the middle he
had in the middle and a little
interesting he had a lustrous um silver
beard and you had parted at the
chin
yuck
and it would separate he wouldn't braid
it or anything he would just come
know even just said away it was
just a clear i think that he
was stealing like dean martins or w
c fields shtick know well w c
field to think just was a drunken
real life but it but in the
movies i thought he played it up
though i don't
recall that di martin was just like
i drink a lot you know and
but it wasn't a pronounced like slurring
drunk guy he's like comedians like that
now besides like chelsea handler
like drinking is their thumb yeah i
don't yeah like doug stanhope i mean
there's ron white you know there's guys
like have alcohol on stage but i
think and you did the you did
the euro oh yeah i did it
i hope you did what i did
a whole special on hbo thing like
a one man show where i drink
for
i drink four pints of guinness over
the course of a half i don't
think i know about this my in-laws
saw that before janey and i met
oh wow just by yeah but yeah
obviously and then when she showed you
know when we were dating she showed
them a picture of me and they're
like oh that guy from the special
and so what happened by this question
in the special i just talk and
then you get more drunk it's set
in a bar no i don't you
would be hard pressed to see that
it had any effect on me at
all and then so what was the
reason ah it was like rocky hunt
and i also felt like you know
drinking was part of
my personality at that time you know
what i mean which is kind of
embarrassing when i think about it now
drinking and i guess yeah poking a
similar part of your personality in a
way i didn't talk much about smoking
but i definitely smoked a lot and
it was i definitely thought you know
smoking was a thing where
a big thing that helped me quit
aside from reading that book but helped
me with everything's because harry potter i
read harry potter
smoking smoking cessation quit smoking
i think it's native american i think
i forgive me and i'm gonna hurt
you know harry potter and see if
i like it
well i'm gonna reread all harry potter
and see if i like it
you know erin and i talked about
doing a podcast erin whitehead and i
yes and she wanted me to read
all the books a lot of work
and it's a lot of fat and
i said who do the movies she
went no it's not to say yeah
yeah no it's it's definitely not yeah
and i conceited yeah yeah we're we're
still trying to think of the thing
to do together alright you read the
bible
oh yes read the bible has anyone
done that for podcast yet critique probably
probably okay that's ours yeah next season
three two three people next season three
times we read the bible yeah oh
guy what the fuck geez what i
was smoking yeah oh smoking but that
one
of the things about smoking is that
it makes you think that as part
of your personality and i remember my
therapist saying ah you know because i
was having trouble with something and she
said well it's like you know when
you quit smoking you know one of
the things you think is ah that
makes it seem impossible to quit as
who would i be
if this is no longer a part
of my personality because you don't know
you can envision it and you really
can't like when yeah when you're smoking
and it's a part of your everyday
life you're not like a social like
i'll have one at a bar or
something it's like planning a continuously you
can't it's absurd how much it takes
wow yeah i've been seeing a lot
of things online i'm your dog what
it's like having a dog they you're
always thinking okay off always you know
at least about like the dog loves
you when you're walking yeah how can
i be gone yeah yeah um i've
been seeing a couple of things about
it's love vaping and how people are
like there are some like anti vaping
things
happening right now where people are commanded
because it's fucking ridiculous i like re-tweeted
something yesterday that was like a comedian
who said like oh i'm a men
joining watching everyone realised vaping is bad
for them or something you know whatever
yeah it was really not that treaty
yeah and the the feedback that we
eat so good but i thought i'd
retweet
and then the responses on it started
to be like people defending vaping and
how like it's actually so much better
than smoking and better it doesn't mean
it's good i don't give you what
yeah exactly about like it's yeah why
are you saying like okay it's better
than smoking like yeah you're not walking
around smoking two-pack sos chewing tobacco like
it's still grows and
it still does cause effects that we
don't even know you know a thing
that i then wait there's another thing
where because people were having like people
kid during the hospital for vaping like
accidents or like things that happen really
quickly to their bodies and then people
go actually they were buying like illegal
versions of things that were like like
not the the sanctioned brands or whatever
and so that's where that haven't actually
do your
research it's like talking about it like
it's medicine
this i hate it i remember in
ah doug benson's movie he did that
documentary super high me where he smoked
he got high for thirty days and
was there like all day every day
yeah i think he would wake up
and yeah you and that probably was
what he was doing already
yeah i don't know and then he
was so sometimes she's always stoned though
that's like the point not only okay
i think it's eighty i see him
in the context of auto companies yes
just yes yeah but he there was
a he had sort of like a
panel review at the end of the
the whole thing and there was a
doctor there you know and they were
just like talking about
every all the experiences that he had
had you know and somebody asked the
doctor you know who who's who was
a you know not a anti cannabis
guy was like pro weed you know
um is this is this safe and
the doctor said specifically about smoking while
i'm never
gonna tell anybody that they should inhale
anything to their lungs ever
there's other there's other ways to get
it and if you get it other
ways it can be perfectly safe and
have benefits right and that's but that's
stuck with me the idea of inhaling
stuff into your lungs yeah yeah you're
asking for trouble you know shut up
well there's no no no it's yeah
it's like like why what are you
oh you you like pod yeah but
i mean but we have a pandemic
stuff and i don't weed i am
why we do experience you know yeah
but people who are vaping that are
just vaping all day long right like
that's not of course that's not going
to be right for you yeah and
i'm not
sitting there thinking that inhaling anything is
good for me yeah of of index
i don't inhale good
you think i can't hear you because
we don't know how to say the
same thing
alright alright well what are you in
he solved it yeah what do you
inhale just cupcakes video hey
oh my god
ah so do you guys like this
more than sitting alone in your room
i wish i could be sleeping huh
i wish i liked how mad you
are when you came in here oh
i know you are really mad but
i did find it funny i had
just i tried to like sneak in
a little now then there's like i
don't know what's going on above above
us really but it sounded like people
were dropping marbles onto the floor
i really had no problems my room
i nearly no marine my row two
doors over two doors down yeah not
three doors down okay
whether you're into room two eleven not
three eleven
now we're just doing stuff where it
gets close yeah close references
just a hair shy
um how do you like the way
you're going to a last night i
was gonna tell you a story and
i said save it for the podcast
now will we remember what that was
i am ashamed memory about it you
started to tell us at the t
ma what was it and it was
about what was it about it was
about something that we did
something that we're going to do something
that has been done
something that exists it does not exist
i don't revise it damn it the
pipe something that's not to say should
have written it down i don't really
talk about it or we talk about
last night and how the airwolf sent
this like cookie cake to um the
show for me which was really nice
it said it really ny it was
gigantic
which i can take and weighed seven
to ten pounds i'm like no exaggeration
really have it was it was in
essentially a flat pizza box and the
size of a pizza and yet weighed
so much more than yeah and i
thought it was a cookie and then
when we opened it for dessert after
dinner it was like exploded and it
was like oh
all icing like it was sound advice
percent iso yeah that's another reason why
i feel like shit today me too
it was pure sugar i had something
you know what i do regret it
i didn't regret last night but i
do regret it today now let's tell
the story yeah of walking oh we
got to start walking over heaven get
ready so we ready for this we
finished the show i haven't been i
want
i want to go back even further
oh okay well giuliani i was born
september you shut up
we when we do these shows a
lot of times it's that ah we
it's a sort of in-between time where
we can't eat dinner before the show
as we land like late enough that
like yeah we landed we can only
check into a hotel around three yeah
we're doing quick turnarounds on this so
we're always like landing somewhere around two
getting into the hotel is three and
then we have to like leave for
the show at six thirty which only
leaves like a weird portion of tongue
you're tired and shower any lunch you
don't want to eat down yet yeah
so we will want to eat after
the show for whatever reason it never
occurred to us to research a place
to eat before the show
so then after the show we ended
up looking walking around walking around while
he started every restaurant saying is your
kitchen open yes literally huh yeah we
did that and was like totally shut
down homes like i'm not i think
so but i'm not sure and then
like there's no one there somebody sitting
at a booth with that works there
with a laptop yeah places not serving
food yeah yeah so we though that
was in kansas city we walked a
bunch of different places trying to find
food we finally found one on the
fourth try i believe yeah which was
a place right across the street from
where we started yeah yeah but so
um we ah so so we're like
okay let's do the smart we're going
to go to ah this
place after the show we know the
kitchen stays open just to get there
at a certain time get this cookie
cake i get on my phone i
got the directions ready to go but
you have to carry this cookie well
it was being golan he's being yes
and backpack as lauren was carrying cookie
cake and she can carry the cookie
gets her birthday having my weak little
lady i'm since your birth
a bow can snap look i respect
you you're a strong woman yes quite
good carrier yes between however i wanted
the king to carry i want you
to slay i read the cookie cake
you could hire someone to carry it
using your own money that you earned
so first we walk outside walk on
the stage door and there's like a
handful of autograph people there
like that have eight by tens for
me it's always some of these people
needed characters i think i don't think
they were at the show necessarily hey
these are people who are not show
up in dirty places like go around
looking at events and say yeah like
oh lauren lucas is going to be
here from orange is the new black
let me hang out outside the a
a the place hilariously they had me
sign
shares from clipped just wide and big
bang but they didn't have oranges new
black which is like the only thing
anyone would i yeah no one wants
clipped right but it was one since
this is like a job for them
they don't it's yeah they're they're um
taking these home and going yeah i
got lauren lactose the signature they're going
in selling them but yeah do say
things that indicate
they know who you are and they
have watched your stuff they they they
do that intentionally they do a little
research so that it's so that the
people don't feel but i think it's
a little more than that because i
feel like this they have they've demonstrated
not not just like i am db
knowledge but you know they've actually was
like weirdly developing a show about autograph
hounds
really yeah and it's a it's a
crazy sub well like they i remember
the first time happened to me i
found it extremely creepy because they had
they knew when i was landing at
an airport yes civil yes and i
was like how the fuck would they
know yeah but it's really really weird
yeah and then they also want to
take photos with you which i don't
understand because if they
don't care about who you are why
do they want a picture with you
i don't really get with these sort
of collectors as well in a way
so they have like their collection of
all the people they've gotten and then
they sell the ones online who's buying
that but it could be that they
could also put the picture up there
to prove that here's me with this
pro and amateur yeah
yeah yeah that's probably right that's actually
probably right um anyway so those those
people also did not seem to grasp
how heavy the cookie cake well no
one could it was while he was
in a pizza but it looks like
we're carrying a piano but i said
to my couple even open i'll sign
these if you will hold this and
they were sort of like taking a
corner over i'm like no
no you have to hold and i'm
still holding it you have to hold
it so i can let go and
sign this and they would not do
it yeah so then we get through
that that i can't do it i
can't lead the directions anymore because i'm
holding this i'm calling cookie cake and
then we go to someone directions kevin's
like i got it and so he
were
following his map so we walked even
look at him we want good okay
i have a defense of him but
we walk a good guy know what
it is and i don't care twelve
minutes and then she's coming anyway i'll
tell you what happened yeah sen kevin
and i are chatting and then i
go okay it's up here on the
rights for eleven or whatever and then
he goes oh so we're like what
do you think like the hos
tell bars that's probably good and i
was like what and he's like going
to the hotel bar and i was
like
where are we going right are we
going to the hotel workflows go to
a different tellings like wyatt and we
had this really confused and had put
in the address of our hotel where
we're staying assuming we were going back
to the hotel but we will go
another hotel a totally wrong direction carrying
this big heavy cookie cake now in
kevin's defense we made these plans in
a taxi
that he was he didn't hear it
and we i we carelessly assumed he
would know what we were talking about
yeah and this is why we have
the group thread and this is why
we should put all information on the
raw information on the grill or information
from now on all information on the
group threat from now on every little
thought you had yeah every little plan
you make yeah every little step you
take
take a breath you wake you the
group to aid the bay man he's
really waking barrett
it puts it on the group threat
and puts it what else it gets
the hose so then it's so funny
paul just so defeated buffalo cause knowing
that he had to carry this little
bill there's cookie cosby buffalo bill cosby
and i really got the closure of
the best girls together whoa i'm so
glad i kept talking
and we finally got to
three days so okay so jim and
demille we get to bill cosby no
matter how long i know cause you
were saying buffalo bell so and then
it came together yes
i had a similar one last day
with the steak tastes like wood i
felt very proud of yeah that was
great that was great anyway you have
to listen to the show just to
close up the story i carried the
cookie then yes god graciously wanted to
know that you carry just as we
were trying to show people were gonna
she'd be feeling too bad for paula
not bad enough for me yes okay
yeah and then we
just the restaurants like simon of cyrene
helped our lord carry the cross core
scott from our nice to me chapter
our bible podcast yes sir and i
was i was doing it sort of
like i used to carry a huge
tray from bangalore yes yeah yeah coffee
cordoba were going to tell you you
do it on your fingertips like here's
why that didn't work what do you
think will be good
i'm fucking carried the entire way it's
putin see when we opened it and
how it had exploded from the center
it was all the fucking frosty you
know those probably from when i was
carrying it because the you had to
fit don't put that on hey who
cares we all want more cookie we
add up more frosting know honestly because
the the i could feel it
it break in the middle i could
feel it breaking okay so you're usually
so structurally oh yeah sounds nice to
me no and now we had to
talk about when we got to the
bar and the ladies who were having
their batch so paid jesus or their
rival party and they wouldn't get out
of the fucking doorway and they were
acting like they owned that place yeah
like yeah and it was there where
she so they
they were gonna check us off a
guest list as we were approaching like
because they were so we're basically blocking
the entrance you enter the only way
yeah when we're carrying this huge cookie
cake that no one respected this cookie
cake here's why the cookie cake should
have been on a scale that said
how much it weighed yeah this should
be a doll and we should be
showing every yes this
thirty five lb cookie yeah what would
you guys i would say seven pounds
to ten pounds fifty pounds
i think it probably will see i
lift a lot of weights usually usually
deadlift like ten
somewhere in there yeah
those at the at the hotel the
other day she's telling us where the
jib was and anytime anyone tells us
where the oh my god i have
to say like okay cool because i'm
gonna be spending a lot of time
in there obviously so
and luckily she when they tell you
where the gym is that means i
think maybe i'll go to the gym
i could go to happen and then
i think why the fuck in my
two hours i have before the show
would i go work out right i
just like i remember being in a
hotel with you and seeing you take
the elevator down to the gym on
always doing that on the on the
month long tour yeah yes yes yeah
like i guess that's great i wish
i had the fortitude do you have
any other opinions or memories from last
night of fun things to happen are
interesting weird people oh i thought our
waitress was great she was at the
st paul hotel there was a um
there was a big
booth because there were what seven of
us altogether think there was a big
boom we had had a rasho snarled
tart or what this is carl tart
ryan kevin
three of us this freedom place the
pretzel gang um and there was a
big booth that was had a reserve
sign on it and like at this
point it's what's pretending thirty something like
that yeah and i and so there
were a waitress was clearing off tables
and i said oh is that is
that does that booth reserved reserve
like somebody's actually coming one yeah like
oh right and then today will never
come i didn't look back yeah they
did like literally an hour later an
hour later yeah it was that our
waitress who was snippy no no this
was this was she more jamal diaper
so i never and then but she
was then she went and removed reserved
wd signs from other tables and i
was like does she just lie to
me or write but no that table
remained reserved right great story paul
i did hear ago it's reserved and
like she was being a little salty
yeah like i'm just asking lady yeah
yeah you defend her i wouldn't defend
i know like that ever i nice
eye nice me know bad me no
bad
oh nice i'm trying to think of
anything else that happened last night but
i had a great birthday actually really
finally kind of like i told i
told paul that before like i was
getting kind of melancholy but my birthday
i feel like i do every year
and then it ended up being a
really nice day with lots of nice
comments on instagram and everyone was one
hang
hang out with it's i mean because
i usually just hang i mean you
know we recorded a show on my
birthday yeah absolutely but um other than
that i'm just at home yeah i
was thinking it must have been nice
to have you know hundreds of people
you know laughing at what you do
loved me on my birthday around friends
as well it's true it was actually
a perfect ah
way to celebrate on stage birthdays are
really nice i've done that a few
times and it is like doing a
thing that you really like to do
on your birthday because i think typically
because this came up just this was
just the dates that we got whatever
organically but i never book a show
on my work i would never agree
to do a show on my birthday
yeah thinking someone i want to do
something else
it might have been but it might
be better to do that and just
be like go hang out with fun
people in a fun show who gives
although i will say i did it
one time one time
i booked a show on my birthday
with kristin schall we're gonna do a
two person crews santos horse kristin charles
horace look at it today they're looking
at data oh and we went to
boulder colorado
and
we flew in day of or i
flew in day of with janey and
it was weird to get over the
crack of dawn was a miserable flight
we got there the show was at
this place that i thought was a
theater but it was more of a
rock club the show started way late
and then there was like a weird
intermission so they could sell drinks and
so by the time i got
on people were hammered and it was
late and it was a miserable show
people just like talking through the whole
thing yeah and then we went to
this super crowded gross bar afterwards it
was horrible sometimes the opposite of what
i had anticipated yeah well this was
a great one i'm happy you're alive
thanks me too
yeah it's great and it was rude
to spell that out but um we
need to take a break but we
have a very exciting three-tier coming up
after the break oh yeah kill are
you gonna kill me guys when you
go to this teacher you're gonna love
rebecca
we're back we're back threesome dim freedom
boys the pretzel gang is back we
got it what does it is there
a dog in the front basket maybe
but there's right dog at the front
basket i'm like writing a jazzy and
his likes and his sugar baby and
they're on his like rascal scooter
she's on the back of it and
there's a dog in the front dog
in the there's a die in the
front there's a lady in the back
of your phone and what were you
playing in the bags if it was
instagram ryan is looking at instagram while
he records the show with this phone
on with the volume up
me too much yeah who is it
fair point but sometimes you you can
accidentally hit that volume with your thumb
but you don't realize you're turn the
volume it's not that was part of
our no phones in the bedroom policy
because sometimes you're scrolling through things you
actually hit something it's very jarring you
know what the worst thing for me
is
having to sleep next year way yeah
we're just friends i can still play
that yeah i'm i play three new
mood who you play with i play
with sarah silverman i play with daniel
callison i play with josh malina i
am shocked people are still accessing there
weren't nerds the real work that out
and i haven't just it was very
in yeah yeah now it's i don't
really oh
oh no i don't think playing scrabble
is can will ever be here you're
great and your hobbies are cool i
hear a lot of people are using
words with friends is there ashley madison
oh that was of some words some
friends
yeah
fuck but this should be illegal in
my opinion so you turn the volume
all the way down yeah and you
have the volume off on your phone
yes but there is one ad on
where's of friends it comes up every
like eleven ads that just blasts now
here's my question what's in the five
dollars for ad-free at one point
they they offered that back in the
day but now he is now scott
you're an influencer we'd like to offer
you ad free words you could buy
it for like literally like a dollar
or five dollars or something like that
i regret the day i do it
because i don't think they offer it
now because they make so much money
on ads oh man listen um but
yeah i paid five dollars i think
one of the best
ones that i've paid for is the
re-post app yeah five dollars i don't
have to have someone's name on taking
over yeah yeah my repos yeah i
love it it's all right all right
it's a fantastic feature time is three
year term all right what are we
playing to three years single fish is
called here
the game is called pitches hit song
we've done this before there's a name
of a song everyone else pitches a
sitcom based on the song you're gonna
like it person who pitched the song
title has to come up with the
theme song to the show okay so
it's going to be silly and great
you name a real song yeah summer
one else pitches a sitcom based on
that real song a little real tunnel
then that person who pitches company new
song that is a theme song for
that show great okay so i'm gonna
give you a song okay and i'll
pitch as a sitcom where the streets
have no name where the streets have
no this is because you'd like the
band what i'm talking youtube too
two
t you accent mark
come in you don't have to knock
sir i don't have to knock just
high i can come in anytime i
like yeah you're no who are you
hi i'm mason oh mason we your
recall i three o'clock is here hi
ms sharon next time give us a
little bit of heads up okay
nah i'm sharing an audible you call
an audible it's an audible heads up
thank you anyway so i'm sharing this
robert robert yes and um we know
that you i'm seeing here on your
resume that you've handed me my resume
well you just handed yeah
i'm sure you'd have just ended it
is so you put it on like
lisa frank paper and it smells like
bath and body works yeah saffron smells
like watermelon okay it's kind of a
mixture of all those things okay so
this is kind of um childish so
she's not a whole lot written here
it says i'm pretty good yeah
i passed jobs cafe cardiology as dunkin
donuts commercial and chin i watched a
dunkin donuts commercial employed as a sugar
daddy yes um yeah really sugar baby
yeah it's a technical term where i
paid for a woman's rent and and
you just lay
laid down on our chaise lounge
that's the case we feel faint but
go ahead i thought you say you
have a fainting couch in your office
chair she sounds that we use in
case we face sharon fans from time
to time but i do faint from
time to time
out of surprise or all sorts of
things ray mason so um what are
you hating but what's a way we
could put it back while you hear
by television shows don't you sure to
do that's our business well we just
thought a really funny one it's called
barney the red dinosaur yeah this guy's
going to take the dinosaur community by
storm so taking the blue out
out of habit out of barney well
barney was purple but i guess i
might but if you combine red wow
okay so you think you're better than
me yeah do you think you're an
artist um we are you i am
better than you can have your jobs
wow me too yeah i'm better than
both i'm gonna need to me to
move over if you'll fail
oh oh you're snuggling sharing okay this
might be illegal now can you just
please oh you sharing please can you
just tell us what your idea is
because i have a lunch at three
ten on over dinner tonight okay well
it's ten in the morning and i
also have a new zealand four weeks
you mow right yes three ten to
you that's a great thing
about ah california you can surf in
the morning and ski in the afternoon
though i wish we were there oh
well we are in st paul no
please this for st paul television saint
paul television what is your idea i
have an idea for a show called
where the streets have no name intriguing
because where i'm from streets two of
name's tracey
nice and we're in st paul right
now and they certainly have names names
like minnesota avenue and forth
these are great so know what is
happening on this show well ah for
me show is all about the characters
okay so like this like this you
do need people so yes so there's
a person named ah quality who want
quality quality quality oh
okay and i wanted to look at
ticket inspired to name the character yeah
what's your process you look around things
and
and the e i did and i
saw a quality grace he said that's
a great name quality all right so
i'm glad you're mad but please continue
so would you have had it's the
logline the logline is in a mysterious
town where a really funny name serious
town
in a mysterious town okay i heard
in um serious town yeah what did
you think i seen them serious zone
serious town is this you know doing
like a native american thing are you
oh no smoking no no no no
i'm gonna put you out okay
in a mysterious town where a very
funny man named quality the log line
yes we're a very funny manageable do
i really need to have his name
ah street signs start disappearing everyone thinks
that it's a local teens playing pranks
but suddenly everyone realizes they can never
remember the names of the streets and
ah cars just start crashing into each
other and it's a mystery it's sort
of like a lost style mystery so
do the street lights also just they
work they totally work but people just
don't know where their signs they're distracted
so they're not looking at the light
right there just narrowly intersection through
they don't know where they are sure
no one can figure out how to
get home and all of these ah
everyone's relationships are severed and torn asunder
marriages breakup look oh my people who
love each other people who love each
other to people who hate each other
know like each other weight people with
their people break up from their people
from their person
yeah oh no no she suddenly ah
finds out that ah he starts to
unravel the thread and he's very funny
he's very funny how is he funny
and what's funny jokes funny nose are
funny hairs know maybe oh okay sharon
i think we've heard enough and i
feel like you actually
could make up a theme song me
i forgot that part of this yes
because i do think that this sitcom
isn't weight who's supposed to be me
oh is it supposed to be our
friend here mason who was shot in
someone is supposed to oh oh here
and sharing you're supposed to shame me
i thought the two the two i
see how it is now
is it wanting to one remember what
no because idol song happened that was
sharing can i take it i came
up with the name of the song
mason clovis show you you did the
same book and i'm the next round
it'll be just as follows excuse to
share chinese house i'd love to hear
i'm supposed to do because i made
up the song
oh no okay it's turn are mine
was telling me that i have to
do it
okay and i wasn't really listening to
good is where the streets are have
known and you were listening to this
show no i was i was ok
make sure you work in that they
thought it was the work of teams
im serious tone and um
and
serious sound and um well covered at
this point
and um serious yes we've heard this
line over and over ssh you're in
my office and um town with no
name in um town has a name
i should stress that everyone knows the
name of the town you know um
stare
there is tone there are all these
signs going ms singh thay don't know
i don't want to give away this
much and just the theme song okay
fine i'll start over and um serious
chow and um tuk tuk tuk in
um sticks down in
okay i think i've heard enough i
don't want to sell my show to
you guys street signs um is using
the genes huh to blame in i'm
serious
and um
okay you guys are obviously insane i'm
drunk well yeah fainted on the panty
wow today's ten am why did you
do it to get drunk well oh
you're just part of my deal i
do reuse yeah it's very catchy and
if not so we're not going to
buy information yeah i'm not telling you
to okay read a stalemate please close
the door on your way out please
let me hit you in the ass
you got oh he's just good okay
okay that was fun next round you
name the song title paul pitches pitch
it okay you and i do that
and then using song no yes i
do okay
ah bawah tba
fuck you
ah
hi oh oh hey sneer okay either
way i'm gonna wait the um put
it away put it away but in
the way anyway now you guys doing
drugs
we're just doing a little bumpy to
get us through this come be you
guys are cool yeah thank you so
much but who are you we're radical
yeah we're cool my name's end table
end table yeah what was your process
for coming up with that name we
should ask his mom i guess my
parents named me in table oh really
smelly hippies
lamp
it feels to me like i'm not
going to accuse you of anything real
guy feels to me like you're just
looking at an end table and lamp
next to us oh oh no it's
a weird end table that we had
this meeting in our hotel room be
honest isn't anywhere that i'm in your
hotel room i mean this is where
we take meeting and it shift
two and she's did when he walked
in and yeah it really really cool
i love this energy not to weinstein
you but i'm gonna take my dick
out
and jesus this plant will you please
feed by playing it
it craves humans
i love this guy no no i
am sorry but until you have a
show you want to picture yeah that
song yeah yeah no no it's just
a show just a shari you may
have been misinformed i was my emails
are in all hieroglyphic but it doesn't
need a song so let me tell
you what the show's about yeah
it's called ball with the ball oh
tristan hey and it's the story of
how bab bar met the baby boss
babar the elephant by bar the elephant
met the families tab bar bar bar
bar bay bar
rob bob
it's not rob for sure but it
could be any of the others as
far as but it is okay aw
oh la la i love those books
oh so great he's a king i
love the baby boss yes the babe
was adorable burning calories winter all of
our interests so it's crossing over of
two different worlds and if you can
buy both these properties than
we're in business well i already own
the baby boss oh great do you
own by bar i own rob i
own it on dvd not familiar with
rabbi when he looks in the mirror
i own it on dvd is out
enough yep
so we do this so we must
be sworn to secrecy will never tell
anyone that we made this show and
then what happened so here's what happens
yes the baby boss he goes on
safari he's going to kill an elephant
okay like moss he exactly yeah everything
you does is like a ball he's
gonna kill bab huh he doesn't know
he's gonna kill bab bar all
he knows is going to kill the
king of the elephants does he know
who babar is no he doesn't but
he finds out because bab bars wearing
his fucking clothes like a real person
i love his clothes and being boss
is like what's we're both wearing suits
neither of us should be wearing suits
because they're both babies get well no
babar is not a baby baby no
he's an
elephant he's a grown man he has
children yeah just children yeah yeah nice
green suit so the baby bus in
the bab bar realize we both are
beings who should not be wearing suits
i think we should be best friends
suit friends their suit friends there's unlikely
suit from likely this shouldn't be weird
just to be prone on the dodo
channel right
wow okay so ah the looking at
bab all right now the show follows
their adventures other good they go on
advantage on adventures mostly it's trying on
clothes okay they go shopping a lot
alright wow a lot of bespoke suits
a lot of bespoke suits there was
a bespoke or best pick it's best
bouquet
okay and ah eventually it we follow
them all the way into the future
where they shop for closing space is
it in real time the show yeah
it's gonna run for fifty years so
we have to have retraced travel kind
of technology catch up with us in
order for your plants we have space
travel technology right but shop
being in space dillard while you pretend
that's where dillard yes i think you
flirting the song
alright well i was thinking that try
to work in teams yeah go to
teach them to do what we want
them to watch it oh certainly we
need them to watch it i mean
the demo okay well if i had
to write a song for this and
i do write theme songs for all
of our products and you do have
to ah in when i say products
i mean television shows obviously which is
the products that we put out and
ito chips potato chips potato chips it
would go a little something like this
first you take a bow babar the
elephant gad now they're blah blah bay
boss jeans love it adults love it
they go into space the space suits
but
not the space suits that you would
have heard of or the suits that
are three piece suits bow it dabba
teens love it hey watch it it
starts right now wow i just understood
how you got inspired right i think
that song was great and
it served my vision okay i think
we're gonna buy it we're gonna buy
it ultimately we need we need content
for fifty years yeah so yeah i
want a something that runs fifty years
that's a cash cow that's ideal for
us so we could get the cash
cow in there too oh moo i
need to change the themes no no
he's just a recurring character the cow
that gives you cash for asking
trivia cash for gold cash for gold
well congratulations that's the green light i
was stuck in my head smash for
gold cow i was seeing that all
last name gigi for cash that's checking
the cash well thanks guys i'm gonna
go to my home now don't let
the door hit you where
the good lord split you said about
my cleft palate how ruby you have
to door hits you there you really
walked out wrong
okay okay okay now it is time
for paul's name i picked song
okay the song goes
no why is is always hard for
me
yeah any song your favourite song first
i was the pina colada song it's
scaling in the navy game saw escape
the pina colada song
escape song
parentheses do you like picos use me
knows escaped parentheses the vehicle odysseys me
oh hey hello you been there four
minutes oh i'm so sorry may show
oh you must be juniper and juniper
ding dong juniper ding dong ding juniper
we hear a lot of great things
about you juniper thank you
i have you seen have you seen
my performance side in the square we
see yeah we see it every day
he were right i mean you know
our office overlooks the square and it's
protesting us so yeah we've seen it
yeah keep canceling the o a and
keep canceling it
i the problem with that theory is
is that that implies that we would
have to renew it every day and
then cancel it every week we could
just keep announcing that it's canceled okay
reminding everyone still cancelled you know a
lot of networks don't do that put
out a press release by the way
oh a barney miller kill
cancelled now i would like to pitch
my idea to you you were very
hungry are you okay yeah i'm on
day ten of my hunger strike canceling
the o a i have something for
you to eat if you need it
yeah
yeah for these nuts you started your
hunger strike ten days ago i'm hungry
for use nets
don't understand
kind of nuts and you
she isn't a witch
alright look shit what do you pitch
we're all business okay okay okay alright
yeah yeah yeah yeah my man know
okay so he's made it okay so
the idea is it's false up okay
just by police because i've been fucking
island time so the idea is that
ah okay so it's okay so you're
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah okay someone
you see a backstage a grocery store
sure i'm sorry to see your backstage
at a grocery store okay and you
this is where all the fruits and
veggies is where they all hang out
for showing short time under the shower
okay what when they got performing get
all glistening wet so your nes yes
subject to him okay so look nasty
yes sir well attracted to him okay
alright this is backstage this is where
the magic really happens where it happens
okay and these people these veggies these
foods they're all fighting and then one
day incomes abandon of alcohol a bottle
of al
alcohol comes into its mpa colada ah
alcohol yeah rum um comes back stage
arpino in it pineda comes back steak
and i believe colada comes back stage
seven
shit you doing some say yeah fritzl
hey turned into that but now i
just do
like a king
yeah pretty awesome
he made a tv dvd
okay so i doba di asia bow
tie so okay
so i say ah about ah d
j as well these fruits veggies there
are having a strike because they don't
want to be eating okay so the
alcohol not your time they got so
excited i know but the alcohol comes
it goes i deal for you when
you come and get mixed up in
me
me and we get ah all the
employees had the tip said and they
do it and it's fun bitch is
a good time did everyone loves it
okay and she's like it has an
end though inadequate raise your last for
what episode is it like a special
because it's special
nobody oh escape at the end because
they get to leave they'll get even
consider the drink okay alright so just
to sum up
the fruits and veggies are backstage at
the grocery store they take a shower
to get all wet to the track
are nasty acids
then pina colada shows up and everybody
has a fight and then they escape
and it's a good show bitch and
it's a good show bitch okay so
under the theme sung by young yeah
let me take it i'll take this
one oh okay that's okay um i
can back you up doing bass sounds
if you know that
okay okay i know you love your
bass sounds i'd love to do just
one bass sound you want to know
what i have planned for my mel
i'm honestly bad to go pitches somewhere
else oh no oh no we can't
let her do all right here's my
song
mark phase our girls list all gone
girl shine if all the people who
are poor who call in saw all
the god eat some food but white
time to be so rude there has
been to call laura is making a
mess and a body saying oh we're
gonna go in bless this mess be
cause we're fruits and vegetables let's escape
with our escape my goddess ape scape
scape and escape cheapskate we gotta go
to a place where we can escape
apm really was
the ireland we specify the guy will
say pianos pianos all the bests yeah
those all the day pianos in the
west pianos at nih np hours during
the day pianos all the one true
holy way oh to have a piano
now won't you give me a piano
and how
now i gotta have won't be out
of here dancing yeah oh yeah me
i yeah ya know i got up
the ad oh i gotta be out
oh god oh god oh god oh
i gotta pee yeah and oh there
is so
good bye know the song doesn't make
sense yeah unfortunately the song okay guys
gotta go put my mask on this
alright put it on
and ah by ju nie juniper we
love you love you hey okay fun
game fun yellow dogs paul tsongas say
he is a wide awake we got
randoms hats over his eyes
the last we love this and thank
you thank you lady love you thanks
for listening to a special on tour
edition of threesome an o t e
o t yes we'll see you next
time bye ma bay
uh