three
we all did
what did you do
hi welcome to the real good
so yeah in the musical question three
i did a monster get my stuff
hi everyone welcome to the town will
welcome to three-time paul i who
i'm scott
that only leaves kevin oh my god
i'm kevin wait no one slower
no lauren this episode sorry dude um
lauren is on assignment
what guides well just sign
yeah he's for this yeah
hi this is lauren laccase outside the
capital reporting live from carson y'all as
ah whatever cafe cardiology
yeah i suppose what we know we
talked about we talked about don't die
today because i feel like i'm gonna
forget every time that
it closed down because scott didn't work
there
why would it close in their greatest
hour of need why would you kill
hello would you kill a bit gaudy
ya'll is that's right that's an impression
of okay so when i was in
college your impression of people's visiting people
huh yeah i know but here's where
it sounds familiar i was like ooh
oh man this person i knew i
will say it to my other friends
and it will crack us up one
other ah but it's it's someone else
now okay so when i was in
college we did a we did like
a thirty minutes crossover of romeo and
juliet and west side story oh god
where
the scenes would inner oh no it
was actually really good and left everyone
in tears but ah and we would
like make it so from stifling laughter
we would like go to high schools
into it and stuff anyway you like
oh yeah we traveled locally locally if
it happens at school educational um but
there was the guy who played the
priest oh boy no it wasn't the
priest it was the it was it
was whoever is in west side story
playing the priest was the drugstore guy
the director guy i feel like we
talked about
it's on rpm recently but ah he
not this particular story but ah okay
he had a voice he had he
would he would say all those lines
like this
why do you kill
so like the cowardly lion she found
out about you you saw them
sound like
cameron calling ferret or being ferris bueller's
dad oh nor zones no peterson why
would you cool why do you kill
you and a little bit to use
sure
i watched like the behind the scenes
thing about ferris bueller that was actually
pretty interesting really yeah almost everything was
and that was interesting was that john
hughes looked like a psychopath while he
was filming she had this like mullet
and weird sunglasses the entire time and
and every interview he did he was
wearing sunglasses huh um what's in this
box but this year main
hey yeah
because now when you watch people you
can picture who is direct to get
and he was like being weird was
you i think he was cocaine head
wasn't really sad i think so i
think so i got i got sent
a bunch of owe barbie cars are
very bars tracks bob per repurpose scripture
prescription food
i look i've worms
eat this prescription food
wait so i'm telling worms i've been
worse than you but i'm allergic to
he feeds his shit to them so
i'm always just telling me that um
they shopped him up to sue have
friends and their child this the kid
is now much older so i feel
like it's very okay to tell this
story oh good this kid was like
my buddy she's my buddy
and then the dad was like what
no you're fine or whatever and then
this went on for like days or
whatever and then the kid finally was
like complaining about it so much that
the dad opened the kit will open
kids but you just mimed by the
way like parting kiss scene but cheese
actually because he got gotta look like
he was five he got a yeah
yeah you gotta see a guy right
up to that ah i got a
blue telescope cooler so
and it was like a baboon's ass
and he had strep in his ass
way he was like a baboon's ass
in what way it was puffed out
like i said it was n it
was strep throat in the butt but
he attracted a lot of mates yeah
drink bud strep but except through o
strep anus stripping this strep throat in
in the bud patriots wrote in the
butt
in the but that's a love that
is a lot like like a eighties
rap song don't you know the song
what what in the butt oh yeah
well yes what on yeah it's it's
a terrific song i can't remember the
name of the artist right now harness
chevy
his name is schiff
i'm a chef and look at all
your hit songs
yeah many people don't realize you are
the singer behind what was in the
bud chevy and what do you got
who you're i see you turning your
mic sam well sam well well some
lord of the rings cry
this is a song of course inspired
by frodo the hobbit
samuel what does this epic open i
gotta begin with the organ
began with oregon ended with the bucket
what one in the bud i said
what was let me see i forgot
i do i feel like i know
what was in the bud as a
reference but maybe you've never even heard
it it's a beautiful song and my
book is doing the watching my butt
oh yeah this guy but then he
i liked it he agrees like first
he's like i beg your pardon and
he's like okay watching so he gets
convinced rather early you want to do
what's in my books oh i thought
you said something else that's fun huh
oh good oh whoa so what how
do you cure strep anus ah just
your penis get on it okay wait
this just remains still
oh and i want to play this
video that i remember now oh hey
i'm gonna play this video i remembered
i do this my turn i wanted
to take it to the movie sholay
want to take you to the movies
short a and it's this like homemade
music video um it's just great
i want to
banks neat trick that it can be
called the latest out there that's a
tax to go to the movies explicitly
use abc like to go to the
movie especially you girl
i'm sure yeah
monday
whoa whoa
suzanne
why don't more music videos have a
map of a continent of wherever it's
taking place just zoom zoom zoom in
on it looking nice limited to
cause i know you like dick and
nothing to worry about on the popcorn
and the rings
got nothing to worry about another worry
about let me check the movies you've
got nothing to worry about hold the
popcorn popcorn in the jail now that's
all your return
okay i'll do everything else
you've got nothing you got nothing to
worry about other than your responsibilities to
hold this popcorn oh my god so
god willing to move will be enjoyed
speaking of great music i want to
give a shout out yeah and ah
brandon thanks
and my good friend tyler durden who's
been here for every episode of it's
pure mao and just the cd pure
moods three year tonight per pure pyramids
three he's up for three of them
fully sente nice mood three with it
yeah um we mostly can't read them
okay dear scott lauren and paul
or dive into the music of the
pyramids discography was something i never thought
would pop up and i'm in modern
podcasting congrats modern podcasting now sure old
timey yeah sorry ninety's yeah encloses economy
of pure mood street dumb i couldn't
tell if sending this would be funny
or not but here it is anyway
personally i thought there would be more
way to hold on hold on so
he did he didn't know whether it
would be funny or not
let's take a look let's take a
look at it well is it funny
i don't think it's necessarily funny nor
are we laughing i'm not laughing laughing
laughing
oh
um but i'm really delighted by it
yeah personally i thought they'd be more
enya enjoy i love freedom the connection
you share is so pure unhappy it
pours through the speakers it never fails
to put me in a good mood
and good moods are hard to come
by these days i wish the three
of you continued success and happiness all
the best paul i'm not listening we
got my la upa here he said
eat all the best tyler brands p
s p s i burned a copy
of pyramid street to my computer hope
you don't mind of course we don't
i don't you don't mind i think
he's so special i was
this is so great and i'm really
excited it's a very nice message at
the risk of you guys getting spankings
what is pure moods again so pure
modes is like ah it was a
commercial that was on tv oh fuck
you i'm trying to get you spank
i didn't understand spam trying to get
you i'm trying to get you say
you got nothing to worry about by
the way we have speaking spanking you
you guys bought some stuff yeah well
here's the thing so i'm a dumb
and
i'm a dumb
oh you're a damn yeah you're saying
i'm a dom but oh i'm a
dumb and my subs love when i
buy the thing this way do i
have this relationship credit
okay so we both unbeknown to each
other acquired some spanking tools because if
if you're looking if you're just listening
to us for the first time ah
there's a rule on the show where
if you tell a story that you've
told on the show but on this
show not on other show another show
like the way i've been spang not
in line
life you get a spanking you get
a spanking if you repeat a story
on freedom and honestly i don't know
if we've ever had a justified spanking
we have believe spanked a bunch yes
so none of them were correct we
still haven't exactly nailed down when you
get one yes there is no justice
but there's no waste as the way
the spanx spankings i didn't administer
the way the spanks of minister by
kevin are i don't know why the
board you did that voice weird i
imagined you like with your on your
knees with your shoes do your knees
like dorothy yeah dorm style door style
do you know dorfler no it's okay
if you don't know what her foot
infection but opin in it okay that
might be by the way yeah um
so look up dorf by the way
kevin didn't want to touch anybody and
of course of course he doesn't want
to touch so read rather than you
extra anus right
all mr baines were baboons rather than
uses open hand he took a sharpie
and he would give a spanking light
tap a slight tap yes and we
realised well that's an inefficient spank it's
inefficient that's not that's not preventative it's
spanking we like to do much
so lauren but this little hand this
little rubber high was at a bookstore
and these were labeled as trump hands
which to me not funny over done
we get it but but i always
as rude as a sharpie hand if
it's perfectly a sharpie to become a
spanking sharpie uh
um it's gorgeous it's a really nicely
made hand take a photo yeah we'll
post you are very excited by your
pretending to spank you onto a boomerang
hey i don't know how to do
that i don't know how to do
that
beautiful and then i bought these i
searched for on amazon fly swatter shaped
like a human hand and they had
the same time we are buying these
things um yeah hopefully at the same
exact second probably probably yeah and you
got five of them all their multicolor
they
did not come in a single
so the all five of these have
had their they're shaped like cans yeah
they drown like hey they feel like
hands and they are you can use
them for anything hands can be used
for they sound like hands
they have opposable thumbs this if you're
making love grace or making love
what are you pretending to do grab
tea use a td lauren is needing
some fang oh oh oh oh you
like this yeah like the lameness lameness
missed you enjoy this zoo like this
lady ya kila why do you kill
what did you q why do
you kill norm peterson a fun little
bit of us serves a frivolous
maybe the sitter shit a lot fun
for future
i also like to say i think
we should put in the news studio
a hook on the wall where we
hang that yes absolutely seven yeah and
maybe a little plaque over it yeah
and it should be shaped like explains
what it be shaped like captain hook
and maybe the hook is captain hook's
nose okay yes in the hooky shape
like hacks captain hook's nose yeah and
coming back to it is like a
cactus hook
has like collapses cause cactus is a
cactus dress like captain hook yeah right
but the movie
no no no yeah of course we
know it's coming off the nose we
see a little speech bubble that explains
so we have the note speech bubble
so cactus hook is talking out of
his nose just shy
sex okay so it's cactus co snow
so cactus host is talking out of
his nose
and he says okay so i get
to tell you that something about these
flies fighters they're actually but does he
starts out by saying i'm kind of
cactus cuz i just say something about
the swatter
oh i want to get spanx now
because he's good they look so good
when it's not you cannot in organically
get spin really nice so if i
wanted to get spanked i couldn't get
pissed if i told the ceo if
you're fucking well it's a punishment it's
not a fix on a treat you
know it's nearly reminds me of when
i was in college and my we
did
this west side story romeo and juliet
scott if you go okay here's the
problem i know what i'm going to
introduce a new rule okay new really
try to get spanked you some good
basic
you get punched in the face you
get slapped with the hand and the
baby hand
you really want to use that baby
which would which would you rather be
i mean when i think the official
one is a baby hand or the
this can be like the desk version
and it's kind of like a symbol
of us recording and this one is
like the officials saying think we need
to test them out to see what
hurts more what's good about shall we
test them on chevy yeah that seems
ah
yeah because and it should be me
because i've gotten two three hey if
you're begging to spank shove in i'm
gonna let you do it it's should
be me because i've gotten the most
you've gotten the most know i'm being
you okay wait i'm filming why he
stands right up for it he's ready
no okay hey what are you going
to boomerang this or you just
anyway even as a video all right
how many do it do i just
give one swat house i would just
even spanked unjustly i feel like i've
been spanked unjustly three times kevin woody
what would you say yes three oh
yes i'm imagining this video being shown
in a courtroom i'm gonna try i'm
gonna try first the fly swatter then
the baby hand then a combination of
both
okay alright first slaughter both first this
water one oh oh god alright creep
and now the hand too
and now a combination of both
three what okay no sit down kevin
and tell us about your experience i
can't sit
huh she's the hand hurt the most
the hand hurt the most wow the
handbag itself it's heavy yeah hey use
the hand but what i think it's
a chevy yeah i think is good
about the flatwater is it provides more
distance yeah i think it's i think
it's more appropriate it has holes in
it so you can really build up
some speed with it yeah yeah i
think
yeah i think it's fair you think
it's tough but fair it's tougher it's
tough affairs huh just who's ah
the cactus whose
all cactus whose sets dorf oh dora
glad you remember don't you know tim
conway from the old carol burnett kodansha
you remember that show where they did
like ah curtain rod instead of address
of course i remember that's the only
way i couldn't know what you're telling
your tongue ball yeah sure ah dentist
can't stop laughing
the dentist who can't stop laughing a
wonderful yeah i used to when i
was a kid i love those when
they would break up all the time
now and then later i realised how
unprofessional truly well there was well i
mean there was so little joy in
the seventies they there's like zoom or
anyone enjoying themselves k lubes i feel
like i only talk about infomercials but
there are infomercials for
carol burnett that's like a thirty minute
infomercial yes and then they showed them
just like laughing the whole time yeah
yeah yeah well tim conway had his
own thing going for a while i
don't how he would do you sound
shows well maybe but he would sell
them as videotape yes you would but
how did he started to start how
do people know what the character was
for him to be able to say
he's really new it has video tapes
ps he so this character dorf was
tim conway kneeling on a pair of
shoes i think i've seen that yes
and then he knows there's already googled
it and he had various things various
activities dorf on golf on this and
so dorf on golf was him but
is actually god and cif to name
without what you think
dwarf oh whoa you know what yeah
nah i don't i think i thought
about it forgot it and then was
just now remind huh i've never had
i just thought it was like a
funny name like dorfman golf like right
sounds like oh yeah two minutes later
um but he he also had dorfman
fishing and i
remember that being advertised ah late at
night and me being drunk and ordering
that ironically because it came with a
ah floating key chain like a foam
key chain it's the brow yeah dorf
on it did it did it look
like door for de just say no
it was like it was like obviously
a regular old foam thing that you
would have if you are fishing so
you wouldn't lose some thing you know
it would float and then they just
slapped the word dorfman got it works
for me so what are we going
what do we got in terms of
doors check us out join join here
the video of dorf on golf or
do you want to know what dorf
means
i want ah both yeah okay dorf
is german for village okay okay that
doesn't help this right now what i
thought that was that's where i thought
that was it i thought it was
like tim conway explanation for what of
me yeah like it's oh it's an
accuracy
helicopter doe really buddy i had a
job
sport combining beauty you know this is
losing a lot when we can see
it either demanding i know the listeners
can't either but jackson by the way
there's the fake land oh yeah the
man who can help you help your
game
how did they get rid of his
let out of the get rid of
his real feet i think are just
directly behind like this angle i think
he eventually committed to have a special
appearance by vincent hsu valley the mean
goes from ghost jin golf the object
of the game is to get this
tiny little weeny ball into that the
tiny little away near haul away
what does a few strokes as possible
so he's got sort of ah the
hitler moustache that the tomorrow hitler mustache
he loved to do bad lennon wigs
bad toupee collecting the right information ski
valley is putting the caddies yeah funny
because he's very tall he's very tough
it's and i mean goes from ghoulish
yeah it was very total my head
with someone else and there he was
wasn't married to wasn't married to agnes
from an enlightened does that rap i've
seen enough chevron yeah i think so
maybe what who is vincent cervelli always
just give a lee who is he
e che only matches give early who
is he married tubes sheva ski a
chef and get that get that answer
for cheney name
mccallion and alice beasley house beetles yeah
actually it was actually passed peacefully elise
oh well at least she was moonlighting
she was agnes from walk back nah
sir yeah my bad day she was
mr pesto yes miss agnes de pesto
agnes de pesto yeah in moolah she
was these like the origin like she
was the third bit
lighting which is some moonlight what like
when moonlight roosevelt was just showed up
and said did someone say mood lighting
what what if the light's moonlighting was
a tv show with a simple shepherd
and bruce willis
oh that's why we have bruce willis
and why we have civil or no
no she was famous already yeah she
was in american horror story
good na roster
nashville okay
nah resto a tv actor for yes
yeah yeah so isn't he i mean
he was in a couple of things
but moonlighting made him a star so
so much so that by the end
of the first season he was like
and it was the first use is
only like ten episodes or something he
was like massively huge yeah and being
thrown movie offers wow
wow here's the trajectory he did moonlighting
he did commercials for cd-roms golden wine
coolers wow he did die hard and
then he did his out his albums
bruno the return of the return of
bruno whose first was just the return
of the fur he put out an
album called the return of bruno who
the fuck buddy knows
oh yeah that was his musical alter
ego though a lot like yeah whatever
gavin who give garth brook gavin mcinnes
ah gavin mcinnes is garth brooks is
a straight guy stuff is probably yeah
i mean you're gonna have to be
more you fucking nail that's absolutely the
perfect description yeah like that he is
that guy who said i got punched
in the face outside of the thing
did he know he didn't yeah he
did me no good no bob that's
richard spencer's affair but i think again
it's also gonna catch them i think
he got punched too yeah um yeah
he's it should happen i hope so
this was it
is illegitimately good to harmonica player though
okay i think it can you like
i'm i'm honestly i don't believe you
bruce willis don't accept that harmonica saturday
night live and and will hear it
and fees
ah
are your we've talked about feet before
imo yeah we're not done talking about
i'm all over that wiki are you
really yeah have a good rating you
really
is it just women isn't meant to
owe on their um i don't know
i had all been i've only released
searched my friends because i'm like how
creepy is a wage and you have
to look for me i mean female
okay
what do we have any any harmonica
video you want to see if you're
on there i'll google it right now
yeah google for me we talked about
that ah backstage at a spontaneous nation
show the idea of like are there
female foot fetishes right he loved me
of male feet yeah wonder it can't
be possible
what do we to tim playing it
on letterman okay that's good no but
linked me to cool op's feet oh
holly that's nice where are there you're
probably in one of those pictures like
your dumb sneakers in there
it's just
look at him go
that's pretty high it's i mean it
is impressive isn't it i'm honestly i'm
saying time
um
i know like half of it is
just getting one that's in the right
key
you know but still
all pictures from airwolf where she's wearing
like sandals or when people are just
like maybe a couple from home or
she why why would anyone like a
foot i you know it's it's i
have to come to terms with this
because i don't know it's it is
weird and i feel like i avoid
posting anything where my feet are shown
because really i know that the picture
oh that's sucks
you think about that it's weird but
it's also like see it's also like
you're sexualized get the fuck da sneak
in some big down there like yell
this phony yeah it's it's difficult because
it sexualizes a body part that you're
not used to being sexualized but also
it's like fine because i don't
because who cares if someone's utilizes it
but someone like splurging but the thought
that was anything else that is of
me online is also gross so yeah
what else you got i gotta tell
your ass okay we need to take
a break we'll be right back
let's come back hi hi hi lauren
has an orange or is that a
tangerine aim what is this clementine mandarin
with some business there wasn't what the
fuck is that the seedless little citrus
your a c
let's little citrus
get out of my house and into
my car
and thereby into my dreams i love
the flavor of adult you don't well
i mean ah i would imagine it's
tangy it's not taking an i would
imagine it's juicy stop describing school
ah this is getting me all flustered
so you guys want to talk about
what's the for ya what's the horny
if you've ever been with i read
so i asked no question narrative you've
ever been ah i guess watching bruce
will
but what does that what does that
mean like like like the hornets you've
ever been in you couldn't you couldn't
have yelled at least you couldn't get
it out couldn't get it out just
like you got stuck in sandwiches like
i'm horny i don't know what to
do what's the longest you've ever gone
being in a state of haughtiness comes
to me at night it comes to
me forty just comes to me at
night
my balls swell up to the size
of deciding a suck
how big was it like it's like
a baboon's anus that should yeah it's
smaller than a breadbox definitely you could
put that in my box we ah
is that you know that ah what
what does it you held a koala
what am i it's a wallet and
a wallaby and
wallaby were those the only animals you've
ever held like you ever do they
ever let you hold a humanity to
arctic animals yeah yeah they ever let
you hold anything at a zoo normal
i don't think so that was very
special i feel like at this well
though we're talking about the way we
were in australia we were in perth
and we went to a quiet sanctuary
animal sanctuary oh my god it was
amazing we saw
oh so many amazing things i mean
ostriches that that hay on the head
oh we'll wait tattoo on wow you
like your head and remember everyone said
it was an emu when i when
i talked about it and because you're
in australia it's an mmo and i
was like nope and i showed the
picture and it said ostrich yeah bitch
and an ostrich beach isn't a hijack
at the big
rocks in my head tragic this isn't
ulcers
but i loved that experience would you
go feed kangaroos who were like right
next to us and stand next to
them i was a little freaked out
by the kangaroos because you you walk
into this like and those we dug
about eggs the jump only limit they
were all injured by like cars and
stuff yeah these were at these animals
at the scene they all had tired
tracks yeah
they were all on crutches the big
bandages but yeah that being so close
to them was kind of weird to
me even though obviously they're around people
all the time like this is their
gig now it's like they hang array
and you can walk right up to
them but it still felt like i
guess because they'd never been that close
to this
animal yeah that's like i don't know
what he's gonna do that's how desensitized
to it i became of like oh
i guess it's cool just to be
around these animals that when i went
over to the ostrich it was like
yeah it's obviously safe to be next
to this ostrich and then pick me
the goddamn they're standing in front of
a fence to get his picture taken
with the austro selfie with the austria
didn't you capture it while back i
literally got
yeah live photo me yeah the live
photo feature for god but just bumped
me right there somebody those are amazing
to see up close said no i
don't think i'd ever seen one like
there and the shoes running so fast
and so oh man feeling love they're
like six foot taller than that probably
like five by seven no i think
they were like seven feet tall with
their necks up their crate with them
don't you
think one heels they're like why did
i make them wear those heels because
sexy i mean no don't get me
wrong i was turned off honestly if
ah if an ostrich were wearing heels
and you came up behind one like
you'd mistake it for a woman like
a woman in like a victoria jackson
style dress wow victoria jama used to
where the poofy the puffy dress
isn't she like alt right yeah she's
insane now
don't even think it's ult there's nothing
ult about it it's not alternative comedy
right she's like a crazy religious right
yeah great great grey really hg hear
about what you hear about the the
church of latter day saints they wanted
to see time fly and i really
what is this a joke no no
yeah you're the one with the church
liturgy you can't you can't
you don't want to be called mormon
well too bad i still feel like
you're like johnny carson lee when they
want to call apparently yeah no want
to be calista this is true this
issue is absolutely true none of them
want to be called mormons
um no you're supposed to say jesus
i still think you're gonna change there
the church of jesus christ of latter
day saints you can't say they don't
want to say l d s they
don't want to tell me his ds
can't even say oh yeah why is
this they don't like the connotational because
it came to him in a vision
from god i know a person who
who um his his relative was one
of the people who connected with god
like one of the one who who
has a direct line yeah hotline yet
hotline to god damn how often would
god talk to him whenever i don't
know i didn't ask about that um
it was just someone i knew from
um growing up and i and he
went on a
mission for two years to amsterdam we
are pen pals i had a lot
of pen pals yeah oh yeah tell
us about one of them what was
the blood type okay i'll tell you
no i'll tell you a different one
i grabbed this bag in italian i
had a male italian pen pal when
i was in like like sixth graders
did it seem exotic to you it
was but it was like it was
harder to know what to say to
him so i really fell off quickly
and was much happier with my female
pen pals bow because you could kind
of know what to write about female
issues i don't know what i was
writing about but it just felt like
oh what am i gonna say he's
a boy did you ask them feel
like pizza probably why you like pizza
you're where it was
born
you like meatballs you meatball i like
hamburgers i'm from america
what's the most american food dog
peanuts and cracker jacks apple pie apple
pie yeah i don't i never hello
i wonder if apple pie and apple
pie are pretty good i don't like
a fruity pie i had to eat
to eat pies lauren are ya
oh interesting that's uninteresting to you
hello we're talking about something in what
i tried to stop you before it
got interesting i didn't want to miss
the interesting part i'd go ahead laura
and i used to be like you
i didn't like fruit pies and now
i do i'll be open to it
what happened was i was acting in
a scene and i doubly in the
first take ate like two bites of
pie
lie and then i draw i replicate
and i thought well this won't be
bad i've you know doing four takes
of this and i think we did
twenty eight takes or something like that
and dead bore because you kept fucking
pie commercial oh i didn't keep fucking
up ah tai kept falling in your
mouth no they just wanted a key
coverage from every angles for some reason
so
ah the prop master came up to
me afterwards and i said how much
pie today and he's had two complete
pies wow
yeah what do you what do you
what do you write down a code
ah
why did you because he was wondering
about like oh never mind oh i
was looking at the other thing yeah
oh yeah um but ah have you
ever had apple pie with cheese but
i never was i've never had that
either i remember being in awe i
think of marie calendar's and they ho
they had in the napkin on the
napkins printed on the napkins um orion
that said an apple apple pie without
the cheese is like a hug without
the squeeze oh you know what's got
you've told that story before have i
yes on this show i don't know
if it will show you five
yeah seven chevy is chevy's gun shy
by the way dick useless okay you've
never heard weiss you've never heard i
don't think i have i agree i
don't know that it was on the
show but i've heard you because i've
never been anywhere else but i have
a horrible memory i had never i
have a good memory i had never
heard of anyone i think part
of it as i say i have
a remember when you're not here to
them also like we get high all
the time okay that's up i don't
think that's your burn off the brain
please talk no plea what happened what
happened not talking you happen to us
well you're not talking anymore knows sqa
sky to do this sound like i'm
from like the sandlot
do you know i've never seen that
i've never seen that movie either it's
after my time yeah i guess i
would have been weird but i talked
about on stage ah in brooklyn one
time i talked about not having seen
it in the audience is like oh
children's movie i have a thought that
i was just thinking last night about
this like when you have these movies
that are
like everyone's cultural touch whatever yeah i
haven't seen a bunch of i'm okay
yeah neither oh and i think ghost
pretty woman sure i haven't seen scarface
i don't know what the godfather two
people shouldn't be like oh they should
be like oh good you get to
see it sometime in the future and
i also think i'm gonna die at
some point and i don't care about
that mu
movie right why do i have to
fill my brain with that and then
die i don't it just but it's
like what do i care i don't
have to see that there's there's no
end game to that yes okay but
you probably know the references from scarface
without having seen yes like what aig
pretty little mouth
i don't even know what that is
i say hello to my best wish
that's a friend porter ya pretty little
bow say hello to my best friend
allow me to introduce my college room
you probably know the pretty woman stuff
ah maybe you would test me big
mistake i don't know which i don't
know what they that's what we did
in front of bubble gums in hawaii
i just know oh that's right i
know it from that okay
if you are doing refugees spilling tea
is from when she goes shopping and
they won't help her when she looks
like a street worker and then she
ah this tracking sex sex streetwalker sex
worker when she comes back next walker
the sex walking deadly rich for man
six workers zombies oh you work on
commission nobody's that somebody doesn't work on
commission don't you big mistake bitch oh
huge associate shopping or something yeah she
comes with all these okay well what
else is there from pretty woman that
people know when he snaps the ring
box on her finger and she's like
oh i've i feel like that was
in commercial so i saw that and
that was improvised
yeah um what kind of lunatic would
laugh like that she knows yes to
laugh okay wait so richard gears snapping
that box and startling her was improvised
keep it in good improv richer yeah
i mean um it's famous what a
load of that scene
i'm not seeing dirty dancing or talking
okay nobody puts baby in the corner
i'm sure you know i don't know
what that is although i is her
name baby that why i say yeah
okay which also is like so weird
right yes she's strange someone literally put
her in a corner or what what
happened ah or or they're saying they're
gonna toss her over there because he's
saying it too
patrick swayze saying that to her father
i think he says to her that
is one i do want to see
i thought he was like defending her
to someone else that movie i can't
remember if i've seen her i've seen
it but just like on tv you
know like just i had ah i
don't know girlfriend in high school not
really a girlfriend but ah okay let's
give him the benefit of the
she really she really liked dirty dancing
and i was like oh like she
was she was a dancer
oh so she got you ask but
actually no um which had a little
firewall stumpy
she was like a dorf
she's real dorf does she's real like
dorf with boo door fun dancing no
shit she was a dancer and she
really loved dirty dancing and i was
being very snotty about like ah no
i have not seen dirty dan it's
like why not to do just live
long and be interested in what she
is in but i'll have to learn
that lesson
i know it's i was and i
think i mentioned this maybe the other
day on a different show on or
am but i but i had a
girlfriend who was telling me about the
best concert she ever saw which was
phil collins and this is nineteen ninety
three i was like fuck that guy
i like we didn't do a big
monologue about why fuck that guy yeah
and she's just trying to tell me
about it
show shy yeah fun times she's like
well he's a really great entertainer i'm
like yeah fuck him because this is
this do anything that's like wrong witness
the murder and he didn't do anything
because i like phil collins know he's
great i love it i didn't know
if he if you were saying like
oh he's like bad no way i
was saying artistic it was all artistic
like he's pop whatever shut up yeah
yeah yeah god why do you waste
so much time when you are younger
trying to be cool and what's that
high fidelity lying about it's not what
you were like it's what you like
you might i may have ah flip
those but but that that is such
a big part of i think your
twenties of like your taste
defines you yeah yeah and if someone
doesn't share that they're not the right
person for right well you're trying to
figure things out but it's also that
that thing of you go through that
period in life where it's just you
are looking for things to despise you're
looking at theoretically looking for things to
talk shit yeah yeah yeah well god
no i mean i guess
you just have to go through that
i was sitting in a diner next
to some theatre kids a few years
ago memoranda
nathan lane manuel miranda
lin manuel miranda fun out of ego
shout a little cool but they were
they were they were like eighteen or
nineteen or twenty or something thirty twenty
one or twenty three twenty four one
hundred years old but they were all
talking shit about other people in their
theater department so hard i was like
oh that's different but i was just
like oh yeah
twenty zero like you're if you think
you're great yeah and you have taste
and you're and you're the best at
what you do and everyone else sucks
and no my reality you're all slight
variations of sucking yeah you reminding me
of um when i was in stockholm
like this was probably two years ago
so it was winter it was freezing
cold you didn't like it at first
first but then after a while like
you've got just start out to be
like yeah it was almost like shit
she wrote um i ah was at
i was freezing freezing freezing calling the
honestly the coldest i've ever been went
to this like cafe where they had
hot chocolate whenever like i was like
a greenhouse sort of really pretty it's
snowing outside and this one then these
like college kids come in who are
obviously like um foreign exchange you know
from
america whatever you call it setting a
broad united grace country the world studying
abroad and this group nerd greatest country
in the world talking so loudly and
being so annoying but the worst offender
and the most the loudest girl who
was so fucking annoying was wearing shorts
just wearing shorts there's just no way
you're comfortable
like it was right it was the
coldest i've ever been in my life
does she take off a jacket like
a long jacket or sigh reveal it
all think now i'm the horny superman
she just was wearing them and not
talking about it and it was like
your annoying
look we need ziggo break we'll be
right back
welcome back everybody we're still here fuck
you yep and if you're still here
fuck you too and if are here
if you want
supposed to be
so learn you have a game sherman
just came up with the campus to
play i want to give all just
trying to see where this goes i
don't give him credit um and we
should stop it's called monologue thief and
the way it works is somebody starts
doing a monologue it can be in
character it can be as yourself telling
a story and much oh my
a good best friend and much like
on the show we will interrupt you
and start telling our own story
but it is ah you can continue
the monologue but put your own spin
on it so basically you pick up
where it left off i keep going
and we can just go in a
circle yeah clockwise starting with you sure
go okay
i was born i'm sure
and but it was even in so
nobody knew celebrated and just the right
way with playworks being bang boom everything
going off around me i couldn't even
believe it that was my mother's pussy
pushing me speed out onto the loading
dock i'll never forget the first shot
i saw this guy shoot liberty lead
down to
shit happy birthday i got to something
wasn't what i expected it was beautiful
jigsaw puzzle of what ten pieces of
the map of the united states which
is where i want to go because
the statue of liberty
she was this person who did it
in times square she dressed up like
her but as i said earlier as
i said earlier this was not in
america this was in france i was
in france time square i do it
because everybody was family
ooh fraud say they leaned over to
me and say boo boo boo rubles
i want to get it outside you
i'd put you in a shoe this
was a populist shah of the dive
in times square fridge now fast forward
to three thousand eight d i am
a mod
portal i have not been able to
die everyone else is dead i the
only living being on this earth all
bugs are dead all sharks are dead
al-qaeda cat the dead there is one
dog i have heard about it i've
not seen it where have i heard
about it in the newspaper that i
create every single day
a i have a printing press that
i put the daily news in and
i roll it off it just makes
me feel normal but i'm out of
paper so i have to use gum
wrappers so it's a very tiny newspaper
that only most corinne show why god
by java mouse i've found a skeleton
of about should i put some fur
fur on my push kid on by
i too i've had to take this
get off put god first that the
fur on topic and every night i
wished to the blue fairy please make
my mouse come to life please make
my condo my mouse come to life
in this make my cum come to
life please think like come come to
life
plea please let me give bird dog
bows this real please i want to
come on this mouse won't you let
me come on this valley magical come
i'll make it real please please please
oh now's bash deal day i'm all
alone in paris french at three thousand
eight d with
my bausch skeleton i don't know what
to do with my shelf should i
go out on the tao
no i should not because what i
should do instead is take this uv
light and put it over the mouse
to see if i really did come
on this mauser if i missed it
every single time i know what you
know you may be wondering
what's my name
well i'm about to tell ya it
goes a little jump dig like this
my name is my name is my
name is m
yes that's right i'm m and m
goodbye forever the end
well we did it we did it
what a monologue well i would like
it if people were would perform that
in their you know high school drama
yeah like debate club or word for
word all the dramatic internal speech speech
copy dramatic terps yeah dramatic interpreted just
word for word do that yeah
and see how it goes i'd like
to see it all written out for
sure yes yes please write it all
out for us ah and let us
know that was ah that was that
was that was
what we call the game it was
using a model up t mana lucky
fuck you so fuck you and your
little friend best friend allow me to
introduce my lovely wife of thirty yes
fellas
phil phyllis scarface there's a store in
on king street in charleston called phyllis
it's mad finally not there anymore but
it was there for it was it
was there when the first time i
went to charleston in two thousand and
six and then it closed down and
then it was just this empty storefront
for the longest time
time and it had the most depressing
like eighties font and it was just
called phyllis and i think it was
a clothing store have you win so
yeah he's fine what do you mean
like what what what would you like
wow because i like i write like
script but it's like tacky i saw
that font the other day that i
was like why was this popular in
the eighties it's like the chorus line
fonts is the only way i can
you know like new york film academy
or unrelated to that yes like that
yeah it's sort of playbill font but
fatter do yeah i mean yeah now
have you been to the burbank mall
like that's like one with a glass
elevator that i filmed in once yeah
he's real close element is it like
new
our downtown burbank were like it was
like buy the old ikea and stuff
yeah yeah okay so they have all
the weirdest stores there that yeah because
hey i'm all isn't used to be
very popular and used to have the
only movie theater in but really yeah
really all the stores are like closed-toe
know it i look i've been around
here for you know twenty five years
whatever so i've seen the trajectory of
it it was like the only movie
theater was there you had to go
to it i believe i saw sigourney
matters yeah it was a cool like
the yeah the mall was it had
it had it has this like train
down on the bottom floor and all
this stuff and then they built other
movie theaters around and they built up
the entire area and now
nothing is there and every other stores
closed every store is a weird name
that looks fake like i want to
take a picture of everyone when i
see it cause it's so stupid what's
stopping it i don't know how to
use a phone
but it's just like who's it for
yeah i don't know always yeah
so phyllis has finally closed it's finally
closed what did someone maybe the head
shop fun
selling e juice
spelling definitely so ejuice did you ever
study chicks
oh no your wolf and the old
rule if there was a vape shop
on the corner that had a banner
that says e you see cigs super
excited about e juice now was that
it was that maybe a a an
early vape so type of thing yeah
or rightly wasn't were they getting it
wrong i think we've talked about once
we never wanted to find out what
it was
let's try new curry liquid i call
it a liquid yeah
now this story is either
alright look we have to go right
look that's gonna do it for episode
twenty five freedom and i know in
the books we only have one left
very very special episode in the very
special episode next week ah no if
in case you're wondering we're not gonna
have special gas i'm gonna cry when
well we we drive we don't know
we might i don't know do you
think will ever cry on the show
i pitch it no we did we
did when we were talking about songs
made us cry yeah we did we
cry though i think we did i
did we did i did i will
say that i was talking about that
song literally two days ago to someone
else and he got choked up but
hey i was like jesus christ i
feel
i feel weird because i'm a very
emotional person and i feel like a
very sentimental and i can cry very
easily i did not cry when during
that episode that's okay i cried on
the way here to a song for
no reason which saw you know it's
gonna make you confuse the alpha popcorn
yeah
and
oh she's weeping
i just started crying to us johnson
is the liberace now
uh i wanna fuck that i wanna
fuck you what do i wanna fucking
in my brand new car
you know it isn't like her dress
is it just a chicago show all
we only know it's ah show demand
chicago now it's shown about chicago yeah
it's about a highway
just because you miss home kind of
made me nostalgic i guess i was
trying
grace
uh alright well hope you enjoyed that
they were all linked for dry right
now i do understeer dry your eyes
a guy wrote back when i played
the mason jennings song that he's opening
for mason jennings and heard it on
freedom and they're playing the show on
september six which is my birthday whoa
are you going to go since since
years fuck that and fuck you will
see next week fuck you love you
a