to jay jay jay jay would you
do
to do two hundred let's count from
one to two hundred ok one point
satra two hundred and eighty did it
i can't believe we made it to
two hundred on you i was really
looking forward to show it off and
strutting my stuff you don't even know
seventeen of course i do eighteen nineteen
twenty but you forgot seventeen sixteen and
then
theater
wow can you imagine doing two hundred
of this no alice i don't think
if i didn't guess how many episodes
we've done what would you say for
ten i'd say twelve thirty maybe but
i don't remember any of them don't
touch my foot with your foot ooh
wasn't me it was me long low
dog wag
wow whoa wag no one's ever seen
a picture of hall with this one
is one one don't give it away
for free yeah you showed up right
tobia you gotta go to wiki leg
it's behind a yes right right tobia
yeah it's in the freak tent yay
he's go around the corner and you
see my leg
three i like the idea that there's
just assume that i have a fricking
like an old fashioned gotcha oh hey
you know shit freak tent yeah i
should i should also have a bunch
of fleas on unicycle
they really know how to do that
back then yeah back then they did
they forgot today's modern fleas are very
adept at all sorts of the snow
moderate please don't want to work there
so easy they want going on looking
like hey please people maybe stop buying
your avocado toast that's what i'm saying
yeah just take the paycheck you're getting
take the
paycheck fleas what do you think they
get paid a dog blood um well
you don't compete in food like you
get paid or please what are they
going to go to a store oh
i know i really miss again one
fleet it's very rich for you from
red hot chili pepper oh and that
brings us to our guests yeah yeah
let's bring him in plea the actor
flee
he did ask cat monologues once that
was cool was the cool huh
okay i got to meet flee well
there you go i know it's been
a dream of yours for quite some
time
you rub his back i was freaking
out i wanted to meet lee anthony
kiedis another one and four and the
other one other ones the other ones
so at least two hundred episodes so
yeah by the way this is freedom
oh i'm not flee them i'm scott
i'm paul and flea is not on
this show no not every day if
you came here
are expecting the flea podcast guess what
you're out of your damn mind runner
gord you're out of your depth yeah
but you know it's the two hundredth
episode and i was thinking about this
a lot leading up to today yeah
and i put together a montage
you put together a montage of previous
episodes yeah here we go
hi welcome to the first episode three
actually rock out i heard you say
that you told me this story before
and we're back oh wow yeah montages
how about the oscars how about you
i know this is my montero months
and months and months i put together
a list of two hundred things i
like about you know stuff why you
switched to the oscar you we talk
over each other
that's true you don't like what somebody
saying start talking
this is a good rule for everybody
yes if you're bored with any conversation
just start talking don't like what you're
hearing make the noise you want to
hear
anyway i wonder that too and blue
out the window as i was gonna
show no way we're crying right now
remember any of them no okay it
wasn't one hundred and eight in sort
of like a fugue state one hundred
and ninety nine for paul and one
for me in my role scott o
share some of the same traits
male gender white may like take your
white male genders
he held the title
what about the oscars montage what this
is muslims not in hair but who
cares you are telltale mad about it
please yourself
spent a full day listening to like
five episodes of this show that we're
recording right now um we don't care
when it comes out or what we're
slowly look we've recorded these two time
we need shit to talk about it
tell us tell us about the mantova
ask the in memoriam montage where they
showed a bunch of people with already
seen this guy
oes like nessun dorma yeah and that
was really nice so it was really
so dorma yeah joe like yeah didn't
have a name too that's beautiful
it was a nice choice sometimes the
song can be you know and it
was jacked it is it connected to
death i don't know the the word
i don't either it was a pretty
song in another language right i think
mean sleep right yeah yeah no soon
means you soon will you soon will
sleep okay so i guess because you're
dead yep true
was that one dude and some younger
do i believe it was his son
maybe was the son yes that's nice
why yes and did his son just
leave them out there and just start
singing and he's like what are you
what do you do you and emmy
he's to be safe singing ness to
endure me surprised his dad like my
dad doesn't know that i can sing
as good as he does i'm going
to wait until
the oscars as good as he does
and then after after the songs oh
i've got a turtle with a dad
that was me did you know that
was my mouth moving
okay what did you not like about
it they show you no pictures of
this person that person various tamale dead
people although sometimes they get them wrong
i don't know about anything they leave
people out and that's usually well here's
the thing too this time because they
didn't want to leave anybody out but
they still did i say they did
it for a while and then all
of a sudden i was three at
a time no five it was a
a block of nail yeah next only
at the end and you i don't
know why
shot why did he put the names
on the screen i thought that was
rude it was really should have had
my tv should have been full of
the names not in the background i
see that there are things you thought
it was rude you slapped your tv
i did and it's called the slab
too
what florida to what is called the
tabloid stories about it oh i see
i see but i deciphered removing yeah
anyways you slept me the tv so
sad but that is like there's all
the meals jobs and all the make
time for that no i don't i
mean joint for that well you know
because we took up a chunk but
if you're gonna do there you're gonna
throw thirty names of at the end
let's just see the pictures as well
yeah give me time to read two
of them if you're gonna go wanting
thanks they put up fifty names yeah
from far away and then they go
right to come but people have paused
buttons now you know wow you wanna
have the live experience that's true i
didn't go you're right i wanted the
live experience i just rolled right through
and i thinking i'm gonna go back
and pause this and read every single
day exactly never did i think there
might have been like a qr code
or something if you wanna see the
complete
list of dead people go to your
local cemetery
they're all burned to the same place
your local cemetery
wherever you are
terry should have a list of every
single dead person who's ever do they
do on the fucking thing
fuck you was the two hundred times
just like see what's thing it's like
the fuck i'm saying every dead person
who existed ever the passenger manifold is
a metal box talking about manifesto when
the gravestone yeah
could you imagine if you went around
to every single one because you want
to know rather than like they have
a list and you say no no
no no i want to i want
to really absorb this yeah well run
to every single headstone yeah and let
me just get these names yeah yeah
and i'll send you make your own
because remember you know i'll just do
a picture cross reference the other
yeah because yeah well you did yes
yeah that's a good idea thank you
i would take up some time it's
a good use of time
users are lowered right yeah oh my
gosh so bored life so boring yeah
do you remember did you have this
when you were a kid you'd say
you were bored and then your mom
would say like here's a bunch of
chores you could do yes jesus wrong
move i never made that mistake i
go and i feel like my moment
trigger some ideas i said it was
bored not die
dying to be put to work but
i don't like i don't like if
you're bored you're boring that's not true
yeah i don't think that's true i
think anybody can be bored it's even
a boring yard i want so say
as a kid i once dated a
mormon girl you know who i found
out you know how to touch her
i don't know did you say you
never escape
published any of that joke so what
oh ah what's what's the more the
people you have your friend jump on
the bed yeah so insanely fucking to
say that no nasty it's actually grosser
than just having like imagine believing in
god
right and then you're like i've gotta
figure out a way she did
hey god i got your guys just
didn't know about soaking he knows oh
invention he's so frustrated god is so
frustrated by soaking like i'm ain't got
me i know
but yeah we never established any of
the rules of what we could do
or couldn't do um in that regard
so i just kind of was like
you know taking stabs at it to
go in like this is alright it's
alright and i've never any complaints but
the one thing was the story is
unseemly
let's say it was a tangent you
want yeah like wage anyway it's your
story your mom did judge it just
said it's a tangent doesn't the story
hasn't started what's happening within that tangent
and describing you're just a tangent oh
is a tangent he's off the hook
taking a stab at it
it's just good it's just good like
this like never said anything
ah
was well received as what i'm saying
da don't know what i'm but the
story part is oh toys best friend
jumped on the
the story part is that i found
out they that she wasn't allowed to
do anything on sundays cost money right
i didn't know that was ah we
talked about this we have yes well
to me but it reminded me of
your story about like if you're bored
so she threw money i'm saying yeah
she threw a book at me of
like here's here's the mormon book of
like
things that you can do with our
money and then we had to go
through here's my user manual and every
single thing was shitty and so we
ended up not doing anything go to
the park and look at a bird
i mean i can think of a
million things but they're not exciting checkers
chess i don't think there can they
play board games and when i say
hey i think so can play
cards cards probably that's more like gambling
and as many gambit cards there's so
many games have cards in them who
know the rest oh my god it's
so true yeah against humanities i my
favorite game dutch blitz oh yeah we
started playing there the other day zoe
fund oh jolly i know june's really
into it from listening to le podcast
last yeah i think she got cool
up into it because they had took
a trip yeah then when we went
away cool up introduce dutch blitz to
me do you like it i like
it but playing it with two people
is different i guess than playing it
is dutch like she dutch blitz like
secret hitler but you go have these
yeah it's it's a card game where
you're basically stacking in a certain order
and then tr
gonna make piles it's like you just
started as fast as you can make
piles like me files you don't know
you're making piles right now do you
know i i yeah i'll just take
a big duty duty
you did it when i ah
wash so she's the bad guy yelling
you out that's so it was just
a tangent when i worked in kelsey
grammer nobody resents the one another it
wasn't just damn jail we heard yeah
i know but it made sense i
wanted
we don't have you on the show
to make sense i wanted to hear
my voice okay oh that's so tough
and i was already gone kelsey grammar
presents the sketch show um i remember
everyone in it yeah i want that
to imply yeah yeah um i we
were shooting somewhere and i was sitting
we were sitting outside and i was
just saying like on the stone wall
awesome and it was kind of chilly
out was november in london
and i remember the one of the
um some cold show one of the
grips this guy named owen who i
really liked stone wilson yeah holy shit
grip isaac grip that's how you to
start wow he was a grip on
kelsey grammar presents the sculpturing wow wow
wow you'll see
wow and he had done a couple
of lisa for that but they but
people didn't really didn't really catch on
yeah yeah real ones some as a
group they were like get back to
acting yeah okay is that how he
broke his nose do it like yeah
ran into a light or something yes
josh it's exactly crazy ah the he
didn't pay attention to hot points
he got hit right in the nose
great what a good story thank you
paul well there's more
that was a tangent so oh and
saw me sitting on the stone ah
wall and he said is oh i
still think anton wilson
paul mate don't sit there you get
piles poles piles he thought i would
get hemorrhoids from sitting on the hell
is that something that happens i don't
think so i'm sitting on just stone
or you put like ice on any
funnier if you sit on anything you
could get hemorrhoids what yeah hey i
want you have a standing desk while
you do that show not nothing any
chances
also i'm doing my taxes oh right
oh my god how are they going
this year not good oh
i would government eight billion dollars oh
my god everyone had a lien put
on my finance oh yeah i remote
yeah i've had so many of those
yeah because i was raised with no
skills yeah why i we didn't have
like homework or anything and nobody talks
about cool money in school no and
you really we had a whole mac
but call me
making you pancakes and that's about all
i remember very economical rambled eggs and
whey how are your pancakes where they
flat ah well at the time i
think i was better because i'm poor
and poor pancakes know we've discussed sizing
you're making tubes right now i'm making
cubes
like the fun cake cubes what are
you talking about there you're so bad
you're paying gigs or q i don't
know i don't know what's going on
but we gotta we gotta stop motion
was mainly based the last one this
way i also had one shop cakes
are so bad they're cube we also
had what job would you make burnham
know no dead
what's going on here what is going
on with you what's up being flat
are you going to scarborough fair
hey yeah i made a box i
mean a jigsaw puzzle box i made
to use the jigsaw i did i
was that was fun i've never used
i think it's a horrible idea for
seventh and eighth graders yeah we did
do it terrible yeah it's really the
show whatever got hurt from my work
the only reason they have you do
it is because like if you're gonna
fly
monk then you need to have that
as a backup know that was our
yeah yeah that was our have to
go to the puzzle factory yeah oh
i see what you're saying now so
why are they making like good studio
was just a it was just a
assigned class i know that's what i'm
saying is it shouldn't be it should
be it wasn't sufficiently done that to
you well they did and i survived
it
um was gonna tell you like that
i like that attitude and i think
the kids need more misery think so
too really you build kids have too
good these days to have it too
good yeah with their ipods and not
getting hurt yeah and their ticks and
their talks
yes your lights your fingers by the
way are shaped like puzzle pieces did
you actually accidentally yeah i guess because
i actually just ran them through the
jigsaw when i was in seventh grade
oh do they fit together they do
perfectly that's nice yeah so yours no
they don't my missing one what happened
i think my wife threw it away
okay
founded under the couch and she threw
it away when i was under the
couch because i was in a hurry
so i urge you with your finger
under the coalition yeah and i'm sure
if that's so impossible to understand well
i was in a hurry so i
left i was in a hurry of
my finger on the couch i'm in
a hurry to get things
that
alabama was the state that's their state
motto i'm gonna hurt some guys like
this i mean a to get things
done oh yeah well she rush into
laughs no fuss about their other voices
were like oh yeah linda oak ridge
bow okay and don't know what alabama
do
what was album's big song that one
you shouldn't be able to call your
band an entire state or city is
a big song
i don't have no i've never heard
that song before it's great like chicago
just taking it for themselves say it
okay the decency to not name any
of their altitude limit ah that one
i know move to alabama hills alabama
bands the ah the official website helped
start their most popular song tour dates
and let's check out there tearing slash
a nope there i mean ah they
have they have a lot this summer
go see him in iowa or what
their songs are yeah maybe one of
your songs we i'm gonna show you
before they could play a note maybe
crossover with the cvb tour making garcia
mana
on an i'm a great guy here
with you
yeah i might have a cold number
one singles swag i got a ton
of em well name some tennessee river
why lady why don't know what else
the river i can remember how that
goes but i don't know but these
are all number one on the country
albums tow just play the one i
like what does it
called i'm in a hurry i'm in
a hurry ever from nineteen ninety two
oh why it was also our passing
period song my senior year so beg
your pardon at between like a second
period in home base or something like
that they would play which was we
have an ad first for help kids
lie
if you live not help kids live
yeah
russian mission to laugh snow foe
really gotta do this this time ross
man
no no
no wow
i have to dip shit
um it's a great suit to carry
on my wayward son kansas kansas another
one other unknow low on everybody and
some haven't been taken like alaska or
above florida florida yeah well yeah yeah
but he had the dialogue it was
a close one ally law
wow connecticut they would play a soul
they'd play a song at this one
point in the day every friday so
my home-based me home room was called
home base home base and they would
play it feels fucking every friday so
is the friday song and the nude
have one new one each year the
school sounds so cool and years so
then you're like this is the new
song for the years and when would
they premier it would
the first friday of the year is
ready to you they would unveil it
they would unveil it and then we
hope this is the song i think
there was ah the principal or somebody
picked up and um two and then
more yeah he didn't like it because
when i was country road take me
home that really annoyed me that's weird
yeah i thought it would be tied
into as nothing moving around like go
going from place to place no i
don't think there's something it wasn't it
wasn't celebrating you guys moving around it
was celebrating the fact that it's friday
would the whole song play
um i guess through the three minute
passing period passing here but calling it
that but i think what it was
oh no songs are longer than three
minutes passing good catch yeah they faded
out most songs were longer than self
imposed fame my high school on instagram
oh um and you know weirdo but
there was some
some reason why i started because there
was some connection to something but you
went there
but i think i think i followed
because of a specific event or something
and then i just saw like the
stories yesterday were like beyond time don't
be late did it and i was
like oh my god would i like
first of all if you go to
school that school now are you following
this account secondly if you see the
story that says don't be late what
is what's going on yeah i'm unfollowing
right yeah i think fucking is
too late if i'm fucking late i
would be um not heating them what
time does school start he think he
was i think it was a two
five you know five and then how
much time do you get in between
three minute we're in it only three
well mine i know this coin was
so big because the traveling know we
had to book it now we we
must have gotten five i
i doubt it you doubt that i
got my eyeballs as big as your
school i bet i got more than
five let's find out how big your
school was i was how many kids
were in your class aa hundreds oh
the nine hundred in my class okay
my high school does not my high
school by the way has ceased to
exist and closed down a couple of
years a new graduate they're like we
don't have any purpose anymore yeah
we did it we got him out
there
um on three thousand people i think
do knuckle three thousand dang i would
have it a little more than that
i think it was nine hundred per
classroom i was less than that by
a great degree really yeah by like
how many factors
oh
we're all sitting down oh no um
so they they don't have ah an
instagram but there is a ah bishop
mcdevitt high school alumni
she just shook her ice right oh
my oh the straw it's it's been
a long time since i've had a
seven and a long time in a
long time in la lola lola lola
lola lola thompson said just have it
up
and it was good how we have
to take a break do you wanna
get back to this after the other
side of this now yeah no you
should you should think to get back
to we'll be right back eat it
and we're back and paul has something
really important i was talking about looking
at the studies like i've been making
his hands and jumping up and down
when something started jumping up and down
on the bed
yeah we were doing my friend thanked
me recording
um there are sixty seven people that
are following the fishermen david alumni so
i do not know any of it
is not enough teach if you don't
have one hundred thousand followers to shut
down thousand that's not enough for including
people from the future school who have
not gone to the school yet yeah
it feels nobody's really
interested i guess but you know maybe
that's not really the place for them
to get that information maybe it's not
i don't know yeah okay so i
was just had a doctor's appointment and
um i was sitting in a small
room were dying by the way we
shouldn't mention to this listener thankfully i'm
not but my nose is doing the
i think i have
hokey pokey yeah that thing that you
had when we were supposed to go
to england no but i just can't
breathe okay so um you also have
a mouth yeah i'm doing overeating yeah
it's really cool he fucking god you
i know i have other holes to
breathe out oh god i was sitting
by
all these very old senior citizens was
either
no and this man
i'll just say because i actually said
another podcast but i had to get
an iron infusion some vitamins and um
you know you're like iron man but
but i was actually people getting all
sorts of infusion for the iron giant
some of them were in you know
tough situations and whatnot but this man
was talking to me at length today
which normally doesn't happen there are you
easily able to cut off my headphones
on and because it takes couple of
by the way if you're a man
don't ever talk to a woman you
know what agree he was very nice
um but i did learn a lot
about him and he learned a lot
about me and oh i um but
he showed me at one point a
picture of him a picture is black
white photo from the forties
of his penis
zara used to do it in my
day he competed a frame
it's all crumble for me in a
wallace silhouette
because it was um a picture of
a woman and three kids and he
said the baby that that woman's holding
is my wife and i'm next to
her and i was two and a
half and they were neighbors growing up
whoa and they recently not recently met
at some point they uncovered this photo
because what's going on
his dad the woman's dad so i
guess this guy's father-in-law kept this picture
in his wallet during the war and
had folded back the picture the side
with the boy before because he's yeah
he's two hands boy if i die
and then fucking the crouch get me
they got they eventually got that picture
back and they done full
and we're like that's handsome yeah how
did they get the picture back
they represented out of his cold dead
just like the owner what's your issue
with the idea of the picture i
thought oh i have not i have
no issue i think i was trying
to formulate something funny to say oh
right what have you had to be
someone who lit it up
what if you had to date and
marry someone who lived like in i
guess one square mile of where you
grew up because i could you know
like back in the back do it
yeah yeah back in the early nineteen
hundreds or whatever that's just what you
did you had to yeah well you
couldn't travel far enough to meet other
people yeah my block had enough people
that
at one of those could've worked out
if i had to yeah you still
got one on backup
yeah how about you i don't i
mean my neighbors to the left to
me to the right of me and
right across the street were all one
year older and they hated me and
made fun of me wow oh i
see so you're saying would it be
you're saying not what does a student
who wouldn't be at this juncture you're
not you're
not saying ah just what a few
were forced to do it you're saying
well would be able to yeah what
would the pickings be like for you
yeah because the people have to like
you yeah well that's a different thing
but i don't know if i could
do it but now i'm liking you
as a kid is different than not
liking guys adult
i don't think i was pretty much
eighteen and they didn't like me
mainly formed human everyone i met as
a child i made up my mind
about there and then and now i
feel the same way well i mean
it's kind of true with people from
like elementary school or something when you're
like everyone falls into these certain categories
and it's kinda hard to get past
that if you were to just meet
them now you'd be thinking about oh
i only know you as this annoying
brow
yeah i'd say you suck you're small
you're the smallest one here
hey thanks awesome every connected with some
people from my past and recent years
it's been very nice overnight but there's
people who are like bullies who i
don't know what they're up to but
actually i do have googled them so
you have a no bully policy when
it comes to reconnecting the people i
have no follow back no follow wow
hello back you know to follow back
remember team fall back on never forget
it you know it's only follow back
girl it's a weird contest and say
oh whoever wins will have any follow
them back because anyhow fine immediately muted
yeah ah what kind of prizes that
giveaway fit like fifty dollar gift
hard they shouldn't say the part about
immediately muting yeah that's like i'm wrong
i'm gonna do still have fifty bucks
to olive garden from family au soleil
yeah yeah year ago yeah chanel oh
the salad we should go get diarrhea
hey i'm on team whose hospitality yano
what does that mean that was one
of my restaurant wound up
we have to go through restaurant roundup
again oh my god you worked at
all garden of course you're not familiar
with hospitality i kind of only get
the same thing and it does always
give me diarrhea but i ah really
like it but you have diarrhea every
day that's not true anymore
i don't know if i've ever eaten
it all of garden hello we gotta
go with these ehlers indians i remember
eating at a place called maggiano yeah
i love mangia my janos growing where
they it's one of those places where
it's like here's too much food it's
the corner bakery but it's fancy
i'm not familiar with the corner bakery
well they were they were hey i'm
in that did i mean this thing
on so i guess i've always thought
they were the same thing but maybe
they weren't
i passed by that restaurant i know
i've talked about on here before the
big yellow house but i i passed
by the santa barbara went again when
we were going to big yellow house
yeah so i think i brought it
up because he was we we used
there it was chain and we used
to love going to it and they
would it was all family style it
wasn't where you daughter urine just an
orange county place well there's one up
in santa bar
herb roads that is good news let's
boogie beppo fan yabu buca di beppo
was family so but this is the
place that i think i mentioned where
they would weigh you and then they
would charge you by the town yeah
yeah oh wait the person yeah they'd
want you on the end of being
weighed or away the way the person
the person would do it
and the scale would be only less
disgusting yes so they so they wouldn't
be like you gained a pound while
you were here no
constantly
right time for way and after you
ate but they don't walk in yeah
when you walk in or when you
go to the table and then they
they determine how much you're going to
pay for your dinner that's demented
and that's so sick and they doubled
down on it too that's like so
does their like were wearing away you
and then we're gonna call your weight
out to the rest of the horrible
yes but it was fun like because
no no one else you were like
a kid well if you're no i
always wanted to have it done but
i was a kid and they if
you're under whatever twelve or whatever they
wouldn't weigh because it's not dramatic enough
yeah
that's like that's when they should do
it you won't be shamed you have
no idea what those numbers mean but
but i but so i pass anytime
i go to santa barbara barbara barbara
nah he's like seems to laser focus
on you waiting to take you down
he's doing it to me too
to the detriment of his own comedy
it's true that's true so anytime i
go up north to santa barbara oh
how beautiful she is
i passed this restaurant
it still has the cy it's been
closed for twenty years at least why
have they not demolish it with why
actually it's someone won't get off the
scale
the old man from up this is
my goal weight i can't stop looking
at it but yeah why wouldn't you
like turn it into something else it's
all its be funneled about a big
blue house and you can put a
bear in there sure it was a
classic show now what was the idea
he was a vicious bear who had
a hell honestly i was just right
past the point where it made sense
for me to watch that so i
just said hey
just couldn't i don't know what there's
there in the big blue house what
it was an a junior program nick
junior oh my god so nick was
a thing and then they were like
hey let's go younger you know i
did what was on nickelodeon
i feel like now all the programming
is kids programming i don't know it
was kids programming it was always kids
but it was nick juniors for like
little little kids so it was like
teens who are preteens who like being
slimed and yeah nickelodeon was younger very
cool you know if you're nine ten
eleven twelve thirty four projection some dancing
and then make juniors if you're that
that age and you have a child
no it's for when your your little
sister does the whole program it's adult
programs directed at adults who have children
so it's like r rated stuff and
then of course there was nick at
night which was the rewrite yes of
course a rerun switched i dream of
jeannie i want a dream of her
dream of jeannie i watched the pilot
of the dick van dyke show the
dick van dyke show and then it
it led me to watch that why
we don't know what are you up
to what's your end game what's going
on but it led me to the
rosemarie documentary well you know there was
one there is yes it's very good
who rosemary was a cast member of
the dick van dyke show but she
was really interesting in the sense she
was a child star wow who
who ah then toured the country on
the vaudeville circuit and also made friends
with the mafia
going funny friends with zanini and what
are you guys up to
it was sort of rosemary i just
moved here it was one of these
things where they were like hey you
kid will take care of her anything
ever happens call us and she was
like and i did
she got many husbands killed a fascinating
life rosemary sure i remember watched the
whole dock i did you watch the
whole thing i turned it off ten
seconds before the end we finally finished
the we are the world document oh
yeah good one was great oh that's
about the making of the song yes
yeah it's fascinating yes it's really fascinating
yeah yeah it's yeah the dylan part
is it's so fun amazing because dylan
is i i'm assuming
stoned out of his mind what what's
going on gotta be he's there the
whole time everyone is on cocaine i
think that's it's it's like one of
the stars of the documentary that they'd
never mentioned except al jarreau who's drunk
off his ass yes they do call
him out for being incredibly drunk yes
and to the boy where he kept
asking for more bottles of wine to
be brought in and they would bring
in them in atlanta richie would take
them back out
my god but um yeah everyone's on
coke and and bob dylan is there
and he is not a good thing
and no one knows why he showed
up that's the thing is is like
bob dylan shouldn't be doing this and
he shows up and then he can't
sing and everyone's like what's dylan going
to do they're like like office because
they don't do individual lines
nz i'm teddy and everyone just singing
together it sounds like trap first they
did
because everyone's got their work no one
whoa because they quincy jones directed this
thing and he was like now we're
just gonna do this if you canceling
in this key don't sing don't like
take it down an octave we only
want the people who can stay in
this range yeah yeah so they're they're
doing it piece by piece and so
that's why the solo parts
all the soul parts were at the
end yeah so they did all the
solo lines and no one wants to
give bob dylan one of these lines
because he'll sing it poorly so then
at the very end they're like ok
bob what do we do with you
and then they just like stevie wonder
imitates him at the piano going what
if you did something like yes bob
dylan's like how do i do this
how do i say and see that
to a melody yeah and so is
stevie wonder just kind of goes do
this this choice we make it with
save it arrow law has and bob
dylan's like okay we could i could
do that and then he does it
that's cool and he's obviously super nervous
about it and then everyone applauds and
they go yeah that's it and he
goes this is i was
really surprised at this and it was
very relatable he goes that that wasn't
good never goes no that was fine
i mean that states you didn't like
bob dylan yeah what did you think
you sounded like
ah have you never listened to a
bob dylan album
we should do it we are the
world of style sure yeah so how
do that are you just not so
the norwegian we are the world too
yeah that's what i thought yeah kurt
russell was in it he intruder yes
yes it was we did comedians st
first we did canadian singing i just
know it's christmas to raise
money for the la foodbank and then
the next year we did we are
the world and and kerr russell ah
intro the video of it and we
drove to his house and shot in
his study where his like boots were
by the fireplace and everything was very
funny yes he was very nice i
love him yeah i love him yes
great
did you ever see bone tomahawk yeah
it's great
that's one of the craziest movies i've
ever seen yeah and only for that
one last twenty minutes sir it's like
yeah it's like a west lorne you
gotta watch it crazy never yeah wait
why why you gotta watch it lore
and watch it with holly fucking creep
she was a free movie i've ever
seen is this
mrs doubtfire has there's that part where
like the the tennis masks in the
street and then like a truck runs
over or no my god she's dying
we just oh could you imagine your
daughter loves the bar nice doubtfire madison
there was a triumph street and there
was a
it was crazy and still can't because
it's based on a book it is
yes a good director this like the
bible yeah it's based on the bible
yeah does shalt not cover it's just
that thou shalt not cover fire
what does that i mean that's as
crazy as any of the commandments because
no breakpoint thou shalt not kill weird
that's why everyone talks about thou shalt
not kill yeah that's the star of
the show it's really important we know
that one but talk about the other
nine they're fucking weird thou shalt not
steal covet thy neighbor's wife yeah
i'll do whatever i want with her
sorry it happened
let's let's run them down that shot
not have no other gods before me
yeah that's rude thou shalt shalt not
make unto thee any graven image come
on that's that one stings i'm not
gonna lie out thou shalt not take
the name of the lord thy god
in vain
in first three very self-absorbed yeah yeah
obsessed love zoo remember the sabbath day
to keep it holy when we got
another one other one about him another
one and then we're like okay
by the way also honor thy father
by the way other than one sucks
um well you have to go to
confession and say i didn't honor my
mother and father and by the way
number six number six oh by the
way thou shalt not kill number six
it does feel like it should be
a number one number one number seven
ironically with a bullet thou show
shalt not commit adultery come on
lord knows we all heard it before
moved a few inches away from the
bike that was shampoo now shallows more
mouth related sure thou shalt not steal
as a than okay thou shalt not
bear false witness against thy neighbor lie
don't be a snitch either don't see
us and it just gets ditches and
thou shalt not covet
i mean three three these are fine
but the other sessions thou shall not
kill
um steel
you're right only two
the other eight are just two cares
they had to fill up the tablet
it's true i do like the bearing
false witness against your neighbor that there
there was so much of that goes
by that time so much glad like
ah he he had a whole bunch
of figs
i'm just making shit up yeah do
you think you'd be great on a
jury i've ever gotten to be on
a jury i was on a jury
i don't know if i was great
at it i know what i used
to have someone to be executed you
are telling me yeah but they didn't
count mine because i felt we were
voting on this
i um i took it very very
seriously to the point where should i
we ended up with a hung jury
i wasn't like the only dissenter but
we weren't like they were like the
fonzie
oh yeah what was his jury duty
his jury duty thing was it was
twelve angry men but he was the
only one who was like no this
guy's innocent this guy he knew something
about car parts no he just he
he felt like he was innocent and
then they were all pressuring him come
on we gotta get out of here
and then finally he figured out something
about the rear view mirror or something
yeah
but on a motorbike or something exonerated
the guy was like yeah and then
everyone was like we judged you
too harshly arthur fonzie we thought you
were agreeable
um we have to take a break
okay bye
and we're back and we're gonna play
i don't know if this is called
secret word but it is now and
by the way this is a thresher
if you are confused about what's happening
we've done this one hundred and ninety
nine times this is to do it
again yeah this is a three-tier where
we play a game and we have
fun
doing it and if you would like
to send us once a week and
have fun and therefore you can have
fun listening to us having fun and
we like each other while we do
like each other you like us and
we'd like you love the game write
to us at three dm usa gmail
dot com three m usa and email
dot com freedom it's so easy three-time
u s h
build ca do not write to three
m u k oh my god they're
so tired of getting your emails like
mine yours yeah yeah you're always right
into them yeah please tell law and
stop sinning no cmo i'm trying to
reach you guys
no wonder you're never here
um okay so we're we're going to
play secret word how this works is
we're going to text each other ah
i'm gonna text paul paul's gonna text
lauren lawrence gonna text me a word
and um we then are gonna improvise
a scene and we're gonna have to
say that word in the scene
and then ah lauren's gonna guess what
paul's secret word was paul's going to
guess what mine was and i'm gonna
guess what lawrence was so we are
all texting each other and and we
got to try to obscure the secret
word as much as we can make
ah you know make it flow in
normal conversation otherwise the other person is
going to know exam
really what it is so
um
here we go
i am texting waiting thank you got
it i've texted one to learn i'm
waiting for one from scott and i
have texted paul you can use by
the way any verb tense or whatever
of the word okay oh okay oh
okay okay add
and i have received the word alright
here we go in
hey everyone come in come in well
of course i'm gonna come in i'm
here hello come in come in please
oh she's beautiful so beautiful space me
thank you for getting here getting here
please you're not in far enough oh
i'm sorry i'm i'm a customer hey
i don't know i mean i need
you i was just passing by i
need you inside here right oh my
the door is open
right now i'm using all the air
conditioning guys come in come in i
mean he knows this just click and
close it behind you please oh closure
with expediency alright what's what what on
earth is happening yeah
let me tell you what's happening but
we're having an incredible incredible showcase here
incredible showcase yes okay but i'm hopeful
that may need some some big know
you're not good not anymore
because people were happy we could get
some big goods no
and this is not improv this is
life so terrible life you have a
terrible life if you prove you're supposed
to just say no well you can
say not any more
and also what i mentioned you guys
didn't seem to be all that into
the showcase of the art that was
happening i knew yeah oh yeah and
harry this isn't even a fucking bakery
i see you thought it was cool
i saw the cream puffs in the
window profiles and roles every sort of
little thing do you have a panoply
of
artworks
ah
look this is this is all art
of local artists but it has made
use of baked goods i see yeah
that's like confusion yeah you thought you
were at about okay i'm sorry yeah
the windows just auto hanging of cream
puffs and provisionals percentages and pictures perpendicular
to the acres kicks bested about and
also faster
vote and all sorts of funny little
ways look lambasted lambasted clam baked got
there naturally clumpy
now i don't yes to speak extemporaneously
i don't mean to be i'm not
trying to bloviate i'm not being coniferous
what i say every move not filibustering
oh nifer is carnivorous is that about
trees tears i'm not being lickety i'm
you're going to stay i mean like
a woman okay
a well i just i wanted to
show you all of us our local
artists made these visit this wall is
all of of bakery baked goods obviously
but then this this is just ah
this is a local artist who's using
various things from whose child you discriminate
you might say
various items from her childhood you have
ah wouldn't employ i see oh it's
a sort of higgledy piggledy food scene
let's undo shapes and sizes sir i
don't know what
your what your deal is here just
possibly do you're not interested to the
sorus do so specifically through i'm very
interested it's your name mr thesaurus or
something it's been well captured lunch it
goes grab your teddy bear grab your
blankie go home and cry to your
mommy about about what's going on here
okay this is
condescending and infantilizing
because i'm trying to sell some artwork
here okay if you don't have money
everybody getting the word out maybe i
have money i'm quite wealthy i own
several zeppelin
alright let's ah
everyone's got their word i think i
have a guess but i'm sure i'm
wrong because it gets so out of
control i think i wasn't paying attention
to other states when i was having
fun stuff expediency no no perpendicular no
oh i'm all those were to throw
you on their hail the piggly know
through a lot of red herrings and
no mine you know i know you
i'm supposed to guess yours yeah you
weren't paying attention no i was oh
what was it i i filed it
away i was coniferous no ah okay
a little way it was profitable i
did say if did you say is
that a big thing she said yeah
okay good yeah okay and what was
mine paw yours whose artwork
no no
as well i've absolutely no idea mine
was blankie
blankie
okay well this is good
yours will say yeah no one has
noticed oh i see it i mean
she's supposed to i know what it
is i need to lee
hey you said so many big words
at a certain point i just did
last track bloviate wow that one did
stand out but it felt pretty late
in after you've done a lot of
so good trick paul's trick is to
do like about ten before the real
one you've heard of gerald's game i
think and this is paul's trick
i loved you i've never called gerald
gerald gibbs i've never heard of so
sort of gerald's game no it's that
oh my god it's the best book
here's what it's the best book even
greater movie what happens is you and
your spouse go to a way your
your marriage is upgrade so you can
go to a movie and you just
think there's cure
so you go to a remote cabin
and you decide this is the time
to get into vdsl so you handcuff
your spouse to the bedpost and then
you have a heart attack on top
of them oh ca then a dog
eats part of you and then you
hallucinate a gigantic man and it turns
out that guy was real wo the
big spoilers your gerald's game yeah sorry
every
but you weren't watching that tonight who's
in that hope you weren't halfway through
reading it um two greats in the
mike flanagan diverse um ah preuss did
mike flanagan actually directed yeah he did
yeah yeah i'm carla gugino carla gugino
and bruce greenwood oh
mr usher himself and the guy from
the tall guy from twin peaks the
little guy from twin peaks was there
the giant as they call him to
noise name hold on paul you're losing
shane g remember those great years you
knew his name i roll striking was
it yes okay alright
right now we go ah now we
go the opposite way okay so i'll
take oh we go the opposite way
no real texts yeah paul text me
oh i taste orange and learn new
techs paul
i have texted loren loren has texted
paul i have texted scott great we
all have our words
everybody get iffy
oh come on and get aim here
oh good good good good i wanted
to come in grandpa stop what how
dare you can't control us we're all
working from home
you can't just i want it going
okay fine i'm in the middle of
of sort of typing something what are
you i don't keep a business report
for my work if that thing is
like a hundred pages yeah you're in
the middle if you have one hundred
more pages yes i yes it kind
of reporters this it's it's about a
lot of really into
tense stuff that's going on in the
world do you need any help i
mean i've just been sitting around waiting
to come in to see grandpa yeah
let's do a cramp once okay i
want you all to shut up duvall
dang stop your whining and whinging and
grumbles and mumbles i'm sick of it
now there's gonna be some changes around
here oh no everyone has to do
their fair share it's called teamwork
that makes the dreamwork that's exactly right
right i'll close my job close your
laptop oh ooh
my fingers ceased your computers might i
happened to be walking on my hands
today okay i get it you're in
the circus yes it's my dream grandpa
always wanted me to be in the
circus too it's history informing idea i
wanted you to fall from the highwire
to your death
oh grandma
i have murderous game and can keep
living here with you why you're just
so controlling it just feels like there's
just you call these meetings that just
go on and on they're completely interminable
i don't know what's going to happen
every time you you call us into
the room we never know what it's
about my heart just starts beating
just can i tell you something yeah
what i do it because i have
a compulsion i don't really have anything
you'd talk about it is what you
see you can't oh my oh my
god i don't just say that i'm
used to sentimental old vu oh my
god i was so worried your job
him totally unhinged you
so the crowns we pick it up
for you grandpa can i know you
don't want me to touch you but
putting it back in my cranium here
yo you're getting more and more like
a skeleton what are you playing my
ribs like a xylophone do do do
kick out there and once i saw
mister mental peace i was so nervous
that
you are calling us in here to
tell us that you are going to
like die soon or something like that
my heart is just beating a mile
a minute i probably won't die for
another seventy years or so seventy you
already are ninety three years old i
go and i get iron every day
i ask young people about themselves and
then they find out all about me
you're just getting iron like scrap higher
and it's all in the backyard and
honestly there's
too much of it back there boy
but because i'm magnetised he said you're
magnetised so what that's good
look that means my blood is reaching
nutrients like you're sticking to the refrigerator
i love it i wanted to talk
to you about something yeah what is
it dear there's a stigma around you
that people in the neighborhood are discussing
at great length i stick mata yeah
i mean the fact that your palms
start bleed
being indiscriminately no it's not discriminate it's
it's when i want to have it's
what you have a stigmata that of
your own choosing yes you go yeah
well i can't take this like a
defeat to i can't take this like
a heart what's wrong with your art
you know i have a bad ticker
i have a bum ticker but you're
only fifty seven years i know but
i have i've had three heart attacks
already i can't take these kind of
posts we were talking yes
somebody's called the paramedics and they'll company
the ambulance
okay that felt right yeah it is
there's somebody having a heart attack i
don't have it you know i don't
own a smartphone i know you don't
owe one i'm ah fei will you
have one somewhere i do i stole
it
yeah he should be recovered jesus christ
what's wrong with you
i'm having like these weird palpitations where
i can't like wait for hear about
them well the fact that they're occurring
is bad enough well right but it
what's your problem well um oh honestly
i'm just waiting for this meeting to
end because it goes ah it's going
on for so far so sorry so
i did
realize the meeting was going long it's
going how long would you say it's
it's interminable i'm gonna say meeting a
juror okay thank you lol right by
asked me to meet example is the
meeting happening anymore okay good i'm turning
on my laptop now
we woke up yeah yeah okay yours
heart car no so close competition it's
palpitation okay i said it twice so
i thought politician than i thought that
felt almost like an add on after
lie finds the first time i said
it i i almost mumbled it and
i felt bad because he also calling
you
mumble it was the way i thought
it wasn't dick so i was like
you can't just try to get what
i know so i started again
yeah was yours interminable yes
and was yours adjourned
yeah
that's the perfect word to ended up
fasting no no no not what was
yours trying to remember now fuck wasn't
it was grumbles grumble and you say
though i'm sick of your grumbles mumbles
ah
good stuff really good really good stuff
if this was fun that's sounds like
a two hundredth episode banger to me
yeah it felt like the the three
trouve album waiting for if you didn't
care for this episode don't listen to
the first hundred and ninety nine no
that's on you if you're new now
it's too late yeah you know if
you're new now
are you new now hello human are
you new now um alright that's going
gonna do it for us yeah thank
you very much for listening to us
whether you've listened to two hundred episodes
or you've listened to part of one
and just sucks you listen to this
one and then sixty seconds in turned
it off thank you sir
thank you anyway we love we really
see so much yeah we're out here
just talking nicely about you and you
don't even know you don't even know
like a dumb idiot sorry for you
yeah if you'd like to write joseph
course three team usa gmail dot com
has previously mentioned and if you'd like
to call us we've you wanna leave
us a voicemail here's what you do
don't use your phone no well you
could go on your phone you yeah
but
we're not using the phone for the
purposes intend to know you're using the
phone as as modern times do which
is you go to a website called
hag claims eight dot com and leave
us a voicemail that's right and we'll
answer these voicemails on our three medium
episodes which come out on wednesday every
other week yes
those are little many episodes you can
hear those at cb world and also
some sort of apple podcast thing because
subscription to apple podcasts lemonade ah i
don't know maybe someone in your house
listens to it real loud you could
hear it that way i'd be a
great way to do it maybe if
you're passing by like a podcast shop
you'll be playing it in the window
could be hiding in here
here yeah for all we know that
aren't hearing it that way arius thing
i can imagine yeah the seriously though
can imagine that's it that's the only
just like one person hiding if they
were in your cabinet here and they'd
been listening to every episode have that
happened one who's a monster that's a
scarier ah no person because of person
can have ill intent yeah monster just
is yeah and you can run away
so a monster would tear you limb
from limb but he's not doing it
maliciously yeah it was passed down sir
paul was a fast monster we're talking
slow monsters yeah i'm my monster can
be slow and it's gonna tear you
limb from limb no nobody says it
has to be fast there's no faster
yep it says
tearing them from the mess to be
faster you when you run when i
run probably eighty miles an hour whoa
that's really slow yeah that's so slow
you're right yeah i'm not a fast
runner but tearing limb from limb i
do it real slow yeah real slow
and by the way you only have
four limbs so it's not like it
takes a lot of time well it
can take a long time if you
go one by one one a day
day when every two days vitamins what's
vitamins what's virus vitamins um also we
have ah three visiting on the tubes
which is we re-release our old episodes
out from behind the paywall no one
else can do this no
gift toy yeah no there was absolutely
no call for it nobody was like
when were you guys released a water
run while the three visiting on the
twos start didn't happen it didn't happen
never he was fabric he know a
group of writers wrote that one was
made it was a false flag favorite
literacy theory
i think i want to memorize it
and i know we yeah you really
want to slaughter what is it it's
the meme jonathan frakes where he's where
it's like beyond belief factor fiction exactly
and he just is it just made
a compilation of all the times he
says something's not real oh yeah like
ah you know they got three good
company compilations out of that because they
got the nose
they got the yeses and then they
got the questions that he asked again
it was real
have you ever written a bike up
a volcano that really yeah it's true
that you got tricked it happened you
did it
this was about yea like you it's
like when you tell your parents something
that happened in your childhood that didn't
have to be a group of writers
wrote that one oh that's right i
said what's so funny is so good
um so i do know what it
is because i sent one to you
yeah i'm all right we have to
go
so you gotta go but we'll see
you next week yeah right here we're
not going anywhere i'm darkness right we're
gonna break off a brand new hondo
and i'm flipping the table over after
two hundred saying that's it we're done
no we have a whole new episode
next week yeah we we are gonna
flip over the flow right yeah okay
so maybe they won't say that we
break all of the equipment every single
episode we do
that never happened it happened off my
alright bye