sarita ah
oh
yeah
oh mellow oh yeah i'm paul f
tompkins i've got aquaman i'm more in
lab case i wanted to be you
oh too quickly we are three billion
yeah we are three d r three
dumb and this is the show where
we talk huh great descript
thank you just say yes what's up
yeah talked about this we talked about
that we talk about it right like
we talked about a baseball bat
you know yeah man let's get real
let's let's immediately get real okay alright
i'll really only get all the way
i wanna go all the way real
okay like how how crazy how crazy
like of how crazy the glass eye
oh okay shape their me to what
did the same one we share it
you don't remember
you guys are trading off glass i'll
share one brown eye
you guys share an asshole
do you know what i mean sounds
like you do
um you ever known anyone with a
glass eye let me start the no
actually i oh well jerry cozy speaking
of that sounds really good actually look
at fuller
i feel suit
alright stuff so something something horrible just
happened i think truly horrible actually did
just happen um which is to somebody's
mother that i know but it's about
glass side this should this woman was
attacked on the on the train in
chicago in the middle the day ah
by a guy who just punched in
the face while she was reading and
she has she lost her eye i
know her oh
my god i'm not kidding ouch
that this isn't the worst terrible a
lot you know i think about this
a lot because ah some you knew
i had ah someone i was someone
i was dating had a really good
friend who when he was seventeen he
well no he came down to visit
and she was like hey before
or you meet this guy he's the
part of his face is a little
unresponsive so don't say anything about it
or what you know but basically when
he was seventeen he was at a
backyard party and some bros came up
to him and just were like hey
get the fuck out of this party
in one guy hit him once in
the face and it show
shattered every bone in his chat and
and made and he needed reconstructive surgery
and his eye kind of drooped a
little bit and i was like this
is i mean the the anytime you
see someone getting hit in movies it's
usually like to knock someone out or
people are just hitting each other or
something you know but no nothing ever
it happens people just kind of rub
their jaw oh right you know and
then they hit each other in the
face some more it's really dangerous to
hit someone yes and like so terrifying
i think that's the kind of fear
i have more than like i'm not
afraid of flying or like a lot
of things that people
back up down here down here this
morning i'm not afraid but i am
i'm like afraid of random acts of
violence like i feel like i when
i carry my water bottle i'm like
ready to beat the show someone wants
it like i feel like prepared for
that i mean i call that where
being a woman yeah i mean that
is that is honestly
what it is yeah because you spend
your whole life walking around that way
where it's like someone's getting someone's and
get me like you do think that
all the time it's like the most
dangerous game of tag yeah just being
a woman being alive i'm afraid of
random acts of kindness yeah i see
that this work because i gave you
flowers and you spit me i was
scared but i also wait the other
day
i was driving and just the other
day were you walking down the street
just the other day as well yeah
what does that
working at a law because walking in
the lab does j just see those
the song you think it's a song
about a scientist who walks into his
lab he's gonna something that was taken
early in his lab that was early
operation was explaining his whole day get
to the lab i were talking this
up in bed
but i was driving and a bird
slapped into my winch oh and like
i thought it was almost like a
pile of wet paper towels it was
and then like like it was swooped
low and then was hitting anything and
then ooh flew sweet bird and it
flew over the top of the car
ouch i think died
died oh um but i chased after
you like in the rearview mirror it's
gone i didn't really do much checking
it for you it was quick moving
traffic it wasn't like go back and
like ceo yeah but i know just
something no matter how careful you are
things just happen like something could just
happen i always think something like you
know when you're driving on the freeway
and
and there's like something that goes under
a truck and it takes some crazy
thing i'm like what is this just
flies into my windshield and like yeah
my whole life is over yeah what
if no someone threw a rock at
co-op and i alright ha that's maybe
a year ago when coming back from
a concert or something like that and
just like suddenly miss the window thank
god and just hit like right next
to it or whatever like just metal
of
the car yeah just like gotcha jaume
you hear and you sit and you're
like what am i my own order
don't do a looking dude i don't
know yeah sure i knew her wow
but i was nowhere near this
i was miami by the way john
malaney having boxes young box forth
ah so good when i was ok
when i was a kid we used
to throw rocks snow yeah we did
what we said so well and burns
her in cars rock rock rock rock
shows when a thursday and you could
throw we threw rocks at buses here's
what started started with this that's okay
it started with this it started with
ah crab apples
there was a a house up the
street from us that had a crab
apple that's trained gigantic crab apple tree
and so we would throw that's grandma
apple isn't gonna kill someone right from
wrong i'll say swerve not that people
should be throwing anything at a car
but i'm saying a rock is much
more dangerous than a crab yes canned
crab apple will be hard yeah i
guess i guess it's mushi crab apple
musashi countries myself did you say moose
yoshi wu i think it might be
mushi i didn't say for real
yeah just making sure it's for burning
that's not how i say martius obviously
that's not how i say mushi
i say mushy but then we mesh
hey i say messy
well we grabbed mosi
well built into that we went from
we went from crabapples to eggs and
one time we threw eggs are almost
better than crappy wow are better than
crab apple bed all day qua bubble
did you ever get egged in your
house when your kid while hanging telling
keep talking telly yeah so we we
threw an egg it with
you're going to get a few cars
you through one egg at a few
cars yeah it was a big egg
we've got a dinosaur and you in
return your choice we should have saved
it we threw yeah we had eggs
and we were throwing at cars we
we we hit this one car and
we were like we were crouched behind
a bush and then we were
would like ah spring up and throw
the egg and then hide again of
course yes perfect health and ah nineteen
know what we were god what i
guess i was probably like
ten or eleven something like the busy
street
yeah it was a pretty busy street
yeah yeah maybe town i lived in
busy town richard scary yeah my best
friend was a lowly worm
he couldn't throw any aches no arms
close of course but a hat
what do you guys talk we put
around
richard scary bitty town it's like oh
it's a book and cartoon ooh but
it's a children's book with like a
busy town of all these different animals
doing all these different jobs okay and
you guys read it as children very
adorable your eyes a little apple car
that's cool she's a main character yeah
i think so i'm gonna wow or
the cat i mean i've seen i've
had to watch that show
oh i've never seen the show i
revisit that i just know the books
and i think of them as ensemble
pieces yeah i don't binge watch that
yeah
itchy binge watcher i carry ya i'm
telling richard scarce busy i'm gonna make
it a note right now binge-watch razor
scary i mean don't so we hit
this one car and the guy fucking
slammed on the brakes oh no he
leaped out of the car and chased
us and we've oh we ran
can split up it was writing but
do you guys care plan before it
happened like look at this happens now
so you just split up on your
own playboy throw eggs have fun yeah
yeah so yeah that's been more life
should be like that we were terrified
and i like i dove down a
hill and i watched him chase mice
like ram
and jack he didn't catch any of
us what are you jill
yes he didn't dive down the hill
wait never occurred to me that they
did it on purpose jackie chester it's
rona just some right it was insurance
fraud
i thought they did go up there
according to my favorite comic
my favorite tackling oh and you're the
dice bad diane plays those jokes get
me every time um really wholesome i
remember going to eg oh wait are
you done with your story unbelievable well
then after an believable there there was
a kid that we were friends with
named wael
ali he was really the the instigator
of the throwing things he liked to
throw things and he was the one
that suggested rocks and hey i know
this egg shit yeah let's see yeah
yeah cracks yeah huh the egg bit
as slogan for raw does crack it
hell it cracks window to differ cracks
we threw so what i remember of
rocks we did not do that for
for a long time we did that
once and i remember throwing rocks at
a at a bus that it's easy
to get yelled at for throwing eggs
and the big let's really let's escalate
yes yeah i know or maybe rocks
was second
nd and then we were like oh
maybe they and then the chasing looks
like tie ever yeah let's retire on
top
it's not going to get rid of
the bad guys and you still look
at that as the best thing you
ever did yeah absolutely i'm proud of
it
um in eighth grade everyone was egging
everyone at my school and i remember
going in some i guess someone not
just for halloween no new year round
i mean i don't know when if
my people chosen this month that it
was kind of going off you know
moments like let's get to october let's
say that's good tell me i um
i mean did smash pumpkins went one
year i felt bad about all because
some billy corgan being from chicago and
the size we had to to honor
him um we unabated kogan
we but i remember someone's older brother
drove us to like go do it
and then some of the boys kinda
aig so yeah real cool guy no
um but yeah i never actually threw
an egg at a house but i
was in the car i was complicit
possible deniability on this p d d
you forgot the pd toilet paper houses
or is that just know about here
no we use i mean definitely happen
to people but it was more like
the swim team would do that kind
of shit to each other i don't
know why typical swim team and my
cousin used to do these kind of
pranks with her friends a lot and
they would like put hot dogs on
plastic forks filling the whole lawn all
these animals would come and like eat
them over night went wow what was
the chevron sort of tune yeah hotdog
all that and you just like that
identify tongues in plastic forks sticking out
of this little grass oh in order
to elevate them yes so there's the
caucus the helium stick a hotdog on
top of it and then got it
all these animals come and eat it
overnight so we're talking dog
dogs cats others raccoons coons what's the
opossum the squirrels what's the point though
for when you come out in the
morning there are no hotdogs there well
i just think my dogs know and
you go to thinking deal with all
the animals and so then there would
be a lot being torn up or
lie okay but like then they also
would do with a
like flamingos all over someone's lawn but
this was more of like i think
once they're getting older and they would
like have the money for
so i'm just cry
yeah that legitimately scared you something about
it was really good idea
someone came in and did and i
didn't feel like i heard anything and
then suddenly someone came in to deliver
my jacket to me which i'd left
my previous location got it and was
right behind you and paul pointed and
you turned around and that was a
legitimate screen smile on my face yeah
it wasn't like a horrified life
i've never
oh mike myers from us our
salt point ah i help listen kids
pointing um but what i think once
they were a little older and like
they had a little money or something
they would put like plastic flamingos all
over someone's on his birthday surprise or
like whatever like right just like you
wake up and there's any size flamingos
on your lawn except for the waste
of money yeah
we used to know i think i
would like if someone's food i remember
someone did it to me in to
take and lauren give me flamingos more
give me death i'll take that someone
did it to me once where they
put ah like construction worker signs and
orange cones all over oh yeah and
so
i thought that was so cool that
then i found a construction site and
i went back there like you know
at midnight or whatever and i got
a whole bunch of orange cones and
i piled them in the back of
my car along with a few you
know like construction signs and i had
them in my car and my dad
saw it and was like what are
you doing and i was like
oh no no this is to do
to put on someone's lawn and he's
like where'd you get them i was
like oh at a construction site and
he's like you just stole stuff from
a construction site and i and yet
i still don't think it's that big
of a deal
i felt like i got much that
stuff costs so yeah i felt like
they don't care do they really i
bet it was annoying maybe yeah um
can i say we should put the
book
that's a shirt what were you gonna
say no you tell your story then
i'll tell my story okay so in
my town of evanston illinois i wanna
do by now okay um every year
at the fourth of july that we
have a parade in the fourth of
july and it is a whole big
to-do in town and people put chairs
out to to mark their
or sub-bass if it wasn't a big
to do hey yeah but everyone's like
this big parade no one gave shot
on but everyone marks there like they
save their spot like oh a week
or two and advance oh wow but
ah you'd put your whole mean like
st central street in town is lined
with chairs like leading up to the
fourth july and would they be unique
chairs
yeah everyone knows i mean you know
what you put out like it's just
like you trust it and you only
sit where you put your chair like
i love this so you we get
there and you do it or you
don't so it started getting into bear
you do it or you don't those
are your choices oh okay yeah ikea
ikea ikea yeah yeah yeah yeah
so i was starting to but when
i was in high school becoming a
little noticeable that people were putting them
out earlier and earlier over a year
and it was like getting kind of
comical so my high school boyfriend put
out chairs like two months in advance
and then he was in the paper
because it was like a whole first
guys you doing yeah it was a
joke like he was like like make
sure it was making fun of the
whole thing in the paper for being
like funny but like people have put
out the chairs so the lighter side
of news
that two months so we're talking i
don't know this two months they might
have been june like but whatever it
was was just far enough that people
got what it was for yeah right
that's really funny yes funny so do
people still do it or know ah
put the chairs out yeah yes but
not that early but it's like we
no one steals chairs know it's an
understood thing it's like you
just oh sure yeah thieves understand these
types of things i don't think anyone
i mean i'm sure you've done one
or two and they have their own
chair i'm sure somebody somewhere else stole
something in my car again the other
night what if i told you about
just say someone or some thing someone
was in your cars in my car
again yeah gone are just different ah
this has happened like three
three times i go to my car
and the change drawers open and the
doors slightly ajar but shuns heavens nodding
like it's him yeah no way would
i do it easier this is having
to lock your car oh yeah who
i liked the car but i but
but since i've talked about this on
on another show i think were they
so they they say
stoles something and i think put it
back but like later yeah put it
back the second time they were in
there something like that but but it
happened again two nights ago and and
now he just knows the story from
another show right from this show it
was on the show oh you guys
i do i do not get a
spanking because you say you can
tempt me into heavens allowed whoa
yeah i view it no i was
saying someone did it over ny you
get your makeup and i was not
giving noise not giving any more detail
than that and you guys wanted the
detail so that's your fault it's not
my son mike nahan know why we
should say i told this on this
show well i don't know that's what
i was
but but it's not the way ignorance
of the lawsuit she's fighting i was
withholding i was like oh you are
withholding you bitch
camera is on we need to spank
you
fuck dammit kevin get your spanking sharpie
always gotta spin kevin get ready everyone
getting frame kevin go a little closer
right
this black i don't deserve this but
then again i do i gave you
one yeah on the last oh yes
no way that justice is served
alright but since but it happened again
crazy are you guys i would hate
that well i don't know what do
you have anything important in there you
know i've i've started i've ticked up
my ipod which is the only important
thing now i'm wondering
if you're saying that a thing that
you talked about before it happened again
if someone heard it on the show
and goes and tries to do it
now no oh well i live i
thought that i'm saying does that count
as a spangle offense know the first
part was definitely not bankable saying saying
that this happened to me
me the other night look and then
you guys were so confused and i
was i was intentionally not saying what
it was trial by fire
whatever is what does this tell my
jury is that right what i don't
know what you're talking about people i
know so why can't you just decide
that someone is wrong and then we
go for them because look yesterday i
mean you banked when i didn't have
heidi
but you shouldn't have yeah we need
to we need paul to be spanked
that's the only way to bell hell
no
but i'm the only one who's deserved
my first bank we made the rule
that you get spanked if you repeat
a story and then we have gone
so hard with that world that two
people have been saying two out of
three were incorrect yeah the control yeah
it's like control now paul you're looking
up and spanked yet but we're victims
here we feel the sun fare well
it's an unjust system yes
it's just whoa wait i can't remember
what your spangle story was and why
it was repeated or i'll go oh
no
yeah remember what it was it was
de linda thing but i'm not gonna
say what it was yeah
i'll know what to call my marine
da da and even a story i
like brands a viral video and i
bet everyone did talk about it on
the show everyone on twitter please tell
me please please hey please we beg
of you oh yes we're so lonely
ah
we got to take a break oh
okay let's take a break i will
see later bye
welcome back bankers hey spanker oh here's
the story that i wanted to tell
oh yeah because you the construction equipment
reminded me of it yep my comedy
partner when i started out was gonna
name rick roman and rick and i
went to high school together he was
a senior and i was a freshman
we met doing
the school play was oliver oh wow
and what did you play and what
did he play he played mister shower
bury the undertaker i don't remember i
was just in the chorus i had
and i know i've met you i've
told you this before i had one
line that i can't remember but i
always i was like the bartender and
i had to put during the show
you were imploring people to consider themselves
one of you
i did i definitely did that
i definitely i did not extol the
virtues of food oh too bad food
park well it's very glory yes huh
thanks know that i've never seen from
a commercial yeah okay yeah and pretend
i know pretty good show so there
are so many songs that were used
in commercials yeah growing up that i
just knew from commercials and were sups
surprised to find them be from plays
and stuff like vaughan de la buena
ma try germany its own tba sat
from that was from oh it's from
ah sound music but ah oh yeah
remember that at all yeah yeah forgettable
song forget about south african with her
and well the keys keys keys amen
the famous best from the fantastic suitcase
keys on the ice um so um
right i just really quick huh yeah
i've only got very serious stuff was
the song we had to say my
children's theatre auditions everyone had think that
makes sense thank you so you are
auditioning children for theatre you ram oh
and you had to sign an order
the base job
scott to show the kids how to
be in a play i got i'm
seeing a show it's like wow stage
i was like check-in okay what's this
consider yourself
ah you just like sally bowles for
every singing consider yourself or your garter
belt
i was missing neil diamond isn't weird
gov city zo it's weird her name
was sally bowles and she wore a
bowler ad it's weird oh yeah i
just gotta chill got aquaman and you
always worried ocker pants
i thought i'd find something that went
into it that's what comedy is just
like started going hey did you get
out there ninety nine percent of comedy
yard come look look look look like
but i'll get through come through queen
yes queen can't always do loss ah
so rick was weak we stayed in
touch we we became fast friends
when we say hey i need you
we did catch and we stayed as
sweet as we were and did you
love ya like a sister yeah we
um and then um when he he
went to school in arizona and then
he would come home and we would
hang out and there was this guy
that rick that was in rick's class
this is guy named mark and we
for some reason rick well i was
very easily swayed rick
like tormented this guy in a weird
way like my rick and i went
along with it he he invented rick
rolling what is that you would roll
onto what is it i know i'm
a web there's a website that explains
it let me i'll send it to
you at a job
i don't find it so um continue
i'm going to find this website don't
send to me he would just like
we would just do we would we
would fuck with him all the time
he was he was a waiter at
the howard johnson's near our school and
we would go there and we would
just like we would comedic only torment
this guy and
and we were so delighted with ourselves
we didn't realize that it was genuinely
annoying to him you know what i
mean ah and but one of the
things we used to do regularly was
we would drive around ah and we
would if we saw construction equipment we
would pick it up and we would
put it on his front porch so
sawhorses
just like you saw horses i would
get them in asia any horse we
saw
we will lead it to mark click
on that website that explains rick rowley
by the way i can't believe this
is happening website youtube dot com
wow turn it up weight notice that
yeah that's it
this is really getting in the way
of the rick rolling by the way
about the pre-roll i know what this
song is but what the rick roll
you just were rick rolled
i just did it to you that's
what rick rolling is is when you
insert fucking da yo into something else
it is when you trick someone into
clicking on that video again again oh
my god is he eight
i owe you
huh i want every outfit he wears
license this is happening you are seriously
seeing this guy for the very first
time oh okay okay but i'm processing
information for the first time remains to
ooh never gonna give you up
no okay so you would you would
find construction i was literally dressed just
like him and heard you thank you
okay so being recalled is simply to
watch the video well it's
no it's where someone fingers someone they're
going to want to see something else
yes you misdirect chairs what's annoying just
for the record yeah okay this part
hadn't loaded so it just said youtube
dot com i was worried zoe would
low trick me yep that's yes i
rick rolled do okay i'm just giving
you credit where it's fucking do
okay so construction equipment on the porch
yeah and he begged us to stop
doing really and we didn't stop doing
oh no eventually we got bored with
it we stuck but i for one
sti but i forgot all about that
and then out of nowhere i recently
remembered it and i felt horrible oh
what i mean there's worse things
you can do yeah it's just annoying
but it's also like was what was
his issue with it like i gotta
go well he's real with women yeah
dealing with it yeah i i the
those those pranks where someone does it
to you and you never find out
who it is those are the bad
ones like something like yeah something like
that happened too
a friend of mine where someone was
pranking their house a couple of times
and i think they were so upset
about the first example of it that
the person felt like they could never
say it was them yeah and and
it's become a big mystery somebody to
me one time they left a weird
sign on my door that was vaguely
vaguely threatening but it was
clearly supposed to be a joke but
it was still weird because i didn't
know who did it right and it
was very unnerving when i found out
who did it was somebody that i
didn't know that well and i was
like that's not a cool thing to
do yeah this person thought that would
be hilarious anywhere what address was out
well i can tell you because i
don't live there oh yeah ah
um yeah what other pranks no one's
ever gotten me yeah i just got
you thousand first ten points the first
and worst and there was um let
me think pranks i mean i've definitely
been pranked like in sleepovers and stuff
we used to do um what we
used to try to
do a lot of those pranks like
putting someone's hand in water while they
yeah they can see him he would
they p um no we never got
it to work damn it we tried
she doesn't wake people up i don't
i was ripped i would well you
want weed that we did do at
sleepovers was like putting doing like whip
cream on your hand and putting like
a feather under nose when you go
oh yeah your face that shit
yeah that is good that one did
happen it's good shit um i don't
know what i'm like light as a
feather stiff as a board which isn't
really really praying but we always believed
it was working
when i went to summer camp i
used to go to this place called
forest home in like the redlands california
and ah so i went there ever
since from pretty much like elementary school
through high school i went there every
summer and so in elementary school use
the whole summer no just for a
week oh so
and and my parents would go in
the end they were separated from you
the whole time you were separate in
they got to like for a week
being on this lake and hang out
with adults and the kids were taking
care of it separate yeah it was
not bad so so i forgot we
were where we were in um elementary
it was just more like you know
elementary school
but then um then there was like
indian village i think was when you
were in junior high which was tps
you would sleep in tps and stuff
and then finally when you were in
high school you want to make them
or the widow they were already premade
and stuff and then finally when you
were in high school premade tv premise
primitive from it's primitive
quantity proposes setting the chai so finally
when you were in high school you
got to be in cabins with like
you know seven of your other friends
bunk beds and we had we we
would have to go through inspection every
day where you know you'd have to
clean your and make your bed and
all this kind of stuff sure but
we had a really cool guy who
was in charge of us
and several of the other cabins and
he was like look no one's able
to prank me um but if you
can prank me there everything ran on
like a point system there whatever if
you can prank me successfully you'll get
five hundred points but no one's able
to do it so if you if
you if while we were on inspection
can if you can set up something
in your cabin the pranks me you
know you'll get five hundred points sounds
weird it was fun though it was
like sure it's fun for you he
wants to be praying you know he
was just trying to ultimately be prank
he was just trying to do something
fun for the kids of like they're
going to try to prank co i'm
sure that's what he led you to
believe that sounds fun it is fun
grey
i'm praying my pants off
i'll give you kids you can wake
my pants um so we got him
everyone was doing these elaborate you know
rube goldberg type things and we got
him by literally getting a big ass
plastic trash can filling it completely with
water or something oh shit i had
to throw my trash
as i say i haven't taken it
ah but we just leaned it up
against the door which opened out towards
the person and we just filled it
completely with water and so he opened
the door and this giant trash can
full of water just completely soaked him
and it was very simple it was
not complicated but he said that was
the best one anyone had ever done
because get this
oh um no okay so i used
shia fuckin burr you with this man
volunteer at a camp um for a
few years it's an adult and we
play this game where um it was
well it was i guess was just
hide and seek but it was like
the counselors all hit and the cap
can pretend to find us so
it was good i know there's more
to it than that but i can't
think of it but ah everyone was
trying to hide really well and the
counsellors the counsellors and i was like
the more counselors each like the kids
found the more points or whatever you
collect them all and this the head
of the camp at the end we
we no one was like finding her
for a long time like no one
could find it
longtime oh shit and she fell down
a ravine know it's like it's worse
now is just crazy oh so she
had hidden so there were these big
um what do you call it like
a little i'm trying me out okay
but like one of the metal trash
cans you know that you'd have at
a campsite with like a piece of
wood that you put over it to
keep animals out of
like jazz dumpster size or like a
barrel okay and she crouched inside of
it and put the the wood over
and over it and no one found
it for hours when they finally got
her she'd be pulled out she was
like i couldn't move her legs oh
crazy manager an hour don't you just
go yeah i'm given up on this
but you really want to win yeah
yeah well yeah it kind of breaks
my heart i think if i remember
correctly she was somebody who like she
was new and like really want she's
new in char one to one her
so it was like this kind of
like oh no issues like an a
lot of pain after that wow and
she smelled like garbage well yeah i
think it was good but yeah
i don't even know dads remember that
so crazy that's right yeah that was
so it was a bummer i've one
other forest home memory which is i
think when i was fifteen i play
the jingle for first home here we
go for home memories not forest lawn
memory oh i have quite a few
of those as well i met terry
but ah when i was fifteen i
i got just like one of those
horrible crushes on one of the the
girls in the girls' camp oh that
is i just didn't know what to
do with it and i was it
was we were there for a week
and i was just constantly anytime i
would see and i you know she
was very friendly to me i was
when i was fifteen basically like anyone
who
is friendly to me i started thinking
oh they want they they want to
be in a relationship chatting with anyone
who didn't talk to me oh i
was like oh i love them
yeah i have to make them like
me and then i tell you that
then it was ah did i tell
you the cocos story when i was
fifteen you know coker yeah i was
i'm away and he's ready she rips
may she rip um when you say
rest in power cocoa too soon rest
in power cocoa too soon love coco
of cocoa i had a book about
cocoa
when i was a kid i loved
it so much what was the book
it was just like a book showing
memoirs of nose like children by every
little done inside like we have cocoa
cider as told to
just like rummy kitty yeah it was
just a book of pictures and then
like of cocoa with her cat it
was about coco getting the cat and
then koko head cat she had a
cat coco account online picture there's a
very funny story that i heard after
she died that ah hilarious coco
coco at some point um when she
had the they gave her the cat
as a kitten and one point koko
ripped the sink out of her habitat
and when the people came in and
found it she blamed it on the
cat ah she likes i did the
cat did it didn't i also hear
the coco couldn't really sign well eva
eva understand like really is like anti
cocoa cocoa truther yeah and you put
all time like yeah oh cocoa because
he yeah it's just a dog doing
a trick like yes eva is like
good people trying to prove it stevie
wonder can see well you know that
wow yeah it's great there's there's a
big conspiracy that he was out not
actually yesterday was imagining
married to him i had a whole
like what i was listening to
we're going to be oh stevie wonder
i was um less flicking the bean
driving the car was listening to the
cd wonder song and i was like
rob how incredible to marry somebody like
that where like someone who has called
me my shari'ah milwaukee yeah but like
just an amazing artist we saw him
the other day at this thing i
was doing and yeah mike yeah and
it was like er no
everyone was trying to figure out he
never will everyone was trying to figure
out if it was him everyone was
like his that stevie wonder or stevie
wonder looking guy
and it finally came down to like
i think he's not looking at anything
and so we were like ah and
then he's holding the book upside down
right and then we heard what he
was saying oh it is stevie wonder
but it was a good five minutes
where people were crouched around well there's
probably a reason why he wears sunglasses
because his eyes look like they can
see is that what you're saying what
what what are you saying no i'm
just saying we were like oh he's
no we just how does a guy
wearing sunglasses oh i thought you were
seeing his eyes and no no no
no we'd like he thought he was
something we thought oh this is maybe
just a guy wearing sunglasses just like
a cool guy with long braids yeah
well honestly exactly like stevie wonder
but no eva anderson because she does
magic she knows all the mentalism stuff
right and no and and ah does
even do magic yeah well she would
do it once a year with her
dad oh yeah yeah her dad terry
anderson so once a year she would
get the call to to do their
dual duo act oh
and so and she would be i
know she's you know she was at
the magic house on the one one
of the time she invited me i
was out of town fills me with
feelings yeah we do yeah i know
i'll never get to see it again
but um because she's in that whole
circle of the magic castle and all
that she she knows that cocoa is
like it's literally just a trick
the interpreter is is feeding all the
information with just like cocoa doing gibberish
and the interpreter is just saying like
oh coco says this this this so
what end but isn't it american sign
language no it's not something where like
anyone can interpret what coco saying it's
the interpreter is interpreting oh so no
marlee matlin i've had the same guy
all the time well how do i
look and also are talking um wait
for the record is when i explained
stevie wonder's blindness since i asked if
yes i'm blind wait really real name
seba yeah he's bb that's blaney real
name alan wonder he did all the
noises for bba
i'm a bba truther ah
his real name is steve linde like
steve land hardaway judkins steve linde hardaway
judkins judkins the young stevie wonder was
born six weeks premature and saginaw michigan
the stunted growth of blood vessels in
the back of his eyes caused his
retina to detach the oxygen pumped into
his incubator exam
rebated the condition leaving the tiny baby
permanently blind oh i wonder if that's
something that you could take care of
excuse me i'm getting emotional noise if
if that's something that you could take
care of um you know with modern
science like if we'd be able to
catch it now and yeah ladders or
something oh man maybe hey should i
tell the coco story or no
yeah i don't wanna hear the cuckoo
story alright so i have this i
had someone to whom i sat next
to in a lot of different classes
would you have that where like they
would do yeah yeah yeah medically so
i would be in several classes sitting
next to this um this girl and
she was my buddy and i really
you know she was as far as
i
was concerned out of my league and
just she was my buddy and we
would always talk and so my friend
and i buddy who is out of
your league yeah no but i have
one never entertain yeah we gotta have
one he's got to have these we
have a sidekick you gotta like kicking
yeah buddy is because ideally suitable brain
yeah okay cool
but i i was purely just happy
being your friend like she was she
was very cool we have a great
relationship her never ever term now you
know why i never flicked any of
my ever like your beans
your little beans
no i i'm telling you truthfully when
i say goodbye to our hands to
god you never flicked your little beads
i never flick my two hundred two
year cool past your balls about her
ever poked your balls high thinking about
this girl if he ever was doing
doing your balls hello anybody in there
you never just going with a spoon
and then ladled your balls oh that's
how you masturbate before you even know
how when you're a kid you take
zero do i do this
just go to the kitchen grab a
bunch of inputs figure it out what
don't think you're good i don't drunk
know i figured it out i never
i think i think in order for
this story to make sense i think
you gotta start over no no
no it just i literally had zero
feelings for her okay oh she's cool
i like her right so my friend
was dating someone who worked at coco's
as a as a hostess like the
restaurant focuses the restaurants sort of like
a diner like marie calendar's or whatever
and um here right yeah yeah they
have clothes here yeah oh that's right
yeah so that's why i know
very driven man they were good buddies
his girlfriend was good buddies with my
friend and they worked together coco's and
so we went to go eat at
koko's and but so my friend could
see his girlfriend and we had a
fun time and we were hanging out
and then um as we're leaving i
go out into the car and my
friend's girlfriend calls my friend over and
goes hey
um she likes your friend and and
my friend comes out to the corners
like oh my god she likes you
um my girlfriend just told me she
likes you and i was and it
it said cool the girlfriend said the
girl said was out of your league
like yeah she's like she likes your
friend is what she said right
so this sets me off into a
like a whole like oh well she's
so i never thought that well i've
obviously she's so great i like her
one calendar year of me you can
re carry calendars and that's just a
month
it's a marie gallagher year which is
just i'm one of your earth months
no of just me being like wrestling
with my feelings with her and yeah
and it not be reciprocated for some
reason and then finally at the end
of the year as as we're going
off to the summer my friend clarifies
with his girlfriend she's like no no
i was talking about your other friend
who wasn't there with you like your
own my like your handsome friend
yeah she likes she likes steve the
guy on the football team
and can i tell you i'm very
lost in the still question did it
change your dynamic with the girl yes
see because i was suddenly anything weird
i was suddenly acting like ah when
we call it achieved your d a
cheater d cheater d man she doesn't
mind t-shirts thursday sheet or d but
she your d
e it changed your dynamic oh but
she didn't my d achieved my d
so this this person came out of
coco's yeah my friend's girlfriend was lying
your friend's girlfriend i'm not using games
i understand i understand yeah said hey
my friend likes your friend why don't
you make it like your flank up
saying okay so when you heard that
that
the rule those out of your league
yeah make up names yeah makeup names
please okay company so it was like
sambora marry so for us the girl
is out here leaf mayor maybelline is
her friend and l'oreal so saphira likes
your friend is what she says to
more likes your friend and i'm the
only friend there so makes you
you like sephora yes because he comes
out and goes so far likes you
and suddenly this hot girl you like
never had a chance with you like
suv like first likes me first and
i'm like wait right
what don't you get do you need
me to draw you know i write
j i write like i'm so confused
okay you are not me she likes
you let me tell a story i
was
what to tell what's what l'oreal said
to the river who lori l'oreal israel
is the regular girl and who my
friend your friend safari know your friend
is my or somebody okay this is
my okay for clarity's sake mike mike
mike comes out to the car and
says laurie howell told me that sephora
likes you okay because she said hey
laurie
likes your friend okay alright now i
got it and we went a year
thinking she liked me but was not
reciprocating and not and i was too
nervous too and so in your mind
to make the first move i'm just
nervous because she likes you yeah never
gonna do anything stupid mike fucked all
this i know mike didn't fuck it
up but i mean he misunderstood my
last onder stuff
l'oreal should have said your friend dave
yes the popular football guy not shaded
here consider you mike's friend and even
all of this
we have to take a break
bye
welcome bags flat nearby like your bags
everyone lorin do you have a feature
safety and it's a simple game
the game of murder now we just
must kill those inside who did it
ah okay we've let's kill one of
us decided to do this okay so
this is a simple game we all
know and love and um it's a
little twist on it because i always
thought it's called twenty questions but it's
called twenty one questions yet one was
only almost like different so
someone thinks of something then we begin
by asking questions and you can now
repeat a question that's been asked and
whoever guesses it right gets to start
the next round just ain't broke don't
fix it this is a classic yes
twenty one question yes kevin will keep
track of the amount of questions shove
an excuse me and he doesn't want
to but he will okay so before
girls are you doing
he looked at me so mad so
real steve months and has been doctor
says we wish you and me too
you already just doing drops now and
oh my god oh no what just
happened is good because pen can tell
you if it's a little like this
evolution i love it and that we
should say we wish you a mitsubishi
okay another birthday i mean branded okay
okay
should i go first with my yeah
yeah think of think of it yes
you got it no fuck you got
it yes okay i'll go first okay
is it
a is it is it and you're
just gonna try to guess out no
is it an alum okay it and
is it a living thing no god
damn it
is it
a mineral know is a
vegetable no
are you counting the question
why you write him down are you
writing down the question you can't repeat
a question keeping oh okay sorry he's
actually doing a lot of good work
is it a common object yes
is it made of wood no isn't
made of stone no
is it
a little old statue no
it made of synthetic materials yeah
is it
the roof mo
cool into early on these guesses
is it useful yes is it clothing
no
is it a piece of technology no
is it a tool yeah
yeah
you did round
no no
no no can you only answer yes
or no
ah no i don't know but okay
it's it can be sound it's sort
of a tool not typically around okay
is it an tool i'm using really
loosely yeah yeah is it
a phone no it's technology i don't
consider it to be
how many questions is that
sixteen oh just shifting fat so thank
thank thank everyone okay get really serious
so it's not technology but it is
a tool would you consider technology to
be like an invention as that would
answer with seconds i know but i'm
trying to technology i was like electronics
so that's what i was just not
electronics go and tool it's not really
a tool it's an internet
shit is it in this room
yeah
is it
a glass know you can't see it
is it behind me
current post
is it freddy krueger
it's in this room but we can't
see it
damn it's a riddle
fucking molecules and shit
what the fuck
is it very old
the invention of this thing it has
it's been around a long time i
guess not doing yes or no is
different because i can lead you that
was probably more useful
it's been around for
many many many many hundreds of years
hundreds of years thousands of years million
man i don't think so but i
would say at least hundreds i don't
know how far back action hundreds and
hundreds of years actually thousands if we're
talking about zen's and thousand other cultures
and years is it oh other
or cultures it must be one of
the great pyramid you're on the right
track with what i was getting at
really when this thing might have been
in use in egypt but we use
it today we use it today let
me look my people ooh
um
is it an it's in this room
yeah you know
question two more questions but i can't
it's in the room but i can't
see it seven you have a theory
on what it is now okay
thanks for that okay
yeah i got you know is it
is it up ah pop like a
poli or ah you know okay one
more question
today no
i just yeah i guess we're getting
another hint okay assurance right haven't you
get to ask three questions oh me
with the seven three
um do you use it yes is
it in your house yes
um do you use it every day
yeah is it up your butt yeah
it's my book like it's a coconut
okay did that help anybody know because
it's in here it's in my purse
oh is it a mirror no a
tampon know a gun no
a key know a something that ain't
inkling about what the ancient yeah what
the ancient views i didn't use is
it is it a brain hook yeah
my brain
is it hieroglyphics alright it's lipstick motherfucker
oh my turn okay lipstick wow yeah
that's a classic trying to keep it
obvious huh okay no i think this
is a hard game so now you
can you don't say just yes or
no you can help guide us it'll
make an okay
we learned from that round i think
of something yes i do
i know what it is do you
very good
is this something
is this something that no
is this something people use daily
not a lot of people okay but
some people use it daily some people
use it daily so it's not alive
probably licenses
ah is it a tool
no not not not really okay is
it something that rich people use more
often than non rich people i would
not say so okay is it toilet
paper
so some people don't notice daily ah
it is toilet paper damn is this
something that can fit inside a breadbox
no
i forgot about that yeah question classic
is it something that can fit in
this room no whoa is it a
is it a structure people go inside
no
is it
um so keep your car your house
but it's bigger than this room and
it's not a tool on a building
on an airplane
so then it's a big thing is
it a is this a statue
yes that too just that same tone
it's nice that you owe this something
that is like an idea in your
head though are you crazy where it's
real i mean like is it it
is it something people imagine like it's
not like ah actual object it is
an actual object okay
um is it
bigger than an airplane yes
what is it it weighs at least
we've decided it's not a living it's
not well we haven't talked like people
use it not daily not daily and
it's not a teal go inside it
so it's not a boat
oh hey wait or something
do people go on it as if
you can't hear
you try to trick him if you
looked around furtively but so do people
go
not lately not lately oh it's about
something easy to bridge down no
something that is it in los angeles
no
in many places yes
so no one has gone it's not
um it can be seen from space
california oh
california knows how to pop no one's
gone on it leaving phone yeah we
don't some people use it daily but
on a lot of billy johnson coming
out of the house
yes you can see it from california
oh probably so from it's ah it's
in the water then so it would
be oh alcatraz know is it is
it is it in the water no
mother fucker how many is that sometimes
it's on the water oh right yeah
that's kinda what i meant but yeah
okay so it's sometimes don't okay but
sometimes on the water but no one's
using it lately or not a lot
of people are using lately we talked
about if it's living i haven't gone
on it like is it living no
shit
um so it's not a whale it's
bigger than an airplane and sometimes it's
on the water
is it what
is it
shadow
um no um is it
it's a shadow on an airplane i
don't know are shadows bigger than the
actual things like using them every day
someone uses it every day it's sometimes
it's on the water and it's fuckin
bigger than an airplane is what's bigger
than an airplane
to like the golden gate bridge but
that was not for ratios not bridge
sometimes zonal water but people aren't using
it all that much anymore
and you can see it from california
sometimes it's on the water but sometimes
it's not on the water so it's
gotta be a is it island is
it a island it's not a island
is it made of metal no
what is it fuck this is about
living but it's not well i guess
it could be organic in the sense
of likes fruit is organic but you
don't get be no no the question
should be something bigger than too late
know what's being used lately um to
ask if it was toilet paper yes
ah um it's not a concept it's
bigger than an airplane and it can
be seen from california but people aren't
using it like an abandoned
place like because i thought alcatraz because
if it's not just it's in several
places so it's gotta be a it's
a generic name for something like coincide
specific yeah okay you ah so what's
like a bridge
is it
do we ask if it was a
highway yeah we did we did that's
lawrence question believe we said highway but
we don't know if we actually yeah
yeah we asked second sorta sorta how
many area is it sixteen is it
a highway no damn it wait is
it a is it a byway don't
leave
it's i don't think it's anything from
this land belongs to me
okay so it's not the new york
island
ah um gosh ah but is it
something like that where it's like the
flies at a mountain know
is it a natural structure yes
is it the grand canyon no
this is debbie it's pamela anderson tar
tits
um god so a natural structure that
can be seen from california is ah
but sometimes it's on the water so
it's not in space
bigger than an airplane maybe it is
is it in space yes it's in
space so maybe it's the always
is it the moon yes yeah wow
i was close yeah we'll see what
from everywhere huh eighteen and an an
nine game no nineteen california did i
say can you i didn't say you
couldn't see from anywhere else ooh i
think i did say you can see
it from many places hey that was
good i agree i
i don't know if the moon has
ever technically on the water and technically
it's a concept because i don't believe
in them you can see the reflection
of the moon on the earth it's
reflect you but you were you were
thinking about the reflection of the moon
i was ok fine good job good
job guys thank you think of something
okay um don't think of toilet paper
okay whatever you do i like
i think of it's coiled paper okay
so let's talk about okay ah why
ah yes i'm ready
is it an a manmade object yes
maybe a woman yeah chance so a
doc women only make new stuff it's
on shark things and shark tank
you know object is it a building
no oh oh okay yeah i had
to cut that i already messed with
that um
is it it's not a building is
it's is it something
you have in my house probably no
is it a vehicle no
is it
yeah you're trying to break the silence
thing isn't something i can hold in
my hand yes and get it all
i can hold it all
sounds like i can just touch it
grab it yeah it's tick yes is
it common yes not the rapper kamen
sweden guess it yet he's a man
made object
is it
was it something that was invented past
the nineteen fifties
i'd say to give to give you
to give you more info i would
say right around then is it
is
is it something that
two in a row from oh sorry
so my main object made around the
nineteen fifties i say i thought of
my own pretty early on in that
i didn't want to say it because
i didn't want to sound straight so
let's all be willing to sound stupid
okay is this dog's tail um is
it ok so it's not like a
tv because
he said i wouldn't have it probably
anyone hold the ten i can't hold
in my hand although screens getting smaller
these days i tell you how we're
gonna take the tv on the go
it's both good and bad enjoy the
go it's great sharma comments do i
paint i hate the fucking script addition
to be the bears to be all
the the bear decision to be the
ma
no i kid were you doing like
not bear zandi jacket that you are
sure the tree are you wiping variation
yeah tp um tp manmade tp man-made
tp me bong ho you got a
bunch of dp balls on your ass
hey how embarrassing bear
um ok i can fit in your
hand
is it
is it metal no is it cloth
no
it's it's skin is it plastic yes
it's vast okay hi stay ahead is
captain plastic holding your hand piloted twin
peaks oh sure
and is it a common object that
like you've already i did i'm sorry
sorry sorry yeah then i'm afraid you'll
lose what was the consequence of nothing
you just don't do it it doesn't
count pathogen should be a spank heaven
should think himself yeah
okay i can do it now and
we're considering going to be speaking to
that's a punishment when i say um
ok it's it's made of plastic
common invented in the fifties you can
hold it in your hand but not
in your it's probably not is it
frisbee no
is it a toy like that yes
ooh
circular no
is it a rubik's que no
is it ah
sounds circular it's plastic
you'd hold in your hands a toy
is it a is it a wide
circular is it kimberly i'm i'm gonna
ask you this is it soft or
hard
ah is it malleable no hard
it's a toy toys do kids still
play with this toy yes
the fifties is it some can you
is it self-contained like what it does
is the game or do you use
it to do something else
i would say
like a rubik's cube is done but
like kranz you use know it's it's
it's it's it's own thing but you
can also use it with other things
but it's you know you if you
buy it it's it's own thing
is it a light brain know how
many react shevlin eighteen
move silly putty
no that plastic but malleable that's mainly
i would consider that but yeah i
know why did i yeah i thought
that's what you're getting at when i
was eliminating it with all these questions
and then i asked it and anyways
i blew a question ah
i went out there yet how many
is it fun for the whole family
or solo activity i wouldn't say the
whole family would be interested in this
no
normal families are your family that's not
a question i'm kidding but but adding
but i mean it's not it's not
a thing where it's like
like around like a rubik's cube or
anything like that where it's like anyone
in the family would be all that
interested in this you know it's pretty
much directed at you know one age
range yeah is it a dull yes
why is it a cabbage no you
only have one left right or is
that it isn't a barbell was the
twentieth army it's a barbie but you
are out of question when it was
the twenty first question that doll yes
damn i blew and they don't call
it twenty-two questions lord oh my hey
john
look such a look such a look
from aaron get it sorry i liked
it
i liked it i liked i i
blew that game because ahah it was
fine only buddy question and if you
were listening at home and you knew
it was a barbie from question seven
then deny you nicola look your sand
can come spin kevin come saying comes
bang kevin alright we're at that time
we're at a time i had fun
i had pho um hello fun leave
you us fun and we'll see next
time on three aa mean i do
like
a
uh