three
hello everybody it's us again i'm paul
f tompkins i'm lauren laccase i'm scott
aka robin where are your friends that
you love and we're here to pass
friends were you were your best friends
we're here to talk love that you
love where your best friends right here
firstly i love we're here firstly
before we talk to each other you
listen to us and you don't say
a fucking thing right oh we can't
okay hear you but still even if
even though we can't hear you don't
talk during this please don't it's just
disrespectful what do we care actually crying
talk over we can reverse the entire
time talk over just like we're doing
right now we're talking over each other
you're talking raw talk ever
one talks crossbow buddy listens what cross
todd what do you see at the
arclight i have a receipt here ah
don't worry don't worry don't worry don't
worry i learned actually they're showing porn
at the archive
don't worry about it
anyways they went under the radar when
i said here's nice daddy guys being
the film i saw and then you
sorry i just wanted to make because
someone's gonna hear that and think i
forgot that that was a movie that's
a movie anymore nope no number that
you got put in movie jail movie
hell it'll never get out oh um
what do you know what to
in the disney vault oh no right
yeah place where you can't get to
it
what are we what what is this
show what do we do what is
this show let me sum it up
this is a show where three friends
get together they talk they have a
spirited lively discussion about this that and
the other thing we're sort of controversial
firebrands yeah yeah i've heard to saying
oh i thought you guys would like
my socks i wore them by happenstance
oh
let's check them out they say i
don't k yeah on the bottom they
say i'm high not i love it
why the bottom of the foot like
the solar yeah oh i'm
wow i get i don't care i'm
high
ah ah hi what ever been high
don't want to talk about it
not your image i can't and they
were no were you high watching i
love you day yeah so turned on
movie gum me going huh
just a fervent oh the concept i
mean twenty four frames per second so
many wow
oh wait can i bring to your
attention a news story that was sent
to me oh please but play the
jingle bam bam bam news that that
that that that that that that that
that that that that dow okay this
was sent to me by a twitter
follower and
it's a screen shot of a clickbait
news ad or whatever you'd call it
and it's a sponsored post and it's
a picture of well that's the headline
says his ex wife dropped a bombshell
in d'avoir data that so i'm guessing
something about divorcing and there's three pages
of abuse the town divorce
chilling divorce and then three faces of
shock and horror and then the the
couple is me and d j qualls
next to each other
hey
now as i've said numerous um shows
yeah i am told often and daily
that i look like d j qual
right how does that make you feel
hot
um this person made this clickbait where
we're married and apparently i divorced him
and it's pretty great oh so that
was a mistake in the clickbait that
was someone just took that there's been
one of me where it said you
won't believe how these these celebrities died
and there was just a picture of
me like in drastic world
and i ready you die i don't
know i never clicked it
because you're a ghost and you can
use my hand would go right through
um do ah do you remember the
first time you ever saw d j
qualls yeah road trip and did were
you like i do look like me
i was like wow is this a
mirror i'm standing around monday for two
how did i get it the movie
had baghdad in a movie um you
know yeah i did think it's isn't
it
ah yeah i did think that yes
because they didn't know how many times
people send you like you look like
this person yeah yeah i don't know
and i've done it to you paul
once once yeah i felt guilty about
it because yea i think you look
like a guy in narcos or something
like yeah that was one of them
a lot never
it's never never no never know people
will send me literally any person or
thing that has a mustache right
the way like i have it's like
look at the stuff she just looks
like you
okay this was a
wait that's a title
yeah but not for the show by
now we've named it now we need
to but we don't know what the
name is exciting what an exciting time
this is oh boy um this is
our second episode by the way right
yeah yes okay people send me pictures
of i mean i do get pictures
of girls that are not unattractive but
they just have big blue eyes and
some me
you can forward them
just the pictures of girls like you
don't allow the yeah honestly if you
are generally conscious you're constantly sent me
pictures of girls i think is really
funny bitch does girl auto i get
sent and it's happened again that lawrence
sent it to me the other day
oh yeah and this is this happens
once a year
but it's been happening for three years
now
there was a story in two thousand
and fourteen where the cake boss was
pulled over for drugs yeah constantly these
days like over the last few days
constant it's like and send them to
me to people saying why you gotta
talk about this on the podcast like
we did years ago i thought it
was new too because rob delaney re-tweeted
it and then i saw that it
was old but i still didn't care
and send it to you yeah
yeah
but people send it to me a
lot and it's weird that it's like
cc'd on em yeah yeah oh yeah
oh yeah everything you get i'm cc'd
on emails changing my settings it was
i'm i mean it was kinda odd
when it first started happening that i
was i just rolled with it scott
what's your news item my news
we need shared one we play the
jingle tito it's time
he said kick boss wasn't drunk driving
news decided from three years ago ends
mine from the fake fury my mind's
war there you go go ahead from
nineteen forty one what happened just that
for one more
um my does war happen guys it's
been so long since there's been a
war isn't it i mean yeah
well i guess do one you mean
address one where they draft people oh
yeah that's true that is true it's
been a long we have a lot
of volunteers nowadays yeah is that really
why because people are volunteering so we
don't have to draft well no big
enough for oh also i think because
hanahan warfare is not the rage anymore
more saints gone out of fashion but
they don't draft people just to be
in the army oh not in this
country no but i know that now
but i'm saying they wouldn't if they
had like some big thing no well
i remember back in nineteen ninety um
i was in college and they and
a person came to our college to
talk to us about
being a conscientious objector it just in
case a draft was about to come
yeah um there was the first the
first gulf war there was concern people
were concerned that they're gonna bring the
draft back on my mother saying to
me if there's war i hope you'll
go to canada
wow yeah i mean i was twenty
and you were precisely one
ah i was gonna go the other
way you'd be too yeah okay yeah
um but yeah it was it was
kind of scary there for a second
i mean you were right in that
age you know how old is too
old like thirty five they stopped taking
you or how i can't recall i
don't remember my name in thirty five
might have been cut off maybe it
was a little young
anger i can't even remember but like
for vietnam yeah they they were just
taking everybody i have a friend who's
a couple of years older than me
who remembers seeing the vietnam war on
tv and thinking like he was he
was old enough to be aware that
it had gone on for a long
time and he thought oh my god
i'm gonna grow up i'm gonna have
to go to vietnam because he thought
it was just like this
war will never end yeah that's funny
well i mean it's funny that's hilarious
it said it's frickin hilarious fucking hilarious
do ah do you have any any
lauren do you have any family members
family members do you have any family
members who are in the arm service
my grandpa yeah he flew planes in
world war two may remember just like
that my father was in world war
two
he was in the abbey yeah my
grandfather's in world war ii my father
was in the vietnam war wow
it's intense they're better men than i
would you ah if they're though if
there were a draft i'd go
i mean one hundred percent i think
it is interesting though the paul you
and i probably grew up with because
we grew up sort of during vietnam
era yeah we i remember being very
fearful of it happening yes you know
like yeah it might happen yeah and
i might have to go i remember
that it was like i was afraid
of going to jail and i was
afraid
of getting drafted but lauren i mean
did you ever was at a part
of your life at all no i've
never i it's it's something that i've
heard about but i've never feared that
at all or like thought or feared
it for anyone else in my life
but i also always like i have
bad vision i never have to do
anything did you ever picture yourself in
the armed services
like just for fun well like when
you were thinking about masturbatory fantasies yeah
well shuffle camera
um when you're thinking about like what
job you'd have when you grew up
i no no no no no no
i would know i mean for a
bunch of reasons there was an army
recruit events i think everyone's wonderful know
there's an army recruiter in high school
who would take me out to lunch
and i would string him along think
saying i was thinking
all of it because i wanted free
lunches my god
and eventually after you know like eight
lunches he was like look it's shit
or get off the time i are
you joining lunches and you haven't shit
after any of them
and you went out to lunch in
a toilet did you ever want to
get out of the toilet i never
wanted to be but i am imagined
i imagine when i was like my
because my my older brother joined the
navy haha to get money for college
and he was lucky that he was
in there right before he got out
before right before we that first gulf
war wow really oh yeah so yeah
dishonorably discharged yep that's right yeah he
was stealing ocean water oh yeah can't
do that
was stealing he would take a tin
cup and scoop out of ocean water
and put it in his footlocker is
that when the movie tin cup it's
about my brother it's my brother's story
and the store the footlocker yeah and
the video games income oh no footlocker
footlocker is it's it's a lock that
will be at the foot of your
bed yeah it would be like a
little crate with a lock on it's
where you you
keep personal effects there as well as
do you keep your uniforms yeah yeah
yeah so to speak a cute play
on words the shoe store yes yes
yes but why do they wear referee
outfits then if it's all because like
each far longer had a little referee
in there oh really like yeah just
sitting in the cupboard yes to keep
the clothes separated
i used to call that movie the
engine in the breadbox huh just to
be offensive i guess well i was
fifteen i went to see it with
my mom and it made her laugh
so hey
that's her uber all right yeah tell
me about it i'm red boxes wait
so what would happen at these lunches
well he would explain what my duties
would be the army the marines it
was that she was the army army
and do it because i think the
my high school was
right next to a recruitment centre right
um and so yeah he would just
basically like he would really gloss over
basic training like oh that's no big
deal and that's and that's the end
but you know in the eighties like
every army movie was about basic training
and how early well yeah i don't
know if that's the case i you
know i have all i've seen
or movies then say it's horrible but
i wonder if it's like fine now
there's just no way it's good now
it's gonna be really hard is that
the whole point that they're showing you
like how hard you can push your
body well yeah and there's trying to
break you down to where you don't
question things anymore yeah you're not like
you don't really have an individualities i
think i mean maybe that's just maybe
i'm just getting that from movies
no well i think it is it
is about i think conditioning you to
be a unit you know because they
you're not i mean i don't believe
that is supposed to be about individualism
in right yeah but ah and also
you're not supposed to be the type
of person who have someone gives an
order you're like well what i'm okay
that's good but what if we you
know you're just supposed to follow
yeah what have we did it oh
nine hundred hours kind just snooze a
little on the other running can you
imagine like having a run i mean
so hard i mean it's very impressive
pulling like just doing pull-ups i did
you ever take the presidential fitness oh
yes i did not why didn't you
did you abstain i don't yeah i
was conscientious object
yeah i don't know why we didn't
at my school but i don't remember
taking that at all what is that
was how you became president
well we wouldn't have our current disqualified
it's
did you not take it nowhere was
it not a thing but it was
why is it called presidential i guess
because the president made it an issue
of like every school child should be
should have a basic level of fitness
i can't remember who instituted that but
it was it must have been at
least carter because i remember taking it
ah don't worry we did some work
at least like that if it wasn't
that but it was like we had
to do the sit and reach or
you like didn't did you do that
where it's like oh what's up along
with l b j j o b
j wang ruler on a really long
couple rulers connected or something on top
of a milk crate maybe that's just
my cheap school and then you'd put
your feet against the mill like
it's just an aisle of gold and
other schools and they were maybe like
a real ruler that's made to be
the length of the thing you would
like then what like a fourteen inch
ruler like they were making these special
just for this fitness really was like
yardstick probably and then you're trying to
like put your feet against ammo crate
and it went past
at the edge of the milk crate
and you would lean forward with your
hands on top of each other and
try to press the furthest number you
could and then that was your score
so if you get like i got
like as far as i could reach
sixty inches or something that's not like
your age sixty nine
three cats and then we had to
do like the hang or the pull
ups or either yeah that's really going
to hang and hang for a really
long time i you were supposed to
do overhand pull-ups but i could only
do underhand and maybe wanted that you
know and that i've for some reason
i've just never been able to do
pull-ups do you have to climb rope
in your gym you know what i
was forced to to
take gymnastics when i was ten and
eleven or so by my parents ah
because when i ah ok so here
i grew up no the end
um when i was six seven and
eight i ah was in baseball was
in little league did you guys ever
do literally deserted by baseball my school
okay in eighth grade so but this
was like during the the you know
afternoons and evening games and stuff like
that nighttime yeah
yeah and i sleep sleep time um
good night moon the dark of night
the dark knight rises um so i
for three years in a row i
was forced to and this is my
recollection of it i was forced to
play baseball little league ah and my
coaches would always yell at me and
the
the team hated me and i couldn't
bat for shit and ah at one
point ah i was always made to
play right field because that's where noble
two that's right and at one point
someone hit a fly ball and it
hit me right in the nuts
and then you win ten grand max
wish i got the last laugh
so so i i remember and there
were so many afternoons where i was
crying and crying and saying i don't
want to go i don't want to
go and they forced me to go
and so then after my third year
i was just like i can't do
it i don't want to do it
anymore please don't make me go and
they said okay well you have to
take gymnastics then or you have to
do something else first it was to
get made fun of for
yeah and and i could see the
carter then you don't like that they'll
flip around being and a unitar so
here's what here's what actually happened and
they didn't tell me this until i
was twenty maybe when i stopped having
your cycle
when i went into kindergarten they did
i guess the kindergarten ah equivalent of
the presidential test but they just revised
presidential for this
they were just trying to figure out
your basic level of fitness and i
couldn't i guess i i could not
hop on one foot i was so
uncoordinated that they were like you need
to get him involved in some sort
of like physical activity and so they
put me into these things but they
never told me it was because of
that they say
just helped you they were just saying
like you have to do this and
they never gave me a reason wow
yeah so i took i took gymnastics
um from ten until twelve or something
like that and i was forced to
go to a i couldn't just go
to a regular gymnastics place i was
forced to go to a christian gym
gymnasium
called athletes in action i remember and
it was where you would do i
don't know you do an hour of
gymnastics and then after fifty five minutes
they would go okay chalk talk and
then you would sit there and they
would take out chalk and like i
guess sort of draw bible study or
whatever why yeah like chalk from the
gymnastic
attics like yeah hanshi yeah pancho yeah
yeah chalk talk
dog yeah so i was really the
name of the show top dog
look it up i learned that lesson
the hard way look it up
just look at john talk look it
up jog dog um um but yeah
so i got i got ah i
was really bad at it of course
and the only thing i was good
at was i was incredible at climbing
rope and i used because i have
really long legs and i could use
them i couldn't pull up
do show
show
these getaway sticks he's preparing to stockings
get stuck
i'm wearing ted stockings right now
is that your what you call bra
ah tits
just put knee highs on your droopy
oh my dads are drove huh okay
i'll be high paced perfectly by to
charge but yeah i could propel myself
up the rope so yes i did
climb a row to answer your question
yeah wow jeez what day is it
because they have the rope in your
school lauren could not claim that shit
i've never seen
seen it i oh yeah hanging i
only have seen it in movies we
had like a big rope hanging on
the ceiling yeah well enough to the
side if you don't play basketball and
they let it down i was always
terrified when it came down because i
knew i would be able to do
it there were three rope singing and
they'd be like everyone has to sit
in a line you went behind the
rope and everyone divides then you just
wait and watch each other climate are
just idiots
i mean if you fall f danger
there was nothing there right yeah and
blue master it and i only got
up on the side like just pull
my hands up as far as i
could i like going up and then
i'd be done about sixty inches or
so at sixty nine
sixty nine the rope
yeah i know what i what i
love though on days when we had
do you ever got guys have scooter
days where you have these little like
um it was a little plastic thing
with handles on the side and four
wheels on the bottom and it was
just like a teeny little thing you
just run around with them like you're
asking the hair and you're you're like
hands down
anywhere like you said the ass and
the hair like it was a fable
you'd be like this oh i get
oh okay that's so huh
but you're small so you're not like
it's not that weird and it was
so funny we'd race around and then
one time i was racing someone around
the perimeter of the gym and then
he cut me off and i roll
i like ran straight into the wall
and i was in like bio fourth
grade or something and my glasses went
straight into my head oh lightning cut
my head i have a glasses in
my head story really new i have
been afraid of that my whole life
oh my god it was so horrible
i like rammed my head into the
wall and my god like askew and
pushed into my face and then i
had blood dripping down my face and
go to the nurse
and she was this old woman with
like really big lips and she's like
yeah i remember she told my mom
like ten times she was like she
might want stitches for cosmetic reasons and
kevin what does that mean did you
get no i have you have a
girl scar oh yeah
um so my glasses i e z
it hey it's just you like deja
awesome
because my score yeah god damn it
you look like if d j qualls
played freddy krueger okay mike
for the record he's a handsome boy
freddy krueger no i feel like i
feel like i've talked about d j
calls more in the past year than
like anyone and probably will get to
play woodhouse
i'm getting d j he was on
um the night i know what show
is it um was that kid who
reads speaks to the dead sixty minutes
no tyler or something tyler perry's house
ideas house of past loves um he
was on that speaking to someone who
passed away but anyway please tell me
your story of your glass lee i'm
telling you
last season the head story ah boo
boo but maybe move i was ten
years old ah prime gymnastics time oh
did you do a cartwheel i was
i actually was ah everyone at our
ah gymnasium was encouraged to do a
cartwheel aethon for charity as
many as you could do as many
and people would people would sign up
ah you know and say i'll i'll
pledge you know a penny per cartwheel
or five cents per car whatever you
write me well i mean considering a
thousand well i mean first of all
this is like nineteen eighty seventies but
worth a lot they will worth a
lot more vastly
like er it's not bad you could
buy shit for a penny pennies were
a dollar dollar was five dollars pennies
on the dollar but um right but
by the way it was it was
how many can you do within i
think twenty minutes or a half hour
or something like that um and i
ended up i did more than anyone
expect
did because everyone knew i was like
an uncorked coordinated dork you know but
i did ah say i did one
hundred and fifty right you know and
so for you know a ten year
old that's a lot it's a lot
of car wheels you know a dollar
one i never done one of my
entire life yeah so boss ah nope
i have a fear of diving forward
into the unknown so when i got
to school and i told everyone how
many i did ever all the kids
were kind of mad because they had
to pay so much money and they're
like huh okay who knew i would
do one hundred and fifty and so
his dad paid per kid for every
everyone pledged to sue those adults
alleging well it was some adults but
it was also kids you would go
around and say hey would you sponsor
me in this thing like kids do
that you know keeping money but then
like so so so it's like collectively
the school did like five thousand and
you had pledged a dollar you owe
five thousand dollars no one would ever
do that no no they peep know
every
the person pledged a certain amount per
cartwheel that you did and they would
per person so like they would not
just do for as many cars as
the school does it was like oh
sponsor scott only and i'll give a
penny well i was the only one
in this gymnastics thing oh so i
came to school i came to school
and i was like hey do you
mind sponsoring me for god was this
your idea
thank you penny for every curl idea
i found one back
but anyway i couldn't do cartwheels all
that well i was really shaky on
my basically would just like kind of
like flop my body over and so
so these ads falling down during p
a one point everyone was like hey
show is how you do a cartwheel
because you're so fucking good atoms yeah
everyone hated you and i did em
and they were like
you can't even be the adults that's
not even good form for these cars
you can't even like get your legs
up like completely over your head like
god and then do you hit your
glasses okay so the glasses story i
was ten i was ten years old
how did we end up talking about
the carpet you asked about it i
don't know wow you say can you
do a cartwheel
read back the minutes oh yeah you're
right i did kevin's got it so
ten years old i'm riding my bike
around kevin writing every word we're saying
it's taking his his hand is bleeding
please go so like seven i had
just gotten mirrored sunglasses which were in
nineteen eighty i think they were like
a new thing oh i i
thought mirrored sunglasses were the cooler were
so fucking cool oh my god what
i'm trying to remember where i first
saw them but they were like maybe
a movie or something but it was
like holy shit guys like maybe a
cool kid like bad news bears or
something like that problems like aviators are
like yeah like literally every other sunglasses
up until nineteen eight
eighty or so you could see the
person's eyes and it's disgusting
but these were like holy shit commemorating
so i e i saved up my
car wheel money and i know i
paid all that to the tip
but i bought a pair of mirrored
sunglasses and they were expensive i think
they were like three dollars or something
like that and i bought them and
i was riding my bike around by
myself and i thought to myself these
are so cool you can't see my
eyes it would be so cool to
be like riding my bike with my
eyes clue
closed and everyone looking at me saying
oh hey like obviously thinking well that's
a kid with his eyes open and
but they wouldn't know that my eyes
are closed because i have these mirrored
sunglasses so i love kid logic because
like why even thinking
so i was like you know what
i should do i should start at
the other end of the street because
my house was was on one end
of the street i should start on
one end of the street and i'll
with my eyes open i'll count how
all count how long it takes me
to ride my bike from here to
my house right and then i'll go
back and i'll do it with my
eyes closed and it'll be so awesome
because idiots these idiots no one will
know they'll still be thinking to themselves
look there's a normal kid drives like
cooler to have people see that your
eyes were closed right but no one
was around but this is like and
no one there were no windsor
there's no one here it's a ghost
town on my street and that's why
i think i've felt like i was
safe too because there's no traffic or
anything like that so i i go
to one end of the street and
i countdown it's like ah thirty three
seconds right i'm like ok alright so
at at thirty three i'm gonna open
my eyes and i'm gonna be right
at my house
and so i go to angeline and
industry i closed my eyes and i
i start pedaling and i'm like one
two three and then i don't remember
anything
i wake up in a neighbor's house
and in their house in their house
i wake up in their house and
they've dragged me into their house and
i have ah ridden my bicycle into
a car and i'm sorry car park
car yeah and ah my glasses my
new mirrored sunglasses have smashed into my
face
entire faces bloody
that's like horrifying and they're and they're
like and it's my next door neighbor
and they're got home i've never been
in their solo for so close i've
never been in their house before this
is the only time i've ever been
allowed into their house they never let
me for summer never invited me or
my parents do they have kids ah
yeah
yeah yeah my like one year older
than me yep wow i had a
neighbor like that too yep the end
the my mother's neighborhood my other neighbors
had kids the exact same age as
those neighbors and they were the best
of friends and they and wow they
would make fun of me as i
was walking just brutal
so so yeah this is like so
i want to set tails in a
row they take me to the hospital
and i am logging i get stitches
for cosmetic reasons and so for six
months i have a fucked up face
with stitches when i'm ten years oh
my six month
and everyone just makes fun of me
the same way that i did to
you frankenstein to the way al frankenstein
style i love frankenstein love that that
mean mein jab from um a you
reminded me of two stories one is
that this new rog moved to my
school um and she moved to like
my neighborhood and
and my friend and i went to
go hang out with her one day
we went to her backyard to play
and she wanted to play blind man's
bluff i don't think it's the my
other friend to play bindmans but which
i thought that was called blind man's
buff because the man's naked yeah that's
how we
yeah makes sense i can't remember what
that game so it's i think what
it is is that it's like kind
of like marco polo on languages as
some kids were playing that the other
day when i was staying at a
hotel and they were playing the fool
that is a dangerous game it doesn't
make someone using your module paulo well
especially with like kids running around at
the pool and everyone's closing their eyes
eyes and there my first concussion i
think was from running alongside the first
kitchen and then you played nashville for
seven years i've had i think two
concussions um but this was so this
blind man's bluff are playing so basically
the new girl was going to be
the blind man he closed her eyes
we run around and she has to
find us by the sound of our
voice and
and with her eyes closed yes like
tagged someone yeah yeah and it was
fun for about eight seconds then she
ran full steam into a tree like
a big tree and her nose just
like explode oh it was insane and
then her nanny came out which i
had never known anyone to have yeah
yes fran drescher and that was insane
but
then my other residents your goat are
you doing friendship
the other store i thought about your
story reminds me of is that i
went to disney world when i was
ah five with my family it was
our big trip moment like setup a
lot of money to do this and
my mom my grandma my aunt and
my dad and my brother were there
and so my mom and grandma my
aunt when did something that women would
want to do i guess my dad
took me and my brother the
bathroom yeah but it was a nighttime
they may went out or something my
dad took me my brother to see
lady bugs the movie rodney danger yeah
okay when we got there and women
would not want this really young man's
think my dad was letting us do
something that was for the kids but
we went in the theater i remember
that and then i i
i woke up in bed um and
that's all i saw four minutes of
the movie and i woke up in
bed and was like like next to
i thought was my brother who was
snoring and i was like shut up
shut up shut up it was my
grandma and i was in bed with
my grandma i didn't know what had
happened at all and it turns out
i'd gone to the bathroom by myself
because my dad didn't he
didn't understand that he could just take
me in the men's room and like
watch and make sure that i was
okay because i was five right and
then he let me go to the
women's room and i slipped on a
wet floor and hit my head and
was like completely unconscious like five minutes
into ladybugs i guess i went to
the bathroom and your dad like the
end of ladybugs he loved the film
david film ah knowing that some woman
came out like found my dad somehow
and then like i they took me
home and put me in bed i
mean there have been helping shining say
you knew the house but yeah there
have been multiple times where i was
put in bed with a head injury
oh really
the one where i fell by the
pool i was taken to the hospital
i was throwing up i clearly had
a concussion and i got a cat
scan or whatever and that's when they
said she has two marks on her
head on her brain like this is
our second just to bruise brain and
my mom was like i don't know
what you're talking about and then a
couple years ago we pieced together that
story and i was like at disney
world i probably had a concussion
ah did the cops ever come to
your house no actually yeah well i
made friends with a cop at one
point not to keep it friends with
my friends tell you why don't we
take a break okay let's take a
break and i want to hear just
friends with a cop ah we're i
don't know the name of this ah
show that you're listening to but it'll
be right back
yeah
welcome back we're here it's lauren paul
scott and the same show you've been
listening to and right before the break
lauren was gonna tell us a story
about a cop that she'd be friended
yes i got into multiple it's really
i don't have to get into all
the details but i got into multiple
get all of em deeds well first
of all before you get the cup
story how many concussions lifetime i would
say
to um there's a possibility for a
third where i was jumping on the
bed and hit my head on my
radiator and then my dad pushed my
head together with a towel while i
was bleeding oh i have i not
not to interrupt your cop sorry but
held it
but it's reminding me of the head
injury that i had
i wish we were over at my
great aunt's house happening you guys
i know it's
a charming life i guess zero editor
i know katie dipl one said that
she had ah concussion she was not
funny before the concussion then got funny
yeah and i kind of like maybe
it happened to me because i got
to see those two marks brainer the
coffee bar it's where i lost all
sense of reality i remembering that i
did have one head injury in high
school
all but there it was it was
untreated but okay okay well i was
it was after a it was my
freshman year of high schools after doing
a show we did oliver and so
me and my bill sikes know i
was a freshman so there was no
no leads for me no no no
i did have a featured line i
was living
hotel remember landlord i used to remember
the whole thing but it was like
a little speech that i got to
give before this before the great song
that everyone loves oom papa oh god
so um but after after the show
my friend rick and i um dick
scott he was my friend he was
kind of a dick though no i'm
not i use a dick was had
a chick he had a big dick
he was not a chat
that's all i got so we did
this we tried to do this thing
that the we saw the dancers in
the show do which is where we're
sending back to back with link arms
and then one of us flips over
the other wow yeah right oh yeah
so we had no training no weren't
instructed by a court i've always saw
it show
he tried it and i tried to
flip over his back and then we
both just fell and we both landed
on the tops of our head
god it was like i can still
feel like the impact it was sunken
feelings like home it was so it
was like a direct hit just on
this concrete floor oh my god and
then we we slowly like got up
were like i don't feel anything like
that didn't hurt and then people i
remember people looking at it like you
should not
i fall asleep like you should stay
awake and then we did we just
stayed awake the whole night we like
went out we went to howard johnson's
and i know that that's part of
it but why what does it prove
by you staying away or like what
does it stop while opening or if
you go to sleep then you can
just go into dreamy time bye-bye and
die forever why i don't because the
dream lord comes against you because like
you belong to me now have a
concussion but you stay awake long enough
it goes away yeah guys i always
thought it was to see if you
had a concussion i don't know i
don't know why i know i know
i know well don't tell us oh
wait so so my story with my
head injury was ah we were at
my great aunt's house
um which was in downtown l a
i remember and i love it because
she century ah we love it six
three
love it
wow
the monster at the yeah but because
it was randy newman's way over yeah
because he was in downtown it was
a i guess more ah an area
more prone to theft so she had
bars on her the windows over apart
sure ah and they were i remember
they were white her apart
it was brick think ah and they
they were they were iron and they
were white and they were they had
like the points at the bottom and
the top now right so my brother
and i were were having a rubber
band fight where we were like go
most normal thing you've talked about
where we are just you know like
you know you pull back a rubber
band yeah okay okay clearly and so
you should remember mazzy just fancy so
we're having a rubber banfi while my
parents
now that i am remembering it she
my great aunt was not fair so
it may have been she had just
passed away i can't remember because i
believe my parents were packing up her
stuff so either they either she'd passed
away or were they robbing her
the airfare right up into dollars label
they may be moving her to the
home where she ended up that's probably
what it was um so we were
in bed some bleakness god
my brother and i having a rubber
band fight and ah i shot mine
and i went to go retrieve it
underneath her window and i stood up
really suddenly and ah ah the iron
pointy bar went into my head and
and i i my brother was like
hey
come on keep going i was like
i don't feel well and i went
in i sat down and i remember
like feeling my head going ah and
then i looked at my hand it
was covered with blood
and i was like wait how your
body that kind of shuts down you
didn't think anything is really wrong and
you're like this hurts a little and
it's like obviously yeah so i told
i think my my father was going
to mcdonalds at the time for for
burgers and so i was like mom
this apps like lucky
so i showed my mom and she
she was like oh no and i
expected when something like that happens i
expect you go to the hospital right
away yeah and she was like well
your dad's coming back with me down
so you know wait here put put
this pressure on it i guess so
i'd like we waited forum and then
i remember they were my dad got
back and was kinda like
well we should eat first because we
have so and i remember i got
my burger with fries the hole and
i asked for no ketchup and there
was ketchup on the burger and i
was upset but wasn't blood
yeah i remember just thinking like you
won't even take me to the hospital
and now i have to eat this
burger with yeah polaris but yeah i
had to three three only three stitches
i think from the oh my god
yeah when i think about the one
time that i hit my head on
the radiator um i had a babysitter
over and i was bouncing on the
bed with my brother boingboing
flopped right off onto the radio slap
my head and then my dad came
home right as that happens the babysitter
was like okay i gotta go you
know it was like thing and then
he just put pressure on and they
went to sleep oh um but i'm
guessing it must have been a small
you might have just been a senior
school yeah i mean i'm sure he
he knows right i mean i don't
know um but yeah very
tell us about this cop oh yeah
well okay i had multiple um car
accidents in high school too too oh
but this then so the first time
i was just driving around aimlessly with
my friend natalie who's my best friend
to this day and we would always
just drive around to listen to music
like once we had the abyss
oddity to drive so i was alone
with the car and we were just
like drive around was fourth of july
or the third of july but my
town does fireworks on the third as
well and i think it was the
fourth of july yeah i think it
was fourth hundred law i don't even
know what song i was in saturday
that's right yeah um and why would
he wonder if it
was the northern lights in the park
he's more if you stay on obviously
that's why he went to the park
i think it was gruber dave gruber
allen who said maybe the most unpatriotic
song of all time i think it
was the fourth of july i hear
it was a saturday twenty four thirty
five
um but anyways i ran a stop
sign there was a big bush to
the left and i didn't see there
was a car at the other stop
sign so i thought i was safe
and just went and this was going
thinking and i crashed into the back
a great behind the passenger door and
spun around wait did they they t-boned
you i keep on them oh i
see so yeah and so they were
they
and through the stop sign sign first
yeah but i was expecting it got
it and they spent around and then
it was an old man and a
woman and the the woman had spilled
her fruit salad all over the man's
lap oh he's very kind at the
same time my homer i'm sure it
wasn't come yeah it's like when he
was checking tae hae said fruit salad
yeah
then my home room teacher ran out
from behind a house where he was
at a picnic and heard the crash
and then saw it was me whoa
and he said my dad's a lawyer
and he's coming up behind me don't
say anything like what the homeroom teachers
yeah my dad's a lawyer yeah and
he was at the picnic too so
he the dad walked up and then
they anyway
the cop that came there i met
for the first time this really nice
cop and so that'll happen it was
horrible i would gotten a lot of
trouble couldn't go out for the fourth
of july and it cost three thousand
dollars fix the car and i just
i hate i felt so brutal that
yeah i mean i didn't pay and
i didn't have any money then um
in a couple of weeks so after
i got the car back my car
had basically become
like totally submission in the front and
i got it back and it was
a great front entry in the back
so i described my body
right my dad also had just given
me his old car and like said
you can have it official it was
like a whole thing of course ruined
it and then like a couple was
yours though yeah true it was mine
debris you can do whatever you want
yeah well jeep cherokee and then i
got the car back finally and i
was driving again with with nab
early and someone ran a stop sign
and hit me oh i tell him
that though i know well then i
was crying a lot and one was
like stop crying it's not that big
of a deal and i was like
but you don't understand i just got
my car fixed tonight today and i'm
sixteen and whatever and then the same
cop showed up when he's like lauren
and like that like a thing he
remembered your name
yeah somebody who's like it's you again
right and then that we had that
whole thing and like that was like
kind of funny but also like horrible
for me and then like a month
later my dad was out of town
and my mom and my mom heard
something in the basement and she came
everyone was like there's something in these
i'm so scared i was like go
to bed like i was wrong i
was like just leave me alone
i'll just go to your room like
i was like really not sympathetic quiet
old woman just like maybe it's an
animal i don't know and then she
called the police and that guy oh
boy and then he was like oh
my god it's you again and i
was like she thinks something the basement
he gave me his trading card which
i guess a lot of police officers
have i beg your pardon
his trading tops it's like baseball yeah
yeah i you see i've never heard
of that it was neat and he
had all his like stats on the
back like his like what family how
many muggers zero salary like how many
kids he has like what he's forced
in like whatever
does this i like it hey nice
really cool oh i'm sorry did you
ever see another one of these ever
in your life no but i've never
gotten that intimate with a cop it
was my third time meeting maybe they'll
give to you on the third thursday
meet someone i'm gonna give a baby
a half or two maybe a few
minutes okay my top five here you
collect them all you've earned my car
that's an yeah name it it had
the effect that it was supposed to
have on you where you don't fear
the police anymore and you're not like
frightened by them yeah no it was
just like funny like oh god i
can't believe this i had an experience
with a cop where is that all
you have to say about the cop
is that the only time you ever
saw him and it goes three times
then i never saw never saw him
again i'm still have the card probably
someone who seems anything
um i think his name is larry
but i can't i'm not positive about
that i'd have to i'd have to
say my file worries no me tell
you hopefully still pub patrolling evanston um
i had a weird experience with either
there was when i was that age
actually i was seventeen i was driving
around by myself and i had an
experience where all
of the cops in where i grew
up or it's a private town you
know so it's like they they're a
lot of them and they're constantly patrolling
constantly you know pulling people over so
i put their cups they're not like
security know their collars but but it's
like it's like burbank where you know
it's a private town and they have
their own police force i don't know
they have a weird rule and
rank that i just learned that um
you can't put on a drag show
in a public establish establishment really and
there's all like a law i just
saw something on twitter about it interested
did somebody get in trouble for having
yeah this show is cancelled and then
um daniel franzese he would think i
was being about being like we have
to like make a change i think
that would be one of those things
where they're like oh there's this antiquated
law
la but no one right which it
sounds like some old fashioned thing that
yeah but i guess somehow we think
it was arrival drag queen shut them
sounds like a movie
it's like i just put out just
went out because of this letter we
got right this movie yeah yeah um
so there was a period of time
where i was constantly being pulled over
for various things and um and i
found out once later by a different
cop that the reason i was constantly
being pulled over because i had a
lot of stickers yeah carre about this
yeah
and one of them was a what
have the jamaican flag and was like
one love and people think you're a
hippie then people thought smoking that it
was possible because they're like they're like
where's all your pod and it was
like totally bought and i was like
i don't smoke pot he's like why
do you have that sticker on the
back of your car inside jamaican that's
really funny but um i was
how dare you my heritage so i
i was seventeen and i was in
a couple of things happen i was
in a band in high school and
also pretty cool i also had a
girlfriend where oh where really turned around
for this scarface
so are you the kid that got
your sunglasses embedded in his face no
the question is are you the kid
who rode his bike with his eyes
that would be cool yeah that would
nobody nobody knew that gets you ever
explained didn't you see the car and
you're like i had my eyes closed
no i never talked about the logic
of white house i just said those
like you suddenly realised i may know
there are there are two things in
my life that i never brought up
the logic of of why that were
like deep dark
secrets that i think years later i
finally admitted there was that one and
then there was the time there was
the time that i woke up and
didn't want to go to school and
took a red marking pen and drew
dots all over my face like i
had the measles and then forgot i
did it and when my mom asked
me what was on my
face i didn't know what she was
talking about and that sold it so
well because it was a genuine like
i don't know what your diet yeah
she thought she was like we need
to take you to a doctor and
we went to a doctor the doctor
looked at me and took out a
scrub brush and some soap and watched
it oh my yeah yeah
yeah and i couldn't explain why it
was on your face and their n
and my mom was like did you
do this did you do this and
i totally sold my brother out i
was like i don't know i don't
know what and so my brother got
blamed for it for years for like
sneaking my room and drawing on my
face which any must
have protested his innocence yes yes and
if he was probably very convincing but
then everyone was like damn he's a
good lie well he was he was
the bad seed of the oh so
he just families so they assumed that
he would do it yeah so and
i was i was kind of sweet
and and you know an innocent little
viewer remember like on the way to
the
doctor what it was oh yes yeah
okay as soon as they were like
look in the mirror i was like
ah oh i'm in trouble here but
you know like i was too silly
to explain i feel like i've had
moments like that as a kid i
just didn't want to explain myself it's
like that's embarrassed i knew i would
be in trouble more than embarrassed you
so i just never said so it
was maybe fifteen years before
i brought up that it was me
and oh my god yeah so anyway
so i had a girlfriend and i
was in a band and so i
was driving and i saw cops you
constantly seeing cops pulled people over and
i was i was making a left-hand
turn in front of these cops and
i was like really nervous about it
i was like oh i gotta drive
rye
right or else they gonna pull me
over because i've been pulled over three
times recently and i was so nervous
i drove over the center divider and
ah and that was like well maybe
they didn't notice and started like trying
to drive away as fast as i
couldn't they of course you know got
to me but they did this thing
and and they would i didn't know
this when i was a kid but
what they
yeah we search your car please like
it's an order but you can say
no it's yeah right so i didn't
know that they they would always say
like an order so it was always
like yeah yeah yeah terrify yeah so
they weakling they went all throughout my
car and i had just gotten back
from a performance so i had a
ton of guitars in there
and out of guitar i had i
had like four guitars just like every
note
yeah i had all of our equipment
like
what a great song by the way
girl understand you just go around back
and forth
um so the clots aren't is this
just imagine it faster
so i'm saying though i'm still own
her
i'm sitting on the curb and that's
the bathroom
i'm sitting on the curb and these
cops are searching my car and they
come back and they have a really
stern look on their face and they
go okay we have some questions for
you number one where did all of
that musical equipment come from and i
said oh i'm in a band we
just had a performance
okay number two do you need a
loose singer
please can now listen to this law
that say i'm singing but yeah i
was like that fits my guitar work
perfectly
so then he says number two we
found ah a pack of condoms in
your glove compartment yeah so what and
it's a twelve pack why do you
need that many condoms that they're just
trying to embarrass you aren't they and
i said well
i'm in a band
and he said my third question is
may i join your band
hey i get out of here kid
oh my god wow why were you
pulled over initial because you drove over
this
insane yeah i got pulled over multiple
times in high school and i always
cried my way out of it i
mean i was truly terrified too but
getting the tip i heard i dated
people who were would say they cried
to get out of it yeah just
it's i've never gotten to witness as
an adult though i've read my yeah
i've i've had people get out of
it as oh yeah no i can't
make myself cry i'm usually just like
okay yeah
well what's the what's the saddest thing
that's ever happened to you okay here
i go
well if we need to take a
break when we come back we have
ah we ah ah one of us
always brings a segment and i brought
a segment ah so let's take a
break when we come back we'll have
an exciting game that we're going to
play stories you tell anything look none
no story to tell well well you
got any of those make you think
of anything ah
i had a story about my brother
getting the tip of his finger chopped
off we were kids this story about
getting arrested from your side from sphincter
look we won't
huh
this was a moment in our family
of great sadness
i can't believe britain will sheep in
this
and you're no better
imagine being like ah like
look when we come back paul's going
to tell his story
please i don't have to tell your
daddy
yeah i just thought it was funny
that i i was thinking like oh
i have a story of this topic
and then oh speak it to take
sides but we do have to take
a brow would you know we do
have to take a break but we
have to let's come back in here
one of these stories alright alright we'll
be right back with this show
welcome back scott paul lauren and eric
yeah
man paul was going to tell a
story about his brother getting his fingertips
my older brother we were move it
was my brother my father and myself
we were moving this ridiculous piece of
furniture down into the basement from the
second floor of the house we had
a ridiculous about the furniture was just
like this crazy cumbersome cabinet
it it was like this law k
k k
hey always like none of those words
do triple c um
so we we must have gotten it
down one flight of stairs okay and
so now we are trying to get
it down this down the stairs to
the basement and so my brother was
in the front my dad and i
were on top front party in the
back
i describe my body
so we lost we'd lost hold of
it and so it slammed against it
slammed my brother's hand against the wall
and it was just very tip of
his pinkie like it could have been
he would he kind of lost his
hand and were like crushed his hand
oh so it cut off
off it like severed the tip of
his pinkie woe and he was screaming
there was blood spraying and what was
he screaming was he like he was
screaming high yeah
ah
oh those two marks on your brainer
so like i know aren't they oh
he was he was taken to the
hospital and to this day has just
like a weird um like little nub
of a fingernail growing out of that
oh yeah because have actually cut
it it off everyone top of his
pill i don't ah
do you know what i don't know
if he ever has to trim it
or any just probably because it's sort
of like you know your pinky toe
with mine has like just a little
tiny toenail and it'll grow out
hurry i do remember i had this
friend in middle school who had um
her toenail i don't know what happened
to it must have been something like
something fell on some yeah just black
well no like it was only half
down like vertical oh wow so it
was like that thin in the middle
of her toe i know i don't
like it tell
did you make fun of no i
just like mass interesting note that i
had never forget it that's interesting away
i hate i think i just i
don't like hate feet where i'm like
don't let feet touch me ever like
some people like really hate fee yes
you ever google lauren lucasville why did
you ah lucky feats popping off y'all
hey pop it off responses
by wiki yeah oh there will be
got these pens
well let's reach out to when you
can if i can get some money
from wiki feet i would be glad
if they could do because yeah oh
yeah nine years disgusting but i know
what you mean like their feeder i'm
not repulsed by feet i have friends
who are but they're not great yeah
and don't think about them too much
and only one yeah see
someone's here a long period of time
because if they're clean they've just had
some sort of liquid all over him
once they're slimy
why okay but if they're drive their
growth think about the brief window of
time that your feet are clean yeah
so small it's so small yeah i
mean i think the second my feet
touched the floor it's like when you
drive i'm thinking okay and even if
they're even even if you're on a
bed and you've like
someone's just washed them and you're on
the bed and you're sick i'm really
exhausted wash your on the bed somebody's
just washed your fee i'm still no
mind
veronica i'm missing something obvious mary magdalene
and then she dried them with her
hair hey this is a good segue
by the way those two are just
from the scripture and then she dried
them with her hair you said mary
magdalene is a good segue to our
to the segment that i brought this
is a game famous horrors
number one with a bullet lower lab
guys okay
um this is this way wait was
she or was it yes she was
she was crushed no sex workers so
chicago right was she a hole she
a whore to feel or what was
that license plate they the personalized led
display you said to laura this i
found your license plate
oh yeah it looks like something slut
or something i'm sorry i'm sad i
mean it's actually arrest ah i did
mean to sexually harass you family member
song yeah alright this is a segment
it's sort of based on a game
that i played a couple of times
very early in
comedy bang bang but i adapted it
here to actually be not anti comedy
and an actual game okay and this
is a game dude can one of
you or both of you bring up
your timer on your phone does that
possible let's both do it um so
this is a game called duck mary
kiss ooh duck marry kiss alright how
much time obviously sixty seconds obviously based
obviously sixty seconds
obviously based on the popular expression fuck
marry kill ooh scott this is duck
marry kiss now what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna do you one by one
and the other the person who's not
playing like you're just spent a little
bit later the person who's not playing
if you would time it if that
was also time it and and call
time you're just
playing the game yes you're gonna see
how many you can get in sixty
seconds okay okay and i am going
to read names and you are going
to tell me if they are a
famous duck a famous marry or oh
or a current or former member of
kiss oh okay great okay okay don't
want to hear a kit duck marry
kiss you want to go first lauren
are excited
yeah i love games okay so ah
paul let me know when to start
and then stay time when it's yeah
and go donald duck correct simmons kiss
correct howard ah duck correct j blige
mary correct pickford oh whooo
incorrect that mary karr um um car
mary incorrect kiss louis ah duck correct
ace kiss correct poppins mary correct bushrod
duck correct stanley kiss correct the demon
kiss correct dark wing duck correct winstead
duck incorrect mary steam virgin mary correct
cadman
um um kiss correct ludwig von drake
mary incorrect doc vinnie vincent
kiss correct huey do duck
correct the onc warrior ah kiss my
members webby van der quack duh okay
let's see you got one to miss
fun three by the way
the other person should be counting because
now i have to remember oh okay
okay ah let's see yeah we you
got one or let you do no
no no i said that one two
three four five
six we were one two three four
five sleeve all of this in seven
eight o d you counted three wrong
okay so we got to let me
count how many i did one
you got eighteen now okay so you
don't have enough to keep going i
believe i do let me say yeah
i have enough okay alright paul are
you ready yes i remember duck duck
marry kiss all right let me know
when and and ryan you can err
sorry
yeah and keeping check of the oh
hey you're ryan
kevin you can you can say how
many ah wrong okay oh okay okay
alright and you can pretend to be
ryan i don't have to keep track
i think i should do you want
to do isn't it easier to know
do you know how many there are
no yeah i will yeah oh okay
sure so just let me know how
many wrong okay here we go so
just keep time yeah set go mcdonnell
mary correct launchpad duck correct spaceman ah
kiss correct gizmo
duck correct heart mary correct daffy duck
correct star child kiss right poopy face
tomato nose
duck correct click click marry incorrect kiss
murphy mary correct dewey duck correct the
fox guess correct yankee doodle
duck correct singer
mary incorrect kiss murphy oh i said
that one freely ah yes correct fair
fair mary incorrect kiss lou retton how
many people i know mary correct space
kiss correct flint heart glam gold duck
correct st john
mary incorrect kiss jesus wilson
merry time all right well i got
wrong was kiss well how many people
are in case i thought there were
four former members and current members so
many wrong for wrong and i did
one
think brown thinking pain from mt mt
mt mt twenty two so you got
eighteen right wo thai gay night nice
fun alright i have one more left
whoever says what it whoever whoever says
what it is first actually you know
what will we'll play it by playing
games jimmy pardo rules whoever buzzes in
first and you buzzing by saying your
name okay whoever buzzes in first will
get the chance to answer and if
they are writes they win and if
they are incorrect they the other person
wins okay ready here we go you
don't say that one person loses that's
very
positive spin okay here we go ready
fillmore paul paul
duck correct you are the winner
wow and that is of course duck
marry kiss it finally pays off that
i memorized my own name
i had a hard time thinking of
what to say right then yeah well
that was fun yeah did you have
fun yeah i love games yay the
musical fruit games games musical fruit the
more you play the more your tune
okay okay alright we should wrap it
up why i gotta go somewhere
and it goes somewhere i'm going to
korean spy are you oh nice going
to korea huh right now are you
really going yep for the war okay
i got drafted oh cool
i'm gonna mail a jeep back to
myself ah jeep wrangler may like the
toe like your car oh um i
had fun i had fun i had
fun seeing you guys yes to see
um we'll see everyone next time right
that's right we will on this show
which has a name and you should
just
read your whatever you know what it's
called yeah why don't you tell us
what it's called yeah seriously tell us
by
a this has been an year with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com