wow
oh and welcome back to three duh
mine bill cosby huh why i'm loose
okay
and i'm charlie rose
charlie rose is a great name it
is a great deal right right yeah
rose is such a cool last name
and only the two of the biggest
assholes i've ever had it pete rose
and charlie rose this scene oh yeah
i pictured a football field i'll give
you that there was really what did
you picture when you've checked
mean grass those white lines and the
hawaiian dream so many young men e
o whoa what about the grid ayers
what about the pigskin i pictured the
pigskin
slideshow reasons because good to touch the
gray green grass oh millennials i'm with
you i have no idea why this
is such a big generic song yeah
he loved it gen x loves tom
jones singing
green green grass of home
pete rose said a funny thing it
was a real asshole thing but it
was really funny thing was when ah
they were somebody was telling him about
um a player in the in the
japan league that was about to like
ah obliterated record literally a record of
his and his response was hoping to
start killing high school games now
it really hit me on this video
of um oh god i'm gonna i'm
gonna madonna like a virgin i'm honestly
going to mess up every detail great
seeing what you can remember to trim
it's an m p n and p
yea the mpa and np
i mean yeah nbpa player um his
son was ah scoring ah
yeah slam dunk
jesus christ i was just looking scott
he was scoring a slam dunk and
he and then the dad who's in
the nba yeah because like he's celebrating
on the court and then everyone's like
there's like tweets that are split between
like should he be on the court
and like i wish mine was like
that like it's like people were like
ron j
james wright yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes he should be on the court
he's fucking loop right yeah some people
were like oh my god on the
court like that can be kicked off
swiftly it's like shut up i hate
everyone you're not a famous basketball player
yeah like everyone there wants to watch
him react yeah like come on i
think when i watch a
show like so you think you can
dance where the the contestants are there
like in the auditions like the parents
are there in the audience and everything
the parents are crying watch children dance
at some point i always think what
would it be like to have supportive
parents
right yeah where from you what if
they were here crying during this episode
dude on the bachelor oh if only
they had lived to hear three of
the things that a greatest regret of
your life being pushed over the top
it wouldn't be like paul we get
it now we understand that those three
boys were you get it
on the bachelor um after the final
rose they had the parents of one
of the the contestants was there and
he they were sobbing there were sobbing
and like out of out of pride
and were even kicked off and he
was kicked out and and they mentioned
how they had xanax each had sex
four times in a windmill and they're
like
and they're like laughing creatures and like
his dad's puff numbers trust and i
was like this is dad are you
proud of your sons did working peanut
he's twenty five eighty five i would
be very proud of i had a
son who's such a cockpit on television
as i have six and a windmill
multiple times when i feel it's my
regret about being childfree by choice yeah
but that was just usually i have
a special jane who fights a lot
i just wish
i just know how many times our
coach had sex and i can't even
imagine my parents sobbing and anything my
parents i think would be really embarrassed
if i was on the bachelor my
parents have cried at things i've done
though out of palm shirt because your
burns are great they're so nice i've
like
so at my wedding i don't even
know well i wasn't checking them out
if they were crying but i will
say that that my dad right before
like was sorted trying to needle me
a little like huh i've never seen
you so nervous oh huh for somebody
like yeah it's like they loved the
station i was like no i'm not
yeah it's like you
yeah i'm semi nervous about you know
being in front of a big crowd
of people which you know i have
stage fright but but i'm a grown
man dad yeah i know i'm thirty
whatever
and she's
twelve and he's pretty nervous i'm basically
her dad by the way can i
say something yeah sure there are people
out there who truly think that because
of this show that cool up was
under age when we started dating we
just put into red is not true
it is not true guys not jerry
seinfeld also would not be
laughing if that were the case i
don't think what they'd say about francis
scott he married someone who is under
age then we've only started it i
mean yeah started being so much about
she was still in minnesota when she
turned eighteen that's why you couldn't get
her you got the receipts i've got
the receipts and here they are i've
got the receipts
and the hero they are ah
ah my cbs coupon the other day
was your cbs coupon vs coupon okay
you took risky on the seaview i
mean receipt yeah okay yeah i'm not
talking well today well here it's by
the way it's very early early library
code word so early lauren has
lauren lauren's needed it to be very
very needed to know why i needed
it to be said it could be
late i said it could be no
i didn't know i didn't need it
i just i just said i got
it i did not mean to do
it between one and four that was
all well neither could you should this
be no i could
they're salaries free until eight o'clock tonight
i could've done it it was just
a yeah we said well nobody would
go let's do it at ten guys
this should be a spin-off podcast where
we just do scheduling yes i like
dick pete people love the when i
tell you i'm very tired right now
i'm not exaggerating why are you so
tired i was watching the bachelor all
night
ease up all that walk to the
bank and yeah instagram i was i
know my instagram has become like a
serious tour but that was the most
people like it i know people like
family here to ask to do i
really felt i'm not doing bachelor in
paradise yeah okay i'm not gonna commit
to that because it's every monday and
tuesday i can't do that i can't
do that okay
i had to able to watch that
whenever i feel like i can't feel
like there's a time yeah ticking clock
yes but my instagram story was so
long last night that it started deleting
the first ones
them on my highlights but i was
like loop around and my dashes were
so small that i was humiliated yeah
but i need everyone to watch them
i've i've i finally tried to watch
all the way through of one of
your story was about time i tried
to watch they wouldn't even try
the dashes were like periods yeah yeah
and i was like woman made it
well you couldn't get through it because
why it was just so much i
watched a lot of it hitler let
me tell you something it started off
being like really sporadic throughout the episode
and yeah like here's a funny thing
yes then people start going i only
watch the show through you this is
like how i know what's happening on
the show then i'm like well i
don't watch
to leave out anything really crucial so
then i'll do like stories that are
kind of like okay just you know
like this is kind of what's happening
right now and now it's turning into
me like recapping yes live recap live
recap shortening episode by like a dot
and i one die talk over it
and just say whatever i feel yeah
but people i don't think anyone said
i only watch the show through you
could you include
good morning
like yeah i really need to get
along importance oh i know they don't
care about that it's so it's so
hard because i want to do a
service to the world and sure it's
the only thing you can think all
you do that's dealer charity work yeah
i didn't think of that you didn't
think of sharing work now think of
it didn't come up anyway anyway that's
that any
are we going anyway gang so we're
all tired are you tired i got
a good amount of sleep i watched
the bachelor i was i yeah i
was just like you guys are real
late night textures by the way i'm
always asleep anytime you guys are texting
after say ten o'clock sort of dan
yeah i go to bed around town
and and i always
wake up and there's like seven texts
between the two of you and i
always think well what friends i have
well no it's just i wish i
was as funny as them i missed
it i can't chime in now it's
been nine hours that doesn't stop me
bro yeah i try my web i
guess i when i get the text
it's brand new to me and i
chime in ho
my god i saw the funniest meme
ah okay i keep talking about it
and i maybe i can play football
every habits have it's a sound i've
just scrolled through my thousands luckily the
sound mean yeah i want to plug
in your ego plug it in and
plug eighty if you call it a
me it was worth yeah do you
know where that comes from that glade
plugin song no
oh is it a paradise it's a
parody of a song called rub it
in rub it in it is by
billy crash craddock and i remember seeing
a commercial like one of those like
k tell kind of commercials for his
album just attacked and it was a
greatest ever just physically assaulted lord and
fell on me quote unquote
farnham was my kid
was an open secret in the engineering
world that kevin you just followed baby
just kevin falling towards you like this
way
hands out like finger flexing knee wait
guys finishing a story about chronic billy
crash craddock and it was his greatest
hits compilation i've never heard of this
guy but he had a song called
raw beauty and raw beauty and it's
like a country do right then he
had a follow-up song to that called
you you wrote you read all
wrong wow that's sick you so the
first time didn't work and i was
heated admonishing or is he giving tips
on how to rub it in like
he's just a bad boss like first
he's ordering you to rub it in
right and then he's not satisfied with
the rubbing in quality at this point
why aren't they just coming up with
a y
are they paying this guy so much
money for these commercials just come up
with your own if no one has
ever heard of this song rub it
in rub it in right well why
bother keep in mind yeah i was
a child yeah and this was not
a son for children right but some
say when you are an adult you
put aside childish things yes and then
i learned to love robin robin right
alright what do we have in the
main world going on this is ah
let's check in with lauren's meme corner
i follow this account called which um
let me tell you i would literally
never follow this account because the team
is so bad i think if the
bad juju
jerry the account is called basic white
bitches other doesn't fuck you i guess
i guess i only follow because my
mom kept sending me stuff from basic
white bashes and your mom kept sending
you stuff and it was private so
i couldn't see so i was like
let me i'll just start falling so
i can see all these games she's
sending me right and this one that
came up is hilarious
off at the pass it says i
am going to bed early tonight and
then it says me at one thirty
a m the weeki
yeah
ah ha
yeah i love this
okay
yes alright well it's i want that
song yes oh i get it what's
it from how do we record it
i don't know but if you toy
around every episode will be
joel comiskey donkey galileo's born nicole and
camp oh oh jaane kahan okay
hey blade again yeah we'll see
ooh
yeah
oh
on the program
ooh and chicken on the gas
ah i love this idea of i'm
going to bed earlier today than it
was three am you're just you're doing
this
da hey goldie
oh
i would say that is that is
i think my favorite type of internet
meme the one where it's like i'm
gonna do something and then you take
a video thanks something you know me
when this happened yeah whatever i really
it's the one of the few that
i really enjoy their kamala harris waving
wow i've seen a cover there's one
show
she's waving really really slowly at someone
far away or something yeah i've seen
and it's like my pulse when my
semen
or released
future prize or six that's the first
one i can say but there was
one before it the one i remember
i think might have been lewis foretell
was ah me me watching my dinner
guests leave feeling life poisoned each and
every one of them
i love i never think to do
any well i never see any videos
like that either i you know what
it never occurs to me i only
see them when someone else does yes
to that i really enjoy it yeah
yeah i love it and then the
the dancing like goats the the ones
who are sort of like oh yeah
yeah yeah unison it's like a specific
kind of humor that is happening now
that i wonder um who is making
these because like the accounts finding guys
funny videos who's making them just keep
i remember seeing that goat video just
on its own use of going seeing
it
you know why remember that goes so
wait what is that oh look it
up learn something new it's nancy dot
com alright fine
is that a meme that i
if it rick rolls me i'll kill
you
no it's being worse than that is
yeah it's what it's super old it
is about me is is it's about
opening your asshole yes is it something
about opening your asshole it was an
okay it was an internet shock site
it's front page feature to picture entitled
hello da
a g showing a naked man widely
stretching his anus with both hands
this is fucking
he wildly strictly just goes to both
goats dot cx so-to-speak goat sex right
but it was but why nothing could
change so much the way the only
reason getting his anus with both hands
the only reason my ex and i
want good sex the only reason i
know about it is because you love
that and that makes you you i
just use a reference to
it is something which i can't talk
about but but a thing going oh
so i was like what is it
again because i remembered i remembered it
from scott's writing for the mark twain
prize
i remember like twenty years ago when
i was about goods good sita sciac
sets you at the mark twain right
remember anything good yes ask say make
him do it himself never go outside
six does he you thought it was
a website but it was a man
widely spreading the anus with booth using
any of us will ever get like
the presidential medal of ohio
not me you might well they have
this all has to be deleted
all of what we were just talking
about like to be debris i guess
sir
ah i want a chance but didn't
eddie murphy when it yeah i sucked
he wants like some prize like that
yeah congressional medal of honor yeah i
don't just add just a serious i
mean i want it but i mean
like the idea of me getting that
seems impossible i tell you you know
you'll never get it how do you
get a congressional medal of honor just
to be like rosa parks or something
yeah what does that emerge where they
go even with no i'm kidding you
know like what is it called the
presidential it's not the middle of physical
fitness award do you think you'll ever
win i could do one pull-up huh
you'd win the award for least amount
of pull-ups a man can do
i mean one yeah but no we're
a personnel other people could do less
than you
certainly mean jimmy you deserve everyone else
while still doing pull-ups right right right
right right yeah did you yeah did
you have to do those are was
gone by the time oh how many
did you use that this stretch know
these people to hang forever that was
like so you had the option of
either doing somebody pull ups as you
could or you could hang for as
long as you kill him
gonna pick pull-ups boys shows offs
well doing pull-ups was like better but
i would hang i could hang forever
yeah sure i could just i was
just hanging for like so long and
then at a certain point they're like
alright stop a timing you and then
it's like yeah look i get off
with something else i'd love to see
you hanging from a tree oh my
god haha that's dread monster don't get
you kicked off twitter i know that's
why i said it here he's not
going to kick us off to show
my dark monster yeah um caverns are
at jack and he's not changing what
you're like jack kick him off the
show yeah come on suspend his account
his check i beg of you delete
your account delete your account elite you're
a kiln can we all leader account
at the same time yeah that would
be fun i gotta say i am
i'm too much on twitter too much
time on your butt i see
still like it
come back till i've your back you
know it's still frustrating sometimes still frustrating
sometimes so frustrating and such it's just
too frustrating times so fussy to tell
but ice overall you're exasperated know i
just like thinking about the listener and
how like we just devolve so quickly
i'm happy about it i'm not exactly
happy thinking about them on their frustration
a lawrence center thing by the way
oh good on our honor phones good
um yeah i think it is good
well i just feel like
oh okay cool game now ooh cool
nah he'll go back i will be
chapel
oh wow is this from the next
star wars movie gone on a ram
na jana caught on camera
is it corn damn that's cool i'm
hearing corn chicken chicken corn that it
was corn canned corn canned corn can
makes more sense when wow that but
lizzy my new white but he is
not trying to make sense is he
i don't know what if he is
desperately trying to make when you first
saw
and a big coat you think oh
my everything's different now
i'm trying to decide whether i saw
rich hall parody it before i saw
the actual thing problem price is really
not i saw the movie in the
theater or did i stop making sense
in hermosa beach and what are you
beat me
were you trying to get there i
sort of like oh yeah yeah it's
out of philadelphia the theatre of the
living arts wow which was lauren you're
being condescending know i like the name
of the arts are alive it was
a movie theater it was a it
was an art house movie theater now
it is a performance venue but it
was an art house movie theater at
the time
wasn't like going to the art house
movie theater so cool when you were
young abs yes like it was like
wow i'm seeing a movie that a
lot of people don't even know even
as a thing we've done in san
luis obispo very smart yeah san louis
obispo when i was in college and
it was like we would just go
there everywhere i mean that was that
was when our you know independent films
too were like huge time
it was like you know what i
what i find very comforting about those
movie theaters is that they all have
the exact they show the exact same
movies right so like you'll always see
a double feature of a hard day's
night with the monkeys head like that's
always there as your tear raised her
head yeah with head why was it
oh why did the eraser movie
and head why did the beatles make
they made a couple of movies why
do they do that though they do
that because people like debido well guess
because people don't get to see them
that much without the internet yeah and
so it'd be like a way to
get own them the movies are actually
pretty funny and fun they have like
lines and stuff i kind of always
being more like music video there no
silly i
could i get a lot of em
i can't tell whether they're sort of
improving but i know they're scripted because
they're too funny yeah you know what
i mean but they're they deliver i'm
really well yeah they're very good they're
very charming and surprising because these nice
break maybe someday horizon is good help
is not as good but it's still
fun like they were ahead of their
time with like the the there's like
a fight scene that
has like comic books down effects before
batman did it right um and then
yellow submarine which is an animated movie
right weird and had is not that
great in my opinion no head is
very experimental it's very of it's two-tier
to watch arnold schwarzenegger's eraser and head
it would be just like watching her
raise her head
my aunt had a video that she
took at um
adobo beatles concert like a home movie
and it's really yeah like back of
the day yeah and she watched it
so many times and burned whoa no
yeah isn't that sad so she took
like a super yeah movie and where
did she see them in chicago sometime
and yeah would have been chicago or
indiana but what made everybody put there
the video recorders in a bag although
super yeah i know like remember those
lockbox oh rerun la rerunning the doobie
brothers you don't understand what we're talking
about um and will we relaxed people
to ever talk about it do you
already know from that sitcom in the
eighties yes i know my know messing
up to things
re-run what's that one from what's happened
dynamite yeah dynamite is is good times
what's rerun what's happening i'm gonna let's
rewrite he was saying computer what's really
keep saying it and you keep going
to see other picture of him oh
right doors you do he's adorable fred
berry fred berry rp alright oh yeah
he was
alright albert no that's cartoon
our bill cosby
one of the others
ah
like i mean me was on the
bad bone it truly looks like oh
my that doesn't have the fat albert
theme um give me hey what's what
wow beam wu doing or saying so
use having to use this yeah
a man and man ma
miranda
mazda raceway laguna we get a crush
on d i know this is raised
by tv rego is he from that
no is he from that no superman
oh okay and i'm like wrong on
everything okay so rerun dean dean dandy
rerun snuck and yeah he was going
to a doobie brothers concert i don't
feel like i really am familiar
with this shoes he was like coached
by he was gonna go i think
he already hits and he was approached
by a guy like hey while you're
there could you tape recorded but yeah
i'm a secret concert taper yeah and
so he was just an old-fashioned with
an old-fashioned reel to reel i think
that was a real reason it was
okay it was yeah but it was
one of those boxy shape
because people had their homes so we
had to wear a trenchcoat over it
but he he loved the the doobie
brothers doobie brothers were so good that
he had to do the rerun dance
which if you'll remember it was sort
of like this i see listener image
of it and then the tape recorder
fell out and spilled out right in
front of the doobie brothers yes and
then all went
to the edge by the way they're
playing a tiny tiny venue right and
i guess it was their old high
school or some oh okay yeah i
don't know if we're supposed to think
they were all literal brothers
they were a family that went to
this so funny but they all moved
to the edge of the stage all
pointing at the border on the ground
didn't they come by wherever they used
to hang out the next day to
talk to re-run about why that's wrong
yeah yeah yeah it was a rerun
why was his name re-run it was
that before they had reruns of tv
shows
they didn't have the technology to re-run
television shows until we're eighty nine a
class that i runs i think it's
a serious question okay let's look at
temperature we're all we're all very upset
it's called what i think you if
if memory serves he was in some
kind of dance crew and that was
like his dance name and then it
just carried over into the shot was
it based on the word rerun from
television shows being re yeah people did
not invent the word rerun no i
want i wondered if it meant something
out i understand what you were wondering
i
do not know if it meant something
else to him maybe it meant somebody
else but reruns have been around since
dammit like you'd be a kid and
go on to re-write yes since the
fifteenth probably since you were little
since cool off because nothing better when
they first started to star in the
sky
the reruns that took balls like the
first time that the first time that
ever have is like you know what
we don't even know what we're gonna
show you an old one and they
paid off they didn't get any residual
that's right yeah do you know the
story of the wellingtons know they i
knew you didn't were they brothers they
were no
but they did go to the same
ones okay great they were the ones
who sang the theme song from gilligan's
island and they're the only people other
than the producers who made got caught
in on the money yes well publishing
rights and so all the cast who
are on that show that was rerun
countless billions of times like i've got
enough book
why do i so autograph recession of
the welling garland hotel it's of our
rich beyond rich which is crisis so
i'd love to be one of them
willing to meet to take me to
wellington sasha wellington's if you're enjoying the
show hashtag well am i understand wellington's
don't say it
hashtag fun times hashtag riera hashtag fun
times hatch hashtag time funds out buns
out funds out bugs
we are the good time same because
i was disappointing groups i have no
memories about what's happening so i want
good time good time seems great let's
hear that good times v
you need to need a baby
a
thank god so not getting served keeping
our head above law
make it over when u k
oh good
easy credit rip
scrubs never seen an episode of this
okay listen
what
again in the
hanging in the toilet
the time i said hanging in the
shoreline shoreline i think i don't know
what that means dave chappelle posit that
it was hanging in a chow line
hanging in the chow chow wine maybe
oh yeah that makes sense
doesn't you know the challenge or airline
whoa joanne ah i'm gonna look it
up alright well you gotta blow you
look at luke luke it you lose
it huh oh wrong we have today
greg will be rabbit
and we're back we are there we
missed you along mister show march we
go to a cold dark void when
the break happens when you can't hear
us we're floating in space with fun
baptized babies it's terrifying i'm getting huge
i'll do it i'm still scared
but then we get to talk over
here then we get to talk over
here we got talk oh yeah another
way
the chow line can did you look
it up
hanging in and giant chevron into up
and said it was hanging in and
jiving um dr what's something that you
guys are learning right now oh
i'm going wheels because you haven't learned
anything
i don't think so what am i
in the process of learning or when
something you've learned or what's something you
want to learn i will say i
would like to go back to school
to do what i thought oh man
really grabby dangerfield you want because you
didn't finish can i finish please can
communicate with you in the grip sign
up of ca
and you know i've college i've looked
into like night classes and stuff i
don't know alright get your degree no
i don't care about that i would
just like this i would like to
know more about it
about subjects i failed in high school
and college not me bro wow like
why i didn't need the men i
don't need them now history and feeling
you have big gaps in your knowledge
yeah i've a big gap
and you're gonna go daddy
oh i did a show in philadelphia
on my old history whereas that i
don't even know my history teacher came
to the shows we did super oh
really wow that's nice and we did
a meet and greet afterwards and then
he he was in the line i
didn't know and then i looked up
and there he was you recognized him
took me a second but i got
got him a new york minute it
yeah you know what you're right on
this one scott
that's mineral second um is that true
yeah that's that's what that ah ha
and he told me he emailed me
and said he he watched both shows
ah i was i was very touched
and he said um he emailed me
and said that i i clearly had
retained a lot from ah
history class he could tell from stop
trying to take oh history teacher pulse
funny oh i told you i should
know because of what you said in
that one semester
new york minute is a second because
as it was explained to me a
it's in the turnover in the time
that it would take in other places
than new york to like honk at
someone because like a light is green
like it would take you a minute
to be like excuse me sir in
new york it's it's like a spy
that second so that's why a new
york minute is is like instantaneous okay
now who explained this you don henley
yes
it's all in the lyrics there
he explained
that's what this song it is other
places it was mad but in new
york and the second in a new
york minute
ooh what's something you're learning big brain
um
i'm sorry talk right now and honestly
i everyone must know that i have
a phlegm problem when i am on
podcast it's not it misses early today
but i will say it happens to
me like when i'm talking on podcasts
more than when i'm talking in real
life i don't know what it is
and i if anyone out there is
able to i've been to the e
n t and they
i have no issues what your necklaces
and my necklace is an l and
then um
an alien an l x and an
aloe you can't have them together i
feel like i'm from other space
um right now i'm trying to pick
up again the ukulele because i bought
it when i was in london oh
like a real kay mccutcheon i know
why i bought when i was in
london because my friend when we were
there was buying one and i was
like i want to do it it's
the best place to get them well
yeah it was just yeah it was
it's obviously not but it was just
ah
i was here you know wanting to
be part of the group so i
got one like a group of two
ah well she's buying one for her
and her sister and so then i
always i wonder you one of the
three that had them yes we're all
working on holmes and watson together yes
and so i was like well i'm
alone in my apartment a lot that
will be good for me and this
is the person that played the queen
you know this is will ferrell's assistant
and yeah jillson oh yeah joe he
only hires people whose names are wrong
with this and i was like i
was working on it for a little
bit when i was there but i
fell off pretty quickly and then it's
been now two years or something and
i was like you know i want
to try to gank so i have
also mike got me a guitar that
i've never played
i'm like feel bad about that so
i have to bus my guitar more
because gulag got me a really nice
one and then for a while it
was like an every day yeah practice
her well she hasn't given me any
fucking guitars i honestly we like talked
about snow and it's like oh coops
give me several guitars but it's like
if someone a pet because you're like
there's guilt if
you don't do it right early it's
like let me ask you this why
did he give you the guitars i've
been saying i want to learn how
to play oh okay but i told
you this is on you when i
told him now almost three years later
how many chords you know none okay
and i told him i teach you
i'll do i want to turn okay
i told your hand smith five hundred
and hour
he should have given me never got
that i'm really status medic that guy
who had that sign up that dan
smith will teach you guitar
um but i felt like i told
him he should have given me lessons
with the guitar like so yeah how
are you supposed to fuck you mike
how are you supposed to figure it
out yourself that's the that's the part
where i get seven i'm like well
i don't feel like trying to figure
that out and then year at least
book that yeah or something where like
they're like my strings
as different colors is something to make
it easier we went on can watch
it online he can we're watching online
and like we're trying to ah he
was you know he knows more than
i do but i was trying to
learn but it's also really painful so
that i might you go really easy
so i went back to that and
i'm learning how to play my girl
have you ever heard the eddie vedder
ukulele album no
no it's great it's real given her
that he's nodding in the booth yeah
yeah pick it up because it's got
it here also it does exist it
kind of is probably the wrong outfit
yeah can i tell you which one
ah this is the new rick rule
ah oh okay
oh go go go get go
oh god
ah god oh wow oh wow
about that ball bead oh yeah i
have to know let me the guy
is just that's just nonsense right he's
an actual language i know i think
he's just making like fun noise okay
alright i was afraid he just going
i've could always join and then it
was like my being racist no i
think he's literally just singing uh
say a little diddy you're gonna mccord
but it gets serious when he gets
to the courts and serious here are
some of the yeah i also decide
culture the corner of the courtyard
we wherever you go i'll never be
this good
ah yes
i love this i love his voice
i'd rather this
without you
oh it's okay it's beautiful oh my
god i gotta download that now i
was just in speaking of learning things
i was just in awe goatee dot
com and download for free
no results for any vetter on yeah
ukulele songs
as well as my spy eddie vedder
wrong probably are you spelling you're going
to leave on my spotify but oh
wait i'm on some playlist oh wow
blue blea people who beat up by
just ah film something i did a
guest spot on a tv show i
can't wait the required me to come
out cheney told me because i saw
her to play oh yes that's right
sorry fiona's play yes um i had
to do a ah in the scripts
that i had to do a little
soft shoe oh cool which i you
can do no i can't i only
know i know anytime anyone anyone can
imitate a soft soft shoe by just
dad like i mean like what i
did yeah that's what i did but
it may but i promised myself you
should say
uncle somebody's gonna nurse i had to
do that too oh you did oh
yes but because they didn't want to
mark up the table yeah ah they
used like it was like a sort
of serial that looked like sand yeah
yeah but it was also one thousand
times more slippery than saying oh my
god i almost broke my fucking nose
oh that would be the worst and
wait because the shoes were br
brand new shoes so they were very
slippery on the table to begin with
that's already bad they should be criss
crossing those mo folks on the bottom
they tried that it didn't make any
difference so you're saying borrow somebody else
to borrow a background guy's shoes so
it's a show with tables is it
fresh off the boat i can't i
can't okay i mean you're saying one
it will learn how to dance you've
been wanting to learn how to
to do that yeah want to learn
how to tap dance you should have
like well you know i should yeah
i'm watching t show is good but
let me say one's wants to teach
us oh that's really nice feeling this
is my feeling but i'm mad that
i haven't done it you know and
that's how i feel i want to
take seeing lessons which i'm signing up
for one thing i want to do
that to wait the la la la
la oh teach me
just play them back
and i'm but i've been wanting to
do it for like five years talking
about it probably for five years so
just do it i know but i'm
saying what the fuck are you doing
it five years ago i yeah i
know somebody that i can recommend to
you okay i have a i would
like the recommendation i will give you
the recommendation i just feel but it's
also it's like thing that i made
it i know she wants but
same thing about piano with me was
twenty years ago i want yes but
this woman there's like this quote that
i always butcher and just make up
my own version of which is that
this like ninety year old woman basically
said like she started learning violin when
she was sixty now she's playing for
thirty years and it's like yes you
start now yes because you and i
start to your hundred what do you
want you want to adjust the age
is every time i do i've heard
you mentioned this before yeah he was
she was sixty seven thirty yeah because
you only just started and she's like
she's twenty yeah and that's actually the
stories that she's also up in the
world could you only fit in one
like guitar ukulele or i'm honestly doing
my plan is to do all three
i want to do oh i'm trying
to
kill them all god sort of out
yeah i feel like they will compliment
each other as well yeah it'll be
helpful like like you sing better than
i can sort of thing so paul
what are you going to do are
you going to do tap lessons i
wanna do tap lessons i also want
to do voice lessons because i feel
like i can sing but i would
like to have better control of my
instrument yeah and i also like to
to learn piano just because i'd like
to learn
i want to learn piano to be
able to say i want wanna be
able to know what a key is
you don't want me yeah i was
i was at the recording of the
score for the ferns movie the other
day
and they were like at at one
point they needed us all to snap
during one of the songs right so
there and and then the percussionist is
like so you guys know i mean
you guys can read music right like
like we're all just assholes who are
like sitting there that they're like hey
anyone in the booth come on and
he's like so you read music right
you can ah so after like
three bars you come in on the
fight and we're like ah stress i
like sorta new so i could like
you could pass i could like you
know nod to the other people when
there but um i would like to
like be able to like totally read
music yeah i feel like something about
piano that i've been thinking lately it's
like when i was growing up it
felt really impossible
yet now i feel like i got
some long arms i can focus on
this i could care enough like i
feel that maybe it's better we both
have beautiful fingers oh we do i
think that we it's ashame they're being
wasted they're being wasted so will you
promise not you due to what your
question i promise long oh don't
you promise to do at least one
of them by the men but like
sign up sign up for lessons yeah
by by the end of the year
yes and then paul will you do
so by the end of the year
say well i'm not going to do
anything yes yeah danno do piano time
today upa were in history
it's a history class two piano who
gives a shit about history you don't
care i have all my history from
school but history was the one yeah
oh my oh and you obviously you'd
be using your heart it so i
think you should do history yeah but
i've been thinking about piano to what
i'll do to a school or which
like go online go to go to
a history of piano class
it's to kill him just histories of
actual piano yes it just shows stupid
pianos one fell in a silent movie
maybe i'll do one thing you have
made one wow you guys make something
maybe a new one thing who also
there's the tap thing christine woods wants
to teach alright i don't have any
contact info for her she did show
her the other night and shin and
she was like the other just the
other day and i saw her i
didn't know what to say
um and she was like oh i'll
teach you and so anyway well now
this was a while ago that she
said this or did you say okay
a few months ago okay but then
i heard i heard my name when
when someone says that you do you
think that they really mean it yeah
she sent me a text the next
day about it with like a gif
of someone tapping saying this will be
you well it isn't please
close you can see yourself in that
gif alright we present we have to
decorate
mo alright we're back we're back janna
the car we're back the clock and
chicken is in the corn my mom
and oma it's in the coin can
go upi blah blah is that gonna
be in the new star wars do
you think that's that's the new candido
so yeah lin manuel
written
ah alright we get it look everyone
knows this is what happens at this
part of the show and it's this
isn't everyone knows this and why will
it be different for this episode pretending
that you don't know the stuff trying
to think you're so much smarter than
us here's it makes me sick to
my stomach it makes me physically ill
you are rude thoughtless little pigs
i'm nauseated i am now saturated with
time for a three cheer it's time
for a three cheer a three-tier means
it's a feature that's played on threesome
yeah what is a feature the teachers
gave everyone hey i getting angry get
to the root what does the game
all smash
and we have this one submitted by
robert yoon at robert yoon and his
suggestion is play it again just june
you know what's got when you're right
you're right and this time at this
time i am right okay his suggestion
is play it again three
a film critics that would be us
review and debate unlikely and ill advised
movie sequels hey movies sake whoa such
as citizens came to see this game
he's making he's having sounds like the
title yes apollo third whoppers to that
one not paulo's thirteen thirteen
please choose another west side story gone
with the wind to philadelphia to hamlet
to two because there was a movie
cure of course that was funny ferris
bueller's second day off kazaa blank or
like even more blanka than the best
okay okay ra ride let us do
it robert
okay why pick all the good ones
yeah well before we
so how do we do to chevron
give us a movie and then we
talk about it pop music i guess
we i guess so yes maybe sheva
will suggest a movie that does not
have a sql okay we will come
up with the title and then we
will talk about it as usually are
about
we could talk about it as if
why would i say it again we
will discuss it as if we are
three movie critiques okay very good chef
in venice with a classic movie
pulp fiction pulp fiction pulp fiction hi
everyone we're here on three movie critics
discuss unlikely sequel but let's start again
why is it okay excuse me
well this you always do this hey
let's start a good yeah well i
feel like there's a lot of people
that are tuning in right after we
intro the show and they tuning in
right after i don't know the show
why do you care about the intro
so man can i introduce show because
i want people to hear it yes
but they're doing it after we've intro
welcome to the show where we review
few movies that are sick sequels yes
we are three men you're not gonna
ask her to start over
can we start over in easter because
he said we are three men
if you call me shoe one more
time i will kick your teeth into
your anus weight then you will use
both hands spread and ben goatee dot
sex
everyone will see you smile but you
are a man man so why did
you get upset with him saying hey
move said she to me so you're
upset at him for saying three minutes
know and are fraying listen to him
now oh okay liz oh no no
internet dinosaur i want to quit the
show doesn't know robbie i want
shame we lowe robbie never quit robbie
never quit never never never quit i'll
be robbie never quit and that's an
interesting thing because it brings us to
the movie we're talking about yes which
is a sequel and unlikely sequel to
pulp fiction yeah pub fact pulp fact
now let why did tarantino do this
this why did he surrender this fantastic
property that shouldn't have just as great
ib this great wonderful april practically the
first thing i wrote down was this
is great i p
that's and wait that's still i'm looking
at your pad that's the last thing
you wrote down yes that one at
the edinburgh this was great i pee
now now here's like so you held
it in the entire times yeah robbie
you usually go to the bathroom twenty
times during a movie well i'm no
longer interested in pissing on you
fellows we agree we will discuss this
until we all got home
hell we also together we have three
separate entrances we all went to the
same high school step into one two
a one to one bed but that's
all we have is a bed it's
three doors open up into one bedroom
room we want a big california king
we all open the doors at the
same time we were we tried to
time yes sometimes we can't do it
to an open open and then we'd
show
zonta lay on the bed because it's
a california thing it's slightly longer that's
right the king so we sleep like
some sausages on the grill and we
roll back and forth back and forth
back and forth all night
so
this movie pulp fan club fact i
loved ah you love it robbie you're
out of your mind this movie was
a shambling mess well i'm i'm i'm
gonna disagree with you there okay good
good i'm getting forefingers here's what we
do rags at the end i'm just
looking
you know where i'm gonna go all
right well unless you can sway me
let me see if i get to
join the movie picks up where the
original film left off with john travolta
and samuel l jackson leaving the diner
then it continues where the original movie
flashed back to he goes to the
bathroom it's essentially yet
shot just the same movie as pulp
fiction but told in a different style
told yeah total out of order in
a different way yes now it's in
order yeah now it's just in oh
i don't have all the scenes you've
never seen full choppy waves you think
it was such great i be i
wanted it to be right and i
wanted to fit in and i and
p
people you don't have to do that
ravi who i do i do because
whenever i whenever i'm wrong and i
don't fit in you're very very mean
i power cold and calculating with your
with your cruel blurs my robbie i
agree blobby you have to be nicer
robbie it's look my father or my
father look
so what if i'm your father look
you are my father look
who doesn't know her father's okay blobby
law dad was your what was your
low point in those fool my low
point was when tim roth he's back
and better than better than ever low
yes
that was my low point oh tim
roth feedback big hit low points
better than ever low point big hit
me big part was highlight pretty lady
go bye-bye oh pretty late to go
big down touchdown oh here's what upset
me the most okay me know like
big absence lady feet
no lady was oh lady i used
to use time want no lady feed
lie is at this time no lady
philosophy you want on a dashboard aw
levied on a dashboard oh wow
so you want your foot fetish to
be met i get used to lady
feet in movie when no lady fuckin
movie confusing cadets
he confused adding me opinion different in
that um me want to see most
definitely all full feet nude all feet
nude big big big hit big when
happens all feet nude what happens big
big hit when our feet in shoes
and clothes say
taylor blow your nose
shoot
now we all know that socks are
referred to a shoe clothes shoe clothes
of course they're like shoe underwear yeah
shoes shoes shoes shoes new underwear you
wear your shoes underwear underwear your free
foot and free food and in the
current camp law she's a girl
good
loves her shoe collection
would you watch this show
are you fucking kidding me it's a
manic episode i would i would absolutely
watch this shit do if there was
three campsites so good show like this
or it's just random gibberish
it starts out somewhat weird that's basically
every episode by the way yeah i
was trying another movie okay shelvin it's
a wonderful life oh it's a wonderful
life hi everyone we're back and we're
talking about it's a different wonderful can
we let's okay let's do the intro
again why i didn't
after that the people that just it
doesn't remember waits for the people in
julia tuning in
yeah because i just added to this
show as a new house yes yes
now be we know snobby is it
possible that i possibly could do the
intro what do you think i guess
so i i'm your dad and i
say yes are you her dad though
yes because your half sister
i'm so glad we reconnected from twenty-three
me too and i'm gonna give you
all my money huh bobby and your
baseball be sucking eg bloody luck and
a good second boy is teaming up
against me all i've ever been supportive
to this family trying to build character
i guess you're right it's turning me
in
to a man finally um welcome to
the show the show where we review
the movie that is the sequel to
a popular film but the sequel is
a strange or ill advice sql now
we have to wait until these movies
are made so sometimes it's a long
way not on every week sometimes it's
year yeah go but harry had too
many
at once yes you have a very
specific contract big backlogs working out by
the way me be helu big bag
la go boo boo
da da da da da da yeah
i'm doing it down again
i'm here to do to do to
sequel to the film and yeah
so this is it's a different wonderful
life and it's about tanzania yeah it's
about jimmy stewart being reincarnated after he
dies like dad didn't you watch it
can i confess something please i fell
asleep
before i fell asleep the very beginning
i woke up at the various aw
those are the two best scenes though
tell us about him well at the
very beginning ah right as it picks
up right where the original film left
off sure everyone's happy there the christmas
tree ah jimmy stewart suffers a massive
heart attack and collapses right data chandelier
falls on his head
yeah well only his head yeah right
after he has he false diseases says
my heart and then crash yes and
then the the um everyone manages to
get out of the way up to
run knob on the banister flies off
and just hits him in the head
faster yeah he's hands is it becomes
a bloody pulp and then i just
fell asleep and so that was just
the first few minutes dad so
so a did get a lot crazy
clumsy yeah okay so
jimmy stewart goes up he talks to
clarence clarence is like it's weird that
you didn't wear they didn't clay yeah
i should call you daddy you see
it just for what i know of
you it seems like you would say
daddy before so is that because i'm
a blonde bombshell in a pink mini
dress you obviously
so huh exactly right well we have
related yeah a perfect spray tan and
teeth are dazzling white
ah you were just showing that too
is that smile proofs
so
jimmy stewart goes up to clarence clarence
says oh hey clarence isn't it yeah
and he says oh that was so
terrible what happened i guess you didn't
have a wonderful life because it was
cut so short and you want to
go back this is clarence thomas is
clarence clarence sends him back into his
dead body no not into oh okay
he's never johnny forgive me he's a
baby that
was born there in medford falls then
so is it like boyhood where we
watch and we watch him grow up
he's approximately five years younger than zuzu
he starts a romance with zuzu
he and then it's just like hardcore
you like it but you like it
yeah
you did i loved it yeah how
did you feel snobby i found a
kind of him better and it's not
just because my name is snobby
although that is a fun coincidence it
is fun that i tend to think
low of things of low it is
kinda fun that i didn't think low
low of phase no why do you
care i didn't think a low things
so how many fingers do you give
it to up the butt
alright that's our show bike
i didn't get to get my finger
ah show their sorry we have to
end it it's part of a weird
contract okay bye
good too good shows to do good
shows alright but we have to wrap
two minutes later i was i wasn't
getting the news i thought it was
that this is the end of our
oh i felt literally abrupt to end
our episode that way but i was
like okay i was gonna say um
this was weird
yeah but that's somebody else but if
sometimes show was wired yeah but i'm
not saying it's bad no i'm not
saying it's bad honestly when we were
doing our own show don't you hear
honestly think that they knew for ten
years yes yeah like i said we've
been talking about doing ours and our
yes and that's why i'm revving okay
we have to go all right
right we'll see you next time we
love we love you hi bye
a