wow
three
oh but but three domes three dumb
and that's how we originally spelled it
isn't it we any thought about to
think about it be dumb but don't
say if you do your job yeah
nobody at the welcome to three double
ah we all have colds we owe
are still sick
we have a little bit of the
study those this very specific show everyone
has the cold getting so big
thanks grandma i don't want to come
down for thanksgiving over the river to
the woods we got here umm welcome
to the show i'm scott i'm laura
and i'm paul and this is freedom
this show where three people lose your
sock over you so defensive
what do you want to know
that if you have to ask you
can't afford it it's free
um i want to ask a really
pressing question that e please oh you
have brought today shut up a second
before anyone gets upset yes we're going
to resolve the habana viejo today and
this leads me to what i was
going to ask you as you brought
the memes and you brought them in
a disney bag yeah i'm talking all
my briefcase it's a
white shops bag labeled from knee from
the disney store or just labeled disney
for no reason or meaning yeah there's
a third alternative neither of you even
considered okay hold on you are walt
disney oh no frozen no no another
one saps up stop i see a
little bit of a little thing underneath
it oh it's a gift bag
because there's you did a thing behind
you lower and you cannot see but
from my vantage point i see a
little inscription on the bags that says
to paul what you can't see is
that disney says television animation which makes
me think something from a studio you
got and i want it and i
actually i'm so curious what gift you
received to what
it show is for well what you
can't see is i see a little
silhouette oh man scaramucci scaramucci will you
do the fandango well how did they
write that song oh man they were
so drugged drugs i mean you gotta
be because again think about why you
gave one generation to the next but
please tell us um i do voices
for ideal voice for tank
tangled series yeah to tell you just
now ended on four chan tangle but
also i occasionally voiced the the role
of gladstone gander a nemesis of donald
duck on the new ducktales that's huge
or didn't do a dark voice know
i talk like me oh even better
now what didn't they give you even
better
i ford that was for my birthday
i forgave well because right how grateful
are you that you literally got a
present given to it for you this
day corporation i'm gonna shove that fellow
zika bag there was a pair of
brand disney branded earbuds
that i gave to my are they
shaped like mouse ears my lovely wife
jeannie no that's weird i shouldn't be
with my black or something but they
had mickey mouse on the on the
the case i like it on the
case but there must have been something
else in there and perhaps it was
an edible or drinkable thing yeah because
that would not have making me weak
edibles this is what disney came up
with all this shit hey there was
a brick of hash there have i
already mentioned this to you that i
was watching the imagineers show on disney
plus i feel like i've seen some
of that was saying it's all i've
seen you mention that to me ah
disney made up the whole disney thing
but one thing that i always think
is so fat
fascinating when i learned about disney which
i do all the time is it's
a constant quest for now because there's
always so much you can never know
everything like oh i want to know
what what kind of guts it takes
like if you made a theme parking
just say called otterman i know yesterday
it is crazy because as long as
i've been alive
the the name disney is just a
brand yeah yeah i know he's a
guy but it's like yeah one of
the most famous prevents but hard to
reverse that and just go yeah that
was a man's like i've just calling
i open the same locker on laccase
it's just kiss land i think like
no one has done is go down
to laugh because oh hey going on
now
just like the best comedians
though the one of the best guys
who should have been a cast member
should have been okay honestly seems to
have hosts who are good enough to
be in it
only occasionally he's like just fitch's fault
of the child i loved to talk
about some other things that have happened
on the show boyer your yearning are
you going to her no no okay
but i will say it feels like
what the coven restrict i'm guessing it's
covered restrictions they're barely putting people the
host in the sketch there in like
three things
are you complaining because you've been asked
to to and i'm like i wanna
be in more than three if you
rest of house you would be in
every sketch just going
absolutely
nah was still forget can i get
the background with a mascot but i
don't like when they're not in a
lot of stuff i want to see
them have i want to see shaquille
o'neal i have to figure out how
to do a sketch yeah i'm actually
okay with not seeing the host that
much really i see them a lot
if they're a comedian especially number one
the first episode was just george carlin
doing a monologue and then he was
like peace out
that's so so seventy s yeah that's
so seventy s about that people were
smoking grass before leaving they wanna join
on fans too they did one thing
left
why were we oh yes just just
so i don't know what else i
know things rocket sorry oh charles rock
i knew about tamsin power focus pocus
which i just want you know because
yeah i've never seen it the way
he died is quite it's gruesome i
mean wow but hey we're all getting
bombed oh come on it was his
choice but it was a really gruesome
way he
did it yeah i'll leave it up
to google to tell everyone google over
to you is trending even gruesome jeffrey
toobin
as everyone can't get adsense yeah talk
about tube and talk about you by
the way toobin is a song in
the teenage mutant ninja turtles coming out
of their shells tour coming out of
their shells yes exactly it's about like
say inner tubing like down the river
it's about ah going through like a
pipe
line of a of a wave what
is that sir what are the freaking
odds that you are on a zoom
and your dick needs to do something
eighty percent
he's like oh no here it comes
there's no situation you're like i gotta
take my pants off while i'm doing
the zoom even if it's some long
thing maybe maybe this is how you've
been resolved by now but the first
thing i thought of is is that
there was like a sexy anchor who
was on that he was like all
manage to me on track like it
was like this using camera
on and he doesn't you think it
was intentional that's why they that's my
way maybe it's all out in the
open now i just think it's hard
for that to be an excellent i
could see it if he met he
was just looking at something else on
a screen but i always wanted a
how can i tell because he's jerking
off can i but don't do that
in a meeting today the meeting mon
nah don't don't call me lady mon
um here's i have a personal zoom
accident oh we didn't come up with
a term for that zoom skipton no
no he's sick ok missy elliott
really awesome zoo is good to go
it was the
i was doing a show with ah
the great sunday service from vancouver and
people your best friends in canada we
met them that's right yeah that's right
they're wonderful people we had ah a
fun show after the show we would
because we're doing it by zoom because
of the the quarantine because lockdown and
so
after the show after the event was
over we would just hang out like
have a drink and try everyday business
i'd be going to a different zoom
room with that wow because you're lingering
it's a public it's a public forum
and i know that am i wrong
why don't you look of what she's
saying is is if it was a
pup
like zoom that people were like to
watching a show on yes to hang
out after on the same zoom is
risky right the the the the the
live feed was stopped yes but they
could still be in the room or
something over there on the room i
wanted to get through youtube or some
more into watching it through youtube oh
yeah ok lauren saying there maybe there
was a mistake and he kept going
yeah i get it
well i feel you were looking at
her like she was making no sense
yeah you like to be like i
was fully bananas when probably it's where
your story's going speedy
sort of
but it wasn't the public okay well
here's what it wasn't joe you and
me tell you why that we don't
want to know what you're doing it's
the dirty exact same story
yeah me be clear here
so
so i feed was over and we're
hanging out and i had been wearing
um to nick my my show too
from paul i dress like a glass
roman senator
the crown of leaves i love i
think that's a great look if it
was final leaves irl oh i think
it's maybe there they maybe they're bally's
olive olive leaves that they were big
over there ali bey pretty yeah t
olive tree is sweet now you know
it's not i know
it was i'm sorry i apologize if
you got people like olives um yeah
i hate them all
i'm like oh no me neither yeah
i wish i did because people like
i'm gonna drink but i hate them
in food greek food is the one
food that i do not like oh
really yeah because of the olive content
i guess so i just don't like
any of the angry i like feta
but other than that i just don't
i don't like any of the combo's
i don't like the flavor profiles you
don't like combo's
they really choose your hunger away oh
say make it a combo because you
just serve me a plate of combo's
you just throw in i don't like
your nation's cuisine i honestly i never
order pizza i just get pizza combos
and put it on a plate in
the shape of trying this the same
thing it's the same commies combos are
those little nuggets they're a little ch
chips but they're not chips they're little
pretzels without pretzels when they have a
filling inside and they're a little they're
a little little oh i think a
little peg and then there could not
be more machine neck so yeah
true
it's a children's toy that you can
eat it's a peg for your mouth
huh
every night scott isn't madame put to
see isabel can someone make a drop
of it's big for your mouth lord
saying that
okay well what the frick had oh
okay you're really watching your language today
know why
were you with somebody recently where you
had to do that i did a
thing yesterday where i couldn't swear okay
oh the live thing was a ubi
halloween thing yeah i mean they didn't
say they didn't say didn't say you
can't swerve but they said they made
a comment about i think you can
let all your swears afterward
no every dog will be watching this
so yeah my point was just meet
all the guy i was trying not
to because i also knew my nephew
was watching it and so i was
ah they're not gonna swear and become
the coolest aunt ever yeah yeah tom
right so i've been wearing pajamas around
the house
very luxurious it feels wonderful is that
your day-to-day uniform around the house honestly
it was for a bit during the
quarantine it was a fun thing for
awhile yeah it was fun it made
me feel good i've been putting a
hard shoe in months that's what i
wanted today to be kind of like
i'm wearing sneaker yeah but i typically
put on like a slide whenever i
could
i'm wearing sneaker but i have a
wing a lot of sweat pants but
lately i've been finding i need more
support not in my but you know
what i mean but look under it
but it's like i need to feel
like i'm doing something like yeah like
when i'm walking around the house i'm
like yeah i'm proud i'm like i'm
like just wearing my sweat pants and
sweat gentlemen you know and i just
feel like it's unproductive feeling like you
know when i'm cleaning or something still
feels like i should put on regular
it started to make me wonder why
i ever
ever put on regular clothes yeah you
know like i wasted so many decades
of my life by putting you angular
objectively look worse and like yes you
absolutely copy everyone you absolutely do but
i used to i used to watch
like big brother or something and you
know reality shows and go why are
these guys just wearing shorts and tank
tops right our time it's like because
there's nothing to do
do and that's the sort of uniform
of nothing to do it doesn't use
c for me it became it became
like at night my my wife and
i would get in my alive
for it to coming soon to a
stream out already was a report to
hey when the bore out one came
out who's left to food i for
my god i'm excited i think i
think you really like babies that was
great it's been out for a month
by this point okay well i'll i'll
watch it soon and probably know the
answer when i
saw the first borat i laughed harder
than i've ever to lauren me to
chicago my knee too yeah so fun
they ran down the hall and they
get that fight oh my god is
the funniest thing i ever seen yeah
yeah anyway they better top that so
here's the thing i didn't wear the
the pajama top for performance
i just put on a shirt shirt
so you are going below the screen
comfortable yeah while the screen business yes
would you still let stand the center
zoom mullet i have a zoom shirt
that i have right by my chair
that i just i do have like
a couple a couple like outfits on
hangers yeah that are twice my anger
it's on the
dogs bed bath ok well that's gross
the next step for me here's a
dog's best why you're the dog's mouth
alba so what's a zoom shirt to
you like a button-down button-down yeah yeah
yeah yeah like like a thing that
i would wear on stage right okay
so i've probably put a jacket on
as well yeah and then after so
after the show is over
i hit stop video hide video so
i could change oh and i think
i double tapped it ah the double
tap because i started to take my
shirt off and then one of the
guys was like whoa paw and i
saw myself on the screen and i
like ran off right away
a camera pressing the button yeah right
off camera it was faster
oh my god they were recording i
was more of why go laugh she
wants to see your body i it
i wanna see you run away fear
yeah i museum
the frame is very tight so it
wasn't much of a runner
oh my god it talks about bug
spray i certainly shares the test member
how he learned how to toss last
yes without ancap huh
that's fine i did it underhand and
she could not catch because it was
so low it what's the problem with
underhand i could put it right there
in the pocket i could've put it
in the book to solve a problem
like underhand
mixing up sound of music and you
have what's called my fair lady my
fair held you solve a problem huh
why can't a woman wear a dress
more than once that's what i was
thinking of was doug benson um can
i ask you a question lauren show
um and i want to ask you
both of us what are you free
i'm going to say
guess what what the fudge are you
about to say i want to ask
you about this but we haven't seen
each other now we're seeing each other
i hope you can talk about it
on mike and maybe you've talked about
it on mike elsewhere but i have
i haven't heard it but can we
talk about your who wants to be
a millionaire experience we never really talked
about we texted about it
what i want to hear all the
do you want to break it was
the most amazing day i'm not kidding
i think it was the happy that
it was and and like silvers another
story that i have
caravans tell it
ah that was a good break but
what do you want to know well
the minute wow i wanna know what's
showing just like well he wasn't there
but he was still alive at this
was the alive at the time they
did a little i do a little
interview with yeah he didn't look i'm
dead he was quite old it what's
weird is
that that show is dead as reaches
yeah yeah it ain't talking to me
hey i'm on my way to ever
leave me alone on my way
it took me a long time i'm
backing him amsa show doesn't seem that
long ago and then to see like
the clips and then are exactly twenty
hosts like it's like they've been so
high no but it does here my
mind it doesn't seem chris harrison why
meredith vieira there was any other vieira
there's the daytime version seth rogen less
but
anyway there were a bunch of dorota
photo frame but um it was the
duty you could even tell if you
want oh i love yeah there and
you're listening you want to see it
on hulu but i think you have
to have some sort of game show
package but if you want to see
the last moments that's on youtube somebody
like me put it captured him but
which
is the most exciting part but it
is fun to watch it play out
because it was so tense i mean
i truly was so nervous so let's
let's go back to the beginning okay
you were asked to do this ah
and what what were the parameters at
that point what did you say when
they said do you want to do
this we just say well this wasn't
march and they they said do you
want my pulse
he just told me that there there
was this password faster people will do
it i guess and i said of
course i want to do this you
said this to the publicist yes absolutely
published just laid this to them i
was playing we should decide you're talking
to the publicists and don't have direct
contact with yeah i don't i don't
know how much people listening know about
how this stuff all yeah so i
want to make sure that they're carried
along on this journey so what happened
was i was payback f tompkins i
was totally fine i was told that
my the way it works engaged in
the story that's the difference the way
it works with celebrity episodes is that
you get thirty two thousand five hundred
dollars guaranteed for your charity even if
you totally not even if you crap
out regardless of your level of celebrity
so you can hey and sad i
was like i gotta do this why
why is this happening is a mood
letter was even
before the monsieur there was no like
no press it wasn't like a thing
it was just like he you know
he said the name in the movie
wrong it was like before it even
came out right so i was so
excited and i the thing is too
for the celebrity when you get to
bring a the smartest person you know
to help you write and that was
very important because there's no way i
would have gotten as far as i
did and then i also had
my dad is my lifeline and then
we should say you brought your husband
mike i brought mike and there's a
new thing to wear you i almost
forgot tall i was i was very
fine line first i went home and
then i was like well it should
be you like you know mike is
mike knows a lot i know i
know what mike knows and doesn't know
so it was very easy to go
like and i was very upset that
you
didn't even consider you were your um
you know once i decided that it
was mike there was no even thinking
about everyone although somehow you considered paul
but not me well that was such
a flash you know it was like
this guy who's barely even shines by
the way i normally know like all
the questions ah in
like baron holtz was on one yeah
i watch and he there was a
morse code one that i was just
screaming at the screen wow you knew
that yeah work and it may like
because here's something know he he called
his lifeline of his father i believe
and his father gave him the wrong
one wrong answer and was pretty certain
about it but somehow he
worked it out of what his father
was trying to say instead of what
he actually said and did the right
answer but i was like with with
having people that you can read really
well because with my dad my dad
eventually while we can get there but
he was confused with his response and
then i had to ah okay yes
here's what i think he was
i would say about this right um
but mike was great because he knew
a lot of stuff i didn't know
and yes i should say i was
upset that you didn't consider me until
i saw how you guys did and
you can did you know all the
answers ah your you know what was
interesting is yours in particular i think
once it got up to like sixty
four somewhere around there i didn't know
one or two of them and i
was like yeah she made a bed
we weren't so lucky we're like live
texting while we were watching it right
yeah right yeah know what you didn't
tell anyway you did right and i
was so excited it was very exciting
to watch and i ah mike mike
and i were really doing well and
it was going really well i was
so nervous i truly couldn't even like
thi
think straight i was so nervous and
like so many the questions were really
hard for me and i don't know
a lot about presidents and that's an
interesting thing that came up later so
there was a president question that i
didn't know but mike knew or something
we got through it and then when
then he had to leave and so
at thirty two thousand five hundred i
was alone and the only lifeline trade
him for anyone
no and here's what you could do
you can keep your smartest person for
whatever question he just leaves or you
can get to fifty fifty and i
chose to pick him because i thought
i'd rather talk it out with someone
than have a fifty fifty where i'm
alone a guy that doesn't really help
write sounds so yeah and then the
other thing was because of covert so
everything
is just shutting down right that this
was the last day i think the
next day was the last day they
were shooting at all and and someone
had a positive test or something that
was like something crazy that happened shut
down before some people got to play
day so it was really lucky you
know i didn't know that you know
we just didn't know how serious it
was whenever but they didn't have the
audience there well in those episodes like
they're airing two months into coven but
everyone's doing the
cute like touching elbows yeah haha this
is funny you know yeah it was
day one of talking about yeah yeah
never even heard of it and then
um you can they didn't have an
audience where you could do ask the
audience to then you had the option
of chinese economy and now turn out
to be amazing for me he's he's
very good at it oh my god
he was great but he did do
it wrong with kaitlin olson he gave
her the
wrong answer right well do you remember
something about like assuming with the heart
or something like it was a biology
hasn't yeah that's the law he didn't
know where to begin yeah because i
often go to sleep but i had
to do a couple alone and i
think god knew this one there was
i hadn't seen uncut gems yet but
there was an uncut gems question yeah
about what is the rhinestone or the
diamond studded oh yeah and i have
just seen on instagram a lot it
was yeah for me so i got
that which was like amazing because i
never never worked out if i got
it wrong or if i had used
him on that one and he didn't
know it whatever so then the next
one was spelling out atlanta's more sets
last name now and i didn't know
oh my god because i thought i
knew
but constantly like i was now was
alphabetizing cds with her in and i'd
be like oh she comes after morrissey
okay yeah go oh yeah well it's
one of those names were like you
think you know and then you start
looking at all the options because they
were all just like different variations of
our ah yeah ss yeah and jimmy
knew that one he was like i'm
really good at spelling and then i
called my dad and there was ah
for the next
points about presidents and my there's you
who watched the moment online because it's
fun and my dad says it wrong
and then i have then he says
it right yeah and then i have
to thank variant figure out which one
to go away no clue well i
think the last one is him going
like oh no he goes james jim
james run then he then hangs up
and i was like but it was
one of those things where oh
because it's how many presidents were named
james yes six years and had the
same name right and he was one
of those moments i'd been watching clips
of people on a millionaire and you
know how you can be really cute
like you call your lifeline and then
they're like this and you're like alright
so what else is going on like
you didn't like phil yeah well classic
was the first guy whoever won the
million yeah yeah
his dad and said hey dad i
don't need your help i just want
to tell you i want the million
eight so yeah i think best moment
oh you know i have to say
that quest easily effective yeah that question
is so easy that he got that
it's yeah it's not fair yeah but
the ah the moment was happening where
i was like his dad's phone number
was
well we don't know these days but
with everything in our phones i wouldn't
be able to answer um and i
didn't know and so then he answered
and i was like are you sure
and then we like talked it out
with your dad and then he was
silent for like ten seconds and then
he goes james and then he hung
up and then so i had to
sit there and then jimmy went to
commercial and i had to like hem
and haw
over this right and then jimmy calls
my dad back and it goes to
voicemail why because my dad's ringer was
messed up so there was we before
it was even dirty why did jimmy
call your dad back because he goes
let me call him and um let
me just see i want to his
ass is mine and then he reveals
that i just won like a lot
of my oh okay with his help
but that doesn't voice me
oh so actually it's kinda better oh
okay yeah that's great and then i
got to see the million dollar question
and i didn't know it and i
didn't have any lifeline yeah i don't
think i knew the million know but
apparently someone on the season wins a
million yes i saw the clip of
that yeah very exciting i would love
to play unfortunately oh you know i'm
not ah you know yeah my shot
i tv
over five years yale's i don't wanna
get in there it feels like you
stay in there i feel like it
was very random that i was there
like jane fonda was i was truly
like just don't let them question this
right but it was amazing we were
all doing so exciting new mop was
was pumping her fists like tiger woods
yeah my god it was crazy and
i played for the
crohn's and colitis foundation and then i
got to do like an interview with
them which was really nice and that
was cool that's amazing and and did
they i mean is that that has
to be one of the biggest i
think so yeah ah no donation donations
that they would although the there must
be i'm sure all of those corporations
have like these fundraisers where people go
like
a million dollars you know yeah they
were really excited though and i think
part of it was like just talking
about it on tv was cool yes
definitely how did you end up five
hundred thousand okay now dig into you
sandra thousand oh do you wish that
you were polluted you're one of the
biggest donations do you wish you were
playing for your own banking there was
a moment
like right after like can i just
have a little like i have a
tasting like wet my beak wow it's
like that's how bad i owe much
money but i was riding so high
like we and we were in lockdown
right after that so we were just
like at home like me and mike
like oh my god you believe that
happened and like just talking we were
like oh yeah go through every question
we try to remember every single question
that happened
and what we said yeah and then
we had to wait months for it
to air and you did you tell
anyone well you're dead we call my
family and everyone was crying it was
like so exciting and i told a
couple friends that i had like i
was weird you didn't consider total because
i didn't want you to know i
wanted everyone i i i wasn't allowed
to tell you why you knew
well i want everyone to have to
see it because oh yeah that's thanks
yeah expanding so the night because you
not telling anyone or even giving a
hint of like hey watch i mean
you started were like hey i'm on
this thing tonight you write down made
it so exciting because we i think
me and co-op assume that you didn't
do well or something because you were
just sort of now
enchilada back you know so the fact
that you were getting up there were
like she she couldn't have got this
high could you i literally heard when
i got to the million dollar question
i heard get the confetti cannon ready
whoa and i was like whoa amazing
no idea so whatever and i got
to meet the creator of the show
and that i met some of the
guys who wrote the joe millionaire
joel and the question yes the guys
who wrote the questions were um really
nice and they lie later i was
dealing with them about how there was
like they're like oh this one question
was even supposed to be in your
games so that was so lucky that
that happened wow i need it really
like a lot of times just the
stars align for a person
or it's like like your instagram thing
yeah for instance you know where's just
like total luck and then you know
you see other people in there just
after thirty-two they're just they're okay you
know you know when i thought about
using my lifeline on the herbie one
because i knew my dad had seen
uncut gems but i was like i
don't think he'll know what herb yeah
yeah when i was like if i
if i waste him that
good thing it's such a it's such
a ah thing you have to wrestle
with like i don't want to waste
lifelines because you can back your mind
into not being sure about anything totally
and so i can like like the
tiffany haddish one that was last night
and you know there was one question
where she worked it out perfectly in
her mind but then she started going
like oh i don't know should i
call this person i call
this you know when you also want
the person to be able to be
your lifeline so i was like what
if i get kicked out and then
he didn't get to ever have the
car or that would suck but being
so but i think the calls are
are almost worthless because most people don't
know to condense the question oh yeah
tiffany haddish didn't really well like she
shorthanded the question but mm
most people yeah say i int every
word of the question than say a
disadvantage tell me not to do that
like before and they're like most people
do i don't know if you're on
the phone like you only have thirty
seconds of ah i think my dad
didn't even understand no matter how many
times a explained it though like it's
this much like there's no time to
yeah did you study at
all did joe and i regretted it
because i was like actually almost thinking
about brushy you gotta brush up on
the presidents at at the very least
yeah and well we all should i
always want to learn yeah and i
wanna look up here on a table
of elements i said at the night
before i was like oh i should
study that and then i didn't do
it of course and then the question
was about the periodic table it was
the last question but it wa
um and i wouldn't have and also
by the way couldn't wasn't even on
the wikipedia up here at a table
yeah it was really hard to find
that information it's like one of those
things where you have to be interested
in that subject in order to know
but it's yeah it's usually usually the
final question is one of these things
where if if it's in your wheelhouse
you it's relatively easy like like the
yeah i remember the first person who
won the million it was or at
least the first million dollar question was
who was on the first cover of
people and oh i want to try
to guess yeah what year was it
was i was probably in this like
nineteen sixty nine or something i would
say really john f kennedy he's dead
i know but maybe he was no
long
you're a person
it's not corpse week like i feel
like i remember when i was a
kid when people magazine debuted interesting i
don't think it's that old ah it
may not be maybe in the seventy
s i'm not sure okay farrah fawcett
you were so close macklin smith you
you you not not in terms of
the person but
nathan smith farah
the tub fancy keeps saying farah farah
ferrell will ferrell
faro faro faro faro pharaoh sanders pharaoh
fair the pharaoh king talking to king
mark born babylonia moved to arizona for
who was it why i loved that
when i was a love why did
i was making fun of something that
people like shit no doubt you've heard
of this here's a song so random
the songs were not meant to be
funny i lived for a lot of
fucking us now like this is the
greatest thing that could have happened it's
so not funny now and it's no
fun so funny about it it's no
offense to him i mean oh if
you're listening steve no fancy you know
what's really what's really wild is that
i love when i was
a kid i loved steve martin and
going back and listening to his stuff
as an adult and even thinking about
it like the stuff that i love
it's so anti comedy that yeah doesn't
it doesn't hold up for me at
all really so you only get that
you have to be really aware of
comedy at the time to appreciate what
is
funny about it at the time because
you're like yeah i think playing with
i don't know i remember when i
was a kid i just like because
you is silly you know what i
mean but but now i understand like
he was subverting what standup was at
the time it's what i liked about
it in high school though and when
i like me and my friends memorized
all of the albums and would do
the jokes over and over again
yeah so it's like i don't know
like it's from maybe if i were
to listen to it again i would
but i think i would have such
nostalgic for it but are you do
you guys not want to guess about
pharaoh oh wait i thought we got
it no you didn't we said king
tut's scott
pharaoh
pharaoh comma pharaoh comma j shelby fero
know who's a famous pharaoh pharaoh ramses
what
pharaoh is a last name fero i
don't know faro has a famous son
o f a r o w yes
oh woody allen mia ah well i'm
a pharaoh afar we gonna take
a movie rebecca
we're back and laura and you said
you had something you want to talk
about let's game is talking yeah wow
la ram guy santa thing ah one
of you make please listeners make us
a theme song for when lauren wants
to tell a story
we need more drops lauren has something
to talk oh do it again because
i talked over lorena da samba da
da old okay so a few years
ago meaning ten um i was having
an improper versus probably eight years ago
was having an improv hearse with my
team bang rang at usb and we
were at a betsy star's house and
her kitchen at the time i think
pry where there was a party the
night before there was like probably ooze
all over the counter you know food
random whatever ryan stanger for my team
grabs a clementine from the
the fruit bowl he goes watch this
shoves it all in his mouth and
chews it with the peel on and
we're like oh my god and then
we're like that was crazy and then
he goes things like i'm having appeals
the next one that was black oh
oh go oh he wanted another one
but he didn't know that the one
he yeah well oh god how did
he barf i would barf oh he
just oh are laughing so hard
black blah
oh that could happen with the most
disgusting and we were all like oh
my god
yeah it was like okay so guys
it's thanksgiving if you're listening to this
the day comes out and um we
wanted our own thing i think east
yeah so we had to have a
little pebble feast and you remember charlie
brown when he his family for some
reason had abandoned him and he gathered
together
the other children abandoned by the families
don't remember and they had a thanksgiving
feast of garbage
dude i don't know you that charlie
brown thanksgiving sure this isn't heath clue
i don't remember me drifting through the
iphones are very bad guy i'm using
garbage figuratively oh he's cliff absolutely a
garbage he ate fish bones they had
like jellybeans pretzel sticks and toast oh
that sounds okay i'm gonna watch that
this thanksgiving while i'm alone while it's
name is mike leaving no i just
mean very important to note that ah
franklin the one black peanuts character sitting
all by himself alive mean that um
put online people were like look at
this like there's like six cars i
like these why is that mister rogers
kind of thing where it's like you
know how miss yeah mister rogers sort
of broke barry
lawyers when he washed his feet with
the mailman character because there were all
these people saying like oh not the
mailman character an actual heute person but
he wasn't a mailman was watching mr
mcfeely oh no who who anyway have
i thought he was a mailman he
might have been a real life mailman
oh maybe he was a guy and
they were like this is my friend
yeah wait am i
a racist for looking at him and
thinking he's a mailman
is that like something that i don't
use like an ingrained thing that i
need to re-learn maybe so not all
black people are male okay alright
alright anyway so we're gonna do our
own thanksgiving feast of the oh he
was a police ah oh he's a
police officer oh my god i cb
the land that's true so yeah he
redrafted huh
mister rogers why you have to pick
a pig
should come home if so we're going
to complete moment we're gonna complete the
eminem's challenge we have our six favorite
ah flavors of mgm's but also lauren
brought in a new flavor i got
my paws on a bag of krispies
and we're all gonna try him and
see if they might
affect the wrangler rankings yeah so ah
you know this is like having
you know a player in in their
rookie season go to the finals or
something i don't know what i'm talking
to and i am looking i am
like air bud
i in my little batch i received
one that was chopped in half and
it looks like a little rice krispie
instead is stuck inside oh fun alright
fun so we're gonna we're going to
go backwards we started at plane last
time and then got weirder and weirder
we're gonna go backwards to see if
the plane is still good at the
end way lawrence already
eating one oh yeah what happened yoda
trying the crispy very troubling look on
your face i have a really strong
opinion about this okay i don't like
what we're starting with krispies starting with
crispy i don't like the um flavor
it's like the chocolate is weird huh
you agree
i got one that didn't have a
lot of crispy and it was better
i eat two at a time and
it just tastes like a nestle crackle
to me taste a little stale i'll
say the talk yeah chocolate taste cheat
chocolate chocolates cheap chocolate taste cheap it's
done dry everybody does just weird okay
alright that's interesting okay well i'll let
you know i got these off ebay
just getting target
in the nba section um so as
people will recall round one scots favorites
were plain peanut and peanut butter laurens
were playing peanut butter mine were playing
peanut butter and fudge brownie we took
the ones that peep to people oh
that's right i've seen i've got i
have a strikethrough yeah so plain
and peanut butter around to almond pretzel
let's go around mint dark chocolate got
around to ones okay round two oh
we all liked almond pretzel and mint
dark chocolate almond pretzel and mint dark
chocolate should we wait what's which one
should we do first um the pretzel
pretzel alright here we go preto
ill more crunchy it's like crispy but
more crunchy it's a ball
huh
oh like come
it's okay but too much pretzel i'm
haunted by scott's ah review last time
when each of the pretzel all these
tastes kind of stale yeah yeah yeah
i don't know it's not the freshest
pretzel let's be honest not okay should
we go to mint dark chocolate mint
dark chocolate
i'm going to have a little palate
cleanser yeah a little water hey if
you're eating along with us have a
little water along with us oh shit
we probably should've told people to do
it with us that's that's a good
idea around we can add that in
sure mint dark chocolate generated that in
his true
dark chocolate it seems like a gum
hotel
too much meant i like it for
that reason
i like hotel mince i don't like
these i don't love this yeah just
like punishment candy this is like last
thing in your cabinet kinda like fight
it finally okay almond it's stocking candy
i don't think it's a bad thing
but i have ah i have a
good i have a high tolerance for
junky stuff now these are big these
are probably the biggest eminem's these guidelines
are flavor wise sizes and i like
the shape and are shaped like an
almond because that's what's inside
alright okay i actually really like it
these are good when you're comparing these
other ones takes the cake i feel
like we're in awe in the stratosphere
alright let's i feel fancy when i
eat these i feel like trash make
crispy going backwards let's go to peanut
butter the other ones remind me my
home
hometown these remind me of beverly hills
beverly yeah
name
well now what peanut butter peanut butter
these are these are great these are
literally having these are the ones to
beat for me these are fucking bomb
dude alright pull on mother fucker
let a motherfucker open his peanut butter
if i fucked my mother oh because
you're come back
she's nice she raised me
it's the least i could do
disgusting
goddamn those are good that was fucking
great peanut butter is great alright let's
go to almond no sorry not almond
peanut peanuts stupid
i mean peanut is like peanut butter
in a way closet okay george washington
carver yeah you got me
so we came up with it
peanuts like good butter the first thing
he did was made peanut m and
m's
and work backwards from there no one
must know the time is not yet
right
oh i leave that room where the
ark of the covenant and i'm eating
a peanut going it's kind of like
peanut butter
ah she's kinda like peanut butter like
peanut butter already existed no
he made it up and he's like
oh whoa yeah if you just need
a regular they taste like meat butter
my watching that peanut i been an
eminem's are good
having had the almon just now you
know all montana fancy almonds so much
better okay so really well because yeah
if you are trying to have a
healthy snack you need almonds over peanuts
yeah but
peanut eminem is a classic i'm an
m almond is kind of like who
even buys ormond and is a conflict
nut why
it almonds are so so bad environmentally
they require so much water i didn't
it's cool guess i knew that because
people are mad at in general yeah
cryptocurrency
what time dr hershey
the electricity it takes to make like
bitcoin how does this whole much did
you take anything isn't it a fucking
picture on a screen i thought too
i mean it comes up as a
picture on screen but it's a real
thing i could hold no no no
it's just like the the computer power
like all the you know understand how
are you what i don't like you
guys don't get it no
no we don't
felt like you do it's a drawing
on a screen no cryptocurrency is like
got a plane go to play it's
like that ah the christmas carol that
robert zemeckis made that thing really so
bad for the environment right playing playing
playing my plans your chance plan de
plane de plane to claim i'm going
i'm okay how do we even
what do we do pick our two
favorites or what or pick our favorite
this is so intense situation let's knock
something out yeah okay i got ah
i think we can safely knock out
crispy for sure crispy i don't like
i don't like mid dark chocolate meaning
that we're not going it out like
pretzel like we're talking about what's going
to be number one yacht
not my number one i don't like
pretzel do you guys like pretzel i
don't know i'm not seeing my number
wow so we have four that are
in contention we have almond peanut peanut
butter and plain
i try really hard i feel like
i can knock out peanut
oh my god i love peanuts peanut
this is so you can knock out
we need two votes to knock one
out
okay okay okay um no wait hold
on stop stop so i can knock
out raymond
you're you're being contrary no or you
are honestly here honestly i'm so conflicted
because i like almond really really really
good but when i go here to
these three or am i gonna reach
for almond when i'm not thinking about
how i just had that flavor and
it was good
probably not do you know what are
you knocking out almond with me i
might i might but i'm just saying
i'm having a problem let me let
me save you the trouble in honor
of the white man pillaging this great
nation on this special day oh yeah
thanksgiving i'm gonna say i'm gonna knock
out ominous because it's bad for the
environment bad for the guy knock it
out almonds okay
but that's a really righteous little choice
so we have the three ah picks
from the first round are our top
three here this is so intense and
this is so expected you know i
mean um i think we should make
our our choices and we should reveal
them we will reveal we need to
we need to really think about how
we're describing this though best
first imam of all time if you
could only have one rest of your
life which one you have i mean
like how are we yeah we how
are we defining that i'm defining just
as which tasted best in our taste-test
yes i think there's just a winner
of the taste test yeah okay alright
so everyone taking take your ah packages
behind your back and will reveal thank
you
packages behind your back will reveal too
we we've taken plane we've taken peanut
and we've taken peanut butter behind her
back and we're going to take out
what we think is the best eminem
at the same time ah when i
say hold up the packet three two
one go we're going to hold up
the package and the coloring just move-in
zoom duh yeah do it alright three
two one
we picked peanut butter shit peanut butter
congratulations p o jedi agenda oh she
sure they make peanut butter and jelly
i mean i know they should not
and i'll tell you why there was
a there was a ah we didn't
even celebrate a candle
yeah manorama nam i felt like i
just stopped that horrible notion peanut butter
imams are fucking great yeah good congrats
congrats everybody stuff fruity inside that you
ever had yeah there was a trader
joe's about your broadside oh what does
this magic seventy seven um
ah there was a trader joe's impulse
buy candy bar that i saw many
times in line at trader joe's and
i was like i'm finally gonna get
this i bet it's good peanut butter
and jelly chocolate chocolate bar yummy chocolate
that sounds bad i know what you're
talking about having the chocolate was bad
yeah well i think it was adding
the jelly
although that's right an m and m
is so yeah yeah you thought that
chocolate was the problem well peanut butter
and jelly let me get this straight
youth on the triangle wu peanut butter
and jellies is good i don't actually
like jelly why lauren stops stop saying
that i don't shut your full mouth
lauren stop trying
to impress your friends i don't like
jelly as your nephew listening to this
you better be just homework um alright
so happy thanksgiving everyone yeah happy thanksgiving
you enjoy that are going to enjoy
eating where we have to take a
break shall we play a game we
have to take a break first then
we play global thermonuclear war yeah we're
we're grateful for ah let's go around
i'll play a game we're grateful for
so we'll pick the game that we're
the most grateful for when we come
back we'll be right back
we're back and we were just wondering
if lauren cheated at million yesterday like
wishes a quiz show or what no
but you but paul said he wondered
if my dad possibly was googling there's
no way for many reasons but part
of it is that he was confused
about the ah he goes giddy
it wrong but he later said i
just saw a chart a bar chart
in my guevara for my head and
i and james had more he kay
had no reason to understand no
but actually that's how i describe a
lot of things so it really makes
sense like i'm just like i just
know that that's how that is or
what i'm remembering yeah know why i
wonder if you would talk to that
would you have been able to figure
it out or no no i swear
i did talk it out for like
ten minutes and i was like um
james literally i was like i don't
know i was mad
soon but i i couldn't and then
jimmy sandbank do you have as much
time as you ne yeah yeah yeah
yeah so dr phil taking what thirty
five nights i made a dr phil
joke at one point about how i
was taking operating on dr phil time
because he was taking so long i
was really on a question about jack
nicholson times i was like yes wait
you actually
how old was this question about time
it was truly like if you take
one penny out of a dollar how
many do you have like it was
really like what a dungeon yeah this
woman who was from harvard or something
you know they kept talking about that
yeah and then they both were like
ooh and then they almost said it
wrong and i was like wait it's
coins let's slow down um
take a really long time on that
question then i was really nervous but
i and jimmy was trying to help
me he was like yeah can you
think of any and i was like
yeah i got obama i cook i
don't remember anyone can you go backwards
from the from ny can't do that
because there's only forty five i know
and that's what you know this is
the kind of shit that bothers me
though about my dream
can you go backwards from now like
like counting back for the presidents were
from oh whoever is currently no way
and the thing is i feel like
i need to learn this and i
also need to learn where all the
states are because there's only fifty and
there's only forty five presidents and i
have to be able to like well
that's the thing to do if you
go on jeopardy you have to for
figure out the states yeah you have
to you have to you have to
brush up on geography you have to
run to president john f well there's
even an animaniacs song about um the
president or it was about the states
and then there's another song about the
president so i was like why did
i never learn these songs yeah that
would just i could just go through
it in my head and what's try
to go backwards we got to
to me humility and we've got ah
big tea yeah my new ammo he
is ama george w george w bush
before that is clean tone will clean
tone yeah and then got over that
of course george h w yeah i
got for him is ray a little
male ronald reagan before that is carter
nosy before
reagan i would be really confused i
wouldn't feel kabul i remember noisy nadie
my ah tepe my fifth grade teacher
being very upset and telling the whole
class that ronald reagan was going to
be a terrible president wow and she
was so mad carter didn't get reelect
wow she was right so he looks
another
that's even another level is knowing whether
they were a good or bad president
or what they did exactly i mean
i could never i could never i
never ever retained i never because in
school you're not really taught that unless
there is an actual ah you know
like a nixon scant type scandal thing
that happened but so okay so this
is
in before carl this is where it
starts getting complicated because of the nixon
thing so before carter it was slower
so from seventy yes seventy six it
was forward but ford took over for
nixon like seventy three i think as
nixon had just been reelected he had
been reelected and then he got impeached
or was going to get impeached
you didn't actually get impeached do some
people get to get impeached while some
people don't he resigned before his time
yeah they they basically walked over the
senators walked over to the white house
yeah in a big dramatic moment said
hey you've lost all your support if
you get impeached everyone's going to vote
for you to be impeached wow and
he said okay i'm gonna resign and
leave
later and now is this connected to
what the listeners i held it might
be so i started learning about ah
by learning i mean i read like
a couple tweets about ah the twenty
fifth amendment which is like that sort
of thing i think we're so if
the president decides he is going to
resign then he
the vice president takes over but if
he there's like a whole complicated thing
like if you want to come back
you can come back yeah well it's
it's very murky and as a matter
of fact ah dick cheney had to
like wrote letters that ah like secret
letters that he only told i think
his chief of staff about saying if
i become incapacitated you know
what to do with these letters because
he was very worried about the chain
of command and um but he didn't
want anyone to know that he had
written these like resignation letters essentially cheese
i don't know it's crazy anyway so
before saying before nixon then you're you're
sixty eight and this is where it
gets really bad for me lyndon johnson
lyndon lyndon vi lenin
and then before that it would have
been sixty four which would have been
j f k one yeah yeah because
he was killed and sixty five is
iraqis killed and sixty four sixty four
oh no i would have said three
sixty three sixty oh so then he
was he was he was he was
then nineteen sixty sixty to sixty four
but
killed in sixty three so then who
took over for kennedy oh johnson johnson
did yeah so johnson was then can
you name sixty three to two seventy
two can you name the six james
so yeah um i don't think i
can you got madison yeah buchanan yeah
um monroe
monroe began
sorry about what happened you in the
back of that row of
remember that i don't know you're talking
about this is famous too close for
comfort episode where jim j bullock was
like it's not reverse raped but just
as rachael ray finally but yeah my
grape somehow raped by a woman did
you ever see the show boring too
close for comfort monroe tools for comfort
was a show
as ted knight from ah humanity and
caddyshack mary tyler moore show plays a
cartoonist in the san francisco bay area
probably married to ah this nice red-haired
lady ah their two daughters live beneath
them right i don't remember du da
dark-haired one and a blonde one
it could not have looked less like
each other or an oiler sniper ready
and looks like he has three wives
in the ah and then it says
a conservative cartoonist tries to meddle in
your family and relative interesting he used
to draw his car to his cartoon
his famous crutcher was cosmic cow
and he's draw with a puppet on
his hand i think i like a
voice yes no stranger says yeah can
you fathom that and show that bad
lasted that long so then there was
a neighbor or roommate or something monroe
named monroe who was played by jim
j bullock an obvious gay man yeah
who had to pretend to have the
hugest crush on this blonde woman
oh well also he wasn't out right
i mean he wasn't al but it
was like it was it was obviously
a weird time where where you could
like you couldn't ever say you were
out but like everyone everyone who you
are yeah charles nelson reilly paul lynde
like people like that as opposed to
when i was growing up and like
the the late seventies you'd look at
liberace and just go oh he's just
he's eccentric or he's oh he's fun
i can find the right gao yeah
you know i mean yeah but but
so monroe wayne was like the urkel
of chuckles oh okay yeah you're almost
there so you had four yeah ah
so ah
madison monroe james washington james lincoln okay
jimmy i think said something to the
culture
me too but he did say something
to me like one of them is
a little tricky or saying well he
was trying to say hey yeah um
and that i would have never thought
of right so who's that who's that
sixth one actually now i don't know
oh wait we don't have we don't
yeah well we have five jimmy carter
monroe carter monroe kurt addison madison ah
you can't han and that's fine it's
four oh ho on people are screaming
at their for them garfield gar we
are building is like monday da dah
great and great love we got along
yeah i thought we only apply six
no i thought we only have five
say again we have buchanan madison garfield
monroe harder monroe carter oh i see
who's that six i give you hints
yeah yeah and this is without any
knowledge of primeiro um yes king tut
it's um okay it's part of the
this last name could be and this
is our three-tier by the way
we still have to do that yeah
let's see the teacher we try to
guess who people are based on the
weirdest clues that i'm going to do
with the person okay this last name
has is part of a better word
that means spots
spots ah james k polk yes
polka dot po i see part of
a bigger name that means spots i
was trying to think of like melanoma
james k melanoma alright it's time for
three-tier and we're going to bring one
back that we've done on our previous
sees oh shit this one is called
it's it's one that i'm thankful for
because i thought it up it's called
switching pitch it truly thankful i'm really
grateful honestly just reflecting on the year
i'm so thankful for switched-on pitches
ooh yeah either to see it's rays
is um switching pitches let me remind
you how it's played ah one of
us swells it one of us is
is going to be the pitcher pichon
switch it switch and pitch it
well you just switch just switch it
lets you say am i doing it
yes
okay so one of us is going
to be the pitcher and the other
people will be the network executives listening
to the show well what's the pitcher
receives is one of us will say
the title of an already established television
show like i believe we've said law
and order before now what the police
got to what the pitcher has to
do is is make up a new
title which is deeply held
a belief of mine every word is
the opposite of the of the real
world real real
transfer hey
everyone loves little belittle and then they
have to pitch that show two or
two inch it no they said they
do switch it
they have to pitch the show to
the to the network executives and then
they have to sing the themes that's
fright and it has to include pianos
okay okay right okay so paul is
going to be the pitcher and we
are going to throw out a title
to them learn do you wanna go
in the next room okay oh yeah
there is no natural right side it's
too close for comfort okay alright
you for meeting with me hey it's
no problem honestly we're not doing a
sorry hey oh did were you frightened
by i didn't realize that my zoom
was on oh hey solid stop tubing
that hey i can overdose you tubing
honestly i think i was doing that
privately i'm so sorry i thought i
had clicked it off that's okay i
enjoyed it okay um so who are
you my name is paul ryan i'm
there to pitch you a television program
when you think of your name to
think of the beatles of the bible
i think of the beatles of the
bible okay the bees job
geez
john mongo and john yes don't like
miko okay now what john was like
joining gringo thanks for safe i say
it i hope it helps okay so
before i have to i'm honest i
was in the middle of doing a
few things i didn't realize this meeting
was happening right now and i am
zoom set on automatic start so um
why why would you do that
new updates yeah just have i have
a meeting starts when i realised that
to sit down and have the meeting
say medic start yeah so i just
want to know what your idea was
oh okay yeah here you pitch this
bad boy i would like to just
tee it up and pitch it to
us this is a television drama oh
so it's not funny it's serious okay
i like
like the okay sometimes it's sad okay
and sometimes it's scary so all the
all the boo all the drama
uh-huh and the taos the yes sometimes
his mouse no
you are going to be in this
law
put your dummy away he doesn't hurry
he hasn't buried this is my natural
it's did you you clearly made it
yourself right oh yeah yeah looks really
taking off in the core because people
are just buying tickets to see his
performance marine corps in the korea i
just and you can clearly rags like
maybe you
shouldn't have an actual lit cigar in
his mouth oh
i guess i'm just talking to you
he passed so this drama is cognac
welcome back you're totally sin yeah this
drama is called
appropriately far
in spite of discomfort appropriately far in
spite of discomfort i love this title
wow it roll immediately makes me wonder
what kind of lunatic would say something
like well here's the thing it's it's
a love story you see whoa and
it's about two people who are both
dreadfully ill with diseases that could kill
the other person oh like the novel
coronavirus now this looks like they they
these are made up diseases from fancy
high so we can change the rules
anytime we wow love that yeah what
kind of diseases are you thinking of
that you made up well
all the diseases you've made up okay
ah there's mandalorian
oh and you may already just on
the first one well that one unfortunately
that tv show started and so i
might change the name but we don't
get the rights this is the ideas
that the ah the the man the
love story and yes it's a man
and woman's story that's part of the
says he called a man delorean know
he drives a delorean and he is
oh his e but that's just that's
just a coincidence is that another one
of those george lucas stupid names where
he just is like mandalorian camera tv
you just put two of them together
what he's
the mandalorian mandalorian yeah yeah this is
off topic i'm just you asking me
about my mandalorian or giorno no i'm
in george lucas's i'm just now deconstruct
why can't i can't speak to that
i know how stupid his names are
like skywalker because he like goes up
and travels around kyi or han solo
because he's like a loner that is
how i came up with mandalorian but
now i feel like it
if i say it is a stupid
name i'm i'm saying no idea oh
just say it's us to me why
we love this thank you this is
making me feel better good it's really
good good now hit i can't show
see this for details his disease is
if he kisses
a woman huh
sophie kisses any lips softer than his
oh wow he kills the other person
no does he take sandpaper to her
lips then so we can kiss our
don't get ahead of it oh is
that the season finale this is why
we want to be really involved with
the creative it's the series finale but
i'm oh he just rubs her
yeah sandpaper and then the observed begin
to note tenth season i can see
it i love that and then she
her name is susan it's very it's
passing options and everyone calls her lazy
susan because she's so industrious it's like
an ironic ah i love that i
like when women are teased for being
good
at at something yes exactly and it's
all men who do the tcm does
this woman know how beautiful she is
or she has no idea just no
idea which makes her even more beautiful
when she watched the game with you
wow the movie the game by david
fernandez yes some eighty i've always wanted
to see it
you want to see her watching with
him yeah i want to see it
by it i mean her watching the
game you know once i'm on twitter
i saw someone referred to pennywise as
it the clown and i've never forgotten
what an interesting detail as if you
don't like pitch i just think it's
a close thing that is stated right
okay well coming back on topic because
i rarely so lazy susan has a
disease what's that her disease is if
she kisses anybody she says she did
well it's just
i mean this is part of the
pitch okay so chase for me just
feels like we are a cape we
are cable know what is somebody fucking
so yeah clearly although we can do
all that of course oh they just
can't kiss like this is willing but
they would any woman rule pretty boy
which was the light that was the
title i was going to give it
a try
your demon rules and i was like
it doesn't lose and people were like
yeah i agree and i'm like oh
okay i gotta change it
yes i feel like this my child
is more descriptive they have to stay
away from each other because all they
wanna do is kiss yes yes she
so her diseases if she kisses someone
she enjoys it more than the other
person well that's tricky yeah right yeah
so isn't that usually what happens when
you kiss someone that you enjoy it
more than they do yeah yeah for
you
i often talk to his wife so
they have to oh that unites others
more zooms zuma zuma zuma zoom boston
mass o two one three four so
they have to stay away from each
other they have to stay appropriately distant
ah yes
from each other yes and then the
rest of the title for discomfort yes
i know it with a pro what
is it appropriately distant distant in spite
of knows no appropriately distant because of
because of discomfort does comfort
it is with that theme song baby
i'm glad you asked yeah okay i've
got a disease called loving you you've
got z god love in me we
got disease god love each other bus
we can't f d in the same
room
now where appropriate leash sisters shop
i mean ah appropriate is distance because
of dashcam for mr fawlty to duan
did what i said hopefully this is
for discovers right before a live studio
audience
i love it
do you want to buy um okay
well how much is it yeah how
much oh we're gonna talk how much
will it take us to get us
into this show hell i'm going to
write a number on my computer's camera
oh by the way i want a
star i want to star in it
and i want to start on the
hollywood walk of fame for being the
best zoom
yeah oh there has to be a
category by now
all right you drive a hard bargain
let's say it will cost you
lifetime donuts i get donuts for free
forever and do i have to pick
them up yes do i have to
make them yes when i make them
you pick them up when do you
want them i want them as soon
i want to buy you want them
all at the same time right tomorrow
he e u d o d o
d you want you want your lab
supplies
it's tomorrow how many day by yo
do you want to eat in a
lifetime they're there all of them they're
all going to get stale within like
four days so you never see me
donuts okay no but how many do
you consider a lifetime supply
ten okay alright we could do that
probably thousand oh no divided by twelve
huh to avodah oh great job with
the pitch wow so happier worked out
for all of us and that's how
we played richard richie to a
so you worked out for all of
us oh my gosh it was up
next ah lorne you had to be
next sure alright i have a title
one day at a time okay
ah reimbursed runs told delma they can't
do that and they're fired that's so
funny high right oh oh two oh
shit you're on the zoom hey we
had it set to autostart hope you
don't oh no that's fine we're together
by the way even were of no
no not to
i'm just wearing the same routes to
the same room and we're holding hands
um alright well it feels honestly whatever
makes you happy so i'm so glad
you approve ooh i've never met it
doesn't make me happy but i'm doing
it anyway my name is tab and
i gab tab jab is that short
for something it's like so
deb it's short for tabitha
oh like the tv show tabitha he
yes whatever it takes so coincidentally understand
because we are here to buy tv
shows like ten you know that and
i have a really exciting pitch for
you today okay good good stuff so
do you want to know the title
first or what you're in charge you
tell me
this is your this is your pitch
we're just the people listened to and
decide your fate so this show is
called a million years already happened a
million years already yeah this is not
biblical not biblical is it supposed to
well you believe in the bible yeah
we do we believe it's literal here's
the thing
we keep hoping that things will be
biblical right and because we are biblical
ah a million years is hard for
us to fathom because there's only been
six thousand years yeah it's really an
it's actually something that kind of takes
place in a sort of supernatural realm
okay the oh wow people sort of
have lived past lives
and they have so many feelings inside
witchcraft stuff like harry potter a little
bit like that but ran by the
notorious turf j k rowling we are
a biblical movie hater
oh so we don't like her we
don't think we're like oh no yeah
that's great so it goes like this
there's a family of a hundred and
they lived on one shy of a
dalmatian family and they live on a
compound and two shy of a later
donation family
and the way it works is they
always
yes tell us everything about where they
live like how about the way it
works is
one person
is the is the person who is
oh my gosh okay so frazzled my
notes i'm sorry i've never made enough
to know that scary oh well that's
because you're in the same location i'm
not really used to visit or halloween
costumes yes you're just playing a conjoined
twin i just sorry yeah that's what
we have two hands you know to
apologize
next year we're going to be the
human centipede okay we're looking for later
if you're interested yeah so okay just
kind of zip through this so work
says there's one sort of psychic in
town that everyone speaks to and she's
no biggest this town there's only one
psychic well it's a family so really
how often does that strike twice in
a fan
yeah good mostly of town full of
only ten people she's got let me
see that i did she go by
in a question and then she just
slammed onto right back in my phasing
she's good well so okay the way
it works is the one cycle we
stop saying the way it works is
your annoying phrases seem to have any
meaning
you're absolutely right so the unfold is
so much better actually better i loved
it there a psychic in the family
she's very old one hundred and five
she's the grandmother matriarch and she is
able to tell you what your past
lives and everything happened a hundred years
that already happy
and and so she tells you what
happened and you kind of counterstained yourself
and others based on these types of
experiences you've already experienced the you are
called
and so we also see two really
quick don't talk wow don't do is
that
this is what occurs if he falls
asleep below what occurs is this isms
what occurs is how does it unfold
baby what oh ca
are you awake
wait am i getting a phone call
oh my that's my ringtone is coding
me what it is there is
the way that people interact is damaged
scientist it's damaged by this knowledge dumb
it down for me oh they be
basically you look okay so ah what
would happen is i'd meet your character
if i was the grandma would say
oh in the past life you actually
were um a piece of shit you
are far you are a murderer
and then you
yeah that's pretty easy i guess like
you took objection and you're able to
take your murderer and then care about
a human mess with your life because
you weren't going to murder but you
think well i used to and then
suddenly become the farting murder and everyone's
trying to catch you and you want
to set it on my life being
a happy husband so this is the
type of thing that will happen so
my finding out stuff may pass
as you start to change your future
and that is one hundred years of
things already happen what's the theme song
it goes like this
one two three four five years already
huh been six only this guy's gonna
cut him to him okay ten years
already she changed it to a hundred
right at the atlanta maybe
she's making this a long theme song
so she'll make the show huh i
don't know i feel like she's pitched
yourself as the grandma eighteen i think
she wanted to do it
do you have this like too many
cooks cut thirty years forty oh so
what one episode you have any is
eighty is thirty is do i need
to three
she went back to killing my one
nine hundred years already been you could
be for murder
no way no she's just redoing the
pitch and song for the pitcher is
actually a word
buddy about to pitch just wow i
already knew that part when i came
in here it's written in the show
i think she could hear us oh
we not a mute my double tapped
it oh no no they're fucking
where do you double tap to me
alright oh sounds interesting thank you the
seam song might need a rewrite that's
fine but do you see yourself playing
the grandma i'd like that very mo
you're right all right we'll give you
twenty million dollars for one episode can
it be thirty million yes for two
episodes ah it's more it's very worse
but take or leave it worse
that's a better title it's very worse
the and yeah
alright i'm next and then we gotta
wrap it up okay so paul you
give me a titles right give me
a title
hill street blues
okay
ah
he should be here any minute actually
because his his agent called me and
said he didn't know how to choose
two hi hi everyone oh you're late
for i'm sorry i had to hear
in your own home are you running
around to laptop i'm sorry i just
had this is the only way to
get exercise is to run around my
laptop comes down to hear some other
time
oh i have to set our ok
i'm just because you schedule this pitch
during my exercise hour he's yelling
i'm sorry mister what was your name
again
toobin okay mister tobin your agent called
me because their agent had told me
that you do not know how to
use zoom and yet here you are
so i figured it out bitch okay
hey wait i like where this is
going okay what's your show called sweetie
pie alright here we go you
ready for it yes i am putty
hill avenue rock wow you know it's
a musical and what does the title
again pothole okay avenue la okay because
an avenues different from a street and
a pothole is different from a pot
hill
it goes it's it's indented into trying
to get out of it's like a
slack tighter whatever right like remember might
grow from the ceiling but libido anyway
it's a musical years i ever see
com rocks dulac tight i ne le
and cop rocks dulac tights on the
ceilings de la
tights are on the ceiling because you
have a ceo up there yeah you
invented cuckoo macabre yes oh my god
i'm so employee oh i'm being sarcastic
oh shit oh you're right oh start
keeps getting me i can't believe it
i honestly don't need to handle this
he's singing me so hard you suck
anyway he hasn't super carb rogge it
was so good he hasn't said anything
that has upsets me yet
anyway okay this this this is all
about you know how when you're driving
down the street me know i have
a dry yeah you
i know i know you don't i'm
talking to him okay right which again
i drive my own car so what
will you know when you drive down
the street and suddenly you hit a
pothole yeah and you're flying up and
you hit your head on the top
of the car yes it hurts i've
abandoned up there my bald yeah you're
driving down an avenue right yes
it doesn't it rock is this about
my life yes wait another pitch about
your life why does this keep happening
because you're famous dude no one knows
why yeah wait i'm looking to watch
the show oh yourself and wait i'm
looking at twitter and you are trending
wow
why oh you're famous bro i don't
want to be i love what i
do
me
ooh it's epics sarcastic shit say city
again there's no show about you dummy
but you are trending and it says
zoom dick yes oh
you can see the dang things ugh
june tell us anything about the show
i already told you dummy the show's
about driving down the avenue yeah you
drive let him sing it all right
rog rog rog rog rugged rock and
rog rog rog rog rocky and raku
there's a guy named bo ladies driving
down the street rock reggae rock rag
rugged you gotta hey don't defeat the
opposite on top of his aid a
rock or rock rock rock rock rock
rock rock rock rock rock rock rock
nah right guy right removable bubble bubble
bubble bubble read before bubble bubble bubble
bubble bubble go to voters huh
oh wow
is that it yeah that's it paul
i do not want to buy it's
what do you think
feel like i have to buy ah
come on dummy bombshells he's gonna sing
me if i don't okay really really
watching by my show you really know
i beat your gassy gary oh you
got me so by it but you
do want us to buy it yes
please
that being said i do think that
we could buy it wheat let's let
me check my wallet i'll check my
wallet as well i've got a hundred
coins i've got thirty coins yeah either
two hundred and thirty coin which could
equal upwards of multiple dollars yes now
these coins were made by
electricity which is bad for the environment
i don't know that's a conflict for
me ready alright i'll take it one
coin we have to print them onto
record it's coin and it's very expensive
to use a computer to do that
it's a three d printer oh but
we need to put more dees dees
nuts
we got we got you banteay teams
yeah but so many slater tag d
bitch alrighty bit i'm so grateful for
that game i'm grateful for that game
i hope you guys enjoyed that episode
and enjoy you know if you're making
travel if you're traveling around because of
the holiday
maybe you shouldn't be but if you're
making travel up you're also making some
but i hope you enjoyed the extra
long length of this episode in the
earth how long was it ah yeah
it was probably like an hour and
fifteen manta damn saw some roller ah
you know gaunt a good fifteen minutes
of it was as chewing that's true
oh yeah you're right
miss chu well goodbye her happy thanksgiving
everyone i mean nice good bye
us