three
wow
oh
ah
oh yeah we figured out how to
do it thank you wow yeah this
is how we figured out how to
do it
boom boom boom boom boom
hi nora later
yeah i was hoping you guys would
continue doing the beats i see people
we can do it to do well
it's it samples zoe shoulder store how
we do it scott were you as
alarmed as lauren and i were by
the theme song huh yeah it was
very loud and very frightening it was
you know like seeing a ghost or
anything like i feel like it was
a little bit frightening like seeing people
come to it was like yeah yeah
yeah
those cats though they're quick is best
professional use their quickest vs lady
lightning is that a shirt yeah they're
quickest fast as lightning we come off
and we can't have we've barely established
it as a fun thing yes here's
what's going on too many shirts yeah
too many sherries hey yeah hey
they're going high yeah huh oh yeah
liking oh no no it sounds like
that sounds like it should be on
the tv movie it had that song
um the one where he was just
chevy chase shit and they're like um
going to justin timberlake ham or whatever
the indie justin timberlake who jay
justin tustin jonathan to to to to
to timberly jonathan taylor thomas oh okay
um was with chevy che oh wait
something to to africa no it was
thinking of jungle to jungle yeah sail
to africa it was a movie about
a boy and his father about a
boy
yeah it's about a boy it was
about a boy and his father played
by george wendt isn't it and it's
and that song isn't it that like
sort of like powerful
free class but it's uneven it's like
more like um what it was those
commercials for like pure moods it was
like that was just pure humour those
cds from like the nineties where i'd
be like um and yeah and like
different types of oh like you'd hear
like an orinoco flow yes hello we
only know day we only know freedom
rock were a little bit older yeah
turn up man
i don't know now what freedom rock
brother there was a commercial for sub
compilation of you know like sixty song
yes sixteen like yeah the summer of
love they return to innocence as the
song that i'm singing i just realised
the return to wait don henley no
oh what is his the end of
the innings
since yeah play return days so wait
if it ended with don henley this
is like a school song this song
this is like a reboot this is
a great morning song i want everyone
to hear okay let's hear it alright
it's like if a if a family
member dies and they and you're going
to be sent off over the side
of a cliff
ya ya wait for it to really
kick in okay
still waiting
you know it's careful way
oh word
oh shoot i won't be able to
prove anything to you with this who
is this
yeah chevron
why get on my why he leaned
away from the bike to say it
i mean it was while loud music
is playing enigma oh
skips you
let's hear a lot of ah sadness
by enigma
may i still love it well wait
enigma the guy with the puzzle tattooed
on his face but i don't think
so no enigma who does sadness sadness
yeah based on the mercator sounds are
huge sick news this is sadness yeah
yeah this is like church cool man
when amongst break it down well i'm
a phone camon can i'm here to
stay it's fun to be funky in
a monkey way monkey monkey funky funky
funky funky oh but they're all shaving
like the center of their
kinda like a concentric circle and it
looks like what world
when they scalped the native american yeah
site
oh anyway freedom rock had these two
old hippies okay can i say about
the past song that i was obsessed
we will get back to this but
i was obsessed with musket i was
obsessed with doing a mashup before mashups
were anything you thought of it first
we're comfortable mushrooms
come up with marsha
i like bernie
i have parties that isn't like that
guy i have parties party um i
pulled the mash-ups yeah pretty much it
had the same beat as soul to
soul keep on grooving thinking of jungle
to jungle simply understand yourself so i
want
i didn't have any d j equipment
or anything like that but i wanted
to put those two songs together like
bleed into it can we hear soul
to soul keep on keep on groove
and don't stop play understood and i
think tom's diner to maybe o da
again
the same ish beat but i love
it yeah oh sold us hey can
we talk about this can we talk
about soda oh yeah okay yeah um
i was just thinking this in the
way here when song good morning sample
other songs yep and how i think
it should be necessary for it to
say um the track that it is
in the title yes because i drives
me crazy when i can't figure out
or if i like love something and
then i find out like a kanye
song when i find out it's like
some old song i'm like i would
rather listen to that old yeah like
the one the the one the the
the one oh yeah keep thinking about
it was i was listening to
two how soon is through the wires
that's why i'm thinking no yeah but
yeah knows not to how soon is
now by the smith yeah great and
then it was immediately reminded me of
so many chick by a chick yeah
i was like oh well i guess
i always knew that those were the
same song but i was like that's
great yeah they no i didn't i
didn't realize for
or for like three years was ah
shut up and drive by rihanna is
blue monday i've never realised that i
just play little shop and drown never
realize it i will not acknowledge your
talking amounts understand yourself and simply wasn't
you simply misunderstand yourself i i'm a
huge blue monday
a fan i never quite heard it
somehow but yeah this is yeah it
up and drive guy
and do during our new new new
new new wait until it kicks in
dude you don't like why don't you
just ask kevin to get into the
part where it kicks in
here we go here we go here
we go here we go here we
go oh oh oh oh pick it
up pick it up
here he goes
yeah i guess i just thought they
were similar chords but monday can i
tell you that i'm not familiar with
either song you don't know blue monday
oh yeah this is going to be
the best day of your life we're
gonna play blue monday you're just gonna
change your life long time
i'm of the song yeah how does
it feel to treat me like you
do you know okay singer look good
feel
to treat me like you do what
a baby i don't know this part
is upon me and show me who
you are what something like oh told
me to shut up and die when
we went down to the beach
baby c d f g h i
j l a man obey this just
rip off of the alphabet yeah you
can review because i read up of
the elves you can see that over
there we can listen every single song
includes every letter of the alphabet
oh by law that's why so many
songs have the word quiz in them
to play songs said the quick brown
fox jumped over the lazy deer with
a tie for all your lakota the
aid of their party there is a
way to ruin that you've done one
of them the singing the alphabet over
but await ruined another way to ruin
any song is can we play a
little more blue moon
a pro grade this is another way
to ruin any song for anyone spider
man spider man does whatever a spider
can i would argue that ben yahweh
anything different over another song would ruin
the song i would say it enhances
every song here
great
hey mickey you're so fine you're so
fine you blow my mind hey mickey
hey making oh say can you see
by the dawn's early light this is
like stars on forty five hits was
last started for let's explain stars on
forty five n three o three stars
on forty five was it was like
disco or rock back
yeah please
got bumped again seconds ago apologies to
freedom rashi rabbi well have you ordered
sushi yeah freedom book is the new
mandamus
so with forty five was in the
early eighties i believe or late s
they would have disco ish medleys of
whatever the popular hits of the day
that would have this ah clapping beat
behind it
and it would be like you know
what were some of them like the
one we find stars on forty five
here we go
ah so this is just one song
and normally it doesn't have this class
okay this is the song yeah
da
a
i know this one
yeah the the first one was the
theme song they would do at the
beginning yeah okay it's all songs i
know now yeah okay o que shit
ah nah i love what's happening you
are my candy huh
and you got me wanting you to
the transition into another one honey oh
no it keeps going and letters let
it live
remember when he was on brady bunch
and the gay downs oh yeah oh
yeah yeah me think this is davy
jones this is the argentine
this happened late
now this is needed
this is
okay thanks you
that's embarrassing it faded out right when
you when you lew proud was really
cool thank you lorna i'm proud of
me amy
kevin my wife likes me faded out
right when he did that oh wait
so many tangents there was like a
thing this happened this happened once before
is where you went oh
because it went into the beatles we
were talking about david jones then it
went this happened once before jones on
the brady bunch and then behind where
that the guy say about that song
this happened once before i used to
work in a restaurant called cafe ordeal
still there in the valley oh pardon
meal go visit there's a plaque dedicated
to course most famous alumni on this
spot um but
ah i used to work saturday nights
and they would have bands on friday
and saturday and that the owner peter
a great guy theater cardio still there
if you didn't care yeah he he
ah he owned with his parents who
were english and he was not english
but he he was really into he
he when he hired me it was
like we have great bands and you
know ah
the the members of chicago play here
all the time and so and that
was like a selling point but um
so you're saying chicago's not impressed no
no but i immediately told jimmy pardo
for sure i hate them no he
loves yeah there's favorite band so ah
that's interesting in any case there was
a beatles there's like four good chicago
songs oh boy
there's more than that i like i
like sir there's a solid or full
moon what about twenty five after that
yeah no one because i don't understand
what that's about at all what is
that about waiting for the break of
day is now five to six to
eight or foe the break of day
if i guess it falls off from
there i don't if i was you
i don't know
i don't know but is it subways
or buses it's about
got drugs of course it is what
drugs number drugs have you ever had
twenty five it's crazy it'll give you
had six or four it'll make you
six to four if you take twenty
five and then you do six and
then you go to four okay well
sing like yeah so the rest of
your life you know i know what
you guys are talking about i've done
it yeah that's right you're in the
orinoco flow
i went to a block party recently
um well what was not a block
party my friend was living this was
two weeks ago she lives around the
corner oh hold on i'm just thinking
she was living i don't know why
i'm saying she was living at the
time okay we tie friend is guide
her two weeks oh um she around
on the corner from our house there
was a house that every year does
a chicago cover band yeah i thought
about it let it go yeah
they do a chicago cover band at
the house yes and so they invite
everyone in the neighborhood so they don't
bother anyone because they're gonna be playing
loudly and we went to it and
she does part know about this weight
or are you not allowed to complain
about it if you were invited basically
it's like a way to go hey
we're doing this thing we'll do every
year it's our midlife
icing well like a whole asian and
afternoon thing yeah yeah so that's alright
yeah yeah yeah and it's also fun
because we could hear in her backyard
but then we went over there and
watched it for a little bit and
um i was thinking when are they
going to play the hits and they
did at one point but that was
like a lot of these chicago songs
i don't care about i like like
five
and i wanna hear them cry what
a cool up and i went to
go see them at the greek and
we were similarly disappointed because we when
we first got together we were constantly
singing their eighties love hits like like
ah yeah i can't even remember what
they all are but um but then
when we went to see them they
were playing all that like
horn seventies band music and we were
like these guys are a bunch of
band geeks yeah i have the meaning
of of the song the song's title
is the time at which the song
is set which is called y twenty
five or twenty six minutes before four
a m because of the twenty five
or six to forcibly like forty five
or twenty six to four
yeah not how you say that you
don't yeah it has been incorrectly speculated
to be in five availed reference to
drug quantities or mystical illusion i was
joking wow
right but then it was banned it
was banned for a while in singapore
is banned in singapore yeah they're like
the sucks they don't more like don't
singapore if you play the song will
kane you thing
one of the caning countries anymore i
think it was yes can i just
finish the fact that cannabis beetles can
famous finnish information that he got the
beatles cover band always opened with that
song and i grew to hate it
like beatles cover band fad cordiality oh
yes they play every saturday night you're
talking with cafe yeah just couldn't
let you get i don't think we
ever got something we've got to the
beatles no beatles cover we did but
you're saying something but the beatles cover
band played every saturday say shut up
and you didn't listen hey
the guys laughing before you die good
morning good morning radio show which i'm
not opposed to we should get a
serious exam show we should just do
this oh my god it's totally we
doing fuck up all of our careers
and just become fuck up
every other time know michelle collins nikki
glaser come on um when my friend
did the morning show at indy one
or three one which is the whole
reason i started comedy bang bang he
had to get up at three am
or four am to do it yeah
sounded awful yeah but no that sounds
awful well that's why when when i
would do comedy clubs and they would
want you to
to do the morning radio it's like
i it does it doesn't make sense
first of all nobody goes to those
shows because because they heard person they
didn't know on the morning radio show
yeah it was very funny but then
also like it's cruel because i have
a nighttime job and you have ah
you've made the choice to have this
weird datetime
job like they have nothing to do
with each other's you're tying to all
of society
you know maybe percent no morning radio
people make it up like you just
don't know i know but i guess
that i'm saying the listeners when you're
on listeners aren't getting up at three
a m l but i'm saying that
you you are when you're on is
early enough that everyone is up because
going to their morning yes oh i'm
not talking
about meme law no but i thought
it was funny to say that i
know you did honey i know okay
you're hugging it's getting better um i'm
going on k t late next week
okay with sam ah yes oh boy
um and i always feel weird talking
at that hour that's like seven something
but oh yeah
that guy and then also when people
can see you yeah it's even weirder
yeah yeah what are you i'm promoting
my new cartoon harvey street kids oh
through netflix and twenty nine congratulations well
that's fun that'll be a great time
yes i'm sure it'll be fun i
did that one time
i did it one time weiss yeah
guys oh hey with his song
we talking about freedom rock yes the
time has come so what is it
rock is one of those it was
a commercial for one of those compilations
can we hear a little bit of
it kevin should have been hearing it
currently are you just going to play
the commercial so then there's no way
we're hearing stars on forty five no
but i want when i want to
hear your take on no no no
no don't play it hey i wanna
hear
your take on and see how closely
it aligned so here's what i recall
okay is that there's these two old
hippies some sixty song comes on the
one hippy says to the other this
freedom ride something like that right i
felt you under here yeah he says
i'm excited because i know amen is
that freedom rock so you remember the
same
yeah makes me think about his room
and he says turn to corroborating evidence
yeah she says then turn it over
the end would you say
then turn it up and turn it
up does he say man does anyone
say man says impartial i think it
says the freedom rock man commercial either
says the freedom rock man or he
says that freedom block turn it up
man okay let's let's check the tape
let's see where the man lies i
bring her into your new years start
i remember
you don't even realise this song yeah
i'm elton john they say man a
lot to rewind rewind
all these songs represent freedom i said
oh hello john i meant okay sharing
clapton should get yourself such freedom rock
yeah well darn it
man on every single line re mans
in as many seconds what about a
baby
john hans
to the stars on forty five
alright alright i can't hear this is
now this is music for the seventy
is basically was this ah album it
was yeah it was a two record
set i believe it that you could
order for around twenty dollars or so
zak yeah by the way it starts
on forty five is the reason that
weird al's song is called polkas on
forty five i don't think any
one remembers that thank you that's kept
me up
yeah you haven't slept in years i
have it and i feel a thousand
and i'm so thankful you're just now
you're no climbing under the table and
you're pulling this is my ovaries so
moment blankets confirmed i've been waiting my
gravity blanket okay wait i watched little
people big world which is a fantastic
reality program um i don't know if
you've seen
it to tonto lc i've heard of
it it's never she's been on like
my whole life i've lived i don't
want all people spinner
i've watched these people go from like
children to having kids of their own
like i'm like they oh wow long
time so it's like to grassy but
with little people um no
i don't know what this oh so
all of this is reality show about
this family and the the two parents
are little people and they have ah
four kids one of whom is little
and the others are average height and
then you just kind of see their
life they live on a farm on
the north west coast whatever don't know
lauren the northwest killer des
id wait why if the shows telling
you they live in farm
they're dead they're dead this is heaven
is that they went to god
i understand
and now it's really wonderful because the
show i'm loving it because the parents
go horse sought out that that duh
yeah mcdonald's the parents got divorced right
up your alley right you're quibbling are
you are you afraid you're going to
be penalized if you don't yeah i
love every interjection
really yeah i love every other one
that one is one that you didn't
exam then what i denied you the
next one coming oh but i think
that's what's fun about it so so
now their kids are old and when
the kids are like in their twenties
and some of them are married with
kids the twins are they fuck yeah
no the twins are one is averaging
one is little
and then they they're both married to
women and have kids with them ah
the little person had a little person
child and the average had had average
child but it was could've been anywhere
because they just work words genetics yeah
i'll let them like lisa de um
average height personality because he married
average height woman i don't know i
think that makes it automatically less today
did they did their farm and this
is not me like searching for comedy
i'm just genuinely interested did did their
farm that they had before they have
children was it was it everything was
because i think there was no i'm
saying where everyone they got the farm
after they i think i think so
because because because was there
original house everything was scaled down for
them and they're like oh no we
need we need some stuff that's going
to be average height or oh look
there's multiple shows that are about little
people that are on t lcd okay
i'd be thinking about okay this they
have a farm they run a whole
thing where they have like pumpkin season
and they do it they they have
like a pirate ship they built there
it's for people to come and wait
you just said to
weird things that i need to understand
it's awesome they built a pirate ship
sky i watch it so regularly please
terms are somone pumpkin season is october
they have a giant know a pumpkin
season is but in what relation to
them then they had they they they're
fine they host of like you know
like we can go pick out a
pumpkin and go on like a hay
ride and do all these things they
have okay
the whole farm is like pimped out
with all these things they have a
pirate ship for kids to play on
pre show
they say the my point is what
got me into this is that the
parents are divorced they're both parents are
now divorced yes which is why i
love it because they're have the the
stories are more intense because they're both
dating people there but people doing both
average height which i just find interesting
so they both were like i'm not
satisfied with this i want you that
you could see them through the years
hating each
other no wow well they just have
been together forever and they started fighting
doesn't happen with people who have been
together forever necessarily but it did for
them and it was like watching them
fight it was like crazy but then
finally to know okay they are getting
divorced they do hate each other like
it was like validating as a viewer
and then now they're kind of making
it work with trying to figure out
where they can really live to like
both
have the best experience cause they both
love the farm it's like a huge
thing they each want the farm that's
the problem when you gain first one
doesn't doesn't want the pirate bay i
would absolutely live there live there they
thank you the mom i follow all
of them on instagram now because i
was like let me just double down
because i like them all so much
i want to see them double down
on this shit with super sloppy double
can
the mom was when you split aces
on these guys the mom posted a
story yesterday from bed and she's you
wearing a weighted blanket i said some
but we said some blankets just anything
wait if you're a little person blankets
fly off your body ah there for
everybody that we're winning like i don't
know like you know gravity blankets it's
it's kind of too
trendy everybody it is a gravity well
they're heavy they're very heavy and because
everything is gravity everything yes but except
space space force they're the i actually
hadn't want to try one because i
keep seeing everyone talking about them on
intraday are they like comfort yeah like
thundershirt for dogs so i always put
on my thundershirt
when it starts raining and this will
help me so now what do they
do because he's a weighted blanket so
it's for people with anxiety or people
can't fall asleep i don't really have
those issues but i think how nice
to put on this weighted blanket and
just like conk out it seems great
so peaceful amy the mom posted this
video an ad for a weighted blanket
okay and she is talking like an
actor and it's fascinating because he doesn't
act on the show they don't they
really don't do that so she's she's
reciting lines i love my weighted blanket
it's so wonderful
sleep so quickly and she's like smiling
and it's so bizarre hey you want
she's being held hostage by this yeah
i'm going gonna say about the blanket
well janie
some people just like that feeling yeah
it doesn't i don't think it's necessarily
an anxiety oh yeah i think some
some people just like some of these
more than a feeling janie when we've
when we were oh yeah most of
our relationship until probably until like five
six years ago ah she liked like
really being weighed
down by a by she had two
comforters on her bed right and so
for the from most of our relationship
we had that and i just were
sweating learn to get used to it
yeah yeah and then finally i think
we got new when we got a
new bed we got new bedding good
news like bad and we try to
this bedding
and now we just have like a
normal setup where with a weight with
weights like we have a dovey no
we don't have okay we don't have
we don't have a way to blanket
so she's more oversea yes she got
her now she's the one who's hating
she guy you know she got used
to the other way carrying amy yep
um i love this blank quilt blanket
i love it it's soft and every
time i use it i feel like
i'm getting a great thing oh dear
acting when one last dress with my
blank will blanket oh dearly one thing
i've noticed as well is that isolate
so much bad it is like
theater god like she'd be a great
community theater actor in the morning i've
always i've always wondered why wait wait
will blink it like i do like
well like some ways like well um
she's trying to make a natural ah
with your sleep so why don't you
swipe up use my knowledge
swipe up
hello but she disappeared yeah i love
it so endearing to me though because
i i like them so much and
like just so funny to watch her
like do this ad i've never seen
her act so happy i've never i've
always wondered why people when they're giving
speeches went or or like when a
minute
easter in church is reading his sermon
or what why do people always go
into the sing song yi speech voice
it's like i i part part of
me feels like that's why trump was
elected because he'd never does the sing
song speech voice you know i think
if you're not if you're not a
ah ah i don't know i think
it's i think it's hard for
for people to make a written statement
sound natural zone like commerce sound not
because i think you have it in
your head like this is what a
speech sounds like when we did the
between two ferns was hillary clinton every
ice we go every time i saw
her on a comedy show she did
the sing song yi speech voice with
whatever comedy line they gave her that's
why we were
we're insisting to like do it all
improv yeah because yeah we just want
to build rant some people can't break
out of the singsong yeah she's not
a she's not a gifted ah or
performer in order yeah yea i semi
enjoy watching chelsea clinton ah call out
people who insult her on twitter do
follow her i don't follow where people
call her ugly every day which it's
just
so stupid but she like writes back
to them with like kind of plum
oh shit yeah yeah and then i
sometimes i'm like oh that's really nice
a lot of times i'm like ah
why am i seeing this hate like
i kind of don't like to acknowledge
the bad like bring it up to
my feed with like some insult to
her and then she responds i'm like
right i don't think humans are meant
to
process as much ugliness as we are
currently seeing all day hook theory yeah
you know like even if we don't
agree with it it's like every day
we're seeing a bunch of people insult
each other yeah and going weiss
oh and i think anytime i open
my twitter and i see so i
see for sure something that makes me
feel bad on some level either if
it's something to me or something about
politics or whatever and i'm like this
is not good yeah i need a
cleanse it's hard it's slightly a piece
of my brain yeah it's different than
a class
oh i need a spa day or
to have some early surgery la bob
do you think if you could do
the internal laws but no law about
me could you do would you do
eternal sunshine for like anything in your
life just erase just erase or something
i sometimes wish i could erase
you know what i've had trouble sleeping
the past couple of days because i've
somehow have thought about people with baseball
bats and like hitting me in the
face with them i don't know and
and it makes my eyes like i
i'm i'm laying there i'm like i
can't go to sleep because all i
can think about as a guy with
a base
ball bat hitting me in the face
oh wow you know it's similar orb
it's similar to it's similar to me
watching helicopters and movies and and closing
my eyes because i feel like the
blades are gonna are gonna hit these
guys i've told you about that i
told you yes i think yes really
did on tour and you brought it
up on stage and and say
said oh i may have betrayed that
in confidence ah but yeah yeah it's
interesting so you would just want to
get rid of like thoughts that bother
yeah well there's also there's also these
things where like conversations i've had that
that now i think of anytime i
do is so something where like
like anytime i and i don't go
to carl's junior anymore but anytime i
would for a while i would remember
this time i went in there when
i was twenty and we were there
we were the last people before close
the only people in there and this
so you told us this yeah yeah
yeah don't get a spanking on this
show yeah on this show the fries
the fries yeah on this show
oh threesome i'm on i'm pretty sure
who's going to give me this but
let me tell the story heaven yeah
okay i'm right i'm having does kevin
says kevin says this thing kevin gives
a thumbs up and now he's very
excited about it he was like yep
yep he's told me it's all that
alright wait should i get a video
kevin shaven this is part of your
job
well now my phone's okay well that's
i can look
yeah
but that's just that's the three-time promise
um nobody anytime huh
anytime i've had a weird conversation with
someone where i feel embarrassed like oh
i was in the wrong about that
even though i've reconciled it in my
mind like well i'll try to do
better anytime i do a certain thing
related to that yeah oh sure oh
yeah or just anytime i've i've done
something that i said something i shouldn't
have said or whatever marine those moment
it's i cannot get rid of i
would love to erase every easy-open thing
i've ever said do you know what
i've thought about this so much because
i don't want to erase as as
embarrassing as if my thoughts are all
the time i would i would like
to erase um some experiences so i
could experience them again
for the first oh like wow way
of look yeah it's like going to
disneyland that london didn't know whatever time
it could be i mean i think
of it in terms of like like
are no keys by the way oh
like like the mona lisa
simona lee says most disappointing thing to
see in real life what about the
sourness of the immortal bard now that's
like like huh if i could read
a book again for the first time
where i could see a movie again
for the first time i forget i
tend to forget books so when i
you wanna fuck for the first time
again
first janey could you erase this from
my memory because i want to do
it again tomorrow still what i said
i kind of wish i didn't already
i wish i didn't know so many
bad things about the world i think
this is gonna be too dark probably
but like i remember really learning and
understanding about molestation and i know i'm
sorry but i remember like learn was
at an oprah like actually there were
so many horrible stories or were exposed
to me probably edit
too young even just like as a
teenager things i didn't really understand about
things that happen people and i don't
know and i i feel that i
like then i do like a deep
dive like wanting to understand those types
of stories and like reading like memoirs
from people and all these hips things
and now it's so in my head
that it makes me feel sick and
thinking about that happened people makes me
so sad that i
i truly wish i didn't know so
much about that watch the whole thing
about about cheat oprah interviewed child molesters
who were who were molesters and she
interviewed them and they talked about their
process for like the grooming children to
don't them but i think show i
hate knowing that but does it are
you able to a i mean
i guess were you able to protect
yourself and those types of situation i
was too old to have you attractive
to have that be something that i
could write be so but do you
think that it will help out ah
if you ever have children yeah i
do think so but i think i'm
so worried about that for a videotape
you'll just show them they don't listen
to guys like this um but like
i feel so concerned about that for
all children in the world that like
yeah yeah it's almost incapacitating in a
way yeah just like if these horrors
are going on yeah how can i
experience any joy myself yeah or like
not knowing that that's happening to somebody
because so often you don't know until
someone's an adult and then that's devastating
so i don't know well the horrors
of the world
you know when you're confronted with them
it's like difficult to find any joy
but it's sort of figuring out that
balance i guess if like i don't
want to be you know sleeping through
life where i'm just right my life
is happy i don't care i know
but well the idea of of you
know when people say i wouldn't want
to bring a child into
to this world it's i mean on
the one hand yeah i get what
that argument is but on the other
hand there's a lot that is great
about being alive and being in the
yeah you know and you never know
what an individual's experience is going to
be it's like it's a gamble no
matter what i mean well yeah i've
been having this
thought that i don't know if i'll
be able to articulate because it's so
it's kind of just like it's ah
it falls in the category like a
stone thought but it's none when i
was thinking but i'm just i was
thinking oh but i am really high
right now so hard where i got
yeah well when we get high for
every episode yeah but i was thinking
about how when i was a kid
i had the idea that all
all adults were like always adults and
it was very hard for me to
wrap my head around the idea that
people were all children at one point
and even now i think i'm still
understanding the fact that like everyone's getting
older and they're experiencing that for the
first time it's not like everyone is
just older and they know everything you
know what i'm trying to say i
do ok and
then i think about kids and i'm
like oh god like when you have
a kid it creates this person who
like has all of their own feelings
and experiences and they just go through
life completely autonomous of you and everything
that you've experienced and then that makes
me feel crazy i don't know i
don't even have a full point to
that it's more just like the thought
that ever
everyone is experiencing life for the first
time there are as many mean yeah
lifetimes as there have been people
what
we need to talk for him to
argue with we need to take a
break we'll be right back
we're back hello i was thinking about
life ah how you know how movies
um they pretty much like all movies
are based upon star wars predicated upon
star wars know they're all based on
happily ever after right every movie ends
on happily ever after
or if they're a tragedy tragedy wrapped
yeah but you know what i mean
they're they're all they'll they'll add two
basic stories and like at the point
where it's like and everything worked out
or and that everything was horrible forever
but like really lifetimes if you if
you were to make them into a
movie it would be like eh
anything's really interesting and then the movie
just ends because the person died accidentally
or like everything is so great happily
ever after and then just like you
know fifty years of boredom and then
you know there's a lifetime movie channel
is that what they say that's what
those movies that's okay check this out
how many people out there do you
think are like really bored all the
time all the time oh god oh
i think that people know i don't
i don't think i think that that's
something that artists tend to think about
idea i don't give a flying but
i don't even assume that about people
i just need legal or actual
the people who are like what's life
i think even if people hate their
jobs they've they find ah wonderful things
in their family and in their you
know out of their job experience yeah
i think i think you know people
people all for the most part they
they really enjoy what's going on you
no i agree i i like to
think of it that way i just
imagine that there are that isn't people
i guess i'm talking about the privileged
people who live in this country are
well-off and yeah i mean yeah there's
definitely a line but i mean i'm
just thinking about people who like have
who are just like retired and they're
like
like seventy and they're just like bored
yeah like i think there are people
who are actually like unfulfilled and they
cannot find it i think i think
i don't want to make for sure
there are people that are unfulfilled i
mean i i think about
your experience of retirement was my best
experience of retirement was you retired
is that why we're all here three
two one points bar
oh paul's gone um my my in-laws
my ah my mother-in-law and her husband
when they were both retired they were
traveling and they were just spending time
with each other and they were so
awesome but they were like extremely devoted
to each other they loved to just
being together
and it was fucking great and it
made me feel so good like oh
my god that's a thing to look
forward to you know in their in
their twilight years that they're having this
wonderful time just being together yeah i
don't know that i'll ever retire i
want to be like betty why can't
imagine that either yeah imagine retirement but
i can't imagine a time when you
know i'm older and i
i i'm not working as much yeah
okay yeah there's always some is telling
me there's there for you wow yeah
but they're also currently there's just so
many excuses not to do things like
wow we can't really do that because
this is coming up and we can't
really fit it into the thing you
know yeah that i look forward to
a time where it's just like hey
we got i have sick
x months where i don't have to
do anything yes i do this i
think what i mean because retirement is
not for a lot of people it's
like the way things are now it's
it's pushed farther and farther away yeah
where people have to work much longer
than they used to and we social
security maybe going away she's just god
yeah going to be horrible i guess
for me it was
you don't necessarily have to find a
you know a bunch of a million
things to fill your time you know
it could just be that you're you're
leading a quieter life than you did
and you get to be if if
you're lucky you get to be with
someone that you love being with and
that sounds like a look like a
very nice life to me
yeah when my dad retired i think
he was looking for stuff to do
so he started like a fishing fly
business yeah this can happen a lot
though that people are immediately like oh
i need something i need something well
i mean yeah every you know i
don't know life is just what you're
doing while you're trying to go to
sleep who
i mean yeah it's like god i
just woke up i can't sleep for
another fourteen hours that's the most depressing
way to think about okay what do
i do during these fourteen hours i
are you do you love sleep i
when it's good it's fucking know a
good night's sleep
it's great i mean i feel like
my sleep lately has been really really
good but i don't relish sleep in
that way janey loves sleep she loves
sleeping yeah she loves it and she's
very good at it one time she
said one time she said
i what we were talking about like
she slept late she sleeps later than
i do usually lately we're in lower
kind of like the flops and i'm
i'm i was surprised when that turn
started happening where i would be in
bed law after her right um but
one time she slept like for a
long time and she said
yeah i wish i could just sleep
and sleep and sleep and never wake
up and i say honey that's death
and she said i know
um and that's why
ah sleep i like sleeping um but
i i i do feel like a
little i wish we didn't have to
do it i wish i could just
like reboot i think i've wish i
wish we could just sleep for i
wish we could sleep when we wanted
to and for as long as we
want to do like you could program
it yeah
yeah and say like i want to
sleep today i wanna sleep from four
pm to nine pm yeah and just
do that i wish we didn't have
to do it because out but during
the time that we would be sleeping
we would be constantly shitting would you
want that lord i cut you off
you say i was gonna say the
same thing okay
no i wish we just didn't have
to sleep we had energy and we
just i mean think of how like
a third of your life is gone
i hate thinking about that it's gone
yeah but that's true for everyone so
it's like i never existed well that's
true it's almost like yeah everyone the
playing field that's true
but i guess that's the argument for
people who are like i only sleep
four hours yeah but then those people
like aren't well yeah like yeah there's
like no way to actually be functioning
on that little did you you follow
the whole like arianna huffington thing like
when she like collapsed oh yeah well
well you know her whole story you
wanted to make sleep crusade yeah so
she like um was so
one who worked so hard and like
barely ever slapped and pushed herself all
the time i was always working and
then at one point she fell asleep
from exhaustion at her desk and hit
her face on her teeth on her
desk and broke her face like it
was like totally a problem whoa
i'm sure i'm telling you to describe
what it was like totally a problem
it's totally a problem i rub my
face it was totally a problem yeah
totally a problem i faithful broken that's
good um and i just listened to
a podcast interview with her i can't
remember what it was but it's about
breaking up with your phone because i'm
trying to do this i mean let
me see if i can jog your
memory due to start with locks gates
yes
it was in a garage um and
did you find yourself fast-forwarding yeah just
three the first fifteen
but she um she made a whole
crew like she wanted a whole crusade
basically to change her whole to change
huffpost and like the whole environment so
the whole working environment i've ever taken
out during the day or they're encouraged
to nap um you're encouraged to get
a full night's sleep and not respond
to things until the morning like there
was a and i love
my job where they're like you know
what go nap for a half hour
because it changes the environment for everyone
looks so good in school when i
think of myself in high school i
was the most tired of ever been
well unlike you know i couldn't believe
my dad once said to me he
was like you know what i used
to get on you about sleeping late
and how you were it was just
so terrible to try to wake you
up you know when you had to
go to
school or church or whatever but now
studies show that ah you know in
the teenage years to early twenties or
something that your bodies are meant to
be like a sleep until a law
firm or remember my mom screaming at
me or just make me feel so
bad for sleeping late and like the
summer when i was like eleven o'clock
and i like hello hello
i remember how hard it was to
wake up it was painful so hard
and so my dad would throw water
on me let's say he was get
like you get a tale of honor
st louis he's he was from the
you know a military background so that's
a boy no i mean i don't
think that he ever had that experience
of like he never had
had a life where he could wear
a basketball wasn't being bounced at his
face mine was like my mom would
open my door and then just be
like law for like so long huh
yeah like from downstairs to say here
so why don't why doesn't school in
high school why doesn't it start at
noon then and go till
tess go at noon to six would
make new netflix yeah makes dollars and
sense my dear girl well absolutely my
dear man i would have loved it
i would have loved it but i
hated getting up so early and i
remember like falling asleep in classes and
it was oh yes no chance that
i'd retaining this i got caught napping
at mister show one time i just
i
had my head down on my desk
right because it was like you were
in high school when you join yeah
it was a prodigy right choice showing
up when you would list those drafted
drafted mister huh
but yeah i remember bob owen yards
twenty kids in the hall was kind
of fun either way but i'm an
american citizen so it was just show
up i remember bob coming in and
just like like like lat laughing in
a in a rueful way like whoa
man yeah oh man
as he retired i didn't know what
else to do like it was i
think it was also like a crunch
time for the show where we were
because we were we were writing the
show but we were all also in
it and shooting stuff on location and
coming back to the office and writing
and getting paid for half the time
that you will yeah and i just
like it was just one of those
days
i was like i this has to
happen some day yeah this has to
be copied playing solitaire ones this is
very very solitary that's like i got
through i got out playing a computer
game yeah we we have the computer
now i'm not shooting with cards bob
could not understand this like it was
you got scolded or mocked for doing
something like this but then i remember
one time he let jay johnston br
bring a play station into work and
play tomb raider
i really like how does he get
away how is not only easy getting
away with this how is this encouraged
i bet that he wanted like jay
was talking about it and bob was
like bring it in i want to
see what your ways yeah it was
something like that yeah and then they
and then everyone just played they played
tomb raider they watched jay play it
for awhile like mother fuck i played
like
i had a window open on my
desktop i'm sorry just realized though that
like i i feel like i'm always
on myself for being my phone so
much but i used to sit on
the computer and play solitaire waste my
life play the sams i loved that
stuff but that's like equally lame like
i don't know well it's not new
that i'm doing this yeah but everything
like you know you
look at anything you do is though
this is a waste of time yeah
no no i know i mean i'm
saying like i'm giving myself a break
something i'm doing myself right everything goes
i was giving you a break too
thank you hey speaking of breaks let's
give ourselves one guilty right oh one
more minute break okay we more minutes
and that podcast what do you got
i'll give me a break sixty five
nine okay we'll see
yeah this spy
we're back whereby i love us
century boulevard we love us um wait
santa monica bar he's max madsen what
was that why don't know what that
is he's back he's back mcmahon so
chef and do you know what that
is you with yeah he's back mac
madson max mad so presumably mac madsen
left at some point
yeah it's a mitsubishi company oh gosh
yes and isn't mitsubishi company are you
going to play it or cheese
awesome are you going to play it
on or why you gotta play it
i got planner should i make it
teeny for my phone um from my
phone um should i play feature well
we we've got to hear this goddamn
max matin max match helmet right also
pay the price mitsubishi company show
even kenny find it say just how
stupid this is let's play it chef
ah nah someone out there oh yeah
yeah and mitsubishi wishes everyone holiday cheer
and it's time why the boeing's by
hiring you will need to be t
v
oh i don't know why you vote
remember this as max madsen and not
we wish you a mission valley the
christmas version was broke that was brutal
that was the christmas find out hoover's
shoe christmas find out who version christmas
fun okay what's your feedback is cold
laughing game laughing i've got that home
is well we're having a laugh
learn the rules of the laughing game
are straightforward one layer begin looking saying
the word haw with a straight face
the second player continues saying haha followed
by hahaha and so so in a
cert so forth and so so
in a circle the object is to
keep going as long as possible without
cracking up if a player breaks so
much as a smile he's so much
as a smile okay okay who wants
to you are huh every time okay
you add what you you keep adding
laugh sounds yeah okay okay let me
get into my headspace let me now
go up the version i
af and said you could use other
laugh sounds like he okay but do
we remember that and no i think
you just have to do more than
the last person okay so we need
to count okay got it let me
think about ah oh maybe it makes
sense to try to copy what they
did that's more fun
we're already adding wrinkles to this oh
and also you have to wrinkle okay
listen wait okay or so we're we're
counting we have to count we have
to keep track of how many yeah
i don't think it's going to get
that high come up with a broken
arm we're breaking our ah i got
it okay let me think i'm just
breaking breaking our oath know i gotta
get in i'm sorry
prepared for this i gotta think about
this oprah for snow crack a smile
no crack a smile we raise your
mitsubishi
we wish to be sure
your next layer is you have to
sing that without spam right okay ready
huh
huh you have to say haha i'm
so sorry but started wait for it
huh
okay back to note not smiling alright
haha
hahaha
ha ha ha he
ha ha ha ha ha
you're right yeah it's weird when you
say it oh you're like a love
between us it i thought
okay well i am allowing myself to
laugh between started but i don't think
that's in the rule we started getting
okay
huh
ah you don't know it's not my
turn i'm laughing just ah okay we
just decided that wasn't a allowed not
allowed to okay great ready listen
listen listen to okay alright everyone our
isn't to me linda you know that
video
no my mom and i quote her
all the time now we've talked about
it you get the spanking now i've
never talked about this yeah kevin we've
talked about linda
listen to me you i'm to be
like me i've talked about because it's
only not a char if you film
it
no joke alright here we jump up
and stuff come you can do it
with something kevin like that like a
pen or whatever yeah definitely use a
pen like you're cool getting spanked stance
vertical my story okay
alright ready and yeah i'm in trouble
i didn't feel it yeah hey could
look
don't give me the pen
and may i present you with the
ceremonial i swear we talked about them
before well what is it well if
you can't tell me what it is
i get my spanking back what did
you think yeah
okay this is another huge thanks scott
i don't want to do that this
is like scrabble no one does i
don't get into her okay huh okay
haha
ha ha hoo ha ha hoo hee
ha ha hoo hee ho ha you're
out
lawrence okay
we just start over because i can't
remember what it is anymore well then
you're out i won what no haha
who just happened
then there was like wow go go
go we should start over because i'm
losing sorry but that was more for
okay ha ha he ho ha ha
ho he
i can't do it
did you ever do make me laugh
oh yeah i loved it but you
didn't like it no it was it
made me laugh was this for people
don't know it was a game show
that got revived a number of times
yeah it was an old game show
and when i yeah i was here
for just a few years i guess
it was after or around the time
mister show yeah it was around like
ninety nine
oh i did it i did ninety
six okay thank you and um yeah
first tv credit the idea was you
ah it was kinda was a game
show who's game show where comedians try
to make contestants loud were just like
regular people just regular sixty seconds to
make someone laugh and the the longer
you didn't laugh the more money you
got yeah
and you were comedian on that yes
um you are not a regular person
i didn't mean it like that i
just meant you were on it yum
i remember watching both versions old and
new of that i believe can friend
whom ken ober uber from from remote
control data for awhile and then when
i did it
marc cohen or good friend marcos was
the host i did it under both
regime oh yeah right yeah um have
you ever been interested in hosting game
show i would do i love game
shows you would jump hand i mean
i've i've tried to create a few
yeah still like trying to develop one
it's tough but it's a thing that's
come up over the years i might
be more inclined to do it now
i don't know the problem of the
of hosting the game show is if
it's like a regular straight-up network game
show
the job is mostly like the heavy
lifting of explaining the game yeah right
and i was like saying the sun
would that over and over but like
if you do it like dick clark
or steve harvey like there's fun to
be had while steve harvey's having a
great time he's i like watching him
he doesn't get so upset with people
saying um um who is just going
to say oh i always think
in the other night why didn't i
create the proposal the worst oh i
want to talk to you i almost
texted you oh my god you watch
it i watched it and it's the
first episode is like they picked the
worst one to start with it was
crazy maybe it's the best one no
way the proposal works is this new
show that comes on right after the
bachelor and it's a per
person who wants to get married is
behind a shroud there's twenty
right there behind you like a shroud
of turin a wall it was a
shroud i think shroud is something that
goes around you like a curtain you
mean yeah but they were hiding something
yeah right and then this there's a
whole bunch of women who kind of
do this horrible miss america ask pageant
where some episodes it's men for yes
but in this first one was
a man and then all women have
been twenty women who come out and
then they and then and they say
like little facts about themselves i think
they're meanies sometimes yeah and that was
really weird because they're all not used
to that it's not like miss america
where they've been practicing yeah no they're
all like i have to be in
a bikini and they're going to like
they're kind of like old day uncomfortable
yeah and then then
i'm like there's a point where the
guy behind the thing goes like and
are you comfortable marrying ah a um
an amputee because he lost a limb
and then what by the way i
the prize for these women is to
marry a police officer from bakersfield ways
like so like you could get that
girl go to a bar
you could meet him yeah night and
then it's the one thing i have
to say is it was it was
more regular people than the bachelor totally
i did were pretty normal are pretty
normal looking and it was like flooring
to me actually because because i was
like wait this these are not models
who are trying to like gain you
know fame after this these are like
kind of regular
or people who are looking for a
regular person but they didn't live in
the same city so how's it and
the end they the man proposes to
the one he chooses and then there's
no follow-up no and then there is
a little bit of a video we
just say well i didn't see it
i see the answer so yeah there
you see they're still together okay you
see the answer but nobody is so
weird because they're like
why do you act as though they
really are in love with the person
like like you're the third person i've
been looking for like i know and
it's like yeah have so little information
about this person because this is not
like the bachelor where they spend all
this time they spent canals week which
is already ridiculously social this is literally
like twenty minutes yeah they've had twenty
minutes i mean it's an hour but
like
like you talk to each one of
each the man is talking to each
woman for a total of five minutes
i mean like not even by the
end so like it's crazy i'm like
why did i not think of this
and then at the same time i'm
going because it's so crazy i would
never think that would be an idea
like i would never let myself suggest
that to someone i was wondering why
aren't there female hosts of game
shows i can't even think of one
jane lynch oh yeah oh yeah um
but that's one but isn't it weird
yeah it is weird i i don't
know i think i had rosie o'donnell
host a game show at some point
may oh ellen does your game show
that was running which we've talked about
that too i don't want spanking
it's a deterrent see it works works
it works i still don't know what
listened to belinda is um it's a
viral video of a little boy talking
to his i don't know what the
relation is cause he calls her linda
but he she's trying to punish japanese
like linda listen like i did
thailand thank god
he's turned to reason with her
houses
yeah i'm going okay but i have
to yell at you guys
in this you number this is not
familiar to me and i know that
we talked about that i think i
got us thinking sorry i think it
was false banking you will you i
feel like on tour at least i'm
sure i've mentioned not the rule i
know and i'm sorry if i got
you an unwarranted spanky will label it
as unwarranted what i posted
yeah look we need to wrap it
up huh we need to wrap it
up guys rap rap rap rap rancho
de nati hours and forty five rapid
ou
i'd love to see can you see
early lai aide who was ah lee
hae out of the tie task leaving
do la da da
yeah anything
okay patrick crackers we'll see next time
nah i remember the road kids
polo
a k
nah last oh say so
oh yeah oh yeah oh nah
whoa hey cx i buy
a