don't don't don't don't don't three the
street hey guys welcome to three dom
i'm scott i'm paul i'm lauren and
we're back we're back the crocodile crew
the peanut butter gang
the pretzel gang them threesome boy that's
right we're all back here and we
have many names names like lucifer the
peanut butter keeps the peanut butter peeps
i was on lucifer never forget dying
never forget that you were who'd you
play you will able that's right kids
so weird able from the old testament
you know as kane and
goes back and possesses someone else this
woman but someone else he possessed someone
before yeah you're famous for it that's
what that story is about cain and
abel yeah that's why can't kill them
what age does kobe know you just
think of has been possessing oh okay
yeah she's like she's like deadman boston
brand of its ray farmer
circus performer that's right i love how
in a comic book anything can be
explained by a former gymnast or former
circus performer anyone who doesn't have superpowers
yeah like oh well i was a
former gymnast because can't do this shit
jumped off buildings does that come up
a lot yeah hell yeah it does
lower high it comes up a lie
you'll find this out when you talk
about the marvel
a universe why robin telling his period
because he did so much gymnastics
there was a female robin paul oh
that's right that's right stephanie brown what
about in the dark knight two there
was oh yeah kerry yeah what's an
underwood
carrie underwood she just keyed cars
why did carrie underwood key a car
while she has a song about breaking
up ah before he cheats gotcha yes
yes yes didn't didn't she come out
on social media and this is a
little gruesome but didn't she say like
hey i have an accident and i
kind of fucked up my face yes
i've been hiding so when you see
me next time be gentle but that's
that's what happened and then she came
back and she's still a dime right
and look different at all yeah she's
still a dime i mean it's repulsive
when he did but i feel like
i don't know so sometimes these guys
i go before scott calling her a
dime was gross i've never heard you
never heard of a dime though she's
ten
that's stupid but she is stunning and
it does make you think what the
fuck happened her face what what could
have been so bad that just the
tiniest imperceptible change made her like come
out and say like hey guys this
is gonna finally i have a theorem
do you think that she did a
little
but somewhere there and there was like
a settle down period where she was
like oh no i look fucked up
and then it like all settled down
she realize oh i'm fine maybe there's
such a strange settle down period it
takes like six months or something and
a lot of people who get it
don't want to not work those six
months so there's like one movie like
nicole kidman for instance which she's
in the movie nine and she just
looks so weird nine which is one
less than a dime by the way
and the nine-tenths and then she looks
then after that she looks fine because
like all settles down yeah kidman is
so beautiful yes and in the beautiful
ishi and in the undoing she has
a lot of lip work going on
that i found
and unnecessary i don't think it's yeah
i ain't beautiful here's what's so weird
about that show i watched the whole
thing much to my regret don't no
spoilers because i've not seen it did
you really not watch it no of
course not what the huh
what the hell do you know how
much fucking tv we've been watching during
the pandemic when everything was the whole
you're doing i didn't watch it you
know what i love about the undoing
guy who just were talking about the
mandalorian oh do you can't prove that
ah i like shows like the doing
because every week i was like can't
wait for sunday i got something to
look forward to yeah sore is it
the day of the week do you
think you'd like more than the shows
um yeah really i'm like i love
sunday but how can i make it
feel good because i have churches out
now sure she can't go anymore i
have um crotch
these are hot
i have reached a saturation point with
that type of show what murder mystery
murray like affluent murder white people murder
mystery watching the flight attendant yeah it's
not all of those things great but
it's fun i think it's fun to
ignore tv review podcasts i think it's
like really um it's like
like you know it kinda reminds me
of pushing daisies paul meets like a
mystery sort of like it feels like
it has like fun funky comedic almost
atone to it for a little ah
search forty five no search party meets
pushing daisies media it's misery riverdale it's
a great relief will berries greg berlanti
to
flight attendant yeah oh so yeah it's
like riverdale and yeah it does have
it has a sort of specific tone
yes i don't think i'd get ever
watched riverdale because apparently there was a
drug on that show called jingle jangle
and that's only know these big time
movie yeah and i can't i can't
do that but here's the thing about
nicole one of those guys is going
to buy our house
and he backed jingle jangle yes um
the ah nicole kidman there were times
where i could not figure out what
she was human
i cannot figure out what she was
human
i'm saying she was thinking yes what
she was trying to express oh yeah
album with the too much filler and
so it's it's really problematic and i
watched it on the bachelorette and stuff
i don't know if i mentioned this
when we did that no who would
who added on the bachelorette that walker's
here claire she can't hear to see
be quiet there's what it is i
first of all chocolate cake from redness
it's not even a judgment on people
because i feel like it's doctors who
say like you could dump their angst
i had friends who have been told
they've been sort of coerced into doing
more than they thought oh yeah because
they're like oh you could probably get
this stuff why not do it and
you want to please the nice doctor
like you know also telling your faces
fucked up yeah do you like see
i don't know if it's like ccs
about hooks like do do one hundred
more over here and they'll be you
know oh yeah and then it's like
too much and i feel like with
claire she is very pretty and she
got too much and it's you show
her her forehead doesn't move at all
and then when she's crying you're thinking
she's crazy because
oh that's interesting maybe because she's crying
so much because because there's no tv
show face when she knows she's on
camera no i have a real point
the face
rip the crying we have to remember
to evoke that sweet i have no
real point when you're crying and you're
really trying to express something and you're
like matters mean it's like her faces
and doing anything but the eyes are
going to answer what's going on the
eyes have it as she's like you're
freaking out but your your face is
and isn't going away and the same
with nicole kidman where she's
she she's missing a couple little movements
in the eyebrows that are gonna tell
a lot you know those elevens you
know yeah who i to my knowledge
has not gotten it and i respect
it and she's a great actress is
naomi judi dench dame judi to know
naomi naomi watts yes and i also
think art and oh what's her name
from um twentieth
century women oh julia moore know no
better but she'll and this oh benny
yeah yeah neither and they're great actresses
and they have expressive faces and i
watched i went to a talk back
with annette bening after that movie and
don't you talk during that movie i
just shouted at the screen i looked
to talk about outside the building well
that's paul has something
ing to talk about i just want
to say that someone in the audience
i might have told this story before
oh tell us i've never heard it
okay i was in england and oh
the person who asked the question was
tradition they were like asking her like
do you ever find that you knew
when you watching yourself on screen basically
long-winded way of asking
you're getting old well how does your
how does it feel like no and
why don't you do any work was
asking in betting yeah oh so insulted
but it was like they were trying
to be really feel when you watched
the grifters and your nude and you
look so amazing and she said she
was like i think i get swept
away
buy a story when i'm not thinking
about the work that the actor has
had done and i want to tell
beyond play honest characters who are able
to express everything and so i actively
don't do any of that stuff because
i really want well that's the thing
when you're playing a character how many
characters can really afford to get plastic
that much i always think about it
during shows because you're going okay either
this character got like
like a full facelift well it's like
i think about the joke the jim
gaffigan has a lot about he was
watching baucus ah yeah hotplug is definitely
out trump is bad
no about how i think he was
watching monsters ball and he's like well
why don't you just move to l
a and be a model like you
can be highly bearing i remember
it's like let's say you know it's
the plastic surgery thing is really tough
because i you know i think like
we judge it so as a society
we're judged so harshly we we we
demand it but then we judge it
so hard it's so fucked up because
it's like everyone's everyone is expected to
do it yeah and we're like why
do you do it you freak yeah
yeah
it's so stupid i don't know should
i get done or what i think
you should you need it we have
we don't want the swan did you
ever watch the swan back in the
day ah do you mean wait oh
well yeah well yeah i watched where
everywhere oh my god so defensive haw
yeah yeah yeah it's like scott what
watched it it was a reality show
where the remote
oh you know i studiously avoided that
show i did my god i watched
this and out and i couldn't believe
it but it was about people who
if anyone out there hasn't seen it
regular people they wanted to change themselves
they would be going to a hotel
for like six months or something yeah
and more family time and they would
do like head to toe
yuri everything they wanted any little thing
they'd have a hundred things done and
then when they come out at the
end they reveal at the end like
the biggest loser kind of thing yeah
and they look totally different and their
whole family is like who the fuck
are you is like she's saying that's
horrible it's so weird i wanna know
i wanna where are they now on
all those people on every swan i
want you to write this alright or
produce it directly
alright alright alright starts to be your
next year my whole year yes tracking
these people down here good by whole
year
it's not weirder than like my god
sharing gilly and doing the marvel documentaries
like that there they have the marvel
six sixteen on disney plus i talking
about today it's understandable was happening well
the yeah yeah it was an alison
brie like interesting people in that well
i don't want to tell tales out
of school but someone i know was
asked to do one and then the
pandemic kit and it was a bummer
because they couldn't do one but so
what do you mean scandalous what do
you mean do one make one of
the episodes make one episode is about
just different yeah sky but it's people
that you maybe wouldn't think would be
into doing that sort of thing oh
what based on the names that you
just said
oh well pouring i'm like oh i
can't breathe after puck come on man
come on oh you mean gilly you've
got to work with me here okay
we can't play the story we can't
play this game which was trying to
be cool you are cool already you
don't need to try shy smoke you
don't you should okay indoors i was
you
smoke indoors restaurant smoke all around the
town what's the closest you've come to
doing crack huh i will say i
i came
closer
like these type of questions you know
it's like you've been dying to have
a smoking cessation smoke crack and then
i was like closing um i can
i i didn't even come close to
doing it but my friends when i
was eighteen we went to a bar
and my my good friends ah came
out of the bathroom and he'd done
some cocaine in the bathroom and i
was scandalized and i was like but
then that may be how we all
think cocaine is bad and then people
said we're square yeah yes
shut the fuck ah um but that
was like i'd rather be square they'd
be some annoying asshole one cocaine no
cocaine is annoying people everyone who does
coke socks yeah i think he was
kinda like hey do you wanna do
some
and that was the closest and i
was like no no thank you and
that was the closest i ever came
to doing coke i don't think i've
ever come close to smoking crack i
don't think it's ever been near it
i don't pipe once i may have
been near it i'm not sure i'm
not when things down track by yeah
where in your mom my oh no
oh close up huh um when i
was a kid um my dad was
rehabbing an apartment building and we went
to help my brother the apartment was
on crack
my brother and i went to help
like rip out carpet and do some
stuff and then we moved an oven
and there were like all these crack
pipes behind oh and i guess it's
a good place to hide things that
you're never going need again behind the
up maybe you dropped it while you're
trying to light it i think they
were thr
throwing them back there whenever it was
maybe it wasn't as crash repairs but
i thought it was i mean it
was like little yeah glass i remember
the first time i saw a bong
and i think i've mentioned this that
my brother kept his in the garage
in like a shoe box in the
garage in a bunch of junk yeah
yeah that parents are such snoops yeah
but i saw it and was like
whoa what is this
what do you do with it sounds
like you already knew whoa what is
this fucking trippy for you to
ah dirty enough of new the first
time i ever saw bong was i
was visiting my sister here in los
angeles ah what she's doing before she
moved out here for ah she lived
here for
the olympic man i want to say
like i just remember he was a
little under ten years yeah wow ten
years so and i visited her we'll
just have a real beach ah yeah
she lived in redondo yes i came
out here was the olympics were happening
um and with that torch that went
right by my house that's exactly right
wow wow i went
two i went to the improv of
the hollywood the world famous hollywood improv
i saw our cindy hall and the
still standup wow rick overton you want
coke standup yes or no i didn't
have that idea of completely formed in
my head i knew that i was
if you liked comedy i loved comedy
i want to be part of it
i had no idea how did how
did you how to do that or
that that could be a job yeah
it was two years away from starting
standup and i didn't know funny but
that was an informative moment for it
was i went to the groundlings i
saw phil hartman wow that's amazing oh
yea in eighty four yeah wow
they director hayden yes they did while
it was he did the same character
for the whole show is a a
chick hazard mystery he did this this
detective character like philip marlowe aha type
guy and i guess it was one
of his groundlings characters and so they
did like a an improvised mystery show
um and it was amazing i was
wow yeah i'm sure credit bomb but
i went to a little gathering my
sister took me to gathering of her
friends and ah i was at this
house and there was a little long
table and i didn't know what it
was yeah and i picked it up
and i turned it over to look
i realize oh i did not realize
their water for you at this point
i was
fifteen ah and i spilled bong water
on the carpet oh straight out of
a note outside as i was turning
it i the the the people whose
house was right no no no no
backwash
oh man yeah on the carpet like
we're able to get the smell out
or anything ah not that night but
ah i like woody allen sneezed into
the coke remember when woody allen he
goes to los angeles the worst place
in the world and he sneezes i
want to move to a place where
tuning right on a red light is
the
only a cultural ah oh yeah always
had it i don't remember yeah you
know it's so close
i just had this gross memory because
i think the first time i saw
a moody long yeah it was um
was my friend's brothers and but but
aside from that i remember i went
to their house once and i was
in middle school and i went to
the bathroom so gross and they run
to the bathroom i agree
and there were older there was like
a pile of cubes in the ah
pile i owe like they'd been shaved
off or pluck out and now i
went under stand why would that determine
whether or not they were in a
pile but when i was a kid
i didn't understand how they got there
like just like didn't get why they
were there someone cared
made them it was so like jesus
on the beach that's right it was
where i stood on the beach there
was only one set of feuds that's
what i carried you
um what's the closest you've come to
doing crack yeah no i mean now
no not not at all yeah by
daniel paradise yeah yeah yeah yeah i
bet it was every day on the
rog missy my right yeah we lose
crazy too and crag to see me
here
we've we we've talked about drugs and
how we're not we didn't oprah smoke
crack whoa nelly way yeah she had
an episode in episode yeah i know
bought it up as google actually this
is what it looks like one of
my favorite things snow crack
there's no way she did them just
i swear to god oh my god
shoot with hulk hogan rock crack and
then parentheses not but ah she admits
to cocaine abuse oh that's cocaine it's
right back that's right and that's using
crack cocaine i can't believe i knew
something about oprah that you deny yeah
sir
oh my god she broke down during
a taping of her show in ninety
five while i wait the article just
disappeared when i'm reading she smoked it
before the show or during the early
part of the show oh my god
there's a technical primary episode that is
for segments so anyway in her she
in nine nine twenty five crack with
the audience then they turn the camera
here i'm telling you everyone get some
crack should check out you know what
i bet you i bet you a
hundred dollars she's had this removed from
the internet every link i click doesn't
work whoa can you do you guys
have you seen that commercial about the
the job interview that's like happening
over zoom or something and then the
it's it comes in um in media
rez ah and ah okay i got
one to work and the woman says
okay well this interviews gone really well
but i have one question to ask
you i've looked you up on the
internet and some interesting thing
things came up and then the guy
goes all of that is still on
the internet oh that was so long
ago and it's a commercial for like
scrubbing the internet of your weird shit
that you have like oh wow should
be possible to get things erased i
mean it's such a fucked i think
what this service does is like it
starts enough websites about you think everything
ever should be up there yes okay
it starts enough websites about you that
have like
certain reasons why they would come up
earlier in a google search so that
shit gets like put down oh right
yeah that area yeah yeah like a
dog can i like really quickly with
those circles on the stick sorry go
ahead don't tell me really great last
time really what are the signals scott
are you pregnant
what does that mean because on this
day yeah if it's a circle your
pregnancy pee on the stick i can't
see what you guys huh yeah why
do i know all the things today
on a circle it's lines what you
want me to get up always my
friend kind well here we are
so what are those you see what
do you do those circles on the
stick can i also get up no
i don't take orders from the likes
of you take a zoom you know
my fucking mom shut the fuck up
you're not my god you're not my
father and i'm sending you a picture
of it even if you're right there
well yeah i wouldn't have to walk
so far to peer around the wall
that is in my way and not
in you guys as well so
far by the way is three feet
do you know it was nice that
they nicknamed him bagel boss instead of
bagel boy because these nice easily could've
to pick a boss who's that he's
used the bagel boss he's a little
man who got very angry at a
bagel shop and he so xy you're
not my father you know my boston
you're not god that guy was so
insane i don't know what you're
talking about when you send me this
picture what are you talking about i
want to jump into the pool i
don't i seriously don't what asked the
question i guess you're talking about when
you share two vegetables or fruits or
something growing on the show they're really
far apart from each other as only
two and i'm like what is yeah
they're our neighbors i don't i don't
give a shit what is it maybe
it's like a pomegranate i don't know
this picture did not
help by the way yeah
so i get mad at me because
i don't know you and me saying
ah also when you take pictures and
i could you doom landscape yeah post
would you mind landscape yeah do you
know what that is i of course
i do but why do you care
well because it made it it's easier
to post a bunch of pillar you're
gonna post a
yeah it's ticket please take a new
one of these that was no help
at all anyone
what does this makes the difference oh
that's true um i don't know cool
cool up actually i asked her she
knows like they are v like oh
yes oh yeah yeah um i asked
her she said oh it's whatever these
are they're our neighbors though and so
she's getting whatever these are their native
probably pomegranates i don't know is this
interesting to anyone
one might not be what fruit my
neighbor has what does it fruit my
neighborhood growing so few and far between
because it and the same to have
been there for a long time so
i'm just gonna walk you don't fucking
nosy about my name all i can
see
like ah jessica fletcher over here who's
ah merger she row oh
reducing road emergency road mercy row murder
she ra oh fencing i mean yeah
he's free ice cream
oh my god we need to take
a break we'll be right back
hi welcome back hi and during the
break we were talking about the fresh
prince reunion and ah paul paul has
not seen it and lauren and i
why does she it why did you
lie it was during a break it
was during april it was the
graham show a break so the railways
that i'm raring to of all time
leading up to starting what
right what fruit my neighbors have but
i've never seen her so sure the
fresh print neither of i i'm sorry
i watch everybody that was a little
after my time you know but it
feels like you wanna like no no
ended up on tv at some point
helicopter helicopter heli was it on tv
like every shower she's looking for some
why he's like a zombie-like now look
after i just feel like it would
have been on like i feel like
i've seen a lot of things that
i don't care you know you're absolutely
right because there was a time when
i first moved here ah after i
was between jobs like so is after
missed
after show but during a deep depression
and i was just before dag probably
you might have been posting i don't
remember but i remember watching should i
watch all of dag you you could
knock it out because a day and
a half yeah alright you have a
nice day how many seasons was it
it was one season thirteen ep
episodes oh you can knock it out
in half hours fourteen hours oh yeah
that's half hours that's right oh today
i'm gonna knock it out yeah i
have them on v h s oh
that's helpful
um i was watching on
maybe the usa network yeah a they
would have like a a block of
four sitcoms it was for sitcoms that
did not last it was working the
single guy boston common and i can't
remember before i was working gordon was
admiring oh hey
she was savage but that was when
we all first got to know her
little was on acre love that show
so when i became friends with orden
he was like oh my god i
love working i was a good show
i remember it started as a regular
sitcom and then got like mehta yes
a few episodes in and it was
really funny right dana gould talks about
that show because he was on it
for a while he brought it on
and around which
is how yeah they're friends yeah his
character did not make any sense from
episode to episode right like it one
one one week you'd be super smart
the next week he'd be super dumb
like there was zero consistency that sounds
like dana that's pretty fun you know
you're right you're just writing to his
strengths but i remember watching shows and
not enjoying them and feeling very bad
in common i remember that show i
clarke zach galifianakis that's right race yeah
wow i didn't know that your old
costar hey old friend
so nice i'm wearing his jacket right
now i'm wearing his underwear i'm him
zip by where he was such a
good person to work with he's so
funny yeah we were talking about the
first freezing because ah
we because talking about the french bread
every union special was on and it
was so good we mentioned that there
was bad blood and paul went woo
so the bad blood so we were
gonna explain to tomas airwars they had
a character and play a child she's
like hey johnny yeah do you know
the the premise of the show yes
in westfield now i was born
alright so you of course know because
you're from philadelphia i'm like that must
have been a thing that's right so
an vib he goes to live with
aunt viv and uncle phil but aunt
viv gets replaced three seasons in not
even then many wasn't it i think
it was after the third but it
went six or something like that i'm
not sure i might have been even
earlier but she's
but the original viv for anyone who
grew up watching that show is dove
it you know i mean like you
just that she's amazing original live and
new viv perfectly fine just doesn't have
that all viv has exactly and there
was like a whole apparently behind the
scenes drama with her and then
kind of ended up being that she
got sort of like blacklisted and sort
of seen as crazy or too difficult
to work with difficult and then she
wrote about him in her book and
and i feel like she is reaches
yeah she'll look a pretty crazy youtube
thing couple years ago that was like
a rant about this thing but then
he and it was an unboxing video
which was
so where she went to the suicide
forest and saw the my god
that was so horrible
um but we'll sit down with the
actress in the special so they have
first time and okay five years and
the whole cast their onset and they
like do a whole thing that's really
sweet and then he separately speaks to
the first amphibian and they have this
really nice conversation and she basically says
like you made it so that like
i couldn't work
and with that i think he was
like a teenager he had never done
anything it was his first thing and
it was so his mouth was aligns
of his co-stars like it wasn't some
expert to his credit he took he
sat there and took it and took
responsibility and said i was young i
was scared all the time i and
apologized like you did really well and
we were she explained oh i want
to
if you're gonna say but she explained
that for the first time that ah
now because it's about the fresh prince
you actually know interesting she care she
explained that she was like really depressing
and then abusive relationship and she had
recently had a baby and she was
going through mostly her stuff and so
she might have been not fun to
be around but she didn't really talk
to anyone but no one like esther
said like hey
everything okay they just kind of like
she was she was acting weird and
different so they ostracized her and fired
her that's honestly a question that people
don't ask on sets yeah or hearing
this podcast you know what i mean
like
are you okay no okay weekend weekend
can't get into that but no what
are you going to say that will
smith he's been you something about jayda
you were gonna say oh well just
the cool i've told me that he's
he's in these like youtube therapy videos
with jayda table talk i mean just
to sit there and wait sorry are
these these are the same thing because
she has this show
oh right table talk is really great
it's three generations of women in the
family talking about issues and this gnomes
have guests on and then they had
will on and they did a sort
of big fuckin moment where they talked
about their all these rumors about their
marriage right oh right i saw this
stuff talks about her infidelity rhine valley
and it was kind of i'd heard
it was not letting her
off the hook with some of it
i my opinion which i didn't like
because i was like dude we don't
show us this i should have let
her off the hook about it we'll
know more and feel it yeah okay
like they had already gone they already
dealt with this for many years like
and then i felt like he was
letting her sort of like keep apologizing
keep saying what she did wrong right
which would she which they had indicated
that that had already taken place i
think any priors infidelity in marriage the
responsible party should apologize once the other
person has to accept it and then
it just never brought up again that
seems like a way better so but
i don't know if their therapy thing
as a separate thing oh i don't
know anyway but but
e heat cool up was saying like
oh he obviously is like gone through
some work in that regard because he
likes sat there and took it pretty
much in a responsible way he didn't
take all the responsibility which i thought
was kind of like if you're the
superstar maybe you take one hundred percent
of those possibility ah for the aunt
viv stuff yes right you know
if you're like if you're worth one
hundred million two hundred and five thousand
dollars and she hasn't worked maybe accept
every bit of the responsibility and well
especially if you were if you were
essentially a kid who shot to fame
practically overnight like i think you as
as a grown man you can then
say
say yeah i didn't know what i
was doing i was an asshole and
yeah i'm sorry when she did he
yeah he definitely did i just see
my buyer part yes part of that
conversation is not but you have to
admit yes you and she did this
to his to be fair what are
you talking about do that i just
think that he allowed her to take
some of the responsibility she was talking
right and
he never stepped in and said no
no no no don't yeah don't take
this it's not you yeah i deserve
all the blame and when you watch
the old episodes with her jesus honestly
so fucking good yeah he's like write
a really great actor she's a great
dancer she does like amazing stuff on
the show she's got this let's replace
you
you okay i don't feel like i've
worked with people who are miserable
i just was gone
steps in everyone's like the first lord
was so much better yeah i've worked
with people who have been like the
star of a thing that have been
miserable to work with when everybody else
was was having a
everybody here is having a good time
you know and it's funny that even
knowing like later or even like people
were i apologizing at the time like
this person is going through something clearly
blah blah blah and it's like but
it also feels like it's not the
play
race of the people who are subordinate
to say to the person maybe all
the power are you okay yeah you
know what i mean no it's it's
tough when you're in charge of a
thing like the comedy bang bang show
you are a sensibly everyone's possible though
i didn't have hiring or firing power
that was the production company
um but yeah you're sensibly everyone's boss
it's your right no one can come
up to you and go like is
everything okay and and you're under in
production it will but maybe that's just
like any job you're under such a
results oriented schedule of like you have
to get this done otherwise all of
these millions of
dollars are wasted it feels like it's
on the pier in your case there
wasn't really someone who was doing the
same things as you but like if
there was an actor and another actor
could say are you okay yeah right
yeah because it's like the only person
who could really say that yes and
it could be that the producer of
the show asked if he was okay
like
i i don't know you know but
it was i also feel like if
you are that person and i've been
the person who is sensibly in charge
at times and i look i have
ah i get frustrated and i can
shut down and stuff like that but
i'm also the type of person that
can say hey everybody i'm sorry
i'm having a hard time with this
you know what i mean like that
yeah i call it out that makes
it somebody can just acknowledge a thing
and say i know this is a
drag i know i'm being a drag
right now i'm just having a hard
time with this thing getting this to
work you know whatever it is but
to just not acknowledge to be to
be miserable every day
day you know without any acknowledgement of
it but everyone else is not miserable
but i do think we are going
through something personal it's different than being
like oh i'm frustrated with this task
that we can't of course i'm slightly
you don't want to say because yeah
it's like what ever i never say
no and everyone on the crew knows
no there should be like there should
be one friend on every
i said thanks that they hired and
that you that like a sort of
entourage your st vinny had it right
in and eighteen in he was sitting
here there was no drama in his
life because he had three bros to
tell there was one time there was
literally what i i remember i stopped
watching that show and then when my
wife continued to watch it and there
was there was episode where apparently video
chase was supposed to be addicted to
cocaine and was real downfall yeah but
it was one interesting season where he
went through some struggles and then they
were like i was watching do that
anymore
say fun just to watch him have
a good time and not be all
depressed but i was watching this particular
episode he was on the tonight show
or something and oh yeah supposedly yea
we mean any yes someone in the
bathroom or in the last guy on
the show it's somebody going very poorly
and it's like he's the exact same
he's already different he's
not any different yeah he was fine
it was so weird like what she
told me yeah he's on coke and
he's fucking up his life i'm like
yes he seems exactly the same as
the last i saw the show well
maybe it's not the fault of the
writing
i'm not blaming the room my god
how dare you how dare you how
dare you um we gotta take a
break no we don't um no but
i think you're right i think that
in every job in every job we
could all every job at all reach
out to our coworkers
if they're frustrated and just say hey
everything going okay yeah and just see
true although she's out show business the
only job where you can get away
with that where you can be like
an unpleasant person oh yeah well i
know other jobs you have to be
like the boss do you know what
i mean or you have to be
you have to be unpleasant to
somebody who's a lateral well in hospitals
like doctors to nurses and stuff like
they have a god complex true i
am god
i got but i feel like nicole
kidman nah you can't be um mean
doctor you yuck be the good doctor
dr shaun murphy no but yeah i
mean nurses are always it feels very
scott that you know is if you
watched a lot of that very similar
to show business to me like there's
a hierarchy and where the doctors are
kind of like the stars of the
show and they get to treat there's
an operating theatre yes and there are
p h o yep
i find the term p a confusing
because it is used for so many
different things yeah yes and all assistant
sure public address
yes haw peer approved fizz what is
it with physician's assistant okay and other
necessary pieces piano set for piss ass
in his ass
we're gonna need to hire three piss
acids
it would be so funny to train
someone coming up she was gone i
got a job as their play on
the pitch when they're like doctor if
someone hurt
so you hire a bunch of p
a's and they don't know anything about
show business and you tell them that
npa stands for business and they go
through their entire career thinking it's piss
ass and then they start calling plays
pissed like i was a piss ass
for like five
i worked my way up oh that
would be so great
i want to have another show just
i could do that no just for
that reason to make people call themselves
a pizzo yeah only reason
not the good doctor i don't think
you should have a show well if
that's what you you're going to be
you shouldn't have a job and that's
why you're gonna be yeah i just
love the way you gotta li
shouldn't every person doing have foxworthy shouldn't
every person have a tv show at
least one yeah yeah at least one
only you know what i mean one
i wanna see what my mail man
would do with a full thirty it
would be fun to like every single
person in the world gets one shot
at a pilot presentation
wow like a three hundred grand budget
and every single person and there would
be someone and be a waste of
reasonable that at all and the government
the government pays for it and it's
like yeah my tackle and everyone has
to go into the army at some
point and in america everyone at some
point as the two pilot front or
figure out how from retire
at any point in your life yeah
yeah so if you do when you're
four you've ruined your job ruin your
shot yeah your or maybe you've been
like that that kid right boxes and
boxes toys i know it makes us
millions and millions of dollars i know
that kids are riches
and they're trying to shoot as many
as they could my friend was doing
was working on the show and they
were has your own box just like
a ball yeah i think it's usually
what exciting than that but zoe cells
trying to do probably a row because
he was getting older but they were
having only celebrities like dave grohl was
on it and stuff you cheeses because
everyone's kids like the youtube
e yeah the two young guys who
listen to songs they've never heard before
i was like guys you see when
they had barack obama that was really
cute i did not see it but
have they really some of these songs
i'm like you've never heard this well
isn't it the case that one of
em maybe has heard it and brings
it to the other i don't know
but they also they also get requests
so it's like phil comrades in the
air tonight that we're going to see
a world where you're like their fifth
album was i've never heard that before
is there ever yeah once i didn't
say they'd never heard of any saw
scott you're trying to put origin but
i do think the concept not really
doctor it's very cute it's a very
cute concept but it's like this should
be one video max
everyone wants to monetize every fun thing
that's true i do too so every
person gets one show and they you
can save it until you're you really
feel like you have a good idea
what if you die yeah if you
die before you get to do it
you have to donate your money to
a cause you don't like so it
kind of gives you this
sort of impetus so like what cuts
don't like like why you don't something
like antiabortion yeah something you're against and
then you then so you know i
better get this die to get this
done so to take long and so
you kind of some people dude squander
it early because they care about peta
i have to get this done before
yeah yeah so like if you're if
you're a make a wish child you
know the time is running out so
you gotta make your shush child if
your make-a-wish child you or your pilot
is yeah it's like it's just like
anyone else i mean like you have
your wish is separate of that shirt
no you get your wish okay so
let's really break down one of the
children
what if your make-a-wish is to not
make the presentation and keep the money
whoa that only works once wait once
in your life chose one one kid
and and whoever's everything everything's first yeah
and then maybe then they do that
ah we had to make a wish
clause yeah exactly and if and if
that kid dies then another kid turns
into that kid oh this is good
oh i love that so it's what
freaky friday know it's the make-a-wish clause
ah because what good is dead they
don't trade places yeah yeah but that
wait how am i dad are they
going to be him they're gonna be
him so what does that mean
p
but that is essentially trading places because
now what's the closest random place suddenly
paul if you were dead i'd trade
places with you then i'd be you
and then i be dead because it's
right good friday of like switching places
with the dentures and they're in hell
weekend at bernie's friday yes american alibi
the hell oh yes i made a
wish i just worked i didn't know
the guy was why i happen to
be dead and a sinner i was
just working with jonathan silverman and i
why a single guy sat list of
guy and i was talking to him
about something and then i asked him
was a simple lexi blues reboot
um wait why can i think of
the guy's name from oh andrew read
from mccarthy oh i know we talking
about him and i said do you
know him and then he said yeah
we didn't move back and dara oh
it was a movie i just was
talking i wasn't thinking anything yeah this
is a movie where i carried around
dead guys like we were
site huh i was like i made
you walk around ah one of course
i know what that is smoothly where
we carried around a dead guy but
i didn't know because i had been
writing i asked an obvious question right
yeah and then it would imply that
i've never seen that well is it
bad that i until you just said
it
i wouldn't have even have been able
to say who the stars a weekend
but i don't put him within and
he was like that's totally fine i
just honestly i always picture just bernie
when yeah but i mean two and
they're in like yeah we think you
should shoot him and injured people and
they were like nineteen years old or
something yeah yeah i think today like
three of those they definitely need to
i know they need to
i don't think they made a third
if there was a thirty it was
like a directive video sequel that those
guys weren't in do you want me
to look it up look it up
so high luck oh i wanna say
he's a really great guy he's very
fun look it up and we're on
good girl looking i'm looking at weekend
at bernie's fr
franchise
look look up we're going to bernie
i'm hoping the franchise the weekend at
bernie's
would you like to have a weekend
booze at your house huh
memorial pillow here everyone has a special
anniversary coming up would you like that
weekend at bernie's the joy of dye
to your anniversary party where a dead
man sits there toshio do you think
he's alive but he really is dead
but wearing sunglasses we in bernie's two
is the only thing that's coming up
here alright they do not take a
third bite yeah
they didn't know it was a modest
success grossing twelve point seven million against
a seven million dollar budget
um do they say anything about sql
no they don't that's so injured andrew
mccarthy i couldn't even tell you that
he ever did anything other than pretty
in pink he's done shopping fresh horses
mules part of the brick pack yeah
he directs a lot now does he
like get interesting luck
episode i was in and he waits
you work with both of the barrows
both of the bernie bros bernie guys
wow joe bernie bro not just on
the internet no that's blown out of
proportion
um have you worked with terry kiser
the titular bernie yeah no you know
i always think it's like richard dreyfus
huh
huh from jaws yeah the super big
guy my guy for mr holland's opus
yes the titular mister hollywood fl beautiful
beautiful beautiful koh hey that's something that
happens we can ver know what we're
gonna burn easy mr hollins signs beautiful
um yes he sings beauty
awful boy within his son cole is
there nice beautiful weekend at bernie's photo
challenge open mr allen's opeth so wait
i've never seen a holland's opus i've
never seen it he sings so in
the beautiful voice who is deaf and
he find first of all when i
was a kid i was really confused
by this maybe because they
show a scene where they take he
takes his son to a parade and
there's these fire trucks going by with
really loud sirens and all these kids
are crying in his kid is not
looking at his watch but i thought
he went deaf from that i didn't
know ah ah and then in very
calmly wet so this gave you a
fear
of firetrucks i just didn't get it
i was like that's the explanation for
why he's deaf and then ah because
he's just the first step that burnt
know what's the name mr hollande figures
out that his son is deaf that's
how they initially figured out oh because
he's a baby and he's a baby
say okay got it and he um
shoving his baby why aren't you crying
but this is a wicker stay you
too good for this so he then
he's a teacher by the way i've
only seen this like once and it
was yeah this is like nineties or
something he's like a profess he's like
come what does it conductor music guy
orchestra teacher and then he teaches all
these things and then his son grows
up she's older things and
then these things beautiful beautiful beautiful cole
two and when he's grown up he's
they're all grownups i think i think
i think that would be lame i
would like to watch that again i
just want you watched castaway it's nothing
like that has been thinking of rewatching
my god it's so subtle ten minutes
it was on
cable and oh my no exaggeration that's
all you've seen no no no i've
seen the whole thing in those theaters
at the burbank you seem to only
seen the last time it was like
what's the big deal to rewatch it's
on hbo max guy was sobbing at
this movie yeah and it's such a
good ending and i didn't know why
do you remember it all was so
good and when he's in the middle
in the fourth row
it's a little like a little lazy
i know i didn't love it but
the part with helen hunt or he
reconnects with her and there's that whole
reconnects with her but then he like
finally leaves her to her new life
and then he's literally walks outside of
her place and he's had a fork
in the road you just look at
how i'd gone oh what do i
do now and some chicken rolls up
and any direct
actions bad-boy no use wow have wish
yeah right outside of her house he
is a different day watch wade is
close he goes to return the package
that has kept him a lie this
entire piano and then he sees a
woman with the same symbol on her
car and she tells you know it's
it's actually really in their cult what
was the package what was in the
pack
that we don't know we don't know
but it was employee delivers it right
yeah because it had these angel wings
on it so he felt like i'm
not gonna open this oh right right
those are the place in the angel
wings everywhere it's like a big symbol
of this place ride spoilers for castaway
by the way yeah i do yeah
i do want to see that again
and it's also it's very unique to
in
robert zemeckis is movies because it's not
a big special effects movie it's very
there's only one special effects and that's
the human body that getting there that's
right he hit harrier he spent a
year letting his hair grow yes skinny
yeah i i do miss that era
of filmmaking
when big event movies didn't have to
have like huge concepts they were just
like you love this guy he's going
to do something fucking crazy yes movie
you know being that simple is what
makes it so good yeah like just
this character and then the beginning i
mean it's a really fun movie too
because he's i forgot everything about it
and he's like an kind of a
jerk a bit
at his job he's like really specific
about how we didn't watch the jerk
he's got that pingpong gas station or
something he hasn't mentioned with glasses because
everyone's eyes cross someone shot motor oil
no but i mean you realize is
like it's like he's like working on
the schedule and life is all about
getting packages right on time i love
above and then he's like nothing to
do for four years sub stay alive
oh another thing i didn't get that
i did that because that jogged my
memory of ah that whole thing with
the deaf kid i didn't when i
was just watching castaway i kind of
didn't get something that was happening
i a little bit later i was
like oh my god i'm so stupid
so there's a part where he may
all agree he like he's at the
end of his you know fucking role
i was gonna say rope but then
he has to go get this rope
so he's because he's trying to use
trying to offer them so no but
that's that's not so i think they
edited this also there's a there's a
trivia that i was looking at the
huh
like coyotes since it was in theaters
yeah because going to video great kelly
carla i look this up again susan
susan
so she okay what's his name tom
hanks he he's talking to wilson and
he's like i need fifty you know
i need thirty more feet of rope
to make this boat to escape and
then he was like i know where
it is but i don't want to
go get it it's i know i
don't want to go up there again
he climbs up really high he pulls
up a rope with a perfect new
saw
on it oh yeah with a big
log on it and in my head
he now he tried to kill him
yeah of course he was testing it
with this log but in my head
i go that last so crazy at
this summer that there was this new
saw on the island from like previous
so what did they cut up or
did they cut out
ever attempt suicide oh video you just
see that he pulls on disney baby
you guys okay i don't think no
i don't remember i remember there was
there have been something cut from the
beginning of the when they shot i've
been maybe a deleted they initially show
him it's weird that the volleyballs name
is wilson and his wife's name is
well i my
theory is that he needed to be
named wilson because he has a strong
connection he call her wilson he got
home he called the ball rita and
he calls
he calls his balls volunteer rita and
wilson oh um also it's the name
of the company's sports sports coach well
nobody said it had to be a
wilson ball because every character that he's
ever worked with any any any character
they become as close within a film
he has to have either the middle
name wilson or
huh sounds are free but right now
the way i'm thinking about volleyballs remember
that interview inside the extra studio but
he talked about this because he feels
like he's cheating if you know
it's like a kirk cameron thing what's
that because he's so religious he can't
kiss other actresses on screen oh so
he married his coworker them his wife
yeah oh and the public not getting
to see him fucking mad i watched
so his wife will always be will
always double for the kissing scene oh
so
that's that's really funny i watched she's
trying to hire her to kiss her
on edge oh and sushi and then
she has this woman for you
yeah where he stands in for her
okay you're gonna take either when i
didn't see this loophole coming
we to take a break a pic
huh
and we're back warren has a three
jersey each this was submitted by ken
edwards celebrity and edwards from the band
failure yeah awesome celebrity head is basically
the game fassbender explains an inglorious basterds
by the way
little trivia i just read which i'm
sure you know paul rust is in
inglorious basterds that's a little trivia i
know i've never seen it but um
your little trivia i know male masters
olden correctly but the trivia i know
so brad pitt is in it he
quentin tarantino's supposedly like a script was
nine years old it wrong and he
clay
named her man juicy that i've heard
scripts are rife with spelling yes and
he was like that's because both words
are spelled wrong right i believe he
didn't know how to spell those words
but i think okay yeah everybody is
someone we all know boy that's the
truth could be a real live person
or fictional fictional character as long as
they're fairly ubiquitous each player is assigned
their celebrity by the person to their
left it's a secret usually write it
on a post-it and put it on
the player's forehead then everybody takes turns
asking yes or no questions about who
they are nobody can ask the same
question as someone else did per rotation
for instance if lawrence asks am i
a boy and then scott asks am
i a girl pull up to wait
until the next rotation to ask about
his characters gen
nder if that's what he is curious
about first person to guess correctly wins
but your guess is your questions so
don't waste around unless you can guess
my friends i usually keep playing until
everyone has guessed there's an offer hints
after awhile thanks freedom boys okay so
how should we do it since we
don't want to do posts on our
heads we should just like oh and
we can't get nearly so we text
each other
yeah let's text each other so all
ties technology just like fassbender did it
in glorious yes altec scott
um and i'll text paul and well
ticks lauren wait
if you're asking am i whatever you
know what i this you know why
that yeah no no no you're you're
texting who i am i'm texting paul
who he is paul sexing you who
you are and we have to guess
who and we have to guess who
we are like but i'm telling you
who you are
ah what am i telling you oh
that's right wait wait i read the
rules again who are we telling the
person to your leisure leftward let's see
i think what it should be is
you're okay you're you're i know how
about in my head i know who
you are and you're telling paul who
i am and meanwhile got it okay
yeah i'm yeah
so i'll tell paul scott is so
and so yeah and i'll tell you
paul is so and so okay and
lauren i'll tell you that i am
so and so why okay this didn't
work out so
um okay so it's gotta be someone
ubiquitous okay got it gotta be a
bigot has gotta be someone got it
alright so i have texted lauren who
you are all okay and i've texted
paul who scott is so high tech
scott who lauren is okay
wonderful
a u k
how many times you text me a
day and you know when he or
you're saying i'm scott walker we had
a whole
six you about zero the hut
that's a long time just because he
drives a zero laser power gunboat fan
boat um
okay text me that shit homie
come on come on get gimme ah
can we do fictional people as well
yes yes but well no not really
when you take one
oh no you should ask a bunch
of questions about process and have them
all be the opposite of what you
want to know i'm just trying to
fill up time here okay got it
alright
so now we're lauren why don't you
start and you ask a question about
by me yes me me me and
and we both know the answer and
we can confer an answer is that
what it is yeah yes okay god
is correct am i tall no no
um am i a man yes whoa
yes nice
am i alive
we should establish if it talks
alive in the isn't an memorable to
assume yeah that item arrive yes yes
so you're fictional interesting yeah we give
you that one
he's looking for someone who's looking for
somebody somebody's like a versa online helicopter
um am i a woman
no
okay
i forget who you are oh that's
right um okay so i'm a man
ah
am i ah a fictional character no
no i'm a real live human man
oh i don't know if i'm alive
okay paul um
am i male
yes
why didn't you ask that isn't that
part of the yeah but two people
can two in a row can't not
in a in a round okay got
it
am i
um fictional
no yes yes you are
so i'm not tall i'm fictional i'm
not a woman got it
am i alive currently yeah yes oh
yeah baby yeah
am i powerful
um
i in a certain way but not
really no
um am i related to a holiday
um i mean in a way not
tangentially not primarily okay
um
have i won an oscar no well
shit
i want to do
i'm sure he did too really oh
interesting oh shit
no extra toxin
we gotta do some of the villain
time while paul thinks of a question
am i contemporary no
right yeah i'd say that
am i female you're still not right
i mean male i'm sorry i mean
no god did you use it
it's the same question over
am i an actor yeah yes hutch
it
thank you to be you ever yeah
we turn into the versa
m i
very intelligent no no no am i
male
yeah cheese
yeah i know that's gonna be like
something like that wasn't was that really
i just wanted to narrow it down
okay okay so i'm male i'm not
tall and i'm fictional got it am
i primarily a television actor yes yes
okay yes yeah okay got it got
it
am i
like goal yes yeah
are these yes or no questions or
are they just like questions yes or
no there yes or no am i
fassbender laid it out for you and
when he invented this game i'm staring
at his dong am i an animal
no no
um
am i was my most popular show
on during the nineties
no
okay no but it's close okay interesting
go
am i human no new m i
dancer from a movie
ah you were sure
you have been you have been but
it's not what i'm known for nah
not especially
oh my god um am was was
my ah most popular show on during
the two thousands yeah yes okay the
twenty first century interested
ah
do i have a favourite food ah
pry am i known for having a
favorite food i don't think i don't
think so
um am i from of popular tv
show you were
ah but not originally who i don't
have kobe just everyone knows oh got
my risen your carry person you're done
here you're up cleaning in digital i
make statements
by the way i don't have covered
either
um okay um a two thousand s
am i a sitcom star
yeah huh but non non-committal i got
yeah okay
ah to move faster yes it's hard
though this isn't so random it's rounded
ah why don't we start making some
guesses and we just go that's so
far off or that's close and my
part of the disney universe no no
am i um am i from a
comic book no no um am it
was my most popular show a drama
no okay but there was some drama
okay well then why when i said
my sitcom starting with yeah maybe not
current
me as i would it is yeah
that's that's really nice it's like john
stowe i'm joking really starting to say
on saying when i say like my
sitcom star we need to speed this
close it down with a filibuster well
you don't even have a question yes
he does look yes i do what
is it see knows i just need
to wet the whistle
yeah yeah that's it now your question
that i have been saving up but
ah gee am i merchandised yeah yeah
am i from disney no no um
i am i
am i am i am i caught
i don't know any shit comes from
the two thousand am i from one
of those shells shows paul was talking
about watching the three inner foreign row
no i don't actually know
ah am i still popular no
i don't think so you know i
agree am i um human being ah
yes in the along with everything that
we've talked about meeting you're not a
real human being right but yeah you
are kamikaze humanoid
cartoon i don't want to say okay
you're a humanoid got it um am
i right
i don't want to waste one okay
so um was i on must see
tv on thursday nights no shit
sitcom is that was misleading okay don't
stick with i mean in the sense
it's not but it's like it's not
how he's going to get there no
okay so my most popular thing wasn't
a sitcom yeah okay go ahead um
but it wasn't a drama either
huh what could have been reality show
oh i'm just speaking out loud because
we're waiting for your question yeah well
luckily to my earphones ah are you
am i are you me
do you want do you want a
letter no okay okay sorry i'm impatient
people love this right now they all
don't know where on the edge of
their hopefully bringing a while i i
think we should do is or oh
no i have a question should we
drop in who we were at the
beginning of the game i don't think
so because it's gripping well let's ask
josh okay let's ask producer josh if
he thinks sam iris gosh yes you're
fixing wow
nonhuman ubiquitous
okay so here i'm fictional characters male
are not powerful necessarily i'm not contemporary
i'm not very intelligent i am comical
i'm not human i have no favorite
food i am not a disney character
i am merchandised and i am not
still popular yeah okay describes it perfectly
when i when we say you're not
a disney character you're not
like associated with it but you actually
can i just say a little follow
up subsidiary and at disneyland you're a
subsidiary of disney but you're not a
disney character weird yeah that should be
a major tip okay i think and
i haven't asked a question yet right
wow didn't you can make a guess
and my roger rabbit yeah
yes we gave you gave it to
believe there was no way i'll cut
poppa lee's ok now here's a question
though our characters favorite food i don't
remember him ever known i don't remember
but it's funny and definitely but the
powerful thing like he has more powers
than a human being does right but
he's not like she's not a power
yag yes ok am
i have no idea what's going on
with me right now yeah am i
well try to maybe try to narrow
down my handsome know let's go where
you came from maybe um am i
so am i oh what a sweet
question wait if i'm an actor but
my main thing isn't a comedy or
a drama
dramedy is impossible my god um okay
it was i on an nbc show
my main neuroscience ctv you really are
and you're not
no okay just like go you didn't
get it
didn't get wet i didn't lose i
lost the game scrying the the guy
didn't get on nbc okay i said
must see tv to say thursday and
then now i'm asking generally nbc should
have started there you should just shut
the fuck up
before you said hey literally no clue
why did you hear once you tried
to figure out like where you originated
okay what i mean because you we've
said is not common my friend saw
movie it's not comic strip yes queen
okay okay was i on my my
big most famous thing was it abc
yeah
you were an abc but was it
my big most famous no it was
not your big most famous thing was
am i truly brown yes yay
okay so i tall i'm not a
woman you're i am male i'm not
handsome i am a humanoid
i'm from a town that's charlie brown
come to love it if people describe
the vegas humanoids well this is like
jeopardy like oh humanoid answers in jeopardy
you would never ask the question and
then have the answer be humanoid when
matt lauer addresses lucy oh right god
it was related to his big weird
sex things yeah it was like he
was aware that they're like okay everyone
knows how to put on a ca
costume
his office door and then put on
the lucy costume are they going to
talk about this in the morning show
this next season oh my god okay
look so keep going you gotta help
me out with this so during a
hint yes cable
huh very in right now google tv
it's very right in the tooth oh
ah
okay but not a drama but there
was some drama there was some drama
but not a drum okay so was
it an hbo show yeah yes was
it okay so this is two thousand
and hbo show what it wasn't the
sopranos because i don't know um don't
be mad at wow i'm mad at
the situation
tion
um
what else is on hbo come on
you know this know it how am
i fucking supposed to know it guys
have no clues do you want another
clue we've already this is where i
know i'm an actor who's still alive
who is on an hbo show in
the two thousands the n dead said
it wasn't a drama it wasn't a
comedy but there was some drama
how the fuck do i am i
supposed to know it from that because
when you get it you get it
yes
if a show has some drama i
mean it's extensively more comedic than dramatic
right but it's not a comedy you
said am i barry oh
that straddles that line here the actor
right um here and not a fictional
character know on honest show i know
this show is a show we have
discussed you have not won an oscar
we've discussed it today you didn't even
ask that fucking question that's a gimme
did we discuss it today
yes we discuss an hbo show today
oh my yeah on the show made
a joke similar to the joke i've
been making
that you aren't getting i don't know
i'm lost on that one oh yes
i don't even know i don't know
i don't care i don't care okay
lol right grace though every martian is
like oh you won't go there think
of other hbo shows just come on
game of thrones oh no ah a
little bit of drama game of thrones
so i don't know two thousand
like it's not on anymore
well game of thrones isn't on guys
so you can't throw that one's already
been eliminated oh is it entourage yes
am i little bit of drama c
o so i'm one of those guys
i don't even know their name actor
adrian grenier no ah what's his name
dylan kevin dough ah whoever played e
zinc and obvious oh jeremy pivot yeah
yes how was that night i can
guarantee you no one listening to this
news jeremy piven until well wait at
least two minutes before i wake
wait till you you'll never listen back
to this now and we said a
little bit of drama many times and
i bet to thank you earlier in
the episode said it has some drum
yeah you know i mean like it
was like this was a whole thing
we were doing it's bad you guys
suck no we don't talk you said
this you suck at this game you're
the only one who didn't guess we
you guys got me
major fucking hands you knew it was
a touchstone are you kidding and that
his character appeared at disneyland boy's mind
always tough so knowing come up subsidiary
of disney yes i never ever thought
this agenda said it was a subsidiary
did i say was a character that
does not automatically translate to touch so
what other movie companies or subsidiaries
was mine obvious i was not tall
i was not handsome but i was
not a woman trump's charlie brown right
there australia you're saying those original description
charles schulz wrote humanoid
now he sold it to the paper
we got a rap show about a
humanoid charlie brown thanksgiving this humanoid celebrating
this episode that's about an hour and
ten come on we're good alright alright
guys it is new year's eve and
i stopped all from singing this last
week because he was way too early
but here we go
nah you just say flutter you too
new
his new yea oh we sound like
um when danny tanner and and joe
uncle joe in uncle jesse would sing
a are these people from full house
with little who are these people you
talking about rockin law will lower bud
michelle
like what would they sing to michelle
you emily the teddy bear
huh guys we hope that you're doing
well out there don't ah god speaks
for himself don't get crazy i mean
look don't drink and drive don't drink
and drive don't drink and drive and
it's about that don't go anywhere for
that matter you'll go away where don't
do anything be safe this was a
rough year for everybody we hope you're
you
you're hanging in there still for twenty
twenty is going to be in the
rear view in just a few hours
and hopefully this new year will bring
good things and we really appreciate you
listening and i've already been vaccinated because
i'm a celebrity and i have a
special love to undermine who we know
who's gonna get it first
i know a health care worker is
getting but that's except that's right yeah
i'm sure my sister's good but i'm
saying nurse i maybe she'll give me
some runoff getting it maybe she'll give
me like part like every celebrity over
he's gonna get it first and we'll
i'll be like of course and who's
gonna die from it kevin hart vaccinations
are poised don't say that all the
presidents are gonna go get it i
can't wait to get those microchips injected
into me
bill gates contract by everyone
well look twenty twenty one is going
to be better for everyone hopefully so
at least some ninety percent of the
people i wouldn't but hang in there
everybody we really appreciate listening we love
doing this show and we really we
love hearing from you and it's um
i'm glad that we that we all
have this together entourage really is one
of those special shows that isn't funny
and isn't dramatic so you're right
but supposed to be funny but also
i don't care about the drama yes
so i mean i get where you're
coming from but well i like it
and it was just madness drama that
character that we were referring i know
i know now in retrospect that paul
was referring to it for real so
to answer the call to try to
figure out what a show is by
hearing it's not a drama not a
comedy entourage shooter
just pop trade him i never said
it wasn't a drama we said it
had a little bit of drama and
we didn't say it was a comedy
we just said we did at one
point say that he was come star
which technically on treasures it was a
half hour wasn't right so guys were
hoping you were hoping you're doing well
out there okay entourage pioneered the half
hour show but that's not really funny
not really i love that show i
don't care but we know we're doing
well we hope by doing well we
just wanna say the same three things
for another five minutes and then we'll
let you go i just want to
say hey joe
okay ma gonna
like i hang up now
alright we'll see you in twenty twenty
one ah wei dan bay
da da da da yeah oh any
way when each day
nah coming in the back selenium were
all xy
hi long la rose twenty one anyway
ah yes yeah raw starting january
nah and there willing
a good
when everyone died is there new year
oh wow possible ah a merry christmas
y'all building alone
uh