hey everybody it's scott paul and lauren
and scott paul and lauren got paul
and laura and we want to tell
you about a podcast called three um
that's right it's ah podcast that's been
going for about three years and we're
about to start our fourth year
on thursday november eighteen can you believe
it thursday november eighteenth the fourth season
of three am drops to the world
this is going to be a big
day for you you clear your schedule
clear your schedule it's our ma if
you don't tell everyone to clear your
schedule call your mom and tell her
that you love her that everyone she's
ever met loves her call your mom
and say i listened to three-day you
can't change
me wow three items for the kids
and you just wouldn't understand mom yeah
you're old and in the ground tell
her that but it's coming out season
four were coming out for a brand
new year of threesome and it's as
easy as looking at your calendar and
saying oh shit it's november eighteenth what
did stop on
lauren wants to do they wanted us
to get through to him wherever we
get our podcast just subscribe now and
then when it shows up it shows
up not sure about season four here's
a sneak preview
okay you guys if you don't fucking
leave right now
i swear to god you look okay
no you've offended me
he still was holding the knife why
would why would that person hold that
knife that way i'll never know help
me help me so i mean that's
what he was saying oh okay i
don't need help right now i wouldn't
help you if you thought you needed
help so the flower was gently floating
down like the petals work yeah the
stamen was you
you know obviously separated from about the
pistols the pistols
i'm so high why did we get
high during this episode to be bad
i ching the tao every bad thing
you guys ever done i know
that's why i decided to get a
divorce oh no it makes sense to
me yeah yeah against her enough help
help me what's wrong for scare her
oh i thought you didn't help with
the story but you need help right
now yes no it's fine officer we're
doing a podcast no way yeah we
have a permit no worry
got away
anyway so that's a little taste of
what is going to be this season
on three of them sounds pretty exciting
does it taste good because you say
sweet things on your tongue and salty
things in the back yeah let's just
say yeah
anyway three dm is a lot like
the tip of your tongue and it's
on the tips of everyone's tongue because
people are gonna be talking about this
show so much and you're gonna able
to believe you're not going to be
believe what happened with ethereum yeah so
three three three
can't wait see you then see you
on november eighteenth anywhere podcasts or i
hate to leave this promo without discussing
how sephora theme is very similar to
the gyp theme but we don't have
to don't have time because we can't
hear getting ready for the next season
will bring up the crisis
see you that on november eighteen lauren
take us out november eighteenth of a
routine routine
yeah