three
oh
um yea yea yeah i meant to
say yeah but it turned to do
a yea your freak i feel like
yay is the upgrade from yeah it
really it's like yeah plus yeah we
started with yeah and they were like
how do we make this
is better
do you think anyone in their life
has an ironically said yea yeah i
say yes fucking know i i mean
when it was first invented like did
they did someone say it and and
someone transcribed and said man i gotta
put that into the dictionary like someone
say yay when somebody said yay did
someone else over
here at say i gotta put this
in the dictionary and just described the
trips crime i sent away to barrels
it's a palindrome you know it's got
to owen burrows a people's court and
yea whenever i'm like when a palindromic
expressions mean a lower lab guess i
just won't tell you something um when
i heard i'm listening my name is
paul f tompkins my name is scott
ackerman and i'm listening when i also
have frazier and i'm listening
hey i'm also singing dosa aladdin's great
grandma things that yes yes did you
know that well this is a freedom
bombshell lauren i'm so happy we're breaking
this email that i can do that
but that is kelsey grammer ah i
don't know if i knew that but
that sucks
i really know happy to hear new
sucky info you know what like he
was a huge character on reality recap
yeah yeah um on real housewives of
beverly hill was his wife isn't with
ex ex-husband of community we'll marry her
when they did
when she did her season would hear
on the show yeah and he's like
i'm going to do a broadway show
and i wonder to have a thing
so it's good that she's doing this
and then he gets divorced start within
like the season and she has been
cheating on her in new york the
entire time when oh when this broadway
apartment with patti lupone yes he went
for an older actress
know who anyway i mean he's a
young woman i e o the same
without someone very young um so anyhoo
i was just gonna tell you guys
that when i first moved to l
a i tried to get a job
as a transcribe or person really for
reality shows or for just transcribing things
that people would send like hey lee
listen to this audio for shows like
it was um the test so i
someone i knew who i knew your
story straight okay hold on trying um
during the summer you can have a
glass of water i don't feel like
ah
oh give me a sandwich
i knew somebody who did this job
and so and it paid like decently
i remember i feel like it was
like fifty a lot of like you
see improvisers did this for reality shows
okay why didn't know this was before
i don't remember cool cool i'm doing
to me did it a little bit
oh weird yeah so the woman i
went to the woman's like office slash
house and she gave me
me a dvd to transcribe as like
my test and i had to like
download this software and the dvd was
like of some a and e show
like you know like someone who's like
i can't stop picking out my hair
like whatever
i i transcribed it and i think
i really should go work until i'm
trapped in a wig store
and i thought yeah i everyone thinks
i'm highly lately because it was true
yes i keep laughing weird and also
i posted that video of me crying
dancing to chicken in the corn which
i don't think scott has probably seen
i've ever seen
um but any writing like in a
in in the spencer
got it
anyways um i didn't get the job
and i don't know why huh oh
wait you were gonna say the test
what was the test i did the
test i put the transcribe the show
transcribed it i thought i did a
really good job i'm a very good
typist but dan wasn't not fast enough
i don't know i she just never
called me back i like what and
gave it to her and law
it and then i just didn't get
the job and you know it's really
at a point where i wasn't being
like particularly like i didn't really care
i guess i was kind of like
well you're still being sitting right between
that movie or some movies starring yeah
yeah but i just remember that it
was like a weird little thing i
tried to do and i didn't get
it interested what's the weirdest job you've
ever had paul i mean we've talked
about the how
that store
we have gone down in deep detail
of every job have we talked about
my my medical reenactments no no we
sure haven't
well did it take place at a
restaurant and well i was working a
bigger square at the time but i
needed extra money okay so now i
have this in the contest absolutely helpful
red booths i was in santa maria
california working alternating working for dean witter
and bigger square and neo flex three
famously sucks is that correct well guadalupe
does guadalupe
that's so which by the way i
was listening to del the funky homo
homo sapien the other day and he
mentioned doing a show in guadalupe and
i remember i was living in santa
maria when i bought that album and
i thought that was very funny that
he mentioned that the next town over
that sucks so bad well maybe not
everyone thought it sucked okay um so
i was hired
by the local nursing school they needed
actors so they put a they put
a folder they just saw you and
they're like you must act you got
the look about you this was the
dumb door yeah you gotta think you
could have something caught in your ass
we need you to
you look unwell
this was the santa maria nursing school
something like that yeah i don't know
some some nursing the local nurses yeah
the local nursing school so they put
a notice up at the f a
theatre school i was out for actors
and they said we will pay you
ten dollars for about two hours work
and then there was a stampede
at the time but you were like
sweet because i mean something like that
you're like i'm getting paid to act
ten dollars sure before yeah i mean
now i can call myself an actor
but it wasn't like it wasn't um
a full-time job or anything so it
wasn't like a big time commitment was
like hey come over come over here
on a saturday well it was like
i already had three
jobs it's ten dollars and we expect
you to be here monday through friday
tonight every two hours and yeah my
dogs are be down i wouldn't take
ten dollars for two hours if he
were a regular jobs what i'm saying
like on a saturday scott i i
have other jobs i haven't mentioned actually
now that you're reminding me of these
acting jobs that i had okay heard
alright oh i don't think i made
up some jobs while you were talking
so
ah so i went i went i
agreed to do it my my roommate
and i agreed to do it and
we got there and they said okay
well basically what we're doing is we're
giving them good we're giving the nurses
their final exams and they have to
practice on really on real life have
told us this but keep going i've
told it to you on coming back
to me but
go on so i don't know if
it was on this podcast i was
the person who they said okay you
are going to be in a wheelchair
and the nurse is going to adjust
your wheelchair and they have served me
well they have to do all of
these things and including they have to
lock the wheels on the wheelchair that's
like the most important thing that we're
checking so they don't go round
and round so that so that you
suddenly don't like you know drift other
room roll out of the room or
whatever so that was the thing that
i was doing and then my roommate
was supposed to be in a hospital
bed or he got into a hospital
bed and he was was never going
to be anything yeah
hey d jumps right in
but they were going to change his
bedpan they were gonna like mine shady
and i've good poop in it no
so they are going to shit in
it
isn't it
it was all going to be mine
but they have the real bed they
weren't doing space where they didn't have
they didn't they weren't mining old town
style oldtown our town what does the
whole channel oldtown her hometown when the
town slash when you have a bedpan
in a hospital bed is it in
the bed
well they they give it to you
and they go yeah here you go
slide this
see what you can do with this
i mean good luck i don't get
how it works if you were like
someone who couldn't get out of bed
how you basically turned on you you'd
turn on your side and you you
you do it yeah love nature ticket
school i don't believe this you should
i think it's a good deal i
tested these nurses they're out there doing
rogue bedpans if not all right so
so the thing that they that the
thing that they were checking for my
roommate was do they pull the curtain
to give him privacy because otherwise then
everyone can see what's going on in
their pan this guy's shit and so
for
or are the the two people that
did both of our tests the guy
who did mine did not lock the
wheels and the guy who did my
roommates did not pull the curtain and
so i got to watch my friend
pretend to take a shit into his
bedpan and he was mortified was your
weekend mortified because i'm sitting there literally
next
i'm watching this and lousy again the
entire time he wasn't naked what's this
hospital where there would be you'd be
right next to this guy's bed because
i was there i was in the
room next to him in the wheelchair
in the book but that's two in
the curtain room next well that you
talk to our hospital system our healthcare
system putting all these people so close
together
and in my opinion everyone should get
their own room men shouldn't be nurses
and this is the proof yes i
fully agree a show mormons job
um just like all cats are girls
and all dogs are boys thank you
all doctors are boys and all good
nurses are girls i was ten dollars
well-earned well i was just reminded from
that story of a job i had
when i moved out here that i
don't think i've mentioned on this show
it was a murder mystery dinner theater
show have i told oh no
no no oh my god okay
where to be so excited right yeah
where to begin okay so um my
my boyfriend at the time was a
part of this thing and it was
the grammar yeah and he's saying those
reality show i'm going to do some
theatre and why don't you do your
liver reality is like let's go to
long beach
the so i did it sometimes and
the he would he would do it
like every saturday did it sometimes and
i will i started like you know
participating um on your own or they
were know with with him and like
um and then there were other something
other people for my improv community were
a part of it and then other
than that
that it was like people that i
i don't know how they got to
be part i guess just actors so
i um i would have different roles
throughout throughout the time so some dinner
theater yes so you have to pretend
that you're dinner oh i thought you
have is you have as many roles
as you want and yeah you can
also have as many i usually get
one role as bad dinner you got
paid them
so don't fill up on bread you
gotta do
so the role that i typically had
was that i was there alone but
my sister was supposed to yeah i
played dumb fish
my sister was called it was it
was my sister was supposed to show
up but she was late and so
i was kind of by myself and
so there's this whole part in the
beginning it's such a nightmare so you're
like a a diner you're playing a
diner yeah watching the everyone pretty much
is except for two people who were
all always men until like way later
into the whole thing
ng but they were the detectives and
so they'd come out and have like
the comedic sort of performance where they
go through the script and kind of
like so everyone was in like a
dining room in this place yeah you're
in like some people would roll at
a hotel got oh i'm sorry sorry
yeah so the idea is you're at
this dinner and then all of a
sudden there's somebody killed right on and
then
exactly yeah and then it's like we
have to solve this and so everyone's
trying all the people at the table
are trying to figure out who the
killer is oh my god completely all
the people at the table trying to
figure out who the killer is i
feel like i've got like sixty bucks
a show i don't know if that's
even true um it sounds good but
i don't know if that's true sounds
good to stop sure
yes nobody was so many our wheelchairs
with so many hours because you have
to drive kind of far which jesus
show and then you had to get
there really early and then you know
it's just a long that was a
long thing so
i was usually by my side but
it was a nightmare for me honestly
especially at this time in my life
because i feel like i have gotten
more comfortable being weird and public i
guess but at the time it was
like it was like twenty three or
something and i'm like whoa man i
have to like walk around these people
and pretend that i'm here by myself
but so there's like a cow
cocktail hour and my character would have
to be a part of that and
there's like these sort of questionnaire you're
walking around kind of like filling out
with people like it's kind of an
activity and i know you're working there
at the time or they do know
they think i'm just so ideally they
think i'm a dumb asshole okay so
they think that i'm just and i'm
like them and my sister is
is not here and i saw some
room for her and she's not here
and so we go through this whole
thing and you know some people will
talk to me and then they start
to say like i think you're an
editor you know whatever like there's like
tires like that and then i would
say that's one thing i hate about
these things is everett no one wants
to be tricked so they're always yeah
i think your thing like just go
just
just have fun i know don't try
to outsmart it that's like when you
go to a magic show oh i
know how you did that trick yeah
it's so stupid so and this is
as good as a magic show honestly
because it was yeah such a good
trick so yeah i would be at
the table with like eight people or
something and waiting when there's an empty
seat next year my sister supposed to
be so that i have my like
alibi or whatever my story and and
we sit there they'll don't have to
talk to these random people the whole
time it's really like being in a
weird wedding like you just like with
strangers yeah and then in the middle
of it okay then at a certain
point the detective asks um someone you
know for volunteer and i raised my
hand a lot of people do of
course
i raise my hand then i get
picked and i say that that he
basically can i say i'm i'm an
aspiring actress and then i he hasn't
somebody i know it
he has me do a scene with
an um with another person from the
audience so like a regular person why
always like attentive you're making new dude
yeah it's like there's all these little
performances that like people get up and
drill it's like someone would be like
audition for american idol and then they
would like saying i'd be horrible and
i was like are you still looking
like you know like so does that
wayne show
it wasn't replaceable here i was just
murder what does yeah what is the
pretext for gamble this is what this
is what happens so okay wait i'm
mistress wants to skip over your first
time just get to what happened what's
the pretenses that they're like let's see
if some talents to some real people
get up and do stuff so why
is there a talent show in the
middle
yeah resuscitation doesn't normally happen
i guess it's just to like break
the ice or some shit i don't
know wow always an important step in
a murder investigation that's gonna hurt i
will not try to argue that the
scripts were good at all okay this
is like really i know we want
i'm just curious like oh no i
unattractive would say i don't really
remember but they but they certainly they
would be like interrogating people it'd be
like sure we understand that so i'd
be like who do they think and
then i got hurt they were having
trouble with this and going into the
talent he hasn't
where are you from who are you
here with that kind of thing and
it leads to some sort of like
everyone saw someone stands up in visiting
weird or like whatever it's like it's
totally okay so it's silly you gotta
like that at the top so
i get up and now now i'm
trying to remember though because i think
i know better shut up i think
i think i might of had two
different parts but there was one point
where i had to get slapped by
another actress who was in the cast
so i don't let this alright so
i know i know so the scene
was like i saw i think i
think it must have been though i
was doing the scene this like acting
scene and then they'd have another actor
get up and then they'd be like
okay we're we're gonna read these scripts
whatever and she was slapped me and
then during the rehearsal one day she
slapped me so hard that it like
really hurt and i was like during
the rehearsal yeah yeah and it sucked
and so that's just a side memory
but so
then we apologize or yeah but it
was it was really it was really
weird and then i don't i mean
and then i get killed okay so
basically there's a slap the lights go
out i scream
and then when the lights come back
up you're dead yeah yeah i'm trying
yeah i mean it doesn't happen that
way i have some there's there's light
so light goods come back up and
it's like i'm absolutely and rose out
of the i have a stab wound
i'm remembering this i'm i haven't i
haven't thought about this in like ten
years did you have i established to
yourself in the dark there's like something
under the shirt or something that was
already
laid i care for my height or
part of your shirt you reveal yeah
something happened and then something happened and
the lights go out again then i
like i like taken out or whatever
and it's like what then and then
that was always kind of good because
i'd be done really early but the
other part of me no longer did
you have to bow at the end
i usually had to stay because oh
my my wax was in
so ah then the well the i
what i'm remembering about how bad it
was is that i really wasn't good
at screaming yet like i feel like
ah like i think i there was
a period of my life where like
i could not say i could not
i could not laugh i could not
act scream or act laugh without it
being like really challenging for me for
some reason you did earlier in the
show
that was when i accused you of
being high yeah that was fake um
but i heard is good
ah but i my screen i think
was so bad like i'm like i'm
just thinking about how funny it must
have been because i think i was
like like a suburb know that's that
was good i was like ah like
i think it was like nah
huh doe married obey anyway anyway so
i did that for a bit but
it was opposite i mean i've always
wanted to do one of those shows
my friend did one of those shows
he did it in a big mansion
with like twelve rooms and everyone would
follow whomever they wanted in the cas
to well room to
get fancier for sure what they were
doing and my friend was the butler
who no one ever followed and that
at some point in the night help
at some point in the night everyone
was watching what lean ship was supposed
to be led into a bathroom up
at the top of the the mansion
where he was supposed to have committed
suicide so basically like at a certain
point everyone follows all the cast members
he goes upstairs gets into the bathroom
and then like lays in the tub
like he's committed suicide never won
it comes in at a certain point
and sees this is the butler this
is the butler yeah right and he's
like the boring guy and then he
told me that in one show one
performance one guy just really wanted to
follow him and that had never happened
to him before so he just like
he's sort of freaking out like what
am i supposed to do yeah so
we just got
yeah he just kinda like clean silverware
wipes out things for a while and
then he's like well it's getting time
to where i have to commit suicide
and you've never done this before but
he just gets into the bathtub in
his clothes and with the guys still
watching with a guy just sitting there
in a small
all bathroom just looking at him and
that's so rude then he turns pretends
to turn on the water and then
takes out pretend razor blades and slits
his wrists and then just lies there
and the guy just like sits there
watching so goofy so unnerving we you
know i just was listening to um
midnight
snack oh no yeah it was but
i was thinking something else i was
listening to michelle collins podcast midnight snack
and she had on this guy jeff
morrow who has a cookbook coming i'm
not trying to plug the whole thing
but just because that's your story it
is he was able to look up
but he was in tony and tina's
wedding in chicago deena yeah yeah i've
heard of it yes i've never seen
it i i've never seen it either
it ran for
ever write probably stopped running somewhere yeah
it was out here in new york
in new york as well yeah so
he was in that and he eventually
became tony but he was saying that
like he worked his way up to
thirty did he was the way he
was a waiter first men he was
tina that he was getting people like
what always like there'd be like drunk
guys who'd be trying to
to get you to break characters if
you'd go to the bathroom cause they'd
had to go to the bathroom the
high places everyone because it's like they're
part of the same wedding it's like
a whole point that's just like on
maybe like you hey man do some
coke like what's your deal like tell
us whatever and then he told a
crazy story where they were doing like
they were just dancing you know it's
like it's a full wedding it's a
play where
it's interactive due to the wedding and
it's everyone's the guest at this wedding
this is ah is is the ceremony
included or is it just a reception
so this is a ceremony to a
church and then like built-in stage within
piper's alley where second city isn't chicago
and then right then there's like a
reception and ah this man was dancing
with one of
the bridesmaids and then he died ooh
he was going morty and had a
heart attack or something and died and
then people all the actors knew it
was real but everyone else kinda thought
it was part of the show it
was like a good five minutes before
like anyone was really reacting properly they
should you should just stop a show
i mean paul this happened to you
right someone had a heart attack during
airshow yeah die but had a heart
attack yeah one reason i was performing
in london and the guy had a
heart attack show is not more important
than giving this guy proper medical of
course they got i mean the actors
on the show the cast was calling
nine one one like it was happening
but the people around thought it was
part of the thing sure and then
the um he he died and then
like they broke you know for a
little bit like deal with us and
then the guy the boss did make
the show go on oh he was
like people can get their money back
if they want but we're going to
the show must go on and he
was like it's just because they were
too cheap to give her one that
right yeah oh yeah that's also the
show must go on was a saying
that was started by tightwads who ran
the entertainment district so wait paul were
you doing stand-up yeah i was turning
down one when london it was pretty
much halfway at the halfway point of
my set and i heard this guy
i heard somebody in the audience go
oh and i honestly thought like oh
shit this guy's reviews are ready yeah
i really i honestly thought it was
a reaction when i was doing
and then i heard some like some
like like urgent you know talking and
um more or somebody than your normal
heckling yes usually they were terrible you're
terrible to see
ah um and somebody said he's he's
i think he's had a heart attack
and so the we stopped the show
lights came up and i was like
ah this was a moment where i
later was haunted by it because i
realized this is who i am in
a crisis i did not know what
to do
and so you ran all the way
no but i was just like kind
of standing there like like trying to
like seeing what was happening what was
going on and then it was this
yeah who were like trying to assess
the situation because you you're in the
middle of a thing you can't quite
tell yeah i felt like it was
a weird thing where okay i'm on
stage literally
there's lights on me with a microphone
i feel like i should be doing
some of the situation yeah yeah but
i don't shell wanting to do i
don't know what to do and so
somebody came up to me and said
um would you like to should we
want why don't we pause the show
when we stop and and we'll clear
out the audience you are still yes
a good idea like this this person
this person from the stuff is feeding
me what to do like in a
gentle way like as if i'm in
shock which maybe girl is i don't
know also in your paul f tompkins
character yes i hate to break in
front of people it's so weird when
you do i know that i mean
why don't we see it whenever the
mics aren't role people are already freaked
out
and i don't wanna freak about more
so um so i said this person
is just kind of telling me like
maybe you should tell them to we're
going to stop the show folks we're
gonna stop the show
so we stopped the show and i
go back stage um paramedics come in
they take the guy out and then
i'm sitting backstage and i'm just like
i don't know what happened in planning
your own mortality
no i think at that point i
still thought i was going to live
forever umm this wasn't the thing that
changed your mind no no no no
i was like well of course he
dies under the name so the main
character
so somebody comes back number one on
my call sheet and says yeah when
number one on their own call sheet
re last fucking true and that's what
the magnet says on my fridge
um so someone from the from the
theater came backstage and said do you
want to do want to continue the
show and i said ah should i
they said yeah the audience is is
a grill they're up in the bar
like they're they're waiting you know to
come back in and i was like
okay and so everybody came back in
and i continued the show and it
was fine it was so it was
special but summer did someone write this
week there that it was one of
the best shows they'd seen that oh
yeah one of the most
sneak shows yeah somebody somebody ah said
it was while they said like it
was it was they they were nice
instead it was a good show but
they said it was like an unforgettable
experience that right you know the show
continued and ah that it was good
like everybody was i think what wanted
to you know i think people wanted
to to
enjoy themselves because this arts later than
i think and then i haven't he
lived which is different i think that
he did i asked i asked the
theater i said you can like you
know who that was right based on
the reservation figure out yes so can
you we can make sure that i
didn't kill him with my comedy right
or confirmed that i did so powerful
oh but they never told they never
got back to me so i don't
know i'm assuming that the guy lift
my assumption is he did not
i'm in between i think he's immortal
i got to see him being carted
out and he was conscious got to
give you the old village farms okay
he gave me a terminator thumbs up
like very slowly
she closed the door on the yeah
they pulled it out sideways so his
thumb could be the last thing it
is the last thing the terminator does
right in number two yeah he gives
him the thumbs up from molten lava
from lava
i would have been saved never seen
those movies wasn't any of us do
a newcomer episode right now i really
do that probably
i mean there's i guess there's not
a lot to cover there's four movies
and a tv show no there's more
than four there's a bunch of termas
drives yeah
ah no worries terminator one chapter three
there's the recent one that was genesis
there's blah blah blah there's there's v
five movies or five movies and like
to terminate your boo boo gotta gotta
see it
the terminator lives enough at a park
a state park and he's always stealing
picnic baskets
alright we need to take a break
i know yeah obviously
we're back we're back i had a
side memory as well of ah someone
slapping me in a in a dramatic
setting um in that movie that scott
and i talked about previously where i
could not drive and ah and you
found out recently they cut that snow
yeah when i was digitizing all my
all my old tape we all laughed
it at your driving at the premiere
at the premiere that made the director
say mushy cut that out i think
so i think so because the version
that i had not because i look
forward i wanted to find it and
post it online but it was not
there anymore that's um it's just real
shit sir
comedy history
well we're keeping the memory alive and
that's what's true there was a guy
in the it was a mob movie
right so i'm in the ma i'm
going to count for the mob and
the guy who's playing the mob boss
at one point we were in the
scene where he was i know what
he was going for he was going
for a very um mob movie kind
of thing where he
he's gonna like pat my cheek like
this you know what i mean yeah
like you but it's all bambino yeah
but instead he stiff arm ah just
slaps my face like leaves his hand
the hair and it's like this is
not in there that's not a thing
that anyone does it's feeling i do
it more than one take
yes or no he did a one
take and i was so mad i
was so mad like because he didn't
he didn't prepare and he was just
like it just came over me to
do that and i was like oh
no yeah first of all that you
can not come over you today cannot
you can't do that you can't do
that there's more takes so if you
have that idea do it later you're
not like this guy was
and after that it was like i
was in this character right but also
that's not that's not a thing that
anyone does so this instinct that you
have is wrong for many reasons it
also sucks because you are being a
professional have lines to do after that
yeah you need to make them make
sense with whatever he's doing and and
that mm
may not the lines may not make
sense because you're so fucking pissed if
what's it's yeah it's going to mean
jar completely already but thanks to this
yeah a completely jarring thing that was
not in the script it's like you
can't just go rogue and decide you're
going to do that you know that's
so rude it was it was sort
of trauma for me
a stay in the movie
i don't think so i don't think
so yeah guys probably the best i
ruined it with my seething rage
and jimmy dore was in that movie
as well jimmy dore noted it doesn't
mean to or
in that movie
i don't get it ah it's okay
it's alright
rauf no i know yeah i wish
we were in the same room so
i could slap you
wow
yeah so i'm gonna let that hang
across
across the line man i'm gonna listen
to you saying ah he pulled out
his dick is teeny tiny dig
i'm trying to think if i've ever
i know i've been hit but i'm
trying to separate it from women who
hate you
um in a professional sense yeah i
don't know i don't know if i've
had it happened besides that one time
because that was pretty memorable but um
it was i was just like it's
the same thing as what yeah how
did the woman apologize to you because
the minute you get hit the lights
go out and you have to scream
right so it was it was in
rehearsal it was rehearsal yeah
oh we were just being in another
song and she just did it and
then it was like oh and then
it really hurt i almost cried i
think and then my face is really
bright red and she apologized um yeah
i don't really you know i remember
like i remember stepping into the hall
because i was gonna cry right um
i don't really know
no i don't remember what happened next
so i don't remember who she was
i remember like very vague details about
her but did she play the slapper
she did
did you get the doors the slapper
is here did you guys watch the
slap that show when it was on
i do watch we watch the australian
one i was better now there's like
different
this slap slay that was such a
crazy show
it was i can't believe they adapt
they adapted it for american television like
somebody said we got we got this
property we are we asked to do
this it's basically there's a party in
somewhat like a neighbor slaps someone's kid
right because yeah they were they were
misbehaving and then yes this neighborhood apart
i'm chairs and everyone does it does
because you're not supposed to slap someone
else's kid only your own yes you
must slap your own kid correct do
not slap other people's kids but slap
your own kid for all the times
you want to slap other people's okay
tell your friend i did this were
you were you spanked paul
no i was i was i was
slapped by my mother once oh i
guess i was too um i remember
my dad once tried to when i
was like maybe an eighth grade something
like that thirteen or fourteen and my
dad got mad at me and he
tried to like twist my ear because
he was he was an old
man and that's the kind of thing
that old people would do you come
from he was eighteen sixties his face
he has he was so furious with
me and it did not hurt like
the ear thing and i had to
i had to stifle laughter because i
i realised it would be devastating for
him you may give a fake
give me that give me damn lubes
i doubt i think i've said this
before but my father used to call
us when he was mad at me
and my brothers you'd call us damn
swine ah wonderful oh weird
a deadline but now your sisters know
they were precious in his sight you
said true kind of yeah it's kind
of true yeah but did you deserve
it never
beautiful boy i did nothing wrong
skywatch but no apt i would never
get so remember what i did to
earn it so so there there were
definite spankings and there were belt spankings
not we're not talking about last weekend
yeah i'm sorry oh shea he makes
cool upset
him with the belt on his ass
there was there was a constant there
was a constant thing where my brother
and i were about the same age
and we neither of us ever wanna
do admit that we had done any
of the wrong things now admittedly it
was usually him now you love it
but i broke that but it was
it was pretty calm
iman to be like okay well we're
going to have to punish both of
you until one of you she ah
fast job so one of you breaks
and my brother i gotta say he
was pretty good about never giving it
up that it was him and letting
me take the belt
wow he yeah ady never broke he
never broke i think i think i
remember breaking at one point going like
i did it before it was so
that he wouldn't get punished but i'm
pretty sure oh
he never did but ah yeah i
was also thinking the other day i
was thinking about the one time that
we must have been five and seven
and we were at the library and
my mom didn't pick us up
and i don't know i don't know
how long we we must have waited
but to us it seemed like an
eternity but i bet it was ten
minutes yeah for we were like well
we better walk to my aunt's house
who i know she lives around here
somewhere
so we've led you to start walking
so we we walked and we got
lost and then eventually my mom pulled
up that she'd been driving around the
neighborhood just looking for us and eventually
she pulled out does your shirt say
leave hillary alone
just leave philly alone oh okay hey
speaking to philly i'll keep piling on
hillary speaking to hillary now ah speaking
to philly paul yeah did you watch
mayor of east town for the accents
yes i did yes and how are
the accents
bad right ah it's not a sham
yeah it's it's an hbo miniseries kate
winslet is playing a um ah a
detective in a small town near philadelphia
um and she is going for the
accent she's gone for it i'm gonna
watch only i'm only on certain words
like yeah yea yeah like water water
water water there are certain like she's
she's doing the o words because those
are good signifiers but the thing is
there's other words that she's pronouncing just
like the way she's doing her flat
american accent you know what i mean
yeah and so it's worse than if
she
she wasn't doing it at all
yeah because no one else is really
doing it that much either so it's
like always is one honest why bothers
it's a lot of the peripheral characters
are doing it and they're doing a
good job like i actually juliet nicholson
was doing a good job okay and
jean smart of course who is terrific
can do the finest american actors yeah
this should interest not good for england
but
i once um did a short film
in utah and the girl who says
after baby sitting yeah the girl who
picked me up at the transitional period
this was this is when i was
moving for babysitting into film and tv
just doing short ones to a tv
and then i did some shorts
um but this girl who picks me
up at the airport it was like
just like a low budget thing that
my friend was making so he just
like had random people that he knew
helping out so some girl just picked
me up from the random her accent
she's from salt lake city or like
around there but it must be like
a small town it was so i
could have understood
and a word she was saying it
was like really it was like she
was amish or something it was like
a very odd accent like nothing i'd
ever heard before and i had to
like work so hard to have the
conversation and not say like what like
every time she said anything but i
can't even begin to like do limitation
of it it was just like very
water feels like it's in the same
family but like but like every word
was like weird like that would rule
you will eat yeah there you go
that's actually something
ah
the the orange county accent where i'm
from was just all like beach kind
of like hey it was ah abe
bro it's going on that's how everyone
talked a big bag a good good
yeah coronavirus is a scan dammit right
yeah why da da da so like
the people in the
that area don't want to believe this
shit because they're a republican
um probably yeah it doesn't help when
the major news source is saying it's
a scam
every night yeah are you talking about
socks are you talking about some local
orange county thing no fuck mainly fox
news yeah it's very conservative right down
there down there it is yeah which
i i don't they're down there i
don't know why that is i've eventually
low booties zo hoax
down there
i guess anywhere that they're like majorly
rich homes there's a pocket of that
but i don't know i mean there
isn't beverly hills right like yeah actually
to be speaking of a little bit
of reality recap again reality recap huh
yeah um josh flagg who i mentioned
on a previous episode
was filming people he was he lives
i'm sorry who honey he is one
of the realtors on million dollar listing
okay thank you the show that parodies
bajillion dollar properties he is gay and
he which is an important part of
the story because he would go to
i never mentioned yeah i would go
to trump rallies that were like in
his neighborhood like in beverley hills and
interview people on instagram and just ask
them questions and so like i had
to assume that he thought he did
not agree with them basically right based
on what i know about him but
he also is really rich
so it's one of those things were
like i don't know maybe he's yeah
and he was entering this one woman
who was so bananas and she had
so much plastic surgery and she was
like just saying you know all the
horrible stuff supporting trump and whatever and
then turns out she ended up being
at january six
wow she got arrested wow i wish
i was there she i wish i
did resident it was pretty crazy it
was like a full circle thing god
damn all those people yeah there's so
much
justly the sheer amount of video of
all those people like easily posting themselves
so ridiculous it's one of the only
like just breaking the law for the
clout for internet clout yeah it's so
funny
it also speaks to like people that
have lived their life thinking there will
never be any consequences for them like
that they can do whatever they want
including break into the fucking capital and
film themselves trying to think of any
consequences that have ever happened to me
in my life let's see well yeah
slapped
slap that one time i got hit
by the belt for something i didn't
do
alright did you ever get spanked or
slapped or anything no i have a
vague memory of one spanking but it's
been denied i don't think it was
redesigned by my home just proven yeah
i mean it's one of those things
that um i was like that happened
and it's like no it didn't like
you know just like i don't think
yes it's not it's not my fam
mls policy so i might have made
it up um but a typical yeah
it's be cool to myself
but no i didn't get slapped or
spanked know must be nice where would
you were you were you given time
outs or times out i don't really
remember having time out i how were
you ever punished you seem to have
no memory of being fun you ran
wild in that you guys i have
no memories of most stuff like i
feel like i just don't like you
you don't
remember any of your childhood until you
were what fourteen
i don't mean to say that on
a previous episode because you hit your
head that time and you're jumping off
the gym three times really um i
have told all three concussion possible stories
i believe so yes okay two possible
stories i've ever checked out that did
that woman slapped the memory out of
you
i slapped the memory i don't i
just don't um i don't really remember
being like i remember being punished i
do remember being punished as a teenager
like ground car accident and oh what's
the car accident grounded i'm sure i've
told this because it's a crazy story
i was it was july third thing
this was the origin of the topic
trading cards yeah oh yes okay so
maybe honestly had i met that man
thrice and then i earned the card
if you don't know what lawrence's talking
about listen to a previous episode anyone
anyone yeah it comes up on everything
since i basically i had an encounter
with a cop three times the same
cop and gave me his trading card
the exchange in the dickens story he
was really nice um and but no
but i went for that first correct
and i got grounded i was allowed
to go out for fourth of july
and put you know weeks after and
whatever and i mean it was i
felt horrible it was mainly that i
just felt horrible i didn't really need
my pair
wants to like you know scream at
me much i was like this is
i feel awful i ruined the car
and it was like so but it
was total
it wasn't totaled but it was like
three thousand dollars of damage oh that
is like thirty thousand wheelchairs totally pushed
in
i was just lucky nobody got hurt
because i hit the back of um
i hit the the back door of
a car and there were two people
in the front seats older people and
oh right so yeah it was sort
of like almost t-boned them in a
way i did tebow in the back
basically whoa and it's my meme around
they spun around in there frozen shit
flipped on the paper she died but
then he came out and comforted me
it was very nice there funny the
the woman out of the car and
walked home because they were like a
block away from home she was like
oh she's like i'll just go home
and then he gave me a hug
and i don't know it was oh
you smelly fruit very sweet he smelled
like fruit
do you associate the smell of fruit
with that old man hugging you yeah
i really do anytime i smell any
fruit i think about that old man
yeah when i was a new driver
i use a driver yeah you don't
know i told you
we've never heard the story it was
ten dollars a day and i would
every time i drive stop lights i
would turn to the car next to
me and say looking here
ah i had i'd had my license
for just like months and i was
ah crossing this like this crazy wide
intersection um in ah it was like
in west
yeah born near downtown um and i
dropped janey off somewhere and what's really
weird is we had a because at
that time we shared her right you
were you were telling the story and
you said i just learned to drive
and i imagined that you were sixteen
years old but now i'm realizing this
is rice right
it was a forty year old man
forty you learn how to drive yeah
yeah yeah and um we had had
this big back and forth about should
i drop her offer should she just
take the car and she kept insisting
no no no you dropped me off
and then you can have the car
for the day and i was like
i don't need the car for the
day why
don't you turn it on you to
go
yeah i don't know how to answer
that question well like it seems like
she's trying to give you the car
to get you out of her hair
or something like you have the car
for the day you go please she
was allowing him to she had to
go some place so she's she sure
i would have been out of her
hair regardless okay
guy
i was really not sure how to
answer
where did she want you to go
well cool up a sign scott location
okay
we have tracking on our phones so
she makes sure i'm aware i'm supposed
to be those sin garrisons parking lot
i like it because i feel like
see you sit in a parking lot
so often when my mom would go
on
on identify so far yeah she's just
dropping off
oh my god waiting car was always
such a thing i mean almost but
then being the dragging your ass through
the mall also really sucky sucky spin
like drugs so boring the parking lot
of eastman drugstore i just always i
would go can i come in with
you and she'd say no because then
you're gonna want to like want me
to buy something for you said it
was drugs cause the details
waiting for ok so i tried to
cross this intersection i did not see
that there was a stop sign and
so i am having to me i
am flying through this intersection and this
ah young woman was coming ah perpendicular
um she did not have a say
op sign so she was gone we
were both going in like a good
two-way she fucking slams into me t-bones
me but it was my fault because
i was not supposed to be there
and we so we both got out
of the car were like super shaking
up like the airbag goes off all
the shit in her seniors i believe
i can't remember she hit an airbag
or not but uh
um i will never forget that feeling
of like
the shock of what happened and then
slowly like my my body had tensed
up because like i remember hearing the
sound of her slamming on the brakes
and turning and seeing her like seeing
her slamming on her brakes and like
turning her face away because she could
see the impact coming yeah
yeah and so i i get out
like you know open the door it's
like glass falling and shit and ah
she starts screaming you know oh my
god oh my god and and then
she starts going did anybody see this
did anybody see this and i'm like
look this is my
my fault i'm not going to there's
no i'm not going to try to
preserve already lol you don't want wages
yeah you don't need witnesses yeah oh
yeah you know when it says this
was my fault well we could see
that i was okay we were both
like oh walking around you know um
and i was like ah that feeling
of i have to tell
oh janey that i wrecked her car
you know um and she was i
call my friend ken who came in
who came and picked me up who
was great and like i was fucking
in shock like that car was destroyed
jane's car was destroyed and so i
was just
i'm sorry i know i wanted to
do i was right though look i
can't blame you guys i understand
it's your fault for marrying her nah
tell me about it i want you
to be with a different name but
my parents would approve also you had
to because of this car this is
part of the deal right you wreck
her car you have to marry her
yeah that's what made us get married
if there was a preacher right there
on the spot we signed a pre
pre prenup what they call a thredup
and so that was various stages of
our relationship all all members of three
of them have a three nup of
course yeah we have a three node
between the three of us yeah so
how did jannie de dah thredup well
of course she was like i'm just
glad that you're
okay you know and i had such
guilt over it and she never ever
ever ever indicated that she was upset
about the car being yeah so out
of anyone i know i almost like
anyone i've know personally if if i
could wreck someone's car it would be
hers because i would think she wouldn't
get mad about it i'll tell you
no and i'm sure she'll appreciate it
i mean that's very nice
it is like she's a nice lady
she'd she'd made i try to think
out of anyone in the world she'd
be the most concerned that oh oh
what a horrible situate i don't care
about the car what a horrible situation
i'm glad that everyone is okay yea
yeah and then i haven't given a
second thought to the car yeah although
there was a previous incident when i
i
we were we were it was very
tense when i was learning to drive
and she would be in the car
with me and it's her car and
i'm driving that has not used by
the way teaching right yeah yeah yeah
well like do you feel like how
confident you feel now i feel like
i'm a very good driver now oh
god yeah i think i'm real but
i it's been
in like you know eleven years now
or something yeah i think i got
my license in twenty ten yeah um
it's hard to be a passenger in
a car when someone period
but you know it's i know that
i'm stressing cool op out when i
get stressed out by someone almost hitting
us yeah yeah me going like ah
or so yeah got to you know
but it's like so i so i
tried to talk myself out of doing
it just going like everything's gonna be
okay you don't need to make noises
no but it's like i don't know
what the solutions are because you have
no control so you're like yeah so
is it hasn't i even see that
like you know and you can't help
but yeah and sometimes you do help
where you're like hey there's a person
you about to hit but then i
saw like that but i feel like
that gets said to me a lot
and i'm like i see them yeah
yeah that's that's what i feel like
too is like yeah yeah i see
yeah i'm looking at them i am
perhaps because i've been a passenger for
so long i'm an excellent passenger in
a car wow you just take zanni
and oh yeah pankaj zanni than any
ah
time three what
i felt like no i felt like
there was something i was gonna say
and you are going to talk about
janey and the cow and how oh
how you got home yes no no
oh you can just review so when
i was learning to drive can my
friend would pick me up after the
action list actually stories i'm sure i'm
sure jumper um sw
so ah when i was when i
saw my permit and i took driving
lessons i did not let i have
many people offered to teach me how
to drive and i was like no
let me do it for fun let's
stay friends so um yeah oh gotta
be way too much pressure it will
be so it would be ridiculous i
don't know if there was a movie
about your life there the song
under pressure would be playing while there
was a montage early driving exactly but
it would also be in the trailer
but not in the movie would be
dangerous not have that extra brake on
the driver's side you know on the
passenger side yes yes yes my man
edgar he told me on a job
he did a great job wow should
all cars have that extra break yeah
that would cost so many accidents all
cars
are you just some brakes to steering
wheels to horns
one of the following items later used
this year well if you just like
honk the horn whenever you wanted like
say yes and wow that wouldn't be
a few long with it um i
don't think so so um ah we
were so we're we're on our way
home we're in an argument of course
because we're we're stressed we're both stress
asked out by me learning how to
drive yeah and so i m i
turn onto our street and then i
have to make a left into our
driveway and she says she's telling me
to slow down and i'm like so
mad that she's telling me what to
do that i do not
slow down and i eat turn i'm
gonna show her like how great i
can do this right and i turn
sharply into the driveway and i hit
the fucking kerr
ah that would feel so dumb it's
such a hard hit it is such
a hard hit did it stop the
car cold or did you go up
on the curb oh no it's not
like i hit the as soon as
i hit like bang i hit the
brake oh and then we sat there
and then i had to like turner
say ah that was
was my phone
i'm very sorry and of course i
will pay for the damages to your
car
and it was like a few hundred
bucks ah that i had to pay
but it was it was mortifying i
was humiliate yeah it's like forty wheelchairs
okay
alright we'll be right back
and we're back back back back back
back freedom i want i want i
want i want i want the knife
ah what that's from the golden child
the movie with eddie murphy edward murphy
the only thing from it that i
remember is him going up to a
poll that has like a
a knife now he's trying to get
a magical knife i do remember that
but he goes up to a poll
that has like a spinning part of
the pole and he kind of treats
it like a ah record were scratching
oh sure sure sure i want the
nice really makes me want to see
the movie that sounds pretty funny i
think that was the only funny thing
but i could be wrong it's been
i believe
i saw nineteen hundred and eighty eight
yes r in my frank's house i
forgive me for when that movie free
know what haircut oh okay i remember
the movie came out because eddie murphy
wears a little leather hat that then
became very popular at hats in the
belfry
really yes there were buying relation after
that movie yes yes yes because it
was all he was wearing this hat
in the poster and everything yeah yeah
i remember that wow so everyone wanted
that hat everyone one of that eddie
murphy hat if i wonder if like
if i were a huge movie star
and i knew that people were going
to want to imitate whatever
the way i dressed i would try
to get a piece of that before
the marketing came out you know what
i mean the idea of you putting
on a little little leather hat and
being like you don't want this because
i'm wearing if i did the other
day i better get a piece of
it i bought thousands of hats and
no one wanted them
what about those monkeys didn't they steal
your hats oh that's right david jones
you're not mike nesmith theory i think
that might have been one of the
last concert i saw no and yes
the surviving monkeys bow houses the last
but ah definitely the last thing i
saw surviving dominance
alright we have a three cheer because
it's three your time and this is
the way we do things and we
like it that way we would not
change it for a million dollars although
if you had a million dollars contact
us know we would much a million
dollar epa ahead a million dollars
while there's not a third one that
i can sing it's not a bad
bear lady song it's a good song
impression i'd be rich
it's good alright this is this is
a three-tier submitted by our biggest fan
josh oh josh loves us too much
yeah gosh yeah jack again we joked
about that before but this actually does
come from josh this was a suggestion
of for a game that he made
um and it's good enough and we
joked about it before but he actually
is a
super fan
he loves us i know we've made
jokes about it but josh showed up
at my house one night
alright this is called selling i'm kidding
but i'm actually really scared
this is a game called alphabet skip
and here's who plays alphabets were you
and here's how it goes pick a
letter of the alphabet at random begin
a three person scene using say an
occupation as a suggestion where no one
is allowed
vowed to use any words that begin
with that letter if someone messes up
they have to retake their last line
without using the offending word for an
extra challenge every sixty seconds pick another
letter at random and no one is
allowed to use any words that begin
with any of the letters selected what
i would suggest it's josh's here is
he picks the letter he picks the
occupation
and and after every sixty seconds he
shouts out a new letter and he
catches us if we
okay now we don't often allow their
voices i know is he going to
be voiced but he immediately texted i
can do that he is he well
why don't we pop open our chat
and he can put it in the
chat okay that's we refused to have
his voice featured on the show we
must preserve the sanctity yeah
it's no good not josh it's not
it's nothing against you it's just that
this is against your illness
so let it be known that i
want your voice to be heard but
the men are silencing it
well he's another man so what are
you worried about we legit lab all
your watch
the computer said it's okay i understand
either target ai that is josh how
funny that computer said okay
alright so josh give us a letter
and an occupation letter b b b
occupation
skiing rochester here we go ok
hey paul hey scott thanks for coming
to work today it is my pleasure
my friend um i guess you want
to know how to ski downhill i
do i do it's something that i
don't currently know how to do
you and i would like to learn
if you're going to be a teacher
huh gotcha
you're out
no he has to retake his less
oops if you are going to put
your arm the role of instructor you
must learn how to ski downhill agreed
this is what i want to do
so let us commence i certainly will
okay please zhang use me wrong it
was painting jobs ding dong ah is
it too late for me to join
this lesson
i mean this this is more of
a teachers teaching teachers kind of lesson
but i just ah well the problem
is i really have to get to
the ah ooh ah the problem is
i really have to get to the
lower portion of the hill because all
that's the part that's the opposite of
the top yeah
i left my husband down there and
he's crying
okay aw new letter yes that's two
oh that's too bad i teach know
that what's s s where no no
yes yeah oh i thought we were
doing the additional challenge which oh as
an additional noel oh okay that's what
i say in my home they'll be
not on my watch no bold no
shit
um i can teach you put these
on
will wake up
new the two of you do i
put them on as well yeah yes
and mine are your lad these are
the implements we will use to go
downhill okay i'm putting them on these
going our feet is that correct oh
of course
so what would you call these all
of us nope
what would you call it you said
you said an s word well what
would you call it thank you
i would call these de roos but
i'm crazy are they named after me
no dang dog god we love you
but no yeah
one way why do i ah ah
you know why why are you constantly
in my vision ah when you don't
know how to do this this task
are you talking to me
hey robert de niro no i'm talking
to ding dong ding dong um you
know i feel like i guess i
just spend a lot of oops i
guess i just am here a lot
because oops i guess i'm just here
a lot due to the fact that
this is ah
a place where i find community
wonderful may i ask because i have
a terrible memory
certainly where are we trying to get
to and what method will we use
to get there we're trying to go
downhill
gravity oh we have a new letter
d gravity will just under the wire
perform the task for us
and all you have to do is
put those on and ah let gravity
perform the task
joe just so we're just up in
order to be clear yes in order
to get clear sure are you a
hill z was
yes i was going to ask but
say the word in order to get
clear for clarity sake for clarity for
clarity yes for clarity
what am i putting on my feet
and these steam thee these implements survive
the gravitational force mr what is your
job i am an instructor of of
this very thing we're doing you know
is
you know it we all know it
the american people know it
number dole
now now that they're on your feet
i'm going to push you robert robert
presidential candidate yes
ah alright here we go right huh
ah
yet am
ah ah we're going
welding were plummeting here we are well
i guess that was fun we reached
the portion of this hill which is
the opposite of the top
true and we did it by news
of no no we we we did
it no with oh no dale did
we cowardly did and accomplished
with these long sticks no long board
law one yes some planks long planks
yeah i like walking the plank with
these attached to our feet it's like
the plank is walking itself and we're
just
deride in russia plank walks you
the end guys we love you too
huh especially ding-dong i can say your
name each other especially they can say
ding dong oh josh wow thank you
so much wow yeah yes
wow just wow yeah josh wow was
he says a plot of the robot
says applause
the computer says pause while that was
that was fun that was fun computer
says what computer says no nai but
it's a sound little britain but but
um a computer says ny is a
schedule says no yeah
i mean i know what you were
saying and just what i was doing
more of a wayne's world computer says
what
well
we had a good end to this
episode when
right now we're we did computer says
what yep that's awesome um i really
want carlos i'm gonna heat up a
piece of pizza oh wow maybe i'll
do the exact same thing okay i'll
do the opposite our class we did
a show last night so to go
wild horses lasagna
and janie as soon as the show
was over i looked on my phone
and janie texted me a picture of
ah pizza that she had ordered whoa
and said i gave up i just
order pizza and i was fucking thrilled
that was instantly like the perfect thing
oh
oh yeah
awesome it's awesome when food is there
waiting yeah yeah food y'all are waiting
um okay will be levies so much
you guys have paid so it'll be
a food way and by the way
hoping pizza you know what else is
waiting for you as giblets in the
store that's right the gyms are now
available to purchase
a global leader jamie yeah love it
huh you're kidding me
a whole
nah ooh i don't wanna die sometimes
wish i'd never been crocs and oh
and carry a gym if i don't
let you down will not give you
ah so get those giblets you fools
and follow us at three team usa
yes on wherever you want
follow us yeah yes yeah i
uh