three
a ah really leaped in here cheese
and use i mean just getting here
was half the battle getting there was
half the that's very true because these
are still difficult times well you know
same if if
you made it into the gym that's
ninety percent of your workout you know
that's not true but that's not true
i would say yourself to work ten
percent ten percent but i mean error
it's ninety percent of your mental just
like getting i don't know hey my
man sam what they're getting they say
you miss ninety percent of the shots
you don't take
yeah i'm not one hundred percent of
the ones i don't take usually means
you've got to get that better i
only miss ten percent of the shots
that i don't take wow yeah well
when i don't take them i'm sinking
um wow swish swish swish swish making
them i'll have one after the other
i hired a boy to take my
shots for me wow that's so old-time
me well we are here killed and
it's time for me
but we're here we made it we
we had technical difficulties but we're up
we're together we're listening gotcha i stop
you right there um no okay so
anyway we made it going to do
it
you expect to have consent you had
technical difficulties you've got sounded some this
is scott sounds a lot better usually
will be lit up yeah i mean
with y'all yeah we're going lauren's normal
i have not knowingly do anything yes
exactly i was trying
something new okay someone here don't don't
do this mean that on my things
don't do new things that's no new
things that's our motto for this year
a little late in twenty twenty two
no new thugs do the old things
yeah do do the old things don't
do the new things do do do
do do do one silver and one
gold
but i think going back to the
old things that we didn't do in
twenty twenty one and twenty twenty would
be nice what were the old things
that we didn't do we didn't do
all the good stuff yeah all the
good
ah cheat on your wife why didn't
we oh i thought you meant on
this podcast but you made it home
many p i mean i had a
hard time cheating during this time yeah
i feel bad for them that's people
have not talked about it enough i
feel bad for the flanders for the
the low down dirty dogs you can
kinda have to
i've been for the two years and
millions of people who are in the
middle of secret clandestine affairs that either
had to cut it off or were
still sneaking out around yeah you know
backs of people you know they're how
humans when we wanna hear your stories
right
whoa yes what have we pivoted to
a hard like salacious loveline sort of
vibe that sounds good it's like assist
josh has said that he would set
up a google phone number for us
yeah you have to call each other
yeah because i'm afraid to give you
guys my number yeah hello to have
um people call in with you know
the things they want to say bullshit
idea yeah bullshit i don't really want
to hear from i don't want to
hear it but i wanna hear it
and i welcome with freedom i'm paul
f tompkins i'm lauren laka yeah damn
it now who am i wait paul
when you get that joker mike
paul is it's nice talking mania a
bowling green mike with a yellow stripes
looks a lot like his flower on
his jacket lapel that's really nice for
my jacket i can make a joker's
flower oh i didn't know you can
make it so customized there's
i went to a place called color
where and i got um this mike
may there it's just a regular mag
but they ah paint them or do
some i want that always changes requested
those colors i requested those colors these
are these are my my professional colors
yes ah rye tobia spontaneous nation
in
joker oh so use them across the
board yes they're like mardi gras colors
yeah but when but at night when
you're the joker and no one on
the joker where the the new joker
stuff i don't wear the old dredge
light but you ain't over the mustache
like cesar ramirez of course i do
ah
and paul your hat matches your mike's
had it does it's true look it's
a little were wearing the same wow
microphone
do you think of your microphone as
your mini me yeah i talked to
it and into it
first i say i'm gonna talk to
you now and then i wait and
i think dirty talk yeah what dr
evil talked into many me why here
why didn't he ever tap his head
ago hammer is this thing on i
bet he did yeah how many oh
my god how much footage unused his
austin power
footage used oh there's gotta be so
much just bad improv bad wreck yes
when like when when his hair would
grow into stubble it looks more like
a microphone like the dots on a
microphone sure yeah sure yeah yeah because
otherwise i don't picture it no microphone
do you think mike myers ever requested
a virtual or hey do you mind
not
shaving tonight so when you come back
in tomorrow i can tap you on
the top of your head but then
he say hello is this thing he
wouldn't look like a true mini me
anymore because doctor evil didn't have stubble
now do you think we're in troyer
shaved his head every night
no i bet it was every morning
i bet it was bought every twenty
four hours he had to shave is
head
if you're in that shaving that seems
like a lot lauren do you shave
your legs
what kind of disgusting question was her
we finally got there so yes i
do i wrote down paul when we
first started doing the show episode one
in an envelope that's right when will
paul say ask lauren when does she
shave her legs i said you're crazy
i'm never gonna ask that it's disgusting
by two episodes thankfully he didn't say
he didn't ask me when i shaved
my legs he just asked me if
i do i don't want you to
ask me when because that's way too
personal okay i wasn't going to and
i didn't good i ask when you
yeah so what do you shave your
legs um in the shower
and when my retail might that be
zero to the to the minute or
so every six days my dear boy
i shave my finances in the shower
oh and a little mirror and a
little edge to the wall or the
french yes the center spring but it's
just suction cupped to the glass um
i put her on the glass and
um it's it's one of those fogginess
mirrors which of course means that it
fogs up every time yeah yeah i've
tried maybe probably six different ones over
the course of my shower shaving career
and they all fuck up i remember
when i went to japan the hotel
for soda
hell i stayed in there had a
foggiest mere like the one section of
the mayor didn't fog and i was
very amazed by that i've never really
seen a quality fall day know how
to do it we don't have that
we just we cut corners here and
you're you're foggy mirror foggo my god
every which way but i love shooting
in the shower
power why because you're naked yes it
makes you feel more like god and
i can't stand for my sink without
clothes on wow why jay it's one
of jane's like there's a camera in
the mirror
they can't see past them here too
the shower um it's it's because it's
you have the steam in there it's
easier to do you know what i
mean you don't have to keep like
it opens up those poor opens up
those yeah oh yours those poor tunny
i shaved my clock's face every
a week with a feather duster what
are you damn it
scott but do you just duck your
own mentally ill
are you still crazy you're dusting your
own home
i definitely think he calls it shaving
the clock's face
if you know what i mean i'm
done i dust the outside someone else
does the inside i shaved my house
yelps
taking my house every few days you
have to do that what every hour
would say
keep it clean
an hour later more bugs
ah covered in bogs just covered in
bugs i have you ever been covered
in bugs either of you know
crappy check your style or your organs
in the news let's talk about fear
factor no i've never i've never been
like caught in a swarm of bees
or anything i know that's happened in
people where they like they throw a
rock at a wasp nest or something
and they all came down to tell
that that something like that did happen
to me oh no i didn't tell
us tell us tell us lauren tell
us a new story i might
i've told her before honestly i wouldn't
be shocked she really did but god
um well one time when i was
in fifth grade my friend was my
friend's house and there was this giant
pile of woodchips in front of her
house like probably sounds five feet tall
and was this down in the holler
it was just huge oh look at
all those nice wood chips you got
must have and take a lot
long time to build up a collection
like that yeah one by one over
the years but we you think she
would have gotten them like three or
four times you know or three years
another
anyway as we were running up and
down and it was really fun like
just running as fast you can do
it sounds running down the hill yeah
it was a blast and then we
each notice that we're getting a little
like um like kind of like it
felt like a little splinter or something
was hitting our legs in our like
of easting in the moment we thought
it was little splinters from the woodchips
and then we realized we were running
on a yellow jacket hive and we
they were all in our clothes and
buying wow and so we like ran
in the house and really taking our
clothes off like
running around the bun her mom was
like what's going on and then all
these bees were coming out it was
crazy god how many many stings did
you end up having it i don't
really remember how many stings i actually
had it wasn't so it wasn't like
i was covered into stings it was
more that a lot of them got
me through my clothes so it wasn't
really official but um
than they were in the clothes and
i was just scary it wasn't official
judges didn't have those know yeah it's
weird i'm only going to show up
at people's houses when stung by yellow
jackets what would be the worst thing
you could be in a casket with
oh my god fear factor like they
put you in a little box prop
probably lord
yeah that would fucking suck
another dead body well kind of like
on fear factor like what would they
put in that will really freak you
out
umm probably bugs are bad for me
like spider riders yeah what if they
put like bats in there
a family they probably you'd be okay
okay i was wanting to move around
all that much yeah they would they'd
they'd chill with you they'd go to
be killing time
you have to be vibrating at a
freestyle doing it can look a little
rush limbaugh tribute and he was jiggling
all around gym hoodie t made fun
of michael j fox know what asshole
he was i bad person ah wow
it's good he's dead switch over to
making fun of michael jackson
who is that hey guys oh my
god
i just remembered i have a very
important appointment
wow michael j accent you guys gonna
watch that bill cosby doc watched it
you already watched yeah paul paul asked
for it early because he really just
wanted to get this to be funny
yeah give me give me an advance
copy it's going to be all about
his comedy there's like some comedy in
there
it's it's really good it's really good
it's it's wild especially for somebody of
my age and i don't know how
how far it goes you know in
successive generations but somebody who was like
huge part of the fabric of society
in a positive way
when i was growing up and
it's a very um it's like a
really ah well done ah very well
researched and presented and emotional documentary it's
really worth watching
like good emotions yeah i'm happy
i'm gonna check it out but there's
also so happy he was released from
jail
on a lighter note there's a documentary
about the anne just like the filming
of unjust like that and i will
be watching you all watch this behind
the scenes absolutely have to they take
it all the way up to a
racing amount of the season finale um
while the podcast i listened to the
podcast every week that talks about each
episode it's the writers' room podcast and
they
actually we'll address that on the episode
that i haven't listened to because i
don't watch the episode boi yoi yoi
waiting to find the seas season finale
she's gonna be like oh he was
over no no you probably erased him
out of like i think i think
she she in the first cut or
the original cut she was like remembering
him you saw clips of members oh
oh and then they remembered there are
old clips
yeah we don't have to
because there's extensive footage of him as
this character why why was he called
mr big
because he's like a big shot he
has like a lot of money and
he was like run around the back
of a town man yeah yeah so
it wasn't a penis thing no his
penis was never discussed as never she
said didn't she say he had a
micro penis but she still loved him
she said that nirvana is in the
first movie right
she turned out to the audience and
said ah he's just like any other
because he'll wonder what i need a
microscope
that's a small one that's right you
hear about micro-businesses or microbiota and you're
like ok i can still see with
the naked eye no pun intended guys
got well my eyes are always naked
from fucking my eyes always naked because
my eyelids don't work wow and that
seems really painful
it sucks and i can't i slept
in ten years i like the sweaters
of the eyes can you really sleep
without eyelids couldn't you just put something
over your eyes
but it's right on your eyeball
like a scrappy blanket
with like the cups well ah but
then you're just looking at the inside
of them
yeah but i still think you'd fall
asleep eventually i mean eventually your eyes
roll back and put a book
you could put a book in where
in the mass cleanup in the wayland
so when you close your eyes yeah
yeah do your eyes roll back or
is that something that like a little
kids thing
or are you a little kid
this sounds like you think it right
now no they just kind of like
the art from side to side very
rapidly yeah instantly whenever it closed my
physicist when i'm sleeping
every time i blink i vivid dreams
watch this
ah had a nightmare
what about winking do you have half
a nightmare it was just the setup
i drove but just from like sitting
height dream i'm fallen was that song
that fuck parody of howling violin szaky
yeah i don't know that i had
an idea that allowed cancer now although
weird al should make a baby album
because i like make a baby
he did thirty dead why yeah i
do want now what albums ever come
my first lot of songs a lot
of parody songs about ah when i'm
you know doing baby related activities and
i just think oh weird al could
make a fortune off of this shit
yeah by selling records you can make
a fortune now what are some of
your greatest hits
they change so frequently it's like nothing
sticks around long enough for me to
even
yeah what what song is that too
i really did think you were starting
one
because maybe it's changed i truly i
switched it up so much they they
don't they don't stick you know sometimes
i thought i should record these should
write them down they're fantastic they're amazing
and i think no one gives up
foot are these are these parodies are
these are originals sometimes they're original and
sometimes they're parodies um like
you know here give me a song
i'll just do one okay um madonna's
lucky star talking
you might have a poop in there
okay
yeah like boo and you do so
well hey that's so sweet is exactly
what i thought yeah
you know they might be giants have
a couple of kids records oh yeah
gotta get hip to that
my dear friends and maybe giants who
never met me paul is like i'm
trying to adjust my microphone so i
can be comfortable and seen at the
same time
you are seeing paul we see you
okay avatar like a waiver the schools
oh man where are you going to
be opening night ah in the ground
by the time so there's no chance
man i've had that movie people were
going so crazy over it and i
went saw it in three d and
it was so bad i've never seen
that me and my two friends i
went with we all took naps at
different times so it was like oh
shit yeah like we are on the
watch absolutely yeah
oh i just watched all of yellow
jackets and i loved it it's good
right because you stepped on them when
you were a kid oh wow connection
did you think it was yeah you
ideally i was like is this going
to be a documentary about when i
ran over that high
um it's really good though i i
waited a long time within the best
part about waiting is that you can
binge it all
true theory that's very true
every the whole cast is so good
what is going on with your cuckoo
camera i just say maybe don't acknowledge
it because no one else no sin
is happening except you but you're laying
out and you know you're not talking
the way you normally do like steamrolling
us and yeah it's like i'm able
to get my thoughts out and i
feel stressed um
i don't like my mom that i'm
able to say crazy how does not
doing his job i have heard you
on ah your podcast with janey tell
her not to call things out like
that and i think he's got a
point but i still understand why she
did it but i wouldn't talk to
him because you do you have the
same thought process so and you're both
wrong
great
i loved yellow jackets of course huge
melanie lynskey fan le ma alinsky i
love juliette lewis i love all the
new people that i wasn't familiar with
there was a lot of great acting
in that show the the the young
lady who plays young jackie
and um we call her we aren't
the first time we ever saw her
was in a show called sweet bitter
and so okay when we see her
when we refer to her on this
show we just call her sweet bitter
she reminds me so much of somebody
i can't figure it out do you
know what actors reminds you of
it was driving me crazy her raspy
voice
never i don't um but what should
the audience surrogate for anyone who hasn't
seen it and doesn't care yes you
wanna move along what you're saying okay
what about feel what if we're the
silver surfer became the incredible hulk oh
okay oh great now i'm going something
everyone understands
umm yellow dragons is good sky you've
gotta watch it i shit yeah there's
just so much time in the day
i got ah you know there's so
much time that you just there's too
much time i just can't get started
i would like to teach watched taylor
yeah i know i know you guys
watch any shows together bonus at all
just everyone's td for themselves
ourselves
no yeah we had a lot of
stuff we were watching but um we
there right well you know it's also
award seasons i was watching a lot
of the shirt twenty twenty one's great
cinema a lot of me yeah you
could confirm they were as bad as
you thought they were going to be
that kind of thing
i just got a screamer that i'm
excited to watch just king richard oh
it's good myth it's good it looks
good yeah like yeah we saw on
hbo oh it's on hbo it was
bill max yeah i was gonna say
this whole maximum watching the max is
the maximum amount of hbo go hbo
you can get yeah yeah
wow they really crushed it with that
huh
um
but if you don't want spoilers don't
go on e s p n o
like where they they're still talking about
it
i liked i thought it was it
was um a lot different than um
um your typical kind of biopic like
that i thought it was it was
much more interesting and and ah well
directed cool i'll definitely be checking that
out well well well well well well
the bachelor
around movies every week for my other
now isn't it hard now see you
understand what it's like to be on
newcomers now because it's hard to watch
new slot of stuff you don't you've
avoided for a long time you actively
avoided all these movies to some extent
because the ones you're watching are all
really popular and most part right adam
family well we just want well yeah
we watched that clash dance whatever like
all those kinds of well we just
watched the next karate kid why that
huge that's because shouldn't be come on
because connor ratliff really wanted to talk
about it
wow i would not call that a
movie blind spots i know but here
i am wasting two hours of my
life it was i said this on
the show came out friday i actively
was mad and was pacing around the
room wow that i'd gotten myself into
this situation i have felt that way
watching lord of the rings and star
wars stuff
like where i'm just like some of
it i have found myself surprised that
i liked and then other stuff i'm
like this is this part's going on
forever i can't do that to do
that as what's going on it feels
crazy i actually were about to bring
newcomers back but i haven't we haven't
announced what it is yet but i
was going to have to watch movie
last night and then it got cancelled
and then i was like i don't
have to watch the
i don't under watch then i was
like so happy it's just a great
feeling the episode got cancelled is what
you're saying yeah we are we're going
back for i know what movie it
was and you you should be excited
about watching it makes it i'll probably
like it too yeah i think you'll
like it i don't i just don't
know anything about yeah wedding crashers yeah
we're doing the wedding your wedding crashers
series
so it's like stops at one it's
like we watched the first one and
then we watched like home movies of
weddings being crashed and then we bring
in good and just quoting engine cars
like the honda i so many times
i've been like out of town doing
a gig and in the hotel there's
a wedding reception and i always i've
never done it but i was like
i could probably just want i'm wearing
a suit i could wow
walk in there right and you really
could yeah we did it once we
were at oh yeah we were at
i think brian zane's wedding at a
at a certain venue and then we'd
didn't invite you to his wedding
no we were there we were already
there yeah yeah again and then we
walked into a different wedding that was
at the same venue i get jokes
i get jokes good jokes no i
was invited guys did you see the
honda crash no what's that it was
everywhere today
did you see the hunter crash which
honda
there's a video going around of a
guy in on like a freeway or
a highway and he there's a car
kind of like trying to get around
other cars and he's taping it and
he's like
kind of goes around and tries to
get in between them and cans and
then he goes on the side of
the road on the shoulder and goes
around them and then spins out and
um crashes shit like flips the car
over and meanwhile the people narrating it
are like haha oh um serves you
right but now look
i understand that impulse sure you know
what i mean yeah totally i mean
like i used to talk about how
there should be an app where you
put in someone who cuts you off
in traffic their license plate number and
it gives you like a ping alert
when they get into a car crash
and die so you can laugh
yeah the kid shared that with us
before that idea
so i understand the impulse so i
just wonder where you do it on
you anyway
thank you i think you understand a
lot of impulses we might not understand
was it are you talking about this
video because you were the one that
filmed it ah yeah okay meanwhile i'm
doing an action
oh no swedish exit
um anyway why it's a spectacular crash
okay i'm sold and but people are
on either side of the issue people
are like people are saying that no
one should be taking glee in watching
this guy crash because you know he
could be seriously injured well do you
i tell you what i need an
update on this guy's condition and when
he is in the clear
or i'm going to laugh at it
okay good guys i got into a
car accident just the other day no
you pretty lady pretty lee you didn't
know what to drive
um okay check this out i'm at
a supermarket is gonna wrap oil stimulates
both
he can't do the beat and he's
gonna rapid it wasn't ever been amazing
i was in bonds parking lot okay
so i'm at a super market parking
lot okay parking i by the way
not five seconds earlier i had seated
the right of way in order to
let some people out of the parking
lot in
turn in front of me like a
good boy or good boy wow that
was really caring i was driving very
carefully and slowly
should not on my phone or anything
like that so you were perfect ah
i made a left into a parking
spot where there it was the there
was a car parked in the one
on the left to car parked on
in the one on the right this
is typical canby how it appears in
parking lots and you've been trained from
your driving training
to know how to park him between
these two certainly you gotta use all
training that's right i used i used
all of it i use to in
the way you learned deep down yeah
because every time i do anything in
a car i act like it's the
first time i'm doing it and and
smart that is the smaller scared thinking
hey
so i made the left into the
parking spot and when and i'm going
like you know two or three miles
an hour or whatever when i'm slow
and when i'm eighty percent in the
car on the passenger side without looking
swings her door open don't she just
sitting i think she'd been sitting in
there for a while because their brake
lights weren't on like
if she hadn't just got there i
think she was like reading her phone
or whatever and then just like swung
the door open and i crashed right
into the the edge of the dough
oh that's really weird accident and and
it it made a major like indentation
in my passenger side major operation of
my
my best friend's ride and ah huh
and so so it was shocking to
like all of us because cool op
was in the passenger side she was
like oh yeah i could barely understand
what was happening and then the driver
was like rattled and shocked um and
so here's my issue so
so i isn't okay for your wife
to yell
i back up i let her close
her door and then i go back
into the space
um my issue is that because i
have an old car you know that
has that's you know has some dings
already oh my god i can't wait
to look into the issue
i basically if she had said oh
my god i'm so sorry
i did that without looking i would
said you know on lance don't even
worry about it yeah let's just go
about our day but instead she was
either she thinks she's not at fault
or a whore she's been trained not
to admit admit fault
so she just like does not say
anything about how careless it was or
anything like that and to the point
where i start going like am i
crazy like was that my fault or
something and colombo's into to you know
make sure everything's okay and goes into
start shopping while i'm dealing with this
so i'm like psyching myself out almost
going like
yeah man it's like is it my
fault or something or have my senses
betrayed me um and so is this
a dagger i see before me
out out damn so um so we
exchanged the information and all that and
then we both have to shop in
the same place which is very awkward
yeah but so yeah so then i
asked up i was like
he's just circling the aisle at the
same time you you pass each other
and every literally was like creeping along
we were in the same aisle one
point and i i just was like
forget it and i just went to
a different iowa used to crash your
heart into her as ringo ah now
what do we do oh who's at
fault so i asked cool up i
said it was my
perception of that different than yours it
seemed to me like she just swung
the door open without looking and she's
like oh definitely she did not even
notice you and you know so yeah
and now it's all up to the
insurance like you know it's all up
to the insurance so annoying
so what you you gotta let go
like this yeah god if you had
said oh don't worry about it like
was there any damage on her car
there were like just first of all
those mercedes benz okay so that's why
she's worried that's why she's worried so
she had like she sent me pictures
of it there just like minor scratches
on it she definitely wants the money
me too on sets we paid for
yeah i would say i would say
she wouldn't be the type of person
with that situation if her car was
like really shiny and fancy that she's
not gonna go and whatever right do
you know what i was thinking about
today because i was in traffic and
a guy in alexis just like drafted
into my whatsapp candy
whoa i was thinking yeah yeah i'm
ray romano's child um i a guy
in alexis just drifted in my lanes
on the highway no turn signal my
fans ah haha way that's right and
my drift into your home is you
and i thought like why is it
that the people that are driving the
most expensive cars never use turns out
they're always rude huh yeah well it's
like wouldn't you if you had a
fucking expensive car like that yeah wouldn't
you be like hey everybody look i'm
moving don't hit me yeah i think
so
so when i had a mutual friend
talk about this because he's from the
east coast from new york city or
he lives there at least and um
sorry mutual friends with us with you
paul and he was saying i'm winning
he had an interesting take on it
because he was saying like when you're
in new york city no one uses
turn signals
pls because everyone is just trying to
eke into like you know there are
no they're basically there are no rules
yeah you know i mean like lanes
don't mean anything everyone's just kind of
trying to like fit through this very
narrow it's a self-fulfilling prophecy that the
traffic is terrible because there are no
rules yeah so he's like who cares
about it out there but in
in los angeles where we are it's
just very annoying when people treat it
like it's new york city and just
yeah roving all over the place and
usually stressful i mean you could always
tell when someone's about to do something
like that though it's like that weird
feeling like when you just see his
car said like yellow jacket says turns
your sunday what it is like this
person is about to like cut
me off or something or like they
they want to get into my lane
but they didn't see me there they
were just going to go and like
crash right into me and then they
do you know it's like it always
it always ah you can tell those
cars and also a lot of those
cars whenever you i like the thing
like that happens a lot is where
you get cut off by somebody and
they have like a huge invitation side
of your car
there car and you're like yeah you
need to start putting kind of turns
like ah you do whatever you ah
of people ie huh
as much as you want everybody needs
to get it together out there because
yeah obviously the three of us have
figured out and you are the problem
listeners why am i here here's my
question for you oh yeah another car
i had i also one other yes
one other parts of the story which
was when i pulled out my insurance
card you know like my turn
yeah when and then too i haven't
gotten into an accident in like ten
years only heard your voice i never
see you but but when i pulled
out my insurance card you know how
they send you like to a year
and you have to constantly replace it
i had three in there that were
all old they send you to a
year and you have to constantly replace
it yes
it's because they they expire every six
months but you also know constantly you
know you should do get the app
has actually i now feel like i
feel secure knowing i have the app
because i often think i bet you
have the expired one in the car
yeah what's going on well i have
i had three of the three expired
ones yeah and so when i was
showing it to where i
was like oh here's ah this is
the policy it's you know i just
have the old cars but it's you
know it's up-to-date and she she was
like first of all she was british
and she was like ah it's out
of date
but what does this mean how will
you like trying to trying to intimate
that like i was suddenly at fault
for the accident or something yeah it
was like it's the same policy number
just just take it down and plan
like you have paid it so it'll
be functioning was it megan markle yes
you knew it doing that
soonish accent i know you're not from
there movies
allows me to ask you a random
questions so ran ok go would you
rather be um a news reporter okay
here are your three options well that
sounds awesome you could be a news
reporter on like ah it could be
he is local or as nationwide as
you want
or would you rather be like a
host like a morning talk show which
could also be local or national like
today's show or would you rather be
like a sports announcer
i'd like to be a sports announcer
knowing nothing about sports and would you
like to do it locally or on
a national level o national tobago international
the biggest platform of international football game
have everyone be the entire time i'd
just be asking about the rules every
single i would like to be a
local sportscaster really because i would rather
learn
about the other sports that i don't
know then get up at fuckin three
am to host a morning show or
travel over the place doing reporting no
thanks ah so stupid when people make
you like you know unless someone's doing
a live remote it doesn't count as
news anymore
more so someone's just standing outside of
a building talking like who gets so
weird actually when you think about it
um i was watching bill the local
news the other day and there was
a woman who obviously they they don't
read the copy before they they do
it there's no time they're jamming up
the news sounded like this was her
first time reading jamming on the news
right chairman on this speaking in cosmic
um but it just like you know
i can understand some people being like
oh okay i didn't quite put the
emphasis on those yams and because our
you know they're good cold readers she
was just reading every word with the
same emphasis like she she was totally
lost eighty per se
wtf yeah that is odd no one
knows who's started the fire when the
firefighters arrived on the scene
you're z billy joel huh second no
no i know sir the fire when
firefighters arrived at the scene okay we
need to take a break ok goodbye
you guys promised to come back though
yeah i guess so promise okay i'm
dead
good because you've left me holding the
bag several times the last wheel started
i started doing an episode we do
about half hour of it and then
we come back from break and you
guys aren't there like oh my swing
we do about half hour i come
back
half hour for me half hour for
you well for me one for you
that's right
do it okay we'll be right back
and if yes guys better be here
ooh ooh ooh la la hey i'm
being
ne da wo okay so that was
my first ethics question that my first
idea so by the way i was
not the i treated her nicely i
i texted her when she texted me
the pictures of everything i texted her
like i hope you have a great
you'll rest of the miss lu i'm
in love with pizza okay to me
maybe a miss
just saw you think a bang and
i'm so happy my wife went into
the store so i had a little
time alone with buddy
so i'm not the asshole right
okay so you couldn't even sweeter it's
really so this is my second ethics
question oh hs ethics okay now lauren
you probably know okay that my internet
was out for all weekend for four
days i know that just because you
said lauren can you lend me some
of your hardcopy porn yeah
and led me through eight hundred bytes
of your internet like and i didn't
specify the my internet was out but
you might have figured out master mast
for your box of poll i know
i'm going to be a boring box
my internet is out yet again okay
so i've regaled you with tales of
being on the peloton and how i
have ah
a streak at this point no of
over a yam have not i guess
you may be said that i made
me forget everything that i ever talked
i have no recollection of that whatsoever
i do know that you are riding
a bike with your eyes shut
i know you are writing a power
sam like your eyes shut because you
don't want to look at the teachers
it's a sin i'm talking many times
on this show but no yeah you
did a bunch of pelletizing it's pretty
i can't look at
you'll be mad i don't want to
think anything i don't want to have
lesson my heart so you know you
know that reference jimmy carter c or
hugo
re making lauren holes were making for
an old
oh i just it's like podcast that
makes you get old like the beach
yeah threesome is the old of podcasts
my beard is so long
on your knees how long would it
be my neighbor your knee your leg
here and here tea beer because your
need doesn't really get hairy it's like
right under your knee and it would
be like having a little beard gets
hairy is really not like ah the
same as the leg but there's hey
my kneecaps are pretty bald let's check
our kneecaps everyone and everyone listen
being reach down and touch your kneecap
to smash down touching a cup to
do do do do do you do
do you like right on the cap
itself there's no hair but then right
under it there's hay to me that
makes sense firing i have one really
long one in the center of my
kneecap
so that's it it was weirdness that
really leg hair only grows so long
yeah it should grow yeah it should
grow like acciona yes even your eyebrows
start to get nearer after a while
you know what i mean yeah my
leg is grown up too i asked
i shave
ah so what what happens so so
okay so i've had you i would
you want your tree knock on your
neighbor's house and you stole their internet
no i've had a streak going on
this on the peloton but my week
was i was i was going to
get on my my week was just
about over when my internet went out
and i went out worrying about
through the rest of the week it
went out through the rest of the
week oh that's a lie one time
my streak wasn't was i was not
gonna be able to keep my streak
going well i have a question i
don't understand i never used boulton there's
no like um not online setting where
you can just record your score or
like your ride don't
i don't know there was a google
sheet you can enter it manually no
but i mean like ah where you
would just press go and i know
that right around when you're on wi-fi
i know i have a friend who
like doesn't take a class he just
like goes through the countryside or whatever
because they have that setting but i
didn't have enough to do huh i
don't i think if i had turned
it on
it would have said like you can't
connect or whatever cannot connect so here's
results valid it sounded like you at
the beginning zoom errands
you did not write that icon's
so here's my ethics question on the
very last day my internet was still
not back the sunday is their last
egg from the i was i was
going to not have keep my streak
going and i've been proud of my
streak yeah she should be
it's something that keeps me going like
some some weeks where it's like smelling
like a streak going exactly so i
guess all i'll at least get on
once this week or whatever so i
instead i still i had my phone
was you know not connected to the
internet it's just like phone connections i
went on the peloton app and i
just let a ten minute long
um class play without doing the class
huh
so my streak would continue going now
am i the asshole is this a
true history that's fair given the fact
that you have you did ride or
no you didn't know i didn't ride
that week oh no no no no
no no no no no but no
but i don't want my streets to
go down to zero it doesn't seem
fair i
no but wait so you did it
you put it on and how many
days have you not written according to
the peloton at that point it would
have been the entire it would have
been that was the seventh day it
would have been but so if you
put in you put in the ten
minutes that means your streak continues because
it's because i like typical i took
a class that week so much so
my streak contr
menus even though i just let it
play and walked away i think this
is a classic i'll allow it but
watch yourself counselor moment yes yes just
there should be eligible there should be
a middle ground where where i say
hey i need to put my streak
on pause because i'm going out of
town or or i'm out of internet
or something like
that hey there are circumstances i want
to take this all the way to
the top of peloton and just yeah
really appeal there there's gotta be an
appeals process with these streaks because like
you know these were circumstances beyond my
control and i say yeah we're gonna
do we're gonna do this miracle on
thirty fourth street style we're gonna find
out where to sit
send postcards and letters to peloton and
i'm gonna dress up as santa yeah
yeah you don't have to but and
i'm gonna be the little girl to
like i have like a carnival like
one of those yesterdays where half the
highway's yeah you have only done on
tv shows i feel like where it's
like so like someone does half on
one side and half on the other
if you always
feels like a tv show tv shows
on halloween like we've gone there i
think it's due to weimer germany if
you're there to see some sort of
cabernet
so what's your idea of the listeners
to flood flood peloton with cards a
letter saying please add a feature where
you can pause it if you're going
out of town yeah that's true because
that would be really frustrating you can't
travel with that fucking thing you know
what i mean no i mean i
understood
and being upset that your streak has
messed up because i have this apple
watch now that i i had a
fitbit as a famously told everyone about
and i was really into it for
two seconds but then i got an
apple watch for christmas and it's way
better i got an apple watch for
chris mas um yeah and i love
it and when i forget to wear
it when i go on
a walk i am pissed yes because
i don't like i didn't take any
steps i still took the step i'm
like i want the average to be
accurate no yeah here's a good feature
of that watch because i got one
for christmas one year um is that
if you start exercising and you forget
to like register the exercise
ps if you're like ten minutes in
it'll say hey are you doing this
exercise can i ask are you murdering
someone you know well join us ross
ask if you're murdering someone you say
no and then they say are you
exercising they say yes and then records
the exercise from the moment it assumes
that you started like ten minutes wow
which is good yeah because when you
don't get credit for your exercise it
fucking sucks i really hate that and
i like when my rings close quote
unquote yeah sure you get those fireworks
ah right like you jenna lauren actually
make it call me king laurin
mine calls me lord tompkins well as
of course you put a rank higher
than me
but yeah when you the the most
shameful thing is when you you don't
exercise really move much in a day
and you close the stand goal yeah
when i was like yeah
going to bed it's like you don't
like when she tells me to stand
up to ten times today congrats yeah
it's a little worried they're just trying
to give you something
i'll take it i wish the apple
watch is connected to the peloton but
they don't know it's connected to the
knee bone so if you are on
the pelton you have to say apple
watch start my workout and then you
have to go pell tons start my
workouts like everyone's involved they they don't
coordinate with each other like like other
smartwatches do unfortunately suzanne it's like you
have two days
it's ah at the same time like
on a sitcom like three's company yes
for sure have you ever had two
dates at the same time paul know
what
i was like i'd ever have one
date at a time one date every
couple of years oh wow wasn't that
bad
so true there's a few years and
there were there two years that i
had where
the lean years twenty three years twenty
five lean years and um yeah i'm
twenty three and twenty five yeah
i'm afraid i'm assuming that my frame
of reference for the sitcom cliche of
two days of the same time and
having rushed back and forth is the
brady bunch that's what i think oh
yeah that one but it wasn't it
was peter ore and it was a
halloween thing where he had to address
he had two different costumes that he
had to get it out of what
what do you think when you
think that do you have a sitcom
that you think of i think three's
company three's company i guess i just
think of like every thing ever there
must have been saved by the bell
whoa my brain leaks sees every reason
lightened um say by the bell
yeah definitely feels like something that would
be covered on one of those shows
but i can't think of it right
now what a sloppy ass show that
was that sometimes he came by the
bell yeah but you get stop time
sometimes sometimes he couldn't like what if
you could stop time there's so many
times you could have used that breeze
if i could turn back time everyone
to smile
he was invited to everything they did
that happened yeah that would be letters
made but everyone has a friend that
you absolutely cannot stand you know like
well of course we're gonna invite him
to this party
well you feel good i mean we
always see him so ah we're always
all seen together we have to invite
him do not speak feel of the
dead oh yeah he died know dustin
diamond shine on shine on you crazy
diamond parts one through five
oh no i know but i'm troubled
troubled fellow troubled fellow and and perhaps
getting our kids into show business is
not the right thing to do well
unless you know there's enough directly into
porn
there is enough cases of it working
out and there's enough cases of it
going poorly that you just ruined it
just like anything in life you just
don't know exactly yeah maybe if you're
good parents your kids will be normal
and be able to add yeah and
maybe if you're a piece of shit
and you're just exploiting your child you
should go to hell yeah look at
like haley joel who seems
he has a nice head on his
shoulders his parents yeah he turned him
right to ah teach him well and
his sister and they seem fine absolut
but that seems sometimes to be the
exception i don't know lauren are you
going to lie i die first of
all i'm putting holly into tv and
film student
she covered by media yeah i'm submitting
her on casting notices all every show's
your team oh my god i i
don't plan to put her into that
but um when i think about that
though that the risk of that i
honestly think it's it seems like there's
more cases where it's okay actually because
kind of hear about the ones where
it's crazy and you focus on them
like people where it's kind of gone
downhill but it seems like there's a
lot of people i think it's when
when you're on something successful that's when
it's bad it's dangerous yeah because i
just kind of doing the countdown now
in your in your twenties is is
right here that's should always be like
reading scripts and going like no this
is too good and throw yeah yeah
well like marijke nationally they like they
just great to be successful business women
yeah they're just too weird trolls who
smoke all the time
that's my yea i don't think they're
trolls but i think you smoke a
lot um yeah they do smoke a
lot but i mean you know they're
busy new yorkers they got to a
certain point where i was like ok
now we don't have to do that
anymore and we can do this um
that's what i'm hoping for with this
show that you you don't have to
do that anymore
you can do this without breakdown to
one day man i'm not going to
be here when we come back from
a break oh dude time halfway out
the fucking door yeah the second i
get that chance
i wish it wasn't trapped in this
podcast
we made that that deal with the
which why did i sign a thirty
year contract do you remember that the
it was an episode of the simpsons
oh yeah wait was it phil hartman
those two meadows who was like he
was honored for such a long time
and it was like somebody came back
somebody who was in the cast came
back to host and like tim you're
still here and he's like yeah i
love it and then they they move
off of the the group moves off
and they say onto starsky this song
what did i sign a thirty year
contract that's too long
he's so funny and he's very fun
another great never too good i never
get never see him anymore i know
where we reached out to him to
do wild horses i wonder if i'll
say yes i hope he will he's
great he's he's usually pretty game for
stuff he's and he's now he's just
the best i'm i'm such a humane
recently did a show with him at
largo so that's how we met
get him there you go her there
you go was really funny and those
will ferrell and molly shannon ah like
new year's day parade event yeah yes
that's such a great good it's such
a great gig i went to it
the first year they did it umm
because ah we got to we got
like really
the good seats because they were brad
broadcasting right from the start of the
parade so basically funny or die was
like hey if you wanna go this
is like the best version of going
to the to the the road tournament
of roses parade you'll ever have because
we're gonna give you free parking no
one's allowed to park anywhere near there
but you can park near there and
you're right there at the
start of the thing and we were
literally below will and molly as they
were doing it they were facing the
other way from the parade that's fine
you hear that it was so we
could hear them so it was like
we'll shouting every once in a while
but but it also is just really
fun to watch the parade like as
it start like everyone as it started
in that yeah when the parade starts
like all of the big
pageantry with like singers and stuff like
that they're doing it right where you
are yeah that's a rose bowl parade
in pasadena tournament of roses the rose
parade or yeah it was pretty battle
of the roses war of the roar
of the rose drove over there like
the day after something this year oh
you missed it yeah i know i
was just screaming where
where's the fun you know um i
don't know that i've ever started ahead
learn no just say that i didn't
realize how big of a production it
was in the town like that they
had all those bleachers set up like
running down the main streets and then
all these like fences put up across
people's yards that people wouldn't walk on
them or so yeah it's it's crazy
because you buy tickets
for for even just like to be
able to put like a lawn chair
in a certain sachem even you know
and they after they have to really
enforce it so like i kept like
going towards the the beginning of the
prayed never on it as you get
closer and closer people are like huh
you know and yellow mature balloon evanston
um for the fourth
of july parade people put their chairs
out on central yes i restarted and
say so yeah then my high school
boyfriend put the chairs out like montana
advances like a joke and then gotten
the newspaper
honey yeah good i have never seen
the beginning of a parade
oh well i definitely have for the
fourth of july parade it's a huge
i love seeing that i love a
parade i really do i love watching
a braid on tv mike thinks it's
the most boring thing ever so i
have to just do it by myself
but i lie i really want to
get big enough to and i won't
but um to be a giant float
yeah to play norbit
you want to be a floating balloon
and macy's day no i want i
want to do the i love the
idea of the hollywood christmas parade what's
that it's the one out on the
hollywood border i mean i could put
it together
i've never heard of it is they
don't televise it i assume yeah yeah
yeah i've never seen this thing yet
it's i lived up from hollywood boulevard
and that thing you said sign of
my existence it was like i've because
i would forget when it was happening
right yeah not in the marathon where
the yeah your like yes yes yes
but but i watched it and it's
like the worst
celebrities and you just really wish because
you know back in the fifties or
whenever it started it would be people
like bob hope and stuff like that
so it's like yeah i'm a hunter
you just want like good celebrities to
be in it but then that's all
you was watching i was watching it
this year but i think there's some
sort of weird right-wing cabal who is
involved in it
it because everyone doing the the parade
is like and hosting and everything is
like erik estrada dean cain like all
of these weird jor like peterson yeah
it's all these weird super right-wing people
see i think it's interesting i think
it might be like a religious parade
or something like
aren't like good celebrities yeah it's probably
it's probably put on in conjunction with
some you know church or something like
that might be the salvation army do
they have something to do with it
oh maybe they so and they also
have these weird magicians doing close-up magic
like during the break they didn't have
normal ones they had weird ones
closer magic at a parade yeah it's
like really not great that's um
i think
he's gonna flow daily close order and
i think i think somebody's marching like
one card of ah a bunch of
magicians like as many magicians as would
be in a marching band marching doing
magic tricks altogether i hate the same
trick i would love to see that
actually yeah that would be great yeah
do think people the metal
right now it's like masks on and
being like watching close-up magic with a
mask on yeah well we're actually i'm
going there very soon you are as
received an invitation from a member of
the magic time i've been forever yeah
yeah within like four years five years
gotta wear masks
um unless you're eating
or one thing i always thought was
kind of odd about that place is
that they required women to wear skirt
yes i think that they require men
to wear jackets and summer like but
like if you are someone who doesn't
want to wear a skirt it's like
a really weird thing to have to
do well they've they have changed they
have ah um
modified that oh okay so you guys
i'm like a new wary like women
years ago you had to make his
way mcgee where i'm gonna wear like
a formal suit yeah okay well that's
good yeah yeah yeah i didn't i
didn't like that
i don't blame you and do anything
about it we're a fucking skirt and
shut up
you took it yeah but now you
were scared sometimes right no i don't
mind wearing drugs but i but don't
like the not all my friend would
like to yes friends who didn't want
to do that right yeah yeah i
did but it was just like it
used to be a deal-breaker now it's
it's a little easier to deal maker
yeah it's a fresh maker doo doo
doo doo doo ah alright we have
to take a break promise me you're
gonna be here guys gotta promise you
said you were gonna leave as soon
as you say good catch lauren yeah
right i'm wrong we need to take
that
bye for now
if you're editing this please cut before
ah
jesus did you do do do ah
where back i got it i got
an email this is the subject line
i get to use all the times
go sorry what what does it you
deserve this you deserve this scott who
are you gonna get punished
are you thinking to me like a
treat it's just someone trying to sell
me something you deserve this sometimes the
oh my god i had the craziest
one actually the other day this this
actually takes the cake um is it
from tears no but ah a couple
years ago i bought a fuckin squatty
potty from this company called
okay and i just noticed i guess
i'm on the email list i never
really noticed this here's one that i
got the other day the the subject
line is love to and then poo
emoji question mark so love to shit
love it absolutely love and then i
opened it up because i was like
what the hell
and then i scrolled down and generally
no more and there's a variety of
of topics they want to talk about
email and then it ends with a
tweet by by their social media and
it says this
deleting a whole text paragraph and spraying
your whole instead that's growth i was
like what the fuck what isn't disgusting
to you from a company i don't
want them talking about my whole i
was like yeah what for
i was like who was the tweet
for this is so grazie they love
we go evenings by day and you
don't like gere they love to spell
it out like it's called tashi first
of all there's a setting on it
says like yeah i know what it
is i think we should bleep out
the name of the company every time
we say it yes i agree
i don't want to even free do
you think it should be called something
more generic like you know
shithole pushers should just leave not even
about shit or anything i would call
it oh just like the spray i
would call it zba day this is
baby that vba day i just had
to say one more thing i opened
that email and i was i was
personally offended if i say things that
are worse than that every single day
but i couldn't believe that they would
send that went on
in their list yeah
knows who's getting that what if what
if there's a duke or a president
alright i i i've talked about this
on twitter but i once bought a
plaid cap from this tartan shop online
and they have emailed me i'm gonna
say every other day for five years
what's so good i just started going
through some of those and like unsubscribing
because i feel like i've put up
in spam it still doesn't work whatever
and i still want i wanna unsubscribe
me off the list but i will
look at ngo the options to be
like email me every day email me
once a week yeah email ones what
are you sure you want to go
and it's like i don't need to
hear from you
every fucking day on recently with my
dentist where because i've left a dentist
because of this that sounds a dentist
i went to before this his emails
was was would win when they were
trying to confirm an appointment would call
me text me yes send me a
postcard
tts and send me an email yeah
even after i had yeah confirmed through
one of them yeah they would and
so this stenting you and with the
implication that you had to answer each
one yes yeah yes and they would
follow up if you didn't answer each
one and be like why have you
not you know and so i just
left this dentist but it started getting
that way and
and people canceling appointments for dentist must
be a huge problem with the amount
of emails and well and also because
you you make the appointment six months
ago yeah and they always go are
you available tuesday fourteen point i don't
fucking know it's in six months but
i've started getting ya with this dentist
where i'm like i love you but
i don't need to hear from you
literally
every two days every two days now
yeah they it the old dentist it
was just when my appointment was approaching
now it's every two days they're like
hey great new deal on this or
like for those of you who don't
have a a cleaning scheduled we have
one opened up today you know literally
every two days to see me do
a double shot it's not my relationship
with yeah no my eye doctor was
telling me i needed ah ah coming
for talking glasses yeah they they said
it was time for mr magoo and
i say they looked at tend to
not be mister magoo yeah they texted
me oh and i was like okay
i'll get to that at some point
then i get like multiple emails multiple
tech
makes a phone call all all just
stuff is getting it's getting so intense
like you have to come in you
have to come in i'm like it's
up to me whether i take care
of myself you need to let me
go i don't want to like it
and then and then i went online
i finally made an appointment and you're
allowed to like says all these dates
are available but then like it says
none of them are we actually click
on them and then i i just
put in my like top choices of
dates which are three random days and
i put them all after two o'clock
and then they're like your appointment was
set for a date you didn't pick
two weeks later at eight am i
was like so what you don't even
need my input just give me an
appointment yeah just tell me what sounds
like a bad boyfriend who's just not
listening to you yeah it does feel
like that was very abusive
um it's three your time guys i'm
sorry i do want to talk more
about this kind of come hi want
to talk more my this by the
way i honestly could talk about it
for hours i fell for the scam
of when you go into your eye
doctor and i bought glasses in the
place oh that's a big scam how
much were they fourteen hundred dollars were
said they were somewhere in the
like hundreds and hundreds of dollars and
they're like oh your insurance will pay
for it and then i then i
needed new glasses after i broke my
glasses and and was enraged and they're
like they're like oh well you don't
have enough insurance money to pay for
it no because you made me buy
fucking sunglasses on my way out never
enough i just had to get new
glasses and i was getting i brought
the fr
games i've just refilling my old frames
and it was still so much money
and it's like yeah hey if you
want to see it's going to cost
you i know it's so i'm going
to sane and i should be right
they always like try to get me
to buy my contacts there and that's
so much more expensive yeah and then
i go okay i'm gonna get them
on when eight hundred contacts
cst or something and then when they
do when you do that they like
ok it's still a billion dollars but
then you get two hundred dollars back
if you send in this rebate which
you never fucking remember i swear i
have gotten the rebate thing and i
never do it and then i started
putting the same amount of money so
people remember hey to new rebates and
stuff like that i really respect you
yeah that's janey chinese great at that
stuff i
think my my skill comes in when
i go like i don't want to
pay a monthly subscription automatically with my
credit card or something so yes yeah
alert on my cal yes yes yes
yes that's great that's the that it's
great but now i'm like ooh you
got my email subscriptions i love to
subscribe to things i love subscribing but
i went through a bunch the other
day and i was like cool op
do you really need this way it
was like instagram re-post for ten dollars
a month
i now know the eve of the
repos step i use used to be
free and then they just made it
thirty dollars a year and then i
was like you know what i do
use it a lot but this is
some bullshit this is some that this
is some old bullshit yeah well everybody
it's time for a three cheer here's
some new bullshit this is yeah hey
and the whole bullshit yeah with the
new alright cyber new business this is
a thresher submitted by faith nicole so
close to faith no more do you
think oh clothes you think it's really
really close you know saving me faith
hills that it's like actress from eighteen
eighty three
do you think what a killer it's
like a um has that and then
i talked com and domo they call
me they call me yes when ah
when a famous person gets their assistant
to put together montage of all their
different roles i just like the ones
that ended up being like they call
me entrepreneur they call me mom i'm
like oh you're not understanding the assignment
sweetie
home and everything's yeah that's fucking know
he's there are so many that are
just like you're just a or or
and i also think you can't really
do it if they're all names we'd
never heard it we can just like
joyce memorize something we don't know these
characters is there any kind of care
i want i love to win drew
barrymore did i loved it when all
the a list when i really knew
what they were talking about kyle mclaughlin
then it trickled down yeah got out
of control you know i don't want
to say it's just crazy you want
to tom daschle did it was just
tony over and over again no it
wasn't
yeah he couldn't do it because he's
been named tony so many times you
don't know what we're talking about scott
please be more online it's grail healthy
would you not be more on how
good you know ah whatever save nicole
okay i guess you only follow who
you fall and a p santa fe
ff as submitted this game it's called
mm
movie trailer you are creating the audio
of a movie trailer one person is
the trailer narrator and the other two
are acting and creating the dialogue for
the scenes as the trailer plays so
for example the narrator says this fall
a family movie to warm your heart
than the other two must make a
dialogue from the pretend movie that fits
with the narrator has said
that's fine it's fun it's and so
xylo anything we do could the dialogue
kind of go like here's a little
bit of a scene another little bit
of a scene and a little bit
of a saint not just one long
scene because i'd be like a trailer
yeah like a trailer yeah okay great
yeah i love it great alright why
don't you narrate the first time okay
i will
and don't just say this fall a
family movie that warms your heart fuck
because i already started writing a scene
for that i've been typing i've done
two drafts at this point i mean
i saw earlier today i wrote the
whole thing
alright
in a time long after our own
on a planet we've never been to
hey
hey what's up
i came here to get your milk
money
doh did you hear where it says
that fits the fish at the narrator's
describing
i think that people will still be
saying what's up so shipping milk money
it doesn't mean when you think moshe
okay or continue with the trailer play
out this is the hook of the
trailer i paused it that's how you
get the people who are existing now
on this earth to to want to
watch it what does that playing i'm
here to get your milk money here
you go
oh
you told me you'd be paying more
this was just one alien must collect
money from every earthling she sees
knock knock
who's there ain't your best friend oh
my god i haven't seen you in
years coming
yeah hey milk money oh here you
go but when a streetwise robot gives
her a hard time
hey there jack and not again not
again unfortunately i'm gonna get you down
to the flip flop i need a
little lettuce for my tomato
oh god you know what my family
can't tolerate this yet again you've got
to stay away from us i'll kill
you if you don't but are they
warnings i am not alive but are
they enemies or frenemies with benefits just
this one last time
application i enjoy fucking you
they've got a team up to save
the planet from certain destruction hey everybody
go get that alien let's well it's
government in that declaration i shall assist
you in this matter we exclamation
do enough
it's a little vague for the trailer
are you already developing away well also
we're doing a lot of action you
know yeah so yeah i was writing
him yeah yeah and maybe face a
fate they've never faced before we actually
reached the end of the world what
are we going to do perhaps if
we take one more step we will
plunge into another universe
ah ok thanks floating now it goes
into that thing where it's like one
big word comes on the screen this
summer action
oh we but will
never
not again have
been
lauded any
more
period action e
then
oh god i'm so tired you i'm
i'm dead
i'm dead to have
oh i'm alive sorry ever
even i'm your mom thought no she's
behind you she's right behind me isn't
she too yes that's what i'm saying
think
wrap it out running around about
my god i gotta pee imagining
ah this trailers almost over i swear
ever
oh and i forgot to tell you
we're all in a gang
already fandango
hey how's it going everybody michelle bieber
burp i wouldn't think i would be
playing an alien but this time i
am
terror has an old name
ah give me that milk money geronimo
tron two thousand in theaters this summer
that was fantastic it was fantastic wow
time for one more sure ah can
i narrate sure yes kind of vanish
can an airy canary
skinny needles are
skinny as a needle when the summer
hits new york love is in the
air i know your study but will
you let me talk for a second
sure hey that's why we went down
here to the park i can't believe
i'm alone again and it's almost pumpkin
time hey you know when those leaves
start falling down off the trees you
no you gotta hook up with someone
i know but how
two guys meet on the street not
knowing what lies in store anyway so
i was telling her hey watch out
for that bus oh accidents can't be
controlled but they might make your life
exactly what you want it to be
how long have i been in the
hospital
fifty four years
we're old men buddy no let me
see that me oh they had the
love of their life while they were
in a coma the entire time you've
been in a relationship this entire time
with a nurse why don't keep me
in suspense how did it go
she loves you buddy you got married
but everything took a turn for the
worse when that poor woman he loved
so much got into the hospital herself
oh now anyway so i told her
hey look out for that bus ah
spaceballs yeah speaks
fifty four years later she woke up
how long i've been in the hospital
you're not gonna believe this but fifty
four years yeah the narrator said he
had a feeling
and her husband still wants to taste
a hundred and eight years old when
you were just born when we started
yes
why was i talking to a baby
about luxury pumpkin season very mature age
ah love so funds away no matter
how old it's participants maybe i now
pronounce you head in a jar and
head in a box
this summer the ultimate rom com i
love you
yeah well hey i'm sorry for interim
denser i was just saying i love
a youtube heads have to or we
need to separate you well but we're
in love and married i know but
we only have one chair it's coming
soon to a theater near you love
in a jar you could just put
me on the floor i don't mind
your chair
oh wait i want to root wow
it's my jar leaking
unfortunately yes you're gonna be dead within
the hour during marissa tomey i legitimately
won an oscar oh hi
and paul f tompkins look in my
first film role
it's love in a jar
hey that door's ajar oh i'm sorry
you race it's nothing personal in
oh he did
ah thank you facing cool for that
fun game we will do that one
again for sure yes um hey before
we go i do want to ah
shout out a couple of our fans
um that josh alerted us to we
asked recently on a recent episode um
who are we wanna know who our
oldest fan
was
and we heard from ah one person
h d model m o t y
l who is sixty six sixty seven
or march tenth happy birthday if this
is coming out around then it's not
um and ah they wrote to say
that they are ah our oldest listener
and send a
picture of a very adorable dog named
ned um who's sleepy but then we
got another email
i'm sorry to say h d but
yeah carry matsumoto wrote to us yeah
hi freedom i've never written fan mail
but i couldn't help it on one
of your recent podcasts you were wondering
how old your oldest listener is so
i had to write i'm not that
old just seventy but i'm a cool
seventy nice there you go so kelly
is our oldest listener so thus far
if you are seventy if you get
your thirty yeah
and you can prove it and you
have to prove it we know these
people aren't liars because of the way
they typed but if you're not we
do not accept photo ideas as proof
no we do not we need to
see like old photographs that are have
not been photoshopped of like you with
hitler or you know
no just like you holding a newspaper
that's really old yes you jumping out
of the hindenburg
but if you if you got seventy
beat we'd love to hear from ya
three dm usa at gmail dot com
were three in the usa on instagram
and twitter and we love hearing from
you thank you and i think we're
gonna get the phone number set up
soon yeah because while yeah hell yeah
why nah that
figure out what you can call us
about
yeah don't just think about random stuff
please we don't want to it here
are your ideas there has to be
some sort of theme you can't just
call a cry about your breakup
oh that's a good theme though you
know what actually cause us to cry
about your breakup i like that um
you'll win a date with one of
us tad hamilton that's right the secret
member of freedom
well everybody we thank you and we
love you and we look forward to
you dates listening to his next ride
yeah yeah see one here
if you want to hear out free
if you want to free it said
stitcher premium and also cvb world dot
com there you go it's good deal
you can't go already peace out peace
out as we say every episode peace
out suki out
a lot of azuki right now who
doesn't girlfriend
ah