three
kind of weird
you are saying what were you saying
booth said jesus jesus jesus i wanted
everyone to follow jesus now and what
he had to carry it to where
i did did did did did did
did jesus what if we all became
religious we would be the most popular
religious podcast yes we absolutely if we
did it for sure we'd be those
aw
we'd shoot to the top of the
charts right away yeah yeah the top
of this religious religion charts never everybody
one religion on apple podcasts what do
you read what do you think is
the ranking of religions right now who's
who's on top ah you have to
be to be ooh
but the bit about dragon age like
ever you say is wrong whatever you
say is shit
yeah well there's already a re why
would i say you jumped right guy
suits his pajamas okay now this is
the show
pajamas with the characters to show yeah
yeah it's now called pajamas wait z
yeah me i can markley but he's
on there a c other suits pursuit
with the characters from susana that would
be next level shit it would be
next level would be so mehta you
know and they're wearing suits right or
they're filing lawsuits i never saw the
show doing both
thank you both
i think it's called suits i think
so oh so they wear suits and
they file suits they wear suits the
closets were a fast women suits for
sure it wasn't called toots what was
cold but gutes why wasn't it called
roots because it was already taken oh
i was called zoot suit riots broke
out about yeah
oh well go onto it go back
huh what do you think about the
cherry pop and daddy's paul wow
pop cherry fucking nerd guys stay there
popping their progeny is the thing their
progeny it's something that i didn't think
about much at the time and he
knows just like three three random progeny
we're the children of the jury about
apathetic
ah we had our cherries
oh that's what it's why oh what
that means scott when you say that
yes well that's sir hey it's not
me oh sure what that means when
you're saying so cherry pie sorry laurie
you're tiff but daddy's is literal i
think it all three are literal so
yeah well then what's the big deal
the dad
is compact cherries but not other ah
fruit lauren the fruit well that's certainly
wasn't clear this what i'm saying if
all ice you're saying yes and you
know what zoot suit riots means yes
oh well it's it's really really rude
should look it up i don't know
oh oh
okay i mean they were i was
doing injury and they dance that's what
i'm glad that's what i thought it
was like hey this party is going
to be so i think there actually
was something called zoot suit riot wow
cherry poppin daddies even do that song
did yeah but deadly even do that
so just remember to do that so
just hurry up and that is ever
do that so yeah guys gonna do
do do do
i remember the time thinking the name
was just dumb and then for whatever
reason it's suddenly like lost a lot
of it and i was like guerrilla
zoo that yeah right meaning google go
just to food riots occurred from five
days in june and nineteen forty three
oh so it's historians were a series
of riots in los
angeles california which pitted american servicemen stationed
in southern california against young latino and
mexican american city residents oh no well
they don't like this target know the
target was mexican americans and other zoot
suit wearers victims five hundred plus arrested
injured one hundred and fifty plus maybe
the song is about ff
from their point of view i was
just gonna say let's look at the
lyrics to visit right yeah i always
assumed the lyrics were just like band
cherry bomb i'm saying i feel like
it's getting weird zoo so wait they
have that name terry poppin daddies and
they're not on the right side of
history here so stop whispering in the
trees it's two sailors and they're on
leave o pipes and
chains and swinging hands who's your daddy
yes i brought up the daddies again
fat cat came to play by the
way the jerry brown daddies we know
it's bad so now you can't run
fast enough you'd best stay away when
the pushers come to shove zoot suit
riot throwback about beer put a comb
pull a comb through your coal black
hair throwback cabal burger whose size
why are they here deb jitterbugging brown-eyed
man a stray cat fronting up an
eight piece band cut me sammy and
you'll understand in my veins hot music
ran i'm getting lost it look terrible
if you're one of them if you're
one of the fifty five members of
cherry pop and daddies will contact you
contact us and sue so fuck you
i don't think this is
i don't think it's good it seems
like they're on the wrong side of
the zoot suit riots but also to
cherry poppin daddies but it's just a
good song but no one has or
knows no one has ever known has
anyone out there who is listening to
this podcast a known what that song
is because he might be as we've
looked by the way you know what
else i will say did you know
what the do you know that
song was yeah exactly a few episodes
ago we mean jokey learners hypervenom yes
gas if anyone who listens to our
show is younger than me and people
aren't
in the new york thirty we know
you're younger than me i'm not that
young wait you're saying everyone is younger
than you i'm already paying all of
our listeners are younger than me or
older than you who's our old so
there's no one in between ok we
know our youngest listeners six that's right
but we need to know who our
oldest i feel like somebody we there
can be no one older
other than you that's younger than me
ah in that in-between is this like
those two years that there can be
no one older than you that's real
scary i mean
i'm a cherrypick debbie
yeah because also roy oh could you
look your child in the face and
say i was in a band we
had a very popular song we were
called the sharing of nannies yeah that's
fucking disgusting no that sounds like a
fun sketch
was really good i just did a
fun sketch yeah your sketch was really
good that you think this is not
really let's keep let's keep noise here
even greater going here what was it
dad well dad
what was it that cherry pop and
daddies are you're gonna pop my watts
daddy
did they ever
it's literal paul it's about the daddy
part is literal the daddy part is
literal but the cherry if you if
you take the meaning of cherry poppin
to mean what i mean that that
is the meaning of cherry pop why
wouldn't you take daddy to in the
meaning of ah cherry poppin because no
believing it's not
oh yes it's it's not cherry pop
and fathers we gotta move on these
traits and more this is the most
anyone talks about them you don't want
to to ever on it anymore i
love the nineties yeah what what band
what scott band do you want to
i don't need likewise sob an okay
what about ah you don't run that
zippers oh
yeah me afterlife who i read of
other areas
i'll see all day
hey da da da da da da
da wow we did it yeah it
was really good that was really good
thou is really good memo anything that
song it wasn't me i wasn't being
david sing that song wow my memory
put you in it where was this
this was at my birthday party i
was in which you sang rollin yeah
i did kidding all right
i by the way i was so
out of breath within two minutes and
that song is seven minutes long long
time that is a long song well
so someone else saying it huh gave
me saying no saying yes hell by
this rule no zippers i had um
very i had various friends sing at
my fiftieth birthday party at a full
band and people saying so
songs that were connected to various points
of my life as i reflected back
and so what did that song stand
for when that was it
that was the afterlife when i that's
significant yeah that's a future
i will be in hell um that
was when i like around the time
that i moved to los angeles was
when swingers happened and that revival was
swing mounting with swill revival for a
second while we were i mean all
that was happening right there on love
from franklin or on vermont people would
go to the darby the dresden and
the dre
entity in a yammer i think i
went one week style i sorta did
in fact i had a girlfriend who
like well first of all i remember
going up at the laugh factory and
i you should tyler was the host
and my friend and i did our
bit and she was like wow that
was like
like swingers from hell and i was
like i don't know well she's great
though something demand you i just saw
you and then thought swingers and she's
like how can i make the swingers
yeah but then i also i also
start dating a girl and this is
just because they renewed she did not
end up being a roommate i want
you singing the theme song reality thank
you so
her roommate reminiscence but she is no
longer with us if you have a
theme song for that in memoriam sure
oh yeah it's so haha before you
say go must remember the two yesterday
said we haven't previously mentioned in the
book i'm sorry your ex girlfriend died
but she when she did ex boyfriends
it's gone i both have dennis raphael
but ah no i don't know yet
ah that i know i will not
be speaking on the matter nah you
killed them
but um when she saw when she
saw me i think she remarked to
her friend like wow it's like swingers
and was like i was kinda like
i'm just wearing a suit at that
yeah that was the timing i used
to get that a lot yeah but
you know you're doing the thing that
was popular and in the nineties you
can have the internet to really go
look at other stuff was popular so
if you knew one thing that was
it return
earning over the hourglass
and i use it was easy there
was no internet if you know one
thing that is
and it was popular that you don't
gel your brain with all kinds of
shit all day you just knew stuff
where you didn't everyone knew one thing
and they would share it i was
thinking about address books the other day
oh yeah yeah and how just like
you had to you had had to
have a really thick one and if
you are popular and then you had
to just like write down everyone's
fucking address and phone number in it
yeah crazy yeah i liked that kind
of thing i liked to have and
you had to carry it with you
everywhere you went did
ah i of course have my royal
box office stationery like analog sort of
like stuff like that yeah but i
don't have any i i finally stopped
buying things like that because i wouldn't
use them notebooks and things like that
yeah because i would see like a
nice mole skiing or what yeah have
a whole wall of notebooks yeah and
i'm i'm the manager
me some nice stationery with my name
on it and i used it all
up writing back to anyone who would
write to me which by the way
if i haven't written back to you
this because i take kids in the
hospital sure
what do you mean anytime anyone would
write alert to to airwolf or whatever
i would owe a fan i would
write back oh no your personalized stationery
so i ran out of the stationery
so i apologize if i haven't written
and plus we haven't even been in
the studio so there's no way to
get this
you know i wonder if it's a
big pile of mail for all of
us don't for also please don't start
writing again
ah take the hint i forgot that
we made everyone's on postcards oh right
why did we do to renewing yeah
another season oh it worked which i
like we already knew we were doing
it was not endanger ah but it
was fun because it was somebody else's
problem i mean it's
other but it was opaque oh yeah
you don't mean yeah remember when that
came out was the big controversy of
they said it was other people's problems
but then everyone said it was because
really other people's pussy yeah but wait
a second this this timer here yeah
we just turned it over and already
run out before i ran out so
it must be
only twenty minutes or so no i
think
gosh so fucking annoying ever got sober
after stuff recorded i thought i i
thought i didn't know you know you
didn't do it and i i handle
this for me i can't because you're
i'm like i'm gonna write about oh
gosh lauren don't look at anything else
making school so you flip that over
probably for
a minutes ago yeah data to shut
up if that writes off his car
for thirty two i'm gonna call the
cops
oh lauren rameau you infuriate us but
we love you okay so what okay
here's what you and your your zoot
suit and and you and your girlfriend
calls you a swinger well this is
the thing though i had been wearing
suits since nineteen eighty eight in
my first call f tom paul did
i not wear suits when you first
met yes you did scott and then
you're like that's your thing oh yeah
now look at you who are you
the balls you're sorry so boss bruce
springsteen shit so brutal for thirteen the
bonds know i found my face out
it was too much work
well it's a bruce springsteen where are
you listing all the things that everything
that i'm wearing yeah but i was
i wasn't like polaroid at a ton
i had like you know a rotation
maybe three years like that but in
different shirts and stuff like that but
i have a bunch i also have
like things that have to have taken
in because i'm going weird right yeah
place right now we're only had like
a couple things that fit me yeah
i started fitting back into
my comedy band enclosing oh nice you're
gonna wear anywhere yeah i'm gonna go
out there and the sweater sin do
you keep them in a separate area
no i just mean like hollywood i
got a bunch of the clothes after
the show because it was stuff i'd
normally would wear but like you said
he didn't fit in them for a
bit well this is yeah they're just
all there they're all they're my claws
that like big metal toy that is
stuff i can't wear i'm like yeah
it's annoying
but um that annoyed me yeah it
kind of annoys me with your closet
really you know about wow so yeah
right oh hey there it's annoying yeah
very annoying could you do something about
a place i'm working on it slowly
but surely are you in like the
same size of like a lot of
his clothes lately so now
no more so does he ever wear
any of yours no he kept it
in my old clothes but he does
wear on my new clothes i got
these big old sweatpants to target that
he'd started wearing and i was like
those are mine and he's like you
are wearing my submit the link it's
not a free for all but are
you doing hey how tall are you
he's six three he is for six
two he
can't be six one he six two
probably i'm fine i know he's taller
than me is he taller than me
how tall are you i'm six two
and a half year probably are we
the same size i think i think
scott is taller than me he might
be like hey maybe he'll tar than
you think you are i don't think
oh scott you're taller than you think
you oh boy
two and a half but why are
you cutting halves when you ever six
to you know i mean it's like
you're six three because he's six three
yeah there was this guy that did
come up work for him i can't
remember because she had all these fashion
jobs um because she went to you
know i just cameras pop turn to
the left she she went to college
for fashion design merchandising so she
i was in the merchandising side she
did ed hardy when that was first
came out via juicers sales really popular
but um i remember some store that
i went into sierra with some do
chore with or whatever duty duty some
dooce past the dooce i said the
left-hand awesome banducci she worked with and
i walked in
and the guy was like uhm how
tall are you and i said six
to anyone oh six two and then
as we were leaving later like an
hour later he was in the news
touched my monkey
he was in the car he was
in a car outside and he just
slowly rolled up rolled down his window
and said good-bye six two
cool up says it all the time
yeah goodbye sixty missing a quote
that's a fun thing to say to
somebody as is it as good as
all mr magoo oh mister boo boo
i love that
you're by the way both of you
are looking like a real mister magoo
today wow were no glasses so you
just don't have money yeah
yeah yeah cleanly yeah reclaiming it yeah
okay my time yeah yeah i remember
that number one nevertheless she persisted yeah
no nevertheless do a clean time when
you kill never been this excited about
west side story you'd have thought automobile
shuttle
my my time no simple system were
clever but oh
should have thought a lot about you
know the c position huh and i
didn't do this kind of shit
if someone was elected i was the
first thing they said they went out
they were a senator they want to
kind of finish kinda finish noaa ship
assisted and like kind of did a
dance and sat down saturday but nonetheless
well that's the occasion i actually said
no taxable goods i don't know there
always were
this is the lab come about huh
there was good enough to toggle a
ceiling
yeah just kinda did like woo like
i did it by glass ceilings huh
what's the difference between a pitbull a
little suck of all loves was a
little bit of pit pitbull at a
soccer mom let's let's not uh huh
that's a pitbull and it's talking about
oh yeah i'm looking wentz huh
people said woo woo woo woo woo
woo
the people it's like
ah the glass ceiling a little this
little little little bit yeah huh
huh
because this is the little little squirrel
religious level
she possesses the same little justice
yeah the famous quote
we all said a little rough
still a little sore a clue what
the level us huh good style this
would be enough in hell yeah we
should just end the episode now that
fucking guy which guy lies which puts
a lot bill clinton yeah i did
not inhale yeah that sounds the first
one
saxophone that time in the timer when
he lied about playing the saxophone on
our city hall and then like they
made him do it he was like
oh mammy yeah and everyone's like oh
he's cool no remember with it that
was i don't know if you remember
nothing enough to remember this but he
was supposedly the first rock and roll
president i do because i remember phil
hartman being like being amy amy amy
i mean but just because he played
the saxophone which is a jazz instrument
they also did not animaniacs now i've
told you that i had a music
teacher in fifth grade you said stuff
that so many time
aims to be there that ah there's
ah a song cannot be a rock
and roll song unless it has x
yeah insane but i also remember when
i want to play what i was
doing i was told to put to
you the clarinet first as a warmup
instrument to learn the sex about when
i was in fifth or sixth grade
and then i play the clarinet and
i was horrible i never got anything
better maybe a saxophone was more expensive
and they were like let's just tell
her because made of brass i rented
it
oh my brother rented an accordion i
remember this having to go to accordion
lessons even though i wasn't taking it
but my mom was like make me
go to
because there's something for you to do
well yeah like well like she needed
to watch me yeah and she needed
to drive him so i just she
had to sit there and wait for
him she had to sit there and
wait for him so i just remember
and this is like nineteen seventy five
i think nineteen seventy six just like
this video screens have been invented yet
there's nothing else to do yeah i
just remember that that scene that was
my whole childhood is being in
the seventy s going to drug stores
and accordion lessons and just like sitting
around a station wagon you just had
to wait around all the time i
was always waiting in the car or
like hiding in the clothes at the
store oh yeah i would do that
too never like carpet stores too yeah
yeah you died in the close but
yeah rhymes going to like um like
the upholstery but i feel like that
was like a place where
went to a lot with fabric stores
fabric store but when they do the
curtains and the things yeah so then
i'd be so bored because it was
the most boring shit editor well yeah
there's nothing for a kid to look
at at a fabric store i remember
going to my mlis you're interested in
fabric wish i was as a child
wait does your mom joanne my mom
is joanne my dad's mike i made
my own brand so i was nine
michael seven ads
michael michael doesn't have an apostrophe doesn't
i don't fucking know i needed as
ralph's that's right and you know why
because it was more expensive think to
sign the apostrophe exactly far more expensive
really don't be cheap put the apostrophe
dbc pga have isos before i thought
this a million times if i had
a business you're like even if i
a mcdonald's franchise or something like that
like if you had ah even yeah
but i'm saying i wouldn't call that
my own business like maybe it is
i don't know but i think you're
a small business owner if you frankly
somebody asked you what you do for
a living that's your business okay i
run sales is big don't do it
oh i had a store but this
but i usually think about when i
think about fast food when the lights
are out of the
don't sing that song when the lights
i don't know it's i think you
make everything it goes out on in
the day yeah oh
huh think about when there's a big
m and then part of it's greenway
give me a minute think about when
it's happening and it's great because the
light is out behind that yeah you
are doing this already would be to
replace any light bulbs in the signs
on my business are you running for
mcdonnell
yeah we already are mcmc but yeah
i would because i always think it
looks like dirty when they don't have
that right and then i'm thinking this
isn't a great establishment even though of
course any today's just mcconnell still use
those mascots i know that they still
have grimace because i saw him on
the thanksgiving day parade then that i
saw me where someone was like they
asked um the
employee at mcdonald's about grimace and they
were like i don't know who that
is and then the person said he
worked there
but you definitely don't see them in
commercials and mean recap well maybe we'd
know they don't do that but fuck
ronald was which one of you is
going to talk to me on saturday
morning grade that's what that's what i
just said he did yes
i was there and grimace was there
but he was the only maybe the
hamburger was there too but i do
not see merrimack cheese or bitmap asap
i don't like i don't like how
ronald looks it's big mecca sheriff
no he's like a bobby he's like
oh he's like a tourist century and
rapidly from the fry guys are those
little things they're goblins i want fries
now knowing that the two characters mare
mckees and big mac who had human
bodies but then their heads yeah we're
the we're bursar's they knew
they were mascots those guys it's fucked
up oh what were you gonna say
because that's a different thing i was
gonna say it's that's fucked up that's
fucked up to have their arguing no
food no yeah you think it's good
ah there's a thing about the bothers
me because just like sloppy oh yeah
it's like nice thing there's yeah it's
a cheeseburger i eat your head no
no no your head but what if
the human body evolved to the point
where you had a normal human body
and then your hair was finally like
a baby body with a baby head
as well
but it's just another bio yeah nobody
on topic on top of your neck
yeah because the biological imperative to pendo
everyone thinks babies are cute and they
they loved them and they don't want
to hurt them so you had ahead
and everyone then all wore wednesday also
your baby's body you said it's up
the audience a body and head yeah
your head is a is a buff
a beautiful baby and your body is
inside said the shirt with somebody
that's a callback to a previous episode
we were and knew for sure her
to see if you can find it
in the archives go back one week
i would just watched i would just
punched me a wall i would just
put people in the stomach yeah and
the baby stomach or that if you
ok so like that
maybe and over like this to be
he saw paul loves babies i do
love babies i feel like when you've
brought your baby and earlier i gave
a short shrift because i was concerned
about setting up period ah yeah i
didn't think i wanted to say i
was thinking about that the other night
i was like i didn't give holly
her
do i feel like i was a
little distracted yeah give her flowers yeah
exactly well another time okay oh this
is making me think you're never gonna
let me see other time for sure
it'll happen later i got to hold
holly it was very exciting yeah you
did this but i was distracted wow
yeah that's on you i have
something i wanted to bring up oh
no scott this is president palmer and
asian ko na foundation corner god rotation
corps not about either of you check
gone okay doesn't have to be okay
lots of it is about somebody okay
okay so we've narrowed it down i
twice now i've been walking
in
our two dogs
and i've seen a dog wandering around
in a yard loose and i've come
up to it and taken it and
and the first time it had a
color that said where it lived i've
taken it to the the house and
said is this your dog i found
him wandering around and it's always both
at times like three always both times
both times three three like ten year
old girls answer the door together what
three ten year old girls answered it
like a thirty year old no three
ten year old girls answered the door
and they're like it's your girl
they're all one person
no they all the answer they go
the first time it was like someone's
at the door and he's got our
dog and then i'm like is this
your dog i've found him wandering around
they're like oh thank yeah and then
ah then i heard them yeah people
need to know the face god is
making is not just just a dumb
child face but it's a face of
disgust yeah yeah like like
like god why are you bothering me
a goblin and the first time the
mom was like i told you you
have to watch the dog so it
doesn't get away or whatever fuck but
then happen just the other day again
this just the other day just the
other day as a matter of fact
wandering around in a yard little cutie
and by the way there are coyotes
on the street constantly though we seem
and cry
out of my fault just what you
have to do it i have a
guy who isn't you gave them the
address i know i haven't been van
and i looked you know i let
him he has
think he's going to catch me but
i'm smarter than them she means the
roadrunners that would transport no way those
are coyotes ever since a roadrunner i'm
only one scent of cherry pie daddy
but no so this time so the
second time i eat cherries you know
madame father said i know secondhand the
dog's not wearing a color other than
i know of no choice except by
ah okay i have thought about that
i was like is it possible that
i have a kid out there somewhere
it's like i know this yeah this
removes yes they'd come for you
ah but no the second time looked
up your net worth on the internet
yeah hello and comedian network um the
second time no collar but i knew
where it was and the second time
i i ring the bell and then
the just look of confusion that why
do you these things are these three
oh yeah and it was like
they're like hello oil they the three
entered again yeah and they're like hello
and they're looking at the dog you
must recognize this as your dog and
then i say is this your dog
and i know it is because i've
already returned to them and they're like
a good magician yeah and they're like
oh thank you again the look of
why are they so crimson just
and no one thing no admonishments from
the parents this time and by this
but how many times is this a
good thing to happen i almost you
just don't do it again that's all
this one more beauty and good thing
to happen but after that we'll be
dump it go keep it they will
keep when we left from seeing you
that day at just chaff in town
yes yes mike
a rescued dog we saw it there
was a dog and he picked it
up and then he was trying there
was no there was a phone number
with it an answer and then right
as he was going to like look
around a person came looking for the
dog and she was a brand new
dog they just gotten that was like
a rescue and he got off the
leash and he was all the nori
was knowing mike was like oh thank
god i was able to bash his
head in
wow
as a cafe owner
i'd had it for sixty seconds
those very sweet i was glad we
got to see that oh you were
there yeah i was in the car
but you guys were like way up
the street but we saw it happen
but does it does doesn't it seem
like they don't care about their dog
to have this twice oh yeah the
kids definitely don't care can i tell
you you know my dog friends that
i that i made friends with during
my friends my neighbors dog was making
friends here's what's
so one dog was barking like crazy
although one out went up there like
sometimes even marked me at all because
i was like hi sweet and they
just gave you the one barked and
then the other one was like jumping
on the barking one like knows like
oh yeah he was so high like
you guys were friends right away huh
i never really said hey sweetie i
never did i was getting so speedy
i used to talk and they just
kind of looked at me like hey
you're alright alright well but often when
i walked by with franny they go
crazy because i'm trained for iniesta
marlette a little more by the way
our dog got a cool output a
big buddha statue in our yard today
and on instagram and molly went crazy
because she thought it was real oh
molly she's like don't meditate here another
thing for molly to bark at every
single day yes i know i'm worried
because yeah it's my so my
dog friends in my neighborhood mate your
world i've stopped talking but yeah i
need silence right now okay absolute silence
for all to do the story
there's a new they have a new
dog in their yard this little black
pug who will not warm up to
me he barks all the time and
i try i put on my hand
for us now you weave a bowl
he smith
unbelievable oh damn ya da oh wow
yeah hey there we're psyched when krum
believable happened like because their songs became
popular again or or crumble from bernie
from believable or unbelievable what
what's crumbly prom believable oh breadcrumb bombs
shops restaurants where they ever says he
knows some trump loves bread which came
from believable
you gotta you gotta do everything you
like fuckin idiot joint
j cao you make chicken
and you just rip up bread and
just shove it on top of the
piece of bread it won't stick check
your bank i don't got anything to
say i ho didn't check and ah
heck yeah that's that commercial yeah did
you like my song was remixed you
got it right jamie and i helped
the little black dog helped to shape
it almost made me
a couple times and he will not
let the other dogs get pets from
me he like gets in the way
he doesn't like if it bites you
will you have it destroyed oh yes
you get to walk some town hall
i will like hold my bloody hand
up to the window of the houses
are calling animal control saying i have
a dog here to destroy
roy i don't think my neighbor thinks
that we called animal control and them
which we did not i yeah think
they think something but no you could
say did you do i have to
i have enough data on my but
i can't i can't say it on
the show and i'll tell you i'll
tell you during the break okay fine
most we take a break now yeah
okay bye
introducing nacho cheese crumble yeah yeah crumbling
oh come in ten seconds a real
crash yeah you're not listening to an
ad this is the show now we
just play that store not talking
we had we're not getting paid for
this show suddenly somehow just to have
ads yeah um but so they're not
breadcrumbs what are they are they're a
little snacks oh little ones they're little
what what what is a big snack
like a big shock probably a ah
thirteen i'll take ah weed by the
way this ribeye
minds me of the sketch that someone
was trying to write tim cutbacks maybe
during the bang bang writers room of
lakeman the world's biggest slider which happened
to be the world's smallest camera
like right on the line trying to
write like a crackers
there's not much more to it just
probably why it ended up not being
a sketch but it was a funny
concept development
ah
huh should we do another roommate reminiscence
and london no
i want to hear about your second
roommate should eventually but we should eventually
two in a row yeah it feels
like if we're gonna do it again
it should be two segments again you
know was ours full two segment full
two seconds wow
oh okay all information from that really
know we have why very little i've
spoken about my next two roommates endlessly
on this show so i'm the dough
yeah we'll skim the jesus and the
holy spirit
but but but but don't even say
that now because that's what you'll say
next time when we actually of course
yes roommate really listen so it's gonna
happen though is we're going to get
out of sync i'm gonna be saying
my two you're gonna be saying you're
too big you're saying i skipped two
and three i'm on for now and
suddenly we're on scott's fifth roommate news
the problem wait no i think you
talk about the roommates ah
in the in the letter confined to
one place yeah well my next two
were simultaneous right is that what you're
saying yeah you're right he's saying you
know i count them as code number
two's oh so you're oh okay cause
i had an apartment where i had
a lot of rotation oh okay that
would be different that would be we
would take those in order okay but
if if if
in chronological order yes yes but if
they're simultaneous what i'm telling you is
this is what we should be discussing
the next time we do we shouldn't
drop discuss this now no no no
no what should we discuss know our
discussion now yeah oh this is this
new business we gotta finish all business
first we gotta talk about something else
okay
have to switch it up now did
you guys ever have clubs like we
had a clubhouse that my dad built
for us the chef did you have
to do the president vice president like
that seemed to have to or get
to that seem to be all clubhouse
business was deciding who is going to
do the specials and then you take
the minutes and the secretary always got
the worst part of it because secretary
and student council i took the mini
it's because the secretary had to write
everything down meanwhile the president gets to
be popular and do nothing vice president
gets to do absolutely nothing and then
treasurer keeps money of which there is
none is how it really works huh
we had a we had a club
in our basement and the club consisted
of
and we sent up a little sort
of little offices in every
officers in the oh wow keep a
quick basement not not a cubicle i'm
a huge hit here because like office
space yeah there were we would like
use whatever existing furniture for like thirty
nine deputy chairmen cool and yeah all
day going like i can't wait till
it's time to go home and look
of coffee we get high taking smoke
breaks yeah uh
um but i was the president sorry
ah wow there were four houses your
basement yeah i wanna make the student
council secretary in fifth grade okay i
wasn't doing that student council in fifth
grade and i had to make a
speech and get voted why why are
they making kids do this so they
do it every year in your school
yeah every fifth grade
aid just shows just fifty so six
thing would stop oh six isn't another
school o six was samsung's eighty five
middle school six three middle high school
can read a junior high which was
seven and i always have to fit
do some math in my head for
that because i went to same school
for first through eighth grade and then
the same school for ninth through twelfth
ninth through twelfth yeah did you love
that loved it loved it it was
so exciting to go to a new
school when it was time to go
to now middle school now high school
that i remember how it was kind
of scared going to high school yes
scaring i still go to high schools
and you're scary about the data
so tell us about this oh that
can't be called ah
that is tell us about your club
so would you guys do there it
was what did we do that would
you listen to the radio or songs
by michael jackson on the radio and
yeah will listen to records of bill
cosby standup i remember we'd look at
how i can't say called her baby
daddies in the same episode
these two guys back every fucking week
there's something to say about them every
time it just comes up naturally they're
evolving um we did listen to top
forty i remember that so the most
popular forty songs and forty seven foot
tall very tall metal jacks was probably
in there at least some of course
of course what year is this
ah this was early eighties so he's
he's the off the wall album had
come out in seventy nine says pre
thriller and eighty two yeah it's well
early eighties so maybe thriller yeah absolutely
he he
well i told him last year silly
yeah i just want to say one
thing yeah he
two roberto e o level of people
id final point on this but no
one can speak after e
if i may i will simply leave
you with this dog
um it was you one of them
maybe the club yeah
it was called shangrila to really like
shangrila the from the book lost horizon
the song nufc howard know the hurt
not the hurt has a single asanga
way does that that was a citizen
who yes no citizen can call it
shankar law or no i can't remove
what they call it an okay as
you sure heard shit what are they
called it shows citizen k i still
all by the way anytime
yes yeah susan
i had to watch that in school
but what class kids in the hall
no you work kids in the hall
right hey everybody i'm the substitute teacher
i'm stone out of my mind we're
gonna lock your kid to the whole
thing
what did you imagine guys we should
be substitute teachers okay that's a good
idea as a trio you know what
because you don't have to do it
that often right yeah we should just
sign up yeah i think aaron whitehead
was a substitute teacher for a while
and she had like a consistent class
because the teacher had to have happened
and it was right yeah well that
would we
we would like bail the second day
yeah when i'm not busy tomorrow sorry
yeah i'm not being yeah i'm not
i'm not busy tomorrow sorry talking
that reminds me of this time when
i was in high school and i
was wearing a sweatshirt that i really
wanted to wear but it was really
hot and i was next to a
cute boy that i liked named events
who is in my line with me
and then my friend was behind wine
with men lunch line oh sure and
i was standing there and she
other friend was like aren't you hot
or like she said like why are
you wearing that and i said because
i'm hot but i meant to say
cold and i was like i said
to myself yeah this is just the
worst thing i could've said yeah yeah
and i remembered forever we should stop
asking people why they're wearing i hate
that like like someone is wearing
in a jacket leave him do it
yeah somebody was doing that to lauren
when we were in new york went
oh my god i want to see
a show together and this guy backstage
he would have let him he would
not let it get my coat was
like a little too heavy for the
weather but i was traveling and i
only had one coat so there was
no option yeah and i wouldn't have
worn it if i lived there yeah
but i didn't so
jacket yeah exactly but he kept going
about it the thing man yeah it
was annoying like i was like leave
peoples i was like oh to themselves
i understand that you're not cold
yeah but i don't live here and
why okay yeah exactly oh my god
that was really annoying i also like
what are you supposed to do that
what do i do take it off
and carry it well i'm going to
make you happy
so no snow no mo bitch not
good yeah good yeah going nevertheless super
i got ah let's put the glass
syllables a point of light so tell
us physical role of tony end of
this story which i don't remember the
meaning we're just talking about clubhouses oh
yeah so so it was called shangri
la love to end it was based
on in the house
moisturizing so i just check it was
a concept shangrila shambala charm but we're
on the road to shine law here
a what's that old saying goes hold
on like what your dough say no
ah things give us clue you were
doing i think it's like chris isaac
or something it goes like oh wicked
oh that there is no other chris
issac song okay yeah thanks i think
that it's gonna go high like that
no ho
a dozen nuns and i don't want
em on them and i want to
follow him well he doesn't want to
he doesn't want to fall it's a
wicked game you think he's gonna sing
a song about wanting to fall in
love with someone i don't think so
and who sued things such as no
guys done moshe for ten i said
for twenty three at the earliest so
oh i don't know what we're trying
to say though it's it was to
be i bet a half hour in
but it's a better half hour it's
not though well thirty fifty who cares
it's your hourglass figure it out and
come back to us okay
if i had a dime for ten
yeah
we had a club that i don't
remember what it was called what what
position in the leadership were you i
think we would always fight it was
my clubhouse so i think i thought
it should be i should be president
but i turned out but then my
brother was in it so it was
like i think he and i were
always fighting about who was what or
whatever but i feel like one of
us was
president one of us was vice and
then i two friends named edward and
one was how could you be team
edward if there were two of them
as hard you need to make a
decision yeah edward or jacob yeah that's
true that's a good point scott your
story scott when you see shimmering skin
do you get excited yeah
yeah and you have someone you right
now no i don't
oh god hi ya alright let's take
a break
huh
we're back whereby time for a game
that you haven't run past you guys
just like i always do ready yep
the game we're going to play is
called henrietta henry jada yum yum yum
yum yeah it was submitted by row
re this game takes e o row
oh dogs going insane this game takes
a cue from henrietta pussycat of mister
rogers' neighborhood oh so your meow meows
it yeah each player must take turns
improvising a dramatic monologue while inserting the
word meow as often as possible if
they like every word
oh okay i just lost i left
it's not you're not started yet okay
okay so a dramatic monologue yes give
me a topic i'll go first okay
um i guess ah tort reform what
does that mean
i thought it was where about to
go to war that's what that means
no no but that's the top that
i would say put that out of
your mind and the topic is we're
about to go okay you're addressing the
troops alright everyone now right
yeah alright everyone meow
but later
everyone yeah
listen up now
she can't just
is it up now we're about to
do something really bad no meows time
for everyone to do with you
no expecting we because no question caches
up it's a question statement it's a
statement yeah i'm expecting right no no
i'm expecting we're all going to pack
up and go home mio
is that what you're talking no we're
not yeah we are now going to
do something very meow serious
shit are we supposed to guess now
everybody take your pictures we all supposed
to talk me out i'll take a
monologue curry thought okay now take a
you keep grab the chump grab my
ankles wow your ankle spread your shopping
yell and let someone go to town
ya know
you need to all take out the
photos up yeah your family's yeah i'm
laughing already out like a million you
know you are out for yourself
someone else did and i'm enjoying it
i'll try again but i but i've
tried to give me a topic i'll
try your topic is you have to
make a speech about um yeah it's
talk about there's there's a recall none
of your products
and so like i'm i'm whom i
use that as a company my addressing
like the public your okay it's killed
five people okay
good evening meal
my name is henry litchfield meow and
i come to you meow meow with
a heavy heart
male five people
have unfortunately male perished
because of faulty shoddy
parts meow in
oh hair dryer
emile moreau cool pass
this this is a new monologue
my ankle pads wear em i thought
i was like a tv no you're
gonna feel
yeah in afghanistan yeah
we need these air dryers i think
you won honestly okay yeah you why
god's turn give me a tub you're
right your monologue is is a passionate
plea to get back together with your
ex who you ruined everything great
laureen and i play the action yeah
one where one person yeah we're two
two two tens we're one of your
things yeah as trying to get their
meow meow meow meow
mail some real words have i thought
he was as often as possible oh
my god oh my fuck yeah yeah
yeah meow meow meow shut up yeah
shut up shut up shut up shut
up well i don't like my taylor
now so shut up shut up yeah
okay just look at me oh look
i love i love shop shop i
love you
now i look just shut up though
okay and let me tell you why
i love me
ever since the day that i saw
you rooting through my meow
trash
i knew that there was something about
you meow that just mao swept me
off my feet and i said meow
i can save this poor girl meow
what a horrible fuck you shut up
you're doing them yellow foliar
okay i'm gonna try game you guys
were too good at it some it's
on grief
okay and lauren you can't keep a
straight face i've learned know through any
take of any
you know as bad as rango but
that was just a boot
we were having a lot of fun
we're having a lot of fun i
can keep a straight face but i
was like oh um what is my
topic your topic is you have to
put down ah the giraffe at the
zoo that everyone loves you have to
destroy it lets everyone know listen everyone
meow gather around me oh hi
hi
what's um what's being see my what's
up plays mio i am ding dong
i am now the head graph harness
or meow at zoo you were just
hired like an hour ago you already
want to talk to us
yep is there something wrong with the
giraffe harness ah yeah the harness fits
fine now it's just that i think
oh god why was yeah long long
neck i was now climbing his neck
at meow snapped in half
yeah it's what
who hired you snapped in half now
and this is not good now and
obviously meow we need to bury him
so we so why are you still
i'm looking at me still alive and
pay you won't be soon yeah everyone
will jiffy can snap doesn't everyone just
meow quickly good hold
hands with each other weekly hold hands
i can do it yes you can
do it about it just matches is
this okay that's enough yeah and and
then we're gonna step on his neck
until xy
oh
yeah and we can't be in charge
of this we need to call we
need to call the head i don't
know the head of the zoo there's
no oh me oh i've been mr
hoffman news meow because my father was
the head of the zoo meow and
he since mail pass was dead you
are so when did you climb on
time
so an hour ago you were hired
as the the head giraffe harness or
than you killed the draft and your
dad and you get promoted to head
of the zoo wow you're cut up
ding dong
what's a place
hey this is a successful creature absolutely
no anything absolutely one listener yeah yeah
time to wind it down in time
okay let's go to a cool down
so yeah yeah yeah okay right yeah
who again you will start you can
return to your own thoughts
and it doesn't matter whatever you're thinking
and just sort of keep that feeling
of relaxation with you as you go
throughout the day you can feel the
weight of your body all day long
everywhere you go because feel the weight
of him i'd like to know how
many times you farted during the show
listeners not you guys gonna say none
i do not
none for me too by the way
i'm proud that during massages that professional
massages i'm fart free now you should
be proud i'm proud that i am
too i do think a lot of
people just let her i feel like
well i see i am too or
else people will assume that
no but i mean sometimes you know
how you drift off into an accident
yeah and ask that you get so
relaxed it's an accident yeah but i
am i'm one hundred percent have never
done it but i'd like to know
i'd like to
but i'd like to know out there
how many times did you fart when
you why do you want to know
that because i'm interested how many wider
norwich is how many people who are
listening to this light to get forward
on
well we want to know these things
so go head over to our instagram
threesome usa
yeah sure and and and just write
it just write it anywhere right
there's probably a boxy right they leave
leave it as the caption for one
of your own photos if you're gonna
post you to make it a story
in tags it has to be public
so and we have to hear you
doing it not know you have to
say i like
yeah so anyway three team usa on
both twitter and instagram i don't really
deal with it twitter that much and
neither does scott um scott deals mainly
with the instagram write me that's my
deal with any evidence that's my responsibility
as the instagram so i've been slacking
lately i'm i yeah maybe stop
saying i love you for two seconds
and post some content yeah i know
but it's just time these feelings all
right well anyway but sounds freedom usa
on instagram followers and eaten email us
three cheers at three most able and
listen and subscribe to this show wherever
you can and if you want to
listen ad-free you can do it on
both stitcher premium and also at cb
world dot com
or right here yeah or wherever you're
listening because we haven't done an hour
weeks good night crocs come back to
us we love you
nah come back come back from bad
credit banks oh crowley i'm about to
da dues your croc believable
a