three
for e
oh
three forty three forty three wow
and you say help me yeah welcome
back to three-time we didn't introduce ourselves
last episode but be shy about
and my friend paul and i'm fran
loren no i didn't say best i
said my friend oh okay let it
be known that no one here is
my best friend no i talked to
about your we know all about your
best friend we've heard a little yeah
same with yours your wives well
yeah she's pretty cool you'd like her
spring whose religion you like her were
parties to cc so were just talking
a little bit before we started we
yeah we were talking about my name
is paul yeah we said if you
don't know and he's twenty million well
we said your name is lauren he's
paul and he's
got then we can't help you walk
out of the country give the viggo
the energy i cannot help you we
were talking before the show back to
africa
live look ultimately that's where we're all
from oh no yeah you're gonna be
that person to say that to anyone
and it's not offensive it's never
go back to africa this is where
i love this is where i tap
out
we were talking before the show because
chevron over here mentioned um that he
has a personal trainer over here and
i think the only seven i think
the only reason anyone ever says that
is because they want you to comment
on their body so kevin very nice
body i think you he doesn't want
that and you said we're gonna spank
grandma compliment his body okay it's cancelled
i think kevin is calling everybody can
know all of your heavens cancel your
communication with kevin his i can't talk
to kevin anymore apparently not you can't
handle it you are one to talk
to kevin because you can't handle what's
happened then to leave him alone he
doesn't want to suck your bone
give him a break you know he's
gonna wake up in his bed in
the morning wondering why he is still
thinking about you na mic mix um
so we're talking about personal trainers and
you were saying you were and we
were listening know you are a a
lauren i'm saying she wanted to get
one and i just need to be
cool because i think
it's like part of the problem for
all of us as we're saying is
the feeling like it's it's not necessary
like no one's saying you have to
be there or you're gonna like i
liked it yeah someone waiting for me
and then like i if i don't
show up they're disappointed or something that's
like right it puts a stake in
exactly i want a candle in a
window yeah and i want what if
by law
and yeah two if by saying that
trainers waiting for me but we all
buying that might because i like to
do classes because i am charged if
i don't go so it feels like
yeah i'm only i only i am
losing but you're not letting anyone down
other than yourself which if you don't
work out you're already letting yourself yeah
that's funny matter leave me and so
it really bothers me if i lose
twenty bucks i didn't i sign up
for something i didn't do it right
letter quest money what if your money
got mad at you because you wasted
exactly which it would you give me
twenty dollars just for no reason yeah
could i wonder why the fuck you
needed it i don't need it would
you just give it to me i
don't want to will you though no
see i actually thought that was a
lie value
roof that says a lot about you
the other day i went i went
to the cbs and i checked out
at the self checkout and i got
forty bucks back on the eight on
cashback and then i left i went
to the manicure place across the street
and halfway through that i realized i
forgot my cash in the oh yeah
boy so mad and then
i called cbs and i said i'm
sure it's gone but i would you
chair and they didn't it was there
and it was now they held it
for me that's very nice yeah and
i came back an hour later and
bad snyder is goodness in this you
know or that's the most unpopular side
yeah but nobody used it probably something
right someone will be there taking it
or given it to them and be
like yeah no one's gonna see forty
dollars
in there and go on just leave
that there but i also wonder if
it came out of like a weird
hole that's like not noticed if you
don't get cashback because i didn't remember
to take it didn't like just pop
out of the machine it might be
trying to come out of a weird
hole yeah or a weird slot
so anyways what about ah you had
a personal trainer okay so i had
a personal number and i got a
story about machines ah traveling internationally when
they started using more machines to scan
passports and everything yeah a couple times
i almost left my passport in the
machine oh yeah like walked away from
it and somebody else said sir sir
sir you look at your passport
i had a thing again fucking terrifying
morris yeah yeah in a period of
time you know when i was travelling
a lot i don't know maybe it
was on tour whatever maybe i did
it with you guys i can't remember
but yeah we did it where i
would yeah hey remember when we all
did
where inferred was where i would walk
ham my my i did this several
times in a short period of time
where i my suitcase would go through
the x-ray i would go through the
x-ray the x-ray thing and then the
other rank again i know the charlie
brown and french moving and then i
would leave
the suitcase their picture only a french
movie i would leave the suitcase there
and then i would go off i
would go to my gate and i
would suddenly go
and i would like sit down then
i would go shopping then i go
oh my god i left my suitcase
somewhere and i would go back to
where i was sitting down and go
someone stole my suitcase and i'd call
security and be like my suitcases was
more than once i did it like
several times in a short period while
the first time i called the security
and all that and then finally i
went back to the to the officer
x-ray just sitting there dumb yeah i
looked dumb but no it i have
a several times were suddenly like twenty
minutes later i'm like where's my suitcase
and i would have to go back
and it would just be sitting feeling
thing that's a bad feeling it's terrible
um so i had a person i
had a personal trainer for a while
um in the mouth of badness
it's madness
it's madness it's just fear madness similar
madness is simply management
so since a mads it's so at
this guy i don't want to say
his name i don't want to say
his name but this is like well
always it though yeah this air billy
flail this is the year two thousand
things
and the year two thousand so i
had a director
it was an director it wasn't director
include you're giving us so i said
it was around two thousand i i
went to a gym and they convinced
me to get a personal trainer because
a workshop please he worked at the
gym and so it was a nice
situation for a while because he worked
yeah nice situation i was there
he was there he trained me hey
those guys it was good it all
worked out emily money gave me a
service for the money i like a
late fee but then then what i
guess he downs fell off so bad
it was it was like there's nothing
better than interrupting is already going to
get going and then
he's literally about to say like what
and then and then what
finish
yeah this so then i guess he
got fired from the gym um but
he's still wanted to train me and
i was used to him so he
was like but now he's damaged goods
well no but he couldn't come into
the gym viable ally because he was
fired from it but why i don't
know what did he do he never
said he never
so i'll take any number here yes
though but he still wanted to train
me but he was like ade somebody
fat well he was like i'll give
you a hell of a promo back
there
wow i've had
you said this would eat up time
and i should tell this story kevin
what number episode is this this is
like eight thirty it took thirty two
twenty nine and a half hours for
you to snap this fucking sucks
i didn't get scared though like i
didn't like it
do you want to hear it i
don't even feel like talking anymore you
have to because we've got another forty
minutes of judo just youtube to mind
too dumb it is youtube and you
want to be out i'm out can
i be scott well you have to
be yourself and usb him and you
do to them you do to ah
humans
so i hate scott
i'm here sigh i'm not here i'm
listening to you i would never say
such a word
look just come back okay tune doesn't
work paul kids leave this i just
talked shit about you it's a mess
it's bad for we need you we
need to we need to know anybody
guys
nah not going to
fuck you
just tell us what happened with your
trainer will be good what did he
do to you how would he do
do you like it okay
so so then what you sending give
me a discount so he started training
me i was house so much i'm
curious yeah well you know how to
access your hobby he has to split
it with the gym when when you
were know him
do you know jim's ooh nobody got
fired when do you even know jims
he's the arrangement previous was that he
would split it with the g yeah
for guys hey guys i can't listen
to a story-wise say i pay eighty
dollars for a session when he works
you pay eight dollars for a session
he gets forty or
yeah whatever and the gym gets a
cut shorter so now that you didn't
get to when somebody isn't working at
the gym he says kiss stay on
with me and i'll get i'll let
you have do it for sixty because
any keeps did he say keystone
it's like christiane
so i think this is a good
arrangement because it's cheaper same guy is
cheaper but he doesn't have all the
equipment so i have to go over
his house or apartment it was like
a bungalow okay said he also does
all over the place this is our
history oh yeah and is the other
guy in the other bungalow wanting to
be a singer
or in a band and this is
the year two thousand and it looks
exactly like scott weiland i was like
well what's your style what's your band
styles like well we're sort of like
stp and i was like yeah no
kidding yeah so down to the looks
so i go over i would go
to his house and he would do
the stuff with me right so then
but here's the other wrinkle he keeps
wanting advances he keeps saying like can
you can you give it to me
like can you give me the next
six months jesus yeah yeah yeah well
and then why were you going to
his house
it's not that five days a week
but how often how often yeah it's
probably four days a week five thousand
six months ridiculous events on four days
a week yeah what's a lot and
he kept like and then he'd go
he'd go you know ah i just
needed for the three months and then
it kept it was like i was
paying a year in advance at one
point i think and so then like
a commitment to yourself
so yeah the guy was a mess
so then ah september eleventh two thousand
and one happens you guys are this
are you gonna joke about this now
i remember seeing people on rooftops shirt
celebrating
i remember when the statue real thing
that happened i remember the your litter
was crying she cried she lowered it
touch the listed address she do to
ah that's how she put out the
fire fire was put out by the
suckers cheers so i think we were
work working
the next day i think it was
the next day was the day after
that my birthday and we that's right
and i went over to his bungalow
but we'll figure out where you were
on it i was like alright let's
like what do we do and he
goes come inside codes
i wanna show you something this is
this is what he sounded like yeah
he sounded like my older neighbor coming
oh she's but even various is like
come inside and he he opened take
out a suit yeah just keep going
he has me sit down on the
floor and he opens up the torah
oh boy
and he's by the way he's an
african-american gentleman from south america somewhere and
he says look at this look at
this
check out ah and it was exalt
and it was it was a verse
in an illustrated torah like sexy picture
with ruth playboy inside yeah and he
shows me a certain verse from the
torah that says something to the effect
of and god will rain down his
punishment tolling the wick boy and he
and you
know how ah in in the hebrew
there's dots above the you know in
the hebrew alphabet there's like the dots
above the letters and he says count
these tots comfy stats and so i
count and i'm like one two three
four nine now read this first read
this first and it's something else about
like god's punishment ceiling because countdown
it's come to debts count one to
eleven he's like wow
and then he just read to me
from the torah for an hour and
you paid for that and he charged
me for it and you but but
you were ripped when you walked out
and that was the last era i
was like fuck this i knock and
i just never called him ever again
and he owed me thousands and thousands
of dollars in training she says i
was so weirded out but i paid
him all night okay yeah because i
paid him in advance for like a
year it's a mess and then i
saw this is a mess there's no
other way around it and then i
i know
ever saw mechanic so for one time
um why summit m bar one time
sommet mbr on an open mike night
he wandered in and i was sitting
at the bar and he wandered in
he's like hey and give me a
big hug i'm like hey man and
he's like anyone can do this
and i was like yeah anyway like
anyone you just sign up and you
go up and he's like i'm signing
up and then he questioned did anyone
bring the tour know he went up
and then he for five minutes talked
about strange conspiracy theories with no jokes
huh everyone was laughing at him because
he was so weird and uncomfortable
l and he got off stage and
came over he said they were all
laughing i said dude they were laughing
at you you did yeah
because i was so mad about the
money and the torah
i have not seen him since wow
could be alive could only assume he
disappeared into a puff of smoke yeah
he might have made money even took
into the lion king i took him
and his daughter to see the lion
king at the pantages because i was
so fond of the charge for that
as well
way to work i will be an
entertainment logo
you sit down and watch puppets you
work out of the eyes
wait the broadway lankan yeah the broadway
yeah the movie you to know see
i took him to the expensive ass
lion king wow well because i was
like hey your daughter would like this
because he was had his daughter occasionally
she wasn't married to some dumb little
kid so betrayed so betrayed by you're
not ripped that's look
my body know he does it does
it explain it a lot of people
have that same experience with trainers so
i get it yeah that was so
typical so
my only my only experience with trainers
was we had a guy come to
our house those that a friend of
ours had recommended and i i have
a problem with that sort of thing
because i i'm not a good student
i'm an anxious student and i'm in
a hurry to know how to do
the thing already and i don't i
get very self-conscious and and
irritated when um i can't do it
right away and so somebody's giving the
instruction yeah drives me crazy it's like
i liked i like to learn things
all by myself i can be like
that too you know but the guy
also he was a frustrated actor male
frustrated so frustrated he brought it up
all the time
he was very it was very embittered
but he was also like cracking jokes
all the time like well kind of
thing would he say about career that
he doesn't know why these other guys
are getting additions that he's not getting
he's as good as these people have
you ever seen if you ever see
him in anything no yeah you ever
see him act no
then my wife hired a trainer years
later
woman is same kind of thing dr
the trainer was her name was dr
woman
impossible
the dog is london was real doctor
roman out there yeah for sure dr
woman was also a frustrated actor and
so gradually those sessions devolved into like
my wife having just sort of take
care of her right on her journey
that's it i just wanted all business
you know what i mean i just
like the
same thing with a haircut
what else were we talking about and
appreciate john where it's
i flipped the kid a fifty seven
piece i'm on my way can i
just tell you i google doctor woman
remained in the box around it now
and the main thing he knows dr
quinn medicine woman i sure hope so
but then the people also ask what
does a female doctor cold ah doctors
how much
what did they do with the lead
doctor oh what do they do and
the lady doctor what is the opposite
to the lady here's another one what
does the opposite gender of doctor
you black firemen well i guess okay
what what jobs agent what jobs are
there where there's a female and a
male ah nomenclature well executor
exactly actor and actor chris executive trick
was getting rid of actress i think
it's slowly going away and everyone else
be oscar jeff rewards that's right yeah
but i do think that's true um
but what else is there is there
um a mayor i guess well we've
changed everything to male flight attendants was
stewardess that's right
the susan masu oh right yeah although
now it's just a mazuz right i
don't know
are men called misuses or are they
is everyone getting the same question that
you've ever wasted but we yeah yeah
here man
i have
then prove it oh i'll massage you
all right
oh sweet a death maybe they're just
massage therapist now it's cool feminine terms
such as like actress charette and comedian
charette march with the masses with respect
to the masculine actor usher comedian both
formerly in the sense that only the
masculine form we used generically describe a
mixed gender group why did that start
with end with only a few
we live in a fucked up society
where men were all women get nothing
why can't where women be grooms i
wanna be yeah grow
would you put nobody record dealing job
iowa
now the director is just using i
have bought all my life to be
the first woman groom let it be
let it be blocked
you certainly let it be after ten
seconds
me too
maybe a road that maybe
alright we need to take a break
we'll be right back by
one of myself and ah
a real comes to me speaking words
of wisdom ie what was john lennon's
last hit the one time he got
to chant oh shit that was my
eyes your salary
welcome back ah let it be let
it hey before we go any further
let's let it be
let it be you get off your
phones are allowed to glance at the
object the object of your phone yes
connect with us laura and i am
ah are you only on during the
show when i'm telling a story is
that it something you'll be connected do
you see let it
jimmy as it as it if you
want more from me guys do a
little more on your end
it's a given ticket doesn't give a
tick it's a given take my friends
it's a give and take but no
i'm sorry i glanced i'm only gonna
bring the breakthrough to mean back show
newark or so and the next bad
you're saying this like that was the
only time you've ever been on your
phone during the show like oh it's
so excusable we were on a break
jenny
janata to do a brain is remarkable
when i who will be because sometimes
i'll bust in on comedy bang bang
or if i get here and i
see the europe recording a command laid
out some classic charles of course and
there's a certain type of person of
a certain character of person who will
be on their phone when they are
not yes i don't do that during
there's very raw i don't think to
be fair because like i lose track
i have no idea what's going on
here i can say what
and you're forced to tell me
what will happen alright lauren bring something
to the table what do you got
right oh just our new segment yeah
bring something to the taping something what
you've got we'll start with almost anything
yeah what do you got ah turn
to name but what i want to
share he what happened to you this
week
haven't seen you oh i see i
got something this is what i was
lauren mean i'm not saying instead of
laura i'm saying did you tell this
to me
i'm debating because i have i have
a i have a juicy story oh
no it's not used to make me
come here i'm gonna vaguely talk about
this thing and then see if i
can get away with not saying it
it's not private but i don't feel
like telling you okay it's not private
but this dirty yeah it's sick and
wrong
the thing is okay so i'm i'm
basically doing something bulking no but i
but my my thing is what i
what happens latin my life is that
i will tell people i'm doing this
thing right now looking
for example like working out or something
okay right and then then i feel
like i talk about it too much
like if i get a new thing
that i'm doing then i talk about
too much and then like it becomes
like i you stop talking about that
just do the thing because i have
other front like so for seventy allen
for example i feel like we'll just
like complete
something and then say hey i just
did this and i'll go whoa i
didn't know you were doing that like
i ran i ran a marathon sure
yeah i've never talked about it yeah
for the six months but for me
i was just gonna run up near
this yeah like hey guys like oh
my god i'm running a marathon a
year i'd say that shy to start
yeah marathon i've started training for the
marathon everyone's just shuffling everything else a
marathon yeah yes so
so i have a thing like that
right now but i'm like i want
just you just bus down surprises yeah
kind of but oh also i'm like
i don't want to become like something
everyone's always going how's that going right
rather just do the thing i know
i can i will tell you about
it later but i don't want like
i'll tell you about it today i
just don't want to say it on
my
like because i'm like you don't want
to follow really i don't follow my
journey and if you if you don't
do it which is look the chances
are probably high you're never going to
end well what it is is i
am going to do it because i
am because it's happening but i and
and and at some point probably well
it's easy but i have to say
the other night
i like saw wild horses and i
didn't bring it up and i was
like ooh look at me i didn't
even break huh it would be my
thing that i would be talking about
because it was annoying had this thing
happen with it there's a whole story
whatever really you're not killing yourself or
yeah because it was annoying so um
no it's just it's it's not even
a busy exciting sometimes napping
and that's what's up is that it
is not exciting and that it's boring
and so i also know that i
would be saying here's my boring story
and telling it over and over and
over and i actually only told it
to three people which three let's count
them down mike number three my therapist
to my parents more than three um
and number one my friend dan and
my friend aaron but those are the
only people that i've mentioned it to
him before memory and your mom i've
mom and who have they told you
know countless people he's just got five
does your mom ask about me yeah
my mom say hello to your mother
for me she
asks about you guys and how you're
doing it i'm saying come on you're
like oh shit i call her on
the phone after i'm driving home from
podcasts and stuff do you ever do
you feel this way after you do
a podcast you need to talk more
no oh i am especially because wind
up and i totally get that but
for me if if we especially because
we
we tend to do two episodes at
a time i feel like i swam
laps by the time yeah i usually
do i'm retired and and then i
get home and then i'm reconnecting with
janie
g
how's it feel now about
from the outside i mean honestly it's
kind of fucking
keep your fucking feels good thinking i
liked it you've ever noticed you dunking
feels good faces of the show like
fire show champion bill marshall bill
she'll want to reconnect and it's sort
of like on the one hand it's
great for her to talk and me
not to have to talk yeah but
then sometimes also like i i'm done
with talking for a while yeah like
hearing or store yeah yeah you know
i feel like you can't do that
you can't be like oh yeah yeah
i can i'm sure you pun well
view zeppelins you're very withholding um what
was the thing that you were thinking
of but happened like yeah what happened
you do you remember this was a
couple episodes ago i told you guys
what i thought my name should be
oh yeah it was like yeah will
occur lumbar skene it was just your
bumblebee lescott dicks
it was demonstrate peacock thank you oh
right but you guys changed no
like at fifty here now dennis j
i'm devastated everyone is like you want
your insane what a fucking nightmare that
would be i decided to change my
name oh wow
so insane but you guys did not
we talked about how we feel about
our names but you guys did not
provide what you think your name if
you looked at a picture of yourself
a picture that you feel like a
professional picture that got hot picture look
at pictures publishing service got we can
only like your head like go on
google and pick the best oh i
think it's got
to be the the name that you
feel like if you crave right what
name when you look at yourself what
do you think is the is the
name that most perfectly describes you
that goes with how you look let's
see i've got a big nose you
know what that means yeah i smell
shit easier
i honestly do when i dejectedly when
i come home and god forbid if
one of our little ones has shit
somewhere like wow immediately it and cool
up you know does not have the
nose i have and i'm not saying
because of her race i'm saying because
i'm a big l mike can't really
sme
well as much as i can and
i feel i will notice it my
mom immediately thing too or she can
tell like someone i'll just be sitting
there at a computer sometimes shit in
my sorry body stop there is a
dust mold or some like you just
tell like yeah something has um is
wrong yeah it's a real hannibal no
i'll just be sitting there sometimes and
suddenly it's like my shit sense starts
tingling it's just because like i'll go
there's a shit crime happening so what's
your shame cry what's your name supposed
to being i don't know i don't
if i was looking at a picture
of myself i was looking at a
picture i want you to put a
picture of yourself that you like i'm
gonna say this is this little homework
so
moment for you guys i have my
ooh what's your say homework um i
actually think i don't know why i
just never come true before it's not
a name that i'm particularly interested in
i would say my name should be
her mouth gets smaller yeah
i can't think of a last name
okay the first thing i'm going with
is gretta gretta also it sounded horrible
coming out on substrate yeah but i
looked at a picture i saw make
sense gretta or like a gretel or
like
goody like buie
jane jane jean jane not jean jean
no no point for me jane
hey jane jane get me off of
this crazy thing um jane can you
get my mother on the phone but
i think jamie tarzan aim yourself is
impossible i tell you that i can't
okay so when i went to sleep
why is it impossible i did it
it's like a snap i don't think
your name is dennis
i think if you look peacock if
you i'm gonna give you a name
that's bad i don't like this that's
better no it's worse it's probably worse
so when you look at this if
you did not know me you saw
this guy okay that picture users might
this might allow you to harm you
look a lot this is my waltzer
doing right
my twitter yeah i'm pulling a face
here pull me on my twitter profile
pic if you look at that picture
and somebody said oh yeah that guy's
name is dennis j peacock you know
listening to the stage name but yeah
that's what i'm saying is is it
that's not you candidly that's you like
making a face thing you know sam
pancake yeah like i think like the
last name pen that is his real
name
yeah that's like i would not expected
to be real right but it's a
very that's like a fun last name
it's very surreal pancake yeah a mystery
that's just like
never occurred to me like someone that
like the doctor's like yeah
it's really fun this is something that
usually people who normally say mr whatever
their surname is choose to say sam
tim like sam are you like at
a doctor's oh yeah just to avoid
having my baby i get to team
do something macaroni sam good sam moroney
actually he's a good director i think
it's really yeah macaroni miss
after macaroni and then those people and
then like every character i come up
with has like a noun for last
name pretty much i think it's really
fun i when i went to college
um i went you know yeah you
know i'm educated you didn't graduate though
ah i did graduate from the college
i went to i completed i didn't
graduate
right from the colleges i didn't go
to ah yeah me neither so i'm
like you guys oh so i thought
it would be funny to tell everyone
that that i had a nickname that
i didn't have oh wow so i
was like you can call me jackson
that's so dumb and so
come on i was like cut because
the slacks it was like a forty
s like oh hey jackson it's very
huge so i was like you can
call me jackson that's my nickname and
roughly all of the administrators and teachers
and fifty percent of the students didn't
believe me
but then the other fifty percent of
the students aren't believing all did call
me that for years and so there
are still people who call me jackson
okay wow why did you want jackson
because it was forty that's because there's
like a forties like slang each type
of hell yeah how long i still
occasionally i'll i'll i'll maybe see someone
who's like hey jackson how long
went after you told people that yeah
how long did it take for you
to to naturally respond to respond know
i liked it like right now but
i mean right away if you were
right back was turned to stone well
sure yeah i said hey jackson you
and i wouldn't i knew it was
that i wouldn't respond trained yourself from
your core it it wasn't as much
of a joke as the joke part
of it was
me saying like haha i've i've done
this is my nickname already but i
still thought it was a good nickname
so i still yeah i'm just fun
so i still was elias being called
it i don't get it well then
my then my teacher sat me down
was like my my whole school i
need to tell him believes my whole
school thing was like my chair
i'm trying to figure out how to
manage me and so they like us
so they they basically were sapped sat
me down to try to get me
to admit it wasn't my real name
oh my jerri and intervention honestly i
would totally do that too because when
someone doesn't like that like that can
be so crazy and when you know
they're lying and you're like i just
gotta get to the bottom of
this like telling me the fucking nobody
it wasn't just about flying and they
will not admit that they're lying even
if it's a dumb thing it is
a man and even more if it's
a dumb thing if it wasn't done
that way it was telling me it
was done with the sense of like
you know you're going to be moving
onto because his actions and they think
you were like you're gonna be moving
onto your professional
career and so you know you really
have to think about like what your
name professionally is going to be and
so there can't be a lot of
confusion about it and so have you
thought about this you know because i
hear some people call you scott some
people call you jackson you know is
like i was like yeah that's really
interest but there was a period of
time where i was like that's really
interesting
that's how i dealt with all of
that myself like literally my point look
at the time but there was a
time where i was kind of like
should that be on my headshots because
just saying jackson quotes will i have
a last name also the ottoman part
of it was like x no no
i was for a minute i was
like jackson oc remember that i was
like
zuckerman is terrible please okay here's action
here's what's making me like laugh about
this it's so vulnerable for you to
go call me jackson
not done in a vulnerable manner by
the way old gambit it was me
it was me like doing it as
a like huh it was almost like
the woman saying she's pregnant too yeah
okay so it's really bad
um it was basically like so it's
like trying to you and if you
call me on it
but um but then i then i
thought about our arnold schwarzenegger and i
was like well he's gotta get in
line he's got a terrible name and
i'm doing my mom and but now
when you hear schwarzenegger no one else
has that name so it's like oh
it's a good name for him because
he made his mark so that's why
i was like you know what argument
is fine even though i'm not really
liking
incredibly fond of it no one else
has it um and so that's also
why during the bang bang tv show
like i would make fun of it
with the kieran's and holocaust stuff just
you meaning to the punch take it
back yeah yeah they can make fun
of you but you make fun of
yourself first you got boy my ugly
um non-sequitur
just remind you just as you have
moved onto a zombie
don't worry i know um
this is about nicknames fall oh name's
the punch karl schwartz oh
is here's he was in twins is
that where you going to ask yeah
was nine twins you know the talwar
de vito with somebody else i have
a baby and junior think about what
a bad name brad pitt is it
is bad but his first name he's
really like goober mcg gong clearly just
saying it's like
real name is really dumb i'm like
a goober mo gong what you're gonna
change your first name why not change
that awful loud noise not even weird
it's not it's a william bradley pitt
oh no but whose name is fake
like there's somebody where it's like they
have a crazy one johnny depp or
something that's the thing about pyd like
if you are picky
ng he's just something for depth the
second wow give me someone who's gonna
fake name if you are picking a
fake name and you were picking a
noun for a last name like a
lot of people do it wouldn't be
pit it would you know i mean
like oh he's right it would be
like you know quick well the two
together just sounds bad to right here's
a whole list of celebs
eighties who change their name orisha keys
alicia arguello cook changed the keys she
plays please keep me yeah i know
ashton kutcher christopher ashton kutcher doesn't count
brad pitt st came back in a
thousand bruno mars peter gene hernandez no
jupiter
a third calvin harris adam richard wiles
what's die
i understand we're very lateral and harris's
nothing cardi b bell callis elements are
that's cool wow i mean i got
better i understand that one now it's
hard to say demi moore oh yeah
i own john reginald dwight debbie morris
d m e it's like diem g
gene guns by the way about demi
moore
demi moore i've i read something really
weird about her because ah someone was
talking about an early eighties movie and
i was like oh i haven't i
haven't seen that movie so i looked
it up and demi moore wrote songs
on the soundtrack for which movie for
this early eighties movie carrier and maybe
shoving can look it up but it's
but because
is her first husband where she got
the name more like was a record
producer or whatever she started off before
she was an actress like writing songs
before she even acted yeah this is
before she was like moving stuff like
so she's she's either sings or just
wrote the songs to someone else sings
on the soundtrack to some movie it
was
a bit of trivia i'd never heard
but i here's some more jimmy more
trivia my mom or ma or seeing
her on the oprah show your favorite
and she um they were they were
fielding questions from the audience sure when
they do that of course of course
that happened of course it happens and
somebody said ah how do you pronounce
your name to demi moore demi moore
oh because because it is a demi
erza to me and jimmy margo's
more ah that drove me fucking crazy
yeah that's great frank ocean has originally
was christopher edwin breaux b r e
a u x but he said he
didn't feels cool enough and in two
thousand and eleven interview he said i
changed my name on my birthday last
year it was the most empowering shit
i did in twenty ten for sure
i went on legal zoom and changed
my fucking name legally
zoom dot com yes fellow who are
not lawyers none of us are early
professionals and you don't like your name
and change your name i'm only a
few steps into the process so i
probably shouldn't be talking about this but
by the beginning of summer i'll be
straight i'll be boarding planes as christopher
francis ocean i liked that he that
was the most empowering thing he did
in twenty ten yeah let's hear about
twenty-one i did fifty and
powering things in twenty ten and this
was the most
yeah john legend john roger stephens well
that was a thing i read about
him yeah that he didn't even like
that name from what i from what
i heard on legend yeah someone else
was like oh your stage name should
be john legend he was like that's
a little corny him and then he
went ahead with it that's big it's
no big state legend that's a big
state yeah yeah but just someone was
yeah but it was either that or
go home
well
you didn't go home tony curtis's
real name is bernard schwartz bernard schwartz
that's like a classic hollywood age yeah
you gotta you gotta change and so
it changes it to a vaguely italian
tony curtis tony curtis yeah that's very
oh miley cyrus's is good yeah random
destiny hope cyrus
cool where did miley come i think
her dad called her smiling mile here
suddenly oh sure sure and what's his
ram
billy ray yeah is a billionaires probably
are you bailey rae do you know
that's on or are you not jammy
ray yeah what is that it's a
song guys can't please don't they campaign
it is a song no i've heard
of it what i swearing now it's
two against one yeah but too dumb
you dumb go ahead do to them
i do wonder what would the show
be like if paul and i left
okay so finally okay so you guys
so ah italy first of all so
you're cutting to the end because you
have no patience oh i thought it
was finally i get to be god
is happening to me now you're not
here i'm alone and this is my
show who are you talking to the
people who are singing
pho anyone wanting those on talk about
ah you couldn't do need ah yes
i could if i had to if
you both died and i had to
keep doing freedom i am
when
do you think what were the circumstances
what were the weird god dripping weird
whenever he weird paul when i died
on the same day but not from
the same thing and totally different yeah
but everyone would be expended my last
worker but aquaman yet lee that would
be now that i would feel bad
for you but it might be like
you gotta go do an episode of
three of my god
talk about it and then i like
you guys like leo wouldn't care i
wouldn't care i would cry nah nice
ones okay you wouldn't care if you
died yeah yeah sane i think that
that's you sad and miss us when
you were in hawaii think that i
think i think that you
you don't care if we like everyone
around you don't care if we live
no i don't necessarily don't like chill
and i i of course would care
i can't even say i wouldn't i
don't like this bit scott i don't
like it i think he's being it's
not a bid i don't like it
but that's what's fucked up your giggling
like a little giggle or at least
i am not
this is not a bad i'm totally
surface do you think the joker if
the joker was called the giller would
he be as popular would it be
what i mean he was introduced in
the forty we get to the point
where we're doing like multiple dark movies
about yeah the giggle or i don't
know dr giggles it would work you
think so yeah i don't know i
think all those i
the joker so fans love it what
if he was called joey what if
he's called joey fatone the goods that
made me giggle did you see joey
fatone on ah with soy may seem
within the joker is stupid enough right
like that's a dumb red alerts down
the riddler like all of that is
dumb but we just saying
i think it would be fine penguin
is like such an insane character that
he got to play danny devito
would the weird black goo yeah no
for no reason i wish i could
do something like that but not all
the makeup doesn't feel annoying every day
to have to put on the whole
thing the one time i had but
abu old age the prosthetics old age
makeup for bang bang and it was
the four hours in the chair and
then the two taking it off
it was um it was really hard
now it's really hard to stay still
and it's like so annoying and you
i also think i couldn't because i
was in their way i couldn't like
hold my phone up to at least
read while it was happening or anything
you know i mean because like if
i'm maiming by the way putting my
phone i feel like i would
i listen to a podcast or something
or like put on a movie yeah
that might work that might do it
i what i did ah you know
a couple episodes of you're the worst
and there was an episode where you're
any eligible for that right yeah yeah
so just to try to get the
campaign going yeah yeah i'm honest
i'm not a big awards person but
i wouldn't mind finding an award you
probably weren't good in it i think
i did a good job so people
would check it out and if you're
anything like our television academy voter i
was a big fan of the show
and i was very grateful that i
got to do right um but there
was so there was one episode where
alan mcleod's character um get something in
his eyes and he has an allergic
reaction so they put all this makeup
on his eyes but that meant that
his eyes were effectively sealed shut yeah
and so he had to be led
around all day saying hey honey it
was a bathroom raese i think he
could see how like he had to
mind where his penis was as a
tim yea now taken
you could take you a chance to
take
talk he also wouldn't have to tell
you where it is
yeah
he is and he's down he's doing
snow he's doing charades where he's like
outlining a human body and yeah you
allied a woman's body by the way
that's so scott's body looks
shut up womanly hips and ribcage um
so l had to be led around
all goddamn dan so stupid it was
crazy and also we tortured yeah all
day long and a fun way my
eyes were covered for period brief periods
of time but i did find it
during your period no you cover your
eyes with period lie go blind during
my period ah lawrence samurais in a
boy
but i had to cover my eyes
like with something taped to them so
i basically couldn't see for extended periods
of time and i found it really
um isolating and i felt that i
couldn't tell if people enjoyed my performance
i mean i lost all sense of
what was happening yeah and that was
stressful to me
and i would have a very hard
time being blind yeah did you have
heightened senses and the other yeah it's
been everything i could hear everything a
pin dropped in the county and i
heard
which county were you in we were
listening hawaii okay i heard y e
county
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back
we're back and it's time for porn
porn lets the word orange and we'll
pipe in the audio don't worry about
it
fuck me fuck twenty allen faq buddy
yeah we played this game last season
where you do a one-word impression of
a celebrity and other people have to
guess who your impersonating then we eventually
added in that we all had to
use the same exact word i think
we should start around
round with whatever word you want oh
bossy okay i'm bossy pants are regina
facebook and i learned
and then the settler umbrella title yeah
yeah i read the cover of today's
book and i learned a lot and
they have alec baldwin arms now
that's his arms on the cover oh
is it really yeah you want a
great guy
and then the second round we use
the same word
as each other so we're starting using
the same word no we start using
whatever word you want that will help
us guess
okay it's helpful to use a word
guy theme of the person god i
have to sink people to imitate yeah
it was lauren start us off
melson
to say medicine oh missed you do
it one more time madison
morgan freeman no it was really my
guess too
madison
although what happens next is paul guess
or do i guess i guess i
have to guess ready yeah madison
madison
madison share no
we just keep going but the word
is related oh it's like i'm choosing
a word that's like part of my
it's like i can't say a full
sentence as this person but i could
say one word that might help huh
okay madison jane seymour merson
madison
this game is we're never guessing why
that's so obvious your impression isn't good
madison
all the listeners are hearing is using
medicine overdose george w they wouldn't have
to hear this you guessed right matters
if you are doing better we would
guess right
madison whew
what who would say medicine to c
everett koop who went so well i
generally ah he was a general doctor
strange no madison
myrtle dr wait is this is one
of the bottles and james guys know
madison madison me on a doctor on
tv dr phil yep ah doctor phil
wouldn't say medicine my if it didn't
boot camp i see a tea guy
he might suggest it
return somebody go somebody be better than
me okay
are you going okay
oranges yeah this is the easiest game
laurel okay what
oranges
oranges are in jazz yeah i was
gonna say peewee yeah i was well
you did say you are a woman
okay fine i thought so too and
so do i jazz
okay my oranges though no reason you
didn't say it had to relate yes
it's the word is smell impression oranges
relates to pee wee herman more than
medicine released dr phil sherry
i'm better and it's a fruit okay
apartment
jack lemmon
apartment matthew leblanc
apartment
david schwimmer
ah lord seizure okay frasier apartment
de frasier live in an apartment or
without a house is permanent apartment john
lythgoe
is it a man
apartment
who had apartments apartment
you're you're lifting up your index finger
a lot apartment
apartment apartment ah why
bill and ted
is willing to trade
is it the odd couple okay walter
mattes about two people walter matthau and
jack lemmon
apartment oh tony randall garrett get some
flourish i'll try it give it a
home you know i mean like giving
some raw to the person
apartment you're bugging your eyes huh is
it jeff goldblum yes ah oh apartments
dot com nice i didn't know why
but i got i got the impression
okay so now draw round whereas when
you bugged out your eyes yeah i
was like i know what that is
now we do around reality use the
same word of the lord is apart
meant and know everyone's different person okay
who goes first few same order same
order smarter um just trying to think
of somebody sure it's very hard it
is hard it's hard to think of
people that's why i'm so sorry yep
opponent
dr ruth
no no i know who is a
potent barbara walters yeah
okay i'm gonna say apartment as this
person good setup again the one the
one rule wouldn't even play the song
report
it's gotta be more than one rule
it does it's called rules the song
is called rules new rules
apartment
gonna need here to
alex baldwin yes
wow was i that good yeah wow
okay go me to film you but
it was by the way it was
the physicality it was but if you're
listening and you're like how did you
get our impression okay not part of
the show for the listener yep
apartment
danny de vito yeah nah who are
you gonna go jump lido o da
da alright one more round one more
round with swords oranges oranges and um
okay
okay um
oranges gilda radner yeah oranges
paula poundstone
oranges
ah louise lasser
oranges you're sort of like i imagine
you sitting cross-legged are you sitting cross
legged in this no shit like this
and like this okay oranges maria bamford
no
oranges
ah rene zellweger you're closer my loser
no scott was good well louise lasser
widow maria bamford yeah with louisa really
the fuck that is i'm sorry i
just remember her sitting cross-legged on s
l doing a ma oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's what that reminded
me
lie out of your mind
ah melissa via senor no but her
doing an impression somebody else right yeah
um sarah silverman yeah ah i just
yeah i hear now yeah maybe a
little higher pitch but yeah it's eight
minus too high no no oh hers
is higher hearses maybe more like
like a little higher no
um oh shit i have someone who
oh shit oh yeah
ah oh oranges
jacqueline yes yeah okay
i'm still
ah yeah oranges
alright paul do you guys who you
got
oh now i'm thinking of people that
i feel like i did the last
time we did this and sorry yana
a little zoo ah do us someone
we've all met
so we've all met
flip around flip around whip up a
flip dive light bring my fuckin phone
paul is trying to tape all of
this probably presumably to show you the
listener so i'm going to delete these
soon
alright
oranges
eddie peptone oranges
oranges i thought eddie pepper down to
it's weird oranges um oranges this is
someone we've met oranges
drew tarver ah does he sell oranges
no one is doing just that guy
in the cornell already you came up
with i don't know what he does
i'm taking a coincidentally he sells oranges
are oranges
is this a famous person or just
someone to leave canadian it's someone you've
met it's someone we've oranges hey my
name is z i'm trying to do
this person good technique hi oranges hello
i'm high arches high oranges i'm
hiring this person is it a comedian
yes oranges nobody else got the hint
so i'm saying okay well we did
alright where were you doing physical even
though they did they know and oranges
oranges are giving a little movement to
stand up give us a little sump
then you know what i mean i'm
knuckling center
and i don't know what movement would
help honestly what's this person like move
like
you know think of it this way
how do they move and how do
you show it what kind of shows
a wins oranges ah orangey orange whom
i met now i made single horrible
parameter oranges oranges
i don't know
guys give up yeah yeah give up
who is it gabe smith
john gabriel's first of all there's plenty
of physicality to go with that give
me an example i ranges yeah no
if i were doing yoga okay let
me try to see let's see if
we can be challenging yeah oh okay
sure
and you know
this guy oranges okay here's mine
iron good huh oranges now
alright i see where i made a
mistake you were you guys both nailed
it i was like i did a
little fizzy orange this is really hard
to do a little physicality you just
added how is worthy doing so like
humans we saying like
fuck yeah alright harris's oranges i fucking
army i fucking irish fucking on his
own he is yeah well that was
super fun huh yeah that was delightful
i mean we all do at least
one good one where we immediately got
it it's true you know you had
barbara walters over there lorne you a
danny de vito
jack lemon lemon lemon pie drunk love
lamb on mr lemon sang orange mr
orange is saying lemons oranges oh he
loves this impression too many miles jack
lemak i know misophonia is kick kicked
in i want my miserable oh musa
yeah well members of rodeos
nah me so here's your ponies
yeah me vanya long time i would
love to hear al pitino say that
when he's fully just kicking oh well
you started did it my good impression
of him yeah that's good enough for
me oh can i please play you
i don't know what this is from
okay good my friend aaron abrams posted
this it's a screen grab of something
that he was wow
watching this is al pacino eye it
looks recent recent piece here he goes
let me let me wait till loops
around again recent piece and there's a
dongle here you can plug in and
writes the the hunger this is a
dongle
that's a dongle yep
yeah new django won't fit in my
case ah okay here we go
i'm tired of talking
you can do this
i know i know i want to
miami
dream about
that sounds like lord yeah no one
to dream about it
you would do that but one hundred
percent definitely like to get to that
point my head i pill and dream
about is to get to that point
in your career you just where it's
like i can do whatever i can
do whatever i want and it is
watchable though yeah i would really enjoy
it's a strong choice that i enjoyed
the name sam pancake was underneath this
chord the
entire time oh like watching under a
sam we hope we pleased you with
this episode thank you mr pancake oh
thank you sam oh well guys we
gotta wrap it up we do gotta
you know it's the way it goes
sometimes yeah well i played i played
numerals play new rules if you could
wow you know guys show flow it
is sad to say goodbye at the
end of every episode yeah but it's
happy because we know we're going to
see chiller for the next episode that's
right unless something terrible happens where paul
and i both die at the same
time and you're not sad
i'll still do the episodes i'll complete
the contracts won't wait will we receive
alexander motion of your going to take
our money yes i'm wondering the work
give it to our widows know and
that's that well at least when you're
doing when the show's windowed and you're
doing the ads predict bills
at least that money should go to
our widow yeah if i'm doing ads
for dick pills i'm getting the money
that's fair do you think i've now
gotten rid of them as a sponsor
because i referred to them as dick
bills look they're pills for your dick
they shouldn't be ashamed that is and
they work they work on your dick
hey
hey i don't want to hear about
it they should call it ticking a
box nation but are they in like
us maybe then a box they're in
like a circular eventually i mean you
get a box in the mail for
sure yeah that's true guys
buy one around andy linear
oh my that guy
nah got real da
uh