ah you think that ah
i tried to do it
twitter yeah
get rid of your last threesome now
and it's time for she'll be like
actually you're that's right that's right through
to now
who put their little boop in
illusionary boo boo
let me say everyone's hi everyone oh
this is scott lauren
what what you were gonna say something
you want it to say look we
were full disclosure yeah the audience listeners
we record these two one time yeah
yeah this is sick a little brick
yeah took a break and it gets
real fun during the break it's like
a new energy and it's sort of
like a cow already it's a reality
show a union show yeah where there's
all these bitter recrimination and we bring
out a host and they kind of
like set us up to talk about
certain things
yes yeah this host who makes a
living by putting us on television and
then talks to us like we're the
scum of the earth yeah yeah it's
great yeah we love it proud to
be a part of this universe anyway
ah
oh that of course oh sorry
don't go cuckoo
um during the break we'd sang some
songs yep
and something that got stuck in my
head from the goddamned super bowl yeah
is unfortunately a racist chant yeah what
yes i think it's stuck in your
head because it got stuck in my
head nights put it in your head
i heard you i was in the
other room and i heard you and
i was like that sounds like that
but i don't think you're actually oh
and then you can't know i
was actually yeah it's it sucks because
you'll find yourself doing it it's so
catchy can we put differently or to
it
i think the problem is the melody
there's no lyrics but i don't melodies
or just know this is from the
la la la la la my god
you can be
oh i just remembered the teams that
were yes yes so the kansas city
chiefs any any team that has any
sort of native american yeah like what
does the kind of thing by all
players little bears oh yeah yeah i
say bear cubs so you just like
they decide to call themselves that
i don't know maybe because the football
team was first i don't know all
the pairs and then the cups that
so that's adorable don't know what's the
connection of bears with them chicago lauren
have no fucking clue you never saw
bear ah no you not even at
the zoo all the time sure you
ever saw but walking around via the
zoo i did yeah
yeah california should be the what about
the white sox there should be what
about the white sox well the white
sox the most unimaginative name i actually
think that's one of that's a great
one because it's so meaningless yeah don't
salute the red sox are good because
they have the red wine sauce yeah
like samson with y yeah yeah
why would i think she counts any
rate versus any red legs really yeah
yeah so reds is okay because that
sounds like a racist thing it does
but it it but it actually is
just about saudi e-mail suck okay great
okay gordy reading so these people i'm
not going back in the story enough
to figure out who they were
we decided to rename the team the
chicago bears in honor of their hosts
at cub park what so cubs came
first the team lived in arena team
moved into wrigley field which was home
to the chicago cubs baseball franchise as
with several early nfl franchises the bears
derived their nickname from their city's baseball
team so
i'm directly some indirectly bear whose sacrifice
because we were rebecca becca the sentence
where it's like as most teams do
or something as with several early nfl
franchises they derive that writ so there's
more than one yeah the guy loves
to know more about that i'd love
to know more some some cities will
have it'll have the same name for
both i
believe what about the e yeah what
about the eagles philadelphia eagles and then
what's the baseball team to fill ilias
yeah so that's in a way that's
based on because the philadelphia part is
based on phillies that's correct okay so
that's correct the washington redskins were named
the team named the team boston braves
after the city's major league baseball team
what
the redskins founder named the team boston
braves after oh so okay there's a
list honestly i can't get into this
right now and this is something that
people yeah google at your something you
can do in your own free time
for yeah for fun if you want
things sounds like a ball if you
gets fun i think you should do
it yeah if you think that's fun
who are we to say more power
to yeah yeah if your life hey
if
you're a racist it's fun keep going
wow
they don't talk about the fun aspects
they're having a ball lots of things
that the the there's ah it's so
weird that these people won't fucking let
go i just stop singing horrible and
although i don't know what the chant
has but it definitely sounds like you
shouldn't have a chant know and then
i also would say why don't you
just change the name
we've already been down this right now
at least one team i know here's
what really embarrassing every year when they
get into this cleveland finally changed their
name to the guardians yeah but like
new era all these merchandise companies will
still sell indian stuff because it's like
vintage because yeah because people because they
know people still liking you oh so
it's either
freezer making it's actually makes more sense
for the city because of the guardians
on the bridge yes absolutely
it's a cooler what does that cool
guardians on the bridge these big statues
ah it's very impressive actually yeah it's
really a role we we drove past
on tours cool and they're called the
guardians ah but ah yeah change i
was saying to you paul change it
to the jack white white stripes song
it's so much more fun to sing
change it to the jack white white
stripes song changes
the wax whiteside sol it's the jack
white white face aw it's how's it
going oh no witcher yeah that a
federation army data that that that that
the data that's when people chant that
at a at a ball game it
sounds really cool it sounds really cool
just changing to that we don't need
to hear that what did i just
hear about jack
white that and i'm very late to
whatever this is that he and his
singing partner were pretending to be saying
quite thank you they were pretending to
be siblings forever but there actually were
just twenty years ago they went away
just catching up i honestly like a
news segment breaking news i'm sure i
learned this at the time then someone
was talking about in a podcast i
was like
that's actually kind of crazy i go
in a funny way like like i
liked it yeah like they like yeah
they were like jimmy bit murky so
they pretended they were brother and sister
it's your sibling your dating situation they
were in i guess is a very
fun instagram account oh really siblings are
dating have you ever seen it i
think i really piqued your i'm really
interested in anything young new insta
graham ah you know yeah way to
think of it you don't like having
followed a key your follower know i
keep the same the day i sign
up for anything it says do you
want us to look for people in
your email who already are on it
and whoever whoever is on it that
day i'll follow and then no one
else ever again that's so weird
wow don't you ever think i wish
i could see one of my white
friends i was waking up signed up
for a service after you sign up
for a platform you would not add
i would not know never thank god
she's always she doesn't adore yeah no
i but i thought that the other
day i was like oh man i
miss this person or whatever i wonder
what their
up to i'm like i could just
follow them on one of their social
shy good but i have the rule
you do other but i also it's
like it's too bad what am i
going to just be on instagram all
day looking like this like you're supposed
to do no yeah i mean right
i'd rather i'd rather do suit that's
the old glimpse of the pete holmes
show every time i turn
ah that'll i mean you know if
you keep the numbers low you see
out of it and it's so funny
it's like i've never seen that ever
on instagram
it's like at the top of my
instagram every day because pete's one of
the people who was on it when
i joined my search ah like when
you go to the search window it's
always it it's a bunch of babies
dogs events almost exclusively it and then
once you click on one thing like
i clicked
on a yeah doctor who picture then
there's also thirty doctor yeah oh yes
like it's i'm not that interested yeah
i clicked on i can't remember what
it was i was like who is
that person i clicked on it was
like an old sitcom person or whatever
i was like who is that and
then suddenly for like a month constant
stream of content regarding that well that
didn't die
don't care the major family problem where
they kind of inundate you with one
person we were like i'm not actually
close with them i follow them because
i like them and they're nice person
but it's like i don't need to
know everything they did every day wait
so you're saying your explore page is
all babies and dogs it often is
yes mine is all like right now
i have a lot of his own
time like weird
i don't want that mine's a lot
of celebrities drama mines all just youtube
influencers wow people though why do i
have so much hello kitty in here
it's like a bunch of hello kitty
valentine oh cool me see maybe you
ate late and a dollar short hell
yeah hey yeah yeah kitty yeah good-bye
start getting the baby ones a lot
because coop was like hey take a
look at this tip right now everything
is babies like yeah it's kinda it's
kinda good when you get tips and
you're like you lead you to others
other tips and stuff and sometimes it's
a worry
wormhole of tips i don't need so
many tips i'm doing great yeah yeah
i don't like when they say things
like if your baby's hot put put
her in the refrigerator yeah it's like
no take her out of the refrigerator
yeah holt yeah hold in there and
she shouldn't be in there yeah and
it's already
okay
paul have a daughter with us good
cat have a daughter with ah oh
with the like go in on your
children should come a new one no
can you contribute your semen to us
and obviously implying that i have to
use it yes
no you can be an egg donor
and then he and i will okay
will both contribute the same and we
don't know why you because it's a
threesome baby so we don't know whose
it'll be no we should have twins
or each one is yes
made me sick as i was ah
we want to see by the way
if we want to see you ah
your freedom babies out there we want
to see them no we don't know
i don't want to see three two
babies what are you gonna say oh
no baby i don't know what it
is it makes me any eyes of
our faces all merges stand anyone's ever
hey you do that with three people
i don't know but don't try okay
and that's my that's my mandate it
is very funny that doesn't make any
sense though
i always wonder
i wonder what our baby is gonna
look like new and cool up like
is it gonna i was praying it
wasn't about you and paul
is it gonna look like oh am
i going to bed if i think
it looks like my friend toby i
was sort of like paying like please
look like cool please look like yeah
she's a beautiful woman but it's very
weird that it depends on the angle
but yeah it looks exactly like me
or exactly it's honestly fascinating that sort
of thing as you watch it unfold
we're like as they get a little
older and stuff and you see that
similarities at certain times or certain expressions
or whatever it's and then sometimes they've
just completely themselves where you can't even
see either of you and that's very
interesting too yeah so cute yeah i
like when somebody like if jane and
i are looking at a baby and
she'll say i can see both of
them in there and i'll say not
me i love her and
i don't know it's funny that we
are looking at the same thing but
perceiving it differently but it's the it's
the whole is this blue or yellow
pants without what it was it was
real it was a dress blue or
is it yellow pants it was a
balloon blue turkey picking always know you
go to court would you like to
yes i'm sorry i'm remember this
it was a blue and yellow rat
with a blue drive or a gold
dress no it was blue and black
black or gliding gliding gold like i
said laurel yanny laurel yanny do do
you guys remember right yeah that's a
beautiful name for a baby laura yeah
my daughter will be laurel yanny yeah
one word
laurel yummy and i am and i
only hear yanny yanny that's right and
i only i'm only saying laura laurel
i'll have a baby came up were
person of babies that you guy want
movies to be friend janie and i
were with some but with another couple
recently with
you love you lol people felt secure
in my life more episodes it's back
maybe but we the who had not
heard the who knew the the blue
dress dress thing but did not know
laurel yanny and i played it for
them and it was fun to revisit
that yeah and also had the exact
same experience that i had before
where i heard i hear laurel if
you're most of the time well i'm
just thinking laurel i'm listening to us
like lords laurel now you just didn't
dan yoni right and then wanting there'll
be one yani that gets in there
and it freaks me out it gives
me the chills i'm gonna play it
now oh yes i can finally i
can play it on here and be
better yeah yeah laurel laurel laurel yeah
laurel laurel all i'm hearing is low
roll me to laurel laurel laurel some
people hear yanny laurel some people here
you girl laurel i heard it not
at this time not yet
laurel
laurel laurel
yeah
they can say yeah this is podcast
yeah i only heard oral means that
i only heard laurel that time is
that one that's just laurel yeah okay
listen to this guy tricked you
hey maybe this maybe that was a
different one laurel laurel laurel
laurel feel like i'm going insane all
i hear is laurel over here too
but i've done it i've died twice
like never join jani in there okay
oh really they slipped up to yanni
in there
what are you looking at i'm posting
about me and paul
ah so you're opposing on social media
we're doing the show i could do
that while i hear laurel laurel laura
you know good point we can't keep
giving her these excuses yeah
it's cool watching like a hawk
are you almost done laurel yanny laurel
laurel laurel yanny laurel canyon county duty
duty duty twenty twenty baby will be
booty baby booty woody okay here i'm
gonna do a trick you tell me
what you hear okay
i'm gonna do a trick
watch me watch me don't want
duty duty
you're saying duty i was saying putti
i just
do you hear duty or prude
these dying law
soda ah great stuff plastic really we
need one of these once a year
not really old things can we revisit
done jack white being married to his
sister
choosing which sex and the city characters
we are yeah oh hey coming back
oh my oh is that oh no
no no no no no no no
no no no i've never seen oh
my god oh mike why are you
watching the whole season from one to
now no carrie fucked him over hard
two times yeah but okay aiden
amazing john corbett one o actor love
him to pieces the hunk from northern
exposure yeah the hunk from by big
fat greek wedding yeah that's right um
oh i like the random bookings
what i would like to enhance oh
sherrie deputy using serendipity i love that
movie um which one surgery serendipity john
cusack and um yes okay i've never
seen it would you be on ska
about this making everything a podcast um
yeah i have a bug you know
i love that
that movie i totally do that um
it's good for christmas time but whenever
someone were julia roberts wears a fat
suit for a little while now it's
like yes she's like catherine zeta jones
is assistant or something i feel like
holding back chat and then she becomes
attractive and well okay i'm okay julia
roberts fouled out there that aid decay
don't start there
but you know it comes up right
julia roberts father okay internet is helping
children with father jeff the killer can
i just say you're right she has
a fat suit in something eight is
coming back america's sweethearts and she posts
because sharing oh my darker that's the
movie that the they were watching the
night of the killer case
ailing oh show us yes show us
a picture of that and then oh
my god that story that that documentary
remains one of the best it's true
her it was absolutely okay why did
she do this still would bang she's
beautiful
would smash yeah that's what that word
hell yeah that's how we want everything
we would be anyway so whether you
would bang her or anyone
that should just be movies now it's
like would you bang this person yeah
because that's all that's all we're selling
these tickets for sweetie pie
um anyway aiden's coming back i'm so
excited i'm actually extremely excited about this
this is friend just like that but
weren't there already pictures of them kissing
that's what they revealed that's without telling
me know and it's like well that's
a big but that thing mr pass
hype machine because we want to see
how it comes together they kissed when
she went to morocco on
her trashy yeah she ran into him
and kissed him while she was completely
not available she was married to big
yeah and she's like should i tell
him and everybody was like no yeah
and then she did anyway the answer
was no way she shouldn't have told
him no given the circum
dances i would say he didn't need
to know ah it's so random but
aren't they married yeah but she cheated
on aden to be with bill when
you want to know if janie and
icos think i might be wrong that
you know absolutely
you know they'll be so gross
but i would want to know what
you'd wanna okay your frisbees yeah if
i like if i kiss somebody one
i would wanna know but i'm saying
i'm talking about carrie and big oh
you're not talking about if my kiss
somebody and i want to know you
think i shouldn't want to know that
i think it's unnecessary complication i'm not
saying you shouldn't want to know that
i'm saying i would not want to
know if so if if janie like
fucked up you know and it was
like kind of like is definitely a
one time thing they only kiss it
was a penalty cause like i don't
want to i don't need to hear
me out of it i would say
rather than tell me that why don't
we figure out if there's a problem
in our matt well that's true that's
true and work on that yeah without
that horrible information
and that would haunt me for the
role nicer i'd be very haunted yeah
yeah would you kiss a ghost of
xat okay i would marry just one
um i guess is that a demon
though if you can yeah i think
so sucky sucky awesome go who alright
we have to i would want us
yeah we have sick bay like
or at yoking of speaking of you
know intimacy yeah okay penn badgley ruling
i guess he doesn't want to do
is yeah teller yeah he's paying for
penn and teller cool
spoke badly
penn badgley is the story of his
story yeah that's funny
let's get these guys together they have
to fund your diet still exist they
have to at least presented award together
yeah just leave and tell it and
that would be really fun yeah please
gentlemen you've been asking for them bed
and tell her and then marie you
can't even these idiots come out and
yeah i also personally speaking exactly um
so he
yeah he's in the news right now
because he said he will no longer
do sex scenes yes or he requested
that no he requests show runners to
see him have sex well that's what
a lot of people are saying yeah
um that's a direct quote but um
yeah what are you probably twenty shots
paul i might come out with a
press release saying by the way i'm
no longer going
sex scenes and anything i've ever cast
in my thoughts are ones like what
i mean i can't if if you're
at the if you're at the level
where you can make a request like
that like fuckin why not why did
you say publicly that's the part i
well i don't know that he's out
i'm not sure how it came out
originally but he said he's a very
monogamous person and his he doesn't want
to be doing that anymore
and i'm sure i haven't watched a
lot of that show but i'm sure
there's a lot of sex in that
show and i feel like cutting off
though the storylines you can do well
possibly or maybe we don't have to
see them have sex in order to
know that they could twin curtain blowing
or used to do in black and
white like he's in bed with somebody
but they're out you know full on
doing everything yeah i will say it
was fallen doing stuff i feel like
sex scenes are so gratuitous they don't
really do anything for me oh wait
you know what i mean so i
thought that i thought that the discussion
lately is that when a sexy is
in a movie it is you haven't
like some people are saying i did
not give consent to watch that oh
some people are so but that's some
snacks and that's taking it
to an absurd yeah but i mean
i feel like a character i'm filing
the characters you know ah boundaries no
real respective right no notice
we this yes then way then don't
watch anything wow that's my lord of
the rings don't want you to see
them go in there travel you're spying
on them yeah they didn't consider also
the flip side of like i didn't
consent to to have sex thrust in
my face yeah but you did if
you're watching a show in which that
has ever done it to ya they
have warnings to watch it on
you can see tom cruise is a
little button that the first okay i
am gonna watch that i have not
seen that movie hey ma
and again to watch both of those
movies don't make me one sca has
no no i wanna go on lorne
hasn't seen okay well i'll just tell
you what i thought afterwards
talk for an hour
my talking for an hour i also
have a hot take for an hour
yeah i don't i mean maybe i
will have a lot to say i
also have a hot take about my
scenes oh yeah what is which is
that they're never necessary we just like
to see corals being yes but it's
not the people baby goats necessary to
the point they're trying so hard like
this was
justified it's never nevertheless i said hey
is every right to say he doesn't
want to do that anymore he did
it for a long time with men
i'm sure many of his shows and
things he was doing that yeah and
he just said i'm not going to
anymore they could have said no they
could've they agree it's a private discussion
is yeah i'm not sure why we
are being asked to weigh in on
no
oh and i think people's reaction is
very like um i'm asking it away
and people are like i'm willing to
wow you know why i just like
me it sounds like a relief i'm
sure to him does he goes again
i'm doing anymore here's my thing if
you're a comedian that i know stop
writing your own chosen making me look
at your butt
like writing your own nude scenes stop
it get out of yours is there
is this there dimmick it's happened i
think it's been like two people i
know have written their own nude scenes
like i don't want to see this
i guess i'm not watching shows okay
yeah i'll tell you i'll tell you
who look well anyways yeah big news
it's like every day i'm seeing a
new update about that and i'm just
kind of going update people are still
shows on you know know him i
know this is a high-level fox news
thing by the way when we watched
the show this was like a gut
filled bet i think ah
well we love you i am committed
to learning everything about you i'm like
do you think i felt a piss
pig fee but i'm sure so sure
he listened garfield lesnar yeah
but um when we watch the show
i like to pretend that i think
the the main characters named you hey
yeah they say oh you got himself
in some trouble this time yeah how
you gonna get out of this you
is you is always in something and
you is no longer going to have
sex scenes you is kind you is
good i even know what the show
is about it's about a serie
real killer named penn badgley who killed
amos
please himself
didn't seem it wasn't someone else in
there playing himself no ah yeah
i also one thing i do about
the show that shows very watchable it
is very watching what a show should
be is not fun it is not
something i would have watched it's going
green and then jane me started whining
in knees
so when you think of her name
you have to imagine her knee before
you remember jay yeah it's my monarch
device j picture blue jay and then
i picture a knee you love you
love those what are those called nut
not ramesses hold on rebus rebus
my rams but rbis yeah um like
a rebus um i guess i do
i thought they were very fascinating when
i was a kid yeah sometimes i
feel like i've seen some you know
more recently they're so difficult i'm going
with the fucking i'm trying to figure
out here it's like come on guys
just tell their apples but nope my
book know what's going on apps that's
very nice like that
like this they do yeah thank you
this is from and other stories oh
that's a racist store why not
anything yeah oh that's the anti-tax ah
oh my god you wrote there's still
giving money to apartheid even though it's
not there anymore
oh my god oh my god how
dare they but i look the thing
is also i've been lucky in my
career to not be considered objectively attractive
so i've never had to do the
same thing oh my god no and
i hope i don't ever have had
ones even if you don't put yourself
in that
category i hope i i hope do
it i right direction movie where i
make you do know oh yeah but
please do put me in a movie
you've never had to do that i've
always i've only i think only had
two kisses on screaming god
all my kisses were comedy and kisses
i feel like but
that you wrote yeah no the the
grossest one was with ah because that
dog one the hotdog one yeah what's
your name yeah it was what's your
name
clever pillar who's that is that a
character she plays
clara would you to look up claire
i know this you know these names
yeah
oh let me look i've got ah
great i yep whereas you don't believe
in that name no the where's the
beef lady you know where's the beef
oh yeah yeah we been like a
little kid where's the beef where where
is the beef they should bring them
to safe they should do what she
could be a hologram come on
miller hologram at coachella
first their beef and you know what
since we were making holograms he is
clever fella we have some money left
over for this dog huh here we
go ah man
yeah it's a leftover pixels we made
a clara peller she's she's smaller
thanks to park wares to me pass
just yeah of course she you the
thousand years old when we were children
she was born in nineteen o two
because an answer your question she was
day no it doesn't you could be
but i'll tell you what she passed
away in nineteen hundred and eighty seven
you know where
in a beef farm in a beef
farm did you mean to say beetham
ah no she die i'm holding my
guess okay give me a clue chicago
yeah the only thing you're interested in
well they have a lot of beef
that's true hog butcher to the world
as well she's like where's the beef
that gets around it's all around you
she's like i'm going
were those guys
her movies include moving violations and w
w e wrestlemania too great the end
and you know where she's buried um
i would guess somewhere in chicago morris
park illinois oh yeah i would sit
next to dave thomas and dean next
to dave thomas the ctv vs no
no when wendy sy is he's he's
no real test away yes do you
know he died of being adopted oh
no
you know how tall she was five
one four eleven paul you win although
you did go over you didn't go
overboard as much she's four ten that's
she is natasha gero elizabeth taylor's husband
larry fourteen ski
for ten ski
oh yeah elizabeth taylor one point married
a construction worker guy was doing work
on our house yeah hey when you're
liz taylor right why not get married
why not and you know how many
children she had clara peller i'm gonna
say six two
and do you know who our spouse
was
roger peller very close william pillar divorced
no they hate to force she probably
like hollywood go to her head let
me see when she got the horse
because if it was late let's see
it would be funny if it was
the year after she did those commercials
she doesn't have a personal life thing
she just well she's life and go
really you're looking for controversy she married
age twenty to a local jeweler william
peller
and so is her maiden name her
maiden name beef
she spent her whole life trying to
find it again
ah she was one of eight or
nine children both born to wife's word
law were with one of eight or
nine children yes that's what it says
details are fuzzy it was a long
time ago these are the sword loves
paul these flairs swerdlin that's minute these
are the swerved loves she spent most
of her early life in chicago of
beef
wow and then she married this june
wow he show me a pic via
the sun lesley's row chicago wow and
a daughter marleen but later divorced she
never remarried oh oh
she worked for thirty five years as
a manicurist at a local chicago beauty
salon and later moved to the suburban
north shore area to be near her
daughter that's sweet
we want french tips what do you
think of all this lauren it seems
like we even you
right now i'm looking at her i'm
looking at her on top of a
hot dog sesame seed bun i mean
a hamburger bun um you know are
you looking at herzing goals i'm saying
goals sweetie um you know she packs
a five grubby um
i feel that was a great life
lived i think it's nice to have
lately to have that be i mean
she died in eighty seven i think
where's the beef was what eighty three
to have that be in the final
years of your life it's pretty fun
amazing and then to be able to
be in all these movies and help
she got a lot of money to
leave to her it was like on
the tonight show and shit she she
made an uncredited cameo appear
once on saturday night la but how
did this happen
that she was a manicurist and ends
up saying where's the beef well let's
see you didn't include dave thomas loved
getting many petty's
and he was visiting chicago this is
not that far off she was hired
as a temporary manicurist for a television
commercial set in a chicago barbershop impressed
by her no nonsense manners and unique
voice the agency later asked her to
sign a contract as an actress
she must have been so funny yeah
like that they were all sitting around
going oh my god she's fucking a
little hard of hearing and suffering from
emphysema which limited her ability to speak
high lines of dialogue she was quickly
used in a number of tv spot
advertisements wow quick but all for wendy's
right likely no she did the massachusetts
state lot
ottery
but then first airing on january tenth
nineteen eighty four
where's the beef wow finally premiered the
ad that shook the world we should
do just a clara peller docu podcast
i think you should play one clip
of her saying it we should do
it you know finding clara peller and
the the the pretense that we don't
know she's dead and i'm gonna say
she's disappeared i'm gonna go to finding
cl
clara peller colon the clara sward love
story is totally is a big one
it's a very big fun big fluffy
behind it's a very thick fluffy fun
where's the beef yes john hamburger she
is not less peeve on a lot
of way
demonic voice ohio's eagles where commercial wendy
this is such a like sort of
indeed you get more low key energy
like if this this commercial would be
so cracked out oh windies oh yeah
it would be like so like romantic
when yeah yes fuck you
where is the fact that beef you
know what i'm legend clara peller she's
mean we salute you here in freedom
freedom salutes clara peller you are an
honorary piss pig huh
i'm sure her family is grateful to
doe hoist her wig into the rafters
ah claire fell her two children that
she's an honorary piss pig if you
know clara peller children who are probably
dead themselves
true usa eighty something nineteen eighty seven
oh wait they would be in their
eighties now i was confused they would
know they would be one hundred or
so really i think i can't do
math isn't it right now but here's
the thing it because we were born
before the twentieth century before the twenty
first century it
you you get to a point where
you lose the sense of how long
ago certain things were oh definitely it's
like the the the seventy s will
always be like thirty years ago yea
i do think the seventy s or
thirty years yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
confusing but it took its refusers children
being in their hundreds because that really
took me for a loop i was
like well she just died she was
eighty five well it wasn't just now
it was when when i was two
she was eighty five yeah and those
people were fifty at least and yeah
another moldering in the grave yeah it's
it's depressing like you watch a movie
like jurassic park and you go like
wow it's jurassic world well see well
dressed the first rescue part
hugo it seems so recent but then
you realize like every single actor in
it has passed away since then it's
like it's crazy i know it's wild
do you think it was a curse
in that movie none of them are
from newman to samuel l jackson they're
all dead yeah in the film yeah
that's what i mean yeah watch the
movie they're all dead wow
samuel laura dern escape but i presumably
died off camera
they're still stuck on an island um
while to me that there's it's one
of those movies where there's a generation
of people that grew up on that
movie and it's a very like a
sacred movie to them i love it
and for me when i was however
all i was one of my twenties
or something
if you were thirty eight i believe
when the first one came out
possibly i think it was like thanks
native dar na or you are you
it was nineteen ninety three so you
must have been yeah it was twenty
four right twenty four years old five
maybe and it was like ah going
on twenty five it was i am
only five two going on twenty five
i don't care about these dinos
tos that's the song you were gonna
say about these dinos ah well just
like when i saw it i was
like oh that's a fun movie
but it didn't have any impact like
just kinda talk three times that of
a lark sleepy luck i loved it
as three times and read the bike
ah i read the i'm stupid i
read a bunch of michael creighton's yeah
michael crick disclosure disclosed what if a
man what if something bad happened to
a man
ah thing like a great a great
thought experiment
learn what do you want to talk
about you obviously don't care about what
paul and i really wanna play a
game well let's take a break what
is it break time i mean we
i would say two more minutes do
you want to run down the clock
somehow lord sure need to be that
evil little literally
what is it from drinking no a
hamsters something a hamster hamster dance i
have to wrote that song well don't
do hamster dance hamster dance you answer
ahead of time step sense jomana lookup
hamster dance i don't even know if
that's what it was we all look
up after dancer we got three different
results
oh
i looked up hamster for the season
four of the wire came up of
course amsterdam
bunny colvin in the like of core
all the coven yes you watching the
bachelor and colvin am i watching about
yeah i'm real i'm actually not watching
this is the first time since i
like how boring here i'm not what
makes this year different than other year
oh he's he's actually doing really well
in cutting out anyone who would ever
start drama
he like the minute anyone goes like
i heard she was interested in her
instagram followers he's like later and just
cuts wow so before any arguments isn't
cutting the title taylor is cutting the
purse cutting the person who who is
being tattled upon it sounds like he's
being led by his nose like a
bull but they usually they are the
ones
who would start drama and so like
any of the fights that would occur
with people going like i can't believe
you told them that aren't happening happen
because he's like buying goods for him
because this iosco that's going around telling
him all these things oh his uncle
is patrick warburton and i'm like oh
okay i understand yeah everyone was like
i don't want a draw
well that's good plus hey elaine we're
going home
ah it's have you ever been in
a helicopter yeah so an uncle to
have yeah it was fun but obviously
like they abc asked him to be
in it like crazy please and then
they had like the after the show
credits bloopers with patrick warburton doing all
this kind of stuff but anyway but
you guys fuckin
thereby
anyway congrats for finally shaking it i
know she looks like i deleted twitter
and i am not watching the bachelor
i feel like i'm a whole new
person what can i say yeah i
don't like this new person yeah yeah
i'll go back okay let's take a
break
and we're back
and we're gonna do with reacher yeah
man people love it and they beg
us to do it they beg they
this they stop us on the streets
and they get down on their hands
and knees like dogs they see please
i'm a little piss pig why don't
you do a three jaeger a sucky
plea his last gabbar no way come
on now come on
oh and oh fun i was being
a patrick warburton we started to watch
this movie called inheritance i think on
netflix and early on the movie um
ah patrick warburton has a death scene
in a car which is unfortunately very
funny and it's supposed to be oh
but he's
looked up or something and he's driving
and then he's like suffering a cardiac
event and then slumps over on the
wheel and he hits it seems like
he hits the wheel pretty hard with
his head and then the car bumps
into something
gently bumps into something and then the
horn just starts going off even though
he's already leaving the word has not
been going off okay well that can
happen candidate if it gets down right
now okay or we're gonna play hitting
the post yay ya we do this
it's like when you're d j stymie
we each pick songs on our phones
and we play it for one another
and we tried to ah end what
we're talking about right as the the
lyrics start do it yes where do
you plug don't rush me we're not
plugging in
oh whereas mentioned during the break we're
holding it up to oh you did
this because i do not have an
adapter okay as of yet that will
fit into your phone great who would
like to go first
i can play the song bad i
will be the de j amazing alright
here we go
coming up on the eleventh hour and
it is still pretty smoggy out there
so make sure you don't breathe in
anywhere you go if you're in your
car you should be fine but people
windows rolled up all the way
why good bad about a bed wow
teenage fanclub with feel now i know
yeah we knew high
my turn paul yes i find a
song for you i find song for
you and then you do it i'm
fine to song for you and then
you do it what about that song
here ah it started with lyrics so
i don't think they'll find a song
for yeah you think it's gonna last
good stuff yay then yeah hey if
you're if you're one of the the
ah football fans sing that song instead
yeah i find the song yeah and
you do yeah i'd love to hear
an idiom so yeah season is already
ready yeah
it is officially autumn the leaves are
falling they're going all underneath your feet
gone crunch crunch crunch but you know
what that means daylight savings you fail
wow i really did hitting the post
fail was a bad deal
okay scott
ready yep
just want to make sure everyone out
there knows to wear rubber shoes in
case you're around any kind of see
electrical charge this afternoon because you all
know you can get electrocuted
if you accidentally shit that was a
tough one to figure out it was
tough
please don't hide yourself away by bears
den and jade bird please don't please
please in the title me too yeah
it's plight but play here we go
it's plight sad news today as the
president is still alive i don't know
what's going on he's in his eighth
term and that's supposed to be illegal
but
i was john cale with darling i
need you oh i like when they
call you darling in the song too
like sony or erratic yeah
we've got the contest winners online up
around the block waiting with you when
the final contest they are competing in
a hotdog eating competition starting at twelve
o'clock we will be live streaming that
on our youtube channel and help you
tune in right now but right now
i've got a number one song for
you this is called brother don't let
me
down by the ppcs
pretty close
it was close to the title so
that was the emperor's new clothes by
sinead o'connor oh okay ready scott yep
alright everyone we're taking callers right now
color number one hundred and forty three
gets to call three more times and
if you are the eighth color every
time you call back you win another
phone call for me but this time
i'll be calling you and this time
your the receiver and
we also want to say that we
have a free concert out there in
central park today you have to find
it there's a treasure map underneath every
trash can in central park to find
the stage and if you find that
stage then you know who's going to
be playing that's right it's all your
favorite marvel characters they've started
that's right the sub-mariner for black panther
unfortunately black kid there's no longer with
us
angela bassett she will be singing lead
vocals
is that an instrumental know and they
started singing do they start yeah right
i heard the singing yeah ah that
was in a daydream by freddy jones
band i need a plug for this
it's more fun when we can hear
the song a little better yeah wow
i'm sorry okay you ready yeah you
already yeah
okay here we go well let's know
is still coming down so here is
a list of school closures catholic schools
closed public school closed private school open
secret school clovers golf school open arctic
schooling
your guy goes
very nice good challenge for yourself suzi
quatro which is before that's right i
never realised that's what it stands for
or any fucking reading yeah
in other news johnson and johnson is
recalling every single product of michelle's and
if you've got one money buddy right
now it's toxic to ya i hope
you can go take a shower wherever
you are and if you can't take
a shower and filter water then god
bless ya honey cause it's over i
love you all thank you so much
for listening by the way this is
my last day
of course i would help my okada
ah i get ah are you ready
yep
am i ready i don't know i'm
ready piggybacking on what lauren said it
is her last day we're gonna miss
her but unfortunately she is moving to
anchorage alaska because she
i was five and dime by hazel
english good stuff hey what if we
took one more phone call i love
it yeah and this is from no
name oh my god so this is
pretty exciting you don't think it's jeff
killer
sleep i hope you didn't fail over
things alright here we go high pretzel
gang um this is a question that
i was asked in a spanish language
class and i thought it was an
interesting ah topic when was the first
or last time that you danced all
night
okay thanks danced all night all night
never play all day
um i danced a lot at arden's
birthday party in december but all nighter
well i mean it was all night
but who i danced for at least
an hour i would say that's pretty
good pretty good okay that's not all
night terror that feels like all night
i mean we're taking all night literally
or do we mean like a
a night of dancing i don't know
i have to take her out a
word i the the longest i can
remember dancing is probably at my friend
julie's wedding many years ago in england
um and it was a really fun
wedding and i remember dancing a ton
at that wedding um
most recently at jamie's birthday party oh
yeah i don't still i don't believe
i danced that night that's okay that's
alright it's ok we don't need you
anyway yeah we're fine without use what
they're trying to say yeah i mean
i'm i'm a shy dancer i don't
i don't really ah get it i'm
not the first person on the floor
yeah i need a little liquid courage
and then i'll get oh yeah well
liquid courage changes every liquid cars changes
everything if i have a u s
entered world like all latin side me
i'll do pretty much anything i think
the last dancing i did was our
friend matt michael's wedding i think and
then people everyone started
like jumping into the pool and then
some people felt peer pressure to jump
into the pool wow and jumped into
the pool and they were not happy
about it what a weird thing i
don't want to do this but i
feel like if i don't do it
people will get mad no no yeah
people in the pool going back like
you have to come in i man
i remember when i turned
that corner where that wouldn't work on
me anymore where somebody saying come on
do it into this pool yeah okay
yeah about one of us is gonna
end up in there at some point
it's been one of the rules we've
had you know last time this was
kinda just i felt i feel a
little bit bad about this but not
that much was when we were on
tour and it was kevin barnett's birthday
oh yeah oh yeah there were shots
passed around i was like i'm not
doing a shot and i didn't i'm
famous for turning down shots yeah i
don't know
if people barely even often on tv
anymore i only do a shot of
it's like eleven drop or something i
don't like the taste of a shock
yeah no oh man just tequila shots
ghoul we were out to dinner in
san francisco and it was an italian
restaurant the end the game was lemon
yellows and they were so good let's
get trunk rice
you promise
i swear we will get drunk right
away on the this absolutely is the
time that i danced the most was
at a it was at my sister's
wedding when i was a little kid
and me and my cousin joan danced
the entire reception yes q yes yeah
oh i wouldn't like poking around the
yeah
i want that dance marathon contest i
guess the one that's in the guinness
book oh remember professional dancer oh yeah
well i've actually been dancing through every
record we've ever done oh right yeah
so natural that these shows are only
like yeah you don't really notice so
yeah we do take them at night
and we do do one back to
back yeah it's kind of every oh
day up all night by the way
taped every episode back to back five
years ago yeah
yeah by the way and we've been
guessing some of this what the super
bowl yeah so stuff that we're talking
about it seems old news yeah exactly
pretty prissy yeah yeah and the fact
that we knew about you is actually
kind of amazing yeah yeah oh yeah
oku gaga guys lawrence ago she's got
a she got a
no other way to say it but
diarrhoea issue i have today orea in
my car
you have active diarrhea i have to
do it yeah yeah it's happening now
i have passed now i'm not allowed
to tell right now okay anyway i
guess i got to show my card
i love that all right ah thank
you this pigs we love you ah
if you want to call us it
is um hag claims eight the rate
at
and if you want to write to
us so there's a feature it is
three to me you say at gmail
dot com and we were through team
usa on the socials and if you
wanna listen to ad-free versions of this
show why don't you head on over
stitcher premium or cvb world dot com
that's right and if you want to
go fuck yourself hey go ahead we're
not going to stand in your way
you don't do it we're not telling
you
you to do that no with regard
to that we would want to enjoy
we would prefer you don't as a
matter i please don't go fuck i
don't care who you don't care either
way i tell okay lauren doesn't care
if you're okay okay paul and i
would prefer you don't but if you
really want to
oh christian if you wanna commit murder
i don't think you should i don't
i'm gonna go even further i don't
think it should be against the law
no because individual choice because laws haven't
prevented any murder now that's ever occurred
so why do we even have love
then nanny state has failed look my
drive home is going up alright okay
goodbye
ugh