three
oh
oh my god merger did you hear
that yeah i think someone's being hundreds
someone was yelling that they were going
to murder someone irl i just want
help with a murder know a girl
but oh i'm not going to help
that person wouldn't
help that person either i get by
with a little help from my friend
basing that on the starter ah welcome
to freedom i'm new scott i'm paul
i'm lauren and
ah big update since our last show
big ups today big ups today it's
way march thirty four if you're on
a date if you're eating a date
eating a day what do you aren't
me hammer oh shit y is a
carnival oh he's a carnival carnival is
a great time um someone
i asked a question for crock talk
oh really someone asked a question i
said it would be revealed on the
next episode okay did you see it
yes yeah no i said to that
person okay okay i was like we
don't know this um you're having outside
conversations with people about us this was
on the most social of medias
the social network yes
you know what's cooler than being cool
being a million cool
um someone asked about what are these
called giblets no straps the strap somebody
asked that so you keep the straps
up or do you keep the straps
in the back right jabs and back
in the front party in the front
ships and back that's right and i
said all over revealed on the next
episode of talk so i guess what
i'll reveal right now is that he
does shops in the front i keep
them in the front although i will
say when
first got him i was like i
should probably have these in the back
in order to have more security because
what if i fall on my crocs
but you can't slip them on when
they're on in the back you have
to do a little step yeah yeah
that's then hook them onto your heels
yeah and it's it's just you know
gets rid of the whole purpose of
the comfort of crocs the whole
this is the color of crocs is
that you could displace your foot delicately
here's what i think is so crazy
were nominated for an ambi and we
haven't gotten free crack shit yet what
the hell you're just sitting there waiting
to even order your free baby first
of all congratulations i want free congratulations
to conan but i guess preemptively when
i
learned about the podcasting podcast podcast ah
academy yeah it's like how many fucking
hours of this have i devoted my
life to i know you should get
you should at least get a lifetime
achievement award right oh my god why
would like to hear from the podcast
academy like would you like to be
a member and shouldn't we vote i
see
i what i liked about the category
that we're in is that there's a
lot of podcasts that i love in
the category that i wouldn't say are
like the most known podcast so i
really appreciate that count conan did get
in there because of course a celebrity
podcast is going to sweep the show
we got groceries we at culture kings
we got yeah it's some
good comedy stuff i can't remember anything
it's gonna kind of tag i like
that show yeah come comedy bang bang
oh no that wasn't nominated i'm so
sorry
as a mess honey i mean we
have to stop talking t m mt
on cvb nah nah yeah said what
about your manners come know this was
a nominee i was proud to be
nominated with the two of you um
i wish i could go to there
i always go to the babies oh
i wish we could go to the
ambi you think that put do you
think the statue is a big headphones
do you think the picture that's a
big head a big headphones you think
it's a big goal headphones i want
to have a headphone and i think
there's all these things trying to trying
to do their own podcast awards and
they all like burnout and a couple
of years much like this one probably
well but i've i they've been our
show much like this show will probably
win visitors
um like the iheart radio awards yeah
or there was a couple a couple
of years ago that tried for a
year or something but i think the
grammy should just take over it it's
recorded media they already do comedy albums
families what do you think you're doing
not taking over it yeah grambling come
on grambling my god speaking of the
grammys i just watched the billie eilish
documentary which i love
love someone watching ya see it do
they does does her mom ah ah
ah ah oh stammer ever go to
the between two ferns said is that
happened in the movie while she was
in the between two ferns movie and
then get cut out unfortunately because i
didn't know that yet
yeah sounds great yeah no as as
zack's sister she played z-axis what oh
that scene that that seems like huh
a crazy okay back story because there's
a whole subplot in the movie that
got cut with it was zack with
zack's family but i didn't know billie
eilish wasn't an a and i probably
didn't know who she was at that
time because i know i'm really late
to fig no one knew no one
really knew who she was because she
was telling us all i'm building a
show
don't billy isn't in the movie her
mom is i know her ums and
the moms in the movie yes so
she was saying i'm confused she was
saying like my daughter is doing the
music thing right now and we're seeing
how it's working out and we're like
oh that's very cool for her that
was twenty eighteen that we shot that
and that's why i chanted airways taking
places well okay so i just wondered
if they ever
yeah she does not mention anything that
the mom is up to but the
mom is very supportive and like around
a lot she was cool she's some
of the parents really seem tight yeah
my god yeah and the family is
so cool and the i didn't like
curse over songs but i just never
really explored the whole storyline there so
i just put it on as
and her relationship with her brother is
so cool and sweet and they all
seem great oh my god and they
were like they are a homeschool and
i'm like i honestly i've never seen
a story where homeschooled kids have turned
out so fucking cool so far like
like not just cool like easy to
hang out there like cool like they
know fashion
and they smoke cigarettes like and they
were leather jackets i just let i
love their dynamic and i also listen
to them on smart list that podcast
to be heard that podcast oh it's
jason for namby probably as jason stated
was jason bateman jason bateman what isn't
this just as weird jason bateman will
arnett and sean hay
a is hosted podcast called smartlink where
they interview they each bring every episode
they one of them will bring the
guests and they surprise each other with
whoever it is oh and it's a
big star and ever always summer for
arrested honestly a lot of times is
jeffrey tambor org yeah but they had
billie eilish and phineas on the show
and it was really interesting
that's kind of what got me excited
about watching the documentary because they seem
really normal yeah she she she ah
the mom i believe was either second
city groundlings oh wow so yeah she
was great and she was really funny
in the thing and they seem really
fun we ended up having to cut
it and then by the time we
caught it it was like she's pulling
eyelashes mom do we
yeah but ah of course we oh
yeah and and also are you going
to put in the credits parentheses billion
dollar know but also like damn if
if we had known you could go
billie eilish she could have been an
early yeah well get it in the
documentary do they get into the fact
that her hair is green because yeah
i don't know she like you can
see the roots are green
when we die a black they pixelate
her hair the entire movie so you
can't tell pixar they pick pixar animates
her hair the entire amen what about
that pixar movie follicles where just the
head the interior life of your hair
and it's over emotions
oh locals have oh the curb
um that's coming it's coming like that
what did they do knows yeah
it was grandmotherly almost oh shit i
don't mean it in a bad way
it was very comforting it's not cool
okay someday you're going to be a
grandma drag it from the record god
willing you'll be a grandma oh my
god i found two white hairs on
my head last night oh my god
yours or someone else's they were just
flying down from the ceiling
their album hey we're just resting on
my head well actually i hadn't i've
never dyed my hair my whole life
until a year ago when i did
it for this random job which i've
complained about on here yes and which
by the way never paid off and
um i but then when i saw
throughout that process of trying get my
hair did not be read anymore i
was going to this
color is law and she she'll mind
goes you only have a few grey
hairs and i was like i didn't
know how to
huh
and then i never really thought about
again i kinda just assumed they you
know blend and i never really noticed
them but then i started noticing white
hairs oh and i pulled them out
because i couldn't believe are they really
white i have to put it up
against something black and then i pointed
out you have the what do you
have that stat black my medicine cabinet
so i play
whoa
brush
cold and as a black backs and
i put a black back put it
up against that and i was like
why does night or why does day
the very opposite of this medicine cabinet
what is de hey i mean they
people joined it right but now what
you should also do is pluck out
one of your normal hairs i did
that too okay thank god i know
your ball yeah just like anything where
hairs
i may look for duda yeah yeah
cool i do look really cool up
grey hairs ever since she was twenty
i think that that i think is
cool like there's like i know a
girl who had them in had gray
hair in high school and she started
letting go gray and then it's it's
awesome it's like the feeling of what's
this process going to be like is
the it's kind of weird
ah that's always interesting that people who
just decide to do it like steve
martin and um right now rob hebel
with his white hair but yeah looks
great no but i mean i guess
for people who are just like i'm
never even gun ah no attempt to
yeah it and it's going to be
great for me for show business yeah
steve martin
apparently you never really think about it
his hair being white i mean it
was it was grey though when he
was young and super popular that's right
yeah what's so strange and like what
you but even when he was in
father of the bride he's not that
old yeah and he but he has
pure right yeah even then he like
when he took over dad roles you
can kind of go like oh okay
that makes me
no sense but it's just weirder that
in the mid nineteen seventies he's twenty
whatever and he's got totally yeah i
mean the most popular game in the
world and we're like yeah i get
it i guess he wasn't written out
of town on a rail it wasn't
burned at the stake people allowed to
be who he was i loved bag
well i just don't i never wanted
to dye my hair
cause it feels like too much work
and now i'm like so i'm going
to become someone who dyes their hair
later like yeah right but maybe i
will i wonder if i will i
can tell minor why would you dye
it well mine are pretty easily disguised
at this point but it's like they're
awesome silver threads amongst ago i will
say that's the very last year of
of the comedy bang bang tv show
they had to
there's a little patch that they had
to like put mascara because maybe it
looked weird on camera like to have
like a little well also just like
every other part of my hair was
was blonde and then it was just
like a white street and you asked
them to do it i think of
that like like the um the owner
you're gonna say something i'm wanting to
say one more thing this i know
you're
i'm gonna say something so i want
to get every song it's idyllic out
here you've been quiet for too long
i know you guys by the way
we're outside again and the temperature is
marvelous it feels amazing um this woman
i am working with she has what
i've never heard of before called bebe
i'm movie
a blog called la blonde birthmark which
basically is her hair grows blonde it
looks like highlights like thick highlights like
she has like ah patches of blonde
hair and the rest of his dark
brown is it possible she's lying know
i mean i don't think she is
she's a hair stylist
she was like she's like she jokes
that she's like yeah i'm i'm choosing
to look like i'm in the two
thousands because it's like this chunky high
alert
right and that helicopters back is good
for somebody like if i saw allies
like outline helicopter but it looks cool
and it's awesome to have a natural
thing like that ah yeah i like
things i'm so glad you said that
before whatever paul was gonna say
they want to forget well my i'm
going gray um and your butt hair
does your body hair go gray like
you don't know yeah of course it
does yeah i don't know
um
because he's got laser and ball hair
remove ah l b r please
asia or google um but i i've
no it's more noticeable depending on ah
i've noticed from from doing all these
fuckin zoom shows what type of background
i'm in front of ah we do
our show we're where we both use
a black background lorem yeah
isn't you're married yeah we're both running
stand by the thin side of my
medicine cabinet
but it's much more i noticed that
it's much more pronounced there than it
is other like if i do a
show just to get with with no
backdrop behind me it's not as noticeable
right but we we share no i
don't i don't mind it i mean
it's weird because it's only recently that
i've begun
fun to look at pictures of myself
and say and see like wow i
am aging you know like i look
like it's like icy aging man
i see now what i think other
people see when they other men see
when they start dying their hair and
stuff like that where it's like oh
yeah porsche's like why buying porsches getting
a divorce ah marrying a twenty two
year old all these things you did
yesterday and getting prostate cancer um jesus
yes
jesus got prostate cancer but there was
he was considerably younger he was thirty
two and there was a guy check
your prestige oh you want to live
for another year or someone else's if
you can um you're fingering a bad
hole we did a wee edit when
we had thanksgiving quarantine thanksgiving we were
outside oh god i remember that and
i took a group
photo of the five of us who
um just be clear i wasn't there
i was not there yeah these guys
said the five of us as if
we were oh sorry yeah though it
was not us five yeah i didn't
do anything i um
and because of because we were outside
in the light there you know there
was sunlight behind us my hair looks
completely white
it's wild yeah it was really surprising
interesting my grandma has dyed her hair
forever umm various colors but throughout my
whole my whole life it's been like
blonde but then during quarantine she hasn't
gotten it done and now our hair
is pure white and i i was
so happy to find that out because
i
when i get older i want to
have pure white hair that pure white
hair is that's the best i look
so good and paget brewster's hair was
so good she went she let her
hair go fully grey or wow really
it looks really nice on her it's
interesting because there is because when you're
like eighty and it's dyed that super
bright red yeah you know it always
looks so that's like that's because you
could see the scalp you know it
starts to get yeah i don't know
i mean i think these are individual
choices people do that yeah like yeah
fuckin go for it like you know
you're not fooling anyone
you know what he mean no i
will say like you're twenty you look
at pictures of paul mccartney and he
did it for way too long he's
i mean he's still going him he's
still on easy letting some graph show
plastic surgery and he's yeah and he's
letting some ratio but it's like three
his face is but he just looks
like a grandma to be anytime i
see a picture of my like look
at that young
kung fu's thirty year old you know
and they'll go oh i do see
that he seems to have oh there's
like some new images that i haven't
seen her weight some new images of
paul mccartney real twitter picture is like
really yes twitter i see on twitter
he's fixed his um his his chin
situation favorable to fix machines smidgen yeah
there
there was yeah there was probably a
five-year period in my third maybe late
thirties to early forties where i could
finally grow a full beard and it
wasn't grey and i look back at
that period i with fondness of like
oh man i never knew what i
had you know sometimes i would
but it's still a paradise as i
feel like from the female perspective it's
just not a big deal for a
guy to go gray no no of
course not like i just kind of
think like it looks good yeah it's
not a problem yeah right then and
often it does look good i remember
it's just that we are conditioned to
think that we're not supposed to have
that like i but i feel like
everyone i know who has grey hair
it looks good yeah no it's never
i don't think it's a matter of
looks it really is like this if
you allow your your hair to be
natural it could alter your entire life
right you're a woman right you can
absolutely affect your career which is right
and right right right right well i
think i think for for cert
than men it could affect their career
too like paul mccartney paul mckay exactly
if he knew that he was oh
no man would anyone listen to me
like we should cut this out because
i don't want to i don't want
to take him down lower show business
center we will definitely come to sound
thank you know my old ipod don't
do the freedom they intro lauren tomorrow
he would
he's one of them
ah is that team laura and or
just team anti scott and paul that's
team lords diff
um i also want to say that
last week how many how many things
in total i know what you want
to say to do this yeah i
do think by the way when i
just north i was crazy that i
said it
so just i waited until there was
a natural lull no there you got
ourselves such thing as a natural
i didn't cut you off i don't
see what everyone okay
the
so last year got all those all
my clunky um
last week cool up and i got
the hell out of town oh my
fucking god we went down to orange
county and we we got an air
bnb and i like listen to like
what's the safest way to do it
and um it's you can't really go
to hell hopefully um because a hotel
like has a bunch of people
will there i know what areas oh
yeah just you pay the condescension in
the right house three wow
yeah you gotta you've got a house
so we got a house and we
made sure that they cleaned it like
a day before we ever gone how
did you make sure of this ah
that's part of like on air bnb
the the thing he also went in
and licked all the surfaces to see
if the teacher klara i was like
a little smart oh but oh the
reason i install stall
nanny cams just for you to watch
them clean and it's not an old
video there joe of course no way
no loop of ten sector thanks guys
live repeat so in the corner um
but anyway i say that just to
say that we went down to orange
county having a great time and it
is so different
yeah oh with the beliefs with the
with the beliefs with them with the
masks and stuff like oh my god
i know that just from falling real
housewives of orange county ladies because they
just got to dinner on time and
don't give a shit well mean the
real housewives of orange county we're out
to dinner and we ah that's why
i went out you shouldn't have done
mba
you said the da here is um
but no what like we we took
our dogs out for a walk the
first night we were there and we
both put on our masks and scott
means he and cool i'm not us
three hours just sorry i wasn't there
and on anywhere tonight
welcome to walking around the neighborhood and
zero people wearing masks yeah and in
fact people glaring at me like fucker
you know annoying yeah like come on
buddy i can't i can't i can't
was crazy and then i just don't
you know i grew up in
nj county and so i just started
noticing like the asshole asshole ish vibe
that's there all the time and this
is the thing that i've hated ever
since i grew up there which is
everyone there not everyone but like fifty
percent of the people by huge trucks
and when they're on the freeway they
zig
in and out going ninety miles an
hour on on the freeway there's a
point when you like go down to
disneyland that you hit the five where
you're suddenly in orange county and you
see just all these trucks like zooming
around and getting mad at people and
and don't like it and and that
it's just like i was like oh
boy this place really sucks
it's where i'm from i can't believe
that when you drive into orange county
the sign says welcome to the o
c bitch does and they kick sand
in your government sign
government sites green and white yeah anyway
so but we had a good time
and it was good to get away
that's nice for a few days and
we went to the beach that was
nice yeah it sounds amazing yeah i
have i've been wanting to do that
i don't know if i will but
go to the beach you could probably
go to the beach i think we
lived there would no i honestly haven't
seen the beach and i thought for
one split second during all of this
whole past year but i haven't been
on the sand i saw it but
i need to i i've been having
the urge to sit on the beach
but it just feels like a big
fucking hassle it
sure you know what though we can't
predict how the people in the party
yeah it's a well you're outside so
it's better and yeah no one on
the beach had masks other than us
in one family ah but far away
from everyone but you're you're outside you're
far away from everyone but i will
say it would georgia we got onto
the sand
and it activated so this is my
dog ga it activated something in her
that ah she started like jumping around
and so excited just to be on
sand not because we were buying ocean
or whatever but i think something about
the tactile like being on san chee
like remembers running around in it or
something like that so she started she
was just
so fucking and we're like what is
going on and then she just started
running oh my god and i was
was the sand hot no no no
no but it was yeah she just
loved his memory was yelping yeah pointing
at her paws saying oh joshi and
then she's like an a bun and
she's like hotdog
no but she was so fucking excited
to be on the sand and then
when when we got down to the
ocean like both of the dogs just
wanting to run around and like let
the dog eat in the surf ah
yeah i'm gonna lee sure how well
we had him on a leash ah
other than at one point when when
everyone was gone we were like alright
let's see what half
and if we take georgia opposite god
i'm so nervous well yeah but she
she's because she's really obedient by the
way so she like ran around morbidly
obese
she ran around so excited to be
able to run as fast as she
could and then at a certain point
yeah she is at a certain point
she poked her head above a little
tiny wall to look at something we
were like oh no okay come back
georgia and she's she's immediately came back
and like wanted to be back on
the leash because likes wants to be
on the
east with us but it was just
it was it was really nice freedom
yeah so i mean um
your tom's
that's every dog human relationship right
my dog like my dog is pretty
obedient in that sense like she'll sometimes
almost dash out of the yard if
she sees something and if the gate
is open or something like and then
but if i scream like really like
forcefully she returns back and comes back
but i just feel like the only
time i've ever been around water with
her was
i had just gotten her um neutered
or whatever and she met one with
his spade spade i think neutered is
for cats get i thought it was
david spade i've got i've had their
own missy i thought neutered was males
and spayed with female that's what i
thought it was two i could use
about that well whatever it was she
had stitches and shit co
and around her neck she snitch yeah
and she had cohere around her i'm
gonna google this because i want to
know the answer for when i later
speak of this but um she was
a big dinner yeah acceptance for sure
thank you all the three listeners by
the way my speed is this and
neutered means this but she was i
was like at a friend's place and
i had brought her and then she
was still a puppy and she jumped
right in the pool with her conan
and it was like really chaotic oh
and she was just swimming and she's
like yeah like get in the water
and get her and it was so
crazy well that's
yeah it's all i've ever done with
her so my previous dog rocky i
think when the first week we got
him he accidentally fell into a pool
that we were visiting and then never
wanted to be in a pool or
anything and and and so it's it
was such an interesting thing when we
went to palm springs with some friends
and we had a pool
and ah georgia just got like activated
by it and we were throwing a
football around and this is before i
knew that she loves playing ball like
we just didn't have any balls yeah
i know yeah we we had no
idea but we're throwing a football around
me and my friend and she she
started getting so jumpy to the point
where she died
dove into the pool to get the
football and you're like oh i think
georgia likes balls and ah and then
and then we set up like a
huge obstacle course for her she like
ran onto some mats and then would
jump into the pool in order to
get the ball that we threw and
stuff fun and it was to the
point where i just hadn't really know
we'd only
i had her for like three months
or whatever but i was over at
ah ah a party at another friend's
house and and you can take babies
and dogs and so i took georgia
and we're just sitting there watching music
babies dogs to the party to the
party guy okay you can't take them
from you can't take them from you
i thought it was like thought it
was like say that spang is girl
neuter is boy but i had a
cat first in my life and i
got her spayed and then i felt
like everyone said they knew to their
dog so i always thought wow your
spy speyside ceo interesting yeah i see
no this is a party where you
go you put your dog in a
fishbowl and you're there
you can always take whichever one you
want and we'll do whatever you want
take a fish or a dog at
the end of the night a dog
key parties of funny ideas if you
want to go to a donkey party
yeah you put like the donkey
a donkey show party
but then you have to you take
home somebody else's dog and at the
end of the day for knifing the
donkey show business has gone completely under
with this whole with ovid yeah what
everyone thought about that all the sanitary
restrictions on them now that sucks too
what is the donkey show lady would
have sex with a donkey um yeah
and then was that also where like
someone comes out and like
put pops of ping pong balls or
they put span then there's the corner
of the donkey show i thought it
was a separate show it was a
donkey show kind of just implied a
bunch of depraved acts they probably had
to adapt i'll google it
good please this is saved for the
acceptance speech though
we went over to my own closing
we went over to my friend's house
in georgia ah like kind of was
wandering around and then very like hopefully
and expectantly had found ah this is
my canford house by the way and
he plays tennis the reason i say
that shout out to my calf is
because she donkey shows which are a
show where women have sex with a
donkey but however it might be
a myth ou
she found one of my conference tennis
balls and had it in her mouth
and underwear
and it wasn't a tennis ball shake
anyway ignores nowhere she ignored the notes
and gas down my drawer i put
tennis balls in his underwear to picatinny
his balls
think it's seamless because like yeah hell
no he is an atlas wonder to
make it seem like they're okay with
the one that resemble hitler never tempted
the one that wonder for this kid
i grew up with no wonder
he fell on a skateboard on a
pipe and i had one matt oh
i mean you know it doesn't affect
the subject anything we did say the
phrase one note wonder yeah to him
now i don't think so he was
older than me so i wasn't getting
involved would want to but she found
a tennis ball and it was very
cute and i was like damn georgia
loves tennis balls
well
well that what is the origin of
it because i grew up knowing this
wonder yeah so weird i don't know
where we got it was it a
wonder well nonetheless wonder is what's a
water literally it's it's it's sarcastic like
you're not a wonder
one no wonder it's like he could
still do it ah
shout out by the way to anyone
who only has one testicle or new
tester ain't doing grad or wait for
listening i like that the resolution of
the story was so georgia like says
oh no it was just it was
very regulatory to me shout out to
people without nuts like it so you're
fine
yeah
i guess what i'm trying to do
is i'd never knew how much you
liked it to the point where she
would be in a crowded party and
go seeking out wells balls ball anywhere
she could find i actually like really
you throw this i mean what else
does a dog have to know my
dad he's i mean holly doesn't like
bowls yeah my dog does not react
to toys of pretty much any time
we
got little tiny tennis balls for molly
to fit her mouth like going okay
well georgia always hogs the big balls
let's get tiny balls she turns her
nose up at it and sleep since
my dice just hang out yeah doesn't
want to play those little tennis balls
i think are very adorable they are
yeah i've had them off i bought
a little boys because i really wanted
her to play and
she'll just like everyone so i'll show
like a toy it's so weird you're
like what she she's like into that
one and then yeah and then she'll
get over it and it's like well
we won't bomb him when we throw
toys in the pool though i will
say that molly that seems fun molly
gets activated and dives into the pool
after the two after the specific toy
in order to
take it away from georgia and don't
have floaties on right and they have
floaties and wanna get back i have
no reason to give my dog yeah
yeah i just wanted to have all
the accessor better safe than sorry is
a winter coat
she's got she got a lot of
sweatshirts and t-shirts she has an umbrella
any hits she doesn't she has hooded
things tough stuff put ahead on dog
but i have a hamster cat that
i got in japan um and like
a vending machine and it was like
cat hats they're living together some dirty
alrighty dr seuss speaking to
cats and hats i can't believe i
can't believe what i do to his
legacy okay believe they killed your book
but these little these little um little
masks you like velcro on their chin
and it's like it looks like a
duck hat and it's so cute and
she does let me put it on
her
right i loved our dogs can have
the hats they just like the shoes
are they will not abide by it
she doesn't like choosy it's it's so
videos of dogs trying to walk out
of shoes yeah is hilarious bunk yeah
it's so great it's really fine there
you can see they're clearly like trying
to lift their foot out of it
it right and don't understand why are
gonna help are you any closer to
getting a dog no you know i
don't have pets but ah we live
our lives by scripture and so janie
is very subservient to me so i
feel like but i feel like saying
he always wants a dog gigi walter
oh sorry she definitely wants it more
than i do i
think you only don't want it because
of the shit aspect why because you
know it's not just that i oh
okay is it defeating
you think all food should go to
you like the biggest sound like i'm
like your weird elitist oh you don't
like cleaning up shit i'm getting a
pooper scooper that's my next purchase also
congratulate you yeah i'm really yeah really
excited and buy yourself a beach parking
pass after that go to the beach
what am i
and go clean up poop on the
beach yeah why not um yeah i
don't think we're any closer and it's
not just that aspect it is like
the the the the chaus of our
lives yeah um there's also the body
there's also the knowing knowing you're entering
into a relationship that is going to
end in grief well i've been that's
every day
decade and a half pets countdown to
heartbreak i can't i can't i can't
i know my cat is i hope
i die before my dogs oh my
god okay okay okay yeah okay okay
um ah delete singer of the who
i had to give a shout out
to that company that you guess
yes i scottish get you more food
that's what i want um comedy bang
bang had a sponsor cat food company
and then scott offered it speaks have
a cat and my cat loves us
still love oh my god yeah i'm
gonna i'm gonna subscribe honestly because she
is she every day is so excited
about this food and she's eating more
than she has in a long time
i'm and she has kidney disease and
so am i really happy she's eating
so much and she just seems very
happy yeah do you serve it to
her in a crystal goblet like fancy
fees i should i really should i
started doing a little bolt does meow
on it
plastic i know it's like she knows
what you are you old enough to
have seen that commercial fancy feast yeah
okay yeah i was feeding our fancy
fees actually because i wanted her to
have somewhat finest in life i know
it's not that good but she just
didn't eat anything and she got her
i got her like a science diet
once you just need the science and
then i got her this
fancy feast she would like she loved
it but she would just lick the
gravy and not eat the food oh
so with this food which is called
small's yeah he eats the all of
the food and this is not an
ad by the way just you genuinely
i mean yes i did an ad
for it on my other yeah but
you learned i have personally i got
up in
paid and i would like to be
well and i'd like to get you
a some free subscription if we could
as you may try to work on
the georgia used to not eat which
was very weird like we'd put her
especially coming off a rocky who would
like wolf up his food we would
put george's songs will fit down that's
interesting no it came the other way
yeah wow yeah
rocky used to go ask first
i used to go then you throw
it up
i've got rocky and he's gonna throw
up
but um georgia would just leave her
food in the in the dish and
then we and we would go like
how can we get her to eat
more and we never figured it out
until we got molly and then the
competition between them like knowing that molly
will eat her food if she doesn't
eat it now they're like insane about
where georgia tries to like edge her
out and you know make sure she
doesn't need it that's like me i
don't care about being alive until somebody
else wants me dead wow yeah tony
paul like ten years ago
scary sigh yeah how many people want
you dead do you think
um probably not that many but the
ones that want it really want
alright let's go over zero back i'm
one of the
we hereby everybody we're back with more
later
oh we're back with more thredup yeah
yes we didn't take away the last
segment from you we would never do
such a thing how dare we but
you must thank us for not doing
that you must thank us
um
hi guys
that dog talk really took it out
of you guys huh yeah i feel
like thanksgiving dinner
wow i feel like i feel like
i've just even eat dinner
apology last night
how dare you is this a what
did you last night segment
i like you know it's cheesy topic
um i got topics i didn't really
do anything i had a um what
does that look like what was paul
f tompkins not doing anything look like
i like exactly what it sounds i
sit on a chair and i say
like there's nothing like data in that
collector
her aa dmg episode yes exactly
what the next generation yeah star trek
slash an episode of that to your
podcast you watch star trek deep space
nine ah sais nah yeah there's an
episode where he gets ah kidnapped by
a collector played by sol romanesco yes
who's great in it and he just
wants him to change into
a different outfit and sit in a
chair yeah that's all he wants is
for him to be displayed because he
has he is a rare one of
a kind so this space collector has
all these things by the way they
always have any it came up in
your ah episode of deep space nine
he also had a baseball car what
does that obsession about here's the whole
episode i watched was all about
baseball card yes i am i'm a
big star trek fan um ah i've
i've liked it since i was a
kid but i will say and i'll
say this on the star trek podcast
that i caused with tawny newsome called
called ah star trek the pod directive
um that of all the sports that
would survive into
to the twenty fourth century would just
be not going to be baseball well
it's gonna be fucking soccer it's the
easiest played skee ball basketball will probably
survive too i also and that was
it being a family's that particular episode
was guilty of this i like when
when star trek talks about the great
whatever's of history so there
they always take us yeah they always
pick two of the most classic things
and then they come up with a
fake one yes so they're always like
shakespeare and mozart and sleep slop yes
so weird it's a classic construction well
because they have to acknowledge that yeah
they
but they can never say anything their
honor if they're in the twenty fourth
century why we can come up yeah
more things have come up yeah but
you know i have sleep but they
never say anything from the twentieth they
never want to take a stand on
like not even to do even elvis
or you know anything show you like
to me you're having never watched that
it felt like doogie howser or like
like it felt like it felt like
an old sitcom yeah looks but like
because there weren't as many single cam
sitcoms i feel like at that time
yeah it it has a feeling of
this was shot they shot it like
a a three camera they just shot
it with one camera does that make
sense like yeah that's that makes sense
of why it feels a certain way
yeah it's like all the plot is
absolutely it's an episode called in in
the lot on that one which i
was happy about yeah it was perfect
for me it was like a lot
and i like how like i wanna
get this baseball card to make my
dad happy and it was like what
it was so weird and like i
did i enjoyed
it but it was forty five minutes
of like boo we'll get that card
okay well i only have five but
i only have five bars to spend
those for my whole life saving my
first spacebar absolutely we haven't recorded the
episode yet so i'm worried about talking
about it too much but it is
totally a sitcom plot i got away
i'll save it yeah but it was
i kind of didn't hate it weirdly
okay well i
watching t and g so i i'm
through sixty three really oh okay well
i i started the first time like
you know what i've heard the next
generation is good i'm gonna start the
the first one i'm gonna get into
it and by like minutes thirty of
the first time i was like this
is a piece of fucking shit what
is this and so i i was
like let me just put
put this into google and see what
comes up i put when does tn
g and the first thing was get
good i was like oh okay yeah
wow and it's like season three so
i did a little research and i
read like what are the good episodes
of season one and two and i
watched probably three seasons of season one
and oh so you are cherry picking
a little bit yeah
and i watched i watched most of
season two and i'm writing down which
ones were good and yeah for who
um for a friend's a friend wants
to get into it and i'm like
i'll watch it before you and just
tell you which ones you do things
who's your friend of real w yes
w don't worry yeah no you don't
need to know
i really want to know ah that's
that's all i don't know if people
use it anymore well you know for
sure that you should
that used to be um sort of
code for ah if you were an
a o my friend of bill yeah
i've heard of that phrase yeah no
friend of bill was about bill clinton
once it was they used to be
that was a term friend of bill
yes during the during the clinton era
but was it coming from that no
it was not what he was coincidentally
made
named bill but i mean i i've
heard the phrase are you a friend
of bill meaning like like yeah i
think we know a bill i buy
your eyeballs your right as well i've
always heard it his friend of bill
w but i believe friend of bill
is also i guess yeah whenever asked
i say the wwe kind of makes
it seem fake because you'd go well
what's your last name
well i your friend of bill w
well bill west or bill westchester because
i am three hundred and two different
girls i'm friends with one of them
one of those dyers me and my
knee i said emily was nobody going
home any other way friend we're gonna
go friends you for friends with p
is pauline
or scavo and what does that mean
you're born know that is a song
by the rentals ah okay down with
me then your dad with pee and
nephew fanbase on paulina person may fans
wonder why were they sing you her
i don't know maybe they she's cool
and everyone was friends with her also
he was the the
coolest well also she's she was married
at the time to ricco cassock who
write produced leisure's first album so he
was the star of pixar's cars yes
she's married to a person who produces
weaver's latest album she's the paulina porizkova
of our generation lena boys cool demo
quality
i think it's really where i was
reading about palladium horoscope of last night
oban sure where it was really good
flashlight under the covers i was reading
google images and ah but it's so
sad that lay and i love rico
catholic like i love every cars album
ah equally and
without measure and i love his production
and it's just such a bummer that
he cut her in two of his
sons out of his will boil your
yearning yeah that's some bullshit at some
fucking bullshit so we'll converse to get
six sons is a little jesus in
the hole wy sd people people
crazy with wells there's always like there's
some selling
yeah but there's like i feel like
everyone has a story about some will
that went awry you know yeah that's
seems it's not have you done yours
by the way no but i've been
thinking about it a lot and you
should go do it what do you
do it it's weird to talk to
i can ask you this i can
tell you i can give you some
well there's also legalism does this but
yeah i can i can give
you see interesting little heads in how
much do you pay how much did
you pay to do well oh it's
like seventy five thousand
basically you end up just leaving all
your money yeah it's weird to say
i'm don't do it well there wasn't
there something like that from some sort
of like crows just you gotta there's
people who specialize in it and you
just basically it's like going to an
office and and him were you thinking
the doctor used all sorts verona i
was thinking about this this ah
podcast listened to called icc something something
bike and oh god i got nominated
for an ambi i can do to
turn i didn't look at any other
category sir um it's it's about this
guy who was um very interesting he
was a therapist but he basically ended
up having all his patients and putting
them into their will oh
oh yeah well that is amazing this
is a thing that i'll tell you
about later that's well it's a show
being made of it you're i auditioned
for yeah i'll tell you about it
like i'll tell you though something you
don't know oh oh okay good is
it called doctor will doctor doctor will
doctor nobody's really good podcast i'll try
to figure out what it's called because
i figure it out well
just think it must be annoying to
like talk about it and then everyone's
like well what's it fucking called yeah
um no but you i mean it's
you feel relieved when you've done it
because like all first of all if
you happen to die and your love
your spouse or whatever isn't left with
all this shit of like yeah knowing
what to do or
yeah having to go to probate and
all this kind of stuff you just
like feel a relief of like ok
now everything is settle there's no there's
just clarity you know nose link next
door the shrink next door as as
a person who and as as a
person who has your person had loved
ones die
um my you know both my parents
have died the fact that they had
all that shit sorted out right it's
such ah it just it's such a
relief it is thinking that so complicated
yeah don't yeah i mean you you
do have to you basically are answering
all these questions of okay what's the
split of of all of your
assets between you know these people what's
the split if both of you die
together what's the you know i have
half siblings i never knew about and
do you even talk about like your
belongings like yeah they know they're like
whatever valuables you have them you put
that in there as well like you
can give to those two people and
oh i almost obama kinda curious about
things
aren't valuable yeah like you can do
it i'm like yeah you could put
that in there oh my all your
beanie babies those are princess diana miniatures
oh my god oh my god do
watch harry and megan i haven't seen
it yet it's fantastic the oprah interview
oh no i didn't say that's great
i got the sense of it from
the eight million tweets i know i
avoided twitter because it was like it
was an
event for me i was so excited
i make out of the room i
still want to see it i will
say it's it's like a you don't
wanna hear his little cool he wanted
to leave then but then deserted beaches
commenting already get huh
ah fuck caddy ya you little worm
for you you top sabeel store thing
for eight hours wow my
one of you are coming over that
what did they throw it in that
hole honestly i was going like look
at this couch check out this thing
on my computer i want to show
you that he's like i'm watching this
i'm like a real sense of your
relationship during the day flails at you
and you yell it here just glance
over here the worst thing for me
is if janie enters the room when
i'm playing a video game i become
so self-conscious about it well because like
it's oh i talk over all that
i will just talk over whatever is
happening that's fine but i i feel
like i've been caught yeah because it's
infantile in a way yeah you feel
like it's yeah i see how it
looks yeah all of a sudden like
when i'm playing the game i'm in
the world of the game i'm following
them right yeah and then um when
somebody enters the room all of a
sudden it's like yeah i'm getting
in a bug
i feel like i don't judge it
at all
but i think partly it's because i
grew up just like with my brother
always playing video games my brother my
dad always watching basketball all these things
i don't really care about but they're
around she doesn't just it's it's entirely
retired early internal here's to your point
lauren about talking over movies and you
just wandering in and talking over me
i think there need to be some
rules established
as of when people can talk over
tel i think that is congress i
yes i think that someone should give
you a heads up of hey i
want to have a conversation okay instead
of just coming in and saying this
is what club does so when do
you blob like that all the time
because i cannot hear either thing i'm
like okay what can you take
the kitty litter you know it's like
i've just like talking and most people
don't even wait for a pause in
it for it to be silenced or
whatever they just talk over the dialogue
it then makes me instead of you
said can i say something then i
can pause it then i can listen
to you you know what i hate
is when you're watching tv live and
there's commercials phuket will do
and then and then you started didn't
you the people in the room aka
me and mike start having a conversation
over the commercials i'm like mute the
fucking commercials yeah yeah can't have the
conversation you all this is happening yes
it makes me feel crazy right it's
like a third person speaking randomly die
from taking this medication
yeah you're not part of this excuses
trying to have a conversation is the
second time this has happened i've heard
an airplane noise and looked up and
seen a hawk in the sky and
thought it was the hawk making going
like what the vo it was behind
you not really but kinds right behind
me is it the ha barrow plea
the um yeah remember my mother
i remember your mother's doing this it
it's never what i when i do
it i think of my mom doing
this that we did not have a
remote control tv for the longest time
i see them and after i moved
out of the house i think my
parent know we have like you moved
out we had a very like an
early remote that
you kinda made noise but um ah
just after that where it was like
it was a big box yeah it
was it did have directs the buttons
hard it's not have a wire okay
but you had to like really like
to watch the wire on it yes
i watched the wire on the remote
control that's so crazy yeah and you
want to remote control on the wire
wow wow barbican ober um and ah
i be kenobi sounds like a sturdy
yeah
god gave to be obo
um she says she had a shed
like a modern remote that didn't make
noise when you when you press the
button and everything soft-touch and a commercial
commercial came on and she muted which
community said i don't have to listen
to that wow suddenly you know what
suddenly you don't like she made it
a feeling of power
power yeah and now anytime i mean
it's any medium virtual like i don't
listen to that it feels amazing when
you meet the commercials and you just
like sit there in the silence you're
like ah yeah when i first got
my first tivo it was such a
feeling of power to to figure out
exactly like how yeah how many to
press exec
when depress play again it was so
satisfying but conversely it always feels like
a a defeat when either you go
too far or you absolutely have to
hear the very last piece of any
absolutely yeah but man when you could
get that damage what exactly was so
good out of god i missed hva
well i've started to lift the t
and g episodes because they're on paramount
plus there is no skip intro or
skip credits oh so you have to
watch these long ass so i have
to fast forward them now and i
tried to time it exactly so that
like right when you see jean created
by gene roddenberry because yeah if you
do it
too early you hear the massive crashing
orchestra yeah duh duh duh duh what
what's good about paramount plus sell it
to me give me a plus paramount
i understand you know what's got a
great selection is discovery plus okay theory
on miller it's part of a bigger
thing though like it's part
of hbo max or or part of
paramount pool i don't know i still
my friends log-ins i don't really know
i stole it till i gave it
to me okay
when you're stealing it from the comfort
of your both stealing because he wanted
to watch this one show and i
didn't think i would like anything else
on there and then i was like
oh i like everything on it okay
well paramount pluses they have ah we
will show celebrity iou it's where oh
yeah leopard you get does a home
renovation for someone that the matters brad
pitt was just won the fucking best
episode and let me just say
say you do not see brad pitt
on reality tv very although it's crazy
and he was extremely sexy being a
guy right like oh my gosh being
a regular guy on reality yeah just
hanging out because usually he's he's so
easy doing the lines going guy he's
high he's raised saying someone else's lines
no he's a very attractive measure and
that's not a question about it but
if you watch that episode and he
makes this whole idea what you're saying
makes this whole guest house make-over for
his um makeup artist who has been
his makeup artist for like twenty five
years or something and it's the sweetest
thing ever yeah it's a good show
great show property brothers team-up with celebs
too
to do things for people that matter
to that property brothers t-mobile celebs so
they can hang out with celebs yes
um i will say we watched robin
we watched roman holiday on paramount plus
which is a great movie and i
realized megan markle did the reverse roman
holiday wow xi in roman holiday it's
a princess who decides to act like
a normal person and then goes back
to being a princess at the end
spoiler and
megan markle is not a princess who
acts like a princess and goes back
to not being a princess at the
i gotta say i'm there the interview
many very much more even than i
already was fascinated with their deal better
deal i'm very the couple or the
royal family well i o i'm oprah
i've always been pretty interested in the
show
better deal
that's really the couple and that they
kind of had to it just seemed
like they had to get out if
you watch today or bring up and
i know i could've just watched it
chan would have answered this but did
they ever did oprah ever say like
well when you first started dating him
though wasn't it attractive to you of
the whole princess di she did as
ask that she was like well what
didn't you think about what it would
be like to marry prince and she
said no she's achieving she made time
to clarify i wish that she had
asked like but wasn't that exciting to
you that he was a prince and
using that part of the reason why
you agreed to date him in the
first place she i don't think she
did phrase it like that but she
meghan markle said she did not goo
google him at all which i'm like
and she didn't grow up knowing about
him i feel like my whole life
i thought about these people yeah for
sure i probably didn't even know who
he was until he did get engaged
oh okay i was very aware of
him when we're friends with princess di
ma of course i did shake her
hand but i also am like his
age and so it's like you know
seeing why
whenever there were flowers of god i
could have been you could have married
him well that's what kind of killed
me about this whole thing because my
homie he's marrying second banana airs on
tv so i'm not you i know
well i actually had this thought when
this was happening because i was like
my whole life i just assumed there's
no chance i'd ever marry
a a prince right because i'm a
foul mouthed guest star
wow for a babysitter yes correct philadelphia
stars wow
it's happening and i'm thinking i'd be
poised in a situation like that i'd
be great so i mean i could
have done it and i you know
as we all know i worked out
next to him at a gym when
i was in london yeah so i
was right there but he's sort of
with megan ah if only you'd worked
out three months earlier now fully exactly
just hit me in the head by
the way i
i saw that i thought you having
some sort of episode i don't know
some nut just hit me in the
head some somebody's nuts just to my
cancer was bce was it decent um
alright we have to take a break
okay
and we're back and it's three tr
time and this one was submitted by
john and apparently he didn't want to
give his last three sixteen yeah i
think so i think it was the
guy with the rainbow afro all fun
looking up he's a really fun guy
not wig but afro
there's never a way just real hair
that he's died um this is called
no more jockeys okay and apparently this
is a popular game from taskmaster um
what does that mean you know what
that's show it that's a that's a
show sort of comedy game show that
i mean i've heard is a great
reggie watts did the the
the comedy central usa version which anyone
watching the chase yes we talked about
last weekend okay i'm boring you're not
boring i don't know the chase it's
a game show with ken jennings and
to other oh i'm sorry i know
we talked to we talked about the
hustle yeah i cannot tell the they
don't have distinctive names yeah che
name joe blend three ah trivia nurse
or three dudes who won jeopardy like
the tournament is one of them when
something else they'll have like a streak
of whatever you know i'm talking about
jennings and the other two guys the
guy who goes all in and enjoying
the other two guys so then what
happens is people ah who are good
at trivia compete again
fenced them and it's kind of like
a betting thing like can you get
more right than the guy may honestly
i just explained it so simply yeah
and that is accurate but they say
there's a lot of excitement for about
ten minutes
that's it that's my big that's the
problem says like game geeks by the
way i watched the weakest link now
and i i saw that too i
fast forward through all of the jokes
and it makes it a much more
pleasant yeah you went away is that
back on the weakest challenge show host
and i believe people we know probably
write the jokes and i'm sorry to
all know
yeah you just want to see what's
out there st louis i want someone
to lose yeah i don't want the
jokes of i wanna see who is
who is to shrimp short of a
shrimp bucket yeah exactly all that kinda
stuff okay so fuck yeah she's she's
like
who among you ah needed the recipe
for ice yeah exactly who you know
boi yoi yoi because basically i was
a good that was a good one
honestly yeah well it's old jokes i'm
gonna whole lot
i need to be able to buy
but they goo some booze
the screen door on the submarine yeah
there you go you guys should work
for that show no thank you it's
really you're really good weakest link goodbye
because okay so on each turn we
go around in a circle and each
person names a person a famous purser
i guess a person we know
no
same thing when you're up so i
mean and the category that they fall
under okay meaning singer actor meaning that
yes so so name yes and you
say it as in no more this
so for instance kanye west no more
rappers
and then what then we cannot name
any rapper ever again okay so then
you can name anyone else you want
and pick a category that they fall
under and say no more this and
then ok eventually we will run out
of people oh okay so eventually or
almost immediately time each time like oh
say no more whatever then you name
a person name whatever so yeah and
that narrows down has done okay yeah
it is like she's good to start
with a more obscure group not now
yes so you can't like if you
were to say like no more men
that cuts out and you know you
could say jonas salk no more polio
vaccine developers say go right take forever
and susan sarandon yeah why would that
take forever well just that's so specific
no but i'm saying just to kind
of get it going yeah yeah he
made a joke but yeah you gonna
try to get really serious well it's
not fun paul well we can't play
like that paul over your old day
okay so call and by the way
i guess i guess if we want
to say who wins or loses whoever
gets stuck says moses oh okay if
we want to do with elizabeth j
paul okay so paul do you want
to start us off yes especially the
patriarch of the group
i'm going to say a petro tool
no more actors you just did what
i said don't do wait what well
guy called you cool my god this
is sick
i'm so used to having her right
to my right yes right my jokes
i just said well yeah but we're
kind of weak i'll immediately put into
ah that's okay okay now let's do
it let's try it and i mean
we get less specific ale next time
i said it because i i had
to say for the listeners who know
that i just said that right yes
yeah well i
thought the jonas salk one was a
good way to start i mean i
bought lamb doug lamb dunked for that
no it's good i really i guess
yeah i'm good but i think the
two things go less this is good
discover some good shit of things like
four types of people peter o'toole no
more actors
barack obama no more presidents
bruce springsteen no more podcast hosts oh
wow
ah
um
let me see if i can do
this
tom selleck no more commercial pitchmen no
you can't because that person is also
an also an actor yeah okay so
but that's okay you just redo it
so bruce springsteen you could not do
as a singer or i mean you
can do another singer no you can't
because i know one is said no
more singers
right but because i've said no more
matters but i put no more actors
no more presidents no more podcasts so
you have those with money alright those
are the three categories okay okay
alright then ah baba baba baba terry
bradshaw no more commercial pitchman is he
an actor i don't know he has
acted but he's not will not accept
it will say he's not an actor
okay i don't like
michael jordan no more basketball players
hello space jam
ok fine okay i guess now i'm
i'm getting a better explanation of the
games doing it to muddy bogs no
more
god i was going to say can
be matomo no more finger wags okay
um i don't get it but i'm
getting it now i'm getting it now
okay um
billie eilish no more singers
dick francis no more novelists or horses
i guess well we don't hope
will disallow both
um guy fieri no more chefs
okay doo dah doo dah guy theory
no more jazz ah da da da
da da da da de guy be
airy no marsha saw the dude guy
de um steven spielberg no more directors
and now it's all real people right
yeah okay well i guess you could
do wow i don't know i mean
fictional character i guess i wanted to
say eighteen no more trustor
yeah that's good
yeah there was a doubt zog is
gonna be good yeah longer sleeps thorpe
okay um
bethenny frankel nomar real house
oh um
the property brothers no more reality tv
people damn it e
ah
the blue beep boop beep boop people
beep boop boop minute talk rack mario
andretti no more race car driver oh
but ah you want some that song
again seep up pippi pop pop pop
pop pop pop pop pop ah when
you pick up poop you must answer
having a hard time
all the people in the world you
know like what okay okay malala no
more humanitarian oh whoever that person was
who did the inauguration no more poets
well you better know your name you
gotta come on alright ee cummings no
more airways go
ah jesus christ no more messiahs damn
david koresh next christopher columbus no more
explorers exploiters more like hey go fuck
yeah i said it let them have
it um
king george the third no more kings
ooh can you imagine what a world
is no more kings schoolhouse rock wasn't
a schoolhouse rock's no more kings wasn't
it not and i'm aware of i'm
gonna look it up while you talk
stephen sondheim no more broadway composers
um
okay
you guys tend do you guys tend
to think of the category first and
then a person yeah i do not
have a regular system yeah
what does my thinking music oh i
remember this now mischa smashing over the
guys and what do i see was
that like the santa this has no
markings
shit
who's that at school has run but
i don't know whose origins the worst
people you can imagine they had our
religious freedoms to be though worst people
they could be who they were
okay versace no more designers nice oh
take easy to anthony cunanan
a um
ice no i can't say that i
like this place
i wanted to get to the no
more kingsport
um
i hope it's a thing they say
once yeah they never do um let's
see let me say ah bob ross
no more painters no
oh that's okay um
bob ross no more pictures bias no
more painters painting bob ross no more
painters
um
james beard no more food critics ooh
um casey anthony no more murder suspects
ah okay ah
ah now can't do that ah did
that not gan day that um wouldn't
be prudent my pants now more vice
presidents ah
i mean if you're listening to this
in the future yes yeah he's president
going to be president one day so
far so yeah we didn't know that
now of course he is
um bobby boop boop boop no president
stated di di di di di bum
bum bum bum they went to clean
myth rock
but plymouth rock landed on their him
ah justin trudeau no more prime ministers
oh
so no more blackface people
punk that's right it's the image dancing
um
i don't know that one oh look
it up enjoy yourself
better than you think it's later than
you think yeah that's a song but
i mean is it more reason than
i think no oh okay um thirty
years okay good
it's helpful um it's also one of
the only times where there's a context
that makes it almost okay yeah
i'm not gonna participate in this
you'll see what i mean okay
yeah just very quickly nothing it was
good
um ah the pope no more pokes
o da po
can't think of the name of any
pope's no pope francis me yeah you
nailed the hard was that
ah ah john wilkes booth no more
john's ooh okay
and then i'm all say oh charles
ghetto no more assassins um
we pop back up
not the temple the people
people talk to people to read to
meet him to tip tip tip tip
jar disney no more creators creators even
of life itself says all the game
and soon ah good point my grandma
no more dead people
oh okay
this ought to do it
ah scott ackerman no more alive people
oh yeah damn is and paul one
know the next person would lose
and we would share winning equally no
no i want no we decided for
the gigging that i won you look
like you are wearing a star trek
uniform right now
just take a picture i worried about
red dress we aren't gonna take a
picture it'll last longer
well another three-time and the books done
and dustin it's all it took that's
all we had to do was just
do the three seconds remember take one
away and that's all it looks great
though that react and thank you for
painting on where at freedom usa on
twitter and instagram gotta follow up
does those little palsy own active person
in i've got some things on the
account but know how to get into
it thank god i did a little
slideshow when i have a few had
access apologize for not having done it
the last couple of weeks but i
did not feel like doing those i
say where those been yeah i just
couldn't see yeah yeah because i've to
live
come back to the episode of make
notes and sometimes i'm listening to the
episode just to make sure i didn't
say something horrible yeah um check with
blackface conversation earlier yeah i mean look
i yeah we can go there for
my next episode yeah we'll talk about
next time alright bye bye everybody
hi
uh