sorry
fifty six inches
oh
a oh wow ooh wow in that
my injury it turned into
oh wow oh is that culture really
culturally insensitive to to make us out
of a didgeridoo i don't know is
it culture insensitive and mechanic sex right
right
wow what about bruce willis doing a
harmonica flute it's hard to imitate a
harmonica
point proven everyone loved that
a special day dumb i'm scott i'm
lauren hi po and this is this
is us episode final episode for a
while see i will feature yeah like
it i don't like it guys so
what we thought it would be fun
to do for our last episode was
we've we've done a lot of features
on the show played a lot of
games yeah and we thought what if
we try of a wet
had a lotta laughs how dental that
sari saris played a lot of games
and a lot of laughs named a
lot of me and hated a show
that slew a threesome girl
um so we thought it'd be fun
to play every single game we've played
on the show for one episode we
thought it would be fun we don't
know by now that advice out it's
real um and we're gonna go in
semi order yeah we're gonna go in
semi order and hopefully we're gonna know
how to play these
bring it all back to episode one
it'll be a game to see if
we can remember so yeah so there's
a metagame happening over the entire game
which is do we remember the games
yes should we score who wins metal
world some of the somebody's metal oregon
some of these don't have winners but
they all have losers yesterday so we
might score
who wins the every show that we
did has three losers
oh that's true you including chevron oh
oh um yeah that kids are what
you wanna hit chili dog he was
a chicago machine so second show doe
hesitate to be shirts get the shirt
so sure you need a shirt to
commemorate voter matters to the chest tourist
manners on your channel ball of course
but bananas shut our manners on your
chest
um so there will probably be no
spankings this episode because we're not going
to be telling stories unfortunately no but
if you play the game the exact
same way you did oh no if
we do more of these you should
have an episode where we just tell
stories we've told on the show before
yes seeing new wrinkles come on yeah
which by the way if you want
to hear more freedoms
please let the powers that be know
your mom are willing to do more
tell him on twitter tom amy's critics
and fan mail to cullen at your
ah cali we love you we love
everything you do we love you send
some postcards to call in that only
read more threesome on them so it's
a ten cent like more three-team bitch
yeah oh not bitch in case of
postbag defendant john there what does the
postman's a bitch
we're not saying a woman either but
i wasn't saying man who's just like
bitching out what's supposed man's a bitch
anything smell for him and he takes
it home and call number reads it
oh duh the postman's a rabbit but
i do think everyone send a postcard
it could be any postcard at all
any more three employees will put up
all the postcards
on the wall allah the hitler camera
forever tell you about i said no
i just know
ah it's the new newman
this is in in nineteen eighty eight
jill that automobile sada the record yell
is no marie calendar
hebrews the banana
oops who bruised the boom i'm gonna
get
okay so the first game is ha
i gotta go this is when you
brought it yes and we played it
twice two people improvise a boring conversation
while the third laughs and make some
excuse to leave oh so it's two
of us improvising i okay great it's
two this is your third chance understand
this is the third time july daddy
was just two people talking in one
leaves it's ok
three talking two of them are being
particularly boring okay gotta go but we're
in cooling you want wants to find
a smooth exit okay yes that's that's
the that's the key is to have
a smooth exit smooth as possible because
i'm not going to because any bumps
right well i think the idea was
to originally to do it as realistically
as possible like if you were in
that situation
ation how is how to extract yourself
from a boring god conversation okay so
without seeming call and i will be
middle of conversation leave
um how long have you had those
shoes i love those oh wait thank
you yeah i got these um probably
three weeks ago now and they're just
they're just breaking in there just feeling
yeah they're a little bit squeaky i
mean they look great but they slightly
i don't know if that's gonna be
a thing that goes away or if
it's gonna be like they just make
noise you know i don't know if
it's because this is hard
he is so quiet i've it's just
amplified to me for some of us
awake i mean you know it's yeah
by the way how how did your
brother die of natural causes yeah yeah
he's twelve
what natural causes what ah so what
what lord i just i want to
go grab a drink i hope it's
okay we're already
it's not okay
yeah so hard
it's not okay lauren his brother died
of natural causes i know i just
didn't want to i felt bad for
paul that you made him explain this
right now right here i just i
was curious it's a bit of trivia
i was interested in i do find
it strange that he would come to
the wake and you wouldn't have any
doubts at all well i'm
missed the newspaper that day i told
you this i told you this about
is your power still sealing your papers
well no i mean no thank god
he's now just stealing my mail but
but that's part of the problem is
i've mailed in payment for the oh
wow
did you hurt your vagina young lady
i got a cramp on my thigh
oh i gotta go to the bathroom
this isn't to say i take my
ah
let's go as a okay let's let's
try to get i apologize i i
took it off the rip now i'd
probably say well okay so sorry you
and me okay
yeah and then what was so unfortunate
about the whole thing was that each
tile that was brought in was slightly
different so they didn't match yeah where
they from different stores or did that
it was no i think it was
just a mistake in the warehouse yeah
paul you work in a warehouse
have do they make mistakes like that
usually yeah mistakes to to happen often
or yeah yeah you know what i'm
i'm probably responsible for most of them
oh that's right you work in the
warehouse that the tile could you see
someone over okay anyway so yeah it
is paul's warehouse that made these tiles
they're um they're supposed to be come
come paul come back here no i'm
here yeah right so just i thought
i had left but apparently oh anyway
i heard you can put them on
with some sort of epoxy some kind
of glue
i don't i want them to be
temporary well there's just what we say
as a proxy on all your houses
i have to go wait why i
hated that
alright so that's how you play i
think we move on so now you
say we have so many games have
so many games so many games so
many games alright this is a game
that i came in with and this
and will only play the final round
because i i did not know we
were going to play this i didn't
create a new list we probably should
have seen
seen a list like before we came
in yay and also and that's japanese
and i'm nothing like we didn't no
no wait okay when you guys were
out in the room i was horrified
that several of these we needed for
a little prep for wow okay but
this is a game called duck mary
kid don't know kevin here's the thing
kevin sat in the room we can
talk we can talk shit about just
what you just skipped the ones that
know i
huh
no okay look doctors if there's a
game that requires prep will change it
to we know wick round of what
do you not like about kim okay
okay so duck marry kiss was i
created a list of names and created
some of them were ducks some of
them were famous marries people within a
mary and some of them were
members of kiss now i had a
list of like fifty of these but
i don't want to repeat it so
i'm just going to do one of
them this is like our bone erroneous
round this was our tie breaker yeah
that we did and how you how
you buzzing she says it how you
was in question was in by saying
your name whoa by saying
takes longer to say but just know
when i started that's the same yes
yes definitely so i'm gonna say either
a duck a mary or a member
of kiss and you have to buzz
in saying your name and you have
to be correct alright are you ready
yeah yes
macdonald lauren
i think paul has it he said
paulin yeah to make it fit make
it even paul what was the name
again
sorry i only say it once what
is it yeah what is it
ah kiss my sorry to mary yes
mary mcdonnell mcdonnell lauryn yuen i think
the best day of my life
yea alright and this is the east
i've ever been and that is the
holiest i've ever met yeah it was
the whore and marry that is the
handiest mary mcdonnell rodley that is the
cornish coast guard it's ever been sick
i'm doing i doing jimmy what's his
face jimmy
arteries
jimmy stewart jimmy stewart what's his name
jesus mary what's his name mary dewar
is it mary watch the hardiest da
da i've ever read hey ma ma
alright this next one is switching pitches
this is a good game we played
twice
so so nice so nice guys are
we all going to yeah let's all
play it okay so someone says your
show to someone says what else has
to pitch the opposite of that title
to the host where every word is
the opposite of whatever word is in
that title and then you have to
pitch that show to the two other
people so it's basically you take a
sitcom
i'm like i think i've we've used
just the ten of us you do
you say the show title you do
the opposite like someone else has more
the opposite of that title to the
house okay okay so um i'm gonna
name a title from paul okay okay
the title is
head of the class
hi paul hi there what show you
guys that's part of my day i'm
a huge coke yeah yeah yeah thank
you very much yeah i gotta say
by the time i mean by five
pm around here it's so boring so
thank you for coming in spicy yeah
right p i'm sorry but the traffic
oh i'm really glad that i
i'm a priority and that's why you're
seeing me at this hour yeah it's
just you have a train i'm young
and i made five of three yes
so we're gonna have to like get
to know understood what it is which
will not take long great what show
are you pitching today it's called bottom
of the phylum bottom iowa yeah okay
great yeah
catchy and i sound smart i feel
like i'm i didn't go to biology
oh what am i watching the big
short yeah i'm i feel smart now
i'll put a sexy lady in there
that's like funny joke oh okay
wait you want to be the sexy
ladies that know i mean i didn't
think with the sexy lady cells in
this town you know if you make
it smart but you put a hot
babe in there it's like yeah it
wasn't yeah yeah yeah so what does
the show about yeah well you know
um animals um i've heard of cat
does that mean i'd love that one
cause you heard about yeah yeah think
of like
skeletons were big s and l rice
yeah from a very specific theory yeah
yeah la y from new york sorry
mary would you like to touch my
monkey
wow that one but she can make
lousy house pip i don't know that
either um we don't know any other
animals i don't well those are two
that i'm ah nope these are our
characters okay to chicken and a monkey
so what's a chicken and they're trying
to chicken is chicken do chickens like
a cat except it's got um like
the inside
a pillow all over it
so others yeah i get it said
they're just funny that's funny money yeah
yeah and so the chicken is like
chicken just like a pillow turned inside
out yeah and alive and how many
legs it got it got to got
to got to leg how many wings
it guy he got two wings how
did you know
that ah how you're a big fan
fan of wings here it's many horns
that guy they've got no horns unless
you count speak which just like its
notes like a devil's horn which is
like a nose and a mouth that
seems out of yeah okay eats out
of a beak so sign me up
it's what you speak if someone you
know my oh
we'll get down here come on now
should i go
yes
thank you you who you sold it
oh my god you're rich now he
doesn't tell anyone about any of this
you're going to get that pool
i'm going to get
alright paul know you do need a
title to measure i know i do
a title team
the title is
laverne and shirley oh is good
is that unfair scott ah not hazard
days happy chairman is here scott tremendous
who i don't know sorry scoot otterman
the guy from just shoot me that
yes yeah hi can just shoot me
i played the ah the guy in
the art class yeah no line cd
git i had a good number
leds i think it was i think
it was an over five if you
can say you're rich now and assesses
two different scenes have pooled he'll have
pool
so scott do you have an idea
of fours we'd like to hear it
because we need idea you need ideas
okay yeah so turning to shows yeah
we're a startup streaming service we need
content okay well i have the perfect
bit of content for you it's a
little ah hour long drama that i've
devised oh ah called ah gruesome evenings
gruesome evenings is the stuff of laverne
and shirley it's a spin off of
laverne and shirley yes are you allowed
to touch that yeah i've already talked
to the estate of garry marshall okay
and they're all in and it's also
a river it's a ah it's a
spin off of all in with chris
matthews as well so yeah
so it's current events but also an
hour long drama these universes intersecting yes
so carbine is say only with chris
matthews by the way yeah isn't that
who doesn't who is chris heroism yeah
this
i would watch that it's the person
chris hansen chris matthews and chris hill's
guys are best friends yeah say hello
to my best friend chris and chris
so the big ragu was involved carmina
big ragu and racism and chris harrison
ragu makes me want to barf ruggedness
ah the the brand the me the
meal was meat soya are you italian
because she's very otellini eighty one it's
made my my grandma she had a
pen pal when she was a child
and made her i know nah okay
so you only eat ah spaghetti sauce
when it's your grandmother makes it so
you do eat dry spaghetti a second
are you doing an
interview you pitching us to show this
is part of the show this is
what the character does study watch that
you just you've just watched what the
show is i'm so sorry because it's
about a factory that makes spaghetti sauce
in on it the whole time yes
see i called matt webcam and his
name is scott garena yeah yeah i
know whatever i say you pretend
to not know i know and yeah
i want to be on the show
and this is my way of begging
you for a role on one of
our shows yeah well this is interesting
so i'm begging you it's all i
want no we're colleagues yeah equals yes
but you're begging your on your hands
we have the same job but on
my hands and knees you are on
all fours for
here you're going running like a baboon's
butt hole asking the air like a
baboon's bunnell i'm just begging you out
of the corners of my ass
but i mean so have i sold
the show like i'm thinking congratulations you're
rich thank you to every itch and
go ahead please do not tell the
show but you are taking my job
i quit
alright so now laura yeah we have
time for me to yeah well okay
yeah alright ah and if we don't
get to all the games make sure
you send a postcard to collin say
no or ok games ah this is
ah one life to live okay
paul got up and is searching for
something okay yes can somehow yeah i'll
be playing shoot you install that matt
lauer door huh yes yes it's press
the button
oh and i to the shine bitch
god damn it ah let her id
hi hello i'm sorry about the shut
up bitch because i'm on it she
was talking to me
manage today okay ah who will always
lauren right oh it's lorne it's no
my name is doherty
story so so totally dirty tanto dori
dota like like it rhymes with morimoto
yeah okay dorado dory dodo welcome welcome
welcome to our estate can i get
you a cold coffee yes my face
on your case
wow okay i have a show to
beach
okay please pitch us your show um
just called a million deaths to die
a million minutes death star die interesting
this is an intriguing show yeah it's
about it and um a reincarnated being
who only died and come back over
and over again
i mean times may i ask what
ethnicity you are
jory dodo
i mean you have an ethnic sounding
name don't ask why you have some
sort of accent hey where are you
master yuan da you see
are you going to put a spell
on me yes i've waved my magic
wand and people tried to put spells
on them ok my secret is out
and from new orleans ah and so
what's the show about
a person lesbian incarnated a million times
over and over every animal everything every
person they have that person there every
person is that person so it's a
universal universal consciousness
every universal consciousness i'm ready the next
time you buy it so what will
wait i brought a gift oh oh
my wow giants i don't even know
how to describe this it's a big
big bag full of meats what kind
of meat do we have in here
so to continue
chicken liver chicken tenders that food cat
food chicken dinner i did oh chicken
soy chicken livers and she delivers chicken
dinner and cat food bank okay let's
dig in oh you lay on it
like a pillow oh you mean like
an inside yocan is bad because that
wrong asleep oh okay okay don't hurt
let's go
chat on it smooth oh god this
is i take your magic line
well yeah what
your chicken
e you're nothing i don't exceed
oh show sounds great
i have a pool and that's how
you play switches and pitch j play
now if you ever play it you've
played exactly like that now this is
a fun game that i really love
did you like this right yes describe
a scene from a movie but in
a way that is hard to guess
describe yes
yes okay no so you basically take
ah a scene from a movie that
well-known film and simplify it so much
or just describe it in an obscure
way okay so you have a film
in mind no i want someone else
oh you okay so yay so i'm
thinking of a film
ah okay i got it and i'm
supposed to describe it to both of
you or just like a scene from
ok a famous scene from a famous
movie
early early morning lacking
he wakes up
what to do grounds to
ah he knows home alone
definitely talk more
i go to friends house
friend mentor who know karate kid
plugin instrument
back to the future yes
nice
okay
now who are you what exit is
that that's that's ah accent that you
use when you are being mysterious yes
okay mysterious sexson um go to friend's
house i've got it okay
suburban yard the help
driveway big basketball hoop
dare we share these spaceship there moments
before a big event
reminding us of years gone by along
came polly
the famous movie with the famous scenes
a man older than his progeny
obviously
um daughter my daughter big event coming
up let's just take it back and
not sixteen candles to the times of
yore when things were easy pretty stand
by me see you as you were
then
a child eighteen again freaky friday and
we play this game she's having a
baby no nine months no big event
coming up
what do we ever get to the
big event because they give more we
do but i was just doing a
scene okay for the yes oh fasteners
together okay as part of them okay
alright i was at a disadvantage have
you ever seen that
i'm gonna die yeah alright alright
famous theme famous movie
traveling
planes trains and automobiles friendship
due date adventure
a monarch is crowned lord of the
rings a monarch overall blanking screaming game
of thrones the wind
blowing in your face fern gully
there was the owls of ghoul
harry potter
sounding your barbaric yop across the world
the world
what a highlander braveheart standing beside your
friend
princess bride star wars your friend from
another country from another mother princess diaries
friend a friend being crowned the salt
spray by the ocean
king king lear
low across the universe
mean more need more trying to give
more
and come on
the nutty professor two clumps lalande professor
two clumps two clumps
what do you take with your coffee
to clubs what a clubber sued nutty
clumps
to which nutty clump in my coffee
is there another seed passage no this
is the one scene that you know
very famous there's not much to it
ah you've seen it and you know
it okay godfather passage was very cheap
murder eyes the price of admission murder
on the orient express what
screaming shouting the polar express
santa claus movie santa claus too
come on do cops then it goes
to clumps
standing at the front of what
just give it away give it away
give it away now make it easy
standing at the front of
a boat titanic yes ah the monarch
king of the world the doi doi
doi doi but i think that got
a socket on it earlier sitting next
to his little italian friend oh yes
yeah kate winslet now is the time
for knows this is not the he's
next to well they're not together when
this is when he first gets on
the ship
and he's excited to be on the
boat i'm i'm i'm king of the
world ha king of the world when
he was with her no with her
it's he's holding her so she can
be like out like wow yeah we've
conflated those like screaming in her ear
i'm yeah well you're king of the
world okay alright that was fun i'm
already someone in the listener
the audience got it i hope so
but i don't think so
okay they got people got into before
alright i'm the i look our next
game is half written half improvised play
oh this also required oh huh
you remember
third okay so we i've given everyone
a play for my collection of early
members this so well ah that was
the one that i said kevin please
her seven please remind me so he
sent me an email okay um so
now ah lauren what play do you
have your we're gonna start we have
ah wilderness by eugene o'neill ah wilderness
not ah wiltern i said oh
how will ah wilderness oh wilderness and
comedy of recollection three x okay so
we're gonna go in a circle so
you and paul so lorin what this
game is is lauren is going to
read alternating lines from this actual play
oh ah wilderness by whose thornton wilder
right eugene eugene o'neill ah and paul
is
is going to improvise lines around those
of those lines the lauren reads yes
all right so ah lauren go ahead
tell me dick begin at the beginning
and tell me okay well um it's
a simple story i woke up that
day and i noticed that everything was
kind of different um dick you must
i swear i didn't think that i
did but i don't know what you
consider swears so i apologize was at
the word different set to swear
i'm awful sorry dick honest diane i
accept your apology i'll continue with my
story so um i looked out the
window and i know jack you didn't
no i did i looked out the
window and i saw that there were
these two birds that were behaving in
this strange fashion whoever had i'd have
died to honest i would
if you looked out the window and
saw the two birds you don't even
know what they were doing that's a
nice thing to say
i don't know if you're being sarcastic
but i'm i'm just trying to tell
you what happened with these birds so
they are they're pecking each other but
i can't tell if they're mad or
if they're having fun and the one
bird is really good at pick but
i told you paw
pop
but
ah i don't i don't do you
think i'm your dad or were you
not finishing a whatnot
okay
um i feel like we got off
on the wrong foot and i if
i've done something wrong i'm very sorry
i thought you wanted to hear this
story about these two birds what do
i care about your old presence you
tell me what you did so you
don't care if i'm here or not
and you think that this the story
is not about what i did
and what about these two birds six
miller i don't believe you ever
okay i see what this is about
this is a setup you get me
to tell a story that you know
is a little crazy so you can
call me a liar why that's a
terrible place pauses it ought to be
closed by the police
i
didn't quite hear what you said and
i'm not sure what needs to be
closed by the police but if you're
going to involve the authorities in this
i have proof that these birds were
acting crazy dick miller i hope you
didn't notice will you stop you don't
say my whole name every time
i noticed these birds and i took
video of them she must have been
a nice thing yeah
i don't know what the sex they
were bet it was dyed
it was their natural coloring okay they
were just brightly colored birds you've seen
birds like this before in pictures and
shit she was low in bed that's
what she was she couldn't be a
chorus girl and are smoking cigarettes proves
it and then what happened i didn't
even tell you about the smoking yet
yes one of the birds was smoking
a cigarette
yet yes she was loaded the ground
yes i could tell she was a
female from the plumage i don't see
how he could insult that kind and
why did you fight for her why
didn't the princeton fullback just because the
one bird first of all the principle
back are you wrong leap yes i
was drunk yes i'm glad i didn't
see you i hate people who
a drunk i'd have hated you
but what happened with that bell after
before you went home
the littler bird picked up the bell
it was driving the big bird crazy
the big bird put the cigarette down
oh what and did you kiss her
ah a little i was trying to
you're lying and you know it i
was trying to bring the bird back
here i was right at that time
lying in bed not able to sleep
wondering how i was ever going to
see you again crying my eyes out
well you know i hate you i
wish you were dead i never want
to lay eyes on you again and
this time i mean it well yet
you're wish you didn't let me finish
my story i am dead
i don't want to listen let me
go the turtle bite your hand that
you can try but your teeth are
gonna go right through because i'm a
ghost i'll go and steer that's the
kind of girl you like what do
i care you can't explain what can
you explain you owned up you kissed
her
i never said i didn't i tried
to give that bird mouth to mouth
i was pecked to death and i
suppose you just said and let yourself
be kissed tell that to the marines
i'm going to go down on the
recruiting station right now become the first
ghost marine and then you'll be sorry
scene
oh right paul now you have a
play i have six players six plays
done by lillian hellman the children's hour
days to come the little foxes watch
on the rhine another part of the
forest the autumn garden opened it up
to a random page which play let's
go for a famous one let's go
for the little fucks the lid
all foxes yeah no wait should i
have vetted this to make it doesn't
matter how many characters right not really
you can just kinda alternating like all
right
when you're reading scott okay scott young
gonna read with you right
um let's see let's see let's see
all right
ah um let me try to find
a good starting place here
okay
i've given my word that horace will
put up the money that should be
enough okay i just need fourteen million
dollars i know it sounds like a
lot but ah i'm really glad horse
is going to put this up because
i have nothing oh it was enough
i took your word but i've got
to have more than your word now
i okay the contracts will be signed
this week
marshall will want to see our money
soon after regina horace has been in
baltimore for five months i know that
you've written him to come home and
that he hasn't come it's resigned but
ah yeah i mean look i'll get
you the money by the time he
comes home don't worry about that i
mean i'm certainly not ah you the
destitute or anything i mean i have
a little lying
around you know i can probably siphon
off my wife's bank account if that
would help it's beginning to look as
if he doesn't want to come home
i definitely want to come home i
mean i'm you know i know we're
out here in the middle of the
field in the middle of the night
but i mean eventually we're gonna go
home and of course he wants to
come home you can't move around with
heart trouble at any moment you choose
oos you know what doctors are like
once they get their hands on a
case like this oh my god my
chest is pounding um yeah can i
go to a hospital by any chance
do you like could you just drop
me off at the hospital they can't
very well keep them from answering letters
can they they wouldn't keep him from
arranging for the money if he wanted
to
who are you talking about right now
are you talking about horace because i
need to get to a hospital has
it occurred to you that horse is
also a good businessman i know i
agree is but things are getting dire
for me my my chest has been
but i feel like i'm having a
heart attack for the past two hours
and we've been sitting here in a
field certainly he is a shrewd trader
always has been the bank is
proof of that i know the bank
probably has proof but ah look if
you want to talk about horse i
we can settle this right now as
long as you promised to take me
to a hospital afterwards then possibly he
may be keeping silent because he doesn't
think he is getting enough for his
mummy oh that makes sense i guess
he probably doesn't think he's getting enough
for his money what do you
talking about nonsense yes it is nintendo's
a good thing when he hears it
yes he knows we can make twice
the profit on common goods manufactured here
they can be made in the north
look i personally want to make it
in the south
the north is a little cold for
me that isn't what we're doing means
rejoin may i interpret you regina regina
regina is sad that morris wants more
than a third of our share
horace seems shifty to me have you
seen the way his eyes are like
really close together but he's only putting
up a third of the money you
put up a third and you get
a third what else could you expect
i don't know what i expect i
guess i expect horace to be like
more cool about everything well i don't
know i don't know about these things
it would seem that you put up
a third you should get a third
but then again there's no law about
it is there
i should think that if you know
your money was very badly needed well
you just might say i want more
i want a bigger share you boys
have done that i've heard you say
so what what does this fucking shark
tank i need to go to a
hospital so you believe he has deliberately
held out for a larger share yeah
i do honestly well i don't believe
it but i do believe that's what
you want am i right regina
it's rejoined but yeah yeah i do
i do want a bigger share than
horace look horace doesn't deserve it i
put in all the work oh i
shouldn't like to be too definite but
i could say that i wouldn't like
to persuade horace unless he did get
a larger share i must look after
his interests it seems only natural yeah
yeah of
of course it's natural it's as natural
as boobs and where would the larger
share come from
i mean i guess we we we
could you know find up before we
go public with it we could you
know stop and i don't know that's
not my business but perhaps it could
come off your share oscar a stop
talking about shares i've worked so hard
for this company i've worked so hard
i'm literally having chest pains right now
kind of talk is this it's medical
talk i haven't said a thing i
know i wish you would stop talking
you are talking very big tonight i'm
talking loudly to try to impart upon
you the gravity of the situation am
i well you should know me well
enough to know that i wouldn't be
asking for things i didn't think i
could get who are you you just
came into this conversation right now and
start talking i don't know you listen
no i don't believe you can even
get horace to come home much less
get money from him or talk quite
so big about what you want
look i apologize i'm not actually having
chest pains this is a ploy to
get more money out of you i
you know what's cooler than a million
dollars a billion dollars
oh i can get him to come
home
scene
thank you i really i receive eight
at the quick this works best if
it's a two person scene yeah oh
expecting multiple people yes
alright i have like five people have
this big conversation about money i have
a short two person scene this is
from the adding machine remember that play
o g roll zero ah this would
be me and laura and i will
be reading from the adding machine by
elmer l rice
says horsley
who are you
well i've came here to tell you
something really big what do you want
well i gotta tell you a big
secret i found out from ah a
friend of mine i don't know what
you're talking about well i think it
to say yet i found out from
a friend of mine that you're up
to no good and you actually might
be making the break squad cars around
the whole neighborhood it ain't right it
ain't fair i ain't getting a square
deal oh so it is true is
it
oh you're a nasty little car thief
break it up the break so everybody
gets sent the accidents well that added
machine was at a square deal after
twenty five years i don't know but
no way a machine when calculated it
costs something to buy those machines i'll
tell you that yeah what calculated what
five books
yeah give me a chance give me
another chance to shoot your brains out
i'm gonna kill you so fast you
won't even know that you will be
killed well the first thing i'd go
out and look for a job what
if you were dead well i ain't
young enough to take up something new
i'm gonna kill you so you'll get
the chance to get new job you
want to know
give me your way don't kill me
give me a chance give me another
chance oh no you'll get the chance
i will pull you to eyes out
i don't want to die i don't
want to die i want to live
and swim
a hey alright look winds up feel
so good we have to take a
break we'll be right back
welcome back alright our next game is
celebrity hunt who started this one ah
this was just one that we looked
up online it's like um oh you
say a celebrities name everyone says huh
next person right light breeze name that
starts with the last leg
owner of of previous level last letter
of the last name this was the
origin of the infamous stop something okay
here we go alright so learn you're
gonna start yes okay and we're going
clockwise or does it not matter yeah
ok it matters
amanda seyfried hunt david de company hans
yardley smith hunch helen hunt hunt thomas
haden church hunt ethan hawke yeah why
not me paul um ah the last
one was church yeah okay um ah
a little see hard
um helen mirren hoz hey
daniel hawthorne huh and eugene o'neill and
lisa loeb hides britney spears huh sam
elliott hunts die ah tamsin grey yeah
oh me too yeah the english address
i think sometimes grey
eek oh maybe that's your wow toe
in high way high way yeah
celebrity hunch okay we also skipped hypothetical
for those keeping score too long away
now is practically over time we'll come
back press conference oh yes you will
choose a celebrity and the other person
will be that celebrity and have to
guess who they are from the questions
the other to ask so wait so
we team together and pick a celebrity
and then this person is oh right
right so we're going to ask them
okay yeah guy no they ask us
questions are we we ask them questions
and understand okay got it okay so
i'm gonna pick sir lawrence riding down
the celebrity and going to show me
the name show me the money um
okay what's that person's name
you're thinking of a person okay i
got going on okay guys ah bill
cosby
okay got it
okay ready ready paul you're this person
yeah oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
you how do you feel about your
new project i mean i feel good
about it it's always exciting to have
a new thing to work on and
i think people are going to be
happy with the new project way over
here me oh shut up boy you
go are your hours much better now
yeah they were not good before and
now i like them over here oh
over here are you spending more time
with your family
sure em love em missed them
great to be around them over here
over here yeah is it hard to
be a father it's such an old
age shoot and you had a kid
later in life yes well ah i
will be dead by the time my
son is in college so that's weird
and my name is david letterman yeah
yes alright let's move on to christmas
find out google yeah christmas okay christmas
my dad who gave christmas idaho game
right side out okay okay so this
is a game where kevin or read
a list of questions and we will
write down who is most likely to
have done the thing and then we
will go through
ooh and find out the answers
okay and how can you vote for
yourself remember you can vote for yourself
okay it's ten how many questions do
we have one two three four this
pen also sucks in case you haven't
yeah it's bad it's okay six seven
six seven got it alright question was
using dry erase markers on paper so
puffy and oh yeah
were puffy and this is i don't
want that okay what about that just
tell me if i can burp the
jingle bells can burp jingle can burp
the jingle bells okay jingle bell the
way oh this requires writing down i
forgot yeah too that's why i offered
you that pen that you scoffed oh
okay scott i still didn't want to
pen
literally let him use a sharpie and
later wait okay maybe i was not
paying attention because i was doing you
want to know your mouth is okay
burp jingle right yeah we just writing
down the names okay yeah ah has
received socks for christmas
okay yes i'm locked-in has a real
christmas tree as a real christmas tree
i'm locked-in locked-in you just say one
person yeah one person out of the
three of us that you think it's
christmas find out who game just the
best game anytime a year has sat
on santa's lap
yep
kip likes eggnog
okay yep yep has gone christmas carolyn
kick up and last question knows the
name of santa's reindeers
okay yep
okay let's find out who yea
that's like this the sad version of
the of when you're watching a sitcom
like oh i love that when they
would do lining see the sting a
little yeah or like on entertainment tonight
when someone has died and they announced
things like puh vs isabel sketch with
tom hanks is one of the hosts
but whose tonight tom
mt yes yeah dude so you got
okay so what do we do we
when he's like sibilance sibilance sibilance sibilance
okay okay so so the first question
is why who can burp the jingle
bells they said it wrong
oh good but the jingle bells so
keep up the lifestyle i've said lauren
no i said scott i said scott
can you burp like on command no
me neither
i you i can but i can't
do it quickly enough to do a
song but still the whole process till
you're most likely because hey yeah ooh
okay so now you just gotta write
it none of us got it okay
has received socks for christmas paul i
set myself i send me i have
received socks so awry but who
hasn't okay so we're all we all
get a point we all get it
right i mean are people playing this
game with people's wanna feed
uno's okay three has a real christmas
tree i said lauren i said paul
i showed me i use a fake
tree i use a fake tree i
use a real name yeah i did
not get rick okay okay how sad
do i also get a point yeah
yeah if you said you yeah i
did because it was funny looking has
sat on santa's lap
i said lauren me because it lauren
yes i have okay we all get
right likes eggnog i said scott i
said me i sent me oh i
love it i love it in fact
cool i've made fun of me because
i bought a ton of it for
our christmas party last year and she's
gonna know it had it janey makes
fun of me for it wow so
we but i think we're both neuro
yeah
i don't know why i made my
eggnog great original like you knox is
good it's just good you can't get
the rest of the year it's like
why wouldn't i have like the shamrock
shake job like it's nasty nasty i
gotta point we all got a point
alright we all got a six has
gone christmas carolyn me
i said me i said scott i
have okay so i've never done it
so we each get a point you
should put molly i used to cruise
missile i used a christmas carol in
the mall in sacramento i said we
we the stores to this too well
to the people to a store i
would look up at forever twenty one
and sing ding dong the bells to
the
hurting young men ah no we are
higher when i was doing a christmas
carol up there
four of us were hired to
to dress up in dickensian you know
our christmas carol stuff and christmas carol
throughout the mall i just keep picturing
in front of difference to the stores
to the stores
alright what's the last question knows the
name of santas reindeers i said paul
me i said scott whoa do you
i don't oh so you're well away
we go dasher and dancer and prancer
prancer vixen then i'm cupid donner and
blitzen but do you read
cause paula morin
no we do know okay and i
don't get the point so i get
a point i got no no i
don't know like oh but i said
paul i said paul so i do
get a point okay right i've proven
that i know them yeah but if
you said you said scott yeah i
did i don't get a boy i
got six point i got five i
didn't keep trying yeah
nowadays prisoners yeah okay christmas who gave
christmas find out okay christmas find out
who game alright now it's time to
play thirty two toothless vegetables
this game is fun okay so we
have to just say a vegetable or
fruit without showing our teeth no repetition
allowed ready okay you take us get
fats
oh no no
grover
show larue community
robo
ah russell flow
green beans
oh sh oh sh
bloom what dorian the odour that type
of orange it's it's some fruit that
like it's it's the it's the stealing
just thinking for it yeah yeah they're
looking for from
right
young
i
little bird
it's one half
right that was good is it if
so someone laughs with that idea i
don't remember if you are a p
there is some game i can't remember
which one it is that you can't
oh wait we're getting into a game
you hate oh yeah you don't like
this ball this is how do you
do this time i'm gonna pull it
together you gotta pull together this is
we sing a song only using the
word do and we have to guess
the song
okay alright so lauren you have volunteered
to go first so let's hear the
song using only the word do
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo two two two two two
party like it's nineteen ninety yeah oh
i was thinking midway through am i
allowed to do the tune yeah i
think what do you mean anyways i
just say how would we guess it
if you didn't do the tune
okay fine what do you mean the
banking try like do do two two
two two two two two two two
two two two which i know that's
just the real git yeah it was
that that's not the tune yeah no
i think you have to do i
think you gotta give your okay okay
okay i all do do do do
do do do do do do
doo doo doo doo doo doo ah
christmas song you do do yes yeah
yeah huh
nah i love it would be dude
do do do da da da da
da da to do house jang bell
due to do to to redo due
to yoga boot do you get my
man down due to dan with zamzam
down and zazu
yeah da that's right stand up and
say i did better you're going okay
well i'll do one more because it's
okay
okay okay
oh doh doh oh hey hey vida
okay okay doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo today
irdeto dude
due to duty duty duty duty i'll
do do do do do do okay
and i didn't duly
yeah no darling no doodles no doodles
no dooley no dudley no duly don't
do that
really want to watch totally negatively
to to to to start helping you
do this every
do you get a spanking for this
i feel like the star spangled banner
comes up all locks were sung that
saw it oh ninety lie oh oh
oh i want i thought it was
fang do you know what the stars
biggest better is a wonderful story and
i'll tell it over and over and
over again is it not patriotic to
spank during the national
the anthem is it not a true
is it unpatriotic bay oh to spank
during the net would do you think
trump would get upset about that well
you because you should have your hand
over your heart but what about your
your other hankins bank know you well
if you're if you're left if you're
a lefty shore but if you're a
righty then you're screwed so wait righty
tidy
lefty loosey oh homie i go oh
me i'm moving into a new game
there is a fun singing game as
well called hotspot someone thinks a song
inspired by word and then using a
song inspired oh yeah song my mother
and then using words pie by that
song okay so what someone gives someone
a word yeah gmbh give a word
and whoever's first inspire
hired train
now that she's back in the atmosphere
afraid that steam i think of me
as plain old changeover are about a
man who was too afraid to plaza
we never did let ya lucky me
go to the si fa la la
ni de la masse
voila me i want to fly like
any go i believe i can fly
i believe i can touch the sky
do you
love fear someday sab se real it
okay strong enough now are you strong
enough to be my man yeah um
i was walking home one night i
got into a big old
huh
yes
hi
yeah ga although troubles seemed so far
away nowadays if they're here to stay
oh i believe and yesterday a tomorrow
tomorrow i love ya tomorrow it's only
a day oh hey i love you
oh yeah
every day i will be with you
every day i know about you i
love you oh my
yeah
and that's how you play that hotspot
bar let's take a break why is
it a hotspot because you're causing the
improv game you get in the middle
and you're on the bass
things like things like
hey we're back next up is paul's
favorite the ministers catch my favorite of
all times always want to play loves
this game is machine drum hey close
with your minister and reminds you of
him yeah yeah i really lean on
him a lot lean on him i
do
alright how do we play histories can
you come up with an adjective to
describe the minister's cat and you're keeping
time and you go in the order
of abc that's the alphabet all right
i'll bet a quarter
and paul you're starting yes i am
the minister's cat is an albino cat
the minister's cat is a beautiful cat
the minister's cat is a calico cat
the minister's cat is a dumb care
to minister's cat is an eagle a
tarion cat the minister's cat is a
friendly cat the minister's cat is away
a grand cat the minister's cat is
a horrendous cat the minister's cat is
an ignorant cat and there's good chat
as a jokey catch administers minister's cat
is a karmic cup you're out his
hard i feel like i was already
helping that's alright i just gotta go
so early on the minister's cat is
a little cat the minister's cat isn't
normal is cat the minister's cat is
a night like cat tonight just
like a cat that lights up as
a nightlife it's not a real cat
it's like felix yeah ah minister's cat
favorite game and i want it again
alright the next game is the last
game here we go one player says
huh the next player says haha and
so forth first person to laugh for
real loses so this one
it has a loser not a winner
great right that's right yeah i think
all the games have losers
i lost my paper okay sounds like
you're going through your notes alright oh
what am i going to happen do
we how do we do we go
around in a circle yeah okay lauren
starchy
and you mix up the laugh sounds
right and yeah and then you try
to copy them i think so
huh
haha
hahaha
ha ha ha ha ha ha hee
ha ha ha hee hoo ha ha
ha hee hoo ha ha ha ha
hee hoo ha ho ha ha ha
ha ha ha ho ho ha hee
hoo ha ho how how how
wrong but okay wrong but imo
but ah wow look good i say
hello to my best friend haha he
ha ha ha hee hoo hoo ha
hoo wow i don't remember so well
let's start with just one huh
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ho ho ho ho e
okay it was
oh no no we both lose because
it's true i did not win that
game you both lost alright well lauren
loss oh this ones we at cornell
e
nice and cold that i don't know
someone pointed a player and says a
title the person on their right has
to say a new title using last
word maybe this is something like a
plural no no it was definitely the
other wow okay you're saying jewels yeah
okay so it's tied to balloons we
kept putting this
okay so all start with a title
it's a title of anything and it's
a title of anything right and okay
any if anything a tale of two
cities
city of angels are just okay sure
angels and insects
insects
in the field
i don't know ah okay then you're
out okay we're just doing lightning rules
yep okay lightning rules thanks
sex in the city
the city i guess
city of night nightcrawler was that one
word
it was one word oh shit napping
well i mean i don't think it
matters i'm just saying or like i
could do like
night of the living dead oh fuck
yeah that'll smart real war
dead calm
call me mummy almost immediately i don't
have one oh la home me by
my name obviously me by my neighbor
home and my manner and that was
kanye
alright twenty one questions this is a
classic this is a classic so we
we think of a person or a
thing i can't remember and yeah person
yeah annie thing and chavez back by
the way
back ah it's just anything okay i'll
i'll think of it um it's any
okay ah yeah i got it i
got is it animal animal vegetable or
mineral and it's not yes or no
questions it's okay it's okay to say
no because it was taking okay animal
okay
does it have fur no
does it have feathers now like in
inside out pillow ya know
is it a reptile no
is it a fish no
those that have eyes on the side
of it's head know
is it a mythological creature no
is it a mammal yes
is it a seal no
they live on land yes how did
you wrong
it's okay yes it does it yeah
no worries over switching off and then
all of a sudden you took over
i mean what's going on oh it
do it hey hey do it she's
like yeah is it long lived
we're we don't know yet
let's
wait so does your animal know because
it doesn't have further than feathers i
reptile i didn't i picked something specific
maybe i was supposed to pick something
general you're like donald duck or something
something yeah is it supposed to just
be that real chevron said anything it's
fine is it real yes like it
exists
is is it a character no
is it famous yes
is it
different emperor doesn't have fur doesn't have
feathers not a fish it's not a
reptile it's a mammal it's a mammal
it's not a seal guys it's a
human being i'm just getting a few
oh my god that's not the amp
no it's not it's not the answers
this specific human being know i know
that's annoying why is it but he
said
anything because it's not tangible
well i understand that we are animals
but like whoa
ah is it someone in this room
no
oh okay so it's a famous person
who hasn't died yet
is it famous do we do we
i think we said famous okay this
is is is this person um older
than fifteen yes
is it male or female female
is it a singer yes is it
britney spears no we have is our
final question
here are the questions i asked does
it have hair is it a mammal
outside is it britney spears but not
limited to a lot of the things
being there before
britney spears didn't have hair one point
so um
and it's it's a singer right yeah
she's a singer yeah female singer yeah
is it carly rae jepsen i wish
it's christina aguilera guys i suppose you
were close i thought i remembered last
time we played with stuff like the
moon or something which was far more
okay okay my turn wait i thought
we had to speed through these okay
we do alright what time is it
oh my gosh we have
fifteen minutes left oh here we go
here we go this is a good
one this is hey fred schneider what
are you doing
ooh or it did that's well you
know why you need a big wind
up like you're gonna clap and then
you put your hands together so gently
find the rhythm
slang fred schneider what are you doing
going to the market to pick up
supplies hey flintshire why ah you doing
driving back home and say hi to
my y for y
why are you doing i'm picking up
my prescription pho hey
huh are you doing getting a mirror
or checking my anus for words okay
presider
are you doing yep there's worms bad
or go to that doctor hey schneider
why are you doing on second thought
i'm gonna keep though
schneider well ah you know is chopping
up the worms that may go worm
army hey for schneider what are you
doing stagy necro on the united states
government hey fred schneider what are you
doing i'm sneaking into the white house
hey fred schneider
what are you doing come back day
red wires green wires now hey fred
schneider what are you doing blowing up
the world using the nuclear arsenal hey
fred schneider what are you doing i'm
looking at a laptop outside of the
white house now hey rich later what
are you doing
renewing my subscription to the new york
times hey bro charter what are you
doing applying for a new discover card
hey fred schneider what are you doing
i'm buying stuff five my new card
racking up points on that
discover car hey fred schneider what are
you doing arguing with a t and
t about their delivery precision
ah yeah huh
oh dear hello there i have to
pee sorry i know we still have
ten minutes okay hey there let's go
play being in a great
oh
i decided there was a better way
to do this like like let's give
it okay yeah it didn't work okay
which did not work alright we to
not go into the listener who submitted
that um it didn't work hey why
not a good game we do not
you okay
okay so we each pair has sixty
seconds to find as many things in
common as they can it's a third
person has that in common it doesn't
count okay so shoving in a timeless
ah okay sorry
yeah me and paul being paul first
okay and we have we have to
think we've seen things we have in
common that's got does not have in
common so we're trying to find things
that we have in common that he
will not have in common okay all
if i have it in common i'll
speak up and you do not okay
for it okay three two one um
have you
i were fucking wow okay um do
ya drive stick shift no me there
oh shit
do you
did you ever have a pet lizard
or a chameleon know i did
did you ever have a pet cat
yes me too yeah did not um
have you ever um um
um have you ever baked a cake
no yeah
have you ever worked with will ferrell
yes i have who wasn't sure um
have you ever ah sat in a
trunk while the car is moving drunk
yeah we had a trunk or the
back of a pickup truck a trunk
i have not done this
have you ever worked at john c
reilly yes no um have you ever
um wow
once you guys got four so say
who was going to be in the
head phone okay we got for ya
ford didn't have okay okay oh it's
you guys against me okay but tell
me jealous one okay one sorry three
two want you have a penis yes
i do yeah fair do you have
a left testicle yes i do do
you have a right tested
such as heater you have non-functioning nipples
yeah me too
please don't care had sex with a
woman these all don't count start over
well that that one could i'm not
speaking about wow stand up what a
sterile day i'd over
oh yeah illegal well right we've had
our lords that's accesible no i didn't
say that have you ever shaved your
beard yes
well let's move now let's move on
move on move on alright alright let's
go to twenty one ah go around
the room telling a story where each
person says a word however one person
has romance oh we're we're telling a
continuous sentence but we all have a
o each ever different genre i was
thinking oh we're doing laugh
last sorry i'm sorry to say it
we're keeping that behind the cart you
just brought it out in front delete
delete
um so each so one of us
has okay so lauren you have romance
okay i have uplifting and paul u
f scary okay sure okay sexually
you really shouldn't start sentences with adverse
i think lasso slick whereby
it
inspired deep fear in grinds
from
heaven underneath
mum is
memorial sheets
that
came hard
scarily
ah i came
underground where writhing only
it appeared inside
the
orifice
internally
then
nothing came
out oh fuck
and that was whatever that was sure
was alright one word impressions oh yeah
good okay
ooh good one word impressions this we
can only say one word and we
have to guess who it is okay
okay stoa
marlon brando
yeah
crook
yay
hears technical yeah we did it all
right and now perfect ground pitch a
sick song perfect wrestling
yeah
so someone gives a name of a
song and someone else pitches a sitcom
based on the song and then whoever
pitched the song title then asked to
come up with the theme song to
the right guys what okay so you
so learn you you give the name
of a song it had to be
me wait is that a real song
no no that's wrong
it had to be good it had
to be you me or paul you're
gonna pitch it had to be you
yeah ah this is a show it's
about um the you familiar with the
highlander legend ah there can only be
one yeah that's all i know about
it this is a guy he doesn't
want to be the highlander oh god
um he was chosen to be it
and sharan passed this responsibility off to
anyone else right and it causes him
a problem at work of course because
yes this regular job at the electric
company rand he has to keep leaving
making excuses to go to highlander business
right and you you've created a song
for us i gotta go
kish j my businesses more important than
this yeah i got it
kids say well said staff said gotta
go
and that's how you play pitcher sit
song
alright now we have monologue thief
we played it last episode monologue thief
new start
i remember like it was yesterday it
was it was yesterday actually now that
i think about it i look on
calendar i see it was yesterday the
way it went down and i turned
the page off it's a new day
and i'm like that was two days
ago now flashback to a million years
ago the dinosaurs roamed the earth i
was born out of a frog's ass
it was not pleasant and i didn't
like it but your mom
is your mom what are you going
to do i still love her i
don't know what to say and all
she says to me is ribbit ribbit
ribbit but what i liked your top
i got oh hi i still remember
seeing all the sights and sounds of
hide em
and see
we've come to the very last one
this is i'm glad we thought this
out yeah yeah this is what am
i thinking okay simply enrolling at the
same time oh god a man gotta
this is how it ends we just
got our final episode of three demands
with a bang but with me whimpering
one way
anyway we got to think of it
any word or thing whatever it is
why re choose to one news i
said nut to your lobes tonight and
tissues all right ear lobes nuts and
tissues ready three two one pound me
to tip masturbate and what coming youtube
masturbate incoming really to one shiva
p ho come rack peel and wash
chisholm chisholm cum rag pee hole and
chisholm ready three two one calculus i
said whacking paul and i said jacqueline
through whacking so ejaculate and winking okay
three two one oh yeah i'd say
so
this it's i was like huh alright
one more time i'm thirty two was
good jerking off in pi i said
that a diagnosis that's a genus and
use a debit deputy yeah so right
venus and jerking off debit debit okay
ready
me too masturbating so i said this
she's okay we gotta start over okay
it got started over starving okay ready
anywhere anywhere three three two one
cholera fedora glass coffee fedora glass okay
three two one ma then mug paul
and a mug and would you say
italian italian and mug three two i
always surveys headshot and express sharma got
to know italian mug okay i thought
of a headshot
but what does it what were um
chops presto scarface scarface headshots okay ready
here are three ways you know paul
and i have guessed it yeah any
time i'm really not on-board al pacino
and well my little friend my little
red friend my old friend okay three
two one zone or you said scruffy
i said john kelso show
can't go because i mean so i
make this zolli because he played his
friend johnny pizza pie
alright look we gotta go well yeah
yeah we gotta love you guys thank
you so crazy listening you something to
do as a whole not individually if
you're listening to this on stitcher premium
go fuck know these episodes are all
going to be ah in the in
the regular feed in a couple of
weeks so listen to them all over
then yeah trying to learn your wolf
and if you're listening to this on
your wolf then may who knows what's
next for us maybe there will be
another season on stitcher who knows so
long in the future everything could have
changed yeah we'll all be
but seriously we love doing the show
yes this is so much fun for
us and it's so much fun to
know that people are responding to it
we appreciate all the messages that people
have sent through various media it really
is strange visitors that come to us
it really does mean a law and
it's been really fun interacting with you
guys on the web
thank you professor
and we will be selling spanking slippers
yeah flappers through amazon through amazon there
huh there have been some people who
offered to design us i know some
spanking slap i'm not against it i'm
not against either not for it i
don't want shevlin thank you so much
for being here since the beginning is
that right
can i keep the cd pyramids yeah
you can keep it and you've been
with us since the beginning right shaven
since episode two you weren't here on
episode one no korean korean was hero
oh thanks to korean for ah hitting
quistgaard she got started yeah pushed us
out of the nest girl by the
t-shirts say yeah sucking on shilly dough
da da da da da da ga
ravages ah guys thank you whoa drop
them mike
trump and mike
customize everything
every
a way
a well see ya mike java ma
embracing things
bye
a