sorry
wow masha
the bizarre bodies like wow you're talking
about some wow like wow a threesome
helicopter masha and when he got around
to think about mash because there's a
helicopter suicide on na
brings on maddy j j is welcome
to three nickel
a one two three oh one two
three four five started watching that i'm
enjoying but i have not yes lord
la shame but we ah cool i've
actually talked about it on when i
was on adtech tommy paul f tompkins
okay tell me scott alchemy it's called
call my agent and it's on yes
and it's a french french and it's
really my law
i like it i've heard good things
about it i haven't seen me everyone
was saying it was good and i
was just i was just putting my
heels down call my age and what
is this about my afternoon oh my
god you're in it what are they
going to say cpm bathroom break to
whose chair so there's a there's a
french guys pretending to be you oh
shit it's about you and your age
why
yeah yeah and he is my cool
really skating impression yeah it's he's wearing
like prosthetics but did you watch it's
like a living care knows yeah every
everything is just exaggerated orc he's a
real dork but cool right guys watching
ah you know what jamie and i
just watched another route
and the danish film starring mitch mitchell
said you watch a lot of um
danish shuttle thing yes shoe i watch
a lot of danish bullshit um it's
an oscar nominated film ah and ah
it's very good it's about for ah
friends um who decide they are going
to
to test this theory that you should
maintain a constant ah level of ah
blood alcohol um in order to live
life to the fullest oh so constantly
he has mean yeah but to call
again another round huh
i understand why it's funny it's touching
because they're all shaped in like so
they they want another round yeah they
need one more guy
we're all round
well yeah work guy
nowhere john lennon glasses so i was
always john glenn john clegg glasses yeah
yeah glutted way yeah my favorite
niggers john coletta every john should have
their own signature shape of glass yes
don't you agree oh yeah john lynn
yeah like angle stop sign shaped glasses
no one does those you don't refer
to it as a hexagon i do
after watching one division certainly oh sure
i don't get it yeah do you
watch any of that lauren i didn't
but i thought i like what it
looks like i just know i won't
understand any of the references
um i understood the a lot of
the references i'm not as steeped in
that lore like i probably didn't i
probably missed a bunch of sort of
easter egg type thing yeah but speaking
to easter that's the holiday were common
right yeah i think we just mannywood
speaking of easter it's over now
yeah we'll have had it a weekend
too yeah so worthy a truck oh
my god yeah i don't yeah shut
up shut up sir we're happy and
we did nothing i swear to god
easter hat just happened on sunday well
no because it's coming up this sunday
it's a real life bread
this recording no but i'm saying we
were we already recorded one that will
come out next week yeah easter just
happened good and then we're on the
next one this is insanity you are
now did you spend it
i i here's the thing last easter
i had just had a flat arrest
and a flashback to last easter because
i do girl oh my god so
last year we had been locking my
heart briefly for like a couple weeks
okay but i was kind of amazed
more than
a couple of weeks because it wasn't
what's his name going like we're gonna
open up at easter it's going to
be fabulous okay maybe it was a
month at that point so what kind
of output uniform daisy i didn't oh
and she got a great guy i
put on an easter dress and i
was like i'm gonna have a new
i'm gonna have easter and i'm gonna
feel like it's easter you got your
easter tree i'm manager
and easter like do you like it
do you does it mean something to
ya my guess i just i like
traditions and i like like i would
like to touch easter parade i would
like to watch the movies or parade
or you know just literal parade there's
a great isn't it like um i
don't know is there where here or
something i like to watch bullshit like
that like touch i like to watch
spec
titles like to watch television special events
sure i'm very excited about them like
i would like to watch charlie brown
easter i want to watch like something
that feels like it's happening right and
marking time and at the time alien
all those eggs and paul really knows
that we were playing animal crossing heavily
at that yes we were the survey
was on the island and it was
very stressful trying to get all those
eggs in time and found something that
you can talk about that i don't
know about huh yes huh and i
you know wanted to kill that fucking
bunny and he's back apparently having been
playing for a long time really it's
tough news costume i know because either
zipper and haunting and if you touch
if you look
the zippers stop looking at that yeah
but i saw a picture of myself
from them and i was like you
know that was like a very i
have such a visceral reaction what did
you put on address and play animal
crossing is honestly what i did and
i'm saying
i'm not saying that was like hello
but i'm saying like i have this
feeling about that time of quarantine where
i can like taste and smell it
yeah it's like it's like such a
specific time do you remember the phases
the quarantine phases you've been through yeah
i've had a bunch of different things
and at that time i was getting
um csea boxes those like farm boxes
of fruits vegetables the confederates were not
get delivery of my groceries i was
going to the grocery store but i
would stock up for like a couple
of weeks and baba list your phases
you'll list your quarantine phase well raw
roasting vegetables was astro theory like a
lady one of them
roasting vegetables because i was due i
was using these boxes and i had
like a use also roast veggies when
you do put them on a pan
for fifty o like olive oil or
olive oils seasonings cut up whatever i
got would be like carrots potatoes sure
whatever the fuck they send me you
ever see a rabbit wearing glasses no
good point
and then cook it for like eight
an easter bunny at the trump white
house that's a good point too so
yes i have more huge classes i
just felt like i can smell those
vegetables and i started to get so
sick of my boxes because right they
have the same thing that i started
like hate how it was turning a
chair and i'm like oh
wow and then i i couldn't stand
it and you imagine like growing up
on a farm then and and and
you're um like you're you're the farmer
or you're the farmer's wife and that's
all that you eat is whenever that
person is growing and yeah how sick
of it better be good you know
what i mean like can you grow
anything other than broccoli i don't know
they don't get anything besides what they
grow that's it no some people they
don't do they don't go to market
like you know more than once every
two months this little telnet food i
don't think no they do i'm saying
like thanks i keep enough to have
like saying farmers now i'm saying farmers
back when farmers only
i only ate the ones you and
i
i was here wow yeah ignored whatever
semi or other faces exact roast vegetables
was a big phase for me that
was the last time i had um
my when we first got peacock i
had my phase lasted six weeks maybe
where i watched ah poker after dark
oh yeah i may entourage phase where
i watched all of entourage again i
had my power walking with my weights
phase blasting music where i was like
i'm actually doing fine and that was
like a good couple of months where
i was feeling pretty solid about that
i had my making cakes phase that
was a solid one i had my
steve harvey family feud fe wow
i had ah now i'm in my
star trek next generation phase where i'm
almost done with that i kind of
need a fake my justified phase i
mean animal crossing was a big phase
for me and it led me to
a paid gig so i wasn't really
mad about that that's good i had
my writing phase that was good that
was really oh my god i haven't
really had any
productive that was the one thing i
was like i cannot have this happen
for a year and not come out
of it with something and so i
just like it's true i mean i
guess i had done some sat down
and like made myself write a pilot
and a and i finished it and
i was like very glad that's good
yeah paul dvd phases yes thank you
you are always allowed to chime in
you have to show your ignore but
you guys can chime in you guys
were going back and forth so we
were at a good clip i was
like i'm not gonna yell to talk
about my phases so i'll do that
now i know you will
um i learned by negative example oh
my god speak softly paul and tell
us your face malaria big stick my
phases were i think of them as
clothing based i went through a pajamas
phase where we're full pajamas yes and
like all day long yeah good good
i went through a um coveralls fe
phase yeah huh where i was wearing
like sort of speed suits yep um
i went through a very depressive like
ah like regular pajamas phase like t-shirt
and soft pants right i did a
lot i felt like the real giving
up no of me wearing sweatpants in
public was giving up but i
yeah boy you like wearing just wherever
i was going i never will i
be wearing crocs in public but yeah
it was giving i never worked my
pants i've turned a corner where unless
i was traveling maybe but even then
only for a long flight that was
really a like i don't i'm not
proud of that that was i will
only do that if i was coming
from the gym yeah totally yeah
i also feel like what i've just
remembered is that i have a lot
of shoes and i was like i've
been wearing the same like two pairs
of shoes or ah yes i i
wore sandals from the start of quarantine
all the way up until maybe november
something like that and then switched over
to the crocs but isn't a fan
just have switched back to sandals now
but isn't it just like
like wait why did i think that
because i had to wear a mask
i couldn't even put an outfit on
like what well i mean steamer nautilus
but it seems yeah well that's the
sign of depression it is but also
like mass depression yeah i feel like
everyone was going through where it's just
like well why should i even fucking
bother to put on cause i never
anywhere makeup like a full year because
no one was seeing me yeah so
for like suffer you know if i
had to do it guys
zoom or some i know that sometimes
they put it on i'm like oh
i look so much like sexy my
know but like it or if i
put it on i go oh yeah
i feel better like right it's like
just that you kind of forget all
i don't think i feel better if
i put on a button-up shirt and
pants anymore you might know it now
and i wore that i wore that
every single day for most of my
life and now i'm like
i a a minute maybe i'm a
sweets guy now maybe i'm a switch
person for me it was definitely like
i would feel i absolutely noticed it
when i would have to put on
clothes to go somewhere for whatever for
their huge better i had to do
and i was like i really like
this i feel more human yeah human
yeah human eye one of your humour
awesome it's just um
it's true no i mean it's the
same for exercising in a way where
you're like oh i i literally do
feel better if i do this yeah
i know and then the next day
you're just like what i'm gonna do
this every day of my life i'm
i look back on the time and
like part of me is pissed that
i didn't maintain things that i was
doing before i mean the way i
have i had fun
what's going on with me they hurt
my ear oh okay because it's too
loud or no because we've had them
on for oh they're pushing my well
your ears are also shaped like headphones
a lot of people don't know that
yeah i don't know if anyone's realised
that they'll like one size bigger than
the actual headphones yeah
but i i look back and i
think you look like you're in a
movie pretending to be a d j
or some literally roll i'm gonna get
around
like i'm always in a control room
but i um i feel like i
look back and i think oh man
i had such good habits like right
before this happened right i was really
working out like three times a week
at like classes doing like two five
week and that's doing seven i was
i was doing eighteen days a week
and i
ah but i'm like sadie that i
like couldn't i couldn't keep it up
but like i haven't no one could
i know but it's like i feel
mad at myself but i also don't
know that's just like barack johnson yeah
but like i i didn't have a
sure way do you mean even the
rock probably like let's something
slipped during you think thinking had a
cheat snack at one point no but
i mean like maybe he was like
you know what i'm gonna take up
the guitar and then it just abandon
better whatever yeah i'd make a choice
but i had my piano phase yeah
that was brave but i do want
to get back into signature cocktail phase
where every night around five pm it
was like let's make a brand new
unique weird car
wow i had a drinking wine every
night phase yeah came in and out
eating whole bags of chips face yeah
wow like saying like let's just have
doritos now yeah like you just go
like yeah yeah it's time to party
i'm not gonna like so are we
do you feel like we're coming out
of it i just celebrated a strong
mentally
the i am coming out of it
a little bit because even today i
was like i'm gonna find a pair
of shoes i haven't worn the entire
year and that's why i'm oh is
that what that is salvation forever but
it felt special to go like hey
ya know what i could still put
together an outfit yeah was looking for
guys like brussels like us
spring has sprung and ah it felt
good to me to put on actual
clothing yeah a belt yeah right and
i mean we can't ignore the fact
that everyone's getting vaccinated and it actually
feels like we're going to be feels
like we could see do something yeah
when i am i'm half maxed i
get my my second one
and a couple which side were you
left side that okay so you'll get
your side but you'll get your right
on my face
i should give it to me just
like your boss palsy yeah i said
give it to me right in the
cheekbone i just want a little lift
you're not supposed to switch arms know
you're supposed to get the your non-dominant
arm because you'll like a lot of
people get covert arm which is like
for a week ah yeah it's her
bumpy hurts and stuff like that
i wasn't too bad it was sore
for a day and then after that
it was only if i pressed on
it um which you loved to do
i know that you're real press on
my arm guy was asking people plea
for my plea was the only way
we can get you to talk to
i was looking for a pressing arm
daddy
versatile left out now lauren is swapped
the headphones down to where the top
of it is down by like this
for a while you had to wear
the the strap was on your forehead
i don't like how they feel i
might you know a girl call here
in a futuristic thing is like you
look like jordy
i know everything star trek to me
now because my god let me go
huh soldier left so what's what do
you want your next phase to be
like what do you hope for out
of here oh hey besides that what
do you hope to bring back like
like just besides i wouldn't mind getting
back into the writing phase i did
i did thankfully complete like a big
project the other day
day so i was nice i'll go
oh good i'm not just gonna sit
here going like well sure i did
one thing but i ended i've finished
in july and then from july till
march right anything else i finished another
thing so that's good about you know
i went on a little journey recently
emotional journey because i think i've told
you guys that i'm yeah i'm a
journey digitizing emoji yes
i told you guys i'm digitizing all
this stuff you didn't just tell us
you've been sending i've been sending some
clips what was that long twenty minute
one that i don't watch i know
that wasn't me i didn't watch it
that was so shaky i skipped her
on it but i was confused by
somebody's looking for somebody's looking for someone
who wasn't me erasmo
i that was a video check kremlin
i think around some day have you
seen the commercial of fucking ashton kutcher
mila kunis singing it wasn't me but
it's like
you know what i've seen it without
the sound because like hits like ashton
kutcher kuchera singing i'm huge huh he
doesn't know the notes okay so i
would say check it out which part
is he thinks oh because it's about
directo it was me it wasn't me
eighty eighty is about it was yeah
easy no way cheeto dust but what
is this because pop chips dropped him
after he did that offensive indian character
now shaggy i don't know why she
was in the commercial it was a
super bowl thing jackie where are you
lately anyway we're gonna say
let's see if he's going to old
video going through old videos and stuff
oh my god for someone he's looking
for someone and he's looking for someone
to capture that dude's clock can't wait
till it ends up with you getting
arrested or the helicopter landing in their
yard yeah it comes and gets you
and we've all been like still trying
would have been recruited like
anyway recruited like an independent dream ion
but i also mean your super jumbos
i so it was making me i
started with the oldest stuff because i
thought that would demand a logical when
chronological that that would amuse me and
it didn't it made me feel bad
and i cringed at myself i think
that sometimes watching old your stuff isn't
cringe makes watching tomb of these supposed
french sigh yeah and and so it
was it was well you also were
watching your old performer
yeah just home movie it was really
hard and then as i got into
more recent stuff where i was good
i was like oh yeah of course
it's a progression right right but i
was i was in a bad because
i was you know like depressed and
i was in a bad state where
i was like oh i've always been
before now i've overloaded eyes oh my
god i think i'm watching
stuff like that would just make you
think you suck yeah yeah that's exactly
what it did i was like no
listen this is i'm not good i
never was good yeah yeah i've always
i've always because it was a weird
thing where i thought i was like
better in these high school plays than
i was for some reason right yeah
and so when i watched it i'm
like oh no of course i'm terrible
like
you're fine in the clip that i
saw where you called her the wobbly
wholesale wobbly hips that was hilarious but
then it's no good she's having like
a sense of natural talent you a
natural talent and also you have guys
don't have to do shit that i'm
telling you my opinion i don't care
if you were looking for it you
got last doing something strange
no i just felt that you always
had like a a sense of maturity
about your performance that i even saw
in that carousel where i was like
this guy yeah that was the teacher
oh that's right
when they kiss the specific yeah no
i felt like you have like your
like refined clip okay yeah it was
sick you had a natural talent and
hadn't developed yet but i was like
oh wow this guy like obviously knows
what it means to be acting and
to be an artist and seems to
have influences that you know other kids
are just like yeah hello mister and
you
you seem to be grounded in anyway
say hello mister i was like okay
how you did it but then i
was watching like the you know my
my variety show my camargo thank you
tried to i tried to prevent you
from giving it
but i was watching you know me
doing stand-up and stuff and i'm like
oh man i forgot that i it's
been so long yeah that i forgot
that this was something that i really
enjoyed and was good at yeah so
that's a question though like so when
we go back to reality back to
life do you feel excited about getting
back
yes i do i da boy and
i feel more creative than i have
in a long time wow would you
stand up i want to do variety
shows again i loved doing it i
love doing exciting ways to do it
but i did a tasty maybe i
will mean i love for you to
do it in this backyard for us
only and it's like a private family
should be helicop
actors yeah what if i speaking of
which i watched a very funny special
comedy special netflix by napier gatsby oh
he's great where he did that's how
you say it yeah see my dad's
hey buddy i see and he did
it outside a universal studios yeah and
ah during the reality yeah so periodically
there's helicopters overhead and he's very funny
about them oh cool i want to
watch there's a new documentary that women
in comedy yes yes with bonnie mcfarlane
erik cole right yeah um and it
comes out tonight so it's already out
when you're listening to this i mean
we celebrate easter so of course we
know it's not no oh no i'm
planning to watch it this weekend i'm
excited
about that um but yeah i feel
you i'm like i can't imagine how
exciting i'll be to do a show
after all improv shows like just the
idea of being back at usb with
everyone just to mess around sounds so
fun yeah can you imagine the next
time that we do it show in
front of like twenty thousand people how
awesome that's
gonna be every time we ever done
i'm just assuming stuff that's positive thinking
oh my god you know what i'm
yeah next thing we could get twenty
thousand because everyone's so so bloody out
of here now but then everyone's gonna
be spending all their money on one
hundred different concerts and then we'll we'll
have nobody i think they just really
booming they'll always choose concerts over us
oh my god i would go to
a concert where a kind of concert
guys
guys don't dismiss that we love to
go to anything i really i really
want to go to a play i
really want to go i want to
go get but i wonder if you're
gonna wear a mask at the theater
for a long time because i also
like that i mean i would do
it but i get this like the
i like the energy of everyone will
see james yes i miss sometimes i
really when you said you cb
i miss running into people backstage me
too because it was my social life
yeah most probably ninety percent of it
was just the people i ran into
why were sweden we don't actually talk
to these people about real things
that is the thing i'm always saying
we have quite fun to just know
like you have like no you don't
have these deep relationships but you're seeing
people regularly we were like oh hey
yeah and it just feels like oh
i saw people tonight and then you
go home and you're like i have
a social life yeah i don't need
to go out i went with her
once i won't have a random conversation
then have a coffee with every
one once a week and that's all
your whole office opened up is very
social and so she would go out
and see your friends a lot in
ah and she'd be like how come
you don't like to go out and
see your friends all the time i'm
like well you know i'm i'm in
the studio doing so many podcasts and
we have these like ten minute conversations
before or after the show it feels
like i have a social life
yeah yeah so you'll see a lot
of people it it and i was
just having a whole conversation with someone
on facebook last listening about how like
you there's some fear i think i
have some fear about going back and
the expect social expectations right that coming
back that like and like moving at
the pace we used to mu
move where i don't know that i'm
ready for in terms of emotional you're
in terms of in terms of just
like busy-ness and like oh okay and
like yeah and emotional like friends you
haven't seen through a lot of the
pandemic and then you think you have
to like fix it or like makeup
philosophy where i feel pretty much everyone's
off the hook in my mind like
i don't know all bets are off
like if if
if if i was not your friend
beforehand let's strike up a friendship if
i was you just wanna go full
opposites yeah if i was i don't
want to see you again
i feel like i was talking to
someone about this the other day that
it was because a friend of mine
posted ah online ah something about how
if you if i have ah one
task to do you know during lockdown
i've one task to do that's my
whole yes it can choose me
and then after i do it i'm
exhausted yes right and i and it
it and how meanwhile kind of shea
when it feels in a day yeah
and i felt like it's i said
yes like the opposite of a fish
growing to the size of its bowl
is like you shrink down to what
your life is at the time and
it feels the same as it did
yeah i feel always just feel exhausting
kind
of just weirdly i will go on
like why did your frame of mind
right my thing lately is that i'm
like i will go for a walk
in a different neighborhood and then i
like just somewhere where i know there
aren't a lot of people out but
that i can have a pleasant walk
and look at some pretty houses and
then i'll get my car and kinda
like drive and just like see what's
going
hang on and like this feels like
i had a day like that so
i think yeah and then i'll look
at the people living their life like
it's normal and then i feel crazy
when i get back at my house
and you're like wow i drove in
pasadena and like everyone's having lunch outside
know there's definitely a bike was talking
to someone the other day who's like
oh yeah nothing changed for me um
i go into the office
it's every day he's like i'm the
only one here but ah yeah go
ahead yeah something did change for you
you're the only one there yeah yeah
and it's weird someone i guess so
yes it's up to me on twitter
like i posted something about a camera
when it was just about how strange
things feel and whatever and this guy
roy
wrote to me and said is it
really that different like yes i think
really is well made on my life
for some people they they don't have
the idea yes because he ability and
he described his life yeah and i
was like yeah not everybody has your
exact your exact life so it's like
well like i already worked from home
i blah blah
i can't be the only person you're
hearing this from the things that are
different i'm i'm a veteran zoom so
no nothing changed for me every day
georgia i hate that i know what
zoom is yeah i love it i
even know what the sound is but
you know what i think ignored you
know what i think about that this
was i was thinking about like when
we go back
i'm like i i would like to
suggest that times i don't feel like
if i'm gonna do someone's podcasts but
i don't really have all the time
in the world i could do it
on zoom yeah absolutely and then we
can make it easier on everyone or
like a general meeting like you would
normally have to drive our dropzone twenty
minutes or want to do that and
then drive home for an hour and
we'll
pitching is good on zoom i don't
like that i've the really i prefer
it to doing an in person i've
done so many just here
so if i know none of them
worked none of mine have either yeah
none of my day there because i
liked the noise but i was buying
but i think it's flat like i
think it's the sales flat i can't
make my like off the cuff jokes
because like i'm like dude anyway i
still make fun i'm great at it
but wow okay but i feel like
it's like people aren't even seeing my
face
you're looking at like whatever you've pulled
up on the screen and then it'll
just feels like yeah i think there's
a way to do it though that
you can maximize the the zoom experience
for the pitch you know what the
problem with my mind words the beginning
which i also the people i'm pitching
to are not figured people i'm pitching
to mute themselves so you don't get
a reaction if you ever
making off the off the cuff joke
like you make you make funny really
didn't work you make a funny joke
they feel like well that just fucking
fell flat and then because you look
people that laugh without smiling yes i
know you like oh but no ya
you have a deck up in the
main screen so you make a deck
is a is a document that shows
what your show you're talking sure
predicament by the way my shorts are
riding up like i'm an nba player
yeah eight years right now okay i'm
married
and i am as well
seeing it mary let's get to take
a break let's take a break and
get married alright bye get married everybody
and we're back so yeah i have
another surprise for you oh hell yeah
what do we got nothing oh okay
we just said we just celebrate april
fools a few weeks ago yeah so
i mean after more recently but yeah
more recently but we also
we just celebrated groundhog day ah a
few months ago are are you the
guy paul who hates april fools and
i was when when it was april
first the other day i was like
i think i remember paul talking about
how stupid you know when i've always
hated when people would post something on
april fool's day that's like awesome
i'm like i don't know it just
didn't do like i just got like
i remember someone doing like castillo's and
all i'm like april fool's day and
then everyone's like you guys and they're
like april fool's lazy sucks for you
that's a sad april fools i don't
know like my life essentially so like
we're engaged people and emily knew it
did i hate though yes that's like
so not funny it's only said to
the purse
listen i think yeah i don't like
the i don't like pranks general news
stories
oh that eilat know like come on
very being honest like paddington tweeted on
april fool's day it was like marmalade
anymore and i was not as what
i'm talking about that's cute but it's
speaking in pranks i sent you guys
the funniest prank i've seen in a
long time you did it was an
instagram story from gordon ramsay oh yeah
now
yeah his daughter pranked him so hard
it is so funny his daughter so
what is up and i watched vicious
oh i watched it slowly over so
that what you do is i would
bring scott over to my kitchen table
and i say now please watch i
want to do with this bible magic
magic magic trick of my bubble what
am i
put this egg into this bottle of
water with you know and then basically
what you do is you palm the
a home the tend to put it
in the person and there isn't to
the bottom looks into the bottle you
squeeze or social value squeeze the bottle
and then i would also show and
hugo let's all do it and then
lottery water washes her face and
you the one that used a machine
that ah ha yea on their head
and there's like what the fuck and
what makes it better as gordon ramsay
laughs like it's the funniest thing like
he has like he has no choice
like no really no no no i
mean i mean in a good way
like you really fuckin got me yeah
yeah gives it up yeah and he
gives it on he he doesn't get
like oh
oh god i'm gonna get you but
you know how some donkey don't care
i do feel like you know how
some people when you pull a prank
on him they then have to status
you and be like oh i'm going
to get you or i'm gonna man
yeah like like i'm going to prove
that i still am higher status and
accept your she was he was laughing
he must really love his daughter he
i was laughing so hard at it
we think in my family we used
to do april fools prank some remembering
now and really yeah and there was
one that my mom did to my
grandpa where she puts surrender upon the
toilet and then the p o j
when he goes simply where does the
duke ego will hopefully you see it
if you're gonna go ducky
i also feel it what if you
have diarrhea like do you play ya
if you call grandma that and go
okay you did this you clean it
up i'll see you guys later that
would be so exciting that's what i'm
saying is you would say that i'll
see you guys later you sit on
the toilet you don't scrap your diarrhea
spills all over the sides
i can't remember what song i was
thinking you hated so much is never
good
oog was lyric everyone was ever gonna
ooh yeah yeah i've never gone to
pool but but ah now i thought
it was um never gone up uga
never go to u-boot why does he
bring up john mayer
in the last time yeah that was
a concert i wanted to go to
o ry y went to see dispatch
but i really wanted to see john
mature would you tell me the truth
john mayer he loves the ladies from
what i've been told yeah by us
weekly not by anyone chosen i know
i heard he's kind of kkk
a dick i saw he was on
ryan he do they're just friends so
or if it had said if he
before before you know anyone
i like it even meet a lot
of people say you're unattached you're here
in l a when i have had
sex with john mayer if he asks
you out would you have gone to
marry him i would absolutely have gone
out john mayer yeah yeah what am
i insane
is it i saw him the other
day he's got a real johnny depp
thing he's rotter and johnny gang i
mean johnny's friends with a friend of
mine i actually mean like saw him
yes he is like that was what
he meant with him but i did
not i couldn't bring myself to talk
to him because i was like
i'm so it's not that it's still
not the right way to meet you
know it's like i can just go
approaching him because he's john mayer yeah
like hey you're john mayer i i
don't feel any of the same thing
now i'm mean obviously that was twenty
years ago that i was like whatever
but i still like his music did
you did you move to l a
in hopes of meeting him
you know what i think you know
what i have thought it is weird
when you and i'm sure you have
this about people where you like new
so you know he was famous before
i could ever have met him in
my life and so i have known
of him for a long time and
then suddenly you're just in the same
room as them and you're like oh
so i could have actually ended up
marrying him like
be like like if a you know
we have mutual friends like oh yeah
and he then it's like that's a
crazy thing when like he were to
date an asshole once me if you
like lower standards one obviously he's like
jennifer aniston's i'm not saying that but
i'm just saying you could meet the
person you could have a connection yeah
that is possible it's na
not just an insane because when i
was in high school i thought i
could marry him is my point right
and then it's like you get to
a place where like i actually have
met this person enough times that not
not even about him i mean like
early could've yeah got marry yeah okay
just to have people like that i
just heard what i was doing best
week of or that we were doing
this
there was some story about jennifer aniston
today introduced too much to jennifer aniston
the world's saddest woman oh my we
was so finally so insane how magazines
have how like tabloids have spun her
life and like she's a thriving l
ty yeah
yeah i can't it is funny somebody
pointed out how dry she is she
does these commercials she needs water lotion
her eyes are dry she eyes go
don't jump in the ocean go jump
in the ocean you know what you
i'm realizing that like i'm listening to
smart list which i've mentioned on this
show and they mentioned her a lot
as a casual friend like oh we're
at jen's house oh and then i'm
like okay then i saw that what's
his name justin or jason bateman was
at her home
lm for the whenever award chinese are
golden globes yeah yeah yeah one of
those he was at her house to
do his zoom presenting or whatever and
i was like why is he at
her house he was a nice house
i'm sure but then that they're all
hanging out together all close friends so
then i'm just very curious about the
friends circle with everyone going to jennifer
and
this is house for parties all the
time maybe they'll have kids who are
in the same pod but she doesn't
have kids well that adds a wrinkle
to it that's kind of what i'm
saying like she just having people over
and i think it sounds fun but
i'm just i allowed we get in
there like the three of us are
cool right yeah we're awesome so why
don't we go over to aniston's house
we're great we're gr
great i i i that does not
seem like a group that i would
want to hang out with oh my
god what i don't know i i
disagree i i do want to thank
goodness i think you really do i
think you really do who you know
who's the funniest his will or not
i have not known this i use
have i used to have a really
good time i used to sit next
to one for the bojack table reads
oh yeah you worked with him and
we had very um like ah bad
kids in class energy i loved that
we had it was fun i really
he has the funniest like degs like
i just i the one day i
have not known him for anything the
one day he was on bang bang
came on and just is like funny
one hundred percent of the time off
stage as well you know it's the
same wow feral where like yeah i
got on a phone call about the
ferns movie with him and like he
and zach is real when you're talking
yeah on the phone will ferrell doing
the most hilarious bits
for a half an hour on a
phone call while still doing business like
still think zach is funny when he's
being normal yeah yeah but that sounds
like a curse i think when you're
luckily funny it's so crazy it is
it's so crazy to me to see
someone like our netter whoever who is
just like that funny for that long
you know like amount mom times to
help catch me off guard on that
podcast and i'm like i'm so surprised
i just but i'm like i clearly
have been in the dark on him
because i don't watch all his stuff
but i'm like oh i can see
how he and amy poehler were
great matt oh are a time for
a time she must lose who would
you like to be friends with she
must thought it was funny what celebrity
do you want to be friends with
dame judi dench darla will be fun
that would be fun jersey tea with
the dames ah t rex with who
oh my god no i never said
that but i did i want to
see nobody's claiming t anything out the
games are dame judi dench dame eileen
atkinson they maggie smith and dame joan
plowright and they are all actors they
are long-lived people they sit around and
they fucking tell stories and it is
great but see this is the thing
about
what about celebrities that you want to
be friends with or whatever you really
don't know what metal poles are like
at all yes and like i think
there's people that i've worked with where
i ended up being their friend and
i'm so surprised none of those people
that i think i'd be friends with
who i just don't have a vibe
with that yeah i will say that
older actors are fun to hang out
with you
yeah and if you can add alcohol
to that it's even better yeah like
when they tell stories about theatre pizza
i love theater p yeah when they
start telling stories it's really fun yeah
movie people who have not done theater
are not as fun i think that's
it yeah yeah
yeah i also think when people are
it's harder when they're just right there's
an actor who would never had to
do comedy because i feel like coming
up in that way you like half
to um be personable in a certain
way yeah and some actors are in
their own world so much that you
just they really are amazing on
screen and when you're working in the
scene they're amazing and then off they're
kind of like not giving you anything
you are and who do you wish
your friends within the babysitting world
are there any famous babysitters oh the
babysitters oh what i did see though
jessica st clair posted her babysitter who
i am acquaintances with only on instagram
um sydney steinberg i don't i want
to shoot everybody on comedy bang bang
because she's so funny um i don't
know her personally we just like follow
each other because mike no
as them but i she is jessica's
nanny and she was like she dressed
up as the easter pig to go
you like the eastern pig or something
like show up the other day for
work with like a pig snout and
be really funny and i was like
that's the best i love that i
think that's so funny and so fun
and like just the kind of thing
i
kid would really remember absolutely i just
thought that was sweet sweet and i
i just think when you hire a
babysitter if you can get someone who's
like fucking hilarious that's like amazing who's
the most famous babysitter of all time
nanny mcphee probably mary poppins yeah yeah
you gotta give it up to pop-in
nanny mcphee is just an ugly mary
poppins right yeah i think so uglier
yeah that's shifted it for me
and be friends with scott
um i would say ok read like
on a real level yeah i can
i say that for like the idea
of being friends with them is impossible
to sort of and i don't mean
that you liked it like if you
go to a dinner pie yeah i
haven't i haven't even committed to mine
i'm wish i actually i liked that
pod when i was gonna say so
someone i was going to take it
the other way to nail you down
i'm not trying to befriend anybody i
was going to take to the other
way of like all the people whose
side you are the enemies with cycled
through the bang bang couch of like
who is a famous person that i
was like wow this person and i
feel like i like the spirits i
like this person
genuinely where i was like if i
ever hung out with this person going
to be so i would be friends
with them and it was paul f
tompkins wow and it worked oh no
i think like seth rogen i was
like wow this guy is so cool
yeah i do this all the time
it's like so cool i if i
ever see him it's like hey how's
it going but we're not friends or
whatever but i was like this guy's
really
nice fairly normal yeah very normal guy
was just like i'm also extremely interested
in his weed line ah yeah i'm
interested in doing something do it was
smiling in the north and we restored
it i do want him to send
me some seth send us some weed
to send some weed we'll talk about
crop that's proud about eminem's and your
weed
the products are so nice looking and
i thought it was fun now he
made this line because he was like
people who smoke we don't get anything
cool like people who drink alcohol like
there's so many accessories if you drink
alcohol it's true and what are the
accessories when you drink alcohol you mean
like yeah i like pretty glasses and
ice giant mirrors and like yes true
like when you buy pot it's
not in a big like glass skull
my favorite but there are more crystal
skull logo looking like pretty like sort
of like subscription boxes and things like
that but his stuff is like looks
cool on your table the descent of
your head folks is i know i
know i had bones are slowly leaving
my body oh like you're
talking on an old phone
wow have you seen seth rogen weed
litres
they're on the size of a table
i've said this before that's the one
thing i miss about smoking is the
accessories i used to have all that
shit yeah i'd fancy lighters i had
cigarette cases i had nice ashtrays yeah
yeah he made cool astros while he
makes pottery how cool zara has my
pottery they're all based on his designs
i think that's i think ish
i'll be selling his pottery and little
boutiques around la and out would buy
it so i've come on three to
and talk about your creepy
a seven i never had to guess
somebody told me once oh we don't
wanna talk about a guy give us
stuff it's not because it's you we
just want to weed potter riga we
will take any illness role
yeah my friends with yeah paul romans
dirty friend who me yeah i've i
know i'm no paul yeah i went
on an edition once where he was
there was a bunch of leslie jordan
was there it was quite a collection
of be interesting and it was like
a lot of the albums it was
like it was like you were again
you're going for the same role yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's interesting for you
remember carol burnett was gonna do a
sitcom mcnary was on it
yeah i know i went to the
base she got cash first and i
was like this would be a dream
if i got no um it was
so fun to see how i cried
at the taping because it was such
a wonderful because carol burnett came out
and it was fucking amazing she pulled
mary mary was on the stage with
her and i was like this is
so cool i got to see a
friend of mine used to work on
watch what happens live and i happened
to be in new york when scroll
when um carol burnett was going to
be on and my friend said do
you want to come to the
taping because a lot of people don't
know that there is a secret little
audience at that show right at the
carol burnett show no watch what happens
live oh yeah so carol burnett was
the guest and they have to be
so quiet i did i was also
a guest so much happens live just
for the record i have never been
fabulous i've never done anything of note
while you aren't really into reality we
get up uh
homes ma'am we do yeah
you and i so i was very
happy to help you better it was
very exciting to see carol burnett and
when my friend knew that carbon meant
a lot to me and to watch
her be interviewed like so god so
cool but then andy cohen's fuckin dog
bit bitter oh i think i remember
that those big thing i think they
showed it
he's got his dumb dog water and
now i know they they i think
he got rid of that dog hope
you got rid of he passed it
on to another ag paid it forward
homed to a because he had a
baby and then it was like this
dog is unpredictable than the baby bib
carol burnett yeah well that was it
was cute but it did did break
the skin but you know that carol
burnett show didn't get picked up and
i was like
what do you people want i know
did you see everyone in america wants
to carol burnett again and she's being
funny do you see the carol burnett
the documentary about the the play she
was in it's really fascinating this sounds
familiar i haven't seen a documentary maybe
i remember hearing about this so she's
it she's cast in this play and
she's
like cast and a documentary about putting
this play up on it's feet and
the cast carol burnett because she's a
name but as i recall the movie
the producers never really liked carol burnett
never really on earth never like only
caster because she was a name and
was kind of resistant to i'm honestly
confused i feel like i read about
this
something wouldn't let her do like things
she wanted to do in the play
and stuff like that but then open
and they're they're treating her like shit
i think yeah and then opening night
the power goes out in the play
and they're light and the producers are
like what do we do what do
we do and they say carol will
you go out and entertain
stain them my guy and she goes
out and basically just fields questions for
an hour whichever i thought was better
than the pl yes waiting for the
waiting for the the lights to come
back on and everyone and she's like
saves the whole experience and they're like
carol thank you so much and it's
just like you are treating her like
you can believe
leave someone before they're like shit i
just think like she's not even known
for being like a mean person or
anything no you know she was totally
nice and kind of like well i'm
dating guys they looked down on her
because yeah it wasn't from the theater
yeah that's disturbing you're like oh we
have to cast this name or what
and yeah guess who isn't once upon
a mattress yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah so yeah she's like totally
theatrical wish i could remember what that
was called i'll look it up during
the break but it's a really it's
a really fascinating movie if you're interested
in like putting together you know theater
types of movies i don't know what
types of movies zahra how you living
together opsi tourney i guess if you
look to put together theater types of
movies
yeah wish they would put together one
for spiderman turn off the dark oh
that would be amazing i would love
to do a fictional movie i would
not of that story spider-man turn off
the dark but of the omega yeah
we love an oral history of that
oh there is a book that the
co-writer wrote or burwell it's fascinating and
he spills the entire t
to a point where i'm like oh
this guy's so full these guys yeah
it is in chai or tea i
was like this guy's ruined his career
essentially yes that sounds like a mystery
it's anybody that's ruining their career with
a book you gotta read that book
of getting back we gotta take a
break will be good book
alright everyone we're back and it's downtime
for what we call three church this
is part of the show where we
do a game this was submitted by
agc you're patronizing my little mostar and
marvelous it's called
it's called one noise impression one no
noise russian impressions players take turns making
one noise or sound and the other
players have to guess who or what
they're imitating so not even words yeah
who were what i mean it's like
my knife i'm on a piano or
just like you know
no well like let's come up with
an example okay is there an example
it's like no but if i was
like if you're gonna send us three
cheers list and exam got all our
hands we're done we're dumb b ball
i was like
a bird no
we're playing now but only hall o
ah it's funny thank you ah okay
now you gotta do another noise because
we both
roger rabbit no
ah who played roger rabbit charlie charlie
sure to frame oh who framed
wow
it's roger rabbit jennifer garner jennifer aniston
know jennifer connelly no jennifer's no jennifer
none taken it is scott was close
to this first guess ah who did
i guess it was i don't even
remember i remember either ca
ah damn ah you went oh i
said a bird yeah ah struck know
a famous bird wow
chilly willy the penguin no bird no
it's not a bird little white museum
is called but that's and jennifer connelly
you're close but it's not a bird
elmo
someone with a bird name no tweet
quackenbush
retired
elephant yes just an elephant yes it
could be anything and you make an
elephant sound because i was doing a
sound and it was just that was
what it was this is this is
not good oh please go back to
riot no i don't i think we
say we only ran like to come
in and narrow the parameters
it should be fast the person let
me do it again and it's ok
mrs amos burton famous gave up so
fast famous person right okay
yeah randy
here's a famous person
so is it okay
yeah peter falk now
she by the way stanley tucci physically
yeah
a robert de niro now owe a
little mouth
it's this passivity like a little puppet
mouth yeah um
i gotta say yeah can i say
a hint yeah he's not a man
whoa you know because that would go
on for ever do it again
yay
this is not good yes
wow okay this person is currently on
television on nbc and it's a wine
willie
ah you do what i want to
get captured the face on video okay
you zoomed in yeah
yeah yeah so go to r go
to r huh
on you say and swat you're doing
this face come on so she's on
nbc currently yes on a drama or
on a comedy
with someone we know she's i don't
watch network television like ah i'm not
aware of what's on television anymore alright
show she's on yeah yeah mr mayor
i don't know anyone on that show
other than bobby moynihan do you know
him some saying it was she was
on a show that with someone we
know who is bobby oh and this
person is not
but someone we know she was on
s n l yeah with no with
ah well what she was on mr
bear i'm saying you were like what's
shown i was like to show on
nbc with someone we know bobby mr
mayor that's the show she's on it
she's on it well i don't know
who's mister mayor well it wouldn't narrow
it down significantly if you did true
i wouldn't argue with
that what about mayor macias was a
lot of films she was in a
lot of movies especially matrix and ninety
s sigourney no but you're on the
writer ne ah piper laurie she's in
she's in a lot of stuff people
love actually one last dorothy dandridge she
won an oscar her or she didn't
make a noise oh marley harley oh
no oh yeah oh holly hunter yeah
i get the face thank you i
get things like because she's like yeah
yeah me now
someone else go is this fun it
is it actually is playing ok good
actually right alright paul do you want
to go no you go okay ah
let me think of someone ah um
now i'm only thinking of people that
people do famous impressions of yeah okay
ah ok got it
oh
ah then still oh no the rock
you don't get another guest robert de
niro know you're famous for just you
just keep going they know because i
want to know the rock let me
try to do the rock what noise
you want me to make oh no
this person i guess beep beep okay
here we go
beep
alec baldwin yes ah okay oh alright
it was but was it the physicality
of it the physicality really helped i
gotta say okay great beep alright i
have one give me give me the
noise ah poof poof
yeah
a poof christopher walken um
bruce
dern
interesting
i like that guess yeah that's a
good guess thank you say okay now
say zoom
zoom
i haven't i'm enjoying it i have
no idea it's weirdly fun ah zoo
a harvey cartel hoof
are you on television or film television
and some film mostly television
are you on like c s i
know have you ever said poof in
real life i think i am rosana
csci at one point oh okay
not david caruso zoo
ted danson yes oh you're also mister
mayor that's right with bobby to manali
hunter and ali we do know men
okay give me a word um how
about yeah dang
what's a place
ding
okay sure to cover glasses put them
on her forehead and she's nodding up
and down thing looks like a guy
to me is that right no it's
a girl dinging bing um yeah they
have done this jennifer aniston
being low
this is good but i don't know
what does that is just fun to
listen to someone saying ding
fun word it is i like it
yeah thing thing is it a reality
where there were no okay is it
television person alright how about a word
boom
courtney cox arquette no boom there she
was
boom boom um is it the nanny
no
um
i don't know i feel like we're
also know this person
i know that in life personally yeah
holy shit chelsea peretti know giving you
my word who do i even know
um how about whoop like whoop there
it is whoop
it's very specific yeah it is your
problem is for the listener the physicality
is is very key to these very
yeah it doesn't help at all
p doesn't what key it doesn't help
at all yes no it does help
i think the physicality helps better but
it doesn't have the listener that's problem
we're just hearing you say whoop and
man okay this person has had a
television show
that's awesome and we know him personally
yeah they are they're lucky a comedian
sarah silverman yes o k now does
it make sense that we now does
yet mixing show ya can we say
we'll do something like woke you know
maybe something like while you sell all
i'm talking around the noise yeah like
yeah i don't think that really is
how the game works well i gotta
get into it i got a ramp
into it well that's illegal that's illegal
it's only got a ramp into it
hey it time is it
ah mine okay let me think of
a purse and ah okay give me
a noise
click
how quick
ah so you're kind of like surprise
huh
surprise smiling okay i'm diggin click
huh are you guys so happy about
click
are you man or woman man man
man lee man i'm all mad what
they represent matt say bazooka bazooka
um oh my god who are you
we know that we know him jon
hamm know jon hamm would be zynga
yeah when he's been comedy he'd be
like zynga
using jack mcbrayer no that would be
belinda
you know the pool
hopefully i was for somebody just jump
in why don't you do it because
you don't wants to final episode will
all jump it okay give me another
noise
um clank
hey clank who gets warming into it
i know i know why doing more
physicality who is this ah your man
you have a tv show ah no
on i'm on tv shows i don't
have my own tv show and you
are um so when we know yes
are you currently on tv yes
do it again adam powley close give
me another noise jesus just do the
last nigeria
jesus no that sounds like dodgeville till
jack woods no
jesus i don't know i can't do
things paul you're very close with one
of those words soul rest not that
paul paul rudd not that paul paul
lynde not that ah that paul another
paw
it's not me you know paul's
hey hey guys
quick paul photos here yeah i'll share
oh my god it goes quick i
can see it now everyone click i
can see it now or it can
a nice um bop
bop
that's bitch it sounds like patino but
it's not it's not your bob garland
no
the guesses are the funniest part yeah
bop bop
ooh could this be i don't know
bop no that's not no discount that
one okay but no no strike that
mop
yeah okay so you're like ah you're
like ah your live yes very much
so you on tv right now
no i don't think right now have
you ever said bop probably are you
an older man no oh okay judy
young okay bop
bop bop so you're a young man
who goes who has a gravelly voice
who said bop what does it say
buh known for saying bop but it
says it all the time it's
according to you i misunderstood the point
of this game hey same buffalo's people
for saying these noises saying another chasing
another noise say say guanglie yeah that's
a noise everyone's heard what is it
a galley
quali
who is that is it vinnie chase
no it's not a fictitious person it's
person turtle sorry
sorry to move in each state review
turtles very real to injury to those
very real working i went to turtle
ones for him or with him with
him he also was auditioning you jim
roam together you know we arrived at
the same time and waited and then
audition separately interesting give me another noise
points piss oink
yes owing owing piss i like this
he won't do it like piss i
don't like i'm going insane is it
is it ringing any bells at all
i settled yeah probably but give us
a hint
ah if someone you know
oh my gram link this
this is so quick like piss on
inc pay who do i know who
do we know who says wings
this is like this and look through
your phone's video little again let me
look at the numbers i bet you
do it's not monsoons is it yes
it is wow okay link piss yeah
come on yes yeah i thought that
was the key yeah yeah yes
yeah that's good okay that was good
wow we did it guys done it
really more i hope you enjoy us
saying oink piss and boop
hope you enjoyed click
thanks for listening everybody you're listening we
did it again wow he's doing okay
now that things are maybe there's light
at the end of the tunnel enjoy
the rest of your thursday to you
know what yes you enjoy the rest
of your thursday and and hell if
you're listening this on a friday t
g i
f yeah but gmo as well fuck
d j f and g dfo o
m a f huh abc started a
gta fo night they should
they should gts foe what are you
doing laura now you are i'm genuinely
yeah as the headphones up to yours
got a weird helmet on i'm just
i can't take it anymore i'm gonna
you want to say one last thing
to the fan i need you
see you next week
a