three
yeah
oh that's perilously close to the tomahawk
no it's not here's what it is
okay what it's it's the famous foot
football chant oh
oh hey but a chop is don't
do it oh god i don't want
to but i got i wanna go
to show you how close it is
i wish the melody it's like that
could be put on a graph like
where he's saying there's just like mum
dad nan name and name new exam
david italy you're not they're not as
close as you think i know
no the believe me i know the
ability of the time ah joe why
don't why don't the tomahawk chop people
just switch over to what you're doing
yeah or what did they go to
hell could be you know what kind
i hope there's a hell i don't
hope there's a heaven but i hope
there's a hell i and we're fine
with that i'd be fine with like
if you're a decent person you die
nothing happens your
bad you go to hell and you're
tortured forever and who decides who decides
sir who sir who benefits ah
the latin que e bodo creek
cute lily what a bano changed his
name to that you know hi i'm
cute
who is q thank you and on
took this letter from the alphabet and
i'm gonna steal it back
i'd respect that a lot
that's what it would take for you
to respect money i would respect his
actions but i wouldn't respect the man
respect the actions if not the man's
every stray you respect the office of
bano if not the man loosely
yeah is there anybody who you respect
as a as an artist but don't
respect our art ah that seems impact
huh you can respect them as an
artist you respect as a person yeah
like there's people that you think are
nice people yeah man probably like beating
up somebody you know yeah and i
go like also you know and i'm
not too fond of whatever they did
but like missing great yeah i hope
are happy what i like is when
you absolutely cannot respect them either way
i love that because it's so free
yeah ever have to think about them
ever again yeah and you never will
i welcome three of my paul speaking
not respecting anyone from both sides i'm
scott
yeah and so about me but my
name is laura nice to meet ya
doesn't matter i don't care to him
yeah who are you my name is
lauren and you're here to say i
love to wrap it a whole new
way
which way will rhyming way anyway but
just naturally i will say my raps
as flowing through me
this is three um and if you've
listened to the show for the past
couple of weeks there's been a plot
point that we need to resolve and
i think we need to do it
on on lawrence topics but i'm not
sure what it is yeah yeah there
should we do it on lord yeah
sure i guess i mean the drain
to just put my topic except for
whatever this topic
is i don't oh really you want
to protect lawrence topics if the topics
are pretty i think that's fair when
i know what you don't know what
that you need to carry it curates
the topics well it's a nice topic
but we have so many things on
lauren's topic there's things that pertain to
i me my slower on the one
announcing them now i'm sorry do you
wanna speak i want to do scott
regarding no one wants you to do
stuff regarding you yeah regarding your ankle
yeah okay what's up this is your
topic gods moment no i want to
do it lawrence topic oh so popular
and it's the same recall scott bad
body i have other i have other
topics to bring lawrence topics this time
the skyfall come on it's nose yeah
it's called scott's moment reached down give
a hand up to a struggling writer
outmoded you're outvoted god's mo i'm always
gonna be voted on the show is
it's coming in as quickly as it
lee i think it's going to be
scott bad i gotta be quick about
it scott yeah it's it's you think
it should be that because you thought
of it using yeah johnny man yeah
well
cause this isn't a moment this is
going on forever right i haven't even
started got to our let's hear it
to ask for the scott hour what
happened to your ankle all right wow
everyone relax last time next year phone
light a fire beat your dog with
newspaper because it's time for just the
scott
our alright last time on the show
i talked about how i twisted my
ankle and then i hit it a
couple of times during the show and
said oh you did
when you hit it during the show
you are really in pain yeah and
it was a little scary yeah that's
kinda like well whatever i was was
so bad i wasn't scared i was
really scared i hated under the table
inside of closet
instead of a closet
and you put sweaters in front of
you and then i made a fort
and then i played i saw your
i saw your shoes and then i
hit it a bunch of stuffed animals
yeah and then when you look at
me i made the face yeah the
eighties
that they are yeah and the extra
dress right to eat
d t too funny o e g
two should be done that he too
should be barbara zoo was that title
comedian yeah he's the guy that does
the songs you have the piano with
the the the stars on it so
much somebody please photoshop photoshop the e
t two posters and i recently learned
it was a brito not at
is that right ah it depends on
how you pronounce it
eight to remember don't sit correctly eight
two not eight e at two it's
like et tu h a lee hae
a toubro a o find out in
any case son was at two voted
high at two like i hit two
i know that in
in italiano and is a it to
the letter e i mean if you
wanted we are looking at how to
oh my god
mary holland i emperor you seesaw when
he realised what he saw on brutus
his son betrayed okay he said soft
meaning his song buddha to british ye
to also did you say julio so
why are we it to brew tay
to boost
it is absolute all new today so
who told me this and then and
then i'm looking down here it says
in french it's it so i think
somebody thought that was a french phrase
dumb but it's probably last person's stupid
it is latin of course yeah it's
from latin times but so so i
gotta figure who told me that
like they were on video motion yes
and like i saw ago and i
saw by the way this this whole
time i'm saying that i saw my
ex you were like think about about
you his tweet hundred thousand likes right
eye has taken off we will go
on a holy shit we start tweeting
each other all the time yeah i've
got to get that number i guess
that
i can't describe what the tweet was
basically saying i'm out of social media
time today i've already used it okay
but let me let me paraphrase yeah
that you came to him and said
by the way i read i read
reading i read something today today and
it was dumb about a bundle anyways
i told you that
hey like i guess you read that
yeah and so he tweeted about it
and the people are loving love it
because it's a little slice of like
inner personal dynamics that happens all the
time yeah it's great anyway so universal
i feel like it's the kind of
thing that will get stolen right somebody
will claim it as it'll be it'll
end up being honest to come soon
and he won't
be cast in it he'll audition and
it'll break yeah and he'll be like
i actually the tweet this line that
i'm supposed to the character supposed to
say is based on my tweet logo
honey hundred days works bay one hundred
and eighteen thousand likes yeah he's taking
off and i just retweeted so we
did a dance this morning screaming what
fame is
theme this house's money started raining yeah
see money did come out of this
thing yeah every house has money in
the ceiling if you get a tweet
that goes viral yeah yeah there you
can't there's it's look you can't jigger
the law yeah yeah you can unlock
it for the money to rain down
just by yourself in any case i
broke my ankle okay so
scott's moment because you thought it was
a sprain of some kind thought it
was a sprain you kind of just
you you actually joking i was walking
around for six days the next morning
after this show i was like i'm
gonna go into the doctor ah went
in it's a tiny stays with that
i would say is pretty intense it
was okay it doesn't hurt to be
big deal to me oh yeah i
guess if i broke a bone yeah
let it hang i'd be fine yeah
also it's a tiny like sticking out
of my arm which is what i
said to cool up it's a tiny
bow also it's dynamo and that's what
she said as she had to call
up as she said to you when
you saw it that's what i said
to her
so i'm in ah i'm in a
boot for a couple of weeks look
by the time this comes out will
be on tour hopefully i'm out of
the boot by the time i'm ready
what a curse you have on your
ankle that you know give a boot
i did a whole tour in a
boot yeah it's sad i didn't a
walking boot and it was gross it
was gross and nursing when i got
back my my foot doctor said
what's a fucker you doing you could
have permanently damaged your foot because i
just was in the boot that they
gave me in chicago and that i
just completed the doctor actually say the
f word
yeah i would be thrilled if my
doctor curse like that yeah it would
be good yeah yeah look it's fuckin
like can i tell you a document
fucking candy this is all fucked up
yeah your bones are fucked up dude
i went to my ophthalmologist the other
day yeah because i have um i
have a thing where ah the pigment
in my eye your eyes bulge outward
so you're thirty mileage yeah my my
tongue is also an issue symbologist is
a doctor eyes dear but not optometric
no optometrist that's more vision up some
geologists more the inner working the eye
yeah exactly and they take a picture
of your eye looks like a foreign
panel plant yeah my optometrist just so
you know yeah mine too so do
they cover both but all they could
maybe because i went that the same
frame when they do that when your
optometrist does it they say
if you gotta go to an optimal
ah this may all we can do
is look at it and say it's
fucked up gotta see your optometrist when
i can't even help you dear you
must to get up so yeah jen
and often does the same test are
they just look at the actual because
those costs money you know they do
oh yes i do always ask when
i'm in there they're like
do you want to pay the extra
one hundred and fifty for this test
that you really should have they literally
make me yeah it's me down and
they say we're gonna putting my ophthalmologist
grabs me by the ankles turns me
upside down and shakes the money out
of me yeah i always have to
get dilated and actually first it's so
moths out well i was i had
to die
related recently when when i do wanna
hear a story i'm just driven china
oh really it's really dilate you know
you were dilated you how much animators
oh hey yeah yeah i don't even
get me started on that i started
well you already are you bowls and
um had to drive and go somewhere
and go to a bunch i tell
you you can't drive i thought you
said i could but
i had to wear these little ah
plastic glove i love those makes me
laugh so much and now checking my
phone and i couldn't even see while
you're driving oh no
citation because i was out of gas
am know with the prices of gas
these days i can't even pay for
the doctor but i couldn't even see
me it was interesting because i never
tried to look at a phone while
my eyes were dilated and it was
like i couldn't even see what was
on the you couldn't even recognize it
as a foe wait this is my
cat i was yeah i was that
i'm scary to me i could see
everything driving wise there was no issue
with that it was one of the
highway cars yeah sorry i was careful
and i they told me i was
fine i had to drive home from
the foot doctor by the way and
they put me in this boot what
what is it it's the right foot
your gas one your gas yeah the
one that you yes you get the
boot in there and then you it
that's the thing right so so they're
putting the boot on me and i'm
like i think this figures into the
story
i was like can i drive and
the the the first person who was
lower by the way i saw probably
ten ten layers of types of doctors
from the very top of the person
who i came to see why didn't
someone else and then you have like
someone under then there was obviously a
hierarchy of like ten people so the
lowest of the low
no person is putting on the boot
you have some vi p foot that
i am not aware of not the
same voice of the lo i'm just
saying like you go on doing what
i hope they don't listen i'm just
saying when you go in like a
blacks when you go in you're use
to light your wiggle a horse talking
to someone who's lower than the doctor
yeah i'm the doctor and then you
say let me see your map them
as being lower there were obviously like
there were people shadowing people there were
are you saying oh i hate that
there were the people who were like
obviously only in charge of doing the
menial tat yeah but i said there
were so many people who came in
some people just came in looked in
on my room and went huh and
then like pop their head back out
early going toward the office or they
maybe they were told there was a
really
weird man
i hate when you're like you're the
doctors brings a guy is like look
at this freak yeah and then they
just go just go in and look
at potential for something else so i'll
have to awesome wait what about the
conclusion of my story well no we
just either inception didn't know so to
answer the question of how did i
drive so she's putting fifty she's putting
the boot on me and i go
so
how can i drive with this she
goes yeah it's a pit anytime you
drive you have to take it off
it's a pain and i said oh
okay and then the next guy who's
a higher up than her comes into
like make sure it's all done correctly
and i go so i she said
i could drive with this and goes
no yeah because this is like a
cast keep it on don't drive so
but i had to drive home fours
and it was in santa monica so
i just was you know i was
done with that stories because you told
me the other day oh rye but
lauren hadn't heard i legit hanging queen
yeah this is lauren hadn't her i
was done and yet but it wasn't
where it was going i started with
this goodbye oh my god
so you just put your shoes back
on and pretend you hadn't been to
the doctor then you got home while
i did it barefoot but yeah i
won't go chicks that's the worst thing
and i'll do hillbilly well you're not
supposed to drive barefoot know i know
like tony smith said i could tell
that way
i've i've done
yeah i'm gonna have a hook having
to have both theater yeah with the
c yeah yeah that was lovely it
was beautiful whenever i've had to like
move my car from the street into
the driveway and i'm just like i
don't know she's gonna just go around
and do it was that just keep
it to the driver i can't because
sometimes i have to let my wife
out of there no don't let her
the garage yeah yeah yeah i keep
it blocked that sometimes like oh she's
gonna blow and i got a letter
out um but i'll get out i'll
get go walk out of the house
with my bare feet and get in
the car and it feels so weird
it doesn't feel right so i started
when you put your feet on the
gas yeah it doesn't feel good i
wonder if the first came in put
their feet in the fire and were
like oh ouch ouch that and then
they're like let's spread the word through
images on the walls the feet the
feet do not belong in fire they
invented the circle with the line through
it yeah there's i'm not the op
though and yeah my regular op though
is not there oh no and so
it's ah
it's a young woman dr rowan beneath
will know an associate okay fine i
don't know students well maybe his name
is on the door but i would
say this is the lowest of the
low but she's a doctor she's probably
second tier shell ranked me so like
work when i say she's associate but
her name's not on the door she's
second tier she's like in charge
rj well i'm your regular doctor he
sure is a way of course yeah
yeah but this doctor was
oh the old riddle and so ah
she is first she she tells me
like she does all the tests everything
my ah oh so the problem that
i have is the pigment or my
i ah like breaks off excuse and
rubs against part of my eye and
it causes pressure and that can lead
to glaucoma but what does that mean
the pigment of your eye
it literally means like the part that
makes the color whoa which is not
what i see when i look at
you it's something within the eye would
you trade all that you're not seeing
like little pieces of brown brick all
i was worried about would you like
a word about would you say get
rid of the pigment all have clear
eyes
clear eyes remember devil horse he oh
yeah he's like glarus he was clear
eyes was the drop oh god you
know a booming career at a later
age yeah now he's done whereas he
is that part of lawrence topics yeah
that is one of the things that
i can't get you on our side
was talking about ben flying routes pt
trivia from lawrence top i wanted to
go in depth on his career but
i'll do it in topics oh can
still feel good of you to wait
then sends money of course ferris bueller's
day off clearest commercial opportunity to come
oh he was one of the writers
in um soap dish she's in the
soma writing room and yes you'll find
him in all sorts of films back
then
feeling all sorts of interesting role it's
true but he made a living out
of being
low key you know and he was
the first to say low key high
key and then who else made a
living out of loki tom hiddleston like
you're from graduations to him and your
fiance and of course you know yeah
uzi louie i saw them on broadway
i can't remember her name but she
was it was her and daredevil and
and him
him and then that was the way
in betrayal where they all playing he
was playing loki there was daredevil and
then her daredevil from the netflix show
yeah yeah chuck ah charlie cox charlie
cox yeah okay so then what had
proud my pressure's good but she said
you need um your eyes are dry
so i'm gonna give you some artifice
actual tears and i'm like one of
my jennifer aniston yeah and then she
told me that i have to clean
my eyelids oh with whoa with wipes
there's visual wiser i lay outside of
your iowa yes oh hell yes but
the inside oh you mustn't try to
clean let's see outside of your eye
understand how that's affecting anything she said
because nobody cleans their island this is
just a separate topics like some wipes
she's like i'm completely flabbergast and then
she said i'll show you how to
do it wish my face and she
i washed my face eye makeup remover
so she says i guess i never
thought about am i really getting in
there well yeah i meant might have
less people who don't
make up yeah so she's like let
me show you how to do this
this freak just wants to touch people's
eyelids well i didn't mind it because
she didn't want to break likes you
do it like this and she it
was like a little tiny spot treatment
and where did you pick this one
i'm superfly gently wipe we should move
eyelids to each other during the show
but are they called those man wipes
for men did have a picture of
oil and they smelled like axe body
spray a testicle there was no smell
that's saying that is what i meant
um a picture of one ball but
then there was so that was that
was very nice like limbaugh yeah oh
yeah fame is old news this honorbound
about yeah hitler had
one boy very close hitler he only
had one ball yearning he had none
at all this is what they would
do during world war two to keep
spirits up yeah that's true so they
were nagging i don't know if it's
true that going had no balls but
but it's the kind of thing you'd
seem to have a little fun when
these athletes existing in the movie a
separate piece like you're trying to commit
a genocide
guide will show you here's yeah only
have one ball he's like who cares
he's only got half the stash i
do want to write what he lowers
the original girlboss yeah maybe only having
one ball led him to like doing
whatever you want hey there's only like
one ball i'm gonna live my life
till i die
we should all cut off one of
our balls but here's the other thing
that the opposite is she had to
ah she was taking different pictures of
my eyes than had been done previously
and she said okay look up and
then she took her look at my
index finger oh and she pulled down
okay you know my eye the way
you do when you're a little kid
to make a scary face right
side note i think that people who
work with eyes have the cleanest hands
in the biz you think i just
picture them you hushing i think so
today long but her her hands were
very she was a slight woman right
small saucepan and it felt so nice
i don't know why but it really
surprised me i hire someone who's suppose
your eyes down
not every day just my my birthday
but i agree i think there's a
certain kind of touch that makes you
go yeah oh my i don't know
there's something about it and then she
did she and then she pushed my
eyebrow up when i looked down and
then the other eye she did the
eyebrow but she didn't do under the
eyes a little discipline under why did
she
give a pathway i know i was
looking forward to it after she did
the first i was like oh yea
yeah my i went to get my
eyes checked and my eye doctor i
sort of kind of always go to
a different person within there i never
have actually been to the guy whose
name is on the thing right you
gotta oh yeah it's the best oh
great destroyers for you
i want this i don't even want
it honestly it's like i don't even
know you deserve it okay maybe i
do but i liked the people who
helped me out and there was a
nice gentleman who came in and did
my and preliminary sort of paperwork discussing
asking questions that kind of seventh tier
one thing he said that i thought
was interesting and i'll just throw it
out there for the listener and you
can take your week really
and if you disagree i don't want
to hear it but i thought it
was kinda interesting he asked me if
i had any surgeries and while i
haven't any surgeries i did mention having
a baby because i was like wow
know is that something and then he
was like actually i'm really glad you
said that because god's original surgery yeah
um because i wanna know how babies
has god oh yeah um okay show
me down there
yes i look at my third ah
it's blinking he said i can't he
said that ah babies they have new
technology basically i have horrible vision and
the technology maybe some memories have let
me if i don't tell you so
when i was in my vision
they're going bad when i was in
second grade i needed glasses and ever
since it's gotten progressively worse my entire
life i have horrible vision but he
shed better there's a new thing and
i don't of course remember the name
but i can figure it out glasses
but there's new treatments for little kids
that help them so that thinking classes
are the baby oh can prevent
all the stuff from happening later i
can just make sure i'll stay better
longer and so he said maybe should
actually be checked at the one year
mark and then you get to come
back until they're three but a lot
of a lot of times they'll say
your doctor has key sectors ah yeah
he said your doctor might say like
they're checking in that's enough he's like
it actually we he's a guy you
could go
anywhere you want i'm not trying to
show you i'll tell you checking your
nuts enough i don't know what i
said but they check it and they
say that's enough but when he said
i don't care if you go here
were awesome not trying to upcharge you
i don't give a shit i'm just
he's trying to let just loudly live
or die i'm just telling you you
should don't care if you go to
hell or you just die to find
out if any
classes take classes wow these glasses is
so cute i know i thought that
was very good information should do that
with viagra like i want you don't
have to have viagra as an older
man take it when you're younger it's
kind of loud tosses um so the
ah there was a doctor came and
she was a woman she was fantastic
possible before that happened that man was
having
an issue with the computer and he
brought in a younger fellow who was
just about a tear he was another
talk of computers for sure but he
knew he was he was a son
of the main doctor ah this he
knows his ninth tier so many doctors
a woman that know the main doctors
a man who i don't know he
has a son who has the same
last name who rocks because the woman
doctor her son is
has been an accident oh yes she's
operating and shot doctor came in and
fix the computer and then he kind
of made a joke about how he's
like the resident we do like slap
the side of it yay blue in
it and and he was very nice
and then i found out that my
doctor is his wife and i was
like what is why i'm all your
hair i have daughters i love
life husband and so he made the
joke that he's the guy everyone asks
him to yeah cause he's like the
guy younger six any understands all the
computer say it's interesting when someone falls
into the same field as their parents
like it it makes sense when like
okay my parents or my you know
they've owned this factory and they're giving
me
me a job and even though i
hate plastics i get to be just
the boss and not have to worry
you know like that kind of stuff
but when someone's like oh i want
to study the exact same thing maybe
you're getting how well my parents might
reject his daughter is also a dentist
at his practice right and i think
that's great yeah there's something really nice
about it to me let me ask
you this
question are there any children of actors
who don't go into acting i love
million there's so many dhoni yeah so
many bills just hear about the ones
who do there's a trillion for first
person came to mind diane keaton
how many children to share okay
but you know george michael on his
last day he took his name from
diane keaton which is such a bold
move it is like what to name
him after another celebrity and then we're
talking liberty if you're if your name
is already a celebrity name and you're
like well i can't he's already got
mine like i'm just like i'll me
lauren cruz almost changing why not scott
j fox yeah that would've been really
weird
i'm sure i've told this story before
but tell it again laurie love it
we had a piano teacher when i
was this spring a bow dough re
mi fa so la ti vo piano
yeah ah we had a piano teacher
who'd come to our house and i
think he's probably a college student but
he seemed really old to me because
i was five i don't remember this
but i wanna hear it he always
he had like kind of
greasy like long hair in the early
and he was a greaser layer was
yeah it was just that and then
he would go like and like he
would like sniff and like move his
hair out of the way while he
was playing i remember that's all i
remember and i apparently did piano but
he changed his name to my brothers
know you did dialysis yeah i remember
this he just i think he was
like
just always liked that name and that's
fine you know i know wow you
cannot tell us it's like what does
yeah yeah whoever you were before you
still are that because you're teaching piano
to children in their home yeah we
stopped soon after it's very weird also
also if you're changing your name just
go like lie about the reason you're
changing it not just like oh i'm
teaching your son p
piano and i really like that name
so i'm gonna change my name to
your son's name i know it's like
oh this is my grandfather's hey live
and people go oh what a coincidence
my middle name just cannot do it
i would say just keep calling yourself
whatever the fuck you were remember guy's
name used to know so you think
every person should just keep their own
name that there i do not think
that all weird lauren
absolutely wow million percent now what i'm
saying but for three josh hawley walked
into my home and changes even my
brother's name i would say you are
ah that is very weird yeah alright
let's take a break
and we're back no i am like
i think lauren's back she knows she's
started typing even though so okay it's
about paul my mom texted me oh
and said i was in the car
listening to paul talk about asking jeannie
to marry him it was a fun
story why did you maybe i'm so
your dad's voice
chapter something no it was in the
car with her
was it on was should i go
for rights
we go for rides a lot i
mean was it on series like seventy
monday what did you get how did
she complete that sensitive she said it
was oh she said i didn't want
to write like did i read it
but you didn't hear yeah i heard
it it was a fun story one
store was a fun story okay i
definitely was in my standup um and
me i don't know where she
he was hearing a serious example if
she listens to that oh that's pretty
likely lasagna if you recorded it on
an album oh maybe she did hear
that a comedian but i just like
the way she gets that honey
good luck um no but she ah
she loves serious and listens to a
lot of stand-up on there it's so
wild that you have to like as
an artist they should call it funny
but you have to set of series
yeah but spelled i wouldn't say everything
there is funny well for the comedy
channels for know how netflix changed it
to netflix's a joke
yeah when they put out all those
dave chappelle stand-up specials
yeah
serious should do that with
and say she's a sob story for
seriously funny this is a joke because
that would be kind of just interesting
exact serious it's serious like netflix is
serious as a funny heart attack yeah
um i have some notes so that
you have to you like there's a
there's this this system in place where
you have to chase
down your own money and then they
have to act like and then they
just get to act like oh yeah
here you go that's nuts yeah yeah
we were when you die every time
you have a standup like bit that
airs on sirius how are you supposed
to know exactly yeah exactly i have
to constantly you know play someone to
constantly listen to that turns into
to a lot of money yeah so
you're paying my mom now i guess
yes she's one of my she's one
of my agents and then i have
a lot of people people listen in
shifts that has happened though like when
you're in commercial in different time zones
you're supposed to get pay every time
they are the commercial and i have
a lot of friends who you know
like i've said to them hey i
just saw your commercial they're like oh
i'm not getting paid for that
it again let me know exactly where
you saw it there is a and
there should be a penalty there's a
website called eyespot dot tv that tells
you when and where your this isn't
commercial by the way for ice on
tv yeah if it's opamps at least
there used to be that i don't
know i looked at many years but
i know it's probably a chip in
your brain i'm sure yes boy
while they're all controlling us
i'd like to be controlled would you
really want to have go fuck yourself
under halfway to robot eighty to do
you need to have another boot on
your foot and it just tells me
where to go yeah like i don't
even know where i'm going i just
suddenly get up and start walking some
cute if you had another boot on
your foot if you want to booze
but be up and weekly
gotta you gotta to boost the robot
and he tried to walk up stairs
we kept falling down flat
no it should kitchen keep you up
okay did you when you were a
kid did you have stairs were they
carpeted in did you try to slide
down them one million yeah of course
yeah right even my aunt's house we'd
put ah we'd throw all the stuffed
animals down make a big ship had
not the bottom of the crash pad
yeah yeah and then
get into the sky hurt them so
it hurts it hurts getting sleepy and
push down and it hurts and it's
not great or write a blanket yeah
yeah yeah either of those are good
i want to carpet some stairs in
my home that i want me to
be um like the stairs let me
bid on this alright
all underbid him alright i just want
to hang out with you guys oh
during the lunch break we had weird
carpet stairs and then at one point
they the carpet was ripped up and
we put just like little remnants on
each step so it wasn't like the
full right like a tread yes exactly
yeah exactly so you
could not lie down that it hurt
like hell i go because my office
is downstairs i'm the one using those
stairs most of the time and i've
i've become very oh because you put
that no girls allowed sign yeah exactly
yeah smart smart for everyone
but every time i walked down those
stairs because they are slippery
i've become there's nothing that can be
done about that i become just very
well they say pour vinegar on or
something but yeah i'm down with your
head hitting every step know i just
because i have become glasses on there
i'll get nice and sticky i'm not
cavalier ever i've i've made a decision
to never be cavalier about walking up
stairs just like you know dump it
up at ah every single time i
walked down now i'm
very just cognizant about holding very tightly
to the handrail yeah time so it's
a tragedy holding my other hand against
the young just for example his team
are you being in while i tell
this comes out in such thick glycolic
forty water thick
thick ropes and a thick ropey pee
my arching ropes of urine urine but
i just know like how your life
will ever own a war just like
that or or like your life can
be suddenly changed so yeah so i'm
sure i've said this before i think
often about when is the next time
i'm going to fall like have a
bad fall enough stop like tr
over something and just like kind of
like in my life i'm knocking on
wood you know well i mean just
having this boot on it's like your
life can just be fun i mean
it sapped me of the will to
live no huh
you are on a thin thread already
this is all it took yeah breaking
a tidy bone in my goal and
now i'm like i'm out yeah how
many how tiny is the bone i
don't know what's tiny to you a
penny
it's round and flat like a penny
it has abraham lincoln on it how
many round flat bones do you think
we have in the human body i
would say knuckles are all round and
flat yep checked out ten of those
round and flat what oh let me
see your knuckles not flat oh my
god lauren pickles are oblong holy
sure their holiday a flat ones look
no when you hold it like that
this good bud gets t i am
the world staring at her i'm not
high but hands are wild yeah it's
crate and feet when like it's so
theatre normal it's so crazy sick when
you think about it oh you maniac
he's spilling the water everywhere it's because
i forgot my name what happens when
you know and i thought i feel
my life event
and so say i'm better than you
laura and i for one brief second
where were the same oh wow recap
yeah i got a couple of important
alright guys
this is a month after by the
urdd something oh fuck it no no
it's just like it's four weeks from
ours earth right ever all i wanna
say maybe four weeks is a good
time to start tuning into the bachelorette
because they'll have weeded out a bunch
of the guys we got two bachelorettes
this season which i will say has
rejuvenated the entire series it is totally
fresh there's gonna be totally new drama
as they get down to fewer
guys and there's like more competition or
less competition it's just here should we
call it yeah if you were competition
it's getting very interesting already i was
way more engaged there's only been one
episode i know this but i'm taking
fish episode the worst okay but i
thought it was better than normal and
by the way looks my phone the
entire time but i'm saying it was
so funny
and then what happened next would shock
anyone a new show came on and
i stayed to watch it live but
we know joe jonas joe jonas nick
nerve no no-nos kevin go jonas kevin
jonas and jonas jonas it's claimed a
prayer for him it's all going to
tell on hello
or it's gonna be on hulu by
eob before episodes now i guess um
really fun show i thought was gonna
be not interesting it's the premise is
that family members of famous people so
like a cousin a grandson on sister
whenever are the people live in la
jolla and and other day nobody knows
who they're related to but they have
try to guess who your celebrity relative
is with clues and all these different
things that has a race of the
people
it's really fun i thought it would
be really silly but to admit it
but i guess the first episode had
a great endy i'm totally don't spoil
it because i taped it i'm totally
on board okay it's on hulu spoil
it for me you would think i'm
never gonna walk do you think frankie
grundy would be one of the hosts
know frankie goes to grundy frankie for
showrunners grundy starbuck
lesser known jonas he's the perfect co-host
no i get a but like frankie
grundy made a whole career out of
being ariana grande's right brother on big
brother right but it was he was
the little brother on big brother anyway
never anyway it's really fun you you
they tell you who some of the
relatives are as a viewer but some
you don't know so you get to
still try to keep guessing there was
one in the first
interesting they all thought this one guy
was related to and it was very
fun and i was like that's probably
right and then it's a fun okay
okay so this an ad i wish
it was if they want to pay
me i'll talk about cleaning yeah abc
come to us we'll talk about whatever
you want to talk about we talk
about the fucking rookie i know i
love abc i'm a big fan of
familiar
in little things as well by the
way speaking of the rookie i saw
some some article that said it was
nathan fielder is the king of cringe
comedy and i thought it said nathan
fillion when i was looking at it
going like trying to figure out i
was like when is it coming comedy
the rookie is nodded what are we
telling doc
our horrible sing-a-long blog there's a lot
of there's a lot of cringe comedy
in the rookie though i and i
love nathan fillion but i was just
really trying to parse this and go
like why are they making this wild
claim and then it turns out your
dough yeah well the phone was far
away from my eyes i will know
what i recently read a headline that
also shouted the hail this was a
headline about ah
alan hay about a woman skipper a
woman whose interior decorator and said like
her home is a fever dream of
patterns and then i went and let
those walls shed three shades of white
on her walls so she says i
used three different shades of white and
then it was like she makes pet
things that are gingham and they're cute
but it was like it wasn't crazy
no way a fever like the madonna
inn or no wo
oh yeah yeah there's so many ways
you have a billion patterns and ramos
like this is not that and she
didn't claim to be that the author
right when phrases like that get so
overused it really it's it's so it
it's wearying yeah i'm just like oh
wow i'm gonna look at something crazy
behind i was anger believes and i
love just made you click on it
though it while it's certainly
the book and i almost bought something
for our website but that doesn't know
but i live in the energy pattern
how close did you get to bike
so i'm really close but it was
a little overpriced and i was like
do i really need this where you
hovering over the hovered over the kicker
and it was a tissue box cover
but wish i had a little i'm
looking scary and you've been looking for
a tissue box cover why why do
you not like
the actual sushi because they make the
tissue boxes themselves in these nice pattern
or they suck i like to show
my awana i want to work tissue
box cover to look great in my
room i would buy a tissue i
just haven't found one that i love
if it were like tope or what
about peanut this one is this one
is she makes all column patterns and
they're really cute babies what what
happened is it would be a fever
dream of pattern if i put it
in my bathroom which i would like
to have wallpaper you want that fever
dream i like that your bathrooms are
crazy i can barely shit in them
and i try
but it's very distracting again because that
is creepy um i shouldn't every bathroom
in your house i don't know if
you know that oh i don't know
that it's actually could you ever been
inside i don't know you have i
think i went inside when you have
been inside
does holly miss me yeah anyway
yeah i would love that thought oh
my god wait how did they test
baby's vision look i don't know but
he said they do this today like
jabba jesse like hey every meal noise
where noise came from it's like she
could see you know what i'll find
out because i'm gonna do it you're
gonna you're gonna do it yourself i'm
gonna do it tonight i'm gonna look
online how to
now i'm gonna take her in i'll
take her in all children what are
you doing the water safety stuff will
i know she she's swam like first
time it was like symbols she'd liked
your height weight and all you were
tweeted that thing the other day the
video of the guy throwing his bike
was crazy wow that's what i understand
why that's been essential there was a
bit the car
all the comments in that thread there's
like just a debate going on yeah
it's a pretty intense toss it's a
water safety video did you post it
or you just sent it i just
retreated it that's all your stuff don't
shoot the messenger yeah don't shoot the
messenger if people can see it on
your page i've heard it's good to
do but they but they're the other
video underneath it is of the younger
the
oh no ah but but i've heard
it's good of like nobody is certainly
teach teach me i'm getting there on
their back yeah it looks great i
think it's great i haven't done it
yet believe taken her now she's been
in like three or four pools she
went to lance bass is cool not
to brag but she'll yeah houses has
i'm friends with him and i went
to his house memorial day houses mom
it's great
and has a great view really yeah
what what i can't say i'm very
dear friends with joey fatwa
we're best friends i see him all
the time chris kirkpatrick and i are
acquaintances well that being said she also
went in the pool at disneyland i'm
friends with st we would give away
his location if you said what the
view was what does it of it's
just a city of like which city
paris france la
ooh la la um no i wouldn't
dare to describe what i saw
like eyes wide shut in there oh
so she likes pools she loves it
she has she's very piece show at
bass she loves bats so should we
shoot is she an aquarius um she's
not but she loves the path around
babies and rasp think you know so
yeah maybe she's queries did you read
that that i don't know what it
was opposed on but i saw it
on t
ritter where it was a woman asking
for advice on reddit or something saying
i don't understand what's going on but
we did a dna test on our
my husband i did a dna test
on our baby and it's not my
husband's and i've never cheated on him
and he's he's very upset with that
makes no sense this is wrong
he's very he's very upset with me
crack tea ah he almost wouldn't let
me into the house but he did
let me enter the house now he's
letting me into the house and common
said he apologizes but he's still upset
and i keep trying to say i've
never cheated i never cheated and then
there's a you know there's advice advice
and then there's a followup where she
goes and
now i've taken now we've checked my
dna and it's not my dna either
the hospital gave the wrong name huh
oh and then there's a bunch of
people underneath satellite to do about this
this is why we either never let
the baby out of our sight when
we gave birth we always like followed
them wherever they took the baby or
they have some sort of bracelet thing
that like makes a musical tone ah
that voodoo
oh um no but i mean they
have they put the bracelet on them
that that's identifying them right i don't
know exactly what but but several people
were like yeah this is why this
happens this is why this huh that
is that's helpful healthy happen i don't
know and i mean why did they
do the dna test there must have
been a question
at some point because obviously it was
the backup so we were doing ceos
yeah so i don't know what it
was about but but yeah wow nightmare
and then they're like i was like
dog so solely so i was half
terrier and her husband was pissed will
also this woman she's like had had
the baby for i don't know say
five years or whatever she's here she's
like now so long now i'm afraid
so
someone's going to take because that's your
baby her away yeah but i also
want my real baby as well yeah
it's just a fucked up situation that's
insane go insane wow yeah but then
said the other families should know too
because that's yeah but but god what
are you supposed to do what do
you do in that situation then you
get to live next door if you're
the president
say america would like then you'd have
jealousy if you're biden hey jealousy do
you remember there was a warning or
tune you know those one-off they would
do like one off cartoons everyone's wow
the owner of the main case money
to the dna test
he was not the porky pig said
you are not the father or dance
and i wasn't going to do it
you aren't gonna do the stutter if
we canceled porky pig under a stammer
oh that's a good question what's the
diff well bob new assessed ah you're
doing yeah samara samara is more like
like like like like like this
yeah bob newhart bob fucking nu har
dee fucking in this is what it
was oh great so yeah so there
was a cartoon by erhard famously paul
britain's uncle oh yeah that's right oh
i can see it i can see
the resemblance actually they have a very
dry and no idea since they been
dry eyes and your official tears only
docked
rojas
massages miss you um this is uncle
earth great zankel okay
i don't know because you're the one
here
i just wanted to say zankel i
would say zankel his uncle zit your
uncle zack
yeah go paul so this cartoon ah
baby gets switched at the hospital with
an alien baby and the the parents
were like right away the baby is
green and everything yeah and the parents
are just like well i guess this
is our baby and they had this
tourism realise there were two babies
the alien baby and the the human
baby and they had little bracelets on
and one said boy said yob and
all i remember i remember like dimly
the father being sort of perplexed by
the what the baby was doing and
then at the end the baby like
is reclaimed by the alien parents or
something
and i remember it the cartoon ends
with the father falling out of a
building the human father the human father
saying screaming yob yob give me back
my yob why and then he wakes
up it was a dream or was
it because then the human baby does
a weird thing wow yeah falling out
of the bill
building yeah that's cool it's like a
high like a skyscraper he's falling through
its dietmar ya me up can you
give me back my a yob yeah
scary should we make three m t
shirts yob yob give me back my
oh yeah sure it's already become our
catchphrase is it public domain now and
i say yeah but i feel like
i will say it already
a yob yob give me back my
jaw but yeah i'm getting back my
job and pay back my son oh
my job my show when we saw
ransom ebay with my shirts and we
saw ransom at the center ramadan were
you there paul i think you were
john mad it was air or something
where no i honestly don't remember if
i've seen that movie after the movie
we all were in
the lobby and i think john said
give me back my money
it sounds about right
i just remember that anytime i think
of that movie which is not often
not enough no yeah i do remember
when we went see conair and we
all wore are junk sawyer because we
are convicts robot orange jumpsuits and we
arrive together yes if people were delighted
that we knew
people in their thing under orders were
like yeah yeah people who are not
delighted when we saw batman and robin
and we just laughed at how bad
it was the entire time and there
was a woman in a batman t-shirt
who yelled at us afterwards she was
like you ruined that movie his parents
were murdered
hi
alright let's take a break okay
hey
yeah
yob yob where's my yob bring back
my yakuza long shirt at this point
well it's more of a nature well
you've got an ebenezer oil love that
let's bring that back yeah and a
big long nightcap too yeah it goes
all the way down why don't i
hear that but have it say three
nights practically we make a really long
make gun and the night kevin's is
freedom
funny i think it would be cute
oh oh no other podcasts doing that
no i know it's an untapped market
i don't think anyone is making custom
nightcaps for sure
go down to the crack yeah they
can't go to a sense of pride
huh that's impractical for sleeping you just
tuck it into the you strangle yourself
your pajama waistband it's going to get
pulled off strangle yourself oh god that
would be horrible if we made those
and someone strangled themselves yes oh and
i was like i remember when i
was a kid there was
was this is before this shit got
outlawed this is before you were an
adult but there was before
like there was a do remember the
micro knots yeah um we were toys
tiny tiny teeny tiny um hold on
astronauts the toys themselves were not as
small as you would think no they
were um micro machines yeah no we're
the commercial famously narrated by joshua junior
i loved how small those were they
were micro that's really funny you didn't
need a microscope to see them oh
but they were in the palm of
a child's hand interestingly enough i think
i had some but the main
reason i knew them is because they
were marvel comics and they were integrated
into the actual marvel universe yeah and
and they were licensed property where now
you can't reprint any of any because
they would interact with the x-men's right
right they can't be reprinted anymore because
the micro knots other than the ones
they created for the comic book or
not um abe
to be reprinted so it's like those
are lost forever that i had news
ruins my day they were cool choices
so sorry should i call my yeah
you're right home is ruins my day
they were very cool toys though and
they need each other eight had a
lot of articulation points but i remember
look him up baron karzai was the
bad guy oh he was like ah
ah this black and red dude um
he was very sinister looking but he
had fists that you could shoot oh
i love that you would like press
it there's like a little trigger in
his absolutely
lose on day one but of course
the danger was swallow and that's wow
right outlawed that it was i read
that it was a battlestar galactica um
toy oh um that um cause that
there they are you can get there's
the gang that for two hundred and
eighteen doll i mean it's my brothers
we loved them it sucks that you
can't make cool stuff but
it's it even one child dying just
not worth it but here's the thing
someone pointed out that i saw this
post online somebody pointed out that in
this happened in like nineteen seventy eight
or something this kid choked on a
projectile from ah um right and lived
ah but and so now that kind
of thing is outlawed because we are
on a bit but we still have
guns you making notes
tons of guns and guns yeah because
great politicians don't make money from little
toys good political on guys you know
i'm more of like i'm in between
i like i want you to vote
democrat you're not a republican i wish
that we had in this country one
hundred guns and everyone jerry
yeah yeah don't be great if you
ended it was like a library and
so i think it doesn't check it
out of the library yeah and it
was they were in libraries if you
keep it out early you have to
pay for yeah good you know record
of returning on time it's right i
remember when they they started having cds
that you could check out the library
and i was shocked because i was
like those aren't books
and and then video and movies someday
your ass kicked you after you said
that
but it was just shocking to me
the idea that you could because libraries
had always been for books yeah and
sand records in the library well i
mean maybe nothing
hey alright
i think it's time for something called
a three-match there's also maps and stuff
and a lapse yeah let's borrow old
man and agenda key really maps so
you could check or or or were
those things that are like don't just
check it out just like just reference
figure out where you want to go
try and let us know take a
pic
sure it alas you could go to
the camera didn't have google you'd go
to the library look up how to
drive to wherever you want to go
yeah yeah because they didn't sell maps
no god you remember the thomas guide
i was gonna ask if you remember
it because i learned so much about
it i had a thomas guide before
i learned to drive because i was
like well one day i'm gonna learn
to drive right
good times out there collecting dust yeah
absolutely absolutely wow yeah i used to
have to use it to go to
auditions and it was so frustrating yeah
like trying to figure out how to
navigate l a who am i just
magellan hey alright hit us free your
time oh wait do we have a
voicemail kev kevin knots we do have
voicemail i love it
as always our our number is haha
laden poo
so easy hey scott paul and loin
loin market i'll crew rep okay etc
this guy's a fan of those i
had an interesting question will be the
joseph r michael from kentucky long time
listener rahim color um i was wondering
question what the mo
most embarrassing thing that you have seen
someone do while walking on the sidewalk
is or maybe saying embarrassing but you've
got i mean we've all you know
walk into a pole or what not
watching rupaul but is there anything i'm
sure by the way
okay huh interesting um embarrassing things i've
seen i mean i deaf aster made
because yeah humiliating yeah i definitely am
in austin when i was there for
south by southwest state in this cool
hotel i remember that had just huge
huge glass as doors and everything
thing as the front of the hotel
and i definitely like walked full speed
right into one of the windows yeah
and and ah you know of course
my nose hit the glass two seconds
before the rest of my body and
um just really really painful and this
in front of a lot of cool
hipster people and that was
embarrassing for me the sound it makes
when somebody walks into a glass doors
it's quite glad when it also like
laughs at you it's like yeah what
a hard one for me to witness
because i would have wanted to laugh
at you but i would have thought
bad thing i would've been trying not
to laugh when you're a terrible person
but it's just hard because i would
just like i would have wanted to
enjoy my day laughing wait because
cause during my day because you know
me you would have won the last
four i wouldn't concerned if you had
if i would have wanted to laugh
pretty much whoever it is but i
think no human would make it funnier
and i would be telling myself it's
mean to laugh so i'd have to
stop right but i would have gone
i just missed out on some really
good laughs
you have to laugh at something i
find funny later i feel like if
i didn't know the person i wouldn't
laugh but if i did know the
person i would i think that's probably
the difference yeah it's like it's sort
of funny if it's someone you don't
know because it's like they they want
full steam into a glass ball there's
no reason for them to do that
yeah right but if you know them
i believe i've told my story about
the great sam neil
ah not being able to find his
way out of um ah tower video
when i worked there
i remember we had so the doors
were two glass doors on either side
of those were glass panels right and
so he was leaving the store and
he was pushing on one of the
glass panels and was so confused why
it was not he was like nah
how did i get in here not
angry just i can't ever see
him getting angry know he was he's
very angry at somebody pretending to be
him online oh really oh that's the
samuel samuel trask mark you she will
treasure yeah you know i know who
that is i thought you're talking about
similar yeah yeah yeah whoa star her
from this latest dressing park movie yeah
yeah my big role but we had
a literally was looking for you and
i didn't even
haven't seen it i don't but a
lot of people have scott i know
and well people out with that i'm
not but i hadn't she must be
doing something or i'm just saying i
haven't seen it myself and i'm curious
to see it um i'm buying here
in my home we have been curious
to see that my home we have
ah and don't be scared of phantom
screens
these are um screen doors that slide
in and out of the wall ah
so you don't have to love that
they're like they're what do you call
that when adored the pocket pocket door
yeah okay yeah but his wife was
called the phantoms and instead of pocket
huh there but they're not but they
are yes and sometimes you forget or
don't know that somebody else has done
that and you walk through them and
oh yeah alarming as shit but they're
designed they're designed with that in mind
to be that people do love so
you can put while no no no
that people are gonna fuckin walk through
so you can very easily put them
back into play oh
okay but when sam knew he got
well here we eventually said oh no
yes there any right yeah he was
able to escape yes i just want
to see them live at tower records
i just wondered if he was still
there if we could go see him
i would love to i would love
to get his hands pressed against the
glass reeled when he came in i
lo i bad i was so excited
that was one of my favorite what
is there instead of tower is it
still just our video there you know
how the records is still there it
was a bank the last i checked
a bang yes yes yes so make
a bank out of anything tell me
about it so sad that it's bank
now do you know
ah they
where i used to live after i
moved out of there cool up and
i were so surprised we went back
to where you lived in the fall
you know our our old place i
don't want to give away the location
but it was in our video we
went back and we we ate suffice
to say there were plenty of video
tapes there yeah we aided
at a place we used to like
we went back there three years later
and they had they had made two
wells fargo banks across the street from
each other sometimes they gotta do because
it's hard to cross see if you
have one on each side yeah banking
which know they'll have a starbucks and
they said they'll have a chase bank
as wells fargo who's a website ah
johnny
rockets
it is really good i'll have gotten
to to to to to to participate
to tip to remember but to olive
gardens facing each other could be why
we roll race jokes at each other
for because she's stuck in a mess
they have a softball tournament every year
using breadsticks you have sellers tee balls
garden from the game show and play
because that's right i have to
to i know go use it yeah
go use it you have to work
why don't you go yellow and go
dallas to olive garden at the oh
take us take us yeah well i
used to work there you know we
did the original team member yes okay
yeah not just you you're supposed to
distribute oh no no no ever with
food cost ships probably it's probably just
for you in my goodness pass this
way
it is but maybe i might the
plan was to go with my team
yeah and i'll have oh but you
guys had a massive falling out at
right now and i'll see if anyone
wants to do it maybe we'll make
a lunch date which we me and
my team will show up there the
same night yeah we'll treat you this
unlimited breadsticks
those are free it doesn't mean such
treat could you send some breadsticks over
to the table
we already did we'd given to everyone
no those aren't free oh yeah well
there's limited so if you order some
soup and salad if you order something
they're free i believe this time that
was i don't think you just get
them at the table unlimited ordering seconds
of soup or salad i know that's
something you'd like to give you a
big bowl and then you can have
multiples will see most of the people
but
look i have experienced defending it family
style most people only order they they
don't get refills it would be rare
whole refill of that fuckin sell it
would be well the salad if you're
if you're because you only put one
bowl on the table if there were
people alone the table
yeah wrong school so said we would
do refills of the salad bowl more
than we would do soups so he
would always be weird when someone would
go like i'll have another bowl of
soup i'm like can anyone eat two
bowls of su before another meal especially
well like what are you shrek most
remote teams like even yeah most people
going for lunch just would do the
soup and salad stuff scott
i'm telling you from my experience yeah
i'm not doing that and i'm not
most people can't love me and i'll
tell ya that customers with your days
yeah i hate to disagree with you
you're so much like those other no
i'm nae just calm and ready
a look we don't have time to
do it make your time to three
dollars fine i've got a rapid yeah
we gotta go
oh hey that's the first tats or
t-shirts or nah i would say the
ernie voicemail counts as a throw listen
i recently appeared on the hollywood handbook
podcast no great my triumph year tag
um and we they showed me some
cameos kevin can you get me on
this and do not mention that i'm
on cameo but i am um how's
that going it's
still happening it's why it's really wild
yeah wanna hear more about that i
said that sarcastically um but um they
showed so they showed a brian coming
from brian cox of succession fame and
he literally if you have not heard
the episode he's literally just reading the
list of things that was sent to
him about the person
it's the most like the least amount
of effort you can put into it
and then at the end he says
and if anyone gets in your face
you tell them to fuck off
who knows what the people want and
i think it's like six hundred dollars
whole seven seven hundred seventy back and
look at this if you're brian cox
why are you bothering um i don't
know but but but it's five hundred
dollars a second i think a lot
of people would do i guess but
he was gambling debts yeah i was
watching a commercial the other day and
it was that o'neill now
narrating the commercial for refer you know
my lantern or whatever and i'm just
like ah he's gotta be one of
the most wealthy people oh you're talking
about ed o'neill from modern family right
i was like boy he does a
lot of voiceover album die and i
was just like bondi beach album and
this is no beach is this moving
that but he's got i'm sure he
has like grandchildren and stuff he
i'm sure his what his stuff is
like a game a gold rattle oh
well while while you can make all
that money make it because you never
know when that's when you're gonna die
in the spigots turned off and you
hey when the sunshine you know besides
like i get it i think it's
you know i think i understand that
but i think it's also getting in
the way of younger people who do
these jobs
jobs who need the mind just voiceover
artists who are talented and not celebrities
one time i went to the fox
lot and i was ah entering a
building ah behind ah ed o'neill and
a bunch of other people and he
did not hold the door open for
me he saw me and
didn't do it i think he makes
a lot of sense i parted with
lawrence you partied with him
was onset recalls why you remember yeah
yeah i saw john calling it i
saw him together after that um no
i i saw a play that he
did ah and you sit up and
we're drinking in the audience party are
you saying it was a taping of
married with children no that's not a
play great play i think he was
on
american toy avatar heg
nice i'm doing lifeboat the david mamet
show lifeboat with george wendt and him
and who else was in oh a
bunch of those mamet like repertory people
joe montana ah john tenney was not
in its but about a bunch of
like the secondary people will always show
up as like all the cops and
homicide and stuff like that oh
sure um and then i don't know
how but we talked to them afterwards
and then they invited us to go
to this bar to go drinking with
everyone to watch when get free beer
i'm like twenty two years old or
whatever and get and we go to
this bar and hang out with ed
o'neill and the cats and they were
so nice to us is like twenty
he was nice it was great and
then george went ah literally walked in
a bar he'd never been in they
shouted norm of course he sat down
they they slid a beer over to
a muse like he just tipped his
head it was great and i got
to work with george wendt who was
jason sudeikis is uncle that's right that's
right and i got to work with
him on the comedy bang bang tv
show untold
in that stories like yeah it was
the greatest thing yeah any bar yeah
and i also worked with him famous
land clipped for ten episodes oh yeah
amos yea did first full-season gray guy
he's a fantastic to the feeling of
a tremor one time he's a great
guy and everybody mike had a fun
bar experience with him at once oh
well let him tell that yeah he
should tell that on the show tweet
and spouse
this edition of freedom yeah what are
we we gotta do it i know
this sounds like a good accept situation
i think we should go could be
alright goodbye fuck off
a
uh