i missed break paul speak up i
can't hear you paul
it's fun try it we should always
bring yoga
re
somebody was screaming whispering which i think
is different yeah learn your scream whispering
yeah did you even realize it laura
makeup hello oh wow oh wow
that would be the greatest somebody wake
of a deadly hello hello i'm here
yeah oh that's pop in in thy
neighbor we're back once again yeah lauren
lucas is over there i am paul
f tompkins is over here that's what's
happening and scott's over
ah i was waiting for me waiting
tell him that wasn't happening until scott
was over there and then so yeah
i rushed over here you sit down
yeah yeah it's not all ah well
we're having fun already we're the pretzel
gang were gym freedom yeah and you're
our little piss pigs yo we love
big jed huh
happen here our listeners said we want
to meet all the freedom piss pigs
we need a name for the fandom
of threesome and they decided they decided
amongst themselves yeah yeah and then brought
it to us and we they they
were like yea or nay and we
say yea if it makes you have
yeah yeah yeah
a will call you pass
and so the piss pigs were born
yep and they love it they love
it it's so weird it seems so
insulting but they love it so much
yeah called that yeah yeah anyway so
hello to our little piss pigs up
there if this is your first episode
you are now newly-minted piss pig
dirty little rat oh lauren we are
waiting for you to finish this email
you are composing oh transaction well who
are you sending money to do business
your damn business i'll put down it's
going to be on break and i
didn't finish it and i keep my
business private imo i don't like that
i can see other people i don't
understand why i don't want youtube yeah
i don't
have anyone able to see mine in
the venmo is like put an emoji
in there please take it easy venmo
i prefer not to use it and
i as i always say i love
cash but you know sometimes you need
love kay cash is king cash is
cash is king when everything goes down
late when we're off the grid way
we're gonna need
monday we're gonna need my ash dollar
bills y'all believe i still have all
that cash that we took out of
the bank when the when the debit
started right casey wilson told to sue
she does send you panic over here
yeah yeah yeah
der got a couple cds
there has been no time she's been
correct no offense casey but it's different
stories if you are not apology yeah
for yeah either those say no i
apologize for getting cash but put it
back and thank everyone no yeah not
like where it is yeah which is
right by my door guys need to
buy or aflame logs they're gonna go
out of business
this get as many as you can
yeah i didn't hear the formula shortage
is coming up again yeah oh no
he mustn't tariffs or you will see
okay are you stocked i know you
might have a subscription because i think
coup i've mentioned one yeah so and
those those were in business like bobby
the subscription service was in business we
had a rearing
ing the o during the shortage though
that was one that people kept saying
was available i had to drive around
to various walmarts we had to recall
so we had to throw three canisters
away you should have jumped them into
boston harbor as a protein yes that's
really disappointing and then all the babies
who drink out of boston harbor suddenly
gets it no
oh no yep those guys know every
call so we're we're we're going back
to the old formula which i gotta
say is wreaking havoc on that little
tom tom owe me one oh yeah
yes what tom tom
oh yeah well i won't even tell
ya i worked on that i worked
with that person recently ah on a
set and they walked past me in
the scene
and smelled so good well we could
say who it is okay now there's
a can't connect these two okay yea
we must yeah alright well let's go
i'll just tell the hotel took that
you're not i told them oh great
good and they said it was a
leave-in conditioner and wow free time fresh
would you tell her that she smells
good even though i haven't i will
not for probably yeah because i think
it's weird
okay it is funny though that can
that is like a smell can take
you out of something like you'd you
don't think about that when you're on
a set yeah but it's like to
find yourself thinking that smells so nice
i'm not this character anymore i still
do good i like smells i tell
you that i like smells that the
you know the delta lounges in in
the airports they
like heard of them they pump this
fragrance out at the entrance and it
was it's the perfume of my ex
girlfriend but and and i have of
it i hit yes isn't it strange
i've no connection to it to fund
name nobody i hadn't smelled it in
what a choice so like her few
thirty years or whatever and i was
like oh my
god that's what she smelled like every
single day it was it's very smart
i was like bujo during tv i'd
buy extra seats on the plane for
my boner definitely put dirt santos out
over it
i don't want anyone to see
turret hope it for be i'll um
i want smelled ah like this was
a few years ago i smelled my
first girlfriend's perfume it was wild like
it just rockets you back to the
past yeah it was so wild but
i remember she used to like
when we were like write notes to
each other she's just for a little
perfume on the note oh interesting yeah
yeah it's like real dangerously garbage castle
high school so why would bite high
school girlfriend be taught me to take
out the garbage because she was garbage
on your mom's side
go shovel the driveway really have her
fumes that i've worn like i'll go
through a phase with them and then
i smell it i'm like oh wow
is this twenty eighteen or like this
is like munoz is that time um
i had one horrible person in my
life from a very long loki oh
who wore the abercrombie cent so when
you walk past never coming it's very
triggering yeah
um because it just a pump that
shit out of there yeah yeah i
do smells should be illegal with abercrombie
i get it it's sort of like
just hey if you can if you
can stand this you deserve to be
in here and if you can't your
lawyer they so dark like why you
know what i mean hello sir is
the darkest store on the planet
the hollister hollister is like an version
of abercrombie b o but i remember
i went in there once i'm sure
i've told the story i went in
there when i was in hawaii once
and i had to get some shorts
cause i didn't have appropriate clothes with
me for some reason and i like
one in there and like i couldn't
see myself in the dresser mirror it
was so dark i could only see
my shorts it was like they didn't
want me to see the whole package
like there
fine get up you couldn't see your
pets i am glad to see me
um abercrombie um i loved so much
when i was in middle school and
i was allowed to purchase a few
things from there which were very special
to me never been in one oh
wow it was it was i would
say like two thousand that was like
peak abercrombie yeah amazing time um but
oh there's that documentary about it were
they take it down i don't like
yeah about
yeah i'm sure it's a horrible company
it's sad when a when a store
is no longer in vogue yeah it
so what now like will they ever
get back kind of like looked at
i did buy a couple things from
abercrombie randomly a few years ago where
i was like let me just see
what they've got and i kinda had
some fun going on the website but
it was a lot cheaper now i
only shop at river cheaper
quality wise yeah yeah well i'm i
think even the price was lower but
it was like the whole situation was
at least yeah newly shopware remote reminded
target but yeah no you have all
your marvel sweatshirt i believe this one
right now i'm wearing yellow nice and
you wouldn't you arch leave gentle your
marvel shirts hanging in a closet like
not allowing all my money i wore
one once
yeah but how you are the one
that made it seem like you bought
a ton of marvel's sweatshirt oh i
just bought a bunch of clothes i
bought that one thing he did i
know he did i know he definitely
let us believe that he let us
believe you guys that shirt a raglan
sleeve or a full longsleeve tee what
the monthly gee maybe if i push
it up like i'm in literally i
like it
classic little loopy i like that shirt
i do too i like that the
baseball tee yeah yeah yeah that's nice
it is it's a flattering cut should
we play sports this year no why
why what do you mean we shouldn't
start a team are you interested in
pickleball no not your broken what if
we stop
the bowling league the three of us
the swing of a league yeah you
can join leagues and then compete you
said what we started i don't think
ok well what for me is that
fun but is there something more fun
we could do paulo yeah mr paulo
no no lands horse bullet forceful
of course oh of course
so the shots for that note do
you have new years resolutions do you
are you doing that because this is
our first episode after the new year
oh thinking about this definitely i have
to get back into exercising i put
all the weight back on that loss
and i've i've realised i have to
accept that i'm like an up and
down guy i was a youth hath
yeah yeah yeah i don't know i
think it's so hard because i
like yeah it's like i because you
don't want to talk about those ryan
ah rosenberg um that number chosen berg
that um it's you get to a
point where you feel ah mentally healthier
saying that you know what i'm not
going to beat myself up about this
whatever but then you get past that
point you're like i shouldn't be
myself up a little bit yeah but
it is it's that the idea of
like loving yourself at any size or
whatever well first of all the idea
just hated yourself equally across now we're
talking welcome to my world easier to
attain but i like the idea of
when my idea of loving yourself at
all is such a
sing to me that i still grapple
with because it's not like a concept
that i was brought up with yeah
and it's you know it's like such
a strange business it's also like well
what does that feel like you know
the name of you if you love
yourself and i guess it's just like
you just need giving yourself a break
what you need more bd big dick
energy yeah
that's what self-love is yeah that's what
we used to was talking about yeah
but the greatest love of all is
big dick ibd yeah at the end
chicago's boudou
but it is like kinda goes
nobody can say for sure
did you say beatty i don't know
i think she i think she kind
of did she kind of wine maybe
but yeah but yeah it's like i
wanna i just wanna be like in
a healthier place mentally and physically like
i don't think my health is bad
right now but i know that i
feel better yeah
when i'm exercising regularly it's like you
have like your goal sorry i mean
to interpret the corner i do interrupt
all the time but i didn't mean
you didn't mean to that's that's what
every other time
do you have a good goal like
i'm gonna do this this this you
don't just say if you don't want
to well there's good habits that i
have here i just want to get
back a walk every morning are you
still doing the walks in the morning
or no i fallen off with that
but i but i i like going
to the gym like i when i
get it when i get into it
and i'm doing it and i get
into a rhythm with it i love
it
real i look forward to it you
know yeah but it's so easy to
get knocked off we knocked off for
a couple days but i also i
just have to figure out i've to
get i wanna get better at scheduling
things you know what i mean i
want to be more mindful about shit
like that so that i can have
more control over my own day you
know right and then hopefully not be
late all the time
and you know not get knocked off
course with things that i want to
do you know it's when you can
get into a groove or you look
forward to i mean when i i've
i've gone on vacation and worked out
like yeah yeah totally where it's like
i saw you on tour once not
maybe not a comedy banding tour but
i saw you in a hotel once
had like sketch fest
going down to the gym in the
hotel i'm like damn paul's really in
the group you know and it's like
yeah i mean for me breaking my
ankle and then oh going on tour
and having the baby has just really
yeah yeah sure havoc on me and
so now it's like going upstairs is
fucking really hard with my knees right
now ah damn and
carrying the baby i'm just like i
got you in the new year
get back into it and just lose
weight so i can just even carry
the baby up and down yeah you
know it's just like she's only gonna
get bigger no really yeah shit that's
right but threatened legal crunchy promised to
get in and gain weight yes she
did get smaller i've been hernias resolution
was to gain weight
she did get smaller after birth yeah
yeah so that's not true okay but
from now only going out from now
on tuesday lose weight they tend to
le tend to lose a little weight
yeah after us we're and then you
have to like get them back up
to their births i know yeah get
fast this weird you're weird you told
her that yeah it's like yeah i'd
lose it's gonna be her first memory
yep just remember my dad telling me
i was weird when i was one
hour old what if you could remember
every single thing from back god dammit
i want a curse that would be
marilu henner does
like i was a thursday i think
it kinda sucked on a nipple yeah
i remember i was hungry i started
crying
she always just remember
huh
i was wearing a diaper
oh i remember which diaper that was
when i shit yeah it was a
white with rose out in public but
i was like i'm gonna fall asleep
anyway yeah what about you yeah what
about you one of mine is to
read more and so i made the
goal of twenty four books that's two
a month which i feel like is
reasonable i'd like to go more than
that but i don't subject our amount
yeah i don't know if they
it's twenty four i don't want to
overwhelm myself and then not do it
at all so i'm gonna say twenty
four okay and where when are you
gonna read these at least at night
and why and where and in i
guess i could be in better on
the couch are you going to then
go to bed earlier and because here's
my issue with reading the phone away
from me here's my
my issue with reading books is no
matter what time if be at eight
pm nine pm i go you know
what that's enough tv or whatever i'm
gonna go upstairs and read a book
i'm asleep within ten minutes yeah but
that's also good special so i think
i'll i'll try to be more you
know bring and that's part of like
bringing the book in my bag if
i have a few minutes
as opposed to scrolling yeah we didn't
we didn't know screens in the bedroom
rule i did that for a while
and i think maybe no tax that
we don't have tv we don't have
a tv either yeah yeah the screens
janie every once in a while once
that like if we go to a
hotel times it sounds great like wouldn't
it be like at home if we
if whatever we've had yeah i'm watching
msnbc at eleven thirty at night think
if we could watch an episode of
suits it's maybe the ultimate indulgence to
have a tv at the foot of
your bed i used to have a
tv in my bedroom and i remember
falling asleep to the tv and i
just i like it so much better
without yeah i i don't watch that
much tv since having a baby but
i did use to watch so much
and i feel like it's kind of
better for me not to have it
available everywhere i turn
i love tv how you too yeah
i love that i love the box
itself yeah you just like to look
at it yeah i like that there's
so much later than my other thing
is going up over my head all
so more exercising and making keeping my
i've been trying to do more and
eating better and stuff so just q
how many push ups can you do
you know i don't know but
i do have she really like real
arm muscles now really i'm like actually
really shocked it's just from how goes
your back let's see those guys i'm
scared i'm scared oh this is my
um i got blood drawn and they
continued okay so we're you're not dramatic
trying to say you're not going to
be able to hiding behind the microphones
right there it's right there okay
okay yeah i mean it's not high
level but it's certainly not all there
for having it's there before
it's honestly really good yeah yeah he
squeezed my arm it did go down
when he squeezed anyone hey i'm that
guy but i did yeah but it
was invitation my fingers are still there
yeah it was good
i don't tend to walk around flexing
ah mahmood crocker yeah you suddenly started
hating so no paul and i have
to talk i remember a comic that
we know years ago was on a
fitness kiss it was it hagar the
horrible yeah do you remember what he
looks so ripped
tweets by the seller so we can
add a second year so horrible when
ah both arms jesus when um this
this comic we knew this is years
ago got into a fitness kick he
was going to the gym every day
it's not karen tonic i remember know
i don't know him maybe someday when
i met him and i said i
remember like
callebs and vaccine here mice seeing him
in largo and ah i think like
he was in front of me i
was trying to get past him and
i touched his arm and it was
fuckin solid as a rock really i
was like wow knows this is i'll
tell you later the answer may surprise
you really yes yeah because does what
not now i do think the arm
my arms getting stronger is solely from
picking her up and putting it on
all day yeah i don't think that's
i my i do a lot of
pelamis these days but it's not i
don't like my arms are like getting
really strong when you put rocks in
her pockets yeah yeah yeah that's smart
but she's like twenty two pounds now
maybe a little twenty years old you're
gonna say
i'm like what what's that up and
twenty pounds that's my goal weight oh
my i just talked about my my
knee yes please yeah i had my
physical ideas my blood drawn and the
draw
they tend to have an easier time
on one arm than the other side
like something to that arm first today
it was just coming oh did you
drink enough water i don't know probably
not i went to the doctor for
a physical and they were like just
there like you are so dehydrated we
cannot get any blood out of you
they were like oh we can't get
any blood
out of you they eventually switched arms
and got it yeah it's like like
go and go go drink some water
like now we can't find the vein
we can't get any blood we just
couldn't get any yeah yeah they're like
you need the size never goes drink
walk over water was coming in then
it stopped and then she's like oh
it stopped to get and then i
felt her pulled under
is that do you watch them like
a needle oh no no no i
never do i don't watch them put
the needle because i'm afraid i'm gonna
flinch but once they put it in
then you look down i never looked
i always look away assuming job i
don't look at all i so wild
to me to watch my blood fill
that thing up it's like wow that
weird yeah and it looks you know
what i love that looks like a
rich beautiful red wow i love the
texture of it yes the segwit blood
of the innocence yes yeah um i
love it i love watching i don't
have an issue with also love they
say i have good veins yeah if
they look my arm they say oh
great that's that's very that your body
is terrible but your veins i'm just
your body's here you actually getting your
blood drawn versus your body's terrible
i'm here for them
saying you just get one owners because
they were want
i'm in the medical videos we should
get more than one i know unfair
it is i also think if you
lose weight it should never come back
on but what if you knew it
too for what i mean you if
you lost weight because you were sick
and then you needed the weight oh
right right no i think it should
be if it's intentional okay it just
sucks they work out and get toned
it should stay that way but yes
it just sucks that like a year
a year was it eaten yeah a
year ago i was like working out
all the time gain a lot of
muscle super skinny yeah and now it's
all gone yeah yeah it's it's not
fair it should not be like how
can we get a whole second
but nothing else regenerates i know that's
like i'm getting enough here to die
like you'd come in yeah when you
should switch the old ones out when
you use brand-new and you've heard the
chief write another one just she gaps
right hey
my floater in my eye no no
loner um floater of what i have
flowed or for us
it's debris i don't know it's just
a little it's ah it's part of
the gel of your i can kind
of come detached and be floating in
your eyes but i was having it
where i couldn't see past it and
i was feeling kind of like this
might be bad so then i it
was lasting for like a week and
then i went into the doctor and
they took the pictures of my eye
and you could see it which i
thought that was very
validating because there's a party going on
crazy yeah yeah yeah more than loader
is like call me crazy narrative yes
yes because it's like a semi invisible
light yeah like it's not it's actually
a thing floating in the eye they
could see it and then the there
is a surgery you could do but
it wasn't that dramatic but they were
like the other option is you just
wait and eventually your eyes will
see around it and like i still
see it sometimes it's really annoying yeah
it's nice photos i haven't got them
in awhile my boot is so bad
i stuff is very scary i know
you know i have that i've i've
i believe i've told you that said
that like ah like sort of crumbly
pigment in my eye that causes pressure
and yeah glaucoma so every once in
awhile i'll have to go to an
ophthalmol
just to get checked out and sometimes
they will if it's if it's bad
they will zap lasers into my eyes
wow just like star wars laser sources
what does it make the sound
it breaks up the um the the
pigment that's like collecting in a certain
place where it's not supposed to be
so it levels it's like so complicated
like they show me the thing like
weird understand is that where you're trying
to say yeah i mean donna how
to explain i don't know how to
downtown for you guy that's okay you
don't have to
just i bad laser i know you're
good they should make good eye pad
these are good we have to take
a break we'll be right back
and we're back whereby me tell you
something if you thought we weren't back
also you were wrong little people in
the curtain yeah we don't just look
at our phones during the breaks oh
sure we look at look at our
phones but we also lose we also
chat with each other we're real
friends in real life we tell stories
that you can't hear yeah yes oh
i should've told you who the comedian
was well i'll tell you that express
dammit um how that ah do you
remember carol anne maryland real friends know
carol and marilyn yeah carolyn marilyn carroll
and marilyn no i don't know them
there was a talk show
a syndicated talk show and their hook
was i mean look at this up
just the host of the show they
were friends i know what you're taught
carroll maryland real friends unlike every other
host and co-host of any other show
who hate each other they despise each
other only talk on camera
but they what was funny was as
you watched the show since their friendship
use integrated you could see their friendship
to say oh like it's not working
you could see one oh this comedian
one was clearly better at it than
the other one and was like i
so mad that i have to do
this with you oh wow that's so
sad it was on abc
from june tenth ninety six to may
thirtieth nineteen ninety seven and it was
an hour long daytime talk variety show
when i watched it for awhile and
i don't know i couldn't tell you
why until you're interesting i think i
just kind of team fame as the
comedy duo known as the mommy's the
mom that's romo that's right the mommy
so yeah and this
this is like pre social media yes
they would have been huge on social
yeah or would they know yeah or
would they be the what were they
the sugar babies who are the people
who may be scabies
oh who are the people the try
guys and the shy guys they would
be like to try guys now wait
there was like it was like a
woman's auxiliary of the try guys called
something baby sia because the wife i
feel bad talking about other podcasters but
um the the why the the wife
that was cheated on was something baby
adultery baby
sorry drag guys you've been roasted by
freedom
yeah only monks later on where i'm
waiting we finally decided we did toe
to toe talked about google's you generally
do you think the mommies today would
have been as big as the guy
who draws the comics who hates her
husband clearly way who says there is
one who draws his colleagues puts about
its to grab and it's like me
getting ready
ie for a trip with the family
and she has to do all this
shit husband getting ready okay i've got
my bum i was on whatever yeah
yeah yeah yeah but every it was
like every day thing that it was
like maybe your husband did a bad
person like yeah this isn't funny food
babies yeah our producer matt says food
food ab
thank you i'll producer
the only reason i know this is
because of the very funny s and
l brenton ah gleason sketch brendan gleason
of ah yes from banshees of yes
yes and from lake placid yes yeah
and where he's trying to explain this
on cnn you see she's a food
baby
it's very funny so
this just taken father of donal that's
right crash crash that's right what what
did you see him in was it
star wars or no let's say he's
not hot and star what about in
his black mirror black mirror is where
i first was introduced him about my
crushes about time or maybe i was
interested in wow what's her name hayley
attwell yeah um yeah about time is
one
my favorite but to be fair i
have more of a crush on peggy
carter than i do and yeah oh
yeah with the shield and the ah
well when she became captain britain oh
mah sure yeah oh yeah i've i've
seen you've seen it i've seen it
that's the thing it's like i've seen
who've seen it so no one can
argue that i've seen even if i
don't weigh in it's like i still
know what you're talking
thing about yeah i remember why she's
better for it watching some ways it
is i were watching agent carter and
seeing some comedians turn up on that
and i'm like yeah what the fuck
all this shit i have to put
up with for the way i dress
and i don't even get to be
in any of these periods i know
really should be right i'm ready to
go what are we talking about get
my clothes i got a mustang
yeah there's a ton of hats i
saw something the other day i'm like
why isn't lauren in this honestly i
was recently why why is lauren laka
story i'll tell you off mike i
was like wow you know what i
had that question all the time yeah
ah i love to know more um
but yeah um don't all great guy
don't all great
guys you think he knows you exist
no did you is that good or
is that bad he might know i
exist um it's okay i don't need
him tonight i don't mean in the
general sense of like yes he knows
there are seven billion people on plow
no i mean like maybe oh shit
when dough wrong missha yeah it's herself
to wrong missy
well i did love on that podcast
that you sent me this which i
have talked about this for the sea
they were like sandwiches or something i'm
not sandwiches like food off menu yeah
yes yeah yeah there's they're very funny
but sandwiches but food yeah it's the
more general topic of yeah not restricted
just to sandwich yeah um wait wait
wait wait wait did you watch
the patient i was the serial killer
i actually am a little scared of
that show but i've watched like four
episodes i think he's great in it
yeah he's great he's so good and
his accent is so good it's so
good he's doing an american accent oh
is any wallace x mokena two i've
never seen him doing yeah right yeah
yeah yeah i think i saw him
in that before i
kind of really knew who we were
yeah he's great yeah maybe i was
a wild movie ma'am so it's fucking
wild that guy makes wild movies that
guys why should i watch it sparkle
yeah you definitely should yeah it's weird
they're both great oscar isaac is great
he's like some sasquatch act in boxing
yeah during it if i had known
this little damp watched it a million
years ago yeah
um yeah i like oscar isaac i
have he's one of those people i
have a fondness doing tonight impression did
you watch fish may may nine eight
marriage i went about looking me up
and woke up as a main night
scenes from
i did not watch scenes from a
marriage because it seemed like a drag
yeah i liked that that was intense
janney watched it and then when i
saw them like walking off the set
and stuff now kerry said i was
like why is this at heart really
bothered me and i actually should like
read something about it because i yeah
remember being like wait what was to
make
your new year's resolution is to read
that's true i'll check that out i
feel like it's like what am i
supposed to get so they're actors doing
it yeah why let me say this
chance you don't understand jessica chastain yeah
a person i think is clearly a
good actor yeah but i don't she
doesn't do anything for me as an
actor you
i mean i like started i don't
think she ain't bad yeah but she
doesn't it doesn't move me ever you
know like i'm watching george if anything
watch that you might have you might
i felt was a jiminy glick movie
she did did she do that i
mean oh tammy faye yeah that's actually
how good that seems so fun to
get to play on a big character
like that yeah and being like wow
huh
yeah you know something like those good
yeah yeah well do you want to
say yes we should all do it
and choose best okay you do it
okay no i mean we should all
make a movie oh okay we should
each make a baby yes and michael
showalter direct oh yes oh i love
that yeah that's simultaneously yeah he
says actually it's going to be whiter
yard said yeah and we all have
to do action when he says good
we all have to cut no matter
what's happening
might be a good idea yeah it's
so far nui a good idea you
were in a biopic playing someone famous
who would you be who would i
be is there someone either physically ugly
people throughout history have been compared to
online honestly
yeah huh no but i mean i'm
either either you're ugly by the way
so much right i guess what i
mean is like someone were you've said
like oh my god her life or
his life is so interesting and i
could probably pull it off if i
don't i don't know if i have
one off the top of my head
oh okay my mom always said that
it should be in the biopic about
gabby gifford i was like why would
i be the person who was too
good
job why would that be me of
all i would constantly wonder you like
someone who gets shot in the head
your own mother i can see you
playing someone who's only in their fucking
head
the mom when i say take it
he's literally just like i actually i
don't know how it would it would
not be comedic like i'm like the
person you being married to an astronaut
okay that part that part that poor
um what do you call what oh
what do you want to be do
it
goddamn it's really hard question because it's
like it's gonna be i always think
yeah also like the big main actors
like christian bale or whatever whatever will
like pluck their hair out of their
bald head and stuff like che totally
change their you know when you don't
really dick cheney i think when you
don't have to look anything like the
person okay yeah yes like
it's just who you would want to
yeah their life story right you know
what i mean this is not somebody
that i admire but um the story
of um h h holmes who was
a famous ah serial killer in chicago
um around the time of the world's
fair he had one piece referred to
as
the murder castle well um and he
like built this crazy house and he
lured people there because people come from
out of town and he would link
to webinar and kill them and all
these various ways it's like a very
very dark story crazy there's there's what
that book is the devil in the
white city yeah yeah they they just
saw that it's about that and the
world's fair at the same time it's
a great book but they just heard
i've heard i didn't just fall apart
like keanu just dropped out of it
or whatever so it gets in they've
been trying to make a tom cruise
is going to do it for and
i think that and and i think
he honored keanu was getting made and
he just dropped out of it so
it's available you should do it sure
if those guys i mean i guess
they're done looking for famous but yeah
so i think i read it too
what should i just tell them i'm
open yeah like just volunteered on avail
a lot just luck if you can't
get anybody i'll do it yeah but
those two were we were talking about
this recently they're they're very contemporary actors
and i don't think it would have
worked with them at in that time
period right now
oh i see i like keanu could
pull anything off i can take yeah
but i mean a lot to not
hey tom cruise no you don't think
tom cruise can pull anything off well
we were taught we were talking about
this on another show it's true we
can say now is yeah it's our
interview with vampire vampires he's just ridiculous
play the vampire let's not die
like a massacre him anytime he was
on screen people would think doing things
things they think what that he was
like more of a renaissance renaissance renaissance
dam canada yeah
i would play watch that actually now
that you're saying you can view the
vampire yeah have fun this man it's
not good
it's not good i think that was
such a big movie at the time
why i think it was such a
pic with noise that i feel like
it was it was a huge deal
because these books were these books were
like a huge thing and so the
the first movie adaptation there's big controversy
about tom cruise being cast and all
that shit and oh so that's such
a modern
er yes but when you watch it
now it's terrible okay yeah i would
yeah people that said that was bad
idea but right good call on the
money yeah i would play jesus of
nazareth wow he's great guy he's going
i like judas that's fair i doubt
i'd agree that's what i'd be oh
yeah yeah we should do the movie
together oh i mean they knew each
other i don't know but i'm thinking
how am i going to do a
full bio
i'll pick on mary if i'm also
watching a holistic and we would discuss
like do it marvel style yeah so
you're introduced to the end of the
jesus movie like mom what are you
doing here and then the next movie
is your yeah i love yeah and
then who shows up at the end
honey we're out of figs it's joseph
and that's my movie yeah that's really
what's going back
backwards so from jesus to mayor yeah
yeah i'm sure some of them do
yeah okay yeah i like it iron
man came out before captain america that's
a great point aig you right by
the way you are because iron man
was the first one the first avenger
yeah oh no captain america was first
avenger it was the first movie where
they were like oh these p
people want to see this and then
they were like let's go to the
forties kid a king yeah and yeah
the part where chris evans is small
it's so funny so much it's so
funny he's a little teeny scrawny guy
yeah and then he gets the muscles
and he's a big normal guy yeah
lorne would you if he were cast
in like
the wasp know like a wasp type
role yeah would you get jacked for
it yeah yeah yeah how would you
do it whatever they tell you to
do i was they would have to
tell you i wish they'd set me
up with a trainer and a diet
and i would eat and do everything
they said you would i wouldn't mind
if they did that right now
i find ya for your gonna do
it right now yeah me up all
right i'll just tell you i have
to cook here's where this idea of
it being your job to work out
yeah yeah where that's your day where
it's like you don't have to do
anything else just worked out somebody's going
to cook for you this is all
taken care of the cooking is where
i really get stuck because i'm like
if somebody just made me all my
meals here's here's what we should do
hire each other chefs yeah like that
i don't want to hey i don't
want to pay for a chef for
myself as a gift but as a
gift i'll hire one for you you
will have to hire a full-time chef
for you hired me that sounds great
whenever someone tells you about a private
chef just like this weird to me
just hanging out and then
making like occasionally they combined go i
made all these snacks you buy oh
okay and then it just seemed so
great well i mean it sounds fun
creeps me for when you white people
over it's just a number i think
they feel hey it feels like part
of the family at that point if
they are i'll tell you who it
was later i can i will tool
swap i know somebody
like that as well now i don't
know them i know someone who went
to someone's house that was there yeah
and it made sense but it's wild
but but wouldn't it take care of
so many of the issues you have
of like at six o'clock going like
i'm hungry but we don't have anything
in the house let's order three pizzas
yeah you know no because then they
go no no no i made you
know not made you
this nice order three pizzas you have
a problem
they're small there's nothing in the house
let's order three pizzas well you don't
oh well yeah some faraway emeralds eating
a pizza no here's my this guy
hey here's my point of view when
you order p o from
set it up like tiktok okay p
o v p o v no wait
when you order from ah from a
restaurant and the p o v is
used so wrong people get it wrong
all the fucking time table on video
that's when you order from a place
like ubereats or whatever i always try
to order because you're paying a service
charge and the tip and everything i
always try to order
like three meals worth yeah so that
you can then don't have to do
it again the next day or whatever
you know i left like last night
i got you got salad delivered and
i also got one for the next
day yeah exactly jersey mike's yeah hell
i'll get three sandwiches and you know
what i'll get a mix way wow
but then i get squishy are we
doing dads right now loveseats machine or
are we doing guys not getting paid
for the guy gets pushy way we
gotta go we gotta take hey i
lost my train of thought i'd take
a triangle near
hey
bahais are back and it's time to
play reacher revealed all our secrets during
the break yeah how about that did
we all enjoy it i did i
did enjoy the show i enjoyed hearing
yours not revealing mine oh that's right
you didn't reveal anywhere a little bit
like i did reveal one to him
but yeah revealing it you just didn't
hear me oh okay yeah
interesting yeah alright well the saucer isn't
that funny i guess so i hear
three charm it's time to play for
three chair or instead us up this
game wherein no let's i'll i'll do
it because i know who sent it
and what it's called i know who
center what it's called this is word
alley oop submitted by tim war
we've played before and um basically we
just text each other a word it's
just a simple and we have to
use the word in a scene and
then at the end of the scene
we guess what word it was yes
so we're gonna each try to make
it okay i couldn't have explained that
as well no but you didn't know
the title of it you didn't know
tim ward's name that's true but i
although i guess i could just stand
in there at the end yeah by
the way this was submitted by tim
when you could have i'm torn on
this you know what one of my
new year's resolutions was to apologize to
learn more so i'm sorry wow wait
from last year yeah
or knows their resolution this year yeah
yeah he said it into the water
alright this is good i love to
of those apologies as time goes on
yeah um alright let's play the game
so sorry what happened no less ok
actually i don't think i like this
i don't like this kind of post
like focus attention and by the way
we're we all i'm gonna text lower
in lawrence gonna check paul paul's gonna
text me yeah but um we we
tried to say the word as like
under the radar as possible so that
we the the no one guesses what
they are do you think that it
should be
that it has to be said more
than once or no no just won't
no once okay yeah just once but
ah we're trying to text each other
yeah it's maybe ah the other person
wouldn't use normally so that they stand
out and you have to sort of
like fly under the radar with it
as much as does everyone have their
word yes yes yes
her aunt can't
hey guys it's me lou reed
if you want to take a log
on the wild side ah not not
really lu i know you ask us
you don't want to go to the
apollo
you don't want to go go go
i really please don't talk about the
color girls either really you know they
say diddy diddy diddy diddy ah hey
actually also i'm just kind of passed
by here um excuse me so much
oh hey sorry are we in your
way this is my friend lou maybe
you know i've heard of your socks
they give you some advice sure don't
lose your head
even when you give it hit do
diddy diddy diddy today apologize actually don't
do that i only bite penises oh
hello sounds like value would help that
bash is your jaw wired shut
it is from biting a penis it
is i was this is a punishment
um what do you do do you
bite like soft penises hard beans like
if if my venus was venus obama
rocks let's make it about you sir
that's no but my dogs if my
penis were softer if it was a
long gated would it be like something
that would i'm not talking to you
i'm actually walking
yeah i'm cooler than him what hey
were you flying miami f l a
no one is cooler and low breed
thank you
i'm actually just i'm opening the store
for it behind them just i mean
just pull up this big guy oh
you oh you work here you own
the store yeah divinity
did you just say do did he
didn't did you did you did he
fled
this is my shop as i'm selling
flowers um just all sorts of things
and you know surreptitiously throwing in a
few little sides like gummies and weeds
thing ooh do you have anything for
somebody who thought they were deed for
a day
diddy diddy diddy diddy diddy godly why
am i hanging out with you you
are so cool i guess guess oh
yes i do have something for that
oh yeah yeah attendees green ones ooh
let me drive
good
forty dollars oh wait i thought these
were free samples because he said let
me try one no i said these
are good and you should have the
green one well you said let me
try one like that it's heavily idea
to play something that you defend and
then i said hey babe think it
will go the outside diddy diddy doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo
okay every day yeah we've got it
alright what ah so no ah you
have to you have to guess possible
policy i know sorry word yeah lauren
has to guess my i think yours
i just have no idea i'm like
ah
no i mean guess i would guess
sample but i don't think that's right
mine was elongated
okay okay now paul you really were
something you ignore thanks lawrence is that
right yeah was your word gummy know
what was surreptitiously i didn't even yeah
yeah through which yes she and you
i feel like you chose lou reed
because of the word yeah which was
no but i was not paying attention
because i was so thrown by your
choice to be free at the beginning
i guess wild is the only thing
i can say but volume value yeah
okay interesting yeah i like it gotta
admit flawless lou reed impression is is
lee louie it was a really good
and i didn't even get it right
away
why you chose it even though i
gave you the word sa right so
now do we want to go the
other way i'll give paul see other
way the other way while you chow
the sick
alright so i give a word to
loughran
alright i have texted paul paul is
texting lauren lauren meanwhile is texting me
this is this is the exciting part
of the game as far as i'm
concerned where we're all silently looking down
at our phones texting one word to
each other on the text
to each other okay okay
alright
ah gentlemen hey there's an issue with
the funds the funds slows an issue
with ooh
it's an issue with the funds i
was doing our banking what's going on
with your outfit ah my outfit is
a list of all it's it's a
drawing of a suit on just a
very long t-shirt yeah that we're having
a problem with i just like it's
really accentuated the point here is oh
you're bumping up again yeah it's just
like oh i'm having a bit of
i don't really care
about all of your body say oh
please i'm talking about my body at
all please do not say your tea
you don't say your food but please
show me please tell me there's enough
money left over to fund by gregorian
cho yeah
when he has been allocated a misallocate
all over the place it is a
mess ooh oh ooh hey piles of
money were that supposed to be i
her alright so much is going wrong
and you are who you know i
hear both fire
i heard and you both owe me
fifty thousand fifty thousand should settle whoa
hey i have to ah my fire
oh for sure d
those buy into a nation although you
ooh alright yeah i guess oh sure
is it a gregorian or chance is
indonesian i got just under the one
alright years was misallocated or allocated um
ah yeah it was i thought you
give it to me i was like
wow you're doing okay paul you gotta
guess i wasn't paying attention to you
goods so i don't know i was
having too much fun singing
which would it surprise you to know
it was super
it's just friday
which is why i've brought it up
you gotta admit like nah ah good
job you really did you really good
i think that dropping the fish suit
on a t-shirt
i know you tried to steer me
away i stopped talking to my buddies
yeah i did not want that
okay i enjoyed that hey you know
what we have a phone number it's
haha imho yeah and i understand we
have a voicemail
producer ma producer is gonna find it
for us matt opera juicer if you
want to call us you know ask
us for advice or something that prompt
a discussion or whatever we're happy to
we're happy to hear that yeah don't
just get on there and ramble like
trying to keep it keep under thirty
percent three second
ids
alright anywhere from three to five seconds
i don't know that he had one
ready to go but he did okay
did okay good good good alright here
we go let's listen to it this
is a voicemail
hello paul guy lauren um i got
a little problem that you guys might
be able to help out with i
just moved into a new home you
shouldn't buy furniture dog small black dog
and really around more and he is
being harassed by the crows local
oh the local groans okay that he's
from out of town crow county you
might have some solutions to help me
really get some peace offering to the
crows or you know something to protect
my dog and i'm not they're gonna
go after him yeah well this is
tough because you can't yeah i guess
my that's my boy hey shut the
fuck up thanks crows are incredibly intelligent
and you
they and humans can be friend them
yes yeah i know someone who is
trying to make this happen you should
go online and figure out how to
please the crows because you can leave
them through my example offering because i
know that nobody eats asking us for
ideas to how it's a crazy shows
rather than saying oh i'm
tell him to go well i don't
have i have ideas honey well then
good i'm glad i talked first
you jumped in there i know that
you can be friend then you can
be friend them a good thing here's
what i've what i've heard is if
you if you are consistent with it
like say they like cashews right so
you put cashews in a certain place
but you want to do it at
the same time every day so always
be cash they pick up on well
whatever it
is so they pick up on the
idea that this is a regular thing
yeah they get they get they you're
like their cashew connect yes they get
the knowledge that oh this guy fuckin
does this everyday greg will always come
here and then they will like you
because they do have long memories and
they can also they can befriend you
but they could also remember you as
somebody who they do not like yeah
somebody memrise gary remember fay
faces um if you can find something
called a crow box which is a
way that you can also make money
from these crows like a chromebox is
essentially like a vending machine for you
could put nuts seeds whatever and there
the crows like to eat um and
you can get kits online and they
pay for the what you do is
you put some coins
around there yeah they put the coins
in and they get their aclu actually
yes so then what they were doing
they'll go fucking get coins from other
places and coins everywhere yes wow i
make like yeah yeah yeah that's right
what do you use the coins for
to buy more food for the crows
i mean it's a fish
just so you know you'll put it
in your bank account and yeah let
it grow yeah you take it to
an ira take a bunch of quarters
to the bank and say i have
this many monies yeah and then you
get a lollipop yeah you know a
surprising amount about cripples i think they're
fair like the person to to ask
about the best yeah that was i
ignatian so close
things which was asked paul yeah and
go among um all right that's gonna
do it for us thank you for
that question whoever you were um yes
please do not tell us your own
numbers tell us you don't want to
know the names um if you want
to follow us on social media at
three dm usa
if you wanted call us paul already
have the name of the temple i
said the name of the phone number
yep and if you want to email
us a three cheer three m usa
at gmail dot com yes if you
want to listen to all episodes we're
releasing where of course three visiting on
the two that's right and ah if
you want to hear ad free episodes
go to stitcher
premium or cbp world dot com and
paul has already put his headphones away
as my phone charger it's your phone
charge my phone nope that's all i'm
just packing my bag okay you guys
are mentally out of here yep yep
soon to be followed by physically thank
you so much for listening we love
ya here everyday
buddy
uh