three
oh
i actually was listening to my recording
when i sent it to josh for
the last episode and it just sounds
so insane just to hear me with
no music going huh
step three let's say let's get the
stems from this episode lauren going through
oh oh gotta get the stems
ooh give me those snail damn i
eat it all from the seas to
the stems welcome back to night oh
la la la la la la la
la love the ticket for bad guys
look like
welcome back to freedom the show yeah
welcome back to it whoever's listening for
the first if you're yeah oh if
you're listening you better have listened before
if you're a new listener go back
going to be lost you honestly would
you be lost or would you just
be like you'd probably be like oh
there's a new story yeah yeah
you would think every story was new
i think it would be like why
is this fun i think you would
be confused as to why someone recommended
it to you and i think you
would realize that life is finite and
you have better things to do
but but well but if that's you
and you fit the box and please
stay
if you fit the box please say
if your box shaped me do you
if you're if you're one of those
boxy droids from star wars yeah guy
who looked like a box v h
dash ten thirty three
agenda guess that was my nickname in
high school
speaking of boxes best ah best end
to any pilot ever the show profit
oh yeah i know nastar the best
ending of any tv this tv show
ran three episodes and the end of
the third episode or the end of
oh right it ran a whole season
did you run a whole season yeah
it's something yanked pretty quick the pilot
this sort of well it's not like
before you talk about the end you've
got to talk about like the beginning
and
the middle of who made it and
who started it and who's on it
was a she did gina johnson know
who knows who um i don't remember
anything about acceptable rice well he's he
there's some incest he know he ah
adrian perez isn't incest adrian pasdar is
a scheming businessman whose yeah troll of
everybody ooh yeah
and ah is always you know he's
super rich and where he's money money
money i let my suits and no
it was cancelled after three episodes my
gosh i don't know how i saw
more than that but um but he
ah so he's the scheming rich guy
right and then just suits to give
him some humanity at a certain point
in the middle of the show people
are like why are you such an
asshole why how did you turn out
this way and he's like because when
i grew up i had nothing i
grew up on the streets i live
in a cardboard box with my family
and ever since that day i decided
i was never going to return to
those days again and it runs like
okay whatever standard characterization and then at
the end of the some of the
other characters say
at the end of the episode he
finally does some like really evil shocking
thing to someone and then he goes
home to his penthouse strips off all
of his clothes and his entire penthouse
is bare except for a cardboard box
and then he jumps into it naked
and goes to sleep she jumps into
it he's like
mcduck swimming pool full of money
and and just oh so fun so
good oh hey you know adrian oh
i'm so happy for you guys
adrian pasdar of course the subject of
gas later by the chicks oh that's
right because that's her natalie maines ex
husband's right it's like so husband he
turns out to be a guideline or
get a slide or that would be
terrible to have a song written about
you wouldn't eat if it was negative
for sure yeah um
if there are so like there was
a song written about me i love
your muscular body and i was like
oh that's okay and you wrote the
song right do you feel like you've
even tour with slating is being overused
because i feel like i'm hearing it
for every situation under the sun yes
yeah and then i saw there's a
new
show called gas slit or something like
that you know people jump on these
words oh yeah they jump on
it's that easy these words michael richards
these words these were no no ah
i forgot about that yeah yeah well
we want to recovery don't look what
a recovery imagine someone having to look
it up
ah imagine someone knowing who michael richards
is kramer my dear boy did you
watch the friends reunion were you write
united and i did watch it i
did to my hippo i haven't seen
it no no yeah um you know
i was really excited to sit down
and watch it and
i was pretty excited when i saw
that it was two hours long um
but yeah i overall i enjoyed a
lot of things about it i did
get depressed afterwards oh really because you're
no longer young kind of no i'm
not kidding like that's what a lot
a lot of nostalgia is just like
remember when i was young and everything
was yeah
and it was so focused on just
remembering it as opposed to i don't
know i guess i don't know what
i thought would be but i i
it made me feel kind of sad
and then i was like wow it's
been seventeen years like i don't know
like it was just like yeah i
don't think i wasn't like i'm old
but i was kind of like
wow that felt like um a lot
of time has passed and then i
feel like i was like seeing until
their psyches and like it was just
like a lot right do you what
what was it mainly like them just
kind of going down memory lane and
james corden asking what about this what
about well it wasn't it wasn't just
the james
cord and stuff which i was happy
about like they see a lot of
time when they first arrived at the
actual studio they used to tape add
at a recreation of the set i
think they spent a whole day there
at least one or two days there
that's um and they kept inner cutting
stuff but so i think presentations yeah
they reenact
did screw they re-read scripts they played
games that they played on the show
all that kind of stuff without james
corden because the james core right was
there wasn't a lot of meat on
that bone i thought i agree but
i i didn't i didn't need them
to be like a fashion show with
like justin bieber it's so interesting yeah
here's my dirty foggy lady handling like
a from runway fashion show of like
highlights cup care ads ah listen they
levine like doing these friendly crawford cindy
crawford doing friends costumes and stuff like
that but here's my theories is that
when you to get the friends reunion
they had to pay
pay those six people and inordinate amount
of money and once you have that
amount of well they have some working
since friends but once you have that
kind of money sunk into something you
have to start hedging your bets everywhere
and that's where the lady gaga of
it in the ceo last word wrong
but we didn't have to be yes
no you don't need any of that
stuff but once they say
send all that money they're like we
better put bts in this for ten
seconds otherwise we won't get the bts
fans wadala actually actually like the part
where they just talk to fans who
had gone through a hard normal fans
and friends was a show they watched
when they were going through something hard
and and that made me cry and
i thought lisa kudrow was fantastic and
she
seems really down to earth and matt
le blog seems really down to earth
i mean they oh they all seem
fine but it was just like i
think i wanted more of just them
talking yeah and and just a conversation
well that's what i did changing tamarind
and stuff all that much because in
front of a live audience you're putting
on a show instead of yeah like
talking you know yeah yeah and i
like when they would be like oh
do you remember this and someone's like
oh not really like when they were
just like hanging out that was more
interesting to me then someone would say
do you remember this the other person
would say oh not really yeah kinda
like it was feel like they were
like talking about if they've watched the
show and some of them have never
really seen it and like then they
would i'd liked how they showed the
clips but then i think
i think that's what made me feel
kind of sad was like seeing the
clips and then like seeing them talk
with them and then they also said
that they haven't been they haven't gotten
in the same room since then and
there's no witches like not like yeah
really you were like i think two
of them probably moved to new york
or whatever or one of em you
know what it means so it's like
all six haven't been in the same
room
it makes a long time though for
thirteen years yeah thank you there would
be some sort of informal like hey
let's get up let's get together whenever
so when i feel like at ten
year reunion what it made sense yeah
privately privately publicly seventeen is good
publicly i was like why not twenty
why are we doing seventeen and yeah
why not wait till you're in the
ground because the movie seventeen again get
buried next to each other than learning
matthew perry right
it was in his honor i like
movies where people become young again yeah
i wanna see
i want to see if i can
guess what was in the friends fashion
show okay yeah wait how what what's
let's do friends trivia first of all
so podcasts what was in the friends
fashion show i want to say ah
they recreated when ah the alpha when
joey wore all of chandler's clothes yeah
okay it's the big biting but he
joey actually put it on not in
that leblanc not in a metal block
put it on okay he disappeared from
the stage he like he he and
no one saw him get off stage
and then he put that on secret
well there's no way that they didn't
see him get off i don't know
matthew matthew perry's snuck off
during the show too and when you
just left he's not maybe he was
maybe he was marks he's marketing sweatshirts
yeah sweatshirts i posted about this on
twitter are not on instagram i somehow
got on this mailing list for it's
just like famous people merch and the
people listed were matthew perry
putti pie the weasley twins from harry
potter i saw you post this i
didn't know if that was real yeah
it was real it was real and
matthew perry has a merch has some
merch line that's that i guess he
participates in because he gives some of
that he must get some of the
money like matthew perry merch it's like
oh yeah he's like modeling it on
insta
graham yeah there's there's a could just
be anymore of a t-shirt yeah yeah
yeah it's all that it's all could
this blank blank blank ah um and
it was really weird and by the
way we should sell those for three
of them we should chose freedom shirts
say be just getting government
could this be any more of a
threesome t-shirt do you think we would
get in trouble do you think we
would have no core ooh ooh good
sue us but no one owns that
okay paul keep guessing the fashion because
you are you're good already ah the
the leather pants ross's leather pants cindy
crawford were the robbers yeah we just
like when it's a beautiful woman
there's nothing you know about just oh
it was just a beautiful woman wearing
leather pants instead of like like a
dorky guy wearing maybe i will watch
this now well it's kind of what
made the fashion show kind of weird
because it's like hot women doing and
then like they had justin bieber okay
well keep yeah like she's just wearing
leather pants it's not yeah hey guys
if n
thing they were slightly ill fitting leather
pants because they were like for a
man okay oh alright i'll give him
credit for that um the you know
your episodes the princess leia slave outfit
was added in there oh i'm originally
an ai tissue i'm out of friends
fashion on come on come on coin
coin about i can't i can't even
go over what the other thr
we were think about um halloween or
holiday related costumes oh yeah
so there's an episode where russ is
just up for halloween he was a
dinosaur or snow he was hanukkah
animal you're getting close that was for
christmas episode there was one christmas episode
who had a minute he was it
was sean penn or whatever was in
yeah how does that right yeah because
he was out of i was really
worried because sean penn was there and
i had to come in dressed as
a blank
i fall god dammit he was like
it was like a furry animal right
well this is a separate but we're
talking two different things the white when
i'm trying to lead you with pete
is where he was like i had
to come in dressed as a it
was a pun it was a space
pun using a food and an object
the sounds anyway sputnik spy he's addressing
a potato i don't remember that at
all okay and then he was the
hanukkah armadillo or whatever armadillo that try
network cara de levine came out and
and just member what came out in
the potato and you know what it's
it's just it's too many things it's
like i don't need
if this level of distraction i wanna
watch the friends talk yes but they're
afraid that teenagers will not watch it
unless yeah but it's like get over
it like why did they advertise any
of those people ominous funny word and
word of mouth gets around oh god
oh of course i check out justin
bieber and this potion show
thankfully he didn't speak or anything but
he just dance
here's my here's my theory about about
network television shows doing halloween episodes yeah
is more more more more more it's
really fun for the costume department it's
really fun for them to make these
elaborate things and it always whenever anyone
shows
up in one of these things i'm
like this if any of my friends
did something this involved they would have
like it would be more involved than
anything you know but every single person
in the show is doing something that
involved and it always takes me out
of the scene it's very funny because
it's like no one whatever just show
up and like a wig and big
yeah i had it laying around i'm
going to a thrift store
i've put on an afro no seventy
s bell bottoms hello re hello
i went with restore i put on
an afro and seventies build a lot
of his hello
hello oh by the way my name
oh and merry christmas
i feel like but i think like
most shows that would do a halloween
episode like that would be more for
kids wouldn't they like i shows like
community and from everything and and all
of all of them they all do
these these sixty minutes yeah leslie's oh
a few sleep
stopwatch
to the subway to the embarrassed yeah
but there were no other ideas there
were no other ideas one man zombie
mike wallace gave me zombie stop watch
it was like ah zombies now watch
hey i wanna see some people wearing
that this this halloween zombie stopwatch cheese
freedom if
he has a face if you do
not save this idea for the next
few months and be the stopwatch you
are failing us because the stopwatch or
fail yeah as yoda hey i really
haven't planned to halloween costume in ages
and used to be such a bummer
because i would wait until the day
day of and then before halloween superstores
were all the rage and they were
open year round you'd have to try
to find something at a store and
they would be all sold out and
then you would have to go to
a thrift store there would be like
a guy outside of the thrift store
going come on in we got huh
we got halloween costumes and then you
get to the friends there would be
a line because it was all a
bunch of guys like me who
i'd waited till the last minute they
looked exactly like you yes it was
all my clubs it was your head
and you'd approach and the guy would
like look you up and down and
go okay let's see we got we
got some army fatigues probably in the
way it was when were they helping
you i don't want to design cars
because they're trying to sell thrift store
clothes that has nothing to do with
halloween he's like oh no piece together
your business lady ah
alright a year at that guy oh
okay put this on now your mom
alright daddy
oh i feel daddy when i moved
to l a like i was kind
of shocked by how many halloween stores
there are too many there's so many
it was good for when i was
doing sketch because no age i needed
anything i'm like i need to witches
like i know where to go i
used to live right down the street
from one and constantly just in there
like buying a makeup for like videos
i was making then just sketch your
personal videos
oh yes man wearing makeup lorne yeah
i know but as you examined you're
trying to say i'm picture you putting
on your joker makeup and jerking off
yeah petro serious i'm picturing psychological science
just watch it over and over again
and no one sees
i'm doing you walk into the store
i'm doing another one of my videos
idea
and it's more clown white
ah clown why did suit the superstore
ever do a halloween episode should of
yeah i bet they did they must
have here let's look it up superstar
halloween episode oh wait i can't just
say something aloud why would you want
enterprise
oh i am trying that for different
screens i have something to ask about
ah star trek and i know this
is not the pod directive and that's
right but listen to the pod directive
the other thing is is i'm sure
this is well trod territory but it
comes up every episode why are there
no seatbelts that is w t and
and i don't know the answer except
that they're in space well how about
reality recap yeah get a garcia was
not wearing a seatbelt in the backseat
and i like a lot of people
on reality tv don't wear a seatbelt
when they're in the backseat of a
car i don't like that did you
say garson aircel who's that she's one
of the real housewives so
of where um beverly hills that's where
i went ah back
get a lot of halloween superstore episodes
apparently okay well that goes because it's
their warrant that would be stupid there's
one where colton is where i think
he's from coming to america and someone's
a bee with a question mark on
their body i don't think that means
there's a lot of thinking
mark mckinney is a cowardly lion type
ah american airlines type yeah we were
looking for a cowardly lion type
ah this one actually is a little
more realistic i feel like other than
colton like colton's is too well well-made
i think but everyone else looks appropriately
handmade i feel it would be fun
to see more handmade costumes on halloween
episodes yeah it was real shitty ones
just terribly shitty although we know why
hate on tv production value forget che
i want to see it i want
to make you look like the people
are real and they did it themselves
i want to look that i want
to look like trash
don't trash your trash okay there's one
where someone's a cowboy someone's sexy red
riding hood coldness indiana jones and mark
mckinney is a chef
and the guy mustard gun to your
head could you name a fourth superstar
cast member ah yeah um no there's
ah what's her name ah laura nash
okay there we go yeah this is
going away from your head now there's
lauren there's colton ny years america there's
mark mckinney know i know and there's
the guy
learn about there's the guy from madman
that's why i don't and i don't
know his name ben feldman and feldman
hey two great guys supposedly by all
accounts no i didn't actually no one
has ever said that to me so
i have no idea though if something
comes out about him he's cancelled
when you go to swim i don't
know him i don't know him
never heard he's a great guy he's
cancelled here's one where america is mario
from super mario brothers and it looks
all cute racist but you know there's
something as an italian american i'm very
offended there's something about like a halloween
episode that i guess i it's like
i i think what i don't like
about it is that everyone is a
random costume even though it's real list
like dick i'd rather they all just
like on that episode they're like let's
all dresses like ketchup and mustard and
related things yes ketchup and mustard related
things hamburger hot dog whoa those are
the things you put mustard all these
peanut butter jelly bean know so no
ketchup and mustard for peanut butter and
jelly
full cry wrong i don't know why
i would want that it's not realistic
it's just anyone ever do couples costumes
on on the halloween up yeah they
sometimes will show up of like hey
we did this and it's good my
voice yeah oh yeah have you never
seen television with this going i mean
it's been a long it's been a
long time since i've
watched a sitcom like the oh dad
and la la la la la la
times i've watched a tv show that
did that
nice someone is a pad
nice what are you still looking at
some of the hot dog look this
is a ketchup but most age-related or
so this i believe this is america
i can't really now you're looking at
so i think you should leave okay
scott i need you to your screentime
has done honey okay alright sign off
buddy just said just want to fight
off buddy your and you're not going
to call your child buddy right come
come ah buddy do me a little
man i don't know why that great
some new rates are too yeah because
everyone doesn't hi and sorry if you're
listening to this and you call your
kid buddy it's cool yeah i mean
i get it it's a thing everyone
to do i don't and honestly i
don't know why it bothers me so
much but it does it does i
guess it doesn't really bother me
but um yeah i don't know i
don't see me so do you call
mike buddy i come pal what does
your body and ease your pow i
am maybe if i put
i think if you call your kid
buddy you should call your kid but
buddy
hey why do you think that because
then it would cure you of the
hab sure of what it was
you'd be just a user excited i
had to put ah i had to
play a a dad in a period
piece set in the seventy s and
some of the dialogue had me calling
the kids buddy and i was like
can i change this because it's not
what we did back then maybe pau
may be champ i don't know brando
friend friend dough sir
um doctor my my buddy went viral
on twitter us had to talk yeah
and ah casey vey he went viral
but yes yes three year old niece
requested a lion king birthday oh yeah
i read to her scar was dead
at
the er depart were not scars from
ssafa mufasa in fossa at the base
of the hill after scars killed them
because she thought everyone would be so
sad when they looked at the cake
that she would get to eat the
whole thing
so any note i loved is ah
i knew it was true right when
i saw it but when someone's like
those know where the kids sunlit and
then someone like linked to the bakery
who had already posted about it and
how like they were so excited to
make this cake because this right request
of a butler and then there was
someone was like i'm glad she had
the receipts like there's just
like this whole like yeah it's just
just a way everything goes believe anything
anymore because we believe anybody you're an
asshole but a very true but and
i just i ascribed to a philosophy
um i think that um with kids
especially there have been so many things
that people have said that you know
are not true
well knowing people disbelieve everything but i'm
like you'd have the whole cake made
and then make up that lie it
exactly exactly this isn't a ruth condo
forever you know what i mean oh
that one oh it was amazing but
was that a joke or is that
someone really said i mean someone no
names someone someone truly claimed that their
daughter app
because chadwick boseman and ruth bader ginsburg
died in quick succession of most suspicious
of yes oh i think that impact
and um this woman ah tweeted that
her she had to tell her daughter
about the death of ruth bader ginsburg
and the child was like
young and it's also you don't have
to tell your children about the deaths
of supreme court justices at all no
just do it wastes time it's it's
out of their daily lives
and the the daughter according to this
woman and crossed her her arms over
chest in the in the wakanda forever
salute and said ruth ruth condo forever
so that doesn't happen it's so unreal
way it's like if it did happen
you you're grounded yeah go to sleep
fuck you kid i always say fuck
you to my child okay fuck you
how dare you let's just go insane
have we talked about this what is
the first celebrity death that you remember
i think we have okay touched on
this just because yeah no one like
i would imagine when chadwick boseman died
some kids have
had to be told about that oh
yeah he was like a superhero yeah
i mean like if a superhero dies
it's it's a it's it's a big
deal i don't remember being really little
and like thinking about this but i
remember when john ritter died i cried
yeah but i was older
um i don't remember who died when
i was like really little that was
like but like i don't remember richard
nixon no one told me no one
informed me about that you know what
i mean like no no when he
died yeah hell's like theirs and i
would have been well he died in
what seventy nine or something like that
or eighty two or something oh well
let's look him
up how old are you i can't
think of how old that makes you
i guess we're about to find the
fuck out okay richard nixon die and
ah god there's too much information about
him when did he die oh ninety
oh ninety four oh yeah it would
have been way too old
you're like twenty only but i opened
the memory you're probably just high
wait what was i do okay so
in ninety four i would have been
back doing it off ninety four i
was doing what i was hearing o
j simpson did all that stuff and
drove by the olive garden the same
year same year yeah so yeah i
don't know i but it had no
effect on my life were obviously i
don't even remember it do you think
oj killed richard nixon
oh it's suspicious on his ways i
have a lot of yellow anytime i
have a lot of questions it just
drove over richard nixon well it's not
too far off from where he was
driving because he drove by us in
orange county and richard nixon was in
yorba linda that's right but um i'll
never forget that fateful day when i
watched that footage on tv
jackson stuff like his honor up to
the simpsons and then it was him
she's a white bronco for hours and
hours they don't make them like that
anymore one of the details in that
um oj was at o j made
in america the one that the miniseries
was in cuba gooding junior that was
an
american ah oh right story american crime
story yeah yeah um i really liked
that miniseries like we really enjoyed it
a lot um one of the details
that i did not realize was a
true thing was that um pizza pizza
places were running out of pizza yeah
because people were ordering pizza to watch
the chase so
that's i love that they included the
setting there that's all that's all based
on um a great book that was
my favorite book about the trial i
used to read books about the o
j trial wasn't just a toobin book
yes good ol to
spare time he wrote a book oh
and a machine with that situation what
happened when it did it i know
but i mean we all agree
finally every tube and releases a book
if i didn't know what i've done
it i wanna stood up and pretended
i didn't know the timer was still
going
so rose he got fired right yeah
from whatever he was doing that's it
well what else now he's opening for
louis c k
but his books were great ah yeah
about kenny hurst stanley good exposure whatever
what isn't considered like indecent exposure whatever
or two decent exposure it was decent
because of what i could turn off
my camera decent amount of
but like isn't that isn't that a
thing like that i wouldn't argue with
more i would imagine it would be
right and you probably use it over
the internet i don't know you're technically
in a public place if you are
you know in a room but i
guess your chat room you i guess
you have reasonable doubt if you say
no i didn't realize that was happening
because they can't prove that
you knew who's the dude in summer
in canada or whatever who's done it
justin trudeau oh no he's done it
like he took a shit on camera
or something recently and he's like yeah
it was the accidental second one where
he's like after the first one he's
like this will never happen again like
he took a shit on camera i
think people were like who are you
why what happened we have one days
ago oh
i didn't know about that but there
was one where like somebody he took
their zoom into the bathroom and they
thought they realised that the yes yes
yes i remember that that's from saying
by the way speaking of zooms
i was talking about them with a
friend recently we were saying like oh
they're so great you never have to
drive to the fox sly for meetings
anymore but i i found something that's
bad about them
okay so
are we supposed to chime in like
oh no so what's your mind be
so i i worked all week on
this presentation i was getting back over
zoom and about how monkeys flat here
but yeah exactly it was like shabby
the ins the outs mainly the outs
um and i
i was an and my zoom meeting
was at one o'clock on a friday
and work tm works all week on
it and then like for an hour
before one o'clock i like was going
over it and reciting it and all
this kind of stuff at twelve of
course of humanism
and twelve fifty nine canceled
yeah wow that's definitely an issue i
feel like that's happened a lot where
he's that will never happen if you're
close to the fox lot they wouldn't
cancel it started rolling away if if
you drove to the box latte and
they were running late they would say
hey we're running late but we'll still
see you whereas for me it was
like what are you doing in two
weeks like i'd prepped for a fence
low noise yeah but
here's my question yeah dude i'm i'm
i'm sorry good well i know what
i was just gonna say am i
the only one that would have been
psyched that i love when shits cancelled
but i would be annoyed because if
i was ready to do it exactly
yes like that would be nice especially
with a week of prep like yeah
all leading to much effort and then
your nerves and whatever but
my question is do you like doing
that and zoom because i have found
that i really i don't like having
to present her pitch on bringing yeah
isolation but maybe worst worse i mean
yeah i don't i don't want pitches
this was more of a conversation that
i had to be very prepared for
but free fl
flowing conversation but i but i had
typed out the conversation in advance of
like and so will say today you
know and i'll say no i mean
like it was it was more of
like hey what do you want to
do with this project and so i
typed out like a point so i
went okay dollars yeah you know have
an i p in next release stick
it to my ex
how can we help you oh thank
you um i think in various ways
but yeah but i mean so now
i have brown now i have to
prep for another week for the thing
in two weeks like which could be
cancelled again yeah exactly so that's why
i mean if if the prep is
already done why do why would you
have to have another weeks without i
know i really only have to do
like a day oh now because i
because i wrote everything just to refresh
it yourself but yeah i'm just gonna
forget about it and that's the other
thing for so much rusher so so
much momentum and and passion for it
and then it's like oh by the
way can you do this into two
more weeks it's like well am i
going to lose interest in this and
two yeah uhm and then it's like
why is it why is it two
weeks from now that's when they're available
it just feels like a long time
and
blah blah blah i think that's standard
now that any if anything has postponed
it's two weeks is that so it's
like daylight savings time they made a
rule did this conversation sap the energy
out of everything somehow you got me
so i'm still raring to go i'm
freaking out over here okay huh let's
go to a break learn falling asleep
ooh
it seems a little true okay i'm
tired huh
wag that yes oh what were you
saying the same thing no i was
saying we're back over i was saying
come back come back everyone come back
good plan come back everybody come back
where
here we know we gave you a
stopping point to never come back but
yeah come back is how many times
do you do do that with a
tv show like if a commercial comes
up just go like fuck this i'm
out ever remember oh you see it
through okay i will i watch everything
to the end
i am a
but i know i am it's actually
i'm more likely to watch like this
is what i find kind of weird
about myself i'm like i haven't watched
mayor of east town but then i'm
like i have seen every episode of
this is us like i will catch
them on my weekly shows that are
on my dvd r but then it's
like we may need to devi or
marie's son so going to hbo max
like forget that it's there
right i have my rotation i go
to the ddr first and clear that
out of whatever has been taped and
then i have my rotation of like
go to this go to netflix first
and then go to hbo max then
go to paramount plus like i'll do
like a cycle through to see what's
new and if you do
don't do that you have to wash
your hands fifty times yeah of course
i we have eat we have pretty
much stopped using r dvd r yeah
we we watch all streaming stuff like
i can't think of anything that we're
recording regularly anymore while i'm curled see
i liked the old-fashioned us of the
ddr like there's something about it that
i just appreciate even though all those
shows
i can get onto other platforms that
i also have yeah so i feel
like i have thought about canceling cable
but then i i really like just
having it as an option yeah well
you sure like an oj chase exactly
in case he starts chasing people again
it's own way and you think that's
chancy yeah i mean i i've i've
i'm familiar with this so o j
was chasing people
who is he chasing oh you're chasing
richard nixon they finally got em dealer
chasing the cops but he lapped them
ah and they was so mad they're
like oh hey how did that go
okay boys um we ah i feel
like there's not anything that we watch
night of any more it's been a
long time since we saw something else
da lu
tabs i watched a live i bet
when better call saul comes back we
will probably watch that yeah airs as
well mainly because there's stupid amc channels
are all on a terrible app and
that includes my show look apps for
the most part stink well yeah i
like em of it like him
mc plus or something there's too many
too many apps to any apps yeah
like i like the ones that combine
a whole bunch of different channels onto
one app like those discovery plus yeah
hbo max yeah but what i don't
like is like peacock sitting there with
only nbc shit and then they have
a super expensive tear
you're right that does it without the
ads and even though i can afford
it it's the principle of it so
i refuse to pay for it yeah
well it's too many it's too many
little things i mean at that point
then you should cancel your cable and
then you pay one hundred dollars in
apps yeah but i like watching news
on cable live and stuff like that
yeah but i guess you could on
apps now that is the one you
could
good but it's not quite the same
like that is one of the things
that we will do every once in
a while with regular tv is watch
local news which is fun to do
local news is such a bummer to
me i can barely watch why scott
honey has it's all it's it's you
know after watching nightcrawler and then breaking
down you know how much of it
is just about the the most sensational
the story of the day which is
always murder you know the whole if
it bleeds it leads thy friends frasier
told us raging so yeah yeah some
movie was that in the scrambled eggs
so i don't know yeah everybody did
was a little aside at the end
but i don't want to do with
those azaleas as grey blue dogs if
it bleeds it leads
um he was in some movie with
robert de niro that was about this
a long shingle
yeah kelsey grammer is a raging raging
bowlby the shit out of did you
fuck my wife to see please please
yeah he only kelsey grammer played frazier
clean frasier crane exclusively
leisure claim um he played me because
when that's evil twin aw flavor we
meet again
um what was the name of that
movie was robert de niro kelsey grammer
was about network news and kelsey grammer
famously said if it bleeds it leads
i don't remember no one did anyone
wanted to show i look it up
i'll look at oh like ah robert
de niro i've met
one that if we dumb look it
up people would have been fine like
yeah it's like noise called but it's
ah what's another way to say a
quarter of an hour fifteen minutes is
ten fifteen minutes like fifteen minutes of
fame ah yeah that's sixteen minutes shorter
little sister
they all were dressed up like stopwatches
edward burns robert de niro oh edward
burns shore remember him yeah the brothers
mcmahon own he's still doing a lot
of the big stuff as me i
think he's on some tv show now
but i can't remember which one wonderful
i can look that updates one it's
wonderful thank you
i love that he's working public loud
and he's working i love bridge and
tunnel tv series first season is available
bridge and tunnel on epics created by
edward burns written by edward burns directed
by edward burns country already says e
united states that's fun you can take
to low e me a low a
lowercase e that's funny i read wall
e as while air i read it
as well a while
really wow chloe lauren can i sing
what a low e no no sand
oh do you know you know what
a note is you know no i
wish i had perfect pitch like chevy
chase but i don't yeah i have
a pronounced pro ball pretty cool well
who else can you name those perfect
pitch and my
friend i'm actually mike mularkey who did
our theme song these girls bitch yeah
so so does he have the kind
where you can say like you can
sing a note and he goes oh
that's a c-sharp probably probably but that's
so imagining a person like chevy chase
who has perfect pitch who can just
hear a song and then played on
a piano or it's just wish yeah
that's that
perfect pitch yeah where you just hear
it and go oh i know all
those notes and then you can just
read ah
ah okay alright i think paul what
you're thinking of though is someone who
can keep a perfect pitch in their
head not perfect pitch if that makes
sense it doesn't i don't know what
how did we get here guys i
don't know where we scared maybe ah
it's so cold here oh you know
you're on a horse yeah i just
mentioned perfect pitch absolut pitch woo absolute
pitch absolute pitch often called perfect pitch
is a rare ability of a person
to identify or recreate a given musical
note without the benefit of a reference
tone that's what i'm
thinking of that's what i mean meaning
if you hear a note you can
go oh that's a c-sharp and you
can recreate it right yeah
and more if somebody tells you do
that right now you can do it
yeah you can do it yeah i
was one of horses law and then
you go law that's not perfect and
she's hearing did she matched it
florio perfect pitch that's amazing though i
was on a horse in costa rica
that was the last time i was
on a horse how many years away
is six seven years ago summer and
what did you think about it it
was fun i was a little nervous
about it on the beach no it
was not it was the cloud forest
part of costa rica we split up
you wrote on it for now
load the first part was an cloud
forest which was so nice and relaxing
this avatar cloud fours yeah and i
stuck my blue ponytail up my butt
nice up your own body doesn't yeah
i know
they say it's unsanitary um and then
i went and then the other half
was on a beach on a resort
and because it was christmas and it
was like oh let's get some sun
and it wasn't as fun but michael
douglas and catherine zeta jones was there
it's christmas let's get some sun michael
and catherine zeta was there um i
i have not been on a horse
the only time i've ever been in
a horse was a summer camp experience
when i was i don't know nine
ten something like that
oh and like my shoe i was
yeah it was scary i was a
little kid way up high on a
horse and you think you'd ever do
it again yeah i think i would
i think i would yeah i think
i'd be more interested in it now
but not so interested that i'm pursuing
this in any way because there's like
horse trails and stuff in l a
yeah and you can take like horse
rides up
the canyon and stuff like that but
i haven't really been that ah that
interested in doing motivated yeah do it
this week
me random so random i was you
know as wherever i was in costa
rica there were all these things that
i normally would be too scared to
do but um like for not wanting
to christopher reeve or you know on
the horse but i went on the
horse and then yeah that's a nice
way to put the zip line
why does the zip line we did
the zipline above like
the excessive drop above a mass massive
massive drop and zip tie was scary
to me i've done one it wasn't
that big so i was nervous and
cool up i think was nervous and
then i talked to the guy who
operated it and i was like so
how often have you have you done
this he goes i do this about
seven eight times a day every day
i go okay how many accidents have
there been he goes none i was
like oh i mean yeah that's all
i mean this weirdly that just put
me at ease where like he's never
seen an accident he does it so
with so many times in so many
people it's like yeah you forgot said
lying was a thing yeah um ah
i i think i would do it
i think i would do is implant
it was fun it was really fun
one was like would you do it
yeah i don't know i mean the
one i did was like very low
key compared to that it was um
at a camp that i worked up
but oh that's right you were babysitter
camp counselor movie star and now stay
at home mom
yes my plans never work yeah i
yeah but i get scared that kinda
shit i think i'm more scared with
the climbing up than i am with
the going zipping you know this was
not climbing mine was not climbing up
you literally like walked away from the
hotel about
three minutes and then you were at
the edge it was like we just
had an edge so you just like
hook yourself up to it there was
no climb it was just laying and
then you just step off and that's
better but that's still scary i think
they said it's the height drop that
is the scary part to me yeah
but i scared anything be fun are
you scared of heights in general
um yeah i guess so i mean
let's see stand on your tiptoes
oh man she got freaked out i
mean i like for example i went
to ah the willis tower f k
sears tower in chicago and they have
like a one of those glass holes
in the floor you know on the
toe yes yes you can and i
so i'll stand on that but it's
still a little freaky i'm a little
scared but like they tell you
you shouldn't wear a dress
yeah because like the people on the
ground floor so it's like a hundred
stories out within this there's guys going
oh my god
where ah
that's why you're not allowed to have
cell phones in there yeah and then
like the like floor cracked because of
their screams and they made the rule
i didn't know that the sears tower
had its name changed yeah probably ten
plus years ago is because sears sears
is no longer a thing i mean
they come out of place or just
buy whatever willett says arnold's brother yes
and i was like what you're talking
about when i heard the news on
sears tower
the original guy trace years i it's
hard to believe they'd be out of
business i i mean that's where my
family shopped for everything we would go
to see what kept them in business
all the time for tough skins that
was their brand of yes tough skins
i suppose if you remember there was
a lauren you didn't think that
that we'd go to sears for our
tough skins everyone getting the same issue
i get were gonna buy condoms
um i remember there was a commercial
for tough skins where they could they
did the jeans on a robot
further
for the robot to like try to
wear them out this was the proof
that they were very durable jeans and
you know what yeah i remember this
well they were mostly like move so
much yeah this robot did lauren i'm
gonna find that commercial yeah because it
was like those dog robots police dog
robot oh no this was a old-fashioned
nineteen
fifty robots wearing some nineteen seventies jeans
um but tuscans were stiff as shit
i remember how stiff those jeans were
like they would hurt the backs of
your knees yeah because they were so
stiff and the chords would always make
the scene yeah whenever you walked in
i was so embarrassed well that's the
plea of course have you ever seen
that commercial for the
the um domino's delivery truck that has
nobody inside it's like a robot wow
that's illegal i would think it's a
theme to tell if it's real or
a joseph legal i think it's real
it's like it's like a little kite
owner has nobody tried it there can't
be total self driving cars on there
i'll find illegally
but it's not like a full sized
car right it's like looking a little
little robot smart car i feel like
i have seen footage of this i
think that bret are our own brett
morris i think ah it's real captured
some footage oh driving around the city
streets here i want to put in
the chet i think
if the drones thing is going to
be really weird it's on straights dominoes
is launching a pizza delivery robot car
oh but it's not on the streets
yet well that was that was a
while ago and now there's commercials so
it was an april now it's me
by the way when we did it
they were not taping this in may
we're we're taping this a couple hours
before you hear it
it's very fruitful hours it's very fresh
i mean this thing could not be
more adorable could it be anymore but
in the commercial there's like good this
t-shirt be anymore adorable let's start selling
them guys come on because this pizza
be anymore in a robot
let's sell that shirt at lee huh
because to be anymore in a robot
with a picture of a robot and
a pizza he's wearing it as a
hat prove this as it yeah if
you like that so and so could
this pizza be any more in a
robot but he's wearing it as a
hat so the answer is yes it
could be more inhale yeah exactly yes
that's our way around it and there's
a yes
on the back
answer yes
ah starts selling josh make some notes
on this come on yeah well we
do everything judges our dad that we
have to ask permission to size family
is josh says he's on it
on the pizza sir john the robot
or on making the teacher all three
oh wow he's on a pizza he's
on a robot and he's making the
shirt paul did you get the what
was the icy that was at sears
that they made was what was it
called was it was it icy
it was like a slushie they had
oh i don't remember well i guess
in the sears by my house it
had and that was a bragging that
was the treats that rich kid
yeah we were so the sears by
my house the point park mall um
it it had to say they will
it our goodwill this election is enormous
you said you shopped at sears that's
why i'm asking no this is what
scott i'm not a i'm not a
top fighting i'm doing a skit i'm
just
doing i don't like your skit it's
a fun skit about like more like
a poor kid bragging to another poor
kid okay i like this is a
good sketch this is a good sketch
we should just pitch this to netflix
just this sketch we don't want to
do a sketch show we just want
to make the sketch we would like
you to produce our sketch and run
your channel
suddenly you just start making one sketch
but ah but but you cannot produce
any other sketches will be the only
sketch on netflix and everything else is
a skid i want to pitch some
skits to them and i want to
show you know i think a skit
show is an idea whose time has
come yeah yeah it's all like football
players in high school
cool it was it wasn't that what
ah the guy said nate corddry said
on ah studio sixty when he was
yelling at his parents oh about the
difference between sketch and skit yeah his
parents like nicely came to his work
and he was such an asshole about
it oh second they were not nice
do you remember the dad yelled your
brother
standing in a field in afghanistan well
that's because nick quarter is such a
dick before that he's like they go
visit him they're cool about it they're
like you know it's a terrible sketch
show they never say that to him
they'll whenever speaks that allowed right now
whenever it says that and then make
orders like oh this can you imagine
abbott and costello performed here
and they're like who's that and he's
like having castello and he gives them
a history of comedy and then he
and they're like okay well whatever you
know your skits are very funny and
he's like it's not a skit censor
what football players and cheerleaders do during
pep rallies this is sketch this is
sketch
it was it's he gets vet and
then then it leads to your brothers
had failed in afghanistan and you're arguing
about a skid vs a sketch get
the fuck am i gonna have to
watch it again i gotta do my
guy who's gonna watch that whole series
but then i saw i had to
pay for it and i was like
oh who oh yeah amazon dot corn
ah you didn't check youtube i didn't
check you to let me check youtube
wow almost everything's on youtube what does
that noise what noise is it windy
is there a plane flying overhead is
somebody running the vacuum oh my computer
just started worrying oh no everybody goes
hot
take take all the blankets out from
of the bags out alright waiting oh
yeah lauren's gonna fix this we're gonna
take a break
and we're back and guess what everybody
yes you we got your cards and
letters please keep doing the three cheers
well we're going to we're going to
play a game
submitted by seattle a card that was
like a christmas card that said go
to hell it was very yes and
it was low lady writing you could
tell yeah um by the way i'm
having an affair with her um it's
nothing you didn't hear that qatar josh
um this game is called menacing phone
it is submitted by camden
in brazil b r z i l
e um two people play a scene
and anytime yes exactly that's why i
i'm pronouncing but maybe it's brazil bra
v
two people play a scene and at
any time the third person can call
one of the members in the scene
and give them menacing information about the
scene slash other player that impacts the
scene example is he really who he
says he is you get the idea
says camden camden maybe we're not as
smart as you think yeah maybe you
want to list a couple other
but here's the thing so i think
that the third person who's not in
the scene can call either person throughout
the scene yeah um and give them
information so i think it sounds like
fun the way we're gonna do it
since we're doing this over zoom is
we will ah when we are the
color will mute our microphones so you
the listener will hear
the um the phone calls but the
other players will the other player will
not yes so the the player who
is not receiving the information will not
hear the phone call the player who
is receiving the information will receive the
phone call that's exactly right yes i'm
ok in the sense so who does
walk
oh let's see the dogs off i'll
be the caller okay okay great great
so i want to meet myself yes
on zoom yes ma'am oh and she
is muted okay and she is muted
and now scott and i will begin
the scene
oh hello ah i didn't think anyone
else would be here oh yeah i've
been here for god like twenty minutes
already i think wow yeah it's ah
i got to remember to check my
phone sorry um excuse me one second
i'm sure i've been waiting for a
call excuse me yeah absolutely hello
you should tell him that you know
what he's been up to and it's
not good okay thank you alright thanks
bye oh jesus dropped my phone
what a weirdo first year ahead of
me hey ah can we just cut
the shit for a second i beg
your pardon i know what you are
up to and not good what are
you talking about sir excuse me i'm
getting a call you're being very rude
that's all i know
hello you're worried because you think
you think that he saw you spying
on your neighbors but what he really
saw was that you were stealing candy
from the breakroom
alright i know what you think you
saw but i can assure you it
was a understandable mistake a trick of
the light i wow how could that
be a trick of the light the
thing that i saw and that i
certainly didn't just hear about on this
phone call well because ah the
the lighting in that particular space is
very erratic and it could make it
look like shadows are doing things that
they are not doing it seems unbelievable
to me can you take me to
the space take it to the space
i ah what are you doing what
was that just nothing it's abuse people
have oh sure
hello
tell him that you're casting your new
your new reality singing show yes master
ah did you i'm sorry did you
say yes master oh no no no
i said ah yes ah mr news
i'll check up but the tricky trick
trick of the year like pictures
so here's the deal i know what
i saw i saw what i saw
but you're in luck because i'm casting
a new reality show and what you
did would be perfect for it too
i admit what i did all right
yes you did see me stealing candy
from the breakroom
well you're in luck because excuse me
i have to take this well i'm
telling you about a show that i
want to cast you on yes that's
hulu tell him you need to be
paid two fifty k per ep
well good news i'll do your reality
show but my price is two hundred
and fifty k per ep excuse me
i don't have time to negotiate i
have to take this call yes hello
tell him your budget is one dollar
per ep okay ah
we have a problem then because our
budget is one dollar an episode so
we're gonna have to work within those
parameters i'm sorry for the whole show
per episode one dollar for that's that's
including everyone's salaries yeah equipment ah catering
grips would you shut up for a
second i have to take this call
very rude i don't know that i
want to cast lou
you have to tweet and expose him
now i there was a word i
couldn't understand i'm not sure what i'm
supposed to do although the second oh
okay hello you have to tweet and
expose him okay that's what underpaying his
employees that's what i thought at first
i thought you said tweak oh it's
gone are you okay you're taking yeah
same
i'm just going to twitter and heavy
negotiations here and i'm exposing you online
soon you will be cancelled while last
what did i do you agree to
my terms excuse me i have to
take this call
hello confess that you've always wanted to
be cancelled do you feel left out
and
okay you wanna cancel me bro yes
go ahead i want it i want
to be canceled just like everyone because
all the cool people have been cancelled
and i want to be like them
so go ahead and do it you
good looking person fake you
oh i have to take this
he lou tell him you're flattered and
you want a kiss
i'm flattered and
i want a kiss
hey look ah maybe you're getting the
wrong idea about what i said good-looking
person ah i really just oh pardon
me one second
oh tell him what you meant is
that you want to have sex with
but i'm saying i'm angry about it
all right you cry
ah can i confess something there's a
mysterious profiteer who tells me every move
that i make and they want me
to have sex with oh hold on
hold up
hello it's really roomy like my identity
look
here's the deal she told me that
if i ever said who she was
she would kill my entire family but
i can't take it anymore i don't
want to have sex with you do
you wanna have sex with me and
really not really i mean oh i
was just doing what a mysterious puppeteer
was telling me excuse me i do
have to take no problem no problem
the answer is not really but i
would here we go
sorry um i i messed up but
i gave my answer previously
the answer to do i wanna really
have sex with you is ah ah
can't remember now i yes i yes
i do and ah
oh hello i was like i'm about
to get a call
you can just tell that you're about
to hear it comes oh wow
lou yeah it was not really i
can't hear you eat
huh what i didn't hear that at
all they own up look we're obviously
being led by the dicks by some
weirdo who wants to be in charge
is your family in danger too
i'm an only child
aloo the answer to the question do
you really want to have sex with
me is not really but i will
here we go okay thank you the
answer to this question do i really
want to have sex with you is
not really but i will here we
go
and c and c and the two
guys had sex that's awesome it was
good it was good for them it
was five it's it's best when it's
one on one yeah loved it alright
i liked that game ah we wish
do we have time for another i
think we're running out of time yeah
it was fun alright like it was
only going again
we'll get that one again thank you
ms brazile la barossa um alright well
everybody that does it for another edition
of threesome we hope you're healthy and
happy and hung wow if your dick
isn't all the way down to the
floor oh no what's happening to me
i'm a little my blood sugar
or just dropping a crystal arm
alright guys great i need a gran
ola more
great to see you guys great teaching
us to yeah great to see you
great to be listened to by the
listeners yes getting a look look for
the t-shirts the right to be smelled
by dogs in the neighbourhood their sense
of smell is very keen can this
pizza be anymore in this robot and
then a yes on the back we'll
have those store sued i do too
okay
by everyone by everyone love you
uh