three
nah
yeah studio live recording you go if
you live or we are and we
are back who's too low leave your
egos at the door we've got federal
bailout oh wow
goodbye new listeners
we have not been him here as
a unit know any uni we have
company here is an absolute unit for
many years many notes for three-pronged voltron
not one year but two yeah i
think we did the entire last season
over how many products just regular run
usually just as well i'm talking
a full three dictum ultra huh
wrong answer three the three ticks come
together one day i mean is that
a term for penis prong yeah it
is cool it's not like dork in
your household
wrong prong a year your girlfriend says
put your
yes a lot of romance novels he
unleashes over prong yeah yeah ooh laughs
this guy zane well we are back
in the studio this is three to
my name is sky name is paul
a perfect harmony and we're also back
in the same room for the first
time yes in a while because we've
been on head carving and you had
covered the novel coronavirus never condoned by
this carbon and the canonical chairman yeah
you had it in this canon but
then in the wiki it's in
don't put that on my wiki i
can't be living like that whether that
was in every single person's wiki every
sunday wednesday god yeah every dummy they
got sick not just go get a
call when eighteen that's where this is
headed and no because ever wants to
catalog everything you do oh harley twenty
twenty three saw her with a sinus
infection
sar sar um ok i gotta address
the elephant in the room yeah you
mike t you sent us a t-shirt
and you are an elephant get out
of here you sent us a t-shirt
in september twenty nineteen we never saw
it until we've we've finally lauren got
here finally we haven't been here in
three years look through the mail
and there's some just egregious things that
we've been responding to like say yes
this person sent this t-shirt of chicken
in the corn and wanted it signed
and paul had already signed it somehow
i read the letter but i didn't
retain the information at a tour stop
somebody so yeah and there was an
what is called a space self-addressed stamped
tumble
i recall from my days of sending
fan mail um as a kid it's
also six in spanish in us yeah
it's called differently and we signed it
andrew back and sent in the envelope
for you send it and if you
don't live there anymore which is very
possible look look i we can't do
anything about i think we need to
take bets on whether this person is
even still a listener
yeah yeah it could have possibly now
people move on from podcast but so
far yes here to steal their t-shirt
from them sure yeah three years back
at signed by all three of us
and hopefully you get it soon and
you love sorry mike t but we
got to when we got to it
and we got to it now and
we also want to say thank you
post this on instagram thank you to
belinda and cooper for making gorgeous embroideries
for us of our dogs yeah i
started these these were ruin and how
long ago were these sent um no
you didn't clock the date but probably
three years yeah yeah look look back
years ago this is gonna go right
up on my wall though i love
it yeah lovely with twelve
my gallery wall belinda is that her
name yeah stephanie yeah well ah they
sent these wonderful needle points ah one
of rocky for scott view my dog
and one of maybe they still rocks
so with us winners still with us
not ah no rocky wasn't still with
it but maybe they did and we
haven't gotten to the mail and that
long whoa because rock
p rocky passed away when did tim
kell packers get married is the day
after
i don't know i wasn't invited the
same these ah you guys you should've
seen the bruise so what if i
hardly knew him at the time yes
same shit
i have absolutely strangers inviting me to
weddings wow
yes you're telling me acquaintances can invite
me to a wedding where a bunch
of people i know are gonna be
there yeah it's like a party that
i would enjoy yeah well we all
enjoyed it you think oh my god
he's back with an attitude i can't
yeah this is paul backend studio ah
if you can't handle me at my
worst you don't deserve me at this
wow
oh and what is this like your
best really
oh wow
why not
shadow
ah is that all for viewer mail
that that's only ones i wanna talk
about well i gone so anyone else
i got i can't get into it
i've taken i got something sent to
me do da do da i got
something said to me
oh dude i didn't get an email
from a company and they said you
have an order that you place with
us and we love to send it
to you it is from a company
it's from a company that paul f
tompkins started an exclusive arrangement with that's
right mine is exclusive okay can we
just see how are you who did
the cameo check-in yeah let's do a
cameo cameo still happening ah the price
got raised but i'm still getting request
and you're at three hundred now ah
yes and you are getting a flood
of requests it was a lot yeah
but i caught up good okay okay
now it's now it's manageable i would
hope it is manageable there are amenable
its managed exist
you're mentioning i'm mentioning it all the
time i there are still some people
that don't i think are not quite
sure of the concept and so i
message them when they give requests they
are huge this is what i do
are you sure you still want this
and a couple people i have not
heard back from so i think i
have to wait until it's almost about
to expire because even if i let
it expire that reflects poorly on
me i think i have to die
oh i see so i can get
a good reading or whatever cameo who
knew there's so much well in any
case a you mentioned earlier last there
was somebody that i was at the
gym today and somebody looked really good
read like your body is so all
your michael chair katanga
look i mean we're all having fun
but look i'm not trying to be
in a marvel movie i'm just trying
to stay alive yeah
a dichotomy that is it's so funny
it's like you you gotta there should
be something in between you're going to
the gym why you're trying to get
supercut like no just adding one year
to my life
perhaps by spending two years of my
life doing this let's hope so
um but it was so i'm i'm
there on them on the elliptical machine
and i stay on my phone that
request comes through i go to open
it and then within ah by the
time i opened it twenty seconds later
they had cancelled their requests ah yeah
it was wild to see that thought
process happening yeah well this was not
a cancelled request you mentioned on our
last
episode or the episode before that ah
um a friend a mutual friend bought
me one of your cameos yeah and
i had a guess as to who
it was who is your guest but
that person it was okay and i
was thinking who is willing to do
this yes all people yeah this guy
yeah and it turned out to be
this guy and this is ah zombie
i do have to
thumbs though
and it's not me i broke my
thumbs in a butt plug x
taxes are pretty went in you want
out or using them instead of books
i literally explode
um but this is this is we've
talked about him a few times this
is tall john paul john bought this
fantasy extremely tall man was trying to
disguise that it was him by spelling
his name differently upon the request and
not realising that his name is in
the credit card information yeah exactly and
so paul knew this was
and i think his request was for
it to be for a friend named
scott who was starting a new podcast
yeah entreated a pep talk he was
he was feeling insecure about the podcast
but you saw you saw easy stuff
and you saw through it right away
and decided to do your own thing
and this made us all laugh this
is paul's cameo to me
me hey scott your friend john really
cares about you and he told me
that you're going through a hard time
that recently your dick fell off and
um economy the ground and around his
dirty and
there's like you know grass and dirt
on her dick and um
you have to wash it off and
you know obviously you have to tell
people about it and that's not obvious
so um i just want you to
know that your struggles while mortifying
and comical ah the real to you
and to everyone everyone knows about your
dick falling down
um i would say rinse it in
the sink
giving a medical advice i don't think
cleaning extended out
like a dry cleaner i think you
have to do it i think this
is something that you have to do
yourself
run the water ah until it's warm
if you have nothing with two taps
turn on the hot first just let
it get hot and turn on the
cold until you get to like a
nice one level
water temperature and then rinse it off
there and it's not different than any
other cameos yeah i think the little
kitchen sink isn't advertised disposal sinker greater
gravel or whatever goes down there you're
not technically supposed to put gravel in
the
in the thing
anyway
best of luck
from your friend jaw and politics
yeah was really good
yeah we're facing a big at the
oh it's just like you seem so
oh it erase it but um you
crossed your eyes and fellow no use
you were huge you seem so beleaguered
during the whole thing like lagers and
all saying yeah i like them
so belinda
and then at the end you're like
and for me paul f tompkins and
you smiled really big yeah but you
seem to really be empathizing with my
my my plight that's how i try
to do it or you know you
really want to be there for these
allegations you've made up exactly yeah that's
great so that was very though what
a wonderful gift from paul john and
and from you
yeah forever now i do yes and
the official camel watermark yes that is
something you couldn't get just by being
his friend and how do i download
it from store or i've just been
keeping the browser open what do i
do i download it i have zero
idea i don't know but that's why
it can refinement from that roll-off it
was like not who came from little
people big world that jimmy
sent me either oh right yeah sorry
i forgot his name yeah it's very
close to about raffle um rolling on
the floor laughing oh not rolling on
the floor laughing
yeah i think that's actually what it
was based on is he related to
matt lmao
you mean matt leblanc no matt lmao
i'm laughing my ass off
lmao i've never heard it pronounced exactly
like oh lmao
alem efo yeah what happened to those
guy one was like like improv at
io what i remember they were around
for a minute or so are they
the reason that i went to war
and they doing improv maybe i'm mixing
it up were they doing in prime
urban improv i o just formed around
them yes but there was this was
the time when real world l a
was
is happening and moving in common io
and then i remember that my fail
was also there for some reason or
that maybe they prefer i remember weirdly
alien draw like after these terrible people
do improv than saying artery i'm sorry
who's there so yeah i'm sexy and
i know is that right already okay
in the house ny
everybody gonna ha good time i went
oh my god oh so yeah i'm
sixteen i noticed one of their suit
right i'm sexy and i know it
for a proper manner but
bad but there no right said fred
yeah it's like only one person can
be sunken right said fred are covert
deniers now well then i guess i
have a favorite sub i'm so sexy
so i guess i never thought oh
i never thought of them as a
band there to do dudes those two
big jack if you're okay if you're
too dude
yeah sure you are unless you're both
hey
unless you both have the same name
that you named the band right you
can't name the band after a saint
after a person's name or fred you
mean yeah wonder right to bread no
no because it's right said fred is
ah i think it's a quote from
something
it's probably like the bard it's like
how directly the duran duran is a
character in barbarella right
i don't i was gonna look up
rights at fred and i realised i
don't care sadly
i don't care but then the one
you think of the guy the one
guy from the video as right said
fred i think there's two guys in
the video i don't that's imposing another
guy lurking behind them hi i guess
i thought he was to be their
duty right said fred is so jacked
though it's hard to like get anyone
else into the fray exactly sexy and
also it's like blonde
indie like why did they go with
blondie when there's one blonde woman in
the group her name now blondie she's
shutdown with dagwood she is the vibe
yeah why not call it debbie harry
and friends these images are did you
look up right said fred or just
to see that and now is sort
of fascinating and yeah the the sheer
baldness of
the whole the share power baldness the
ostentatious baldness so for my brothers fred
and richard fairbairn oh okay i always
say accept your apology i know that
was not easy for you to do
it must've been like really no because
i still don't feel wrong
when they were little one time fred
like said said right and it was
so funny they were like now are
they
that is so funny it was like
inside right i was named earlier the
novelty song right said fred which was
oh so i'm sort of an actor
bernard cribs and nineteen sixty two and
those creepy into the murderer so i
saw both of us are right alright
they married yeah another question like this
yeah married fred also appears to be
unmarried at the moment this appears to
be
oh mercy commanded holding always gotta everyone
is good to their vaccine ah stuff
sounds asking if these two brothers were
married to each other that's sick sickness
not married they just closed hopefully the
supreme court will rule on this soon
still against vaccine despite being admitted to
hospital with covert nineteen oh yeah yeah
no richer
richard richard not fred rye then roy
anti vac sense the green cross code
whatever that is um anyway false tone
yeah
i'm too sexy for my shirt too
sexy for this job
now i'm going no dags i still
love it when people dab in a
comics it's funny i like it but
i know it's dorky i like it
when i see y'all jabbing like really
funny it really gets me
what are we thinking ooh i've been
imploded inside like when kids do it
i don't like it when adults do
it i like it when anyone dab
it's really makes me laugh we go
dumb even when i'm watching a tv
show from five years ago when it
was popular or are just starting to
see like a whole family do it
on family feud or something i love
it
the funniest classy speaking of wiggling our
show next weekend that's right oh well
that will not be over by the
time people are here now people are
hearing this thursday yes but the show
is sold out lorna there are a
few standby tickets are you gonna do
you think i could get a stand
by ticket i'm gonna really paid three
hundred dollars re cameo cameo prices once
it gets
hold out because cameo present yeah um
yeah laura and i are gonna be
captains in ah in an all comedian
ah ah feud it's called comedian feud
um it's like family feud though it's
just what's ripping off family because here's
a little secret extremely fringe family feud
just it's just comedians thoughts so should
i call the mark goodman bill thompson
production
tion
aren't you excited i ever said it's
gonna be fun and i've never been
to that theater before me neither i'm
looking forward to although i imagine delius
been there tonight i don't remember where
the show is what theaters at the
palace the lesion the lesion interesting i
guess i have a show tonight and
it will be my first emphasize with
my one wild horses show doing a
show with nadia how do you feel
about that i feel
i'm excited you know having had covered
nineteen the novel canal binah i feel
much more at ease right now about
doing because you're in the ninety day
window yeah my new dance the naval
kannada virus yeah and now is really
scary because you wanna vote on the
book
yeah yes yeah i did it we'll
see i'm gonna have fun i think
i think but i'm tired you know
i'm finding that um i'm doing some
more i'm having some more days that
feel pre-pay indemnity where am i doing
like four things and i know i'm
doing like woo
let me tell you some new girlfriend
i last night we had tickets to
go see a show we had tickets
to show
when we had tickets to show ho
hoes and um this is a new
segment on freedom but we don't go
digging oh i know this baby doe
go this is a different thing we're
both very tired and i was like
what if we just bailed on this
what you're like
wait a minute for the past few
years we haven't been able to do
anything yeah yeah what was the show
the show was the very funny sam
pancake oh yes i was doing a
um a one person show at he's
very funny this this weird little theater
space that i'd heard ah heard about
but never been to before there's a
restaurant called casino del campo oh yeah
eastman i went to see the golden
girls that sandwich yes i wish oh
so does sam ever leave that place
no i think he lives there weird
he got yesterday
yeah because kinda confusing with the stairs
and the audience was leaving please take
me with you yeah it's like whatever
it like it's like fucking when you
go down the stairs to get out
you have to go up them oh
he doesn't know the concept of up
yet i don't he should watch that
movie yeah well it's a big concept
in that movie oh yeah is i
am too sad i think i got
it because the end of the show
he wants someone to pick him up
he is going up these puppies
s o but he picked up he's
gonna do it yeah you could do
it a true so he sought he's
almost there i think it'll be awesome
he is raised up above the ground
which is one step of putting your
feet on stairs yeah oh so did
you feel paul did you feel better
for having gone yeah dude i'm so
glad i went yeah and i was
i was retired it is weird i
we kept our masks on um can
leave you
mask on
can we come to and ah it
was ah so it was like i
and of course the fucking when i
would laugh it would fog up my
glasses and i'm making me have you
have taken your glasses off i did
i periodically would take them off and
read everything man it's gonna raise yeah
how have i figured this out yet
i don't know twitter
years in the priority should be fixing
so people with glasses are mad if
they feel they fixed iphones to where
you can unlock them with a mask
on yeah i know i still didn't
set that lagom with a mask on
but they add so many masks that
i fell for that were like the
ultimate for glasses wearers and it's like
they were said i fell for it
i thought you meant romance
i'm in love with this man cheney
and i went through a rough patch
and i was involved with a mass
jamie she opened up her hearken
vba sorry sorry sorry if you fucked
the mask i think i go sideways
i think it takes dude if you
fuck the mass everybody i would be
high fiver you so fucking hard right
because we likely coolant would be the
funniest fuck of all i wish i'd
never told you guys that i was
romantically attracted to the mast because this
is
isn't there is it the green color
it's every hasan
yeah
jim carrey as the mass yeah that
is you think he ever did you
ever did it um well you know
you have the mcmahon tried it was
hard to take off sometimes he probably
had his girlfriend visit the thought yeah
people were to the shaft you would
do voices when he would have sex
i hope so yeah yes he probably
has for sure he has you
think it's been requested or he just
provided that oh no that was an
idea real huge obama do you think
dave that's someone else i'm gonna do
a cameo while they're fucking you what
if we moved on to someone i
don't respect like dave cool yay
do you think he did like when
would he do pop him he was
my fantastic sharp full-out when she went
down on him in the middle of
dinner right did you think he was
going like a noise in the middle
of a theater in the middle of
the theater and she wouldn't do that
during dinner mouth you could do it
depending on the length of the table
cloth you can do two meats and
one mouth thickens
wash potatoes to music one mouth
jesus anyway that's not even true
into farming yeah i mean a hotdog
and chicken at the same time yeah
well or like jehovah aggressive beacon it's
already an okaloosa the same please
but
yeah but it's
cut up a steak and then i'll
cut up like bits of ah i
don't know some venison and national girl
i'll kind of veal i'll cut up
only veal and pork chop all you'd
be an important to me you're right
sometimes like young chicken meat young chicken
ie trying to get that vil experience
young chicken meat if you're listening please
we wanna help your song go to
number one so's young chicken meets new
hit single
antivaccine or die trying young chicken in
the corner to get to the good
icac and in the mid-late oh yeah
lauren are you are you feeling tired
do you think because of of changes
in your body due to having a
baby i would say so and i
would say the schedule change dr nelson
come with yes and then the fact
that i had the carpet which i
think also maybe
but i was already tired like this
i think that i am tired because
i get up at five yeah every
day and i lost i'm moving pretty
much all day and yeah and i
have to do other things and work
and use my brain so you're pretty
much around five am wordle sender yeah
yeah but in europe europe today was
a forehand yeah i mean i say
it today so i actually didn't
i was calling your house yeah she
says she loves it there yeah no
shit i'm to sleep in yeah no
this was a real like four am
oh no i'm not getting back to
sleep and then so then good you
know i know eventually i wilson today
was eight am to ten am yeah
i think i did my work around
six forty five and then i was
told i could keep sleeping
cause oh how nice by holly yeah
her face go back to bed baby
i'm good with these toys we got
to get out
yeah she's just the best so is
she sleeping in a more regular to
sleep without she she was a long
time doing one week of mill the
night now she is not she does
not do it anymore but she might
wake up at five forty five or
six forty five or seven so it's
kind of we see but so some
days it's really early okay yeah but
she's doing great when she go to
schools where you can forget
about all this and i'd be in
about five years oh man five years
from now no i guess i mean
you know i guess pre-school yeah but
no no no no no hold it
in oh my god calls on those
no no no no no no no
no no no no novel you get
and you know that's not of this
show
oh no not this show oh no
no no no no no no no
no no no shit shit shit out
of you who shit out oh god
he's shaky thank you my nose it
i shake well i know yeah you
literally were like real your whole head
was like vibrate i did not know
that that happened and your tail went
all crazy yeah all because i sense
danger and your wings oh my god
they were flagging away show off my
crash
yeah wayne's on ya
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back merida high e
and we're back and may i just
say paul brought the blackest banana yeah
it's oversee it's on it's last legs
you are it's really like within the
hour it's going to be too oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's gonna
go black it's banana wow you really
did there was
a ah club in philadelphia called the
black banana who was there an after
hours club who after which hours ah
the idea of one pm and two
pm so after but after one after
two after one after two a few
get there after one ha you're a
little early come back after two now
what's your perfect banana visual
will you know when do you know
it's just right for you for me
it's gotta be the yellowest it can
be yeah yes me too yes there's
like a green there's a little bit
of green at the top of the
stalk yeah i'm ok with that i'll
try it but when you man when
it's not ready and you buy the
hay oh i've never been into a
banana it's not ready what never alway
a's been ready for me that privileged
life you must say actually that's wrong
i hate you oh yeah the littlest
planet today that was wow fantastic and
why do people listen to this alumni
green yeah some people like embrace overall
and some people like him
lockett brown yeah that and i don't
eat the whole pan in the freezer
to make bread and fuck you yeah
yeah we know i'll buy my banana
bread yeah exactly thank you very much
do you guys this is what i
do any bruises i cut them out
while you're such a baby the fuck
thinking oh what a fucking baby any
brand any brand nope i don't like
it i sometimes i'll get
into the dog sometimes i'll bite around
it what come on guy it's going
to be really sloppy duty i just
i don't like the sloppy duty
ah but skyler so this guy's like
good so what's the crust of my
daily mommy banana wow you guys probably
eat the little stick at the bottom
love it it's the best party bus
talking about fuckin what do you call
it a stick at the bottom yeah
of a banana you know the little
thing at the bottom seed absolutely never
get there i always want about a
quarter of an inch of the banana
at the bottom you longer weird it
and everyone saw on one-part the whole
thing will pop out and i'm not
saying you're the weirdest several oh i'm
not your
the most wasteful that's for sure well
i'm so sorry he's doing with pure
scoop well you're leaving good banana on
the table this guy's just persnickety
i just stopped when i stopped
and you don't get stop is one
banana too much for you should they
sell shorter bananas for laura even they
do and if you make a little
one then when you see those little
ones i think now now you're talking
about penises right weather when goosebumps icewine
hello bananas
yeah um no yeah sometimes you see
those and you just think it's a
no for me today but i'm sure
so it's no for me dawg yeah
and for this reason i'm out randy
randy is he still around god i
think i thought he was ah touring
with a band that i thought was
good but i kinda like that it's
not dad in in in and oh
yeah because you play with journey i
forgot to play journey musician yeah yeah
i feel that a personality is a
manager know he was a bass player
daying and session musician he was great
i think it's a
ty i knew that and as time
has passed i stopped knowing that yeah
yeah um i don't where i was
thinking stuff knowing i was once on
a flight with him really and i
was getting on you knew everything would
be okay you were on a journey
with him true true
and we i was getting off the
plane and as i approached the exit
i saw him at the front he
was in first class nach yeah and
ah people asked him to take a
picture and it was of redeye and
so this was like oh that's fucking
food yeah and then ren did it
he was really nice yeah but then
when you go up to the friend
you say and do you have anything
you want to say to me
yes and i said i looked him
square in the glasses and i said
it's a no from me dawg and
how many times do people say laugh
a lot he laughed so much you
love so much they call the airline
just to be clear tease me see
he stayed in his seat while people
were getting off the plane until everyone's
upset he would make sure to be
seen by everyone i well what i
what i realized
later was there must have been a
chain of people taking picture must have
been a chain of people
yeah which you are you asking me
questions just to set you up for
science
wish you knew fleetwood mac's the chain
fleetwood mask
oh that's jim gary's ah this is
freeway recovery where he dresses as a
man that's stevie nicks wings things under
only happens when it's raining gray yeadon
but he closes with cuban pete of
course wants to hear yeah
ah i don't like flying with celebrities
i didn't realize it said the you
know like saying that only fire tell
you the thing that i did that
was like what totally i didn't know
i said it but but like i
was recording an ad or something and
i was like i'm sure i've told
this story but i was like just
at home i to help him and
i was like um well i said
it's my twitter bio boba and then
mike was like it's
traci reardon and i was like what
and he was like why like you're
doing that attitude yeah he was like
you said twitter by ah
yeah then i listened back and i
did but i would just send it
like that in my twitter bio bio
total bio it's not even know you
said it but i don't like terrifying
high flying with celebrities because i feel
like i feel like a plane is
more likely to go down with when
celebrities on it don't you think no
no no i think you're safe
what like when he saw randy i
thought it's all good here daily when
the plane landed i thought were okay
yeah you know all those famous know
but like lying to go down with
celebrity that you see the celebrities getting
on the plane and they're gonna say
so-and-so died and then there are some
later like and scott no i don't
care that there's not that many actually
well there's the the big one i
mean
even if you die and use a
cat you can't care about that you
wouldn't care i don't know really even
if you were an angel you'd you'd
say it's okay okay here you go
right to angel status i'm not gonna
be worried about petty bullshit i angel
status
seven
i've rebooked are you in the lounge
um i mean how many celebrities have
died on planes for oh my god
almost seth macfarlane leah almost macfarlane and
almost mcfarland almost doesn't count no except
in horseshoes and hand grenades but you
got okay so you got the big
three yeah the big bopper valley and
buddy holly yeah you got patsy
kline oh yeah you've got a randy
rhoads oh diddy i mean yeah that
was a weird one where the plane
was buzzing the tour bus or something
you got ah annoying me why what
did you say oh yeah yeah yeah
okay what about ah president of the
lee fan club put about to face
now what's her name from tmc
yeah plane crash no that wasn't a
plane crash wasn't what was it within
what's your name can't talk about left
i left lupus we got michelle lisa
left eye lopez
we've gotten in trouble every time we've
said a name of anyone and followed
it with a fact or what we
believe to get ah we can talk
about anyone and steven van zandt did
he know signals oh from leonard it
was like no one on the white
lamb it's ah stevie ray vaughan i'm
sorry oh it was a helicopter i
think was it stevie ray vaughan
or p v ray vaughan even a
pawn
if gave me poupon v greenwood but
you do have any tv vote
wow well we don't know we'd never
know do she died in a corpse
la lisa left eye lopez are you
taking a picture of the wifi that's
why i'm logging and she's logging into
it because she has too much stuff
she has to look up and show
i'm the resident googler this trip
this used to be stuff that chevy
hello that chat but see yeah exactly
it's like this this password is bananas
and we need to make dna is
your password on wifi should be like
cheese yeah let's stop trying to be
like it's one two nine one exclamation
like stop trying to be something that
no one can log into while these
businesses lee
teachers off of the one but who's
gonna feel mushy chee you know what
nehru i've cracked it i can't believe
they use cheese they've been guessing w
y x p m alright chavez said
chavez sent us a a comprehensive list
my god wait notable celebrities who have
died in aircraft personal chance why do
we want this i feel
this the scary commerce we have john
denver yes we forgotten about john i
just heard the best john denver song
the other day which one rocky mountain
high i mean it was daddy was
get drunk this christmas it wasn't one
of the super famous ones but i
loved it it was so dramatic let
me see if i can find it
hold on what did it make you
feel um skate just was like wow
this is this is ah
i was like this is ah ah
ah ah a sound from him that
i think this is it okay do
you want me to play it yeah
i do this is the eagle and
the hawk so magic
alright the eagle and the hawk by
john denver typical post if this is
the eagle and the hawk by john
denver here on thredup and we also
want to say that if you're out
there and you are related to john
denver we're sorry to bring up all
of these terrible memories about him diving
into play
crash but i'm sure you've heard his
music says that at least once or
twice we can't be the first time
you've ever heard it ah but here
he is this is eagle in the
hong kong three-day
uh turn it off turn off turn
on
this is though it's great
it's very soaring and sweep as it's
fitting an eagle and or a hawk
yeah
it's good can i say yeah it
feels a little derivative of his other
song calypso oh yeah call it ah
great so that's a great that's a
great fucking song he doesn't get his
due do you know what else he
is right now we love you buddy
the west virginia song country roads is
a take rate yeah take me home
grandma's featherbed i don't
no that one that doesn't sound good
it doesn't seem good it sounds gross
isn't about his grandma having sex is
it about when you pee in the
throat and it stays
stay okay here's some more people john
f kennedy junior linger yes of course
my featherbed my featherbed ah roberto clemente
oh yeah and stevie ray vaughan yeah
right yes um steve ray vaughn jim
crow che yabba leroy brown yeah
payne stewart i don't know who that
is it is golfer ah golfers don't
come golfers don't count as celebrities
it's really true though yeah troy gentry
who's this oh the landed gentry hs
montgomery gentry the country music duo or
so that you know it happens not
as much as you would think no
it's oh and then and john f
kennedy junior didn't count because he was
due he did it to himself he's
also still alive
as religious school i'm going on closely
still alive yeah during this he's because
people are gonna tag me and shit
now he's still allowing said guess what
i didn't say that that is my
favorite thing is when people forget who
said what yeah we got we got
we got both the eu and miga
both are the same brush recently over
something that
randi yeah i know right i don't
know about this and i don't like
this but you know the john f
kennedy junior still alive right yeah speaking
on this you know that he's still
alive he's gonna you know that j
f k junior is still alive and
evil eventually overthrow the government and here
the road is you know that you
know this
you say it all the time i'm
not speaking
ah no just ah
what a dumb country you believe is
fuckin like how did that get started
while doing one person said it once
and decided a day yesterday how everything
works i guess i do think there's
a conspiracy for every single death that
is ever like any media any total
person thinks something is not true about
everything yeah
yeah i'm sure someone thinks definitely not
true about everything yeah definitely penciling like
that i'm trying to think of like
who's definitely pence tried to write a
manufacturing licence i know amer that says
random word device had bigness know that
the biggest and m pen the biggest
impact
panel what are these words concerted that
want i know it was free paul
was the biggest seed what the fuck
is that concerted it's got dictionary show
or so now we're just looking at
screensavers here all trying to make you
guys learn new words
sounds like if your vocabulary has an
increased by one per day and i
will be quizzing sorry chips you've got
to improve your vocabulary your vocab and
pinel
oh the word in piano i love
these just the old adaptations reform the
pan pan da da da da da
da da da da da da da
da am but now no ma'am but
now do you think this is our
most disjointed episode i don't know it's
it's just great to be back together
with you guys one
okay and in pronounce spoof
i want to hear yeah i think
it's in panel it's not immunol just
well where did you say the marvel
covers episode of say panel in panel
in panel oh this sounds familiar so
yes
impanel him and you'll be to have
a degree in england yeah but i
like seeing it out of context it
should be to get into it they
want to enroll someone onto a jury
to get in panel and paneled yeah
okay they have to get a degree
in english you should have to pronounce
every single word in addiction
eating something i was zealots oh yeah
yeah yeah see let's well you know
way i think i thought that because
there's this black delicious song and at
the end he goes z lots and
i just in my head yeah why
is he saying that alphabet aerobics oh
and at the end he goes gets
to z and he says see it
but hey maybe i'm
i'm maybe i'm wrong how's sell zealots
you know so yeah that's that is
correct and but i said it wrong
when i first but i but i
thought i was reading it because it
was like a marvel care yes i
gave yeah no i've learned the out
of like that why it's just it's
the gibberish that you're reading in a
marvel nicole and i can barely get
through those summaries yeah i guess
for years i thought it was black
pant her
and he why is he wearing what
are his powers like pants
look
but would just the incredible hulk oh
i just thought you went ooh yeah
you look you you fucking goofy videos
yeah hey i played him i know
did you have sympathy for him because
you played him as a character i
know he was such an lady sort
of you know me
words about how we're not going to
hear a helicopters anymore i'm sorry everyone
about your helicopter it's too sad version
of the helicopter it's perfect he's looking
for someone he's looking for someone he's
looking for someone helicopter
wow yeah or how about this got
me in the feels
he found him
bye
la la la la la la that's
like the entertainment tonight theme anytime anywhere
i feel like entertainment today it always
is like nah about it but then
if someone dies is wow it's so
funny that's just still on why crazy
can get your entertainment news so much
easier than having watched my late when
that stuff's on tv we watch it
every once in awhile and like inside
edition and whatever do you look terrific
deborah norville who's that she's the host
of inside edition wasn't she like news
caster back in the day she's been
around forever she looks crazy in what
way like sexually yeah
deborah she arouses me
creep hey my wife is also aroused
by her what we just watching your
house your mutual hellcats global fucked over
norvell that's us through the whole we
can't talk about real people on the
show why because we will forever be
indebted someone someone who knows deborah norville
we'll we'll write to us and say
really offended have ah you want to
fuck i've my way i feel that
overlap is so so slim i want
you to take the chance so we
get talking about deborah norville yeah okay
also it's a compliment it's a compliment
that you want to fuck size versus
sensitive no to compliment
ah lori and come on why can't
i wake up at peak performance for
last week a sixty minutes lauren is
bouncing we believe we're doing this one
thirty five you're bouncing back and forth
between absolute chaos and total shutdown i
know it's really the way my brain
feels you were on a plane yesterday
though
it went from no i was on
a plane on ah oh no the
ring the grudge
my day was thursday well then get
it together you my dear girl my
dear boy can i tell you something
i'm mad at myself for seeing the
ring first when it was the grudge
that i meant yeah but they're the
same thing hey i wasn't really because
only one has the noise yeah no
shit bring that bring the grudge bring
the noise bring the grudge bring the
noise
yeah i love that song what if
it was called doug rudge what did
it feel like
right right a urban redneck
how about white lauren i was just
thinking about something you wouldn't get okay
to tell try us don't censor yourself
because we wouldn't get ah yes millennial
isn't about center part was about doug
funny doug funny you're
you nailed it don't know who said
it but i don't want to know
dogfight to go in because i was
dug twenty third to garrett from nickelodeon
movies oh and when you said doug
grudge i thought one of his last
name let's ride jenny was doug right
wait i'm familiar with the cartoon character
doug doesn't rush for more money yeah
well his girlfriend's name is patty mayonnaise
what i didn't know that yeah i
just know doug as a barely drawn
character whose name was doug you know
i don't mean does last name is
funny and you're no duh i'm two
minutes behind user arno dog
roger what was rodgers rabbit kevin federer
roger kevin
dodger
okay we're gonna take a break like
yeah
we born a yawning ghost trauma game
okay okay okay
ah yeah pacman pacman know what maybe
yeah but it's from baby
maybe i don't know for me it's
from when you kill the ducks and
duck kind to them that dog gets
up and laughs da what dog con
ah alright look let's take a break
let's regroup alright with different groups slapped
so yeah when we come back three
other people will be here laughing embase
and we're back yep we're back we're
back lauren just blew my mind because
she had a little ah between ah
segment snack animal crackers with chocolate ships
and you know they're from they're from
wholefoods and they're really good they're the
three six
eighty five labels say that there's something
about them that i love and i
don't know it's just the commercials because
their cookies are even middle over commercial
they're what i love is that they're
cooking
what else is free of sugar if
there's something i can't i can't explain
it fully but i feel that the
chocolate chips are cold really may i
have one yeah
so now you think you think that
the cookies at room temperature
but the chocolate chip is cold there's
something chilly about these chips okay break
it in bring it in half this
is a commercial alright or just give
just give it to oh my god
oh god someone talk while this happens
la la la la la la la
la la la la be good be
good i know what you mean good
beagle is a cold burst that kind
of reminds me of ships ahoy chips
exactly what i was thinking too yeah
do you think the chocolate chips are
at a different temperature just naturally at
the restaurant today for
level than the rest of ibm like
they're like oh lepro way of life
but you know what i mean like
yeah like operating on it it's not
like chocolate chocolate right it's naturally cooler
room temperatures is like two degrees colder
i think so yeah i think that's
what i'm getting paultre that movie twenty
eight grams was about do you have
a three-tier force yeah fuck
i can do yeah well guessing anyway
each your boy do it where do
you get a load of this and
it's not me the joker
this was submitted by
he was embarrassed on a previous episode
of threesome we should do it different
one
yeah sure we get closer like read
it yeah this time and then we
do it every game and then next
time we'll do his cpy thomas sorry
about the mix-up before but you're a
big boy and you'll get over it
or your big girl i've no idea
what you are or who you are
i love you
so k p gives us this press
junket one person is a movie star
doing a press junket for a made-up
movie one person is an interviewer from
a random local news station and the
other person is the stars handler trying
to keep the interview on track love
it now
we should add something to it right
as some way somebody has to see
what it yeah we do that other
game i was telling you about last
time which is um it's the one
where you guess the celebrity based on
quite okay you're like you're trying to
figure out who who the celebrities sorry
k p okay god no it's the
same thing though but will do the
press
junket but the the interviewer has to
guess who the celebrity is oh right
but then what does the or the
hand or maybe the handler has to
guess who the celebrity is that's what
it is we'll decide who the celebrity
is you're like if i'm the stand
and what how does that work because
we'll be having this conversation about a
made up movie
and then you the questions you ask
will be like sort of leading lauren
into like who the celebrity is i
swear this kind of so different than
what i'm saying i don't give one
shit
i'm saying something totally
i feel like it's are we just
gonna abandon this k p person being
i tell you what k p you're
not impressing your kitchen digital what i'm
saying is the game you in your
head think of a celebrity yeah and
then i say what kind of shoes
are you you're all i remember this
now and then you say
this is a different thing what and
you know example but are you saying
layer that on top of k p
suggestion no no you're using a band
k p we're not abandoning babies okay
big guy let's go here and gone
into a behind know but i think
it would be a very tempting let's
do i always literally acting out let
me just say everything straight here yeah
yeah i was here to scenario that
you just requested where we abandon the
game again and the humour i said
that and you have you have a
heartless outlook where you think i'm i'm
telling the truth and you're willing to
do it kevin marked it on his
and do it to cut off the
power we don't do it right i
watched the mark and i thought we're
doing this we're going nowhere cutting
a p again no it's not happening
and then you said oh i don't
like this game you're saying even though
i wanted you to do this and
actually let's mash with commands that can
really try to fight can't imagine having
this kind of can i be the
tiebreaker here in a personality
yeah alas
to me it's really fun well i
had a bubble my throat what about
no why don't we add something to
k p's think wow i don't want
to do this i do wanna play
please up i'll just like kpi's game
if y'all fuckers wanna do it why
don't we dilemma where can i finish
my god yeah yeah yeah yeah kind
of finish kinda finish
yeah she's got she's got a finnish
dad vanish can i better finish
fish right okay finish um i do
want to play lawrence game what if
we decide we're going to play that
next episode
right now okay and then we do
abandon kpi's idea for this week yeah
cpy send us something different maybe send
something different with one more level but
one more level on it yeah it's
making making honestly the level i suggested
would work and i would but it's
similar to other games so i come
up with a new order you're not
going to clean make any shinshu at
all your
listen actually it wasn't i was trying
to map it under what i already
said and it made no sense that's
okay p once again you have lost
i'm so sorry you're out no not
forever you got you have another dancer
yes one more chance and then we're
abandoning you for every team usa gmail
dot com yes so so
e alright so what are we doing
we gotta get to the three thing
why don't you guys fucking talk you
love to do it oh really
you know that i'm totally silent every
time i'm not on a podcast it's
weird i wish you wouldn't do that
took a vow of silence yeah with
podcast exception we went on vacation together
i know it was uncomfortable just staring
thank you olivia for the pins thank
you olivia for the pin just want
to say real quick thank you olivia
for my key for the
faker show march we love your pains
you listen to mommy oh no please
queen from march nineteen dominant guess that
was twenty nineteen yeah twenty nineteen boy
man a lot of great mail from
twenty nineteen and then nothing and it's
like everyone stopped for two years like
they yeah you aren't going to be
like ah the mail was still working
pretty famously in twenty twenty
oh hey the united states postal service
and a couple of hundred bucks on
stamps to keep this shit oh yeah
and my good buddy louie de joy
keep it everything flowing i'm so glad
you said to join um bring this
noise bring the joy this is a
game there's no name on this wot
anonymous is it from you kevin he
says he shakes his head no maybe
it's an honest guy who wrote all
those great quotes oh man and then
a great book yeah he was that
man
ask
this is a game called sail away
sail away sail away sail away this
may be the person's name okay whopper
labile whopper blob will be yeah that's
what they listen to their name come
on blah blah blah thank you for
this and congratulations you trick me into
saying your name don't say
more dives for this three cheer there
are two salespeople and one person who's
purchasing a boat each salesperson is trying
your best to sell the boat their
boat to the customer but each salesperson
is also allowed to say three things
about the other salesperson's boat that have
to be true okay and we count
em off like our fingers so that
we know when we're out and i
think we can use fingers
um i guess it's like
yeah but it's it's just not denying
what the other person says yes and
so then then the customer can decide
which boat yeah sounds better after that
yeah great you want to buy the
boat since you have the captain's hat
on yeah that makes sense yeah okay
checks out
i just checked mix yeah i'm so
hungry bowl party next best one ever
missing the crackers now i
i think the salts already makes robot
activate i wish they had the ritz
crackers still but they took those out
but that was when they got covered
in the dust to their to their
deal with ritz expire i don't freaking
know i think it was an acrimonious
split i think the salt on pretzels
is two degrees hotter than everything wow
you ever get a pretzel and you're
like wow this
pretzel is making me hot that's why
i blow my pretzels before anything i
blow on everything before it even ice
cream i blow everything all of all
of my food is dirty blow everything
and that i eat it actually
disgusting come on let's sell this guy
a boat okay oh my whoa hey
sir thinking thinking thinking hi your cell
phone yeah but you need to
what i'm about to try to make
i'm gonna say your boat right now
on the phone okay i've got a
great hey excuse me sir i'm gonna
vote stories my aunt speaker is my
is my associate trying to try to
call you before i can talk to
you yes yes if i can tell
you about it i always get to
go always get to them right before
you do it's called she's right but
she's right behind this partition just come
out ah hello
oh okay you look like a little
gnome well because i i'm trying to
go visit of of eyes type thing
o type thing with a life right
kind of people who are munchkins not
gnomes no but because i don't think
yeah i was hiding behind a partition
oh i so that part was like
the wizard of oz topic but he
said you look like a gnome that's
related that person who's me and you're
wearing a homemade shazam costume yeah
unfortunately i couldn't get the thunderbolt quite
right yeah yeah bo you got my
attention hey god is yeah you look
so now you've lost it i'm so
confident that you're going to buy my
boat i'm gonna let her talk okay
my boots actually a leaf it's so
durable it is strong and it's so
natural made from the most of leaves
in the most world we've got the
made from the motion leaves in the
most elderly sin don't listen we've got
the show listen by the way she's
selling a used boat but a used
leaf by the way this is this
is the leaf that moses was born
in isn't that may sail down the
river and it's strong and durable sprayed
with hairspray it is never going to
crack and there is no leaks it
is so beautiful and green and only
brown and the parts were
it's been seen by the sun okay
is there like a cabin um hey
tell chief just you know leaf it's
basically a canoe they're easy to seat
is made out of twigs the twigs
are very sticky and they are very
picky okay anyway you can beat that
because sight unseen i'm leaning towards your
boat yeah and it's got a b
big big big paddle yeah it's good
guy by the way it's not a
paddle to steer the boat with it's
a paddle to spank your passing you
don't even have to tell me your
facts okay i got a regular boat
right here tape joy
to the bottom okay but and they're
patched their past we pass orleans right
and they match poorly our patch poorly
backs i've learned yeah ah but then
we repacked them over the thorough grammar
package these other yeah they're all good
and um gallagher lives on the boat
oh i'm taking a leave
hey
liam gallagher lazy thousand dollars it's liam
gallagher we should make oh yeah watermelon
liam gallagher the comedian water liam gallagher
this has gotta be sure too risky
i'm taking the lead
alright bye pleasure doing business with you
your opinion venmo or zelle we're done
here
and that's how you play there you
go hey the game and it's that
simple it's that easy blah blah and
c k p that's what would be
happening if the game luis k p
knew
will you take me
alright guys we've got gotta go oh
i'll say we do yeah um thank
you for listening we are threesome usa
on twitter and instagram we are freedom
usa gmail dot com if you wanna
send us a three-tier phone number phone
numbers still in the waves apparently takes
a long time to get within say
that we have a number why are
we doing here because the case
plus when it finally happened or maybe
it's gonna be huge because it's gonna
be the season finale i think kevin's
been putting an emoji instead of numbers
is what he told me he's like
oh i'm using my emoji keyboard somewhere
yeah i wish we could get a
number that was all ten was so
awesome it would be awesome i'd use
the eggplant for every single one well
because i was like the deck plan
eggplant eggplant water squirt water squirt
teach speech
um it wasn't discussing before if you
want to listen to us anywhere podcasts
are but if you wanna hear ad-free
episodes you can hear it on stitcher
premium and cb world dot com there
you go we love you very much
thanks so much for all the male
will be back next week with fish
for fun forty-two forty-two by