laredo
nah
take it out take it
um welcome i'm scott i joined i
bought where robots sorry guys were robot
sorry we got turned into robots since
the last oh such a long story
oh russian file explaining but will favor
your tweets
um welcome to the show this is
a immediately paul's on his phone for
some reason board bus i see oh
yeah okay is that cool to say
yeah i guess it's fine like honesty
i'm easily bored because i'm so smart
ah hell is other people people make
small talk i'm like yeah
you're boring literally get to the good
stuff i want to hear about your
innermost thoughts feelings dialogues and eight let's
make this real i would hate people
who do that i was like yeah
come on we're having a very facile
conversation let's dig down to the real
stuff you can't point it out if
you're gonna do that you gotta just
get the combo you've gotta just do
it yeah you can't shame and blame
yeah shame and blame shame and blame
part of my life just that it's
just a song about me shame blame
shame and blame a part of my
life for you can't do accept that
fact
i'm not perfect neither are you shame
and blame a part of my life
who's made you the most who's shameful
and blame folk yeah who's shamed you
the most and just simple conversation
wow just someone you don't know about
early action but suddenly you're just like
god why do i why are you
trying to make me feel bad i
feel i just had it happen with
somebody the other day yeah just you
walking down the street just you know
if somebody i know but not well
but they just really blatantly insulted something
that i'm that i did
what do you do it's it's in
the future so it doesn't it's this
hasn't had this is a time travel
anyway
bag because i don't want to talk
about the specific thing but like basically
i was a part of something and
this person happened to see it and
they said it was not good and
i was like why would you say
that to me it's my blog lie
now i feel bad and i haven't
even seen it i don't even know
like i don't have my own opinion
is i wanna just say fuck you
but then my initial reaction was
wow now i'm afraid to see it
and then that person was like oh
bye so you'd never said fuck you
know i i was surprised i was
so surprised with it but you know
when i think i tend to stick
up for myself but if something surprises
me so much i'm like duh
you're finally gone i didn't um know
what to say and also you could
always reach out to the person now
it just me dad is fighting you
get a chance to say this at
the time but fuck you yeah i
meant i meant to say that that
was really
i forgot about that being an aspect
of the song whip it by devo
is that it's not too late do
with it you'll feel chapters you still
have a chance to win lane um
i think what happens in those moments
is someone is crossing a line in
such a colossal way that of course
you don't have a response yeah for
that because it's like you have to
process i wouldn't have someone
really to me something they're in is
bad yeah i had one the other
day where i've felt bad about it
my friend was talking about a new
record that he really liked and before
he could even talk about it i
was like oh i hate that record
blah blah blah and gave all the
reasons why i hated it and i
was like why am i who let
him enjoy his record like why do
i why does my
opinion have to supersede his yeah you
know what i mean why because it's
not worth putting in there i've become
so conscious of that because i think
because of the internet you see how
often people do it because how often
people check because this was the album
because the internet goes yeah this is
america i mean on the internet um
you see how often people offer an
unsolicited opinion about so
something that just doesn't need to be
there yeah and like i realize it
makes me so conscious of what i
do that and i've stopped myself so
many times now from chiming in like
why didn't care for very much like
yeah that's the shit yeah not the
taco and i've done that too but
i feel like it sometimes i do
it because i'm like i i also
saw that thing and i
didn't like it and if my friends
just got something they watched like we
have we don't know anyone and end
or whatever yeah i'm like i wanna
say i didn't like it because i
want to talk about it you want
to talk about life because you're an
artist you wanna talk about why something
works or why something you like about
it because i hated that or whatever
and then like but i feel like
it does shut down things because i
don't shut down things like oh i
guess i'm dumb because i liked it
yeah something prevention it also depends on
the relationship yeah and it depends on
what you want to say what about
brother to uncle ho scale well i
would rather let's don't a brothers shins
as an uncle just so brother if
ever brother and someone isn't
oh god
brothers didn't know they were playing if
you if you are another if you
have a brother i mean if you
if you yeah yeah yeah no no
that's true the doctor was a woman
you can hear you can be a
brother without having a brother yes but
you have younger badly
our brothers know i can have a
brother without being a bro good news
for you sorry i guess my brother
really yeah i guess we're undercover yeah
but toddler loves i have my brothers
i would rather love i wish i
only had sisters that i could talk
to uncles about things i don't like
yeah no but unfortunately your brother to
die has been cast what i don't
like is someone i mean putting online
that they hate something or yeah i
don't read
really see the point in that though
i'm sure but even like coming up
with most cutting hilarious joke about a
recent show that's not good what's the
point i'm putting it out there i
feel like i try to be very
sparing with that the notable exception for
me in recent years was making fun
of the new twin peaks which i
really enjoyed because it re
the bothered people that i that i
mean you weren't like yeah yeah and
i and i understood the the the
attraction of being a troll online oh
because yeah you because it's hilarious it
was funny to me that people were
upset that i didn't like this tv
show pairs really yeah no it's just
i've stopped i've i often will like
be like oh man this is a
funny
tweet about something that i hated some
show that i hated and that's just
like who cares yeah no i got
busted the other day with the other
day who were you walking down the
street like those you just the other
day checking my twitter ah somebody had
posted walking down the street yeah ha
my twitter how
it was a good tory
an uncle told the brother you must
not say i was somebody that i
follow on twitter that i really enjoy
i think this real donald trump huh
what's the combination between noodle drum don't
drop and lauren lovers
well l the idea loves and trusts
looking i'm in no way to take
what would it take for you to
have sex adult trump money or there's
nothing that could do it there's nothing
there's nothing out about for you for
me
i'm okay really affected you already have
just really putting myself known but i
mean really being an honest about it
putting myself in this situation it probably
would have to be in the it
would be money definitely well for sure
but like think about this if it
gave you like millions of dollars then
you bought a house with it or
something you'd be like this is the
house that that
i thought donald donald trump got me
but what if it were a transactional
thing that was not about money also
whatever it was through a glory hole
i didn't have to know it was
him until later you know you must
know you must i would have to
know but okay show because the way
the deep blue what if it's a
thing where pubic hair looks just like
the hair
it's all swept over underneath his ball
and pushes into the glory hole
pushes through
just balls through just like hey those
aren't necessary for this i want you
to smoke
like one of those things where it's
like okay i will have sex with
donald trump and then he has to
resign as president yeah yes just like
yes yesterday nidhi he had been asked
to admit he was a terrible incompetent
president and everyone who who works from
sb fired and they have to get
all people who i would take out
but he can never go back on
it
because you'll never go back you can
say like a year later out after
he's out of office like i just
did and i guess he has to
stand by it forever and i get
thirty million dollars the idea yeah i
would need lots lots of money but
the idea of that wouldn't be enough
for you thirty million dollar no not
thirty million i'm just him resigning and
and i wanted all the wrong i
wouldn't you wouldn't
take it for the team for free
i guess i'd probably get a lot
of money in like speaking engagement
speak about the comb over on his
balls so what's cool about his cause
they're so small i mean it's like
small balls make your dick look big
to him what else would i pictured
him putting his balls through the glory
hole i was thinking i had a
whole sentence in my head where he
says i have to push him through
because then you can buy perspective makes
me think
like that's like the raiders of the
lost ark boulder yeah on the other
side right and then he puts his
his dick through there and the years
from the other side of the wall
yeah no because he's like yeah gotta
get back gotta get them ballsy like
now huh yeah i think i think
i would do it here's
the thing i would do it because
i love him so just put that
out there i would just want to
do it but like emotionally yeah my
daughter yeah and magnetically yeah but in
terms of like trying to help the
world i'd really wanna get it's actually
you're so drawn to someone emotionally you
don't find them a trap physically attract
yeah and it's weird that this very
strong
reaction doesn't bring along with it the
physical attraction yeah for like trump well
i can look like like yeah i
can look at him and say i
don't think he's attractive person but i
really am drawn drawn to him just
like humans love him and i love
him i'm in love with him i
love him and i'm in love with
my boys anyway
i got busted online because it's somebody
that i that i follow on twitter
it was funny and this is i
think a fun way that you can
be negative on twitter that's not hurting
anyone but she was saying what um
what video game tropes do you not
like and mine is like she gave
like a list of things like you
know for me one of them is
when you save somebody in the game
and then they say it took you
long enough for oh yeah like oh
my god things had happened and i
thought it was funny and i wrote
back i am playing this one game
right now and a named the game
and it's it's full of long-winded characters
that you have to listen to in
order to get to the next thing
and then fuck
the developer the or whoever created it
or whatever yeah somebody tagged the guy
oh man i just deleted the tweet
and hey yeah people tag the person
yeah if you're just trying to do
a funny thing or whatever or i've
had people tag somebody on something i
said on a podcast that was not
even intended to be like a thing
and then they're like yeah you said
this about so and so and i'm
like that's not even when i met
and if you listen to the context
that's not what i said and like
the podcast was even worse because it's
like you may have recorded that months
ago and you're like i don't remember
remember what my mom obama oh but
my ballpark that's why we have this
flanking rule here we don't remember anything
that's exactly right not so anyway yes
so i wrote to do
so i wrote to me
arena coming up so i wrote to
the guy it said why did you
do that and he said um ah
because he wrote the game and i
was like i know yeah back part
of a understand why would you do
that yeah i said to see a
friend of yours because i'm shit lord
he said he's a very good friend
of mine and i said
why would you bring this to the
attention of your good friends like well
i think he would be tickled that
you mentioned his game or whatever and
it's like the guy doesn't follow me
i don't think he's gonna find this
amusing and some person who doesn't know
who it is is talking shit about
his game and so but the more
i thought about it the more i
thought the
the i i i came to the
conclusion of like well i just shouldn't
have written that and i should have
mentioned the game by name there's no
reason for me to do that right
i forgot i forgotten that moment that
it's payback and i didn't forget that
it's public but i've forgot like it
never occurred to me that oh the
person who wrote this game whatever yeah
because he was this thing yeah
existed yeah you didn't see the people
behind yeah it's certainly end i don't
i like i don't i did i
did a thing that i wouldn't like
if somebody else did right and i'm
so as as annoying as it is
that guy you know tag that guy
yeah that other guy was like well
i shouldn't written the thing in the
first place because that's not what i
want to do anyone could say
see it eventually but also the same
thing as telling someone someone was talking
shit about them it's like you don't
really need to know that yeah i
don't really want seriously helped me it
leads to twitter being like a complaint
box yeah people just you know like
every single day we're just reading complaints
and complaints and complaints about people's lives
are people just like wanna see what
happens you know they want to see
like oh there
now they're gonna get into it or
something or this is gonna be some
fun fireworks for me to watch but
also for his forget it jake it's
chinatown forget it jake it's chinatown jake
g o u j come to me
get a chinatown take a chinatown euro
or zorin jump in
i'm scare all you need to know
is the words forget it jake it's
chinatown jake it's tended now we're having
fun as a fallow we do it
all three of us easy fuzzy hey
chinatown
ah we need to take a break
okay take a break jake it's chinatown
by upi because i rolled
okay we're back
ah yeah the dude friend of the
two jags it's two chinatowns if that
was the last movie i was sad
as it was would have been like
you got me you got me giga
got me to stick around until the
end of this retroactively on board with
just get and enjoy although we're doing
exactly what we were
just talking about i've never said no
i was just roleplaying i've never seen
the tuesday cited the supposed plot or
playing in front of me yeah thinks
it does it it doesn't you're smiling
well and yeah makes me horny be
me ya it makes me horny baby
young yeah do you remember doing forty
first sunday
can i tell you my journey with
the word horny which i hated and
make me oh yeah when i was
younger yeah and then all of a
sudden i want to say this year
it became hilarious yeah it's adorable i
think it's accusing were saying it the
word horny i think is cute but
what could you say instead aroused
but like this aroused but that's the
thing it's like pussy and horny there's
no good substitute leg no substitutions
and horny none taken on the sex
venue um you know like there's nothing
like i'm turned on but it's not
even the same thing you got me
go with you got my mojo rising
like in the mood and yeah i
guess but there's nothing good for pussy
you guys say horny guys say pussy
in a story that's
sewing in the mood the old glen
miller saw those early it is when
you think about it and birds do
it bees do it yeah you know
they were being a little gpa bird
to fall in love and it's like
let's fuck even educated fleas fuck less
let's do it flash ah
i think almost every song is about
fucking otherwise like why would anyone write
a song unless it was about fucking
right oh it was gonna get you
fucked huh yeah what about songs like
they don't this this is the thing
that's not his songs anymore that was
in build cole porter days like references
to greek mythology and stuff oh everyone
used to know greek myths
els yeah well there would be like
good all that liz hell the world
ha
like okay elvis zero luckily there wasn't
that much stuff to learn at that
point so that's true until like fake
stuff this ah poor hercules slew medusa
yeah
i've heard i know a lot of
greek mythology like in fifth grade we
had to learn a lot of stuff
and we read the iliad and we
in fifth grade you had to learn
a lot of stuff we don't sorry
because mythology got hey forget this project
gee oh my god wait what do
you know well i don't know but
can we do celebrity jeopardy
oh yeah i forgot about that we
all have to sing the national anthem
and we all have to do celebrity
jeopardy what is what if we waited
jeopardy game japanese written to you to
say come to the audience i'm doing
that yeah so yeah where do you
go to and they said i wasn't
invited right yeah they said you specifically
can't come as something about algebra videos
tips
oh but i hadn't changed hey i
blocked that out of my memory wow
did you can still come if you
can i say something with some finding
a date that works you probably can't
go people who run social i can't
make makes are so busy people with
social media accounts or big podcast listeners
yeah because ah the the podcast the
big ones a mandolin and were able
to sushi they have this campaign there
tr
going to get there they want first
podcast to record in the goodyear blimp
and whoever runs the goodyear blimp account
it very much knows how to reference
things right from many different bias should
we should try to undercut them and
get their already established can we be
up there
our network's done
i do support their network a lot
i think it's great so well yeah
your email yeah driven the cast yeah
so so sorry yeah sure sure sure
enough about them so maybe i'll just
swing with them no forget check so
but what were you saying about jeopardy
you want to say well i was
thinking what if we actually have a
friend who ah
makes jeopardy games for like parties and
like we parties for like the we
have a little dinner party and then
he put together a jeopardy game and
we played it it was really good
so like like we could make one
like atlanta compete against each other on
it with video and on a computer
no no he just did with paper
oh we could do it like but
the person who makes it has to
do a lot of work sherman and
yeah you could also post also know
a lot of things are also bullshit
oh you boy
can you actually a sigh actually you
could pull it from a real jeopardy
that's true although i've memorized every jeopardy
but anyway would you hold a food
you guys do that sometimes yeah yeah
absolutely for feature shall we do it
maybe we'll do it next week where
we do and how do we buzz
in welfare name sarah name we just
have to wait it'll take a while
make the call you by our name
yeah call you call me by your
name and then that's how you get
buzzed in lauren ah no call me
by your name oh lauren your name's
lauren yes okay you're gonna fucking lose
we should we should try to convince
jeopardy to do a podcast we we
should it would be so unpopular anyway
why name popularity is what they do
which was gonna do it sarah uterus
whatever yeah sarah chanting go because mark
met her
three extra just three people on there
they got to fill five nights a
week come on just desperate friday i
want to see those fucking college kids
make you do it like a lot
of likes topics that we like like
music and movies culture tv songs seem
so crazy mythology now that you've already
told them you listen to
it so much this and i listened
to someone's greek mythology route yeah how
much you listen to a week like
mythology a week ah
your stories both a hundred stories one
hour
i still am waiting to be a
everyone we know seems to be like
they've there an answer on jeopardy i
know and all i have is between
two ferns was one well you come
on you fuck no but not my
name say my name company bang bang
was just a new black guys has
been an answer but i'll own i
don't i can't imagine how to do
something pretty big to be an answer
on there i've been on to paul
outcasts that were that were jeopardy were
they super ego and thrilling vitro wow
that is cool yeah yeah right yeah
but nothing for comedy bad at least
i don't think i'm the one they
treated at this today could get tickets
to the show so yeah but yeah
i guess so so i'll probably the
why would you see the cool face
lord is making rent
sit in the audience i hope i
get a jeopardy sweatshirt i mean i
wish they would show the audience jeopardy
they do everyone's auto to show a
little bit they've been doing it more
lately and it's really weird because it's
a really funny to marie what wheel
of fortune marie calendar's yeah wanna be
cool again and i'll owe everything is
marie calendar's some e
but like talk like the coopers cause
i'm saying i get to go i'm
not this isn't video here yeah i
get to go to jeopardy and you
don't why how come i don't get
to go wow can we do this
at a break no this is part
of the show now i'll see the
video it's like it's like oh content
from multiple mediums
god
my you know ah you know ah
my friend grey yeah yeah she's grey
griffin yeah she's raised by tv yeah
so listen to she would go
we we once found out that we
equally were fascinated with judge judy the
first season or whatever but she would
go and sit there that's so she
would sit there and she was right
behind the plaintiff several times where she's
just like that's so i think ryan
sofie can also be seen in many
yeah really he's obsessed too it's so
funny oh it's so good we should
go to judge judy too we were
looking up i would go i would
go what i love about judge judy
is their theme song is dun dun
dun dah dah dah dah dah dah
or whatever because it's like public domain
they don't mean want to spend they
don't want to spend money on the
saw and she has like mil i
mean she's like one of the riches
one of the richest people in the
world and they don't want to spend
money on a song here's what i
found out some da da da you
are
to enter the courtroom of judge judy
they don't want to pay a guy
for having written myself like a disco
version of beta
yeah
like obviously whoever disney the arrangement was
work for hire and they paid him
one fee for george duties ah teresa
toyoda but i'm here yes and i
found out from doing my show recently
because it came up judge judy yes
one of the most successful entertainers she's
number four on the list of the
most successful entertainers of the year up
from number forty three the year one
elite why don't why have you no
ideal or something new d should get
a podcast oh maybe she did what
did she have a podcast do you
think like everyone would just live
isn't to that does it translate where
people just like oh i want to
listen to judge judy i don't know
what else will my first impressions when
i was in middle when you got
let's hear no i can't do it
now i don't know i used to
watch when i was a kid yeah
tried out i don't i can't even
do it i want to be like
dopey dopey but i do it in
school my teacher thought was really funny
maybe get up and do it yeah
yeah would you were you always getting
hardest at all yeah um not really
but i know i would often talk
i would just shout things out that
hard shell thing my teachers always liked
it would be one thing i have
whoop whoop lady i would just like
make a sarcastic comment about oh yeah
right yeah
oh i don't i can't imagine doing
it now more like honey but jio
it honestly well crack showing up at
school oh no they're talking about honey
nut cheerios she's o'malley class you have
to honey nut cheerios or like honey
by jerry okay lord settle down do
you have i looked and went away
it was very good
get up here and do it oh
we love it alright i've got to
stop
what can i say i can only
imagine if you're a teacher you're just
looking for something to break up them
yeah probably it was probably just like
nice to not have to i had
i had some teachers who loved barney
clown and some teachers who hated yeah
and it was the teachers who didn't
like it i hated them janna was
with red when i was very mention
of course yeah
you punish them yeah you probably were
annoying them right life course i don't
know if it was like all the
time that i was saying stuff but
i definitely could i said whatever i
want so you're like six three you're
shouting us home huh
narratively comparative i get a kid yeah
yeah the kids like two one yeah
your system yeah you're just standing in
your arms can
you're doing richard nixon abortions no
not crook sexual relations with that lady
mr gorbachev i brought a crook lady
airedale that certain relation right mr gorbachev
i think richard nixon just called to
say he's not a crook lady
well easier isn't it
it's pizza day of excited who are
you doing first year three hundred years
whenever i hear something like more the
whole day or something i picture the
grossest pizza paula yes yeah but i
still want to eat it and like
the proportion of sauce to everything else
is out of whack like way too
much cheese
okay jonathan gold what's the team what's
the listen to this food bitch he
passed on he did pass on i
just can't
rip it i hope it's not too
late i own little type rip on
online liking when someone dies i just
don't like it i have a friend
it's f i die in the age
of the internet hopefully we'll be beyond
that at this point um don't type
rip it just looks hype rest in
peace or homie you know something of
real thought yeah it does look
just when it's just that it looks
like you might as well not say
yeah you know rep i've a friend
who barely ever tweets at all and
when he does it's like every four
days he just writes alright p whoever
died that day it's like i'm always
like i always look to you for
my latest r i p knew his
humor of it or that's just like
oh feels like saying so i feel
like saying is just like
days will go by nothing and then
just r i p his twitters an
internet cemetery
the bones of celebrities
where do you want to be buried
in your asshole
you want to put your ticket my
ass
on the ashes new asshole
i mean what do you think ok
look juicy you can begin really wanted
it i would if if you were
cremated i would allow them to inject
your reminder that let's let's let's okay
with something solely for which we talked
about this yes what if yeah you
predeceased lauren oh i see i thought
you write killer
no no no no really she steered
it
nice way of saying murder i'm gonna
predeceased you
what a threat if you die of
course i'm gonna dive over lauren okay
go ahead thank you there's more alright
that was it what have you died
before the i need you to die
first but you gotta remind him before
giddy jake it's chinatown so if if
you die first of content and you
agree to this before you die yeah
that one lauren dies after you yeah
she is cremated and then her ashes
are put to your body via your
rectum i hate this idea my rotting
corpse that it has been rotting going
to live acts but what no no
there's there's a time limit on it
so that if it own
only goes into effect if it's within
a three year window yes the corpse
is still my corpse is still kind
of fresh still intact wait why is
it why is my corpse intact for
thirty meaning it in the ground
it was like they dig me up
will be obvious or they're keeping me
in robbie some have a mausoleum you're
above grau i'm obviously you have that
then you guys both agreed you got
some money you got a muslim so
i'm dead you're dead muslims the way
to go i need to have a
structure people can walk i want to
have a little house where people can
go so i'm dead and you're dead
now
either of us are feeling this it's
not uncomfortable for either of us it's
just really feeling us to do i
only want to know michelle now we're
joking now both of your in both
of your wills were just like it's
not gonna make either of us uncomfortable
because we're both there it's like tofurky
because it's yeah we come back or
dunkin to admit was mentioned in this
podcast so
tofurky so people there's some people that
day when they hear it's done they're
like wow they really did they really
did it yeah whoo here's my question
yeah do you think it would be
allowed no well if you if you
agreed to wait what you going in
this mean if you put something in
your whistle live i'm gonna live forever
if you put something in you will
they have to allow it
to my life it's written down and
signed by a notary
i don't know were they they would
they dig up like it would cost
money you know they dig up my
body exhumed if unless you're in a
mausoleum which is the way to go
yeah okay so they pull out the
drawer whatever it is and i ask
a weird question yeah it might be
too personal no it's ok i hope
it's going to do oil this coverage
have i ever had the ashes oh
do you have like a thing that
explains what you want to happen to
have to die and what people should
do i e we just did it
oh my god we want you doing
a will yeah oh okay well that's
well there's the yeah that kind of
it's all it's all there's there's all
this stuff that's together that it's like
here's who to here's who's in charge
of this yeah here's the executor yeah
we did but we only did it
for money we didn't do like fun
things like like here's or even just
stuff like here's a letter that i
wrote to you that says a you
know all that kind of stuff yeah
we yeah we just did it for
money that and for our for like
you know do not resuscitate some things
like yeah yeah yeah yeah darwish
so no weeds we spent ah yeah
i mean we had to we had
to first of all talk about it
all and then we had to drive
out to westwood is the worst part
of it and um we had to
have like a long conversation with a
lawyer about yeah all that kind of
stuff it's yeah we saw we talked
about it all and then there were
still some questions that we had to
answer on this yeah we're like oh
oh ah burn me up yeah yeah
scotty
so weird
tmi burn well that's the thing is
i don't think i'm going to be
intact i think i'm gonna be cremated
so i think this is all the
site but also it's important because i
i mean i know people who've had
to deal with that stuff for family
member yes didn't for it's like there's
nothing there's no instructions i know yeah
i think about it i you know
like yeah cool i've said that about
harris
it's that that was one of the
things that was so surprising he had
had that all worked out wow all
worked out yeah crazy huh
yeah i mean it's i want to
do it though i think it's nice
to do it i just like i've
only recently been like oh i should
probably figure that out yeah well now's
the time you have to start thinking
about it but like for us you
know we're i think today you turn
eighteen forties yeah like we got dirty
you start how do you want a
job like what would happen right now
like it would all just go to
the state or something like i don't
want that oh no no no your
family would fuck yeah oh bitter feud
that would last for years yeah like
who do you got your family who'd
want your money i want them all
to have it no no but who
but who would want no one would
be gross yeah your dad wants to
buy a bunch of new bikes
ah oh man i wouldn't get a
rear view mirror i think yeah nice
bill yeah yes yeah basketball okay i
need to take a break
we're back we're back before yeah back
before we get into creature feature we
in the fee we gotta tell you
scottish ladies went on sale a few
weeks a few weeks ago we have
three t-shirts
sucking on chile da dao banned e
news so if you if you want
a second chili dog t-shirt go head
over to pod swag dot com now
we we these who designed these
aired yeah yeah errand errand it and
then we we we we had we've
little no no yes little notes sweet
i had to take ten into the
t-shirt process we well i think hello
we had it we had a little
hand in others yeah we made little
tweaks to it and i think that
everyone will be pleased they're very cute
it's a very adorable sharon i can't
wait till second on chili dog and
this chili dog he looks pretty happy
it's very suitable he was i want
to get him in your mouth
and just watch out for all people
are gonna comp and start sucking your
t-shirt right watch out for chili dog
on there um alright we have a
feature this one comes from will hoff
at youngest of one the game is
the genie game one person says what
they wish for another person comes up
with the ironic twist that will make
them regret
wish getting what they wished for oh
so i'd like the monkey's paw yeah
this good game yes he big hit
yes okay so you have to make
a wish on a lamp which we
should act out yes we do it
is our lamp you're you're yeah you
gotta rub this
oh hey just mimed jerome over water
bottle is gruesome oh oh okay so
i'm gonna i found this genie bottle
ah guys oh cool
hey so what are you going wish
for well i gotta just see what
happens when the genie comes out alright
no it's freed me from my prison
mortal i'm grant you a wish what
was do you wish for me to
grant the wish i wish that i
would get to go on a vacation
for my entire life oh okay your
wish is granted oh no lawrence in
a coma
she's took a vacation from her life
i want her entire lives having a
good time in her own brain and
we're strapped forever
poop wait she's pooping several she's just
say that
poop poop
oh yeah now she's just doing it
okay
alright
brown one over
huh was that not poetic enough though
that was that was great i thought
it was great i loved it it
was very funny alright so my genie
and you're wishing
yeah the way i'm gonna rub the
lamp excuse me a video of this
what what an exotic lamp from faraway
lands that's covered with dust i'll have
to clean it off right here and
now whoa
ah but the jee tae jin from
the lab yes i'm a gin i've
freed you from ah did you in
don't i get away rabbi oh wow
where do you go wait you want
to wish oh everyone wants which is
the least you can do a free
yeah the very least i can do
i'm not gonna give you three you
greedy
the bitch is fine alright you get
one alright right away so i'll give
you anything you want think of it
think real hard you dumb piece of
shit my wish is not for myself
but for others i wish for there
to be world peace
oof the world is in pieces you
didn't spell it you didn't spell it
you dumb bitch and why wouldn't it
be in one piece world peace pieces
of the world are everywhere we blew
up the fucking world you dumb shithead
hello sir what so i wish for
world peace
yeah you made the world yet you
own one of the pieces oh i
own one yeah you get argentina you
so do i give the entire country
of argentina yeah anyway enjoy it it
broke up in the pieces that was
already in yeah it broke off into
every country has it's own p is
the earth exploded or is it just
like oh no why are you bothering
me i'm off to my home planet
why did you bother giving me a
wish
because you seem like a real cool
guy but then you you being a
dick i'm not being a dick just
because the you know the the planet
blew up in the air is this
lamp okay is this honestly what you
thought i meant when i said i
want more peace now i knew what
you meant so you didn't purpose
i did it on purpose because i'm
just a rant okay maybe you haven't
for real i mean alright use or
is that your windshield you're still here
yeah world peace world peace
shh the world is back together and
now it's in one piece congratulations you
suck you suck dick ho and you
enjoy it so you're a rude genie
i'm a rude dude with a tude
by gone scene to
done
is a good game
we claim the game to ah okay
oh look at this oh this is
interesting looks like a water bottle surely
it couldn't be anything other than that
it's probably just a watermill it's probably
just a water bottle right paul but
why don't you scrape some dust off
of it and see what it is
is very i'll just blow the desktop
okay sure
but
vampy damn
judge judy
don't be on my leg what do
you want just your genie what's just
genie what could you possibly want just
shooting me
but i think my friend has a
wish i have a wish yes say
it
i would like a lower interest rate
on my house i'm currently at a
one point nine npr i would love
for it to get down you know
below one
oh alright boring wish for a boring
man hey here it goes poof shh
you wanted to lower interest rates yeah
i did so did you get to
look at your house it's lower how
interesting
write me on
zero stars this is not what i
wanted zero stars is the best rating
on my app guys yeah double irony
ironic twist that i gave you the
biased rating hey um it's ah training
um oh you're just pissing that's right
don't pee on my leg and tell
me it's wrong
she's told me before but i know
a book about that that's the ironic
twist she'd ever told you before it's
all me you've got scene three scene
three in the books contra nineveh fell
down but i lie on the box
facebook and jake it's chinatown forget it
jake
tao zhang tao
do you have another game yeah i
can find one alright you better sorry
don't threaten me sorry sorry doi ya
doing your lamp back yeah your hugo
said his dry cause the water was
gone now oh hi i'm dr talk
amongst bringing up a debarment arab but
i'm damn damn damn damn declaim a
man
a yea our own daughter and your
own son
you your own daughter and your own
son or your own daughter and your
aunt huh
and are you beating your meat look
out due to the jigsaw around the
town
ah another one oh
oh yeah what was that for look
your face like remember
afraid you just write somebody said hey
jude home home home hopefully huh hey
jude
home hong kong oh to go into
that place hum hum hum hey jude
okay dude and a game judge judy
judy judy judy dude is a song
that should have shown is about judge
judy yeah i thought it was about
julian lennon easy yeah okay here's the
game okay you don't need to say
tom is the game william graham at
will underscore rambo he wrote it's stupid
but maybe that weird game where you
tell a story in each person takes
one word at a time but i
guess you'd have to add a hook
like one wants a scary story one
wants an uplifting one and the other
one's romance oh that's a pretty good
hook that's a good hook so yeah
good alright so scary you want scar
lifting eye on sky
hey you wanna lifting and paul ryan
i want scary doom doom doom doom
don't i
do do do much yeah la la
la you want you want romance you
want uplifting i will write what i
want scary oh mantic person okay okay
so let's do it i want romance
what you want you want to lift
hey wanna lifting yeah let's try it
let's try to break this down i
think this breaks down nicely across our
personalities i think you do want to
lifting i do want romance and you
do once okay yeah alright and start
the story and work on a golf
let's do the title of the story
together like one of the time okay
title of the story is
intriguing
uplifting yeah threatt
tales
of the
devilish
sunshine okay it's trees oh there's okay
so in in what was intriguing uplifting
sweet sweet tales tales of the devil
evolution sunshine lovers oh okay this sounds
nice yeah still sound nice
thereby
this is the beginning of this
was it
shouldn't have
sung
so easily
once
upon
hey started with
time
there
occurred
happy
things
not sad things
until
a
lover died
because she asphyxiated
a grape
a
joyously
she
intensified
her our door until she gasped
dying
wishing hoping praying that
he
couldn't not return
but he didn't
thereby
moreover
however thereby however good
thereby however
hangs
nick's delicious
delicious
turkey next
gobble the gobble
and seen it's nothing
let's pick it up the pate let's
pick up the pace here we go
alright new story or no teaching keep
hearing okay it's my turn gobble gobble
and and when you have to smile
a smile do you not smile the
smile you want no you don't ever
smile the smile you want
you have to murder teeth or else
you won't get dental
a insurance the only way you can
try to get dental insurance is to
marry a doctor
are you a doctor because i want
to larry
please marry me if you are a
doctor and see ah
yeah
but yeah
moreover
when
a little guy
chances his luck
then he that's to take his chances
little
girls never make good pets you have
to put them in a box
trapped under the staircase like that mummy
loving guy who we know and love
from the harry
and
here suit
potter
a bother
harry and her suit potter who made
a fortune making movies about pots
hey i wonder if you ever were
to go you can reply to my
emails because i missed a few ah
a few when i ate
a poison gum
and i shouldn't have eaten that gum
because it tasted like poison
oh well
that's showbiz
hey
come into my window
i want to show you how to
make an
orange soda
in a bathtub
concluding
the story
i
wish i could murder you again
you are dead
the and a question mark
oh very good what a story someone
please type all of that out yes
really really wow mushtaq we want to
accomplish that shit well guys we've we've
come to the end of our hava
recording while having my show lasted shove
how well how long have we been
going chev fifty
minutes five oh yeah we need lip
the police we need more a number
of the police won't look that's the
sound of the police police we need
to go another ten alright so one
point yeah let's play let's play that
mind meld being again okay like the
one we played last time yeah alright
bonus time bonus robo bonus only zoo
two at a time okay fine okay
so who do you wanna do with
you let's go let's go wow sorry
you're not great at it onto yeah
it's okay alright ready three two one
please please and ni three two one
bro it's pre-race plans knee brace and
hello
whoa i'm great brace and blow ah
three three two one barricade race blow
barricade an accident increase three to one
crown's cone zone crash three to one
traffic traffic three to one traffic and
safety three three three two one police
i couldn't think of what it was
called sorry we also have this guy
talking i'm saying it was hey could
you stop ruining the ram
yeah have we had put it's way
way way way way where am i
who are you
police know it was safety and cones
or something no it wasn't safety cones
i said police whoop whoop that's the
sound let's start over alright let's start
over ready i gotta get another word
from our twitter's suggestions okay one two
three two two one bridesmaid clean brides
remember okay three two one drab honor
right of honor
three two one wow low yellow and
wedding three two one easter easter and
sun three two one bunny
kind of like hughes said it because
i've heard me saying brain dead yeah
alright you and paul
no three to one knows listen nose
three two one years wow okay no
me and paul me and paul kubo
scott i'm terrible at this game one
thing oh well one tip i'll throw
out there
doing and seeing if it worked huh
is it if i say an adjective
it happens a lot quicker because it's
like you're describing the other person's inter
as day ready i was playing a
fucking mind game with you guys three
two one relinquish relinquish in lips three
two one kiss
thank you we'll see what their sin
nagging ah why did you say thank
you just know because you oh yeah
because we were so good questions you
want around lord you are so full
of yourself years yeah yeah you weren't
seeing curves there homie hold i'll do
it again let's do it all three
of
uh oh no
alright alright ah okay three two one
day or kudos yelling disaster three to
one rainbow ma help and three events
it three to one service kevin pasta
and
and isn't podcast i didn't say oh
i saw some are server customer service
listen to podcast and help and kevin
i thought you owe kevin kevin podcast
customer service customer service three two one
siachen sicher seven three two over
we're never here we can't do three
at a time and it doesn't worse
it does not believe in us know
we will never be able to do
it come on i don't believe we
can fly what's your tip saying an
adjective yeah alright let's all think of
an adjective that's due to adjectives and
a noun i'm adjective your verb and
your noun
interesting alright okay alright alright um ah
yeah okay sure alright he doesn't know
it because no i'm doing verb okay
still three two three two one happy
happy doggy think thank happy dog p
three two
right huh would you say woof treat
i said why do you think you
happy doggy it's introit i'm saying that's
how he thanks you by saying woof
okay so i'm not crazy did you
say guys detroit so what does that
mean let's trade
this is why we can't do this
troika okay traits
yeah treat and wolf treated and woof
okay treat three way we're treating wolf
trained wolf three three two one yep
snaps barak trick liver snaps three two
one home mean rollover halloween and sit
three to one job
huh dog collar costume and what dracula
dracula dog color okay three meets you
one picture show kinda good she's dominator
dominatrix rocky horror picture show oils and
apple's three weeks to ah yeah frankfurter
bag bobbing bag and bobbing okay three
two one
on paul yeah cauldron blow job and
bucket bucket three one way buckets we
both said which which had spit bucket
k three reus slammer
and said nothing
it's not paused or in bro my
god it slobber and broom are coming
together slipper room thirty two doi to
work ma yeah no i'm opposite slots
opera room it's true i said words
you said mop would you say
hey i did this only gonna remember
i can't do the same i can't
do this anymore lauren you're the one
who wanted to do three times last
night home slobber brooms slobber brew and
got to stop it because honestly though
is it because of the position that
we're in that
if we were if we were like
standing in a circle it would be
a different thing but we're we're kind
of spread out from each other there's
the mix and everything i feel like
i feel like that does make a
difference yeah probably i mean i'm sure
we'd nail it if we were just
hanging out standing looking in a mirror
any to the space if we were
know what aims from each other's noses
let's just try it one more time
one touch no soy no here's how
we should try it okay how do
we do it you say a word
like you and i will say a
word at the same time and we'll
get those two words don't turn to
paul with those two words and we'll
try to then you guys do okay
okay ah three hold on hold on
all right all right ready three two
one heart
guy coffee haircut
three two one rod brown ma megan
brown
um ah yea yeah three two one
trailheads crayon and chocolate
crayon and chocolate alright three two one
dream draw ice cream three two one
comb cone and white sketch cone and
sketch
okay
ah three two one called e okay
jane curtin comedy three two one sunday
like come on i was doing i
said jane curtin because of kony yeah
show coneheads yeah but a conan sketch
where the girls and i still remember
said coy yeah that's cool yes but
you're looking at me like i didn't
get it i'm the one who
instigated you set it up so that
it would be that we said that
oh yes i like the combination between
comedy and jane curtin or third rock
from the fucking size you said conehead
u s and l and i said
coneheads yeah so go i agree too
like
fully paul three to ah damn cry
thank you it's easy you fuck you
fuck you i hate this boy you
fuck you i'm never doing this again
edit two takes it's true yeah it
sounds like we have to go alright
that's it goodbye goodbye
uh