three
ah welcome hearing now at three
i did hear it did you hear
you hear me do you hear me
what i did like roboto three
daddy another daddy did you hear me
a ufa
are we old enough to be your
dad i can't i've never gotten the
day i am for sure on the
specs yeah
oh damn your measurements yeah yeah oh
how cool are you can i be
your dad does this work no wait
what's the word i'm three through three
o allows decreased yeah this year price
your
your age he died yeah oh i
know
lodge du christ something the age of
price everybody forty eight what do you
mean i know you worry about what
i am so if you are fifteen
but i ever want to happen but
i ain't morton fucking then as i'm
saying
so no you couldn't have been my
dad i'm fifty so i could know
you both would've been teen dads yeah
plausible isn't it could it be but
this probable this whole show was like
a convoluted like spend more time with
your year my two dads this whole
time and i'm like oh you know
we guys
yeah because it obviously wouldn't be my
dad's but let's say one of you
was yeah and that this was some
weird thing joe fucked up i would
be forever from this experience like meeting
you you find out about it after
yeah and like and then you'd be
like oh hey i have to tell
you i'm like the final episode on
the road near your real dads and
and the allawi
we both did stuff to someone and
we don't know who i don't know
who it is but it was kind
of one of us that is the
premise of three minutes baby right is
that they don't know which one of
them yeah and dna tests didn't exist
then i think and but oh the
kid ghost did exist right they did
live together right they lived together because
the babe
rbi or they already lived together and
they find they found a lotta hole
i don't remember if they lived together
you're not eating they did live together
i wouldn't dare
can anyone tell us any other thick
tongue any listeners out there can you
tell us if the three men and
the baby lived together because here's the
thing we can't go baby might have
had it's own apartment with google we
can't watch the phillies are rules these
rules are rules like oh like julia
dooley been a hole oh here we
go we got to lipa we gotta
do we're gonna lead them the freedom
yeah the kidz bop version bleed and
we will adhere to these rules for
as long as we do the shit
how older these rules are these rules
are new there right now and they
are based on the experience of us
wanting to know about three men and
a baby yeah ok here we go
this is the intuitive kidz bop version
of
okay liz rules one we can't google
it we cannot google a chaffee ny
make it okay to we can't watch
the film again because we've all seen
it yeah so we cannot rewatch we
can't watch it again three three we
can't ask anyone we know can't ask
anyone that we
have a personal relationship with we ask
okay for for money if if we
read something where somebody tries to tell
us we have to stop reading it
right away and we are accused ourselves
yeah aside we have to accidentally overhear
the facts about three men and a
baby that's right five is that iconic
she will say fuck five oh sorry
six if anyone tries to tell us
the answer oh stranger can i get
the song louder my headphone question
tear myself down in my headphones i
want to be inaudible
um if anyone tries to tell us
a stranger we have to punch them
in the mouth
seven
was this the adult version if we
see it's buffers and it's not yeah
if we mag any of the stars
of three minutes baby we must avoid
the topic entirely entirely i have met
goot and if they bring him up
but i've met ted danson i've met
dan today i forgot he was yelling
it steve gooch madam danson that
madam magnum pi ma'am no thank you
directed by leonard nimoy madam thankfully he's
not threatening more my god leonard z
night was the what what did you
not know he was a big film
director for when i needed to read
that movie yes so random i think
he he forced himself into directing one
of the star trek movie
he's the third and the fourth right
and that forced himself he was like
i'll be in it if directorships imagine
if that was the character you were
forever like i know everyone warships it
and stuff but like that would be
hard spook spook forever he wrote a
book called i am not spook and
then and then he was like fuck
it i am so yes he did
he wrote another book like maggie and
actually a director i'm hey it's me
leonard nimoy i liked the the race
two-year-olds i'm not majorly ed derek thirty
he he has a whole record my
ears are regular shout up my ears
are round and that pointed as you
may have believed from the
tv i don't wear eye shadow anymore
not any of that shit mine spookiest
character loved it he has a whole
character loved it here's a whole record
do you think zaza rupaul's drag race
is based on star trek what's yeah
space all the characters that's incredible yeah
are you kidding all rupaul has faced
the ball drag her
itself is a race is the show
so rupaul is a character rupaul based
herself on spock then when she wanted
to make rupaul's drag race intellectual property
right you will see at the very
end of the credits it says a
desi lu production what's yes because of
star trek was a desi lu production
yes insane wow that's great and i
did notice at the end of rupaul's
drag race when i was watching she
kind of like takes her her wig
back a little bit and shows the
her plush here yeah where it's like
carol burnett yeah exactly winks at the
audience that is insane she winks her
ear like her over the shootings don't
care when it because caribbean always brings
her here
or what if carol burnett at the
end of the show bent over and
winked her buttle you know she's still
alive that's true oh i forgot cannot
yeah talk that way about her so
sorry what are we going to run
into her you think we might we
might you're the you're the new carol
burnett i've always said wow do you
have any any people like
like that they have no interest in
watching your work give julia
do you have any areas that are
personally like you never will find a
joke about it funny and because that
made me think of for me mister
rogers like i don't interest ideology like
eddie murphy's mr robertson was funny when
i was younger shore but i became
a man i put away childish things
did you get a doc knowing watch
sheen mister robbins haven't watched it yeah
i am true story yeah i feel
like i have to be i feel
like i have to be in a
certain place to be able to watch
that it's good to be theater yeah
would help couch huh
um i've seen it i've seen it
stopped before it ever even came out
oh me they ran it by me
first before making it i know it's
going really well i'm glad you said
yes i had to do you have
any reservations about um only for dinner
oh scott j scott jill how dare
ya
ah um or enable my joke dial
is there any topic that you won't
joke about um yeah
but they're like legit
i mean i feel like i know
what we're talking about is really like
something that's a little unexpected that you
won't joke about i think there are
obvious things yeah like i because i
was surprising to me that i felt
that yeah who do i feel that
way about or what i don't know
do you have one
i e i i'm not i don't
necessarily think that no one should joke
about any topic i agree scarily but
are some that i won't yeah ah
yeah i think i have lines for
myself but there were some that i
used to joke about and now i'm
not into that kind of stuff i
made mister rogers' joke really i linked
like a year
ago and then i was like it
wasn't worth it i wish i hadn't
done it did you just write with
guilt it was and it was a
very mild joke too but don't you
hate when you have a joke that
you just rattle off and then like
later like i really wish i didn't
say that i don't agree with that
i remember when yeah when i was
working in one of the restaurants i
worked at i
would my account what does it tell
you
alien day billy seville suva yohei kaolin
i think valley endo kelly franklin korea
tony macho and caliendo talking martin
ah um i remember i i live
you read john madden put on dora
wait for you why
nah like i'm doing with or jujube
is that that was not a show
titled more like classic charles o j
r um giants i've been doing comedy
maybe for three years and every i
mean you remember paul all yeah mr
years ago sure to say the same
ah but all the mister show people
were you know had a hard sense
of humor you know yeah ah and
i
i was used to that and i
was still working with non coms non
comedians and and non-commissioned officer billions um
and things and there was a waitress
who gentiles there's a waitress whose husband
had passed away oh boy three years
earlier i think something like that and
she made a joke about
or whatever and i made a really
hard joke about it and she just
burst into tears
and i like her in the back
and i was like i'm so so
so sorry shut up there are things
that i'm allowed to joke where i
work
on the back stuffing hysterical
no but that's why i didn't take
her the back she was in the
back and i went to did i
ever tell you this joke not joke
well hold on wait let me rephrase
the whole story rephrase counselor this was
an experience i had and talking to
somebody i didn't really know and if
you've heard it spank me but ooh
boy
i'm rubbing my hands are we canceling
spanking by the way yeah i don't
think we i think is cancelled you
had a really different reaction about it
excuse me um the other day yeah
that was in our last episode cancelled
i
hey i i need i need kevin
to say spanking is okay and not
on mike because i feel like that
puts too much pressure early and kevin
we also like we we should treat
her with the same respect with hollywood
handbook the thing is they will exactly
and shoving is a funny funny man
and he's able to joke and so
but looks aren't everything
oh yeah i've shown the back cry
oh i'm so sorry kevin sweet we
assume kevin will rebel it was here
but that is the kind of thing
where you know people say well she's
she she says she's cool with her
and then the whole set years later
you know so yeah exactly so let
me be neat
we needed in writing this is anita
hill
let me just tell you my story
okay so i was at um i
kind of was like casually like a
dinner or drinks before a show with
a group of just casually you're all
over the place was a dinner or
drink it was drinks i use i
only knew one person well who is
there but they were like come by
here but at the bar before your
show franklin
the company it was literally labelle yeah
right and i um went and i
sat down and i knew a few
of the people sort of but there
was one girl i had never met
before am we're just making small talk
and then she was like tv writer
or something
and i was like um she said
something to the effect of oh well
i i just i haven't i haven't
written this is the longest someone on
the show has gone without being interrupted
and i know i'm trying like a
site but felt weird to me please
it's why i'm like shimmering because i'm
like wow can someone like make another
bag
i have one
why am i getting through it it's
so quiet yeah because it's easier for
me to think whenever one's huh um
because a little break yeah right yeah
she was she was like she's something
like i haven't been working for the
last eight months or something and then
i said oh what have you been
up to when she said i had
a baby and i said oh congratulations
what's its name and she goes it
die
died and then i call home on
the next not on you and then
i burst is here because i felt
so bad and she was like i'm
kidding i wrote a script like yeah
she never had a baby at all
ah and then and i was like
whoa okay and then i felt crazy
because everyone there knew her and knew
she didn't oh baby
i knew she was kidding this initiative
baby oh but i didn't know you
like you were there and then i
was like crying and i was like
i'm so sorry i can't stop crying
because i can't catch up to that
like i don't understand what just happened
right and then that was like it
oh man yeah and how was the
script so funny yeah um and she
she's saying um no but it really
is just that like twenty times yeah
i was i will work and no
play but it's just that i hate
that kind of thing so much that
kind of like i'm going to tell
you a lie i'm gonna yes i'm
going to tell you why don't you
go you don't know me this could
be i'm gonna stay in it and
a flat tone that's like why you
have no reason to die
doubt me and then i'm gonna call
you an idiot because you loved me
have you ever seen that person again
no but you probably know this person
oh shit i'll tell you off mike
this is cray know now you just
cut it our role burnett um it's
and we're back oh that is crazy
who that y'all didn't know her
i probably know or i don't care
right anyway um sucks no shine if
she listened to this don't do that
no she don't do that and don't
do that don't do that please don't
do that you could make lousy house
pet
cause that that was that's an l
sketch that i always thought was ah
um dana carvey and then i realized
it was mike myers oh yes it
was a not successful one that they
tried a couple of times you don't
marry paul yeah thank you yeah yeah
it's come up on the show before
but i'm glad i had the chance
to to say it
isn't dana carvey as well here's everything
about the spanking
chevy doesn't have to be the one
to spank that was kind of the
built-in rule but myself spent we have
you to decide it yourself spank i
feel like i'm spanking pens i'm uncomfortable
spanking you you know i think we
have
we have too many spanking implements now
okay here it's out of a blog
real one saying here's what's up then
okay we need a new punishment when
a new punishment we have too many
speaking things it's overkill we're not it's
too much she wanted what you dark
what is a good okay if if
you're a parent yes slab what can
replace spank
aching i think you had a time
oh okay oh here's what i think
timeout should we do timeouts i think
it's homework in the corner high water
you have to write one page a
one page apology while everyone was just
talking no no after yes episode oh
you have to do it at home
for ah you'll never do it i
would
totally do it i love homework i'll
crush and get a weight it's judged
yeah we have yeah right by the
other two people what well what grade
do you order for it to be
sups for successful and loved it and
it has to be an a romance
writers aref yep what wow hell why
what the whoa hey what's the hill
why the hell are you know up
jew i was making like just know
who the maiden ghostbusters when i go
to the hotel yeah one of the
greatest one imo hell are you doing
yeah ah she crawls out from behind
the cart that's cool that's really cool
i like i like
like the idea that you could have
one line in a movie that everyone's
like i'll always remember you saying you're
one except i can't even picture her
oh i can picture o'reilly very clearly
oh i wanted to tell you the
story oh great is it gonna be
as long and no this one's got
ours oh okay by the way it's
actually amazing that i wasn't able to
think of how that story
because i'm totally like twenty times i
find it so shocking okay
are you told on mike before but
don't believe i have my dear good
board now sharing it with the pre
paywall world everyone who pays gets to
know that story um pay you play
this story i thought was interesting i
was a news story from um from
well i guess two thousand and three
s one started but this guy was
a ham
the i mean i guess it's now
there's coughing in it come on laurie
know what kind
you might know the story it was
this guy who was put in prison
for the murder of a teenage girl
and
for six months he was in jail
and then his lawyer wow found footage
from curb your enthusiasm where this guy
was in a yes audience at a
dodgers there's a netflix documentary i watched
like man it's so good i don't
know anything about basically this guy went
to jail for six months for killing
this teenager but he always said i
didn't do it right and
his lawyer was able to approve it
he didn't do it because he found
him in the background at curb your
enthusiasm and a dodgers game he was
an audience member he was like he
was there but he was saying like
i was i was i was dodgers
yeah then fruit the proof of him
being at a dodgers game but they
found it in an episode of curb
yes yes and yes like behind the
actors like with his
daughter and did he ever say like
oh by the way the other part
of my alibi is larry david was
getting no he didn't even know what
that show really was really even really
remember that that was their doing hum
to him oh wow and now this
thing i saw is that he's so
he received three hundred and twenty thousand
dollars does play when he was sentenced
hilarious guilty
yeah da da
and then he had never watched the
show before but after his release he
became a devoted fan oh and he
got three hundred and twenty thousand
god i wish i could go to
jail for some magic and water joe
like him larry that's like my life
yeah like the stuff that was hilarious
like what happened to me like i'm
riley can can really say what did
it wasn't me and then like i
was at that game and i'm like
no one's listening to me obviously i
didn't kill her and then everybody's like
how you did how much would it
take for you
to go to jail so you're saying
money with three hundred and twenty thousand
for six months do it um no
i think i'd be afraid to go
to jail
i'm not an idiot i know you'll
be afraid to go to jail that's
why i asked the question what if
if okay if they're like you go
to jail for six months but then
you get this amount of money and
you never have to go to jail
again well this guy could go to
jail again alright if you don't you
never if you don't do anything bad
when you think because he's like he's
owed a murder now
anyway one for me went to jail
i think when you didn't mail marine
buddies so i guess you might as
well mirza one you know what actually
don't know that there's an amount of
money that would be worth lou really
so in my life even if it
was like ah ten million dollars fine
i'll do it what kind of jail
are we talking but we talked about
like regular old prison but like i'm
already white collar place i don't
my ass kicked and like i'm gonna
have some gonna suffer like extreme trauma
and like and crips might do that
yeah don't worry you know someone might
like you know like beat me up
or like you know i don't know
whatever happened you can make the best
of it you can be a model
prisoner you can keep out of people's
way it's up to you it might
be me up or do something i
mean i would definitely be a model
prisoner
yeah well you are you're so hot
and prison honestly by prison standards i'm
literally tara banks would you walk in
there because like i was in orange
is the new black my wife behind
to know how this whole thing is
i was a ceo and i got
exact so i really relate to you
guys
you're watching disney luck i watched the
first season yeah okay yeah just curious
if you were thinking like the first
tommy in it yes i usually yeah
were you in it after the first
season i was in the second season
don't call me baby if you can't
return my checks yeah you've just seen
the gif
um i was in the first and
second season okay
cool yeah i just was curious did
you guys ever see me and frazier
know what actually really want to well
yes sure it's never-say-die and i don't
know no but i would find i'll
find all your tie you to i
did find your clip from gold member
oh really yeah it's on youtube is
it really yeah terrible yeah i never
made just shoot me my addition many
times that is
so crazy me because he loved mister
show when he had all of us
thought yeah i think the only reason
i got on was because who is
casting inc i don't even remember don't
remember don't remember although i did go
to receive vs radford for my audition
and they said well that was interesting
that's not what we thought it should
be at all i love this let
me get the producer but it was
like you had to take on it
i had to take off if they
were like wow that's a character i
don't i don't even know how it
was written because when i read it
i was like oh i get how
to do this and you're like i
did it early yeah mo ron would
say it like that
but then they they thought it was
so funny they kept rewriting the lines
and giving me new joke always the
character galesburg okay so gold member goldberg
going to go yes i only love
god
whoa so what did you have to
do i was in an art class
with maya and i was asking the
teacher giacomo she's great asking the teacher
if i could have more time or
something i don't even remember and then
one day i think i told you
this that i showed up really really
late on the second day
because i got the wrong call sheet
i don't remember this so your homework
can be put okay so i do
remember this as i was leaving they
gave me a call sheet and said
ok here's your call time for tomorrow
and i looked at it and it
was like eleven am i'm like sweet
and i show up at eleven am
i'm like hey everyone just really calm
they're like where were you and i
said i'm here at eleven am
do you mean they're like your calls
at nine am you are looking at
the big number at the top or
some no no they gave me the
day before his show and i was
like i went to my car and
got it i said see here's my
coffee and as far as they know
i'm just showing them the damn probably
i'm like i swear to god and
they they were all like yeah that's
fine
what's the rush i had to write
i worked on a show where it
was a multicam sitcom and multi cameras
yeah there was like five two dungy
one multi-campus single cam are weird to
say because there are multiple cameras and
single canvas will they shorten multiple and
make it multiway are they not show
shortening single and calling it sing kam
seek him because he can is a
medicine i think xdcam xdcam
ply can i cam xy xdcam is
huge hondo percent we are having dinner
with another couple last night and the
the wife and the other couple is
not in show business and so we
were talking about um you know the
single town
huh exactly is that what do you
do all day i just had a
baby who died she was asking us
the difference between single cam and multicam
why do they call them that idiot
and we were trying to explain and
she like but wait
she couldn't it was she was having
a hard time understanding what what what
like why why are some shows multicam
and why are some shows single cam
yeah like if it's a comedy what's
the difference between why you shoot it
in front of an audience why you
don't it also doesn't even make sense
any more because shows like you know
parenthood for exam
people use two or three cameras when
they're shooting the scenes it's true well
that's the dirty secret isn't it yeah
we usually use more than one count
oh my gosh anyway so i'm working
on this multicam sitcom front of a
live audience the wardrobe person for the
next scene that i was in put
the wrong outfit in my
my closet and so i go and
change into the wrong outfit oh shit
and i come back and then somebody's
like you're in the you know one
of the producers like you're in the
wrong clothes that's for a different scene
and well i did not throw her
under the bus but people made fun
of me oh my for the rest
of the night i can't believe you
didn't and what do they call you
like johnny wrong clothes they're like asia
you're the right cause it was oh
you know it was like it was
a lot of little dumb jokes my
car running
rest of a long night and you
just ate it and just ate it
i just did it and did you
ever say to her like not eating
it she thanked me early on but
like very like hey thank you like
i could use a little more than
that yeah really this is still gonna
be part of your paycheck yeah did
you feel like you
her clothes were so different from what
they are supposed to be that it
was obvious to ever i don't think
yeah it wasn't like you were wearing
when hellboy outfit it was well that's
what you know i think that was
the mushroom of the script supervisor that
caught it or you know somebody it
wasn't like wildly i mean
it was like all different suits and
ties you know what i mean right
but i'm saying like forever to make
fun of you it's like it's not
like kids like you walked in in
your wetsuit and yeah i know tv
i know it was because here's why
they made fun of me because in
front of the audience i was told
i was in the wrong costume and
then i had to go get chow
and come back oh and everyone boo
now it's a bit they booed me
boo
ooh wrong clothed fruit wow that was
their snack that they give them they
put me in stock
alright like we need to take a
break we'll be right back
ah robot
i like us i like me like
you i like you ah ha same
same saying i like me you know
what i like you we like you
as well that we like you yeah
we're you're you're like the audience at
home you guys like you talked about
this before no no we we we
checked in before the show we were
like when we say we like all
right well i always call
scott before we start recording and i
just say like are we all still
in the pose is okay wow are
we dao with him wow are we
done with him are we down or
yeah i turned into a lion wow
i tend to tell i mean notice
me i turned didn't lose me i
tended to align
welcome back have you ever turned into
a lion yes oh are you asking
the audience sure we want to get
your phones yeah you you what's your
favorite animal
oof oof oof oof
this is tough you don't like animals
i bet i do like animals oh
no power no pets no pets but
i do like adam but what i
had a dream law done is done
okay
here's the thing i love animals fucking
animal videos online fucking animals i love
fucking animal videos animals just in a
committed relationship and just fucking making love
to each other there was a there
was a you know the dodo site
oh yes they had a chose to
do do they put you
you did not think ok it's like
i don't know bird but there's a
picture of a dodoma badoo
they had a um supercut of animals
hugging oh yeah and almost hugging other
animals like people animals hugging each other
oh okay it's nice some are people
some are animals yeah animals are people
too people are animals too i should
say so and what does us and
you liked it i liked i liked
stuff like that i like cute dog
dogs and cats huh so what's your
favorite animal paul it's really tough say
it don't spray it and might be
you make a better door than a
window
every time she's still raised it i
want the news not the weather also
the reason a barn is like the
the you don't the thing of the
barn is not the keep the door
open all the time i agree whereas
the burners are sets been one sometimes
were open sometimes rain says if the
second default and it's the worst phase
of
existence the worst phrase have got to
be done yes we have to be
handful will it cancel were you born
in a barn cancel you close your
barn door it's fine right okay animals
get out my man therein good pens
can't close the barn door once the
horse gets out feel like if because
of how it was
to be a child you might have
been under the impression that you'd be
spending a lot more time on farms
groom when you grew up because so
many games and toys and songs like
old mcdonnell r and is yeah i
had a barn setup that i love
fisher price step on yeah and i'm
so guys yeah that it's like i
thought i'd be
spending times in barnes not barnes and
nobles oh god that's a scotch yoke
his hey that's a textbook textbook scheduled
tax book to talk to books when
i was young my next boss got
all did you see the new star
wars trailer know i think i will
never watch a taxable ta call let's
they put me in one and then
i'll watch you audition for one i
did how to go dad i didn't
get it what do you want well
when you were having no idea it
will go fake are you holding lightsaber
know they had to do stuff from
vanguard oh yeah that's good to us
so like i have no context though
glad gary liege yeah
would've been cool i guess now i
know it would have been cool you
would have been interim bullied forever you
people would hate you now like they
hate all the people in star wars
yeah because why there they're ruining it
or something yes it's always real yeah
i you know i thought about doing
like ah sort of like podcast series
where i watched all the
yeah i mean i want every single
star wars and talk about them and
then i was like i really don't
want to do that but what about
what about some of them are really
fun movie what about what about what
about what about so many what about
what about there's not that much about
finite thing how many were men there'll
be relevent us to be a lie
oh well solo and
in rogue one oh if you count
oh no what about what about obi
wan kenobi but you don't like him
i like these clothes you like five
ways hey what there we gotta get
entry point what about poor gs so
we start with my favorite hero we
start with return of the jedi just
the walk portions
yeah yeah then expand outward pause you're
gonna tell us a dream you had
i had a dream i gotta go
back to that because my my wife
often will ask why
moe hey she'll often ask about getting
a dog what here's what who's she
asked she would like to have a
dog she asked me like should we
get a dog not a lot of
a lot of times know her dad
will not talk to her about dogs
they have a very loving relationship but
as far as dogs go he estimates
on limits
shill a lot of times shill i
i think like trying to do a
psychological move on me she'll say you
want a dog yeah does it work
ever know here's the thing i do
love dogs but i don't the amount
of care that they require yeah i
don't want to do that i went
a lot when rocky passed away
rip um alright being a little guy
we had ah just getting his life
what if i deviate from everyone including
cooling yeah some attention i just kept
noise
i went and visited him as his
own little apartment and i'm just like
surprising gulati like two years later like
yeah la da but he's about to
die yeah yeah well he he passed
away yeah ah in september okay and
then this year know of but i'm
just saying the mom
okay in the year that he passed
away it was the month of september
do you remember and you refuse to
acknowledge what year it was and i
will say it was the morning after
jason tim's wedding and i was hung
over and he's not in the mood
today have to be put down or
did he die dog's final fuck you
it's a bad story if he had
been having trouble we we ah you
i'm just telling we know it's okay
we ah he was at the vets
because they were taking care of him
and trying to figure out what was
wrong with it and they said come
come by noon to pick him up
and we left at where it's ten
minutes away we left at ah ten
of noon and weren't checking our phones
and in that ten minutes he died
oh that's crazy yeah so when we
got there everyone was like running around
like looking
worried and we just kind of plopped
down like we're here to pick up
our dog you know and and then
i noticed there's like all this weird
stress and people are looking at us
really weird who worked there and i
go i think something's wrong and they
the doctor came out and said you
know people don the mask right
it had a dog face on it
i talked like rocky and he's like
remember me i'm dead now is you're
like why that just happened that doctors
should tell you they should remember me
i'm dead now i'm like oh but
in that is really in the four
months between then coop got georgia like
right away
i think she admits now that it
was purely a grief move and purely
just extremely common right and i was
like not ready for it and so
but in that four months i was
kind of like god i can i
can do anything now yeah yeah i
don't have to constantly be like re-homing
biting like
i have a cat and a dog
and my cat is like thirteen or
twelve or something but my old cat
she's still twenty one or yeah she's
just you still have that weird thing
where she's my gracious ladders yeah she
kind of does but i i kind
of figured out a couple of little
slim sorry she's crying
well i tweeted about it because she
would be she was like suddenly sort
of like oh all the time at
night and it was so annoying when
people were like the amount of tweets
i got that were like terrifying you
know diagnoses it was like she's gone
blind and she can't see ny anymore
and she's scared and she's meow and
it's like until i was like maybe
she's deaf
and i know people like shelly cashman
well lumi and dementia that she like
to know what's going on and i
was like to mitch doesn't feel true
just based on my interactions with her
when i had the whales i think
what it really is yeah
yea and they're mice
the mice from sierra derby
i think um she just really likes
attention and night when i'm asleep and
she wants me to note sir
but that's a recent experience like i've
noticed that more recently but i think
one thing i did was like i
usually close the door to this one
part of my house and i left
it open and now she like can
go there and i think that's part
of it she didn't beat a different
space okay and then the other thing
is i think she's always thirsty but
i thirsty i've noticed that about her
just general thirsty bitch but
um have you ever had cats no
never be okay to them they like
to drink out of the tub and
sink is so gross and so my
wow think i turn the tub on
like all the time for her and
she drinks out of it but like
lately what's been happening is she drinks
too much and she throws up some
water yes it's happened twice i and
so i had to turn it off
like
just a second later cause also just
be there ever drinking it and then
she'll be like ooh yeah the barf
is like pure wet like she was
ok so it's like a sleep i
turned it on i got up to
pee turned it on just a dribble
you know
i thought you like turning on the
entire noise just like going to sleep
so very very teeny little streak water
likes it and mikey kay my book
i got him back in bed and
then then i wake up to the
sound of like what it sounds like
water just splashing on my sheets and
florence not mike and it's not my
taking a big shit
it's my cat barfield to my guy
mike at barfi over the side and
it was like so much and it
was like pure water and it was
i mean it was far too but
it was just so gross why did
you start talking about your cat was
to tell the story know what you
asked me if she was still kneeling
know but before that you brought up
your cat years you're saying you should
thirteen that she's got yeah thanks that
she's like gonna you know i don't
want her to die ever i don't
want my pets to die but i
also none of them none of them
okay i don't i find it hard
to believe but okay let me tell
you what true of my old catalogs
be twenty one and this cat is
thirteen so and she's an indoor cat
so she's
i got like another seven years i
would guess sure she does right but
it could go you know however but
they have you got yeah probably seven
more years sign a coyote again she
gets it out um my my whole
point is just that i have thought
when she dies it might be nice
to not have to clean the litter
and think about right
hair and like all the things that
i could deal with all the time
and ah but then i also think
i'll probably get another pet like i
just like having animals around when i'm
away i really it's very nice sum
it is tradeoff it's like you know
the what you get for all having
to do all those things yeah because
you have this little companion that's yes
and when i got a dog was
a whole new way
cause i never really had a dog
and she like this so excited to
see me and wants to cuddle with
me she sleeps in the back
theaters this summer
responses by eleven army shiny
just the genie see the genie in
aladdin
what was one of your eyes ah
and only see the genie oh so
i had a dream wow we had
finally back to the dream we had
five like gigantic dogs of different like
big dog breeds and i loved it
wow i love like you're literally running
all
around while i was like wrestling and
hugging them and it was so much
they were they were the best they
were the best dog right and it's
because for some reason i'm talking about
st bernards a lot lately that might
be my favorite animal i don't know
i actually saw one i love san
bernardo like on tv maybe yesterday and
i was like that's a nice looking
dog yeah do you ever want a
big dog
ugh
i find okay so cool up sister
i guess i should say my sister-in-law
has a really illegal
long locks on the field you'll lock
to teach people don't talk about that
you lock down your in laws as
well it's oh yeah propose to them
as well my father-in-law yeah i made
it legal and if any of them
said no the whole thing was off
ah um she has a really big
dog
who was who's scary to me what
am i eating this shit now like
an example it's like oh it's like
a homeless guy jumping off oh yeah
is it i don't really newfoundland the
idea of those times in those homeless
guys would jump on
when you're paying them you invoke you
and go down look guys downtown it's
like bumfights but a little different here's
what i want you to do here's
what's up i need you to jump
on me just jump jump on me
i mean you hold the camera you're
like i jump on me how big
can a dog be like eighty pounds
more even more higher eighty one
a two one one-pound
yeah he's right
alright let's take a break we'll be
right back
back we're back oh you know what
it's time for guys why tell us
paul tell us tell us now i'm
gonna to oh keep it going keep
them tell us all tell us tell
us now tell us paul tell us
tell us now a bridge tell us
tell us tell us now bridge
bridge tbd what is it um it's
time for feature
oh were you done i thought you're
saying hey teacher like you're gonna say
no i don't know teachers okay well
i'd say what the feature is what
is the picture to us from as
a suggestion this we'll give them a
little bit of street cred at two
headed blah thank you i'll come on
that's not a real name this is
the movie game it's a game where
where one person says an actor the
next person says a movie that actors
in the following person says another actor
from that movie and then the next
person doesn't a movie that that actors
in so on and so forth until
hopefully you can expect the original movie
at the end here's the thing whoever
connects back wins and whoever can't come
up with all done just put on
the song plays
if we're gonna make okay super okay
years yeah these new rules okay clinic
cause he said and so you're trying
there it's sort of two-prong tell me
again you're trying to trap the next
person they don't wish so that they
can't come up with an answer and
if that happens they're out but you're
also trying to make sure that the
person
can't link back to the original movie
because if they do that they will
say something was up paying attention because
i was dancing theme i caught him
at the end and i thought it'll
make sense when we are sure i'd
also you're trying you're going to carry
you don't really want to help the
person meet with an easy one when
you give an answer you're trying to
knock them out because if they can't
think of
something then they're out but as my
kid but you're also she is trying
to make sure that they can't link
back to the original direct quote from
mummy she mounted say melissa see if
i may quote mama ah knock you
out mama also said there'd be days
like this god mama she also told
me not to come
sorted frankie oh
ah okay right whatever thanks help me
not to come frank fret both mama
and where he goes we only want
to come relax don't do it but
where you but where do you want
to come when you and so relax
is about sex why also are honestly
didn't know songs either
or about sex or drugs relax don't
do it when you want to go
relax down to it when you're like
huh that's it's that literal it is
that literally it was a scandal at
the time did i tell you he
said that i did a lip so
disgusting i hope they're in jail i
did a lip sync to franco's hollywood
studios in nice
grade yes you did i'm glad that
i did sick and your your amazing
john lamb material write a paragraph on
it if you so desire okay so
oh no it's a paragraph oh a
paragraph is page
okay lorna you're gonna start us off
yes
she'll never be able to think she'll
never do i love this she sucks
so bad she's already losing she's sweating
look at her she's crying
she's calling mike the arrest going to
be picked up
the original hairspray
their original original hair spray
and then who goes next you ah
divine
pink flamingos this is gonna very short
as john waters was he in in
doubt it
do we we need a new ruling
mit mink stole yeah this is john
waters and actor in pink alana yeah
sorry you could have said lay yeah
well you know what it's hard work
yeah alright oh fine fine fine fine
fine so you know you're knocked out
and then it goes oh i want
to start over it was a bad
one alright alright let's clear
where you want to call wow and
relax start over okay instant family what
is rose from okay neighbors
seth rogen
ooh pineapple express
a man named danny mcbride
it's it's hard for me she made
her mouth very small
i've never learned about the small she's
only the tiniest of dicks could fit
in there oh scott
i don't which is good for you
paul no
fuck i don't fucking knee don't let
him get your hair don't know any
part of the strategy i think of
him as being on tv i can't
think of when you think he's a
tv actor i can't just give them
movies not a single movie that he's
ever been hope you're out danny mcbride
d'youville foot fist way then you don't
that is will ferrell
ooh pharaoh movies has he been in
holmes watson thank you
boring lab guess wow i love this
game jurassic world
oh my god crypt keeper chris pratt
what was the original movie by the
way in st family thank you
i will never win because i don't
know what it is it's good to
remember okay you um um
chris pratt to me right yes sir
this is a tough one i'm going
to share well i'm trying to think
i'm trying to you're trying to win
you're trying to win no i'm not
even trying to yo let's not try
to win why we saying i'm trying
to keep the game going for fun
begins no you're not but shut the
fuck up good to check in though
have to
chris pratt to you ah guardians of
the galaxy
which one
i finished the title so
i just want to make sure i
wasn't interrupting you and you were about
to say volume two you're not interrupting
me but you are trying my patience
um volume two shit i knew that
changes everything kerr wrestle yeah he's good
the hateful eight
walton goggins
oh ah another walton goggins film yep
e
nah ah i saw on a billboard
the other day that off your phone
get off your fucking phone this is
tense she's allowed to be on your
phone no she's not unless looking up
fucking people you're talking about i don't
know what's going on why is it
julie walton dog and i was going
to because i just talked about new
night because i was like his name's
walton
and goggins and then i was like
that's the end of my part of
the conversation for a friend of mine
once someone said he's dead now he's
not friend of mine was actually just
a big name oh jesus christ a
friend of mine once accidentally said his
name is google watkins gugu why can't
google oh google google watkins
who's that guy google watkins i can
think of one
well good for but that's the only
one i can think of and you
didn't see it you know i didn't
see this but i'm fairly certain you
didn't see it
interesting yeah no one's thought although it
has an airwolf connection
wow
wow this is very intriguing yeah yeah
this added some drama to this i'm
gonna say vice principals the movie no
i win you in what was it
tomb raider is there a subtitle on
tomb raider tomb raider sea of justice
raid in the tombs tombs again ah
yes
yeah didn't haze his wife right that
yes yep i realize there were guys
fucking with nori may gavin port what
is instant family who's in it mark
wahlberg was instant family oh yeah since
the family other gay adoption okay guys
i got family over god like you
stand and lose family
me these kids these kids and say
hi to your mother for me her
a mother yeah no that's right you
did do it again do it
do it say idea mother you can't
give them when kicker is
the scientist you received happy happening let's
play again hey i'm a scientist hey
there's some with some going on with
the flowers plants emit she's someone who
wakes up at like two am just
start working out and eats ten breakfasts
and he like i had a friend
who did that and i can't i
was just like is it worth it
but he was really looking
and had a great always worth but
it was easy worth it like you're
you having fun are you having any
fun i mean look the thing about
exercise is if you get in the
habit of it no but he was
doing it for i'm real like to
where he was like super jacked but
here's the thing if you get super
jack then you're just maintaining your jack
ness
i know but isn't worth it i
guess every woman wanted to fuck him
so would that be worth it like
i could do it i bet he
probably liked looking in the mirror i
liked himself and it was worth it
huh could you get super jack paul
could you get super jacked if you
like and i'm talking like like my
own
yeah but like like without like i'm
saying no you have a trainer whatever
whatever you need to do like could
you do it
i think if i
i think i could do it i
don't think it would ever be that
important to me right but you could
buy howard if i had to do
it for a thing yeah i could
do it yeah i wanna i'm gonna
direct a movie starring you but you
have to get super jacked like a
marvel movie to do it no okay
okay honestly i guess i am i
guaranteed to be in this movie
a yes or is it the the
the condition is first yeah well yeah
if you have zane you can audition
you have to strip to the waist
in the audition room and there's no
there's no question it's not like okay
you're right if you read enough to
take my clothes off for you but
there's no yes this sounds like something
else drive in but it's fun
right but it's fun and all that
happens in the dishes you take off
your shirt and i look at you
and judge you as to whether you're
jacked enough lead time let me tell
you something if i if i got
to that
if i got to that point where
i was that jacks i'd be taking
my shirt off all the time i
know i know i would never wear
a shirt would love it what it
looks stops everyone from doing it is
that it's so hard to howling how
much huh well first of all okay
if you're if you're a hugh jackman
huge jacked man uh
um he had to do it you
had to work out probably for five
hours a day and such so my
to chicken breasts no idea was that
all you need is a chicken breast
and like a little tiny bit of
rice or something like that so that
those are the sacrifices in order to
get like him i feel yeah but
i feel like we could get a
version of it right oh you mean
just healthy know i'm i don't mean
even trim down i mean like you
you build up your muscle you look
jacked but not like incredible man and
you want to be reg health man
you're speaking my language
ah i feel like i feel like
it would be
i feel like it would be at
least two hours a day oh yeah
every day i work out like four
hours a week max of like kind
of like right i'm taking a class
four times this week i was yes
so i take a variety you know
what actually don't want to say because
um i don't want weirdos robin fucking
mouth i finally got back into it
this week after being deathly ill for
the past six weeks and having working
on a project that i couldn't work
out during for the previous year and
yeah and it's like i can do
about an hour and i did it
six days this week
yeah but but like i feel like
a commitment to doing that is at
least two and a half something like
that and yeah the thing you gotta
do with a trainer it's like yeah
i love sugar i love candy yeah
it's really hard for you to not
eat i feel like i'm doing it
just so i can eat sugar and
drink wine and shit like that like
i'm you know i'm not doing any
good if you want
get jacked like that you that requires
a um that's like such a commitment
rub your your whole life where you
are thinking about that well i mean
obviously when you start you're thinking about
it all the time i mean to
get to the point where it's second
nature where like i eat these things
and you you're not actually thinking about
what i
can't eat i hear this is what
i will eat and i got there
for the tv show which i do
for five years and then i would
let it lapse in between seasons and
be really bummed and then like have
to like get back down to a
waiter whatever but like once you're in
that headspace of like oh no i
don't eat that it's yeah yeah but
i just think it would be fun
to do for a role you know
yeah just like
just do it for one movie and
then go like oh fuck thank god
like anyone times there's like a constraint
that's put on you and like in
a way that makes you healthier because
like good like oh i can't do
this thing for this whole time because
of this greater purpose or something it's
great like i feel like even just
like when i'm working i don't drink
as much i don't yeah wow wow
well i just i went
ain't for a physical for the first
time in a couple years and went
to a new doctor and as i'm
like going and i'm thinking oh i
hope he gives me a lot of
restrictions yeah because then it's slide would
like to have some structure to my
life because then it's like well like
i i can't backslide on this that
or whatever like i just started going
back to the gym the last couple
of months and i used to
be really good about it and then
i had um you know i had
about of depression which first of all
that that affects your motivation but then
also then you get a medication which
causes you to gain weight yeah and
then it's like it's a whole thing
so now i'm in a good place
where i'm trying to take care of
myself again you know saying
man would be great if the doctor
said here's what you have to do
yeah you can't do these things anymore
i will say i a couple years
ago i went to the document oh
i could just do them so much
harder yeah but i went to the
doctor and was told like oh you
have to have this type of diet
which is like yeah it's one of
the just all protein diets and you
have to lie
like have no carbs and stuff like
that yeah and i try and i
did it for six months i was
just like i wanna kill myself yeah
it's just not i mean if i
was doing for a role it would
be fine so yeah wow because i
was getting my food delivered so i
have yes stay on it and all
that stuff but it was just like
i just life sucks you know but
i will say and
maybe this is too print no i
think i can talk about but so
my father is like can't eat anymore
i don't know if i've told you
this you've mentioned it but yeah it
was on so he can't eat so
so he he basically has the the
like a liquid diet that he puts
into a tube into his stomach so
and this is a recent like over
the past couple of years and i
was and he was just kind of
saying like well you know like you
think it's not gonna be worth it
but it's like well you wanna live
right now your other and you'd rather
not die absolutely right you know so
yeah i find with with things that
i have to cut out it's usually
like no i don't know two weeks
to maybe a month to lose the
taste of the thing yeah whether it's
alcohol or sweets or bread or whatever
right but
the first little taste of it um
fucking back yeah see i shouldn't i
i stopped drinking a coke and like
any pop when i was in college
freshman college and i had to take
things so it feels like a lie
of listeners from all over yeah they
know what i'm talking about family but
i used to drink it all
the time i drink so much coke
and whatever all mountain dew all that
crap like growing up a ton of
it loved it stopped because i was
getting headaches and i've never had it
since i had like maybe a sip
of coke like a couple times last
twelve years or something and it tastes
insane to me now yeah everyone's wrong
it's like i'll have a sip and
it's like that is pretty
good well i said i'm so serbian
i started having regular coke maybe six
years ago or something i would only
have diet and anytime ever i take
a sip a regular coke it's crazy
eighties horrible to me too yeah but
the but like not having it all
makes me think like okay well if
i completely cut out my reese's peanut
butter cups or whatever the fuck
your turn my turn just right in
front of reese's egg so it looks
like a big shit but i i
if i stopped what i'd be like
eventually think it tastes gross like the
same way well i say they say
that eating carbs activates the recent study
is now that like if you have
a carb meeting like
if you drink a glass of wine
it's suddenly like trigger something in you
where you want more carbs and it's
just like a big cycle of like
cars and it happened i find it
myself at night like i'll have a
glass of wine ago god where's that
bag of chips oh yeah you know
what i mean because it's just like
karp karp karp karp and this is
the feature by the way this is
the feature paul did you have one
other thing you want to say
about this before we play one last
game i am last i have no
idea where we are the show yeah
okay yeah alright one last weekend just
give us one more movie no i
don't want to start it started you
still started um
i don't know this the first thing
i thought of the family stone thank
you i love it
family stone
i don't even know what it is
yeah i was
huh okay go see you really oh
yeah i know luke wilson who luke
wilson wow no that's luke wilson owen
wilson luke will oh no look yeah
that's no i'm saying that your you
were doing i was doing that's why
it didn't sound anything like oh and
i can't remember which one is which
h no
however luke wilson says wow and owen
wilson says wow bone wilson's the blonde
one yeah okay luke sexy blonde and
dark haired one yes um okay no
like a brick shit house who who
alright luke wilson
ah i'm gonna say roy i'll turn
and bow around bomb ben stiller
i'm gonna say meet the fockers the
problem with just two is that you
only see movies and only say actors
yeah but it's trauma robert de niro
ah oh shit this is a game
killer the adventures of rocky and bullwinkle
the
i'm saying say paul winkle
yeah
i fucking bullwinkle he not real he
not actor he you know not actors
in other movies he he not real
he not another he gun and get
us into a thing where we only
say bullwinkle movies
um which is another game entirely i
don't know who's in the well then
i fuckin wow can you say who's
in it june foray is univariate she
does the voice of rocky the squirrel
okay what's right what's that you know
that wasn't right why wasn't it right
i mean it wasn't
you pick that movie because you knew
i wouldn't know what you know but
that's how you win the game but
that's fine we can go on forever
if you guys played nice we don't
want to go wherever we want in
this episode we have to know how
right so i won paul one lawrence
loser find the um eat your turds
already day oh well more like l
l l
triple last lap gets loser loser loser
la episode title no yup see you
next time bye
a
uh