three
ah
oh yeah did it we did it
i'm proud of me didn't do it
wait we didn't know wait i'm sorry
we did do it oh i always
missed it i'm getting two stories here
i'm hearing that we did do it
and i'm hearing that we didn't do
it my
right or we did not do it
but scott saying we didn't
i'm sorry i that's just what i
heard from second hand sources this is
not you know firsthand i'm sorry but
i didn't know why what is this
whisper down the lane is this the
show don't know what that is what
is this asian telephone is that better
than chinese
nah don't think so i heard that
chinese telephone is a wonderfully racist old
saying that is basically it's it's the
story gets ah it evolves as it
goes down the line yeah but that's
what telephone is that's right somebody finally
doesn't have to be racist no it
doesn't have to know and it isn't
i'm not i'm more i'm a good
person i
got you i don't think so anymore
you
i forgot you are a very good
person who has a clean moral soul
wait when did you get a a
ninety s turquoise and purple mike
um yeah when did you get so
jealous i like right now and why
dress like a member of modest mouse
because i am i just joined the
band will play ah the tuba
i always thought
the tuba guy in the in ah
who who plays with jimmy oh the
routes yeah like he's really good he's
really getting a good deal out of
this isn't he why because he only
has to go in to lotion here
in oregon here his playing is just
like boom boom boom boom yeah and
yeah he has to do that for
every song it's great yeah he only
to learn equal share tuba guys only
have to learn one thing
and and they do it for every
song it's great but then they have
a bass player who's replicating what the
tuba does doesn't right i think that's
right i think those two are a
package deal oh okay seems like you
don't take things it's like we were
talking about the the musicals with the
kids that are double cast the same
time they'll do the same thing yeah
yeah well lauren this is this is
a grain microphone
with a with a purple ah a
pop filter oh wow yes i had
to blink wonder if i had blue
and a little picture of myself on
my mics within the picture of yourself
because it looks like a bald lady
it is not a bald lady it
is supposed to be like a statue
just like busts a marble bust it's
from my um we
must improve our production company all the
production i'm always doing ah wow
many many productions thank you yeah wonderful
welcome to three-time by the way my
name is lauren lucas my name is
maureen lefkas mine is this crazy khomeini
ah lauren lobbyist
i just introduced myself and this is
crazy
i'm lauren lag guess so have my
baby oh my gosh
ah the countdown is on people either
way any day now no that's any
week now yeah well i can't listen
to this yeah everything will be out
yeah everyone would dick clark's new year's
rockin eve would start at the beginning
of december
like recounting darryl jr here every year
well it would start the day after
halloween twelve thousand
seven thousand nine hundred and ninety nine
by the way we got some listener
mail what we have now who got
a good result from a fan named
chuck bryant ah who oh my god
she's podcast royalty of course yeah podcast
royalty from stuff you should know he
says please pass along to lower and
that my almost six year old daughter
ruby listens to threesome with me in
the car so she may be the
actual youngest listener oh ruby likes the
girl who does the funny voices that's
cool thanks ruby says quote you hallen
gotta do the best bit okay good
okay say they did the best bits
that's the core let's get one thing
right
and then he says don't worry about
the language when i said dumb shit
ah she said hey that guy shouldn't
say dumb okay wow resume does the
best ruby ruby ah you know what
though ruby is not the youngest listener
because the youngest listener of course is
little danielle lacock castle oh my babe
maybe yeah yes
i've been listening the whole time listening
to all of this she has listening
since she was his notes she has
loved note lauren what is what is
your and forgive me if this is
too personal but what is your social
security number so what is what is
your stance is your fucking deal give
me the person what's your fucking problem
what is your stance on cursing with
the child can the child curse white
lady sansa kirsten went to yeah okay
and the tag curse and the hell
the jell-o pudding i um i you
know this might come as a surprise
but i don't think people should curse
in front of children and i actually
feel bad that i've been cursing in
front of ruby
this whole time but what am i
going to do about it um you
know how how young is or what's
the cutoff like when can you when
can you say but ah but you
can say at any point but i
think they bought it anyway i remember
when my mom said fart around my
baby sister and andy was shocking to
us that kind of stuff i say
it
well great card game maybe maybe
did you smell my stinky fodder yes
i got news for you
to me yeah
that was me
like twenty the media wasn't you that
was me
because i'll know we were playing we're
playing a guy it's so hard to
explain it i think maybe i've even
talked about on the show but we
were playing a game where where she
swapped out the first letter of a
word and pointed to body parts and
was like ah you know instead of
foot it would be like boots and
the pieces would be like
zinus
but with the same guy which by
the way no but with the same
with the same letter each time so
then when she got to hard she
we were on the letter f and
women she got to the heart you
went farms and we all laughed and
were so shocked short and my mom
said it condition laugh and giggle yes
she laughed it was like i felt
like i should be embarrassed you should
have
an should should run away i never
heard my mother say that thank god
i said so
yeah that's true that's true wow
i wonder if i inherited my horror
of that word from her maybe yeah
i mean i was not set in
our house it really wasn't i mean
it is a thing you ever describe
right i mean like she would say
you know there's codeword codeword i've always
say expel gas oh they're like spell
have you been expelled it's some school
no just your gas political but i
mean when i was a kid we
were watching ren and stimpy and that
show which i also just watched this
documentary about nickelodeon and um one of
those platforms colonial odeon yeah oh thanks
yeah we get it actually now we
did it but it was called like
the orange years
years and i thought okay i'm gonna
watch two minutes to fix your mind
no because it's fucking broken i can't
deal with it right now that's why
i'm saying i have to get another
stand but anyway yeah it is so
comical i wish this were a video
i'm gonna go get it well while
scott and revamp fine we'll talk about
farting while you go get your thing
so paul how many times
farther today
okay scott and her alone yeah listen
yeah this baby is ruining our dynamic
i know right it's not fordham it's
not radar ledge you would never have
got three and a half dough it's
not three and almost no muslim did
when used to go to a restaurant
actually do
okay okay just a kid sure but
when i don't know as a kid
i wear a velvet short pantsuit
it's dry with a ribbon on a
uniform yeah it looks like you're an
ac dc yeah yeah um but with
a with what they always say like
three and a half like who gives
a shit if it's a ha i
don't remember that no the other ones
no really they would just say four
i don't remember many interactions with the
the host or hostess well i guess
oh
speaking restaurant roundup ah but we i
guess being a host that's what it
always is is like three and a
half you don't need to tell me
that your kid is five or unless
you need a booster seal ryan o'connor
entered the waiting room
well wow
look who turned his pretty little head
up into our show you're gonna let
him in let me i let him
in he was knocking at the door
he was ringing the bell okay all
right well we'll see we expect a
full apology in the chat ryan i
demand an explanation um in any case
yeah you can just say for like
especially
if you don't need ah a ah
booster see lauryn don't know what we're
talking to bay i heard parts of
my other my other mic stand is
worse it's they they broke it the
mike and joey they broke it um
what were those boys doing their tour
and bumptious i don't know but i
have other ones they just know where
they are like i were just getting
this whole room setup but can i
play you ah can i
play you a clip that we discussed
in a previous episode that i couldn't
find in the moment sure yeah profusely
go through them
laying it on your dick
oh there it is your and lying
in a pool of his own yours
lying in a pool of his own
urine and walling pools on your own
anyway okay yeah i'm gonna measure on
the pool of his own lauren liable
i'm gonna pull on lorne so i
want to get back though i want
to get back to speaking of lauren
swear to the cursing what like when
can you say
can you say shared hell here's the
thing i swear all the time so
i'm sure it's going to happen very
readily and it'll just why do you
think that that that people shouldn't swear
in front of kids well i just
don't want ah the kid to say
swear words why you don't hear it
because because it's so foul it makes
my ears but it's so
so funny into it is funny but
it's and it's going to happen anyway
i just feel like i don't want
to as long as they know the
rules of like these are words you
don't say in polite conversation or to
teachers or i just think it's like
i don't want it to be the
kind of thing where their instinct is
to say like fuck i dropped my
block yeah
i have a friend who block i
dropped my fuck her nice um there
was this video she showed me this
video of her niece ah who's this
adorable little red-haired girl um and she's
like in a bathtub charlie brown was
in love with yes the same one
wow she never got older um she's
like in the bathtub she's like playing
with
toy and then she very quietly says
fuck it and then she looks at
the at the camera with like this
look of absolute glee on her face
like i look what i just did
and then her father says what did
you just say and she goes fuck
it
she laughs maniacally i mean that is
raw and then he posted it to
the internet see it's all knowing not
the circle internet this was tribal it
remained for sure oh it was sitting
at least shared it with you as
it was fun sharing when he shared
it with his sister-in-law who is my
friend and then she shared it with
me
oh my god wait this is so
this is a reality recap but scott
if you what you're watching the bachelorette
i assume no yeah tough season yeah
honest but um season will be over
it's probably over this because chris harrison's
sorry it's over doesn't matter yeah last
week there was a point where it
sounds
like she was auto tuned and i
wish i had put my wow speaking
saying yoran and i haven't been doing
oh ryan i haven't been doing my
stories on instagram because i'm just like
oh right gotta take the season off
i think until at least until it
gets good good because i don't know
the beginning is just mayhem with all
these guys but um
um she she's goes like ah like
she she yells up and we we
both went she sounded auto-tune and then
we rerouted it was like she was
like it was so weird like they
did like near the producers did it
as a joke
or or it was so editing or
something and out of tune or something
or they need to speed it up
like that could have been a thing
and she said oh learning of it
and she said belinda and she was
like nah nah nah
nah baghdad
got tutto by leg da alachua
what about lauren what about sorry to
ask you so many questions i i'm
interesting work too
yeah sorry to ask you a second
follow up today but what what um
so at like have you planned out
conversations and at what ages you're gonna
have them with your like with mike
and stuff like that or like have
you talked about a lot of these
issues or is it kind of a
thing where you're like oh i'm just
going to take it as it goes
and will yeah talk about it
five minutes before to have a theory
take it as it goes mentality with
the entire situation um i mean parenting
situation
i mean i think like one thing
that's interesting is that just within our
relationship like sirte when certain things come
up i feel like like related to
parenting
we might have different opinions and then
it's like oh that's gonna be a
thing i guess when we have to
figure out that thing or whatever but
like it's nothing huge not like religion
or something but like ram just there
was some people have to figure that
out where it's like hey which church
or and and i'm assuming you're not
going to church we we i wasn't
going to start now i think is
the vibe
right
like well because okay fifteen probably a
great time i have some babies to
no thinker no yes yes guess what
people think that ah that some people
think you know that ah you know
the the that kids need a baseline
of that of like to to know
what it is i think i don't
and so even though they're not religious
they go like oh
i'll take you to church or whatever
tig family host yeah hosur that's what
that holes are you out i mean
i went to church enough times as
a kid that i feel like i
do have that like baseline understanding of
what churches and whether i want to
go or not ah body of christ
yeah no but
but um i don't i like we
we both don't go to church so
it would be really like a stretch
to be like now i've got to
find a church so i can teach
the hint about what churches so they
can decide they don't want to go
later yeah right but i am open
to discussing religion and god and all
that kind of stuff i think that's
great
i just like when when your daughter
is three and says what happens when
we died you say nothing our brains
just turn i'd probably say you go
to heaven
really i went i will you tell
the real truth i don't believe that
i don't believe that your brain turns
off and you just are nothing then
why are we burying people if their
brains are okay their brain i do
think i do think you don't function
as a person anymore but i think
you have a soul
okay there is an energy that animates
us that cannot be destroyed once we
die yeah i don't know if i
would just grab it that way how
many times telegraphic or six pounds sounds
holographic like sounds like a hologram
and that's what she meant that
um i don't know i i think
i kind of think everybody
i kind of think just everything shuts
down but um but who knows yeah
i mean i think i think for
a kid i understand that people teach
their kids all different things so there's
plenty of people that i probably know
who teach their kids i've got to
be carefully taught there's no afterlife and
there's no nothing happens and you do
go
on the ground and but i also
think it's like a really big concept
for a little kid to accept and
that seems kind of it's like if
even if you grow to believe that
i just think it's a lot to
say to a little kid that like
if if they know someone who died
that like they're just gone
right i think yeah so no it's
it's an i mean i guess i
would like to read an article or
something written by atheist parents who who
raised their kids to to believe there's
nothing when they die and how that
has worked out for them or whatever
you know religion in general is kind
of comforting to everyone of all ages
true from
six to sixty nine i mean yes
but i'm of the opinion that
in the afterlife you'll be ahead of
okay i mean i know you make
that sie da da da the hell
to bay by budget agenda digital squirrel
nut zippers zoom is
that's a great song by the way
yeah new after long why didn't they
ever make any other song they made
an i had one other man they
didn't have a song called put a
lid on it i have that album
that they made okay they made more
than one album but i have their
first album yeah i've got the one
yeah this is good song
yeah good stuff picking on live we
into something about that
now he just wanted to sing that
i want to sing this but i
you know i was raised catholic and
and believed in heaven and but it
was always very it wasn't comforting to
me heaven was always very weird to
me i couldn't i guess because the
concept of hell is the problem yes
that i could picture very easily like
if you learn if you are just
like hey look there's ah
you know we call it heaven but
everyone when they die i want that's
what i think i don't think you
know well i may being raised it
was like well ah only our special
people go to heaven yeah and everyone
else burns for all eternal that have
not committed adultery i mean it's hard
yeah it's a hard concept because when
you talk like i don't
think about i don't think someone who
had an affair is going to hell
but i'm saying i do think someone
who's like a pedophile probably shouldn't be
up in heaven
but what if they were in it's
weird like oh what are you doing
here he's i guess what i know
i my point is what if it's
what if it's not a reward like
like have that that's just where the
soul religions is heaven is a reward
hell is a damnation what if it
was just like everyone's consciousness gets sort
of like uploaded into an a thief
serial you know being and and just
like it's it's it's a place that
everyone just everyone who has ever been
and will ever be just all share
well i actually think the movie even
hitler the movie zoeller did you watch
solo ah yes yeah i feel like
that is a great starting point for
that conversation
just flip on souls yeah
yeah it works that's all that was
my sexual education from my parents soul
there was an afterschool special when my
mother told me to watch it and
then she left the room
wow and it was just explaining sex
and how it happened i'm i'm sure
enough that's not how this mine was
and i'm sure i said this was
in church when i was thirteen or
something the the pastor said if your
kid is twelve and you haven't had
a sex talk with them they already
know about it and i went to
i don't have to have that ah
already know or you'd like i could
still use a few clarified i honestly
still had no idea i remember being
thirteen and my friend saying the word
bush and me going like and i
could tell it was sexual and i
was like i think he's trying to
say that he's going to go take
the girl into the bushes and make
out oh yeah
oh dear i mean i know we've
talked about this and then i dissected
a frog believe i'm dissecting a frog
i should be able to know what
sex is i don't want a frog's
pussy looks like
when when the pastor said that was
he being like kind of funny or
was he being serious i think he
was trying to nature scare that gets
parents to talk to their kids about
sex at a younger age or something
like that because by the time they
were thirteen or whatever they were already
corrupted and you needed to talk to
them about sex
in the context of marriage and also
weirded out by like fucking
i don't want to talk about it
i mean i also remember in church
how they they talked about iron maiden
albums and how the mascot eddie was
a corpse and how that will lead
to heavy metal fans wanting to have
sex with corpses and and a rash
of necrophilia fair did
sure i mean we all yeah want
and thank god that period is over
but it was of course that was
i mean the ladies were wild yeah
they were like wild wild lives what
if your little girl grows up to
be taller than you will you like
that too oh my god i said
you'll have to look up at her
that would be awful i have wondered
about that
um she is already thinking it would
be sweet
because your ac reggie of either yes
she'd be looking down at all i
mean hey i don't know if she's
gonna be so tell us she's looking
at me like i'm little no i'm
not sure i'm saying she'd be a
fetal
wait how tall is my he's six
three six two six three yeah so
i mean it could happen i'm taller
than my parents yeah i'm much taller
than my mum i'm like most all
of my parents but that was not
difficult to do right because they were
too fita high to feed they were
three apples high like hello kitty
what that satoshi is three episodes the
smurfs ah yeah i guess oh can't
you gotta
hayes gave it a quot
so i smell a rat she's five
apples in her hitting okay hello kiddies
five apples in her way as three
apples
lady how could she be five apples
high and weigh three apples she's got
away at least five and a smurf
is no more than three apples tall
so yeah i want to know how
many apples tall i am
so an ashes we should stack a
bunch of apples ha ha oh i've
been saying that for a long time
but now it has context an apple
is seven centimeters so let's we're doing
the hotel are you paul
i'm five nine five nine in celebrate
did you face centimeters oh my gosh
why why couldn't you look up how
many inches is example one seventy five
times seven so your twelve hundred twenty
five years
oh hey are you doing this yeah
i know but here was really find
out
do we need to wait on the
conversion i just understood about what i
was doing wrong um euros am i
no but to your one hundred seventy
five apples tall
i hate seventy five no way it
doesn't matter that fansedge for six so
it doesn't make sense anyway
how many jews apples are no once
you have divided by seven that's what
it is so your twenty five apples
tall okay okay that makes
you did it how many apples does
he weigh
okay hell i don't want talking about
your weight
put it in the know why people
do the math you can convert and
figure out how much i owe oh
i'm all right to put i'm all
right to say i'm i'm one currently
on one ninety four okay so many
apples with that be how much is
an apple way as my first question
yes in pounds not in kilos empirical
i put in blurbs okay and slobs
boy point three three lb boy point
three and it's a boy playing three
three lb boy three three pounds sos
so three apples per point so yeah
so what's your weight one ninety divided
by three so your proxy
lately you're under six hundred apple you're
sixty you're sixty three apples heavy i
don't think that didn't you say point
three three pounds
yeah but divided by three years should
time at pinetree no it's three apples
per pound i think so he's gone
this is what you want to do
but not by pounds your five hundred
and seventy you want to do it
by kilos your five hundred seventy apples
get over it ooh there we go
that's not good
i got a tug loosen apples yeah
you got to eat fifty less apples
a day i've been i've been going
to the gym every day for a
mulan right now thank you very slim
on solo i don't see i don't
base your worth i know but i
feel like i'm starting to look like
myself again do you know what i
mean yeah i really like it was
i had a
ride a rough pandemic guys i didn't
know that you've been working out because
i i saw a picture you posted
i was like i thought you looked
very slim well thank you very much
i'm i'm working on it um i
want to get back to um ah
where i was before i got so
depressed yeah years ago but it feels
good like right around when we
i started this show it feel it's
weird howling mind
talk nice makes you sad it feels
it feels really good to be i'm
back to like going to bed at
a decent hour like i go to
bed around ten and wake up around
six or seven and i'm liking the
mornings again which i haven't in a
long time and i got such bad
habits during the quarantine yeah me too
workout right in the morning or do
you take awhile before you do i
like to do it in the morning
i like to dye my breakfast in
my coffee and then i sit around
for like a half hour or whatever
and then i go yeah and it
feels good i came right from the
i needed a little extra time today
because i wanted to shower before i
joined you guys thank you so much
because you've been stinking so god you
smelted you can see my my
pink like yesterday i said you've been
going to a gym yes there's a
jealous closer my dealing with ah the
post pandemic gym it feels good because
they it was a gym that was
taken over by new people and they
have rearranged cooling yeah there was it
was a bloody coup
ah well next door was like fireworks
or the coup um and ah they've
rearranged everything so like i do cardio
and the the cardio room is now
very spacious and very airy and it
feels extremely safe and it's actually way
more it's it's brighter it's more there's
more of a cross
sprees you know it's great now yes
they left one window open they actually
have a huge window that they that
has to um like shutter openings and
annotation shutters no dear please don't what
is this the telephone plantation telephone you
can still say plantation shutters
can't you ah probably but why yeah
i don't know i well i mean
there's no other way to describe them
when you're talking about a house do
you fit well i'm not talking about
a house talking about a gym ah
talk about a house god we no
longer say master bedroom we say primary
bedroom oh that's good i guess although
i always
i thought it was just like you're
the master over your children master of
the whole-house do de da de do
do de da da but i'm a
white guy but i'm a wacky guy
out of that song the whole subtitle
yeah just be yeah i'm a funny
guy you're gonna enjoy listening to me
sing this song doesn't further anything it's
the worst part um i guess when
i was i was at my parents'
house yesterday and i've found that like
certain people in my family i don't
want to put them on blast even
though the elders
never listen
we'll figure it out really just base
everyone's worth on their weight yeah it's
terrible it's just a dress and you
know i have lost weight as well
recently going to the gym a lot
and it was like finally everything was
cool for this person in my family
was like oh well
you know you look great you know
i'm so impressed and ah you know
and then and then when they watch
tv they're always like well that person
lost a lot of weight then or
this or this news anchor gains like
forty pounds in the last two years
like like they're always judging everyone they
see by god how up and down
their wages fluctuate
rating and it's an i and i
started to realize that when i when
i became like kind of attuned to
it and so it's something that i'm
just trying to drop from my life
of oh yeah absolutely you know i
mean just not even just in like
turning inwards i mean like looking outwards
of anyway yeah gives a shit what
you know i've had fluctuate
thing wait for years and for me
i finally got to a point where
i was like
you know it's it's very hard when
you when you go through when your
body goes through changes it's very hard
sometimes to adjust to that and yeah
puberty i buy now i've heard a
monster and i'm like okay that is
for you thank you
i think it was weird that it
took so long no offense but it
was like um you know like to
the idea of of loving yourself where
you are is really more challenging why
did you want what did he think
because we do the best bits lodi
and i'm gonna you're just
you're just taking things in now just
really nilly
free willy nilly
right well yeah wouldn't make sense okay
um but yeah loving yourself where you
are yeah because i was it was
easier for me to do it with
other people than it was for me
to do it with my yeah right
you know and to say like yeah
like if you're if you're happy where
you are that's good the the most
important thing is being happy where you
are and for me i realised why
i was not happy in certain
places um moda and also ah
also wanting to be healthy too because
i was not i was not take
i wasn't take care of myself i
just wasn't taking care of myself yeah
well you i not that you looked
poorly before exact ah well that you're
hearing with that but that compliment because
yeah i i it's ah it's tough
i meant it as i meant
second is just that you like you
don't mean like i it's like i'm
not saying you're better or worse or
anything like that and i have a
friend who's recently been on like a
weight loss journey but not even it's
not it's again not really focused on
losing weight so much as feeling healthy
and just like changing habits and stuff
yeah yeah and so it's one of
the i also i don't i don't
like it the lorne when it's the
other way like on the
bachelor's reality recap when it's the bachelor
read and she's or the bachelor in
there and they're saying like well i
want with bachelor rinos who has over
the ken marino who i want someone
who has a healthy lifestyle but when
they're really just saying they want a
muscle mass because weight doesn't determine health
but i'm saying that's why i'm saying
i'm like
what if what if would they ever
go for someone who's like kind of
a beefy guy who actually is healthy
and who's kolesar right down and more
when you know they're saying you know
yeah same yeah so that's what i
mean my friend because she she wasn't
like trying to lose weight to look
a certain way or have a certain
number trying to redistribute it yeah but
well
because it's more that she was like
i haven't been eating while i haven't
but you know you can be eating
while doing those things in your body
can look all different ways yeah but
also her she has lost weight as
a result and so is one of
those things where i'm like i know
that that's not her intention but i
also want to compliment that because she
looks great and shows great before i'd
ever thought anything negative about her but
she looks great and maybe we should
stop saying people look great in general
well i know because i like the
jersey comes this whole week like weird
topic well just us talking about it
now it's like you especially with people
that you know you want to first
of all you that's the only person
you should ever say that to someone
you know yeah yeah yeah we're we're
now even with that we qualify
it's so much like nothing you'll back
before you know and yes it's like
it's just we manage well just not
say it just like note it in
your in your head if you don't
have to say anything but can we
can we say that someone is dressed
well i think that was her thing
is a choice you know clothing xy
is something people can well ah unless
you can't afford nice clothes oh my
god but
you can just you could kill me
to get a certain point yes you
could show them try to compliment someone
i mean i said to her we
were talking about it i was like
i'm really impressed by all the work
you've put in because she was working
she's working out five days a week
and she's yeah even on the certain
foods that she's making fun here but
ok sure good and she's doing three
days of cardio in five day
days of um way to stop wow
and i was just like i'm so
impressed by that commitment and then as
we were talking and i was like
and i know it's not about how
you look but you do look good
eight days a week rinko workout tape
hello this is the beatles book o
j dazu i just wanted to add
lucy love
so finish this no groups just that
i think that it's not negative to
say someone looks good i don't think
someone who is working on themselves actively
is gonna be offended that you said
you look good no here's here's the
difference is that there was somebody that
i had not i had somebody on
a podcast one time that i had
not seen in a very long time
and
and i had lost a significant amount
of weight since the last time i'd
seen this person and all this person
could say to me was you look
so good like literally for the amount
of time that we were not talking
on mike this is all this person
said to me yeah it was like
this is i don't this is starting
to be insulting now or they yeah
phone you though they were new
not trying to bone me are you
sure they're trying they're saying there's a
healthy ah like level of compliment you
can give and also what i know
the person really well it's another thing
to like this is an old friend
of mine so i understand that it's
okay for me to say that she
knows where i'm coming from blah blah
blah yeah but yeah will never come
in on somebody online or something would
you ever say to someone
ooh sexy muscles boy yeah like i
like walk down the street big when
you get those muscles okay question
yesterday hey total stranger when those muscles
i would probably say ooh sexy muscle
blow to someone yeah if they were
sexy muscle boy yes yeah right yeah
i know plenty of people who'd been
happy to hear that compliment
i mean if they're yeah it's how
many wickets at least four
it's even tough when someone does look
good and they're proud of it to
say like hey you look great because
then you know in the inevitable time
when they don't in the future they're
gonna like be thinking fuck i looked
so good before now it looks well
shoot that's the thing too it's like
with if you're gonna be someone who's
complimenting somebody's looks you probably should just
do it all the
time yeah you can go every single
day and be based on a change
you see i mean like i feel
like okay you know about my friends
like they look pretty at all sizes
and whatever and if they i probably
tell me look pretty one day and
then they lose weight i'm like oh
you look pretty it's like it's not
really like connected to the same dock
connector lauren do me do me a
favor and reach out
to every single friend of yours and
tell them they look good every single
from you
yes
i think for you should be able
to you should compliment people all the
time and say things like if they
gain weight say you look good like
this too yeah
alright we have to take a break
man we're back hi hi hi thank
you thank you hey i knew it
was much we did yeah i was
scared i was so frightened for you
once
well john always chat
hi ny wait was why not one
of his things to know i'm just
saying he shouldn't have more than two
cats you should have more than two
catchers this true so one is why
not okay about it
who in ten minute walk where where
to be by your ponies quest lie
um have you is there anything else
that you and mike have decided you're
going to do like okay well we're
definitely doing this you know no and
this is i mean and maybe i
don't know what we're very day by
day this is true i mean i
really feel like oh i just wanna
get everything right i prepared everything
i can prepare it with items that
i need to have things that you'd
need to buy like you have ah
what a car seat got the car
seat got the crib got a bunch
of clothes one for the house one
for the car totally and i want
to feel like one for them i
feel like i ah you know i've
i've been taking some online classes we
have a doula who's teaching us things
classes and what
labor and delivery and processing we're still
talking about that yes sorry and um
and so i'm really focused on that
but but it's also something that it
kind of has come up as in
my mind as i've been thinking about
this is like and i think it's
very common but i'm focused very focused
on the delivery part because that's like
that's a really important part and it's
sky
carry a little bit and you know
she's big and then you know the
rest of it is like i have
to raise the child
yeah i mean you're yourself focused on
the legitimate three hours yeah you know
that you're forgetting about the next eighteen
years like the wang versus marriage and
i think that that's okay for right
now i'll definitely figure it all out
i have time you know here here's
my here's my new theory on parenting
you split your money with the kid
like right down the middle right so
right and you give you give you
hear about lawrence half your money to
the kid and then you say anytime
i buy you anything you have to
buy me something of equal value but
suddenly this may six money
alright guess it's just like oh wait
because i'm like i want to keep
things equal because so many parents grow
up and they're like oh man i
raised that kid i spent so much
money on the kid and they they're
not thankful this is a purely equitable
trade of like if i buy you
food you have to buy me like
a chair that's equal you know the
food i think i'd rather raise the
child to have gratis
dude
i mean good luck hey i don't
know it's your baby
i was watching reality recap i was
watching million dollar listing la and or
new york i'm sorry and um the
woman's child she was like asking her
woman's child realtors she was like asking
her kid like go help be the
big sister and helped me get this
thing together then she was like give
me forty dollars and i was like
that's five and the
women's authority darling growlers but i was
like where did that come from that
you think you should have forty dollars
to do a little chore and what
what would a kid spend forty dollars
on these days okay and i'm uncle
you know lego
oh well i mean that used to
be a special trip you would go
to like toys r us and be
able to buy a lego set on
a special day you'd see geoffrey the
giraffe you will love toward us walk
into the bike i'll oh my god
awesome so i guess my point is
is like i'll yes i used to
get walking around money that way
would be like maybe i would get
a dollar and i could go buy
a couple of comic books or something
like that like what cost forty dollars
that is that equivalent of that forty
comic you know what i mean yeah
affording no i mean nowadays ten while
candy of course there's always candy you
can buy a lot of candy for
eighty dollars know what i'm saying is
too much that's why i'm saying forty
is too much like if it was
like no no you could push a
lot every handy with nobody you couldn't
buy a lot of candy with a
dollar when we were you know you
couldn't but with forty dollars you could
buy a lot and i'd damn you
to hell and i don't even believe
it but i want you to spend
eternity there what if i'm there already
um i don't know i mean we've
we've talked about allowances and i think
i was getting seven dollars a week
at one point which i thought was
fantastic sure a dollar a day would
not mind seven dollars a week right
now somebody just gave me free seven
dollars absolutely i'll give you seven dollars
a week you want some dollars a
week
if you send up flowering venmo payment
of seven dollars towards around my house
i'm not doing chores around grouse know
if you take tell you what tell
you what every friday in the afternoon
you have to come over to my
house and take my garbage cans in
and that's it well no deal for
seven dollars a week any idea
i'll be doing that makes me so
sad
for seven dollars a week yeah yeah
you are right yes
but is this garbage
go home and then he venmo seven
dollars or he walks out enhancing seven
singles
we're there to teach the inside of
the garbage can that's it it's in
an envelope it's in an envelope taped
to the inside of the lid but
it's a check had someone couldn't cash
the check trump and travelers check how
much would you do it for
how much would i do that specific
chore for that specific chore for yeah
i have bear in mind i have
three garbage cans run you need to
go up the dry wood do it
are actually the least of it i
like more than travel
you don't know what the demeaning nature
of the entire thing but i would
do it for a hundred dollars a
week
you would do it for one hundred
dollars a one hundred a week sure
whether this is worth it to me
ah yeah will try to four or
an ipad i had a week and
engraved i-pad
every week
every week there's a pub brand looking
for a winning show when raved i-pad
yeah
and personalized not engraved to someone exactly
no engrave to you i want stuff
that no i wanted to say scott
i want to say your name o
personalized to you sure okay okay sure
dear scott there's an ipad it says
deals out on it love apple
ah so wait so you got seven
dollars a week for and how old
were you and what what did you
have to do for it that was
probably a lot of elementary school and
like i think it might have gone
up a little bit in middle school
but not really um and then what
did i do i did a lot
of the the whole concept of allowance
what is it
it's basically just to give your kid
like ah a treat that they want
every once in a while or like
to teach them how to spend money
is that yeah how to say i
mean i would get it in any
we'd always go to candy or whatever
yeah i i don't know what i
would spend i guess i was buy
a beanie baby because they were six
dollars that was kind of exciting all
of dover for candy exactly
they were taxed um but six weeks
you could buy another beanie baby why
every six weeks oh with the dollar
because they were six dollars yeah um
i i don't think it was based
on like specific chores like there was
like a chore chart but i did
a lot of things i did the
laundry in my house growing up and
yeah i liked it but
you can't even iron a shirt why
didn't have to iron anything okay um
but i would fold everyone's clothes and
put them in their room and then
like you know that was what i
do a lot um other than that
i don't know what else i think
that's more than i did already yeah
i did do a lot of gardening
oh that seems hard like pulling weeds
yeah so i feel like i had
to do that i did um so
less sweeping sweep down hate sweeping to
this day of course shoveling snow in
the winter time yeah shit in the
summertime trash cans absolutely um what else
trying to think like we were supposed
ah i was not good at like
cleaning bathrooms like things like that that
required like scrubbing like real elbow grease
i was terrible yeah i sometimes had
to do the mirror in the bathroom
please don't wait
doors locked it's just using you and
me
but yeah sometimes
so yeah sometimes i'd have to create
some windows or mirrors i don't like
that either really any kind of fizzle
i mean i keep my room clean
and then i i liked cleaning like
stuff so like i liked organizing so
you know as i said i would
go to my brother's room and clean
his room
i always liked organizing i liked cleaning
windows because windows felt like
it was satisfying like cleaning windows was
satisfying like there's a tangible result of
the ah yes yeah yeah yeah whereas
clean glasses sweeping disgusting but yeah cleaning
windows is like making making a dirty
window clean and looking through it is
very satisfying for some reason right yeah
thank you don't why don't you come
over and clean my windows how how
much how much would you do that
for
all my windows every single one so
allies there's no you what you wouldn't
do there's no money amount of money
the world's getting climb that insane
there's no amount of money no amount
of money people do real job like
wow i'm every week ground-floor windows every
week so i don't wanna know i
don't really care of her dog take
your entire yeah guys what have we
got what have we got part-time jobs
i think about that so i think
about it a lot
there's zero or there's a health store
that i go no um that's downtown
just plays called baron hats it's a
great hat store they make like hats
for movies and stuff like that you
shall work there i have so i've
honestly thought about it because i would
love to be able to make a
hat that would be so cool it
would be cool i don't think they'd
need any money you could be in
a pr
princess i thought about being an apprentice
yeah yeah i feel like you could
i feel like you get that i
think i think about andy kaufman just
bussing tables maybe only at the height
of his fame when i think about
that i didn't know about that makes
you mad i i think i think
it would be interesting to do just
like i think that's what sometimes although
i guess i guess if i were
going to do it instead of it
being a job for
money it would be better just to
volunteer at a place yeah like making
like a thing of service that you
know learned that is the one thing
i thought about instead of going to
church on sunday like making one of
the weekend days like a day of
service i think that's great i mean
every time i have volunteered in my
adult life i feel like it's so
happy i did it
um there's like a lot there i
did what i get the beginning the
pandemic i volunteered at um
er no it was before the pandemic
didn't have a mask on yeah i
guess it was before just didn't feel
that hobby when the mask um i
yeah won't stop you but i volunteered
at the la foodbank and it was
such a nice day and when we
used to do that with usb collapse
noon i remember that usb yeah ah
yeah
i'm sort of wing of ah she
started the you know getting onto her
thing yeah yeah the volunteer thing and
we did it at the food bank
for quite a few years where you'd
go down and you'd like box up
meals and stuff like that um which
in some ways kind of feels like
it's more of a promotional thing because
they don't really need your help doing
that as much
as like i think they wanted everyone
to be out there like saying hey
the foodbank is around yeah oh well
well you know works like posta meals
and then serving oh that's cool
oh that's cool um but then um
i also one other organization were like
that cool up i think was the
one who organized this was probably through
cb the baby to baby place that's
um where they give women who swapped
babies don't it's like they give clothes
and diapers to babies give them to
each other need them
and so it's it but it's like
sometimes volunteering like i think sometimes volunteering
can seem intimidating because a so i
don't know like i can get i
can get weirdly shy in certain situations
i don't know but like um but
then the things that i've done i
found that like oh there's always a
task you can do that isn't it
sits within your comfort zone like you
do
don't have to do something that is
if you're if it just is mainly
to people out there who are like
afraid to volunteer because i do feel
like there's like an element of like
social anxiety that comes with the idea
oh i'm hearing yes but like well
also the the social anxiety of being
in any situation where you don't know
how to do it yes yeah is
is very big like where you don't
just don't know what's going to happen
like if you can't pick
her yourself doing something like like if
i show up to this place what
are they going to have me do
and there's so many it just gets
to be very paralyzing yeah but like
for example with the baby to baby
charity like there were people you could
see you could stand there and fold
clothes and sort them or you could
like put boxes together you could label
addresses or you or there's something that's
more hands on with other people like
so you could do something by yourself
kind of or get involved with other
people and i think that's like a
good thing to keep in mind with
that kind of thing yeah i think
that's a good thing to do with
your kids too is just a nice
idea still it's still a thing
um but i also think we should
get part-time jobs i did i tell
you about the guy at the record
store who owned a hire me and
recently okay so no no not recently
but someone i should work yeah
when i was in college i would
go into this record store a lot
and ask for very specific things you
know and be like cool cloudy yeah
this is smart people say hey what's
a cool record that would be like
cool with all the chicks at cafe
cora ah i still don't know that
the guys the guy behind the counter
was in ah ah a band that
was very
very influenced by the wonder stuff they
were like a wonder stuff rip off
band in any case so i would
go in there a lot in the
owner would see me all the time
and at one point he said to
me um hey are you looking for
work because you're always in here and
you know so much about music and
i could use someone like you and
i was like oh you know what
i'm in acting
college and i don't have time and
then when i was looking for work
they didn't need anyone and then i
saw him in a mall like the
following year and i went up to
him i was like hey dude how's
it going are you still over there
at the record store and he gave
me the weirdest answer which was ah
i'm not over there currently
i'm doing well i can't say what
but don't you worry about me ah
isn't though i was like oh drugs
what is it
just you just sparked a memory that
i'm trying to place right now of
what i was walking through the mall
this was like a while like years
and years ago i was walking through
the mall in la and
this guy was like shooting something like
they were shooting some commercial or i
don't know what it was but he
came it was god i can't remember
such a bad story but i don't
care he came up to me and
he was like trying to he was
like we had met before i guess
and he was like trying to like
show me how cool he was because
he was doing this thing kind of
wish i knew who it was oh
man what a bad story shows me
i've had that since you were at
the mall and saw god yeah okay
ah hey that happened to me too
it's really relatable see
i used to lie i used to
love going to spencer's gifts i would
go to plymouth meeting mall oh my
goodness adventures gifts then did you have
a certain game in you that you
wanted he wanted to get a fortnite
fan i think that needle thing where
you would put your hand in it
and it would oh i have that
thing yeah oh that yeah did you
were you mature enough that you didn't
put
it on your face because like we
are always putting on i'm sure i
did yeah i'm sure
but what's wrong with putting on your
face it's like a million other people
have yeah oh okay
spencer's spencer is still a thing i
think it is there's this one mall
in burbank that is like every store
is like something you've never heard of
in your life like they're always caught
they're called like times space like they're
just they'll have like weird time there's
even ellipsis time
do you know that mm all that
space in downtown bryan they just read
they just yeah a lot of it's
not has like we shot there it's
got the glass elevator right the great
cloud when i was at a hotel
that we were at wasn't it but
it's right near oh no that's across
across the street but yeah i know
which one yeah yeah no there's there's
a mall with a glass elevator that
we shot ah ah
a talk show in an elevator with
andy dick and jack black that was
fun oh um with people get with
people from them all just getting on
and off during the talk show essential
that's funding the audience for the talk
show it was if it was a
funny idea and it never went anywhere
let's all say it did it did
it did it like this small that's
like a dead zone like it's like
every store is
weird i've never heard of a single
one that i'm in a mall when
a mall goes bad like that yeah
it's like what are we doing them
all spoils when i'm all clooney's wow
clooney's i'm ok
oh i get this
yeah everything used
look at everything right away huh
hey welcome back we're back we're back
the three of us are back hold
onto your hats and glasses and you
know what it's time for three church
that's right we do this every single
time and everyone loves it three years
where we play a little game amongst
ourselves and you get to listen to
it but
you can play along with us we
just can't hear you this is sure
this is a game called text guests
and it is similar to the famous
show gravid watcher but instead of reading
one side of a stage play we
will take turns choosing a text thread
from our phones that we're comfortable making
public and really me we're not very
comfortable with god all
of them have the names of famous
people have them and we read one
side of the conversation the other two
players take turns responding to the texts
or we could turn into a three
person group chat but have to keep
the conversation as coherent as possible since
this is a checks conversation we can
also vocalize emojis memes or reactions as
needed
ed should we just turn into like
a conversation rather than a text conversation
you know what i mean like you're
just reading yay the conversation that started
the person reading the thing is part
of ah is is talking to us
yeah i think that's better yeah because
i don't want to read emoji isn't
shit okay here we go do you
like me to start yeah going up
or we could we could start and
have you will enter that's maybe better
oh okay it's interesting because whatever you
say will affect yeah what okay so
let's start okay so ding dong let's
plays
i just i i before paul gets
here yeah i i have to tell
you that ah i have some big
news that i need to tell him
it's beth i'm on route is the
rule of spot open or shall i
aim for st oh you're here well
you're not you're talking you're here i
hit a little bit of tree
efek on the one ten so i'm
hoping to get there right at one
please forgive yeah sweeney here you hear
someone yeah your or you like take
getting a text in line i'm a
road warrior up and look we all
know that you didn't that needs no
further clarification but um hey paul i
i'm so glad you came over because
ding dong and ding dong sort of
supply can be up but there's there's
something that i've been meaning to tell
you for a long time flight to
pod
yeah i mean i think you should
i think you should say it's got
i think peskin look i think you've
gone crazy and you're saying weird things
i nine hundred feet away just merging
it to sense it off the exit
okay it's it's a metaphor scott she
she's i see i see okay look
i have i want to be closer
i don't want you to be nine
hundred
and feet away so i am here
just waiting to pull in and and
i am a guy who's here waiting
for you to pull i'm here wait
until my holidays pull into each other
the single lane thing is slowing everything
and getting off the freeway ah i'll
leave the room then i don't know
i mean like look i know i'm
i'm i'm adding a lot of prob
golems to your dynamic that dynamic is
for you too i'm so i want
to be friends with ding dong as
well as friends with being you and
i'm sorry that makes you feel like
you you're so far away from me
i'm in the lot
well i m in the lot of
feelings for both ding dong and for
you paul elevator
i'd like to elevate her to a
position of being one of my best
friends but it's not going to work
out because paul gets so jealous i
adore you thanks for having me and
also being sweet and hilarious i love
my pin it stays on my jean
jacket
so i mean i'm so glad that
i mean i
when i bought you that pan i
was like is this gonna stay on
his jean jacket i really was unsure
so i'm so glad to hear that
he's a better friend than i am
because my pin is not on my
jean jacket one hundred percent me
yeah i mean that is true you
are one hundred percent you i'm so
glad that we could work this out
let's all hug you are the best
thanks for sending me this major heart
for you
well major hurt for you maybe you're
getting closer though haha
oh okay okay thanks will take all
disconcerting and the best know it is
the best when when three friends love
each other it truly is the best
thanks paul thanks so much paul
picture of a clock at a train
station
okay well
alright just at the end let's try
i have a tech said i'm willing
to try okay i think this time
um
let's all be characters okay okay
alright rodolfo are you thinking what i'm
thinking
well i have to say edward
that i am not was i'm thinking
of donuts rodolfo now i'm thinking of
donuts well then i am thinking what
you're thinking oh it is look who
it is it's uh what what was
her name again i don't know her
dang dong
was the players taken a long ride
and getting food at some point it's
cloudy but warm
ooh that sounds good good can we
ride with you i'd love to join
you were heading east possibly end up
in michigan
oh yeah a little farther for me
but i could call it a work
maybe and ah gift get some time
off i'd love to do a company
it's kind of our usual route
oh so okay well you said the
way is that faster slow or what
do you think why is that much
else to do i took off today
and tomorrow oh so this drink there's
going to need a little more time
off than that but yes i'm getting
back you know how many guys gonna
tell me well i still need to
organize my christmas crap in the play
room and get it back into the
heading maybe tomorrow maybe not
okay so we got on a trip
i don't know how you're gonna organize
i need to get off work i
gotta tell people where i'm going it's
our plans fluid is slow cold in
that room that honestly i don't want
to go in there i have too
much crap
well then i would say don't worry
about it we'll just take the trip
and i yeah you know we're going
to need at least like five days
but i like oh oh well
i will look if you want to
stay here you know edward denied weren't
even going to take this trip that's
right until you came over i mean
i obviously you're torn between wanting to
organize your christmas crap and wanting to
take this trip that's the problem i
use the stuff maybe i can just
rent decorations
i don't think that's a thing a
renting christmas or a house that's weird
i mean wow that's the best news
oh well i've got it's weird i'm
happy to deliver that news rodolfo we're
really doing it well let's go on
this trip what do you say dang
dong she's so proud of you
and
yeah putting poison ourselves okay well ah
thank you so much are you talking
about yourself in the third person now
dang
well ding dog does do that ding-dong
does that but yeah cute show i
love your dress ah thank you i
is my first time wearing one it's
very comfortable and and breezy i was
gonna say you look great but i've
stopped saying me too i prefer cream
of mushroom myself
i foreclose i don't know how that's
disgusting i do not like polenta
i never said you did so i
don't put words in my mouth yang
gong i don't know that i would
go on this trip anymore dang dog
i just baked a pound of bacon
well then you better get to eating
it i'm going home i mean you're
you're really leading us on with his
trip imo michelin chef to watch congratulations
wow let me stay here and you
can cook foremost be good bacon it's
the only way to keep her from
starting a grease fire
who meet who
she talking in the third person good
i found oh wow look at it
yeah it's me wow and yeah time
flies
it sure does it's it's a beautiful
clark twenty seven years ago
that's what we about it wow did
me bought it oh yeah it was
but you should you fade obvious well
it was obviously made fifty two years
how old are you
i was one i was not born
yet
i have a cauliflower at home i'll
practice holding it
okay well
when we do that to a
ah i need your home address dong
oh i'm not giving you my home
out because mine is one two three
four five i live with said highway
drive thanks
you're welcome we'll see you there or
at your place i don't know where
wearing this definitely not michigan no i
don't think i want to go okay
we had nigel and we do have
so much fun goodbye dang dong forever
ah that was again ah that was
the let see what i can do
it's hot
okay
go ahead guys
ham what this is our first day
at hogwarts i can't believe it we're
going to be wizards i'm so excited
i've been spitting me whole life wondering
when i'll be when i grew up
and here i get to already find
out and i'm only twelve i can't
wait to get my wand
yeah i didn't realize that was the
case until the movers pointed it out
oh yeah matters move you into hogwash
lucky i had to do it all
myself me too i just had a
bindle it doesn't look like a simple
pullout and they aren't comfortable with doing
it
well venetian made them do it i
feel like you hate that i mean
not to be rude but it feels
like he kind of backed into a
corner yeah somebody going to have a
baby look if you could come asap
that would be great where already here
or did you mean oh oh no
god i hope he didn't anyone i
think he means they'll be done loading
up the truck in an hour or
so hold on a second is the
sick freak oh are you are you
supposed to be here
i'm fine with keeping that same cordless
too
i'm sure you are like hey you
know
we were actually getting to know each
other we're gonna be roommates and i
mean i guess you're one of our
roommates too there is a third bed
i couldn't really tell if you are
but you need to kind of be
a little more um openness creepy yeah
well can you walk me through putting
it back online yeah it's pretty simple
i mean
mean the computers over there we all
share this desktop computer and you just
like entering the password and then you're
online
so it needs to dry out it
hasn't rained for many hours and still
offline
no it's not it's not the worldwide
wet it's the worldwide web good one
yeah well the unit is completely off
how is it powered okay can you
just like look at the manual i'm
sorry i wasn't expecting to be tech
support my first data outlets it has
the christmas lights hooked up to it
is dead too
perhaps connected okay well why don't we
just like call one of the like
super what do you call it visors
yeah and they can help us we'll
get the house elf to fix it
so when you hit the best hello
you're not getting anything at all the
doorbell has no power to it no
when we're getting the best hello
it's when people are being friendly and
charming and what you're not being frankly
i'm sorry to be so straight with
you correct correct okay so you admit
it
well i can come take a look
early tomorrow morning
look fine pewter just wait wait yeah
okay okay to see if i'm okay
i can check the outlets tomorrow that's
right let's or whatever you need what
time can i come take a look
at ty live here i live here
we're usually up around seven am then
seven
i'll be there around seven i won't
wake you guys you'll all rake a
look
don't wake us that's great don't wake
us i'll just take a look from
the side of the house perfect watch
your gonna go sure great go outside
do whatever you want whenever he looks
i have a feeling water got in
the box and trip the outlet and
anything water got in your brain and
trip the outlet yeah yeah fucking freak
oh we don't have to come anymore
good great
i'm not even sexually active thank you
for offering we'll keep you updated and
will give you friday night they offer
good morning and merry christmas eve oh
merry christmas eve i feel terrible now
i feel bad that we're fighting on
christmas eve
yeah ah that did it that was
gary jackson decided we did it we
time we truly did not do it
you're right wait scott conflating reports oh
no i thought we did it
alright look everybody this episode is over
thank you for listening and the books
we love you ah please do check
us out on instagram and twitter at
three am usa and if you have
a three-tier suggestion write it to email
to email said freedom usa at gmail
dot com love you guys
said scott love you said scott all
the time
um like you okay
alright bye bye
uh