three
i really didn't know
this allowed isn't fun
christ
oh i didn't know we were starting
and i'm throw no no but i
caught up during the song you did
yeah you're here now yeah space lauren
made when it started was like ah
thanks for the heads up but fine
yeah exactly that's exactly right yeah that
was your face when now
that was not feeling one though feeling
you feeling interface one feeling i think
it's feeling okay because people are always
be faces videos it's hard because it's
hard to convey a feeling without making
a face but you're like that's so
true that face when
but i can't think of one what
oh you know what it is it's
because it's m f w we make
my place when i think i fell
it was my face when i don't
fucking know because it's always a face
my feeling what let's look it up
and vfw is a thing i've never
seen i don't know about i've oh
i've seen oh you don't know about
it while i do ah my face
what about vs my face
one my face when you're right
and my face one joined the fellowship
and they went to throw the ring
in the of
when your favorite movie my piece when
it's when i throw that ring and
be able to this plane welcome to
freedom everyone i'm paul i'm lauren i'm
scott
and this is another episode did you
think that we ended after the last
one au contraire we got news for
you it might seem seeming busy oh
my gosh she's ever busy billy crystal
lady
a new decade
i did did he have a high
touch ya know you thought that no
he didn't have you know
that is all that was missing though
chatuchak chicha did you know the rumor
that's out there oh shit like you
know tabloids and such or i don't
know from the blue wall it might
be on dumas i'm what's the room
that martin short male stripper cutter yeah
yeah i love that i love to
watch the old news by now they're
probably out and know there was a
we're just out to dinner snapped by
the paparazzi i had heard about sharing
a single strand of spaghetti a couple
of months ago and in an alley
by nigerians i guess yeah yeah i
don't think they'd be a good kiss
you don't think that would be a
good guest half of a single strand
of spaghetti in between you i don't
your crazy lord or you don't think
you don't think martin short and meryl
streep would be a good kiss no
no no no yeah i think they
do great together yeah they must become
crazy they must be having so much
fun humor when martin short was on
regis and kathy
pilih and yeah kathy lee forgot that
his wife taught yeah so classy about
it he was he brought her love
yourself he she clashed just like how
is she doing how should i mean
he was like wow or or something
about she's great isn't she i think
it was just that for yeah yeah
your wife is so great isn't she
any comment yeah and then she pressed
it and was like
how she doing and he was like
well you know she passed away a
year and a half ago that's really
awkward and that's why she's only doing
commercials now i love those virtually yeah
she's doing commercials for like the vegetable
pills or whatever and then she's like
you mean peas
taking pills crack and snap teepees swallow
for peace with glass of water
good
in the commercial she's like looking through
photo albums and there's one with hoda
like a picture of hoda and her
having fun oh great like did you
get clear tonight
so ah what can i use your
image in the ad for vegetable a
la photo i love oh oh nah
we love oh hey love hada ho
to come on three days de nightfall
and chapo what are you doing if
if ho came on three damn it
would ruin what we have because we
would be so in awe not like
we would be just frauds immediately because
it would be exposed she's like an
actual conversation host conversationalist yeah why she
rebels thing had personalities personality yeah she
doesn't forget stories yeah i'm sure she
doesn't repeat them never told a story
twice no
well i actually have a ghost story
to tell you today oh holy shit
um oh if they are do a
drop yeah like the fire so i
was giving holy bath the other night
and she goes mommy there's a ghost
behind you
no that's not something you want to
hear never come a child no no
in front of you know um and
then i was like i said why
and it's me
if you're a ghost you'll be a
friendly ghost if you're in me yeah
oh you'd be so you'd be helpful
i would try to be you wouldn't
be just sitting there watching us jerk
off i mean there'd be a little
bit
to kill time well sometimes you're floating
around and you don't know what you're
going to see yeah and you don't
believe immediately do you think if your
goes to floating is fun or can
you not feel anything it might feel
actually really frustrating yeah i just feel
almost like i wish i could just
get down on the ground yeah
yeah stop drop and roll i feel
like it would feel like just not
satisfying like it's not a full step
yeah you wouldn't be able to dance
ghost can't dance i guess ne canada
on a mass scale yeah i guess
they do all the time yeah yeah
bill just dances like a crazy person
you love to eat that's just like
no one's watching in the broader production
i bet even more
yeah anything you don't have to bet
because i've seen it
can you see infirmary today that's right
i was with lauren bulbar oh i
heard about this yeah you were like
sucking her
for what like
anyway so sucking her kiss
yeah anthony kiedis so i said what
and then she was like there's it
goes by you and i was like
what like i like truly i looked
around i was like wow and i
just was like i would be so
terrified to turn around i didn't say
child so i turned to dripping wet
yeah when i asked her again
but and she said it again i
asked her again what
i'll put you again
then i looked around slowly slowly i
turned there was a ghost shaped soap
on my show chat has been on
a roll here for a year and
a half i got it for halloween
like oh you know with your own
soaps yeah you're absolutely sure somebody yeah
you go are you
around trick or treating people put soap
in your bag i just like don't
even think about it anymore but she
was her first time noticing it right
and then i was like oh yeah
i was so happy just gave it
to her and now it's in the
tub but i was like no it's
just a circle
almost ghost aliens yes like so relieved
that there was some physical thing yeah
looks like a ghost so that i
don't have to feel scared in my
own absolutely you should put up ghosts
all around the house so that she
does it to mike while she she's
his birthday card she drew ghosts in
it oh she likes goes yeah i
asked lauren yester
day and i'm so glad i asked
him marry you
yeah and he's so glad he's so
glad he asked me because i said
yes and he always wondered
i said that's all i know am
i going to do it will you
marry me it was a asteroid are
you going yeah yeah um i asked
lauren ah what did holly think about
mike's birthday because it was mike's birthday
yeah and i'm so glad i asked
yeah she thought it was her birthday
all day she said she also says
is when her birthday is but she
is like so sure birthday what point
did she learn what a birthday because
we we were talking about this yoga
day was it the second birthday did
she realize what it was now it's
really from going to parties so it's
kind of like the more i mean
it was definitely asked i feel like
maybe it was nothing to yeah and
like we went to had been to
enough
a birthday party for stuff like i
learned from parties that's what i just
said she has then they saying it's
all kind of regularly like you have
always some ok day it feels like
the fucking truth baby it is always
so happy god it's every day somebody's
every weekend boy like both days i
have to go to some
one's birthday every weekend so i don't
know first start for ten days the
more she hears the song what's on
it goes like this
huh yeah now i went to two
the other day one was a fairy
like one was ferries in the park
so sounds like it was a fairy
quest sales all the time and it
was it was the birthday child six
okay and so am whole was a
birthday job
how old was the day job wow
all day job it seems about six
years
but so let me just kinda like
watched but it was it was i
you know they the the the hosts
got their money's worth i will say
but i think it was a little
long for a ah it was an
hour like they they really wanted to
make sure they got to that hour
and i kind of feel like the
kids are losing tour like this could
have been twenty minutes
well on improv yeah it's telling kids
just going with twenty while we sang
happy birthday to my classes she went
it's daddy's birthday like we've been saying
it all day you drew on a
call yeah remember oh i kept telling
you go say happy birthday to him
ghosts sammy okay goes say
happy birthday him um
yeah that's the titlebar q it might
be because i make up the titles
this is lawrence bailey we wait did
that happen that you became the efficiency
yeah she's the official title list i'm
sorry to transfer when did that happen
she has responsibilities since we left since
we since we've been gone when was
this disgust i suppose ah scott begged
me to do front of him he
said he was too afraid out that
yes i know he bagged
me too because he was moving around
remember a single thing with creativity that's
not a garden oh that's not
he was really afraid to express his
creativity by making up the titles and
i was so right for summaries that
he begged me to do it and
you said you will not receive mormons
i was just kind of lets you
listen to a little song called roar
by katy perry because i think it
will help you discover some self-confidence okay
i i'll i'll try it can you
put it on he i'll try kidz
bop version okay
kidz bop i never i wanna say
this to the listener never doubt our
committee our commitment to kids plan first
we have an ad for something called
ugali know from the makers of kigali
we don't help them
here what do you think so far
how do you feel taking companies don't
feel confident yeah tom i'm holding my
breath yeah that's how i feel
yeah that's how i feel cry would
you do something with a bow and
make a messy yeah
i guess
actually did that epidemic plus i guess
well i don't remember i still remember
so i read did you fall for
everything man
some stupid is just describing how i'm
feeling right now home side given time
like everything's okay nope
okay forget it the songs oh yeah
i'm never have competent were gonna come
and you'll never hear him really
but if katy perry was just like
and that's it
i used to be like this and
now i still do i'm a loser
baie i watched a clip from american
idol rally recap which i don't watch
these days but um someone sent you
a clip no no the instagram so
you found shared a clip that i
thought oh click that yeah full-time say
because see someone saying well sure
or yeah why wouldn't i
it was marie okay it was amazing
it was beautiful rhythm they were happening
i'll go that might be the next
winner the wax away winner and maybe
the wicks oh my dad said that
way we always were two of the
songs she sang was a billie eilish
song called
the one from barbie the one for
barbie or additional ha i know shi
xing like a huge know she just
sang well well i made oh yeah
idea what is the worst clip on
an instagram like the worst audio clip
that people use a lot like i
think
it's like it's like i think i
like this little laugh says young i
likely see people making fun of it
i've seen real ones it's like people
holding their toddler and like doing something
that's like and that's from an actual
song i don't go oh i know
oh okay i don't know i don't
know yeah let me take a look
if someone called cordelia let's hear from
buffy the vampire slayer cordy
oh wait here we go
i'm not hearing what you're talking about
you can't hear the words i can
her ghost in the song they're just
repeating them over and over again hey
a
honestly i wasn't looking at i obviously
play let it play we have to
you have me
the sky light
la vie
louis she'll get her where she says
oh i know hearing said just
why does everyone seem like this new
waste yea no weighing it's waste why
we were wow why we do it
well why are you pointing me stories
very fucking pointing at me it is
like that now everyone's like oh i
want to be joy wow you broke
my
hawley
ah i guess i run on the
forty six
and i want everyone to know everything
okay i know we've moved past the
idea that everyone should sing this yeah
exactly exactly exactly well i'm sure i've
talked about this but i always wonder
how people find their singing voice in
that way it's like where you're like
oh that person is a successful singer
but they sound nothing like that
they talked nothing like that they do
they're like doing almost like an accent
yeah when did that get put on
a gomer pyle i don't know this
you don't know no like over bile
and the guy joe neighbors jim nabors
the most classic example of voice don't
match yeah singing voice ito hey talk
like me sarge what are you going
to do and then he would sing
like this works for music play don't
get away it sounds really good it's
that song let the music play shannon
as i was saying that song yeah
let it play okay okay we would
like to
i wanna hear the part of this
because i just want oh i want
you to fucking hear that are closer
i don't give two shits i think
i lie e o e o e
think i like this little noisy coy
decision life
that's my phrase if i ever have
to do an irish accent there you
go i think i look boy like
this guy for sh
god
stop it ah yeah a shrek shrek
shrek donkey she's never gonna say i
see this i think shrink sucks okay
i think he sucks you don't like
as a person i don't mean as
an ogre know he's great being an
ogre button i do think he's funny
he wasn't even like always an ogre
so it's kind of interesting it's like
it's kind of those things like you
should try things i don't give a
shit he's a nice person you know
what truck actually told try hard to
hate him check actually holds up and
just because you're dressed like him today
yeah wearing a sweater you have a
plan what does he wear a pla
had had nobody not good
you just have a shrek air about
you oh no this is bad news
for me
did you know that they did the
whole thing with chris farley yes they
did oh the whole i didn't watch
the whole thing the whole the whole
thing and then they were like now
let's throw it away no he passed
yes i don't think they did the
whole thing they did like three quarters
of it that much just guessing why
why do you think is going so
confidently because they weren't done
and they had to start over and
if they want to do four of
them they're gonna need somebody else why
didn't they get somebody who could do
a chris farley voice i don't know
what i would like to hear that
filled by the river
that's how you detract oh god doggie
what are you looking if you're looking
oh you did about eighty five percent
eat my shit while you said three-quarters
i said seventy five and you said
i'm you're making that up there's no
way how come and they wouldn't just
didn't get it right well i was
close doesn't remember i said he probably
did eighty five percent no
you did don't lie to us all
you're under oath have you been able
to move on he did about eighty
five percent about eighty five hours out
so eighty four percent yeah we don't
know we can't get the exact facts
and figures we won't know is that
where we won't know until we go
to heaven i know and then it's
the first thing they tell you and
we'll just see all the sessions chris
father did eighty six percent shrink i
think there is an s l sketch
that was all about that which i
found very fast about like someone dying
and then saint peter like taking them
through oh is dana carvey kevin o'neill
yeah yeah like what's the eighth most
disgusting thing that was a very atypical
sketch yeah because it was very quiet
yeah but
it was really fun it was like
how many bugs have i swallowed in
my eye for something like that yeah
he's like what's the grossest thing ever
and he's like like i can't tell
you that you're right you'll lose your
mind right like it was like the
thousandth and one grossest thing right yeah
it was really it was funny good
yeah it was funny it was really
strange performance by karvy though
like of which we have rarely seen
they're great lauren king if you could
if you could star as either hons
or france which one would use my
god i hate this question oh wow
so basically i think of them as
being the same oh come on what
what are you talking about hunter wrongs
are talking
one is han's and was i would
be huns the taller one yeah that
seems right yeah yeah just based on
odds i'm sure whoever i'd be paranoid
look probably be shorter than me you're
either a hands reference which i am
i'm more of a france i think
wow definitely a hands yeah keeping hands
right now
tom season giving huns um we have
to take a break speaking in giving
ho high but when we come back
we'll have an exciting new story to
tell you
why would you say oh we gotta
go live some life okay we'll be
back in a week five
now we're back although
did you know you did doe doe
um i gotta to do that you
know how ah last week or the
week before we were talking about our
friend eggo yeah yeah um and this
remind we got a lot of letters
yeah oh my just loving it just
saying like thanks for mentioning her yeah
please talk about her more that was
um but now i
the other day and it reminded me
of this thing we read up about
you um that was actually right on
the money god i know that guy
predicted my pregnancy yeah but remember we
really read like a weird article that
was like like an ai added to
like no i think it was like
an ai article maybe i don't know
why maybe it was like all right
all right and yeah people people ask
this about lauren
yeah he's shit what does your break
okay so here's one and they said
i was gonna have baby and twenty
twenty three and i was like no
which i didn't do but i did
get pregnant yeah here's one is eggo
woden pregnant a comprehensive exploration of clue
huh and fans eager anticipation of the
snl star's personal joyous news that's so
psychotic
is aigo odom pregnant a go whoa
i'm born in baltimore maryland whoa so
nice of you is knowing you walk
through the garden is a notable figure
in the entertainment world with her nigerian
background she brings a rich cultural mix
to her work so true woden completed
her studies at the university of southern
california earning a degree in ba
biology and showcasing her diverse skills than
a lot of like ah blah blah
blah about her career um alright and
then after the career no aygo odom
is not having a baby why did
you write the article she hasn't said
anything about being pregnant so it's not
clear if she's going to have a
baby or not i mean yeah right
i mean you could leave your spot
anything at all here's why the talk
about agawam being pregnant started when she
shared photos on her instagram people started
saying she wasn't pregnant people started talking
and guessing about it because of these
pictures of bo and yang's husband what
they're saying that she's with bowen yang
oh my gosh since william has
an officially said anything about being pregnant
those rumors are just guesses based on
how people interpret the photos cool when
they show this picture of her and
beau and i do think like ninety
percent of the internet should be deleted
so if i'm if i'm reading this
correctly yeah so because of pictures of
bowen yang's husband people are asking if
eggo is pregnant there's no it's translated
already
and they show this picture of her
and bowen together and they're in like
whoa tim is sharing her love story
with her future husband bo and yeah
oh for future us but they're not
just dating they are engaged the couple
even posted pictures on their social media
showing off their engagement ratios they wait
to think i've been a couple for
a long time supporting each other every
step of the way
it seems like they might be planning
to get married soon and their friends
and fans are excited to hear more
about it yeah that's true i'm excited
to hear more i'm thrilled there's way
more i don't need it
in case you're wondering a little more
okay fine doom two more or two
more whites simpler words pages words words
words words um eggo and bowen are
an interracial couple has mentioned in her
hashtag
ah in one picture they are sitting
on a couch holding hands bowen has
a paper bracelet with the date two
three twenty one written on it and
blue letters the photo was a fun
moment after bowen to three twenty one
written on it in blue letters could
mean can you put that together that
going to be twenty one written in
blue letters was which the numbers
are spelled out
t w o o here's how it
all started the photo was a fun
moment after bowen jokingly proposed to her
on snl by going down on one
knee bow and also shared a picture
saying announcements i'm straight now this is
my girlfriend alongside a photo of him
holding hands as the person writing this
was like that's all true yeah
that's great yeah anyway congrats i love
journalism but but the one that we
read about you was actually true everything
they said was true yeah yeah so
some say you are married to my
passes yeah so i think that this
must be true i sent it to
eggo and she just sent of gif
of her nervously pulling her
collar going oh so it might be
true she self gift yeah it's a
power move i like yeah it was
her pulling her color
i think she was pulling someone else's
color actually she is interesting someone else
someone was nervous near her and he
couldn't pull their color yes so she
she's always helpful she kindly did it
for the yeah exactly would you mind
pulling the leg death kindly stopped for
me
writing a poem i was remembering did
you have you ever written a poem
oh my god yeah i've wrote ah
i wrote poems and song lyrics when
i was in high school really yes
and i had to i said i
had to know what out and i
cannot imagine i still have the you
still have the book
i would be the notebook to i
would swear i think i would cringe
to death if i were to read
can you yeah them next week or
the week after i can't promise anything
i can't promise anything know am i
my home was one of my poems
was published in a in a collection
of student poetry across america
across america okay okay so when you
read student poetry do you give it
like more of a pass like you
have to yeah yeah it's all about
i remember when my favorite student poem
no more pencils no more books no
more wrote a poem about the glass
menagerie or like inspired by the glass
menagerie wagon answer playing fanfic um
no i don't know if it was
an english assignment or if i just
showed it to my english teacher but
she loved it and she used as
an example for years to come she's
like wow how when did she stop
which was she liked boys shelf life
opens you know i only know about
it happening for like one to two
years so i really don't know who's
one to two years one to two
years she's
this woman who will do anything he
wants for two years stay here and
then she starts you off it's a
contract and it's a docusign and it's
like a whole thing i love junkies
kentucky says that but one of the
best things ever it's really great you
could do for your phone now it
feels like it's gotten better what are
some of the best some of the
bay
best inventions docusign oh my god adobe
acrobat yeah
final draft of the make you buy
a new one anytime someone else had
or so fell hyped on this new
final draft why do they make you
buy it every time yeah you can't
update the app like it's the software
it just it's it's actually criminal yeah
it's criminal if i'm working my friend
who is um like no it should
still work for you the one that
you bought
collab unless you'd be able to ne
and you meet all the new features
on the new version you literally can't
sync up you cannot have the person
collab on there with you who used
to be able to before it's i
don't think you always have had to
have the same exact model and then
you have to buy another one and
it's like hundreds of dollars that's bullshit
it's bullshit it's it's
like my word like i'm just like
make on your screenplays like a million
tree million
it's a great investment wow i got
into it with the the whoever's in
charge of the dictionary app this was
the ah you got into it with
them yeah dictionary has gotten worse there
wasn't lookup the word i have fucking
cunt and that is yeah oh my
are you talking to paul my god
lauren
lauren is in a mood today
right always thinking about this kid who
listen to us now and i'm like
i gotta bleep that
just another thing we've talked about in
front of me
well there's kids who listen to the
show like kids turn the shit off
if you're a kid listening to this
well let me tell you about something
called toffee fe okay this was a
candy that was too good for kids
i don't know what this is oh
so that's basically three minutes tough it's
a little round hazelnut cup i think
i'm allergic nasal north a little chocolate
wrist on the top how little
wow desk new phone who disc
maybe point oh i'm getting itchy mouth
when i eat hazelnut and oh so
i'm like i think i'm out girls
can't do anything new and that smell
in that centricity like scratch your mouth
i have my dog scratch my mouth
yeah that makes it go away don't
make sense because they're great but we're
gonna say
we'll tell it to first finish about
this candy anyway their ad campaign was
yeah tough fi fe it's too good
for kids to off he fe is
too good and no one because it
was a more adult kind of candy
yeah i you know i remember certain
candies that that parents used to like
that i would
just be like ah that's it's too
specific yeah was it always just like
coffee flavor this coffee or tea or
coffee was coffee flavored okay it's toffee
flavored but but as a kid did
you like toffee
yeah is it supposed be like pig
latin was it sweet i liked it
toffee fe what would that be fate
off
for me so as a kid though
digit make you want to eat it
of course it did i know and
maybe fruit no one ever let you
know shopkeepers would say ah re let
me see your id son you know
i always thought was the grossest was
sparkling water i still don't like spark
nice
it does i was a kid i
was like oh no i don't believe
in my thirsty slate i have googled
it and it does quencher theories i
know but just don't feel like i
don't hide duration is different than quenching
your thirst know but it is hydrating
yeah that's best i'm saying huh
but we may hydrate but it's but
it's not quenching your thirst yeah not
like it's like i'm gargling with salt
water quenches your thirst what's the the
water wrenching no but the brand of
soda the thirst quencher you know they'd
be like yeah it's just that is
something quest your thirst quenched your thirst
the thirst quencher is wasn't nice
phantom gatorade oh gator aid the classic
thirst quencher lead that would quench it
yeah yeah inches and hydrates you to
read they know what they're doing and
who's not an ad we gotta know
why so late on this but the
recent tisa tick tock two part tick
tock i don't know what this is
like oh
about this woman it's a woman talking
to the camera on tick topics do
you watch me in photo two parts
no i literally watched them all within
two days and i did start doing
double screens i was like i can't
she did it was eight hours there's
more than eight hours it's a tiktok
series were made about her past her
husband ex-husband was a pathological liar called
who the fuck did i marry
and so she's like who the fuck
did i marry part seven so okay
so did it into that and she's
like telling you this whole story and
in chronological order and in really excruciating
detail yeah yeah yeah like there's like
and then we woke up and we
went to the store it's like you
know you're literally like what did details
are oh no they're good yeah and
then by the end there's just one
part that i just thought from
what you said where shit stars he's
a pathological liar he ain't right yeah
he lies about everything he said guidry
doesn't throw kids your third isn't it
doesn't fix a quench
a he
he has this like sort of i
don't know what happens to me like
hurts his knee and he can't get
out of bed and he's like losing
weight rapidly it's it's a very odd
sort of like downfall irish i have
this whatever it is yeah good dad
right i break your knee and i
mean she goes into bed she finally
goes into the ring lose weight i
won't give away anything about it that's
happening around that case people do care
it's also been months probably since this
has happened but she um finds that
he's been like pissing and gatorade and
powerade bottles like he's like only drinking
power he's not eating food things are
that wing in it i was not
in the room and she's just going
on and then he has since released
his own or no hello but everyone's
like why are you putting your face
on camera yeah so you are she
doesn't use his name choosing a theater
name right it's yeah i bet like
the the hundred people who knew that
he was married to her yeah like
you pee in bottles yeah
and so he made up a whole
thing that she cheated on him but
he's such a i want to take
away ah and then his ex was
appealed so she cheated on me and
oh he was a cheater
oh but i thought you said he
said he caught her she told you
why their relationship ended oh and she's
like looks up your world like this
wasn't sitting for me the lies are
out of this world though have you
known pathological liars i've supposedly but yeah
um i think that i have yeah
i have but i don't i don't
know i knew that were lying i
know a guy
to just he refused to admit he
had all these stories that if you
asked any followup question he didn't have
answer for it and it was like
just admit this is not right yeah
that's always just you and me here
what is the peeing in bottles thing
like you know how tina fey talks
about like comedy writers lp and bottles
i think that's specific to her friends
i really have never heard of people
doing i heard that about a beloved
snl cast member used to piss in
jars leaving in the office and then
the assistant would have to take so
it's just an s and l thing
because they have failed psychotic your psychotic
and they're meant to they also are
like compelled to stay there all night
yeah for some reason yeah
no it's like a cult mentality yeah
led by a weirdo i'm trying to
think if i've ever pissed in anything
other than a toilet on my mouth
he says
ah i guess a shower
yeah i guess a show never you
never just outside oh i pissed out
so yeah are you a guy so
outside a toilet one of the hour
and the bird not pissed i didn't
never i was always ancient i've had
to pee outside like for various reasons
i'm i must have pissed in
one bottle on a road trip i'm
sure you did you must have must
have and then a diaper when i
was really young
like one day old to maybe about
like me the other day i see
what lesson
room
don't know what i was doing in
there i guess my pisses all over
the policy that time for me is
is like very hazy yeah yeah i
don't remember much of it yeah so
what does your url do you have
an earliest memory and then i wanna
get back to dictionary dot com i
remember coming out of the womb and
being like it's a way to get
bright in here everybody
and then there were six more weeks
winner
oh you want to go back in
yeah lorem
huh
two thousand a dictionary dot com you
got into oh hey yeah so what
did you do about that so this
was i'm trying to remember what what
you told the registers it was not
the oxford it was it was the
dictionary app and i really loved it
no dictionary dot com slash the source
dot com has gotten terrible now yeah
and if their response or i apologize
has gotten terrible but
you know it's like the the source
dot com used to just move debris
there's like half of the words it's
just the shrug emoji there's like we're
not sure you figure it out try
to use it in contact know now
they only they only list a few
and they're like do you want to
read more yeah this was the ah
america
can heritage dictionary song yeah it was
a great dictionary heritage foundation and then
they rate they updated it and then
they made they tried to charge you
again for it charging okay oh it's
it was an app that you bought
yeah and they're like tapes might again
yeah it's like well if if the
physical dictionaries updated you'd have to buy
it again i'm like yeah but i
don't
but i wouldn't have to you making
people i would keep my airway were
charging full price for it right oh
no how much was added like riz
or whatever is it oh yes like
microsoft word now you have to have
a subscription
holy fuck man microsoft word i'm gonna
say this on on my call man
romelu last remember who i am when
i go to use your app listen
microsoft workshop for getting me and asked
me if i want to sign off
hundred and sixty dollars for how long
for a year um i don't know
that's too much for
microsoft word or you can get it
for a one week free trial for
a month and you get it for
a one time fee of eighty dollars
i don't know there's there's different i
know facts and figures out here but
i just think it should be free
with your phone or computer i think
so anyway used to be wasn't a
free way to buy like a pack
pages easy like microsoft office
yes yeah yeah yeah yeah where he
had all those pages pages j time
pages isn't worth yeah all the features
would you love the feature so much
pay for them i don't want it
at all i use google word do
you wish that you had microsoft but
all the things we're in a different
place yeah get pages
pages is just like nothing pages pages
pages is fine and it converts to
word it dude
pages dirt on the site and how
did you so you got into it
and what happened and the guy was
like move all right who is a
guy i had to talk to a
guy to talk to an actual yes
yeah yeah yeah see like little tiny
glasses who is like the face of
the dictionary fuck yeah poindexter look at
other exactly i stood over and was
like oh
he nice to me i think you've
given it to me for free and
was like wow right
but yeah the guy had the guy
admitted he did it oh my god
oh my god the guy admitted yet
um yeah i guess that you have
a point that it's stupid you know
we we yeah we didn't print a
copy of the dictionary then now you
have to buy new version right and
then eventually it it stopped working there
were like no we're
cracking down on these people really yeah
so many things i think that you
should when you're born you should pay
a bunch of money and then you
get everything for free the rest of
your life that make sense to me
yeah how much
like
yeah considering that all the stuff you'll
have to pay for
you know whoa with inflation or biden
relation rather um
like three million dollars so everybody this
is a one-time onetime three million dollar
fee and then get food shelter yeah
but it's a good house or what
like yeah you get everything yeah yeah
and everyone's houses exactly the same and
everyone gets the same amount of toilet
paper stuck maybe i'm a communist i'm
not good at it
everyone gets the same mosul whomever for
your life that can't be good yeah
but why did you why did you
just say this sucks in the middle
of
he is really like what you are
talking about oh yes i thought you
were looking at something you were saying
this sucks no i was trying to
find the ah the dictionary but it's
not there anymore so they just erased
it they say they took it from
you i think they went out of
business now i'm looking in the store
they went out of business i guess
which question everyone on business american heritage
was american hipster i don't understand why
that
costs any money a dictionary dictionary app
i can google any word i want
well that's true can you that's yeah
i like i like having the app
try to google one right now okay
but look
yeah can't find that in the dictionary
okay who is bill but liquor
and do izzy he's a character voiced
by jim halpert during the episode of
customer survey on the office i guess
i kind of thing that episode this
is a crossover episode by the way
with office lady wait on a network
sitcom had a character yeah named bill
but liquor yeah it's like a character
joe who is still on the phone
going like oh yeah
yeah that's i think it's funny that
america of course television
alright we have to take a break
and we're back we're back three your
time i'm so excited i'm so excited
and i just can't hide it i'm
about to lose control i love my
caffeine pills i love my caffeine bills
it's like kathy lees yeah
so look for little pigs yeah they
play it with me for coffee beans
i took my energy water shit so
kills her
um guys it's three your time yes
this three times when we play a
parlor game and if you would like
to send this three-tier write to us
at three m usa gmail dot com
yes and we thank you for your
submissions and for your service assuming you've
been in the armed forces and um
this is five second rule i
don't know if we played this version
of it but this was submitted by
tamer
maybe it's all mysterious i don't know
anything tamer yeah um and the object
of this is to name three things
in five seconds so i assume we
go clockwise oh and um the ah
person says ah name three famous jennifer's
and then the next
person has five seconds to answer three
famous jennifer's um if they succeed they
get a point if they fail the
next player gets a chance to answer
but can't use any of these ones
the first wrinkles heard recall it's ah
chieh madeleine l'engle
yes and you keep alternating until someone
wins a point i love those books
when i was a kid which ones
wrinkle and talents i haven't ran an
hour one or those one i remember
being trippy then i saw them today
this free trip isn't the right colin
time-worn i guess i should see zach
galifianakis your coworker is to that movie
looked a little too theme park seems
random
and that hasten it is yeah he
gave me a free blue
as a punishment
putting him in yes you put him
in it no um okay so five
second rule i play second but i
go oh wow
um let's not try to get too
hard with each other let's ease into
this what do you say i agree
what happened last time here i don't
know dramatize know that's saying we we
were really challenging to each other and
it devolved into a lot of tears
to the lord of the flies type
of situation yeah yeah it's both were
crying we murdered someone calling me piggy
okay it happens in that right yeah
yeah yeah someone gets called piggy yeah
yeah yeah for sure to anyone it's
like a big part of it it's
like kind of the whole he's the
voice of reason they murder him
no yeah he has glasses yeah those
glasses may break his glasses he's fattening
his glasses yes and then they murder
him yes
so that's a bad sense of events
i agree let's be cut off his
head what did we talk about this
on this show that i don't know
gene siskel had a problem with one
of his problems with the movie the
lord of the flies was that the
book the lord of the flies didn't
exist in the movie was so everything
has said that so that it's like
i
i think the plaza exist in the
book maybe it was a yeah i
get the kids are guys like lord
of the flies
because maybe it was a virtuous modern
version might have been a modern version
and he for some reason was like
you how can you not acknowledge the
book lord of the flies i mean
it's like what does he not get
about it it's a lot like like
if you're watching a batman movie and
you're like why don't they just like
those movies about batman
yeah or why you'll it's it's a
world where like in nineteen eighty nine
no one was excited about going to
see batman that's what i think they
should do in godzilla movies i've said
this online i think that godzilla now
they should say they should reference godzilla
movies right yeah hey easy it's vampire
movies that never mentioned dracula like where
they're all like whoa whoa
what is this he's right happily mixing
this one well yeah when there i
don't have a problem with that he
used to bother me then i understood
why they did it like zombies like
when there wasn't say the word zombie
oh i know they say walker well
yeah and it was like oh because
they're trying to they're creating their own
universe where this is the first instance
of this happening oh yeah
yeah but where we live in a
society we live in ah we'd live
in a society as have you seen
somebody won't say maybe just talked about
it it's the videos of gene siskel
and yeah keeper like fighting it's so
good so funny it's so good highly
recommend googling that okay i read there
the
a book about them recently the you
read it to them i read to
them into their grave sites separately while
they are buried side-by-side yes read out
loud they might eat with their thumbs
pointing up yeah their wives are pissed
um okay so are you guys ready
i'll start i'm ready i'll give palsy
i'm just very quickly and i'll look
at this later but i'm looking up
ah did gene siskel actually say that
about lord of the flies great because
what if i'm wrong what if you're
what if you're what if we one
time said something that wasn't true
now this is hard because you have
to name three things but you also
have to think of a separate thing
to give to the other person right
yeah but we can pause after you
get it okay but thinking of things
is the heart the evenings is the
hardest yeah we could we could well
i don't know what i don't know
how to fix this right here yeah
ready i'm going to paul as paulist
to my left yes clockwise classic um
paul name three
comic strips ah lil abner gasoline alley
drabble great so what's lauren know to
have name three types of hat
popper joker
huh what the fuck
joker fools the first popper popper apa
you got what what is that and
joker is you mean gesture
hopper
hopper okay it goes to me i'm
gonna gray it just to be okay
but can we check it what is
a popper
i think you mean like a portfolio
like good news
i guess it goes like well i
don't want to give ideas alright bowler
stovepipe newsy cap wow okay good point
okay now i think joker
does it because i got it do
i go to the ga or just
uncle fester ah mccovey tester
i think lauren has to i want
to do where to me okay okay
yet another upper she sure you name
three types of headache medication aleve advil
tylenol you dice okay paul
ah name three things you would find
in a tool shed ah hammer bench
ranch ranch ranch dressing
lubricate your car
lauren yeah name three models of car
models five seconds oh subaru folks like
those aren't models are not really okay
but bird those are yeah there you
go oh i see t bird
jeddah okay whoa is jenna model yes
um
escort here you go maybe five seconds
but we're being nice sure alright now
you to me
no you no you to me name
three carnival rides ferris wheel ah the
roller coaster and the swings thing hey
that didn't feel good america around
does this swing thing called zia swings
i mean i know the knott's berry
farm one is the dragon swing so
i want to do it yeah but
i felt weird beings that specific love
that ride the swings i hate when
it just swings like in this the
air yea do like so nervous right
now i really liked it a lot
why don't you go on there was
a player
a place called west point park um
i can't remember how far it was
from where i lived but it was
like you know between half a mile
and three hundred miles something like that
and it was like a crappy indie
amusement park you know but they had
yeah
indiana jones you read it um
but they had um there was like
a big sort of like pond like
a huge pond that was ah you
go over it on the swells wow
and it was very exciting yeah let's
seem scare out that's what made it
exciting yeah danger is deciding yeah i
remember going into this excited very dangerous
when i was a kid going to
what does
zipper what does the zipper exactly like
you're in a cage and they like
flip around like the cages like flipper
oh i thought they were called the
salt we call them the salt and
pepper shakers oh yeah but i want
i famously was my park went on
that with my older brother and i
was too small to get on the
ride but they let me on anyway
and so i wasn't really secure
moored and oh no so it was
just like oh no back area or
it was horrible yeah i remember being
really scared because you'd fall like face
first into the cage part like your
seatbelt today and but like you have
your hands on it like yeah every
time it goes forward it's like it
could just pop open i remember magic
mountain i went on something where it
was like your it spins around
round in a circle and the centrifugal
forces such that they then lower the
floor and you're just stuck oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah and the the thing
was they would always tell you like
oh yeah if you puke on this
by the way it'll just come back
right in your eyes gonna say like
you always see those things if puke
just like flying to the silent flying
back or something in that yeah i
was on one of those as an
and i will try to take a
picture as it was started last long
and yeah i got yelled at by
the right operator really wow because your
pictures your younger could bridge supposed to
just be standing permit yeah yeah it's
just to have like items out because
because because it can fly yeah right
but like got over a loudspeaker and
i was so ashamed mortified but i
one time remember being on that
pirate ride the ship where it just
like five touch and then get caught
on fire so we were like caught
on fire like there was like a
fire and then we were like something
like an api up fired upon it
ah probably yeah can't enter something and
um we were stuck like halfway floating
then we always like come off of
it like
carefully but it was like so crazy
jesus yeah okay okay ready to name
all right paul name three
synonyms for sad
ah blue but down in the dumps
ah in my fields
lauren yes name three non comedy podcasts
the dollop
i'm kind of i don't know what
that is
this american life
this american life yeah um the daily
um um ooh i don't think they're
hardy
okay the new york times to me
they have one
yeah i got it um springsteen at
obama's ah does not name me it's
not as easy as you think as
you were scolding me i didn't scold
you know your eyes are dead we
did ice-cold yeah yes
i was just trying to like
um god what's a podcast i know
serial you're wrong about um okay well
you made up the category so obviously
you're gonna know
made up
i don't know neither of us gets
a point no great you can ah
i can call me oh yeah name
three
um
name three
numbers that are not three
ah three name three places you find
a fire that would make sense that
you would find a fire as obviously
yeah the stove a beach um a
building that's on fire
makes sense
thanks good point i feel like it
it fits it must acquit
um paul name three celebrity trials o
o j simpson fatty arbuckle gwyneth paltrow
yeah well what happened with eddy arbuckle
oh look it up same here
i know you're a fan of lauren
name three nicknames for edward ed ted
ted word
i mean it's technically if you call
shore
ah what would have accepted eddie okay
good to know for next time um
name three desktop apps of your computer
on my computer he can't do this
page's obsessive fahri i-tunes wow
these pages that he's paid leave it
is just we already talking about it
that's why you want paige davis on
the show yeah i love her
and stephen page yes from bernardino ladies
and jimmy page from led zeppelin god
the three of them collaborating three pages
with they could
you know what why would hitler because
collaborators get in there oh i see
yeah i see um alright ah name
three people that were born before nineteen
hundred
charles dickens jesus the christ abraham link
cone you got em chow all three
of them thank you you named the
three lorry name three people born after
ikea dr michael jackson
o j simpson o quit
keto can
ah um okay i just had one
when we oh yeah name three branches
of real housewives ah new york orange
county beverly hills hey nice name to
anymore
ah potomac ah atlanta and ah new
jersey yeah oh hey my name one
more dc that was brief salt lake
city we have that their students that
this is too many name one more
no i mean now we just think
chicago don't know miami that's the last
one my answer scott
it's the last was name the last
one say it miami did it okay
would you like to go with me
to miami
i was eugene
oh name three famous eugene's oh eugene
v debs i'm gonna say eugene cordero
and i think it counts and i'm
gonna say eugene oregon yeah that's famous
yeah alright ah we have two more
you have paul you get to do
one and learn you doing
huh i'm ready cheese just saying three
types of cough drop luxury brands lutens
halls and um rico la yea oh
alright last one to me name three
tissue brands kleenex
ah yeah all chance to steal we
are tied ah scott
kind of embarrassing and get that wow
yeah shame on me the puffs yeah
um
it's toilet tissue but sharman
you just said tissue okay i think
we all knew what i meant but
you can have it you can have
it and paul you're the winner
seven points i want the game with
seven point yea i feel great i'm
on top of the world again what
did i get for thanks if you
would like to send us a three
year three muse age gmail dot com
and if you would like to call
us leave a voicemail give us a
little prompt for a conversation um you
call us at the website
the famous calling website hag claims eight
and if you want a dot com
dot com sorry
ah sorry dot u k we have
not yet figured it out um and
if you like your ad-free versions of
the show sign up at cb world
dot com and thank you to la
nada for hosting us and also apple
podcasts premiums where you get this oh
okay yeah i've done not aware that
that's a thing i didn't we keep
talking about is just what i've been
told it's
like or or it's lemonade is apple
i don't know what it is eliminates
i believe never given us just what
it is but you can hear those
summer um ah the oh no no
not ad-free episodes the three meme is
what i'm talking about oh okay then
it's not not what i was talking
about so paul i apologize and i'm
mad enough to admit it yeah when
i was all guys i appall a
y'all i like ah but the three
meme stuff isn't cvb world and whatever
the lemonade apple podcasts yeah three meme
is where we discuss your voicemails yes
and we release the old episodes every
tuesday that we call that three visiting
on the twos which is fun it's
so fun and i want to thank
my
beloved cohosts
from it's happening doing another episode this
is my final one oh my god
scott steps down from three typically still
use your house yeah you could just
move okay oh that seems like more
work than i want and did you
hire someone to replace yourself ah yeah
it's covering your own shift right yeah
yeah so i've hired you to replace
me okay and then you have to
reply
plus yourself god damn it should i
do your part yeah why don't you
replace me now you have to find
someone to cover your shift okay maybe
i could place you ah can just
one of your dogs available ah with
love okay that works alright we'll see
you next time bye hey