three
hi
dying
oh
i made it a question hi hello
what song is that oh that's funny
gabriel oh you know i thought it
was from alma alma away yeah yeah
big time i thought was from either
always been my baby right let's always
be my word oh hey maybe have
you watched that movie the alley i
really enjoyed my god it's so good
i haven't watched it but very good
deal less commonly in there
it's like high there's a brother that
did that
pippin no she's doing exactly what is
oh really
oh you memorized it yeah i did
hi welcome to three adam i'm scott
hi welcome to three am i'm paul
hi welcome to three-time my name is
lauren que la q for q and
on
i'm q your gilman to this whole
okay guys everybody learns j f k
junior i have a lot of confessions
this is your conversion you'd only be
dictated to another
cynosure song ah i love a sher
whose nature nurture it's it's a nutter
song it's an easy it's another ushers
i'm not sure what really say for
sure why let's time it how long
it takes to say another bush song
vs nudgers usher
alright here we go again the old
timer ready are you going to remember
to time bullet time isn't dear
yes sweetie pie right
lauren you wanna start yeah so we'll
start with
sure song okay three to one another
usher song one second one second on
the dot wow it took me a
long time
or watch this reset and now an
usher song i went to three two
i'm gonna joke three two one i'm
not sure saying it's point seventy six
was eight point seven six interesting sales
do you think you could beat that
i'm going to try yeah we're trying
here we go three two one another
usher song wow
my head was like hey kid lap
well you have another chance that's another
interesting when you hit cool up
do you call her lap
i caught both the two laps to
wow last lap
three to one another usher song was
two point zero two sec whoa not
really making a meal of it okay
okay now i'm actually set three to
one a nutshell song
again
damn oh my three to what a
nurse your song point sixty three yeah
it's really fast you want to be
timed yeah i would like to be
oh now i remember tony lap
huh what does lap even do oh
go what do you think it does
dorner
for a year through your brain into
the fires door door
okay everyone gets you know you're saying
first another usher song yes okay that
was not official and here we go
and go on
and don't tell me i'm gonna three
to one for the cow doe sorry
okay i was timing and go okay
three to one another usher song point
nine five second point nine five wow
you're gonna say an usher song three
to one an usher song
i started even a little late i
was point six eight you you definitely
beat it by a lot yeah but
did you beat my six three a
lot of time ah yes oh okay
great
technically you did thank you for asking
i'm gonna read the text message that
follows
yeah we got a wonderful text message
today ah i have hit really sweet
i hit some traffic and will probably
actually i'm gonna read it how it
actually please okay reviewers first okay i
said i'll be there closer to one
forty scott gave better thumbs up so
now you know what time we
yeah enjoy yourself you freak it's later
than you think you freaks next time
it hits one thirty thinking about us
recording oh and then paul said i
have hit some traffic and will be
there probably a little after one forty
you fucking asshole
the last part was for a guy
who just cut me off
as you're dictating it right addicted and
some traffic will be there for one
forty you fucking ass
yeah and i read it and kind
of thought oh i deserved that oh
it's very telling harder next time
harder daddy
your freedom daddy this has ever happened
to me before but it happens to
nicole parker my friend nicole parker a
lot that she told me a text
and then start stalking somebody in traffic
so what happened in traffic tell us
about this effing a whole
left a real impression i'm sure it
was a man we're trying to do
this for kids now um i was
on a very busy street called los
feliz blvd oh yeah that one i
heard of it i got on to
a bad juncture and that was on
me and so what happens is it's
three landed and narrow sure to
another juncture wouldn't be prudent it narrows
from three lanes to two lanes and
then of course there's all the people
in the fucking third outside lane like
oh can you let me yield to
those guys sucks you know eataly you're
talking about that little lane where there's
always cars parked but then you can
go a long way exact cars pop
exactly and so i let someone in
of course because
you can look good let somebody in
a little further on as the traffics
are moving in another guy just came
up and swooped in in front of
me that's sure it's solely it's totally
biggish yeah i saw i'm trying to
do it and so i edged up
a little bit and you were hedging
that's how i drive you're always drive
always so i think alert yeah that'll
keep you focused
on the wrong thing for bo you
really enjoy
so yeah he swooped in this weekend
fucking sas or what oh for sure
i'm late you should have rammed his
car
i should've i should've i should've declared
ramming speed and then random cramming speed
dresses we should wear a robot lauren
from your lips to god's ears ramming
speed engage ramming speed
intruder detected that's what i say when
somebody gets to my lane that's the
way the janie found out you're a
robot jamie found you gonna come right
out oh no
i do like my song what if
that's the way jay found out your
room
she's been married you for now how
would how many years now eleven years
eleven years i skipped coven we should
have to yeah you shouldn't to god
if only i'd skipped it out yeah
the first year of coven was our
tenth anniversary was no excuse is coming
it'll be twelve this year twelve wow
wow yeah wow
wow so she's just another seven years
ago until now until we split up
we had a we put a clock
on this yeah let's say you were
like nineteen and done we were like
i don't wanna get divorced you know
out of acrimony let's just decide we'll
do it before it gets bad there
should be like illegal thing where you
like an enrollment yeah where you can
get out safely get out don't know
when asked to pay anyone anything i'd
be nice
a no fault divorce too bad we
live in california oh too bad yeah
i agree horrible here it's the worst
don't come none of you ever full
every everything you're thinking you're right so
stay away yeah yeah we're all full
up yeah do you guys dictate your
text in the car one and be
prudent um hey i
i do you know what i've just
gotten into some boys texts oh wow
tell us about this okay because this
part of lawrence topic i remember when
i got into it it was like
i heard people talking about yeah i
gotta get into i read people talking
about it when they said dictated by
siri um but i didn't want to
do it the siri phone i didn't
want to talk to him but i
now have been doing it and i'll
tell you what what i use more
than siri is that voice key pad
yes feature know what this is it's
in the bottom right you know what
it's very helpful sometimes sometimes we'll be
texting with lauren on a separate thread
yeah we have a lot of time
and things to discuss but it's about
you
it's all we ever talk about
but it's so extensive and how am
i doing draining yeah you do it
you're doing better than yeah tell positive
oh zappos oh great okay scott scott
was great on three of today yeah
there's a lot of that just listened
got to say scott was the star
once again i'll never tell him
but we but lauren ah so i'm
sorry it's like all the things that
i know you're not going to be
interested in this is oh yeah why
don't you do that on the main
threesome thread please you be interested in
you do it more
but you always start thinking about that
when i talk about marvel stuff but
i don't bother lauren with that sure
yeah why would you yeah exactly um
why i bother us mainland gossip i
go so i wanna know gossip but
says the only thing i wanna know
that last one i was very surprised
you addressed only to me well i
was i was
is walking a fine line i'm gonna
bring it up to you just the
other day yeah i'll bring it up
later i want to know why i
was afraid to texted you'll see why
okay it's not for air by the
way it's stacia are certainly not going
to be going additionally tantalized listeners and
also are too scared for us o
god but in any case um so
she sometimes when
it's like he's looking for someone who's
like every time he's like versa online
i look out there helicopter shoe charm
now that's right she's still looking for
someone still looking for samurai still looking
for someone he's still helicopter god is
looking for us maybe oh hovering right
there
you can follow up with a claw
or who hit an arcade game
levy what does that have me fun
i'd like to find that i just
wanted enough times to them due to
me just like you guys shrug like
they got me
so if it's true like you're texting
about a topic and then it's you
just have too much to say it's
like what's the point of writing all
this down i know i know a
little thing you do a little thingy
and you like some people i think
do voice memos a lot i would
do videos a lot instead of texts
i would like turn the camera around
video that makes the whole video even
just like a sense of like yeah
okay and then so i don't drag
that marco polo bullshit into my tech
wow marco polo dad on the ah
um yeah you know i do like
when some people will voice text me
voice memo me because it feels like
oh i feel like we're kind of
cheating but i don't really like to
do it back that often only with
certain people yeah so there's some people
i don't feel the freedom to just
start phrase um you know sweet um
freedom i won't let you down
do not leave you to think do
you like george michael lauren or did
that pass like you're one of those
and don't really care what you're a
homophobe he never brought
he never grabbed you originally or too
young right but he's a very sensual
perso yes yes i'm sure this when
he was i mean he's dead now
so well again past yes she did
say best ten she was i said
hey i put in past tense in
one sentence and present ten said another
because i wasn't sure if he had
passed away i forgot but here's the
thing about christmas day here's the thing
about those of us in the study
they know it's christmas after all lastly
no george michael diamond christmas do the
dough george banco da days um those
of us in the celebratory actually we
live forever in a sense i just
felt it's okay to say
a george michael is is essential he
has a way i just found out
videos sorry but no let's talk
videos i found the drums and do
they know it's christmas or from a
tears for fears song it's a sample
that makes a lot of sense yeah
were they there because that songs were
fucking banger yeah it's one of the
best christmas songs actually without tick shimmy
weird and fucked up i think in
terms of the lyrics are so stupid
they don't know it's christmas like their
hunger
erie and they just better podcaster nana
lyrics and now i'm taking me to
take anything either side but it's been
me cry many a christmas to listen
to it but i will then i'll
think what is this i will i
will say i i i give them
credit for where they're coming from but
the lyrics are a little silly but
i feel like some of them are
better than others um some girls are
bigger than
others want to go morrissey in tins
or bud or wait i mean why
did morrissey care what why did morrissey
i don't know i remember getting that
record and going this can't be what
the song's about it's gotta be it's
gotta be a cheeky title that's about
something else nope it's just about how
some girls are bigger than other girls
right
tits or bud or yeah whatever what
a mercy tits or buh
but i have too much wang wang
reality recap yeah i've been watching a
little joe millionaire reboot have you seen
all by what's remote why new joe
millionaire because i know there's a millionaire
and non millionaire yeah um well we
just put it on do they always
go with non millionaire because he's probably
cuter right they're both cute and their
boo scene
mainly normal how do you find a
normal cute millionaire i don't know that's
weird i don't know they're both cute
scott i know that you are begging
for a compliment just there
a millionaire please god you're a normal
man like cuba still the abnormal acute
yeah umbrellas are going long could do
she's going to be you're gonna get
up there no you get up there
you're gonna get a ladder coffee shop
and i don't know
but await but so they're counting on
people not remembering that there was a
joe millionaire dead premises this so the
first year top screaming in me the
first joe millionaire they didn't know until
the end that he wasn't really a
millionaire right so the whole time they
thought he's a millionaire this time there's
they surprised the woman there's two men
and they said one is a millionaire
and one
it is not one is worth ten
million dollars and one is worth not
so jimmy a millionaire and no millionaire
yeah basically and then they both they
can fall in love with both of
them they won't know till the end
which one's the real millionaire but they
are permitted to fall in love with
both they are an actual i will
say because it's not oh thanks i
didn't know what you're doing you really
show
scott is adjusting the umbrella i guess
that as per laura's lawrence command don't
call me laura i have corrected it
immediately will don't do it okay laura
okay so um the fun thing i
like about the show one thing i
enjoy is that ah thanks
the love show or enjoy one thing
huh
it's not the bachelor so the the
women are not doing the same bachelor
tropes right thank you i didn't even
mean you had to fix the umbrella
right then i just that didn't make
it better though
sure
he said that to me as a
video text
well you can because i'm a rebel
look good you did a show here
the other day and i brought him
a nice big glass of water and
he poured it onto the ground why
because he's fucking hassle i've i have
an agent of chaos like the joke
or
and why are you being so serious
i ask another cute thing about the
show just i'll just to wrap up
reality recap is that yeah yeah wrap
up the guys live in a house
together and they're nice they're sharing deets
about the girls and they get along
like friends and you know who the
millionaires before yes we all do as
you do what do you like tits
or boobs yeah
yeah i wanted to but was like
no this one got in a fight
with that one and blah blah oh
so it's kinda cool and then but
i guess i was tempted to skip
like and there's i can't skip to
the end but i was tend to
just wait and then just watch the
ending into what happens but some of
those stuff happening right now is already
good so if anyone cares it's out
there you know it's on hulu are
the people dumb i think that's a
given okay and even the millionaire he
did i don't know he's a farm
guy i don't know if he was
happy he has um he's a formula
there he has like a family business
that's like farm related
mean harry shouldn't be doing the show
he has a helicopter he has a
ranch all this oh okay so he
lives in the middle of nowhere where
the dollars actually right right right right
right so i said that could be
good because then the girl who if
she wants to live in the middle
fucking nowhere she can live forever on
that girl never wants to live in
the middle of nowhere remember the wannabe
previous farm bachelor yeah
it's not a good it's not a
good selling point for a bachelor it's
also just tough even if you met
someone in a bar then they were
like i live in the middle of
nowhere like it's like well i don't
know if i wanna go do that
they ever do bachelor on animal crossing
what what do you mean like the
character i know that people did shows
like standup shows on animal crossing but
if somebody had done a game show
what are you guys talking about oh
my god
animal crossing was so pandemic it was
so pandemic it was peak pandemic i
mean i got an i got into
animal crossing the game on nintendo ds
right that's what it's on right more
like nintendo i wish i was doing
it on the switch that's what i
mean switch i used to have a
ds like a million years ago i'm
no i'm saying that um my nintendo
switch but i was really into it
for
awhile but then you know i feel
like i started to go i can't
live inside this fake world well you're
going to be living in the metaverse
soon i know you gotta get it
and f t is ah as an
avatar i do i do i think
i lasted longer than you i last
longer than you did but there does
come a point where it's like this
is so
sickening to me i agree i started
to go i'm i'm like i'm out
of my mind cool my nephew when
i play the sims on our game
cube that we got for free sims
is a blast but it it's the
same kind of thing where it's just
like you i feel like she does
some sort of thing like that now
not farmville or something but it's like
takes up a lot of mental space
but i'm always pl
saying like word games so i get
it well i do my world one
today guys i'm talking about well hey
today we're in the world part poured
over um i were to lose fun
because it's a very simple thing i
like it i love it i love
that you have to stop after one
i would play it all fucking day
really well yeah i set my instagram
timer again because i was like yeah
i'm on this shit fucking way too
much and then you ran outside and
i went wow and then i looked
around i was like oh i mean
to fold that laundry for days
yeah the world my screen time is
bad and it's it's approaching um first
quarantine bad yeah oh yeah st minus
outta control i just decided to have
it in my fucking hand all the
time it's like what am i doing
sick it real thing apps right after
i closed the thing that gross and
disgusting mindset i have
a lot of screentime because i'm making
deals all day wow you know you
have all those i know maps
got a new shelter device the way
you got new kevin you know i
bought this huh okay well because the
old ones are two most things about
jan no idea too stupid to go
and do but i need to do
is we talk about really i needed
a big idea a bigger one for
your pioneer the big screen now for
my pellets throw it
how's the screen it does by the
way they're not making them anymore i
mean they've started they've halted production because
he checks in the citation because for
two like that two months' i could
have gotten one that fucking window why
have they halted production because of quarantine
because of demand no demand is going
down so they alter production so their
stock tumbled because of mister big because
mister bang i think it's demands going
down also
so because everyone's great getting back out
in the world a little bit and
everyone's thinking i think everyone's in shape
yeah well user pell tons and sold
them yeah that's true yeah so why
do you need the big one just
tell us
well i'm not gonna tell you because
you want an i'm on toronto
to watch bruno
oh no not the sociopath although he
shan't he should have made a cameo
we don't ask about we were talking
about sasha baron cohen bruno
why
have you not seen on conto i
haven't seen his already a hit song
for his song we've got to talk
about bringers don't talk about you don't
talk about i have i have picked
up on that a little bit from
my time on instagram but i try
to avoid sometimes i just scroll past
cause i'm like well i wanna watch
it eventually don't wanna get all the
hits from instagram absolutely luckily people only
make the same joke over and over
again so it's really not ruining them
what is the joke because i do
it's about talking about bruno
they're going to only one i've seen
that they're going to or that they're
not going to i watched kota and
i wept my little ass
you wiped your little ass wiped it
and turned in my we both were
crying and we were like that was
so good it's good right i loved
it it's an extremely sweet movie i
loved it so much yeah yeah the
the dad actor yeah actor i went
down a wormhole looking them all up
afterwards yes me too you simply must
yeah finding their addresses he was santa
tastic catfishing them
i'm in the middle of the catfish
right now
i can't say too much she's it's
a huge muscle mass
ah the girl was fantastic she sign
language and had never sung on screen
so it was on broadway before she
not from another country as well she's
she's really american accent learned another language
sign language and then also
was singing on on screen which she
had never done but she was a
singer previous yeah still that's a different
skill with acting singing that absolutely she'll
start to learn the fishing shit yeah
and don't that alone i understood f
yeah she was i mean she did
that a few years back yes the
first scene also did that yeah the
oriel isn't giving anything away for first
scene of the skimming the first scene
of the movie
you'll see it within one second yeah
on a boat and she's working oh
and sorry spoiler alert and i was
thinking oh god that's a really that's
hard as an actor she's like grabbing
fish doing all this like it's disgusting
and you're back here really comfortable on
like like every new end to grab
one fish you would quit the movie
i've literally done that many times
times with a movie grab fish really
which strangely not ah are touching things
like that i had to um gut
a fish yeah are you there chelsea
how random is that some multicam show
they had me gutting a real fish
for whoa i know and so i
would you inflict that on a jewish
room full of people
i don't know what it was like
it was kind of um yeah i
really don't know why it was real
it just looked better i guess but
i'm so so then i got the
blood on my face which is part
of the scene the biggest race
anyway
i went fishing once when i was
a little kid with ah my uncle
and i caught a fish oo but
it was not a fish that we
could eat we were fishing for flounder
and you couldn't eat it because it
was inedible or because it was like
it was like like maybe this
a big was like a six inch
fish or something i was very small
and it was not like it just
six inches small
damn
you should know whale i mean quahog
and six and you've got a six
inch fish yeah so i caught a
little fish in which do not it
was not like a fish that you
fry up and eat you know what
i mean once you deal with that
shit we kept the sciences that we
keep it because i'm sorry upset yeah
you don't wanna throw i wish that's
drawing it back would be better
throwing it back would be better yeah
but you're a kid i was a
little kid shooting a fish tie but
i felt like i had a prize
yeah it was also much that i
felt like i had a price but
i felt disappointed that i had not
contributed oh i mean why did other
people catch flounder yeah yeah wow okay
so you want to do long night
really found at night found the right
guy was allowed to fly direct i
um i don't go fishing off and
sorrow know that was it it was
the only time the only question they
did they go fishing without hugo that
kid only caught a six inch fish
he's a little pussy
he can't handle it he can't handle
that when he can't provide
i feel like i went fishing once
and then i went fishing twice never
caught any fishing crises a time when
everything was fishing every day yeah i'm
fishing right now once i feel like
it was up near san francisco for
some reason of san francisco vallejo i
must have been i can tell you
what comic book was in a store
in san francisco but there's really wanting
to be sure ab's
so that really helps it was the
second part of a justice league justice
society of america two-parter oh so you're
well aware because you had to know
i really don't know i remote okay
this is what i remember from the
trip we had we'd rented ah some
sort of joint huh we rented
no we rented some sort of a
ah ah mobile what do you call
hospital like r r v we rented
some sort of r v okay and
we drove into san francisco we had
like fished with some some church friends
we drove into san francisco i saw
a a poster on the street someone
was selling this
poster on the street that i thought
was hilarious during the trip which was
the unknown comic in the burt reynolds
pose shoot or with the bag cosmo
yeah with the bag over his penis
as well that's funny
and i was like that's funny
and then we went to fisherman's wharf
and i remember being super bored because
my parents just wanted to like shop
and look at you know dumb shit
and idiots and i've and i saw
this comic book which ah would they
it was was a little bit older
and not sold in my area and
i was like please please please can
i get
it anyway the morrissey song yes and
did you get it i don't remember
i think i might have i don't
know wow he wanted it so bad
and doesn't remember if he got it
or not yeah but that's all i
remember from that trip so it must
have been around nineteen eighty and why
is your i-pad so big
chance you almost tricked me know i've
been fishing a couple times i think
but once was kind of memorable i
was um in wisconsin i think with
ah my aunt and uncle she's summer
they had a face i don't know
somebody hasn't heard of summerhouse but it
wasn't fancy it wasn't fancy by any
means it was a very cool
camp like cabin you know and so
rebel yeah yes camp it was pure
yeah and ah my brother and i
went on a trip with my aunt
and uncle and then we went fishing
on a boat was pretty exciting and
then a boat and pontoon i believe
on a pontoon and then um while
i was asleep my brother saw
tick on my leg oh whoa god
he pulled it off wo with his
mouth no
he got all of the psycho but
yeah yeah it was a little kid
i mean i was like probably i
think i was like ten and he
was so he was like twelve or
thirteen wow so you could have had
lyme disease right but he was a
web why was he looking at your
leg he saw it on my leg
i was asleep i just i was
just yeah your leg out yeah
i was just laying there here it's
actually not it's like a hot summer
day you know laying on the couch
exactly you got it sometimes you gotta
stick your foot out to regulate temperature
anyway i don't even know if i
had a blanket i just passed out
taking an app you know
anyway very very helpful i ever had
a tick it's terrifying to me i
know they free the idea of them
is so horrible do we have them
here we must i'm sure if you're
hiking or something i mean when i
went to little compton rhode island which
is where art in this from we
were in sort of like grassy fields
and then i was thinking there's going
to be
mix in here and get them all
i mean that's i can't even have
fun yeah you know it's like so
you start thinking how to tick and
it's just over that's the grassy knoll
that's how j f k died from
the grassy knoll from the tick a
big tick oh god i'll pick yeah
the harvey album a bag apache take
i still want to know why the
ipad so big i feel like i
can't how big is the biggest one
ah it's like a car windshield
tea i wish i was
okay laura and i lay on it
put yeah yes i guess why you
think he got a bigger okay and
he wants to watch tv from the
tub
top tv
other option was to light some candles
and watch ozark while the he is
he wants to be able to use
it somewhere specific um i don't know
i really don't know i wanna know
why i wanna know wouldn't you like
to know i i'll never tell you
guarantee it's not into
listing but i need to know i
will never okay you'll never never give
it up i will never met even
if my guy won't die so it's
telling my lips so he wants to
watch big porn huge horns huge in
the tv won't do it it's really
it's mostly portable big porn or even
bigger scr
mean for reading you wanted but why
don't just make the text bigger on
smaller one never mind
to think that
alright that's fine why does that why
do they even make the big ones
then are you are you like drawing
a comic yes
i read a book recently yes all
on what i'd like to do more
wrote a book what was the book
you read do you want to talk
about it oh that it's a private
book
it was a book called the thursday
murder club and was very enjoyable book
but the thing is there were it
shifted between um perspectives so there was
like a third person last tool exactly
so there was a third person perspective
but then there was a first person
perspective in the form of a journal
doctors and lawyers ca what's that what's
it what what chomsky harriet the spy
which helps which ascii tom hanks movie
library cloud atlas cloud atlas i believe
the book is sort of like that
is not i do not know i
have not read it nor have i
seen the film neither have i but
the thing is when they switched perspect
gives the journal was a different font
whoa not writing much smut it wasn't
necessary it wasn't really handwriting but it
was so much smaller than the other
one that i had to constant cause
i was reading on a cat's annoy
i keep bumping it up yeah and
then when i would go back to
the the third person font it was
now so big that it was a
quietly mortified show
should it should use a tor yeah
it was like this is good enough
for you as well it should account
for your text size on the first
page and like make it bigger you
know and lauren i'll call you on
musk i will call you on musk
call you on musk that's you on
most i'm going to tell you i'm
on my
scalia on mars yeah yeah like he's
found a phone company called musk soon
i hope so and the downs are
just like in your scheme
ah would you buy a stinky phone
if it was like the best phone
out there but maybe stay a little
bit thanki like it just stank a
little bit yeah
okay you know scott what are these
slides that you're wearing these are my
crocs these are the mcrc slides i
thought i shared with me by crock
but they only have three hole i
need to talk slides you need them
rocks what are you doing you only
sent a three therapy box he didn't
want to add we didn't want add
one week and you only sent us
three pair off the shoe faucet after
three
i didn't even get to talk about
how i wanted the slides good percentage
sides to my friends already have the
slides slide for all my friends yeah
buh buh alright we need to drink
by
and we're back we're back with my
bays we see my found out why
scott baath of dubai admitted it was
big porn he admitted
oh my god he admitted what is
it
i'd say probably leave oh yeah yeah
by tim robinson oh my god that
that show's so funny jim robinson show
the fucking mall one is the funniest
thing ever though i actually watched that
right after i gave birth and i
was dying after instantly when i was
recovering that i bet your swap swap
the baby for it i know it
was one day late
the baby and i was watching that
and i was laughing so hard i
was it was it was medicine yeah
laughter is the best yeah i mean
i've heard that yeah yes yeah man
you feel better about having him use
my coochie oh okay
it closed up after one entirely the
doctor came and said no to heal
your coochie here's what we gotta give
you one dose of i think you
should know them all up you're going
to yell at me are gonna tell
me to get out of your but
i want you to trust me on
this watch the sketch show
how's parenting it's going great
great well haha oh yes now reached
a point where um she's she's six
months old and that's sort of over
it and say george go back in
my my glitter experience with children is
from six months and beyond and so
i really feel like i've hit ok
boys
her
six months yeah
was gonna do the madness but ah
six pumps and me odd udi you're
going to be challenging but it's it's
getting more and more fun for me
because first of all i feel better
physically which is helping but i she's
getting so funny and she's so yeah
what do you hope her first word
is i would love for it to
be mama really when there are deals
updates
other than car but isn't mama what's
there to say right yeah data is
easier to change your name to data
yeah she's saying that by accident yeah
we your people are just saying oh
he oh they said they said it
now no no no they have to
i think it's if it's data if
it's mama it's like it's obviously you're
saying me if it's
gotta they have to include a point
in like sort of a they have
a gesture like a repeated gesture like
know this person well you know a
part of it is i have to
start calling us that now i guess
because she has no she's not gonna
say ma mushin which isn't i don't
often say mama right what do you
say lauren i don't say anything i
just i don't never tell her to
come to mom i
don't speak a word to her
ask her why i've said it i've
tried to make a point because now
she's at the point where six months
is where they start to learn their
own name so you have to be
more specific so you call her nicknames
and stuff you'd be more specific you
call the specific name and then she'll
start to recognize that means her and
then so that's i would say probably
now is a good time to start
putting in that
he's that and i'm some bubble oh
right yeah so you don't feel like
you have to stop calling your dip
shit yeah yeah she'll start figuring out
what we're talking about oh what if
we came over to record and now
we haven't seen her since like week
three or something like that oh you
saw her when she was like three
months three months okay so
so we haven't seen her since then
but what maybe more for what have
we came over to record and she
just would paul scott therefore and that
was her first words l honestly i'd
be i'd be astounded and be thrilled
if that was her first word she
just knew who you were yeah then
i'd be she'd be baby genius what
does she said hello paul hello scott
that would be really cool welcome nice
to make your coin what i haven't
i haven't seen you guys in months
approximately three years funny i lordship me
sweetly three show me a video of
you blowing lightly on her face yeah
and ah no i just don't like
like right in her face she just
oh she starts like she goes through
so many emotions like oh she she
like it or not like she likes
it i think but she's also like
really shocked and the thing that's very
cute because we found we found that
molly our dog hates it when you
go
like that interface
no just even by her that noise
just noise you do okay well does
it make her think of the junk
yard she was raised in mexico maybe
i don't know the sound of cars
ben comparison that's a weird she hates
it so what got her there because
you're doing raspberries the other laps will
do the other leg will do it
everyone say wow
now is coupe la tour la one
she's other la cool up married me
she cool up lop kiss colossus culo
caracas right now she's vi aquaman oh
bob guess that works out great
um i said i have friends who
had a dog rescue dog that would
go crazy adopt don't shop it would
go crazy don't shop adopt osha it
would go crazy if you said the
word abogado gato does that mean lawyer
rob we got this covered maybe we
i think we have the dog will
go crazy
it's not like thou know no one
knows we don't die from that yeah
we did too much so we're just
finally my god everyone just went crazy
to death my god i was gonna
walk with holly yesterday and these dogs
were much ice where they almost jumped
over the fence they were behind it
was like taller than me but they
would they jumped up so high and
their paws were above it and they
were trying to
to attack you yeah they were going
crazy barking at me wow and i
was a kid that was the scariest
but we had dogs like that oh
my god i think i told you
about ah hippies hill or rob hill
in my old neighborhood yeah remember and
there was a the the one point
it was ranch house there was a
garage that had a dog in there
that was made
maybe like it was an irish wolfhound
maybe it was a shaggy dog you
know what shaggy da call those shows
the shaggy dogs what do you mean
sheep dog um yeah um oh like
the character the shaggy dog the shaggy
da yeah but i think people will
say shaggy dog sometimes as it is
nicole okay maybe i just don't find
them by the way like you shouldn't
call something after it's job
why not you know what i mean
like like no that's it's identity like
way like separate work working dog like
life at a time before worried hey
i'm just shaggy yellow sheep i chase
sheep for a living but you don't
have to like that's my identity like
some kind of stressful to have a
bunch of sheep you have to like
get back in
your fence on shame not to move
now sounds great
i bet i could do it easy
okay anyway if i were a sheep
dog i would just actually generally like
stradey hookers me wow you get it
you get it i get it you
get a car yeah in there um
and they said this dog was in
this garage often and it was a
very um scary thing to go up
to the garage
to the point where the dog would
sense you outside because then it would
like jump up in the windows little
willow garage and it was like it
was like there was a monster in
there because it would not it wasn't
tall enough to stay in the window
but it would jump up just barking
like crazy scary it was a horrifying
actually if you're a little kid oh
my god yeah yeah i'm sure i
told you about the dog that
chased me when i was on my
paper route and it made me hate
dogs
when did you come back around so
it was a different dog that made
you hate dogs knows that dog
wait what doc did you think i
thought a dog marmaduke you yeah this
guy remember this dog chased me i
thought you bit a dog yeah i
did that i love to do that
every day wait i thought you were
a dog who had a paper route
and then you are and there's nothing
in the rulebook
um did anyone see clifford no two
i why would we we don't have
holly i'm just curious what it's like
to have a big dog like that
in your life but the movies like
i mean friend of mine son saw
clifford and boy he was too young
for it really it was
ah clifford really disturbed him a lot
but but now with the books because
i remember mikey minutes too it was
the animation yeah i remember liking the
books as a kid but it was
very playful and whimsical and draw he
was clearly a drawing yeah and it's
funny but yeah but if you started
i mean like like in the real
life oh boy that would be to
put them into real life then that's
like the game stuff
like watching king congo near a kid
it's like frightening what's the girl who
owns clifford's name clarified clifford's master
king kong the ninety seventy six one
with jessica lange which my father was
in um that's
no hiring but now i watched the
thirty s one and that was caribou
you as a cow i may get
depending on what age you are i
also was very fascinated with monster movies
when i was a kid yeah so
it was it was very much like
i watched it once it was kinda
like ooh that's scary but then i
found out about stop motion yeah and
so then i then i wasn't really
scared of those types of
movies anymore i would be like oh
wow that's how they do that that's
only do that i don't need to
be scared that's a tedious process yeah
did you ever have dynamite magazine yeah
oh yeah all the time up until
i was like thirteen or something yeah
i have a subscription like i would
order it from scholastic yeah scholastic book
club i loved scholastic book i did
too that was like what was it
like once a month at school or
something
something like that and you'd better from
the satellite yes yes yes i've got
so much but dynamite magazine did stuff
on like it's so wild they did
like this was magazine was aimed at
nerds because it was like here's a
peek at ray harryhausen techniques joke about
long chaney sr like shit is like
these movies are already old oh weird
i just got sad though about kids
who must have been sad on scholastic
book takes they didn't have five dollars
or something oh yeah i remember i
organized everything fucking schools lot of school
stuff is really bad yeah what do
you mean just going to school is
bad well because like teachers have to
buy their supplies like there's so many
things that just aren't
like our government just doesn't take care
of yeah they should the narrative that
kids should each get a free book
can you know how much better the
budget yeah one book to every kid
in the world no thank you person
at the town hall meeting i don't
want the kids to have free lunch
thinking free
lunch one of the power of war
ah yeah well it is one of
the best one of the coolest things
our society does is is public schooling
yeah but the teachers are paid two
cents and no i mean yes we
should put more money into it but
it's like it's it's honestly like when
you think about it and amazing thing
that but the post office
and also have ah i mean ah
pretty much so you're not even gonna
give me this that the public schools
but i'm according to what i'm saying
other guy you're talking about an england
because that's the private school actually they
have to pay everyone estimated to school
no what we call what what they
call public school is private spray yeah
they don't pay i don't understand that
why that is i don't either
why is it called private if they're
back where everything they do is backwards
they call it the the front of
the car the back of the car
they do
idiots yeah the engines in the callback
ate it we hate them
if you're listening to us from there
we hate you
wow
lauryn i'm just i feel like this
bum you out now it's great well
because holly's going to school in a
mere four and a half years i
know they're trying to take care of
all these issues legitimate question are you
already having to look at shit like
that um but i have heard that
you like probably by the time she's
like one of the half i'm supposed
to be doing that or so and
so since nightmare fucking and say i
don't
about that but i would really like
i think that i mean i just
hope that there's people out there who
are like giving money towards helping like
i just think like if hollywood high
school and i knew there were some
kids who didn't have something i want
everyone to have everything i just don't
i don't like that cool you give
your money i could give all of
it asshole
there wouldn't even be that much money
it's like you just have to like
you know donate a little to help
everyone feel better isn't just hard that
people have to go through that yeah
it's terrible he's against it there's enough
shit there's enough shit when you're a
kid to be embarrassed self-conscious about much
less the fact that you come from
ah a family that's not doing that
ok here's what we do that we
we've target those children and we put
them into a special thing and say
we're gonna we're gonna pay for all
of your stuff because tiger sober for
it would be yeah it would be
an anonymous situation where everyone just gets
what they need we put on a
guy fawkes mask and hood
richard should we're giving all the kids
the same stuff
everything that you need to get everyone
will get square pizza
were you ah bring your lunch to
school or some on lunch i brought
my own lunch because what did you
have all the ate the same thing
from kindergarten through high school basically every
single day because it was some some
days where it was a variation that
i never really liked i had a
peanut butter sandwich with no jelly i
had a pack of chips i go
back a cigarette
pack of phillies blunts term desert hostess
cupcake cookie is that kind of thing
and a juice box of some sort
or kokomo all the way through as
senior in high school pretty much almost
every day i when i was in
grade school i went home for lunch
because we live that close to the
school oh wow grade school you are
able to do that yeah yeah yeah
yeah but i would think that you
would want to stay
with all you've all of your friends
know i guess i did i i
don't know why no that seems cool
to go home i think i liked
it but when i look back on
it now i'm sure there must have
been days where i was like it
was enough to go back there oh
you wouldn't want to go back at
all you know i mean will our
schools right by a burger king so
i would go there for lunch once
i was in high school
it was fun whereby fosters freeze and
that's where i would go all the
time and i would walk in and
go your usual you would say wow
no no yeah maybe like what are
you talking about we go your usual
usual are you
i was thinking about sandwiches because i
had either just broke us sandwiches growing
up and i was thinking about deviled
ham the other day oh sure most
would eat your meat sandwich once you
get to school like i would have
my sandwich with turkey and then i'd
get there like the turkey yeah yeah
alone oh man my ma butter i
ah i can't wipe right
i can't believe how badly i mangled
this but my mother made with like
make me a bunch of sandwiches at
once and put them in the freezer
whoa and then i would set them
stay at oh it does here's why
it doesn't work because what you should
do is you take the next day
sandwich out the night before right and
you put it in the fridge
age yeah so that it thaws out
and then you could put condiments on
it or whatever yeah common instead of
what i did i put all bunnymen
big condom it's like putting soda in
tinfoil i would forget about it until
the morning i would grab it out
of the freezer in the morning so
they don't just wreck of me it
would sigh out by lunchtime but it
would be wet it would be like
a soggy
sandwich soggy no sorry da talking can
be a wet sandwich with no condiments
on it oh no miserable one thing
about bologna i just saw on instagram
today that the oscar meyer bologna face
masks you know those face masks that
are like tissue you know as you
put it on your face they made
when it looks like bologna and it's
sold out so fast that they couldn't
keep up with production and they didn't
expect it at all it looks like
baloney or it looks like it's just
one of those sheet masks but it's
but a red circle and it looks
like money comes in an oscar meyer
package oh and like you do when
you're a kid yeah though i didn't
learn about this till i was an
adult where you have never seen the
pony that makes me sick it's gross
do you have the meat touching
my face know you don't like meat
touching your face
that's your takeaway yeah
yeah yeah i we never got turkey
we had baloney we had we had
tuna or we had deviled ham is
turkey much more expensive than i don't
know but it it it it feels
like it was like a tuna goes
a long way and tuna goes a
long way and it makes me sick
doesn't really tuna salad oh i loved
that's the one thing i still don't
like anything salad that was like chicken
salad i don't like i don't like
when there's fucking chunks and i i
don't like some of those things like
an egg salad like i don't like
bananas hello my excelled barf oh excel
barf double to him i wonder if
i just reveled ham it's basically like
the tam that hasn't been blessed by
a priest
that hound i think it's like basically
it's like it's like junk meat that
slut that's slang word put into as
a song a hata just read so
like you put it on oh no
you put it on bread and it's
like it's like putting it's like peanut
butter it's like you know yeah my
yeah we had it in the house
my dad would eat it but i
never ate it
but i was fascinated by the packaging
i loved the little red level yes
the underwood deviled ham pain i gotta
look this not just that the the
logo but that it was like just
white paper wrapped around this camp oh
yeah it was so i don't know
it looked neat to me deviled ham
spread like the devil i love him
and got the first the devil is
a friend of mine
this isn't what i thought it would
look like i sort of wonder if
i would like it we should try
double data growth because i haven't had
it since maybe i was thirteen or
something like that fuckin try it on
oh no no trip to london we
know i don't know it no no
what what's been i don't know what's
in it it's gross to me what's
in it um gross too
me because others might enjoy but i
don't i don't like these sort of
mushy things okay hold up it has
mayo ham mustard mayo's all the sweet
subs good you put it all together
and a big thing they're doing sports
tracker
oh wait i made my things load
just like it's like a patty but
didn't know it had condiments in it
yeah neither do wild to make it
mushy
before you just start once you got
a real good mice we used to
have my dad you see liver wurst
yeah whew which was so gross to
me and then i used to have
something that they used to be something
i loved lunch be called turkey ham
oh well what's that was i don't
wanna pig fuck and then they i
mean when i'm in turkey interface
had a big fight when ham and
imagine a turkey in a pic and
a ham that's just respectful that would
be awesome i don't know i guess
it was a combination of turkey and
ham i don't know but it is
it is it like lunch meat though
or is it a great it was
launched me watched me i loved it
so it's turkey ham yeah it had
a specific taste and it was really
good so it's handmade out of turkey
i guess yeah i guess yeah but
it didn't taste completely like turkey you
know what i write no but however
was prized shareholder whatever yeah the way
that a ham would be but yeah
turkey was so good i've never found
it again know they still make it
i've never seen it let's go to
garrisons right after this i'll go to
i've never seen it a go i've
never seen garrisons you've never
seen a gelson or you simply must
go to gil same skits are amazing
the aisle wow no but it does
remind me of going to usb shows
and getting a little something beforehand yes
oh what a world we live in
now where we don't do anything i
would go get like a little soda
pop or maybe i get a meal
because i was going going from things
wrong i get a sandwich with vitamin
zero wow
you love vitamin zero i haven't i
knocked them off really is it bad
for you know that i've ever used
just like like too many too many
carbs it's just better to drink water
just like why even zero has like
twenty carbs and water is just the
best thing yeah basically only drink water
huh i guess i'm perfect i haven't
setup i get it also bop but
i shouldn't have a sparkling flavored water
from time to time but even that
diet coke doesn't have any carbs though
know it's better for you but vitamin
it does it your poison no carbs
but that rat juice
oh what am i gonna turn to
pizza rat ca so wait so i
would have a sandwich and it always
had just like butter and whatever and
like one slicer verrone butter and one
size of bologna wow
and then then i would have chips
but sandwiches italy or spans like some
nice tail butter i didn't know that's
how it just could be that good
yeah i remember i think i must
have talked about this before but i
remember when my friend was like hey
do you want to go to the
deli for lunch i was like the
deli why would either yea like don't
make sandwiches and they made this big
hoagie with lots of meat
i've never had out till pretty late
and might never see the sandwiches like
that because my mom always just put
one slice of bologna oh wow funny
i have to say i still make
sandwiches the way i made them when
i was a kid really ah and
jamie makes like photo ready sandwiches really
yes you should take pictures of him
and send him to us along with
her words
this is making me want a sandwich
oh man my dad used to make
if he made a peter butter jelly
sandwich he would also put butter on
it wow that's that's really decadent yeah
really interesting now i was reading about
a burger that you put peanut butter
on but supposed to be really good
i don't know about that i don't
know about that either
peanut sauce maybe now i can get
into that no but then i would
put just peanuts on a burger i'd
put peanuts on i put piano solo
berger
why is that a bug
alright we'll be right back
in rbac and guess what me what
i couldn't i can't fathom what you're
about to say it's something good i
have oh i give you a clue
no no that's doesn't give me a
birthday know it but i'm renee it's
better than that even better it's even
better than my birthday it's i'll give
you a hint wait
so you've you think your birthday is
better than both of our birthdays no
i know it
i'll give you a clue okay it's
the segment of our show that the
audience loves the most oh three sure
ah three yeah da da da da
creature da three jerk dad three zat
your three church is that your teacher
gonna play a game
we are going to play a little
game which we call a reacher and
we've asked people to submit some and
guess what they did we thank our
listeners for taking the time out of
their day we blessing our listeners we
we pray god's blessing father god please
bless our listeners in all that they
do let them know that they are
law
loved by us and by you father
god in jesus' name we pray
amen
may their leavings be bountiful that they're
leaving
joy blessing
dropping
tropic i made droppings in the toilet
and i made too many i guess
i don't know if there's a problem
in here well they're bountiful thank you
god thank you father god for a
bountiful leavings all right this is a
game called alphabetical question game it is
submitted by and i believe this person
has submitted a three-tier before and how
dare they angela vof vaak why
edgy lifelong yeah okay nice yeah this
is submitted by vi workshop see who
directed the matrix with her sister
players start by picking a location for
a scene the players then go in
clockwise order and can only speak in
questions additionally the first word of every
question needs to go in alphabetical order
as the scene progresses long pauses or
start i'm law or starting a question
with the incorrect letter eliminates you from
the route so i'd say abc game
yes with but all questions okay okay
okay so you have to ask a
question and it has to start with
the next letter of the alphabet yes
and everything has to be a question
that we say yes and we're doing
one word at a time or just
we're doing we're doing an entire question
at a time it has to be
a scene okay well it has to
forgot got it and we're going clockwise
hard or counterclockwise who gives us
shit while paul paul doesn't know which
one's wit so it always starts with
me
whoever jumps in next to go will
figure it out from there okay we'll
go clockwise alright great and sixteen
and do we need a suggestion from
the crowd they've been very silent checked
it out they said olfactory but that
begins with a d i think some
pineapple but i've heard that's even more
yeah
alright i will start with a question
that begins with the letter a a
right at the old beginning of elf
that's helpful
did elf stand for alphabet yeah and
e t stands for it at me
etc
i see alphabet and etc two of
my favorite etsy sir i'll fall but
too late from you i like yours
from wiki wiki week
at this part of the game no
we're doing now no it's not okay
the game begins now i press ok
the game begins now anyone hear that
noise
boo
yeah it's your boo
it's like two questions but okay can't
hear it myself i think
so you must be terrible you just
write me back and it's impossible
start over can you hear it okay
no no okay we'll start over no
koi no keep going okay can you
hear it
did you hear somebody say boo
even if i did would that help
anything
friends should i be the one to
open my stupid ears and listen to
this
go and open the door won't you
good save
honestly just forget how do you open
this door i think you just kind
of like press on it really hard
oh no you don't you
ah the dojo will save you any
time
just over here i think
question per this is impossible
i think we're doing great okay alright
knowing what you know about doors do
you think that maybe i should turn
the knob laccase do you think i
should try to do
copy yeah
ah most doors
go this way
in my experience but i don't know
no
oh okay oh gosh
so you're on now if i don't
open it are we stuck in here
oh my god i think we might
be but how do you open it
pry it with a crowbar
quiet i'm trying to row with a
crowbar aren't i
ah
really this is me on my birthday
silence
won't you silence won't you alright laura
do it again let's start with laura
okay a great game i like i
like it i like it the other
way okay okay
ah the suggestion is pool
the game game billiards fit this
sucre
okay anyone want to go swimming
rebecca okay
ah
ah but aren't all the pool's drained
in this area can you shut up
for a second
don't you want to shut up for
a second
christ why are you yelling at me
you go backwards to cease
and you're out hi cindy let me
be in let me be yeah amy
it's gotta be e
everyone thinks
yes they do
oh oh
everyone heard that right
friends am i hearing what i think
i'm hearing
hearing what
you forgot a g
ah glasses say what
say what is happy
glasses say what
hear that
i wonder if i can
it's kind of statement is oh right
about you're out why are we putting
people out of the game why don't
we just i don't know okay keep
going to z yeah guys trying it
ah i can't believe it's taken this
long if i give a shit
if i listen to people out your
really why don't we just keep making
a comeback huh well because it ends
it eventually yeah yeah there's definitely will
end of z if there's a definite
end then we know we can we
don't have to take people out yeah
ok if i listen really closely do
you think i can
where are all of these about listening
to
ah hu jia bits on the floor
classes say what ship is on the
floor
two classic questions most of these came
from somebody shows you what okay okay
oba l yeah let's go to l
if you're gonna skip ah okay yeah
knights hampshire don't
ah nice
those protective shoe
lots of them
like don't fuck
lots say what lots of them wouldn't
you
let's say let's say why gibbins on
the floor
huh
ah
may i please
flats may i please have a drink
of water okay
neighbor may i also have a drink
of water yeah oh gosh i wonder
if i'm out of water i'm still
here
another statement is it i wonder sometimes
i wonder if there's a question oh
gosh am i out of lawsuit is
this question going to be awesome i
water
so competent now ah
ah
pretty please
may i have a cookie
quietly i ask may i also have
a cook
really why do you want a cookie
so badly
so we can eat please
if it pleases the court
ah
trying to fatten up don't you think
i need it
underwear under yeah i'm sandwich
yeah very thin
a here comes the yoda construction the
yoda would be amazing this game or
you're not
ah
hey haven't you been worried
wow very worried very should be or
should be
why would i be worried
xylophones are fun to play aren't they
you're losing your mind i believe
ah
they'll hand gesture makes it a question
i believe
oh again zooms zooms god's wounds ah
yeah shakespeare much more tomorrow okay i'm
familiar with him zunes is there any
decent man killed
oh lazy day we did it why
did those green were a lot of
sites built on each other yeah yeah
yeah i liked hell we would plateau
sometimes three people take the same thing
in different ways now and move on
to an entirely different topic i'm proud
of it i'm probably very proud i'm
really proud of that yes my wife
likes us
yeah i actually feel really good about
that yeah well guys that's gonna wrap
it up numerous on one episode of
threesome that we just did
i was crying i cried too but
i cry sad yeah i was so
sad as this episode of sex into
the episode was almost over i said
thinking of the people in the scene
yeah because they were hungry they could
no longer see within the guy wearing
co-founded going ahead bodies yeah yeah that
was hard we thought he was too
skinny does that ever have
but we'll see next week and remember
to head over to the three-time instagram
it's at threesome usa we have ah
our intern is chain i don't know
what is true someday i hope it's
not by the i'm actually out of
this recording we got a firesale and
i think we're going to it's how
you fire satan i don't know he's
trying to eat us
us a lot is going wrong yeah
yeah why did he even enter the
race to become an intern that's what
you gotta easily have enough to do
yeah you know yeah i know it's
tempting every single person every single minute
of the day guy in the contest
with a criteria for the next person
like we wanted someone hot we got
satan that's as hot as it gets
we need to do we need to
think oh what we want you know
what
that is the kind of thing that
st loves his word play like ah
so not like that anymore we want
someone that's extremely attractive objectively beautiful objective
and rich and really smart really smart
yeah really smart beautiful enrich and like
they don't want daily rich because they
don't want think if they're rich it's
good because then they're an unpaid intern
they're not gonna be worried about and
also implies that they're very talented and
made something of themselves is there good
makeup okay wow that's a dangerous way
to think about it so a joe
millionaire type guy that guy that millionaire
oh yeah i'm worried we're gonna get
joe millionaires if we do we do
that
worth it that honestly is risk wow
no argument for that okay so listen
and subscribe to this wherever you get
podcasts you can hear the ad-free version
over on stitcher premium or at cbp
world dot com yeah no i think
we've given you the tools you need
to have a great life it's all
you need it's all you
need teach a man to fish teach
about fish everybody oh gee japan division
this week and everyone sixteen shuttle fish
and keep it as a pet
ugh