three
oh did anybody hear that i was
doing little clicking noises ah yeah paul
we all heard it and we know
what it was so cool so cool
can we learn how to do clicking
noises can you teach me how to
teach you okay how do you think
it's cool how do you do them
i couldn't describe it you could never
discover consisted in nate tell you how
what is
is it how would you describe doing
that i was trying because don't do
that thing like like whim
like like when harlan
williams shares and nevada man and he
drinks the piss out of the bottle
isn't yeah just do that oh yeah
just do that yeah yeah yeah you
do it that's a perfect description thank
you when you have a baby and
they see you doing something they want
to do it too like snapping fucking
annoying and it's impossible my life it's
impossible to discern
tribe how you snap you know what
i mean like press your thumb and
your finger together yeah but where's the
sound coming from it's that's different snapping
as a much more advanced skill yes
yeah but they don't want to do
it but how are like sort of
like if i do like a clicking
thing then she thinks it's funny and
she wants to do that too she's
very into the boing boing song right
now oh really thank you very much
well now you know did you write
the boingboing yeah well first i wrote
the boring song and i was like
this is not good enough and you're
a following go blanco and they said
not enough oiling yeah it starts wow
it's a guy you guys are done
like
a guy your patience is demanding all
time low on ohio i'd say yeah
okay said in just start talking huh
ah so she's into this boys saw
how does it go
there was a few blocks
give us the entire song it's it's
a man it's a man okay sorry
to the man when when one is
asked song goes he says walk and
then it goes do do do do
do do de souza walk around the
room and then he goes tip toe
and then the music changes thirty it's
like sh shit
i always dance like skate that it's
run run is really exciting and then
it's hop and that's when it's boeing
boeing boeing and she's helping them and
so we did that a million times
vary me also did i'm going on
a bear hunt about four hundred times
last night okay someone tried to explain
this to me once shout out to
nicole parker it's her birthday today
happy birthday and she tried to explain
going on a bear hunt to me
and i think she said it was
a game it's a game it's a
song but how is it a good
game can't be a song it's it's
not really a game it's like it's
it's a it's a game that connect
to active song where you're like now
we're going through mud we can't go
over it we can't go under we
go
go through it squish squish squish what
are you doing movements yeah okay in
those days everybody does the same movements
yeah but it seems not by you're
not forced to by law
like you could technically do what do
and everyone from and couldn't arrest you
will not so it's not like the
hokey pokey which is that is mandated
you legally to cause the hokey pokey
holy hokie hokie cokie
are you doing the heat tonight the
hokie cokie by the way there's a
big ass mosquito flight i know i
talk it came in the cayman it
came in through the window and now
it's just like oh cocker yeah huh
this guy
beatles racer
but honestly i haven't really introduced to
a lot of kids songs but she
gets them from school and then she's
very excited about them and so we'll
play them we're trying to get her
to leonard cohen plays music
if you want to listen to but
she and sometimes she likes specific like
pop songs but she's very into these
active songs now so we'll just fine
this year she wants to do a
whole little i can picture doing this
great i mean likes to do the
ones with freeze in it she likes
crazy she's fun and louie for damn
song which i had put on freedoms
page i was just listening to at
the time of making the video but
she also really likes head shoulders knees
and toes and but the problem is
is anytime you see one of these
then it's like more more she wanted
to do it over and over she
was screaming when i turned it off
i'm tired after one maybe in the
middle of the first yeah i mean
i don't want to do it again
i don't i don't
i want to do it again but
it's also very fun she's having fun
again it's fun that she's i i
find it fun that she's having fun
yeah because i always say whoops i
say what did you show me how
you do it yes while i close
my eye
go to sleep forever
or ever
um by the way this is threesome
oh yeah i don't think i ever
have said the title of the show
on the show it's it's called three
we've never once said that think it's
called threesome yeah ah my name's laurie
like this dictionary dot com yeah my
name is rena f tompkins my name
is oscar scott is it
that's right now you know what man
sometimes you play around too much because
people don't really know what point you're
needing i do i do it because
we were giving our real names and
then you come in here like a
clown what's up with that i'm a
clown to you your clone to me
so that's what i am like a
performing clown like a like a circus
clown you're like a circus clown to
me professionally or like legitimately did the
goodfellas seem like we were right to
do it yeah really into it
oh you don't know what that is
never mind never seen that film yeah
it's a movie by scott che it's
a movie about a bunch of good
guys they're good fellows yeah people you
wanna hang out with they always wanted
to be one thing fine fellows what's
the special paper you have that has
these recommendations on
i don't know what that is let
me see what that is watch pass
it up okay you can just throw
it in me too wow he was
really offended okay this is my doctor
that i was talking about a few
episodes back dr feelgood the doctor which
by the way by our next episode
i'll have hopefully some closure on this
foot taking the surgery
well i'm going for the next step
so probably not closure what's the next
step a little guy who follows you
around and keeps poking your foot whenever
it hurts yep
what does that do twenty dollars an
hour makes it feel good to poke
the foot yeah on the nerve it
kind of releases we got me to
poke the foot on the nerve and
releases something nice say i could throw
away this nerd i could throw away
this paper now thank you for pointing
out the way this marker it's dead
zaire two things to do now you're
the trash man trash man i honestly
think here's what needs to happen what
okay so tell us what needs to
happen you need to chug every
a little chocolate alcohol that's right they're
still here everyone throw these away i
want to throw them away with either
your youtube me i couldn't use i
i never said anything but believe those
there that's my snacky and this shows
my snack you stuck your thumb in
your mouth this sort of crisis can't
be good this is a garza pan
clad oh no it's mars
ben gladwin throw all of ours a
pan classic i'm opening it up it's
chocolate it's turning the garza school vu
i'm doing this hallway but i need
you to have one more shot here
am i gonna drink
garza pair alright but we have a
garbage pile of alice exciting what you
look at mama stay through what is
this candy it's it's called shoplift now
this one's good trash cleanups that's it's
eleven hambali that oh thank you so
much rp coby
the blackman enough eleven o eleven ma
larry bird
ah larry bird weird guy what was
his nickname
yeah it's right it's right there like
i know it's needed but he should
never hurt third man the birdman he
was playing basketball very familiar with growing
up why i was very aware of
him my brother had an an action
figure or whatever like a little missionary
well it wasn't actually figured it was
like a baseball player on like a
little circular desk you know like mid
shock statue but it was
the action figure figurine yeah this is
okay was opposable or no no figuring
figuring yeah and i just played with
that so that was you know it
felt like he's one of the mains
at that point we had jordan we
had dennis rodman where you're from chicago
area yes larry bird is not no
boston but
he but he was talked about he
was so good muddy bogs when i
was a kid that was either just
names that was the era you've seen
space chair of have space jam and
dr jia not in many dr julius
irving write the circular bed having bedded
over twenty five hundred women so where
do you get the shield chamberlain oh
probably where do you get the sheets
maybe i should keep dr jays around
cheap yeah ah i think from bed
bath and around you know how annoying
me to put those on you didn't
you would need two people yeah because
it would always be popping off the
second you get over to the side
it's gonna just go yeah let's slap
liberty flat yeah but a flap or
flip flip flam how are you liking
new pillow top mattress cover that i
recommended an add to cart i didn't
know we changed it well apparently it's
going great okay thank you so much
luck got it ah what's the difference
it's fluffy fluffy like really like mine
wasn't before and i changed and it
is and is your life
if better mine wasn't before and it
changed and it is it is better
it is better it's more comfortable it's
improved your mood it's we see no
evidence of that well god you you
implicate me and the horse you rode
in on when the the first person
to say that most of destroy
so love fucking someone who wrote that
now we all say it because of
that it got such a big world
z yeah how do these things happen
that we all know these phrases like
sit and spin
perfect example when i was given the
title game yea no but then but
then okay i think i had i
think i did she goes into a
movie thanks go up on that thing
goes into a movie like they use
it in a movie where someone was
like put their middle finger up and
said sit and spin yeah and everyone
says it was like in poltergeist or
something probably
oh no that wasn't ghost chat oh
yeah patrick swayze yep he was in
all movies about ghosts yeah he's to
listen yeah he's in the show goes
now it makes sense yeah was just
such a good movie didn't watch the
first guy we did echo didn't what
do you mean she's the one that's
two never
watched the movie she didn't watch it
she was like yeah i've never seen
it she like didn't understand the premise
i guess or something i guess not
she just didn't watch he seemed very
confused it really yeah when you ask
that is really funny
i go i love i go oh
yeah you know we love you why
what are we doing here and what
is your pizza commercials inspire me her
instagram is very funny yeah i think
her issues raised are fun are are
funny friend eg odom her stories are
always like well i fucked up and
did this thing
yeah i know
we did wheel of fortune together which
was very fun that was fun i
enjoyed watching the show they wouldn't she
walked on i didn't know who was
going to be there and you were
there with the roadmaster jeff ross he
didn't even roast me i guess i
roasted him by winning a lot more
money for my cheering
shut the lock up his charity was
lease olymp and hilly
hey what does comedy central do now
i don't know i don't think it's
a channel anymore they do the daily
show on so no i mean oh
i forgot about the daily show and
the jon stewart he's bad boy but
he's back and he's back just for
a brief thing right for once will
the election once a week until the
election we need him and do they
somewhat have a regular host now
no it's the news team does the
rest of the i mean this may
have changed by the time this comes
out but wait like people what do
you mean it's like jordan does will
then do the other four jordan klepper
he's really woody junior or um don't
use anymore joy with thy were coming
up at the same time in chicago
day who was jordan club program who
was going down
go in da can't remember their names
that are gone i'm i'm sorry i
was really
you haven't person transfer reference to love
an elevator he like a punch in
the stuff i didn't get it but
you're you're upset because they sing the
song janie's got a gun which we
i'm upset because using this i don't
know why you're upset about that because
it's a song about your wife it's
not about her how many times have
just see this she was the original
chinese na
not the genie in the song which
janie lie you don't know that you
don't know and to prove that i
guess that's what bothers does she have
any guns she's got a gun okay
so genius guy good cheney's got ah
hey god so what was the single
gong she's chinese gotta god did she
do everything in the song love in
an elevator is so dumb
oh in na i don't know that
song i love beta live it up
full of go away okay aerosmith there
la yeah so aerosmith was like nah
that can't be that long of a
ride like here's what happened well it
was the first champion aerosmith was almost
dead they were so some career was
dead
did they come back with two songs
which are future smashes right about skywalker
stuff what about fucking in an elevator
and the other about ah trans gentleman
or vice food looks like a lady
yes which they should not sing anymore
do they still sing it probably probably
yeah who's gonna stop em you and
they're making mrs doubtfire and they were
like this is perfect oh no did
the use of sucks yeah i will
never see that movie you've never seen
it never have never will hear you're
missing out i know everything i want
to know drive by fruiting no no
no no no no no the no
pi in the
yeah here's what i saw i saw
good movie it no it's not small
lauren i'll fight you i've i've seen
the very beginning of i don't care
about actually fighting i've seen the very
beginning sally field where he's doing the
cartoon releasing the cartoon voices so insane
and so irrelevant the thing is already
animated and he's improvising relevant you can
do character this is your
jaw but you should know that you
can't do that it's okay it's not
irrelevant i just have to say that
because people are like it's not real
because the whole point is that he
does a character the entire time so
that's why you need to know that
he does voices i get that yeah
but here's that to be bad at
it but sally field gives an amazing
i'll just watch her in like whole
time the whole time the whole time
i go i know wow it is
the bat i know everything i need
to
no the whole time the whole time
the holes arm see it's going out
i've seen those perfect hey look up
print i try using usually obey i'd
love to do one where i'm dressed
like old lady the whole time his
face in the whip cream tits catch
on fire you have seen it i've
seen everything it was in the everything
i was any good about it we've
seen already have one his face mask
gets run over in the street flights
out the window flies a little because
harvey what's named harvey weinstein weinstein
is final screen this zebra
i wasn't i wasn't hurt gorman harvey
dent harvey da you know who that
is no idea very very intense ah
harvey why can't why can we think
visiting r v harmel a coma no
no it's like a very famous person
i'll look at what the fuck is
going on here his um his mm
movie come on ah yes i can
only think of every other new hire
steam army
a harvey weinstein advise a hobby liars
he agreeable so great and dude looked
like a trilogy this right
um so so so so you're saying
it's not a perfect film
any film is good when you're five
if you watch i know and that's
the honestly that's ninety percent of what
i think about
ah
actually small group of your smart i
yeah have to say
yeah to see if this is your
first episode of freedom law actually i'm
actually smart smart were joking around but
i cannot let that stand i'm smart
i'm sorry okay that being said i'm
smart college graduate i did do that
and neither of you did yeah you're
the only college graduate out of the
three of us and it shows me
one in three freedoms as college
graduate oh you know what i thought
of today what because i read it
in a book yeah right
the good book
in this book somebody said it because
it's set in the in the past
and somebody said that all books are
set in the past otherwise we wouldn't
be reading about it is it something
about a book that says this is
happening right now as you read this
yeah what is it bright lights big
cities with what's written in second per
second second person yeah emily but would
be great if it's like so while
you're reading this
this happened you're reading this book and
now you're doing this and you start
doing it oh my god that voodoo
high school um somebody said drop dead
and what a fucking hilarious trying to
say to somebody yeah honestly say that
i think that's better than fucking in
the horse you rode if you said
that to like a stranger who is
being rude the drop they'll be really
fun
any drop dead it's wild thing to
say it would be really good yeah
absolutely i was watching close encounters of
the third kind ah i was wondering
which kind and it as you were
talking with one too that was seventy
to go through all the kinds yeah
seventy eight maybe and it's so funny
to watch it and it's like oh
yeah
yeah this is it could be now
it's it's taking place but then someone
cuts off richard dreyfus in his car
and richard dreyfus rolls down the window
and flips them off and goes you
turkey
and i was like okay this could
only be happening in nineteen seventy eight
but that is when that was like
a good enough insult where people would
go the very idea of calling me
a turkey but like if someone call
me that now it would be funny
but it would also be like off
putting because it's like what do you
think they were flipping me off and
calling me a trigger like why are
you saying turkey like you flipped me
off yeah
thirty six eighty enough yes yeah because
one day you know an equitable one
is saying fuck you yes and the
other is going you're a turkey
gobble gobble mister turkey what if you
started saying gobble gobble to people oh
yeah whenever lie that there's someone cuts
you off in traffic and you and
you roll down your window you catch
up with amigo gobble gobble would be
so good i'm going to start getting
cut off in traffic so i can
do yes you're gonna start driving really
the slow yeah all of a sudden
yeah alright we have to take a
break okay
and we're back yeah man gobble gobble
gobble gobble gobble one of us right
now ball gobble beach it's like like
the new thing pretty soon oh i
thought it was like free thanksgiving sure
leprechaun should be afraid of cooker yeah
i think it means thanks shall i
carve
you know i want to make these
tighter so that barrel be making you
tired
you want to go to sleep trip
to work bitch
shutter hit us up come on i'll
make these will star in them oh
my god yeah well i mean what
would it take to do that million
billion trillion dough i do i do
it for scale you do for fifteen
hundred dollars a week acting scale for
the producing writing of course that's two
million dollars and have to talk marriage
and yeah
yeah what else so freddy's thanksgiving so
jason freddy easter
i think everybody gets one out to
brunch yeah everyone gets chucky is easter
turkey's easter egg has like the bunny
ears and he's like yea yeah his
famous catchphrase yeah
i never seen jackie i never have
either it's it's one you don't have
to see don't i see saw the
first one i can't you must've and
the is the mom and the one
from seventh heaven oh i hope so
oh my god the bathroom hicks we
talked about um heartthrob anderson and the
instagram account why we have not talked
i think we've texted about him
he's so funny and does recaps of
like old nineties tv and movies and
stuff and like calls out hope sir
they are and he did a bunch
on seventh heaven and they were so
funny and one of them was like
a clip where the moms like to
the dad she's like i smoked weed
once it's like so in today's to
watch that show so much just saw
that clip again today
a for i can't remember why it
came up it's the most like and
there's another one where like look on
his face girl steals like a cup
from a diner than they have a
trial they like go to court it's
like insane
you are right the child's play starred
ah catherine hicks who we also know
as dr gillian taylor from star trek
for the voyage home sure sure sure
sure sure sure sure sure okay so
chuck is easter
jason muscat christmas yeah yeah jason so
famous michigan what about michael myers was
it should he get halloween i'm not
sure there can't be a whole jason
can be helloween buddy and loves it
so much i know but we gotta
eat it's kind of what's gonna be
the holidays we celebrate gerber daisies always
hiding behind the trees of course july
fourth to july or the
oh valentine's day sweets that is sweet
yeah i just wanna do something nice
for him and then i those like
the big ones right yeah i guess
you got candyman he'd be halloween that's
scary and maybe i can get halloween
i don't think there should be a
halloween i think how we should be
a non helloween character santa it started
like chewbacca your empire swear where
they say like that's the one day
that the vampires don't go out is
halloween is halloween i don't remember that
because what is the reason i can't
remember what it was but it made
sense but it also made sense to
justify like why all these kids in
summer summer veil everything sunnydale can go
out at night not beaten by vampires
every
and this is a town where people
acknowledge the vampire town they end up
doing so they know that they live
at home i'm aimee mann herself um
lives in her mouth she ah she
appears in an episode of buffy the
vampire slayer and that's right i think
like the second last season and then
as she is leaving with her bandmate
she goes i hate playing vampire
towns yeah so love notes vampire town
that's fun people still live there and
they still travel a new show well
they're huh
interest rates are low the housing market
is you know you can get a
pretty decent sized i guess so you
know you buy a house for two
hundred and fifty dollars yeah if it
it is if you guys ever wanna
move to the desert know why move
into the desert hey want to move
to the desert you want to do
that and become nyse you want a
horse with no name yeah i don't
want to live there at all really
what about scorpion i don't even want
to go there
that don't even want to go there
not even much at all not even
once more i'd go there i'm going
to go there more
i'm going to go there a bunch
more i'm sure but i just really
don't really care what about the sahara
desert know it takes up so much
but even joshua tree ha ha yeah
no deal like to go to palm
springs um i i have had fun
there i don't go there actively
i don't really know end up there
here's the thing i don't know the
town at all because i only go
in like get near bnb with a
group of people yes and then you
never leave yes and there's a pool
or something but like it i am
curious to go and like walk around
the shops and whatnot that would be
maybe fun do you know if i
can buy there you can buy here
but but it might be fun we
have that at home
we are great to travel with ah
we used jamie i used to go
um in the summer to the parker
yeah in august because it was a
thousand degrees and so they'd have these
amazing deals and then they sort of
realised oh people come anyway yeah let's
because back to the regular prices and
then we stopped going that sucks yeah
really does suck but it was great
it was like a very felt like
a very grown-up place yeah know what
i mean and we would spend most
of the time just as telling the
hole and everything you guys feel like
you're not grownups most of the time
i sort of feel like that
um yeah i guess emotionally yeah sometimes
it catches me by it catches me
off guard where like i'm still worried
about that the fuck what's i thought
i'd be past that yeah that's interesting
but i guess just like mentally you
think about yourself like i think i
feel like it's sort of still a
kid in a way i don't know
i think i do i feel like
i think
myself as like in my thirties yeah
young virile
yeah i think i'm full of comey
writing him in maybe a different point
right now where it's like it's crystallizing
that i am an adult and like
i'm going like oh i'm like i
have like a job and kids and
like i mean we are in a
profession that leads to emotional stunting yeah
you know
where we don't have to know emotionally
stunting yeah i'm emotionally threatened on your
out don't emotionally cent on me but
you know what i mean like i
wonder if everyone feels like that yeah
i mean wait a minute i i
feel like i was just twenty yeah
sure and i'm still act you know
alright yeah i think it's weird too
because it's that thing and i feel
like i've
tried to describe in life where i
like it where you sort about your
as your own god i can't oh
my god or is smart she said
she was always like that little kitty
she lied and then when you and
then you and then you
but i was thinking about how
yeah my older relatives for type ooh
we know throw towing you talk right
now when you have to take one
tibbs and you're like you sort of
think that they know everything because they're
like adults yes and then you grow
up and you start to understand like
they are r fifty for the first
time in sixty for the first time
it's not that they ever experienced anything
any of this before just like i
am figuring everything out and it's such
a mind-blowing thing even though it's very
obvious but i feel like i have
that over and over about like everyone
and like myself yeah that it's like
oh i feel like i'm the only
one who like doesn't know what's going
on or something then you're like everyone
doesn't know yeah
yeah i think about todd classes joke
about you know like you used to
be when you when you were young
and you were imitating someone who was
fifty you'd be like yeah i'm fifty
years old yeah and now you see
people who are fifty or they're like
hi i'm fifty i'm in a band
but a big reason for that is
because when we were young imitating people
who were fifty people who are fifty
did talk like that because they
i smoked for fifty years wild hell
people looked aged much here so ah
yeah it really has like even like
the golden girls yeah and thanks even
damn boy this supposed to be like
like so like not that old yeah
show like they're not cool because one
of them was the mother and was
like eighty right the rest were like
fifty five yeah but they were like
hey
or maybe you know just just gobble
my grandma had like the same hair
like she kind of always remind me
of rose from golden girls and i
think just betty white neural but she
she had the same look going back
to when i was a baby to
like the end of her life like
full on last thirty plus thirty years
she looks basically the same yeah because
the style was so so which now
it looks old-fashioned yeah it's like it's
what we associate with old lady but
then you're like but that was the
style that everyone is just so confusing
yeah it's like make everyone get away
with my hair and i'm like you've
had that hair since you were thirty
it's old person seemed like ever
i gave up on people once they
hit forty i remember like my father
gave up on people meaning like you
you no longer have to be fashionable
you know you know like there's no
pressure to be fashionable anymore there's you
know like we're gonna stop making interesting
clothes for you like and father of
the bride they're like forty something or
something like
oh wow like but they look so
much older yeah yeah mature yeah no
but i mean even like i was
remembering how my father had a over
the hill party on his forty yeah
what his fortieth birthday which ended up
being like you know very precise down
to down to the year
but ah but ah because he was
forty so they nailed it pretty his
birthday exactly right
no he passed away when he was
seventy nine so yes yes i yeah
wasn't trying to force you to say
that but he but i think there
was that was a period that were
forty over the hill like those black
like decorations yeah that that stopped being
forty like more recently yeah no i
mean now people used to retire at
fifty oh
we get the gold one now we
went to ea yeah yeah now we
work now eric idle still has to
work
not so idle or man eric working
more liars please what are the pythons
like one of the things about having
old parents too is that they stay
looking the same for a long time
and then all of a sudden they're
like oh they look old i feel
like it happens that happened to me
in the last two years know about
your own parents are about
no just me looking yeah like i
mean never got to see the younger
handsome me i see it in pictures
i'm going to show me pictures of
myself shoes
mister show clips show watch the video
see that montoya i do have a
lot of video out there yeah not
no video podcasts um i i'm shocked
when i see pictures of myself from
ten years ago me feel like wow
i actually feel like some like oh
i just didn't realize so you seem
like that much time yeah that my
even pictures from ten
sixteen were on tour i'm like that's
i look my whole thing about pictures
zero always obsessing about how bad you
look in pictures when when you look
at the ones you just took and
then you see them even two years
later and you're like wistful of like
why don't i look back yeah oh
absolutely so you should always just be
happy with the pictures that you take
because you're gonna look even worse in
one year that is true
it's true although some people get better
looking that's true that's true dr baloney
i had a glow up then i
had to go down you know i
had a period of maybe five years
radical
and then i started eating again maybe
you'll have another one i'm back at
the gym it's been back to good
it makes me feel good but it's
fucking it's hard yeah it's tough stuff
oh i'm working with a um sort
of personnel not i wouldn't say personal
trainer because it's not that it's a
it's basically awesome skills or therapist so
saying
who and everyone can look her up
because she's on my m instagram your
hearth healing because i will promote her
um because she's great but she creates
a personal like workout thing from your
everyday little while i'm pregnant and then
postpartum which i'm really excited about because
it's a really hard recovery or it
was for me and i'm hopeful that
this will make me feel better but
it's like such ah even
just doing a little stretches every day
i'm like oh it's a lot it's
so hard to to do it is
the problem like yeah like after you
do it while you're doing is fine
after you do it you're like feel
good you feel good where you like
i did that today and you feel
sort of better about yourself but just
hours before you do it where you're
like i don't want i don't want
to do it i don't want it
yeah i mean do you have like
ways that you keep yourself accountable well
it used to be we talked about
this on the show it used to
be the the streaks
the political history oh i'm like you
have a fifty two week streak or
whatever like that that would keep you
again then i don't i talked about
how when our power went out i
wasn't able to continue my streak so
i cheated and then people are like
well it's not a streak no the
point is to keep yourself going yeah
so if i yeah if i didn't
cheat in order to like keep my
streak going because
my power went out and i didn't
yeah to suddenly have a sixty week
streak be race course that counts yeah
it's insane samsung nothing that you did
all the other stuff yes yeah i
am ah jenny i'm an apple watch
ah how many years ago is now
and that is was like three hundred
years ago i think
yeah weird i'm sure
your your name is hg wells idiot
um but i i like getting the
um the little fireworks when you felt
when you complete all the ring oh
i've never i've never achieved whatever the
rings want me to do it's fucking
the green deal yeah the queen bee
of fitness yeah it's interesting it's very
satisfying what do you what do you
do get the rings you have to
close
close your unlucky size movement and stand
circles and always tells me to stand
i'm like yeah you idiot
i gotta get get one of those
again because an apple watch forbidden it
would like especially when i was editing
shows that's especially when you have it
but it would it would be like
you've got to stand yeah and my
coworker would always make me she's like
what's that on your watch okay you
got us wow
well and i feel like we're turned
down that feature with this thing i'm
doing with um this i guess you'd
call her personal fitness coach um it's
very nice there's this app and i
i get i get a little like
applause you know it's like it's the
same thing yes yeah if i click
the button and do the thing shit
really works and i honestly had a
day where i was like
like i could lie and i was
like why lie
said hell who write benefits i could
say i'm paying her exactly tell me
to do this exam and then i'm
going to say i did it like
it's so i really am honest if
i don't do something i don't do
it yeah but i bet it annoys
me so yeah yeah yeah but also
like these little tricks that you do
to you like on the peloton it'll
tell you who's there in taking the
class
at the same time as you and
people you know no no it's just
famous people yeah
um but on this day martin luther
king took this class
um but it but it like then
you sit there going like oh i
wonder if i could beat this person
that i don't know right i won't
even know i beat them because they
finished the class ten minutes ago but
it just like gives you that oomph
to like oh yeah try hard like
the inflight trivia game
you're playing against what's the name of
twenty-three be like i'm going to fucking
crush yeah yeah yeah i don't know
if i would like i mean i
i thought i was gonna get a
peloton at one point but because i
was going to give it to you
yeah oh honey i'm still using mine
know because there was one we're gonna
do an ad and i thought they
would get oh sounds familiar it didn't
happen all the time
we would love to be sponsored by
you and i've talked about you on
this show several times it's true so
you always kind of you do oh
it is the one thing i've kept
going yeah eminem zos is big time
ama now we gave them so much
free advertising yes we said some of
their products so well some of the
steelers are too much
yes and they know they know way
oh well they don't sell they know
they know when they put that out
there shrugging there's yeah i don't know
i don't know key lime we should
move on from marzah murray's and then
do it like a lateral move to
hershey's kisses because i had some really
delicious hershey's kisses we made some bad
ones recently right i don't really like
like raspberry and no no i don't
like that cherry woo but i like
cook christmas cookie was so good fuck
yeah it does yeah paw is it
meant to you you're lying right now
yeah you're a fucking lie remember when
they brought out those swirls those that
peppermint swirl one that was like chocolate
that was good it was just so
fancy looking in the hugs
that's what they're called hugs hugs yeah
have you read the book huh ugh
you women put out drugs oh my
god and they smoking dogs yeah yeah
her she's put out crack okay i
distinctly remember taking the dare program at
school what happened there what did you
do so it was during science class
because i know that's where i
i was i didn't sign it would
be like dare you not to do
something that's yeah that's not how dares
work we had a staff that had
littles like dudes are really excited not
to take drugs
what does it stanford drugs drugs are
really really exciting because
no but there's always like we dare
you not to do drugs no deres
right i don't maybe do something more
i dare t shirt in high school
of course that's funny yeah but in
middle school i really didn't know anything
about it no and then they give
you workbooks that have little cartoons and
the situations and so the schools to
party and this is going to happen
what did she say what should she
do parties
are never that exciting that's the thing
no one's ever have you been in
a party when anyone's come up to
you and said hey do you wanna
try some cocaine
um no but remember when pockets came
up to me and offered me opium
oh pokal pocket ah fuck it i
don't think anyone's ever offered me cocaine
but maybe they will miss square these
workbooks make it sound like every single
party you're going to go to was
like people trying to push cocaine on
you i wish people would try to
give me cocaine like every part
i go to his boring i'll turn
it down just just to spruce things
i just used my kids up just
to make it like a cool party
and actually that the the phrase the
term workbook sends a shiver down my
spine yeah because that meant what i
had news what if i assigned you
workbooks at the end of each three-day
wouldn't you still do that with sai
no i'd have you arrested actually
if you kill what we kind of
want you to get into coke i
want that too lord is fun i
want you to go have something going
on right now or really want you
just to be sucked into my life
and then we like find out like
a long time into even doing coke
law and then we're like oh kinda
makes sense i guess because we wanted
him to
yeah alright we have to stick huh
wow
we're back oh god and it's three
your time it's three church time everybody
you all everybody driveshaft go hey i
know what that is that is trying
to shake bands oh with noise it's
awesome law makes great fake brass
and from break brown flush i did
watch lost and i like that show
a lot
well we're gonna play three turn you
know how these work people send them
to us at our email at three
dm usa at gmail dot com that's
correct scott
oh my gosh and then we play
on in game
did i make you yawn i hope
so
they make this gone baby
we're gonna play one we haven't played
in a while
we used to play this on comedy
bang bang i think i found that
move movie funny when i watched it
and i wonder if i was embarassing
and that was the first one's really
huh i wonder if i was offended
we we at the austin powers franchise
thank you for all i'm so of
course i forgot to the frenzy austin
powers royalty star in goldfinger
ember remember
um okay this is what am i
thinking
okay yeah now how this what this
is is we each say a word
at the same time we say three
to one and then say the word
now it can it doesn't have to
be one word it just has to
be a thing it can be bugs
bunny for instance um it just it
just has to be one thing or
one ima
motion or one you know what i
mean it just has yes yes yes
but it can be more than one
word okay but you can't be like
a sentence where bugs bunny went down
to the you know what i mean
why whatever
but i just want to make sure
like this because they say see because
i know it doesn't mean that let's
start bucks buddy went down to the
how do i do this folks but
you would doe to guru remember that
cartoon where bugs bunny wins too
i love that one looks like we're
down to the
that a lot of it in books
buddy i'm going down to something you
just georgia super soldier yeah i think
he only walked down horizontal planes but
boy did the ga you looking for
source yes there is a cartoon of
that was bugs funny actually satan
fuck you can we get into that
later and elmer fudd is actually like
you don't have been with that right
now
elmer fudd is like constantine hunting devils
you might get into it late on
a future app or after the i
just mean like i look i can't
talk about but yeah i'm good how
can we can we just do this
and then we'll get into that
and nobody will forget
let's talk about it i want to
talk about
what was that big guy who's like
a big furry red thing to tasmania
devil know he has a gossamer as
his name and see the devil because
he's red because he's orange creepy he's
q okay
it's bugs me the devil because why
what are your theories bushmen the devils
because
just kind of appears and he goes
down to georgia he lives underground he
lives by the way but basically we're
done with both go down to the
way we did
if it was fun
oh we have to play the game
do we we have to it's a
structure so heavily on my mind meld
yeah commonly it's called my yeah
to teach my uncle this over christmas
why
yeah right nearby
i just looked uncle let me teach
you hey i knew it didn't work
what we're gonna do work with an
uncle we're going to do it three
ways it was a big it was
a order and it's hard enough with
two people were going to do it
three-way animal style animal stuff that's right
toe is the word that you did
to get your fries double charred ah
weldon weldon zuko
well um so we we each separately
say a word just can be vastly
different probably and then ah we say
three to one and we tried to
come up with a word that is
in-between all three of the words like
i'd like we all will say the
same thing and we were trying to
get it to where all three of
us say the same word at the
same time
now the last time we played this
excuse me it sucked it's like red
oh okay great you love to remember
things that way did we yeah i
do
did we ever do it who who
knows who knows i don't remember playing
this with you guys let's do it
let's do it okay so we're going
to each separately say do you have
your thing in mind no wait any
word at all anywhere at all you
think it was like what delta
i know i wanted to say that
first i was like let's get the
giggle also
um start with a win i think
that's good okay ready yeah three two
one but oh okay i say banana
purple and bugs bugs banana purple bugs
okay i got mine me too okay
i'm i'm three two one eight last
ny you and i said a plant
you said beetle okay so you're kind
of obsessed that the whole bug thing
you have going
okay beetle and eggplant ready oh we
have it okay beetle and egg plant
we'll wait for you sure okay okay
three two wide voting guys and okay
you said volkswagen i said ringo you
said george harrison george harrison okay george
harrison ringo and volkswagen
ah ok got it thirty three two
one yellow submarine what did you say
you say we said yellow submarine
what did you say
it wasn't the same result but to
say java is it paul mccartney paul
mccartney paul mccartney and yellow submarine okay
i got ah you don't get say
um ok i got i got mine
alright three two one joanne kay john
lennon album album john lennon album okay
alright i got mine i got mine
oh god oh god this guy
okay all around specs three to one
imagine yea we did it that was
awesome good wait let's do it again
wait let's do it again
we can feel that high another time
we're not uncles
hi guys go okay ready no hello
okay no alright alright three two one
hardline cardboard airplane uncle uncle cardboard airplane
and uncle interesting cardboard airplane okay
and uncle it carp just say okay
okay okay three two one hobby lee
hobby fester hottie lab stanley
okay three two one howl traps and
webs you said travels at harold harold
harold webs and travel okay okay three
two one spiderman i just had spider
oh hey spiderman the fuck is wrong
with you okay spider
spiderman okay what's in between spider and
spider-man i got it three two one
peter parker oh i said wow peter
parker and web three two one five
he's married again and you said when
somebody already said it i didn't know
no what did you say just now
it's okay shoe spiderman and shoots three
two one wax ah that was good
were crawling games are sowing my email
did you guys you smashed it let's
do as most do no one here
we go i have mine
i have mine at my three two
one wow can i say guitar i
said rock ocean
three oh hold on hold on man
hold on hold on hold on hold
on is it's not three two one
barely ocean and sailing
so i couldn't think of anything let's
say you said billy okay five billion
ocean so we all won well let's
do another one okay let's do another
one um ok three three two one
z okay i said lamppost at atlantic
cv
lamppost atlantic s uv
lamppost atlantic okay s uv three two
one i three my lord
okay i said cigarette light is that
what you call surrendering your your lighter
cigarette lighter you said henry ford henry
ford ice too
okay as umi z for you
okay so i see cigarette lighter and
henry ford henry ford
okay three two one chain model t
adventure and invention
okay three two one j yo i
said we'll use heel i said jay
leno wheel and jay leno oh okay
we got this
come on three guys what are you
going nuts don't
because he gives out voted to australia
now because he's driving around doing donuts
but we'll jay leno don't okay so
go right you say garage to know
i said good i say what did
you say you sir i said car
oh okay car garage donuts okay three
two one
rs wheelies repairs mechanic mechanic okay three
e o motorcycle and would you say
fancy fancy and motorcycle three two one
k
jack i said hey what do you
say happy days happy days a leather
jacket here we go three two one
five k did you say the thorn
birds teamers
for we said fonzie and the tiber
come on we got this three two
pinky
darrow
i could just
ah oh good stuff we did i
think we won i think we i
think we why they were gone we
definitely want your circling around yeah need
whoever we were playing yeah those people
another real money yeah we're saying well
anyway i assume that the audience is
doing this yeah the data like yeah
okay so one guy
better luck next time that was good
if you like sos three-tier write to
us three team usa gmail dot com
if you'd like to leave us a
voicemail a little question to ask us
or something to prompt further conversation for
our three meme episodes while they wanted
to leave us a voicemail on the
website a popular website yeah pag claims
eight dot com everyone's going to this
website
strange because we put it out there
and we were like let's make a
website for this and then suddenly we
were like the traffic on this is
through the roof honestly we should put
ads on there i did turn off
alerts on my phone yeah because i
kept getting all alerts little dings all
alerts because of amber alert that came
out the other day it was like
there's a little girl missing also more
people are going that glyphosate dot com
like again i'm gonna deal with any
of this yeah it's sort of mocking
another person goes aggravated flood alert i
don't want to know
um and these three meme episodes by
the way there which i mentioned there
every other week on wednesdays and i'm
only in it to i was just
really really quiet there's only two ways
to get weird channel three you're smart
there's only two days ago and you
can listen to him at cb world
or you can go to apple podcasts
premium you can listen to a mirror
that seems fair yeah
and then also on tuesdays we re-release
our old episodes that are all behind
a paywall all the old episodes are
at cb world um dot com but
ah we re-release them weekly and that's
called three visiting on the two and
that's just fun name and it isn't
it's very easy remember it's so easy
to remember there's literally no way you
could forget it like ask me what
it is but
is it three visiting on the tubes
of course i remember it crushed it
he remembers i remember these absolutely radical
isn't milking stickers but oh shit maybe
it's not that etc count is forgetting
i just know what you're talking about
yeah okay no i'm talking about three
visiting on the two oh it's three
visitor on the two seat j impossible
to forget and paul easy to remember
possible what is it
what are we talking about the same
thing yeah yeah three visiting on the
right yes everyone knows obviously reminders didn't
forget yeah i know and i liked
that about you
so we're gonna be back you next
way you why you relayed away a
ah dude i barely know you
i gotta go alright y'all gotta try
these chocolate alcohol into the trash will
you throw everything in the trash and
yang the marker that you apparently hate
ah go by fire by