three
after this
oh wow what is that i don't
know what i'm hearing from um interesting
hi everyone welcome misread them spooky that
certainly was some things some spooky shit
welcome to a very special halloween episode
yes this few months early may helloween
and spring we do this every year
everyone loves it
as soon as the weather turns warm
put on your heavier boxes with cloaks
on cloaks yes put shit on your
face like sun clogs on clothes
gets close all the way down um
i wanna know who the oldest and
youngest listeners of three damar yes lauren
as a survey is the time for
three-time survey are you an old let
us know i want there to be
someone who is in their nineties who
listens to three them mindset do you
fart dust too far
deaths
yuck
you say oh you say it's her
laura drove dad was inappropriate i do
not like that that was gross can
i say something happened before we started
rolling that i do not care for
i'm sorry oh my god scholarship just
before he pushed record
he said do we have any topics
now no wait we've never done that
you do know you do know we
don't ever have to know but no
one even when we're talking we don't
have topics you know there's never a
top but see now we've turned this
into a topic so it didn't show
because i got scared
actually i do have a topic i
o c so sometimes we come with
something we want i've got a couple
topics actually we never discuss that now
we are now registered to keep that
sorry i've ever brought it wasn't appropriate
way let me do the jingle for
laurel that's right get out of the
way she's got something to say it's
time for law
rins topics thank you okay done today's
topics i was like reading from her
hearing wrote these down and this is
a true segment on today's topics i
would like to refer to the streatham
usa instagram page where scott made an
announcement this week
oh yes yeah right would you want
to you jerks did yes what are
you talking about the sky god how
this is for anyone who doesn't follow
or use instagram i just want to
explain what it is to hot for
dionne warwick said she she's on twitter
she's probably on instagram she's on instagram
she wanted to talk to somebody the
person who owns instagram because she had
a quest everyone hard
is to get in touch with instagram
oh my god well okay scott put
a hot being hot pink background and
he wrote just to get his attention
and he wrote i just wanted to
say thanks for following us it means
so much to me i love you
all so much love scott yeah i
thought that was so nice i thought
it was so nice when i saw
it and i was like
like this is so kind and sweet
because we do love you so much
but i liked that it was just
from sky and it wasn't an april
fool's joke it was a couple days
before he was living the mass down
a little bit and you know because
god is it there's a softie in
there so there's some comments i just
want to kind of like share i
love that a lot
lot of people knew it was one
of you guys and then there are
people who genuinely were touched by this
so i just want to read someone
the nice comments those are the people
that were like detectives like it sounds
like lauren but it could be paul
like yeah i wonder who were like
i don't know if scott wrote this
ah the show um okay so some
people just wanted to share some of
the nice comments we got great jordan
bailey says we love you too scott
um
now it makes me wish i did
write it in small documents so wait
a minute rice joshua
smalley is that are josh blink twice
if you're being held hostage open look
at my plants i'm not here for
you scott wow that's mean but it's
a kidding or am i oh i'm
looking at those plants regardless peter pelosi
said scotland love you it may say
wait a minute if i'm nice then
people are nice
back yeah somebody yeah yeah well we
love you too this is a revolutionary
grow we love you too what's the
little miss birdie wrote we love you
too scotty ox oh little birdie
so what it was you lord
yeah i like road i love you
too lauren pretend to be sky yes
yes yes i honestly i wrote that
and then i just laughed my bad
leg and she's seventy and then i
left my bed i have two to
like crying i don't even know why
i did it and i just i
just couldn't stop laughing i think i
caught up to it for i was
hoping you win today because i know
that
but cool up like did i but
i thought that was really funny ah
good luck i enjoyed it and then
the comment drooling and i was like
crying the comments because like some of
them were just so somewhere and somewhere
funny and then i even thought the
the genuine ones were being funny because
i she got it yeah it was
just that was gonna be laugh is
a nice mix bad i just loved
it i love the whole experience i
do love them
ah that was love is an emotion
you know i would call my i
would call my dad every year on
father's day and on his birthday and
we would have should be those should
be combined into one for you or
if you're a father fathers is now
your birthday yeah it's a lot easier
well yeah my dad's birthday is pretty
soon after father's day such a vollmer
it's hard to give a go
gift to a dad i think it
should be abolished as well kid yeah
oh no no no no racecar bottle
my dad i mean i feel like
i just get him like i mean
i'm getting a little more creative now
but it's it feels like when i
was growing up it was like wow
what do you get your dad it's
like sex toy well hey guys here's
why i would
strange here's what i would call them
and never got him a gift when
i was a little kid probably i
did yeah yeah but i would call
him to have an awkward conversation with
this weird man
as your dad's personality is zero like
just like nobody say on the phone
like hi paul it was just it
was awkward iso just awkward it was
like hey son you call me son
yeah yeah and it all led up
to me saying i love you at
the end and then wondering what he
was gonna say back and what were
some options like just now
nothing ah thank you oh yeah i
appreciate that oh wow some jeans you
love you i'm gonna say probably yes
he did say at one time and
i was totally unprepared for it because
i had friends and house and it
was father's day i was like oh
shit i gotta call my dad and
i called him and have the awkward
conversation that i say
said i love you dad and he
said well i love you too and
then i was like oh no i'm
gonna die yes so there's people here
wow well that definitely that definitely so
he just he didn't say it there
was one year where he loved it
he couldn't say it he couldn't he
was from a different time is from
a different tie when they didn't say
those kinds of things it was it
was it truly like what's the cutoff
for people who would never like age
cut-off of the generation
and who fathers were not would never
say i love you that is a
thing isn't it yeah i think it's
i think it i think it depends
on i don't think it depends on
your generation i think it depends on
how you were raised yeah maybe i
think it was prob but i i
do think that was probably more common
my dad was great yeah yeah
and it was probably more common i
also think that there's a gender thing
where he could probably say more easily
to my sisters oh yeah my brothers
right yeah um but it's weird to
think that there's still people out there
now like people like our age that
are that can't do that yeah i
can't say i like your psycho yeah
like that's interesting
yeah my focus or where or how
they were there definitely are tons of
people like that yeah but i mean
i do feel like we and i
want here we're gonna say but i
do feel like we need a neutral
live in a in a community of
people who are more open about feelings
as the joker said we live in
a society
he said it in the snyder cut
trailer but not in the movie earlier
was just too much good stuff to
put in the movie so they had
to put some in the trailer it's
like he's trolling people by putting that
in a trailer when he has no
intention to put a unit yeah i
don't know since i've i i did
think it was funny that instantly people
started sharing george costanza gifts
i was just gonna say that i
think i've note i noticed especially um
um the day of trans is where
we transfer well to yes visibility day
that a lot of my comedian like
improviser friends who are men who are
older than me were posting about it
and i thought this is so cool
because this is like i
just thought like yeah you should but
i also was going i bet you
there's so many men of that age
who would not post something like this
yeah and so i really feel really
grateful to be in a community of
people who are like you know cool
and aware and like um you know
it's not even progressive also woke don't
say woke i certainly wouldn't say that
i don't use that word but i
i i yeah you use the great
awakening doing you woke has been ruined
in any context forever yes yeah i
know and i like everyone i also
think about things no weren't appropriated take
anything fake news woke whatever turned into
an insult and then it just ruins
it forever
you know i was very bad and
lauren i wanna hear what you have
to say i was i was very
embarrassed recently because the the phrase lives
rent-free in my head yeah has been
co-opted by bad people yeah to mean
the absolute opposite of what it suppose
so what does it what does what
explains be positive it's like
love thinking about that little yeah it
started as positive yeah everyone of course
it comes from the african-american communities and
the people were never like white republicans
took it to mean like you think
about trump all the time he lives
rent free in your head oh interests
so stupid yeah i hate us i'd
like to pay rent to things like
this
exactly
well anyway you were just saying that
there's probably men your age who are
like afraid to say i love you
but i feel like i was just
thinking like looking at our community it's
pretty cool like i feel like i
also just wonder if that's an improviser
trait like i was i was looking
at these posts that i was saying
i was thinking like wow these people
are like awesome and like
i don't know do you know i'm
going with this yeah totally hey it
was just especially when you're in comedy
and everything is like so everyone's so
afraid to be earnest yeah right doing
yeah yeah yeah everyone's doing bits back
so yeah having like real conversations yeah
i i do think that that probably
over the last year to helicopter yeah
yeah looking for tom law
zama zama yeah i do think that
especially over the last year people are
more probably more comfortable with being sincere
making that too you know it's just
like we've had a lot of time
to look inward yeah and and also
realize what's important and you know maybe
that's come into sharper folk
this for a lot of us your
dad was in the greatest generation yeah
just the definition of that the people
who went to world war yeah yeah
yeah so your dad was in world
war two yes he was what did
you do fun the pacific in the
navy my grandpa was too he was
everybody's grandpa oh my dad i'm sorry
but because i was you know one
of my
one of the youngest in my right
yes that's when my parents were always
so much older than everybody else and
routinely people thought my parents or my
grandma wow that's gonna happen to me
ah as i'm resigned to it my
dad was in the vietnam war don't
do to do first and back aches
me
sleepy makes you awake
caffeine pills maybe he does
he told me i asked him like
stories about the war a couple of
years ago when we were on a
really long road trip
a lot like um
like aragon like like you were like
five hours and you're like alright tell
me about the right wow
is that he helped people you killed
oh my oh my oh no maybe
i don't know that's what's so crazy
about war i'm not nobody here who
helicopters i don't think crazy part about
war i mean it's like horrifying yeah
he wasn't he wasn't on the on
the gun turret he was like flying
yeah i think he probably didn't but
he
i did say that he came face
to face with people with like a
machine gun or something pointed right out
oh my god and they fired and
it like jammed or something and then
he was able to like sora buying
your sly shotgun ammo my god so
he was like that's the closest thing
terrifying but i really think that we
should have we should still have wars
but they for the hell yeah they
should be fought entirely by robots yeah
that would be nice in a designated
area boxing robots and make it fun
well i think they can shoot each
other and blow each other up well
sure but no one else like boxing
gloves fly off there
like missiles are disconnected from the wrist
i just feel like no matter how
much i think about war i still
have the mentality of like my five-year-old
self or i'm just like why are
we doing stupid be stupid and love
means nothing what's that it's a culture
club song that was like dead
like whatever it was or is whoa
are stupid it's called the war song
and it's just so damn wars yeah
it's so bad it sounds dumb and
like nothing in some strange reason or
something like that
yeah just so weird so here's the
fight over territory it's like what but
you literally are gonna die she thought
was robot wars right now i like
being robot zana when it was settled
by the robots yes then it would
be and everyone had to abide by
it it would be like it would
be like sports it would be like
fun for the world where it's like
well you lost so we get this
land right um for like this
amount of time or whatever but isn't
worry about oppression
well yeah not necessarily land that well
but but the but it is by
when the robots but that's about it
yeah that's part of it but yeah
you oppress you you gather the land
and oppress the people um i don't
i don't know that look i'm not
saying wars grade i'm just saying i
don't think it's going to be a
lot more function yeah just think robots
could really do it well i think
robots this is their chance to shine
but here but why fight each other
not us what if the giant robots
and i'm assuming they're giant oh i
wasn't there but they're fighting guns what
if suddenly a title members right
what if a titan emerges from the
water like a good sky yeah i
do can they fight in the war
i mean they're just as big as
the robots can we then enlisted to
fight in the diner they done well
that's just god i'm trying to talk
real stuff and you're living in a
fantasy land i started watching godzilla vs
kong and kong to you
you feel absolutely
it's majesty i was enjoying myself the
only thing was i felt like khan
looks more real than godzilla i was
buying it more when i entered the
water i was going and i don't
know about that well gods because king
kong is just a bigger version of
a thing that actually exists yeah godzilla
is like a made up thing he's
a made up thing but
i also just have always loved practical
effects like i feel like yeah if
it was just like just a less
amazing shot of godzilla but he was
real looking just like sinister early floating
to the water i just said head
with yeah open mouth that can't do
anything yeah i mean the not to
bring up
a sore subject because you're not in
the franchise anymore but i'm still in
the franchise actually just snide not considering
me but jurassic park character was not
declaring characters alive and could come back
any time i'm just shooting out there
sure yeah um but in jurassic park
that's why they made a bunch of
the dinosaurs they made the giant dinosaurs
yeah and then they mixed it with
cd
iphone yeah so so it would trick
you it's a great blend that's why
when you watch godzilla and kong it's
just like alright i'm watching a cartoon
whatever i know that's why i'm and
i still think it's fun but i
it's fun it doesn't i just go
oh i'm not scared in the way
that i wanna be like i would
yeah more scared if i that's how
i feel about the marvel movies is
that the you know the big eye
i i could be wrong but i
feel like the big draw of those
things is the crazy action and knowing
that it's all just cdi i don't
care because only doing sometimes i think
for the marvel movies the draw isn't
the action it's the stuff around the
action but i know what you mean
because if you're just looking at iron
man flying around in it is a
cartoon yeah
battling spider-man that's why they consciously go
inside iron man suit to see robert
downey jr's head and they always have
spiderman taking off his mask yeah because
the human factor of it is is
the stuff that engages audiences yeah the
cartoon but you know if something's just
purely a cartoon like the incredibles it's
great i love it yeah absolutely
hello hey did you watch the tina
turner documentary yes so good god watch
it i want to see tina turner
vs godzilla vs kong
the doctor's alien vs so pharaoh good
it's amazing vs alien vs imagine being
at one of those shows like in
the six oh my god i was
like she is just a rock star
i really was like i wanted to
you know hear her story because she's
such a fascinating person yeah but there
was part of me was like can
we just we just watch this concert
oh my god i know
there's every concert like performance they showed
was amazed unbelievable i don't think i
would've liked to have been there because
now i'd be old shit so if
you had been there yeah you could
have been there in the eighties and
be your same age oh that's true
no i wasn't allowed at concerts then
oh wow because they're simple i got
a picture of you on the walls
and yeah
ah do not admit
no i wasn't nineteen eighty five when
i was fifteen that was my first
concert i was ever allowed why did
you go to winco boingo at the
irvine meadows amphitheatre you can watch it
on youtube i was there and so
are you there who is you know
you can't see me it's just i'm
not going to watch them know it's
a fun show i know it's on
you the whole concert of oil ingo
boingo why why were you forbes
didn't to go to the concerts drugs
um and unsafe environments ah mosh pits
so using his young to go by
yourself music is sinful devil you know
music i they did allow me to
buy records but like ah when they
heard that i was buying prince's purple
rain they shut it down when they
added princes too much when they searched
my room and they
i found frankie goes to hollywood's ah
welcome to the pleasure dome which has
like all these pictures of dicks in
it um it is the pleasure dome
is i think it is a place
where there are a lot of dicks
exhausted thinking about your parents trying to
like keep you from all the fun
yeah like i'm like just timing it
just makes you more fascinated with it
yeah it was the benefit of being
as part of a big family and
and they are like oh yeah absolutely
like i have no curfew or anything
what was your first concert i'm sure
we've talked about this my first concert
i believe was
the band squeeze remaining at a much
higher college i'm gonna say this was
right before ah our that our hourglass
yeah oh wow thousand but that's cosi
fan tutti frutti no no no no
that's sweet from a stranger sweets from
a stranger yes i think my first
concert
we do the leaderboard cool
sure i'm pretty sure my first one
was dispatched remember that band yeah no
um they were like obama probably were
like in the they were in the
vein of vo a r i'm trying
to do the taxi they've okay i
remember food wu da su bo sat
out
ah da da da da da da
da we've brought him back on something
we've not
yeah yeah
well i really wanted to see john
mayer but i didn't i was obsessed
with john mayer but told you about
your body what am i welcome that
album came out honestly that was like
all my friends were like this is
the most romantic person like what feels
like your body is a wonderland accept
your pussy i won't touch it and
i don't go down on anyone that's
like oh
okay i ran our wedding um we
had a we had a d j
hours yeah remember when the three were
like yeah
g j and he played that song
we made ah several playlists for the
different oh no no i don't have
a song for this your big sigh
sigh rennes what's going to happen when
they get there right yeah sigh rand's
psi range
what's gonna happen when they get there
that's great thank you um buh so
we we had all these playlists all
the d j to do is just
press play and step away sprouts play
um and at one point of course
like right after the ceremony have to
do photos and that always takes longer
than you think so i want to
do our cocktail
you really been trained to see that
our cocktail playlists ran out and so
he started playing his own music oh
good oh no jessica chaffin our friend
jessica chaffin who i think is so
great yeah i actually was just the
other day saying to art and i
was like i want i want ronna
to be real i feel like ronna
is she real
well that too but i'm like i
love listening to ronna so much i'm
like this is a real person yes
and so this real person came up
to janie
because the d j had started playing
your body is a wonderful oh no
and jessica and you can i'm sure
you can picture her doing this ah
excuse she goes up to janie and
says ah did you want to replay
this my god i used to love
desire him to play this was this
part of your plan
i love anything that they turn it
off ah yes i think like record
scratch right in the middle early i
don't remember i think we do yeah
yeah that was how we felt i
told you about the the r d
j playing so oh yes yes yeah
and we just it was such a
bone of contention for me that i
expressly said to the d jays
never play cool and the gang celebration
yeah when he started playing it we
at that point so much had gone
wrong and and and yet we had
pulled off a good wedding that we
just started laughing just just just funny
that's just the herald at that point
sure ah kumar
don't leave him out when i first
got married the first time my rule
was they could not play brown eyed
girl i really hate that cy had
that to really and janie was ami
not upstate but she was disappointed yeah
well she has brown eyes to just
run i hope she's oh i don't
have brown eyes but it's not why
i don't want to hear it i
think i just hate that softly
laid out it's it doesn't excel but
i know i think it probably was
played out but i i got into
a van morrison kick just in time
for him to be a weirdo
oh and i got all of his
records and i i i plopped that
one on i hadn't heard it in
years since like my twenties when i
thought it was all played out sounds
good no he is his music is
fantastic great i'm saying brown-eyed girl specifically
you know you know yeah does absolutely
but i i feel i don't know
if i would be fine never hearing
it again sure but that's how i
felt but i
i'm saying like take twenty years off
i'm saying i can't live your life
this is a real you got rich
situation everybody's wrestling well back into the
shore um i wrestled in the pools
what i said van morrison's been with
hot oil
getting full pour out oil in there
it just lay on the top of
the
then put salt and pepper and boil
it huh
val morris has been a widow for
a very long time and i have
what did he recently do he while
he retorted that tie back
yeah i lockdown happened with eric clapton
eric clapton claim that he didn't know
what it was about i think you
and i were talking about this and
i that's hilarious but it's like it's
like a poem that he didn't understand
i think that i said that's a
possibility to give like like air claps
in a backdoor but i'm thinking more
and more that eric clapton like lady
i can see van morrison going hey
man you wanna play my song and
him going you'll do mr van
morrison knit roaring solo
i'm sure i've said this before but
i always think eric clapton's american and
i'm always surprised when he's not yeah
every time you only say that every
time your eye due to space you've
said it i will say it to
his face i have somewhere this this
album that van morrison recorded to break
a contract he had to tell the
record label it's like it is
is just made up nonsense songs late
so he wanted them to fire him
he he he owed yeah yeah you
oh no an album to this label
and so he just records a lot
like what we've been doing a little
bit on the last twenty episodes so
we're just trying to fill the time
liters fifty are great
i'll dig this
sorry i'm just like boo boo boo
boo boundary no it can't be me
if you can find one send me
the link and i'll play it but
ah i mean i said i told
you i saw him on letterman he
was just like blah blah blah blah
blah and blah blah blah blah just
fill in the time doing what i
have to do dave dupe um now
you're both on your phones and have
left it up to me to do
yeah
that's going bad um so what else
is up
thank you said topics were saying the
middle turner was one of them though
scram was one of them what else
can i tell you about what else
i've been up to um ah well
oh well actually just about speaking of
pilots and it is a bit of
reality recap oh wait a minute we
have a really have a re
we have a remix someone sent us
so let's see ah this is tom
tierney i don't have my glasses i
can't see but this is a i
believe that's who it is this is
a reality recap remix and so here
we go this is
this is it and i see that
i need to terminate stick with oh
alright here we go reality recap
oh my god that's what asia
shut down everything yeah it was so
weird i love that alright um so
i was watching married at first sight
which
oh yeah what's up don't worry danmark
continue with the store around the complaint
about married at first sight is that
it's an eight week process of the
show but it goes on for like
a million episodes like it's just it's
really too long okay but there's also
they're not really married at first sight
because they do see each other before
they're pronounced mary
raid so why should they have say
chickens happy makes it go with you
are you are now bride and groom
and as they're turning around yes exactly
now let me really fuck put a
big piece of cardboard between the well
one guy did have the girl come
out he put blindfolds on both of
them and so she walked me out
without seeing him
which i was like and here's yours
um he is a horse and yeah
blinders know people but anyway there's one
guy who is obey he's a pilot
and he fly fly small planes and
all it's better telephone yes oh people
in there and he took the girl
up in the flight and cargo
can you bring it overnight i don't
know yeah i don't know what laptop
i don't know how many different types
of planes flies but in this episode
he took her for a flight okay
and i was just wondering what you
guys thought of this because he she
was giggling and having the time of
her life and then she's like can
you do that zero gravity thing yeah
i mean it's floating around them which
i didn't know is like a thing
but i didn't like it and i
would
not want to go in a plane
like that i don't want to go
in a play like that you don't
want to go into vomit comet i
really don't and i feel like there's
enough scary stories about helicopters and small
planes and i'm like give me the
fucking there's a whole song about helicopters
well i know that one but have
you been in a plane with that's
that's the smallest i've been in like
six
people and i have to i had
to get off i've been to cedar
i my grandfather and father were pilots
helicopter pilots so they've taken they both
took me up in them i didn't
like it because i had a very
queasy sick stomach ah you know where
things like that would make me motion
sickness would yeah vomit so
i was always probably wow up to
yeah um my dad was telling me
a story about either my mom or
someone else that he was dating or
something when he went from florida to
jamaica and he flew them from florida
to
l a how does it help florida
jamaica ooh wow i got to barbuda
blah blah he said everything was fine
when they left they took off because
you could turn around and see florida
like oh wow florida is getting smaller
whatever it is until suddenly you can't
see anything other than water everywhere yeah
no no no no the the woman
started to freak out i think i
would panic and they'd be like no
no it's
and like how do you know where
you're going like if you're not aiming
at something and my dad was trying
to say well it's these instruments right
here they tell you where you're going
well then the woman said she goes
is there like an autopilot thing and
he's like nope just me and she's
like so if you pass out we're
screwed and he was like huh actually
that's the scariest realization you could possibly
have yeah so
why is it like doing zero gravity
well zero gravity bullshit i don't know
i guess he honks his head just
thinks it looks cool ranch the official
report to listen because of the zero
gravity bullshit but i probably i've probably
mentioned this before i felt i've been
following this mormon mommy blogger for like
the last yes twenty years of exile
i'm falling for
and maybe know at least ten years
okay it's getting shorter and shorter but
the kids have grown up and just
started last week it's shocking but they
they were this perfect family this like
sort of her blog was popular because
every family is perfect but the blog
was happy because they took like pretty
pictures of their pretty family and then
they had
had they went on a small plane
and they got the crash was just
the parents and the pilot and the
pilot died and the the they were
burned heavily and the the man was
burned like twenty percent of his body
and the elemental whistle house right
the woman was burned over eighty percent
of her body and she's spent the
last ten years like recovering and like
adapting to this new life and it
is so so shocking to me to
read about it it was horrible she
was in a coma for a long
time and they there was just what
oh it's just wow found that happened
my friend k b they were in
school buzzer no no yeah plane crash
oh my god it's just so jarry
yeah katie was are you joking is
gonna be something stupid god dammit
my good friend k be like what
does it say oh no you're horrible
i don't get it there's still no
no skills no love it's nice
it's a marble not thing anyway but
yeah brian
if that's not the issue colgate i
don't know okay these toys why i
don't yeah just thought you had a
draft i believe you could have a
friend but shoppers i should have known
you were kidding but i i just
that story too like that has scared
me away from ever getting in the
helicopter i just might my dad swear
there's it's safe if you will though
that's what they say about jfk junior
is that he who ah i'm sorry
ah the joy freien and that's another
crazy story or future president that story
so scary finch and fusco well no
they go missing no no see he
got caught up in a storm and
in a storm you're supposed to do
with my dad was saying which is
just literally
the fly by checking the instruments because
they tell you everything you need to
know you don't need to see anything
right okay so rolled the window down
yeah she stuck her head out and
they're were like yeah it's abstractions of
a passing seven thirty seventy
no but they they that's what happens
they get disoriented they don't check the
instruments they think they can they do
it all by sight and then they
end up upside down and oh no
yeah that's so scary yeah yeah remember
we are going to go saw us
we're gonna go into helicopter in hawaii
i wasn't gonna go i wasn't going
to go i was too scared anyways
but then
they could make a cancelled because who
was remade it was three of us
and cool up no i think it
was gonna be jus and tim that
we're gonna go and they don't know
who remain home who remained everybody but
anyway meant to gen char oh okay
who's the core for the for is
you me paul and kula because everyone
else went swimming with manners
yeah that's what i would not want
to do either none of us wanted
to do it but i thought it
was funny labeling us as the core
for ideally yes to dinner they all
went off to do so i was
like oh the core for saying that
we were the most important we were
real yes it's like everyone else is
sort of extraneous
with with a real meanwhile they're going
off having like an actual adventure anyway
and we're sitting there and i'm going
to have dinner there communing with wild
sea creatures and having like an amazing
experience or they're like luminescent fish or
whatever the fuck
i didn't not want to do that
i don't why i that's that's a
final frontier for me i can't handle
that like sea life is very it's
kind of gives me an ah very
scared feeling i used to like to
do it i would scuba diving in
like if i ever when i went
to hawaii for my brother's wedding um
i would scuba dive and i loved
it
it was like you'd find all these
places where there'd be so many fish
and it was and it didn't feel
unsafe or although i will say at
my brother's wedding the last day it
was really rocky and i went out
scuba diving and it got a little
dangerous but um but then i took
up i was like scuba diving so
fun cool but let's go scuba diving
when you have a tank on and
you're like oh sorry that's not going
snorkelling oh i didn't mean self contained
underwater breathing so different because i'm really
cuba diving i wanna try strangling i
did train to scuba dive but um
okay now your story changed we had
to do that in my pool at
school i did school yeah oh my
god really yeah that's where i took
scuba diving i found it terrifying
i don't like that i when i
would get i have your problems so
when i got too deep it put
my ass to sleep and also um
like fucks with my ears so i
was like oh i'm i didn't i
never got certified because i didn't like
going down twelve gabriel recently got certified
oh great a couple of years ago
maybe so you can teach you yeah
but i took coup
pull-up out snorkeling i was like snorkeling
so fun let's do we went to
catalina on our one year anniversary and
i don't like catalina by the way
the nets played out everything i like
i'm saying no to everything but i
i catalina is not excite it's not
fun yeah but i was like let's
make this fun that's got snorkelling yeah
and we took a boat and we
went out in the middle of the
and the the water is dirty there
is no fish
fish of nasty there's the guy in
the boat was like well there's a
lot of interesting kelp you can can
look at oh it's literally like hell
yeah seaweed fuck that and then cool
up can't really swim anyway and i
was saying like no it's fun it's
hard because i was always doing hawaii
where the disaster where it was like
maybe six feet deep yeah it's like
you sees bj
beautiful underwater creatures and it's bright blue
water and and instead it was dark
dirty water with kelp and it looks
like fifty feet deep or whatever you
know i would hate that yeah yeah
it was terrible i was in i
was performing in houston one time most
miserable week of my life did not
have a you are doing stand-up ah
yes i was and i were
went with my friend lisa de larios
hilarious comedian has ever seen a squirrel
he's pointing out every school there's one
like right above paulo and it's coming
down towards la
you guys
i've you know i tried i've been
making friends with the squirrels in my
neighborhood i know you actually hosted something
that i didn't i didn't get but
i want to understand i find it
fun even though i didn't get i
want to understand this um it was
a picture of a squirrel and it
said something that we filtered it yeah
what's that filberts hazelnuts and so that's
what i feed them it's like i'm
like
when the when the whatever the dwolla
yeah i just i didn't know what
a filbert was but i found the
word funny enough that i could not
believe i captured this but i because
i have a little nature cam that
i put out there it's motion activated
and it's the video one of the
videos started with the squirrel with his
eyes closed which i've never seen before
he's holding it like he loves it
so much he
he's holding it he's only a hazel
that looks like it's ecstatic oh like
sydney love that oh my god look
what do we owe so to lose
you say houston aquarium and they had
a little tank where you could put
your hand in and you could pet
this little ray oh yeah
i mean i couldn't make myself do
it who needs it that's what i
say i want nor like it's for
children i should be able to put
my hand and yes and i was
so disappointed with myself that i couldn't
make myself do it what if it
bites you could be kind of cool
story i don't even know if that's
what i was afraid of today even
bite what if you didn't like it's
texture
you know this is what i was
just talking to my friend do like
chinese texture you like i love her
texture she has her vows
that texture that thing where you hate
love three holes you hate when yeah
that's true trip to phobia i think
yes my friend has this and i
was like really many times she has
three holes she never was definitely both
i've never heard of testicles but she's
terribly feel like i've talked about this
on a different show it's it's ah
what do you call it not a
disorder it's just it's ah yeah so
it's just something like it'll be ah
you know how there there were certain
phones that came out camera three different
i have it i have it yeah
some people really flipped out about this
because it was like her activating my
trip to fail so it's it's basically
like people feel weirded out by cities
that have three
holes in the ground shakes each other
but she also said it's like certain
textures will make her feel like crazy
like if there's like a bumpy lizard
or like you know just things that
she's like and i was like what
does it feel like you're scared and
she was like no i just like
really i feel really grossed out like
i really like mediation we feel like
that about nails on the chalk
gboard so it's not that strange it's
just interesting to look at something and
b have like such a visceral reaction
right now well well mom
right right
so in case that wasn't clear
um but anyway this sounds really interesting
cause i never knew anyone to happen
not but i heard about it and
actually the mormon mommy blogger i follow
has as well she's got a bad
day no shit i think norman got
first life is pretty good oh wait
she wasn't in the plane crash she
was in the plane crash but she's
made a great life yeah well so
did travis barker
um he wasn't playing he was in
that terrible one the blink one eighty
two guy yeah it was kind of
recently no no but it was bad
it feels that it was actually heavily
injured and was killed in that crash
right no look it up this vga
i'll hang around the rapper know i
know you're the rapper alright we have
to take a break
and we're back and guess what freedoms
what's that i have a surprise for
us oh and no surprise for me
what if you are shocked by what
you said oh my god what did
i just do i wanted to be
a surprise for all of us i
went to a hypnotherapist
what is i want myself oh my
god what is that oh yeah this
is orange vanilla cream all i really
wanted to try this when someone i
know it's going to be sick because
this was a flavor that i loved
i love that i live in a
claim chuckles shot lunch i don't know
it doesn't look like it's my tone
chicago okay yes i'm gonna pass okay
let your little hands okay
careful with your headphones yeah
paul is ah was still tethered to
his headphones and didn't realize that he
was
i know he is now only look
like tax or something like eminem's into
my open paw okay so you either
get orange or you get white there's
no other colors there are no other
care about the size of a peanut
butter m and m there maybe even
a little bigger they look a little
dusty they feel like something that would
be in your grandma's candy
bucket all right we're gonna eat them
oh well don't eat them
there's one look at it
that's good i don't know what this
tastes like lipstick
no that's i think it's good i
ain't good
i think it delivers on what it
says it is a race idea that
an m is coming yeah yeah it's
not an eminem no it doesn't have
like not an eminent and no no
no nominee i mean eminem and now
and then i don't know my mom
i don't think i can eat more
than two i'm gonna go for my
second
huh
these are good i like these these
are maybe one of my favorites of
the off brand non peanut butter tape
i didn't have and see what looks
like okay
i do i you just why what
yeah oh the whole thing is white
yeah and watching that's it's orange it's
orange on the outside huh they found
a way to make it fun you
should just these is good thank you
m and m's thanks paul we can't
say it enough thank you m and
m's when imams and crocs fucking sponsor
us
amazon and crops they go together croxton
m and m's they like theirs using
them but they're like hot oil and
vinegar and salt and pepper the pool
you literally put imams in your crock
holes you literally that i'm sure to
many you should go fuck yourself and
put mgm's in your crackles my name
is my sponsors first of all because
of that the second loomis
we did review several of their products
and call them disgusting yeah but that's
fair they know do the same to
kroc they know what they're doing no
they're discussing weight some of the the
this flavor is really making me think
of something but i don't know what
maybe like a creamsicle or orange and
i mean i know what soda
it's like the textures remind me of
old candy oh yeah it's a little
chewy it has an interesting it's not
it has nothing to do with him
and them like taffy nothing to do
with it this is where i'm just
it's a fruit candy like laffey taffy
in a shell
i don't know i don't know anyway
we'll never know but those is good
well i thought that was interesting and
i i have seen people tag us
in some other weird ass flavors like
yes kayleigh like pacifiers ass ass pie
we understand that everyone's eating ashley's days
we've come out with wow
for these molesters love to eat i
don't think you know what do you
guys actually enjoy yes i'm an m
alright good stuff huh
i'm just pondering the m which m
mars are murray murray yeah so the
other one yeah i didn't realize that
no mam mars
mars they're two different companies i believe
we could look this up but um
i don't know i don't know if
mars mars and murray's i believe is
the what the abbreviations are do you
want to play some of the songs
people sent us yeah now no alright
here here is ah someone sent us
a drum remix of our threesome thing
theme this is a guy named patrick
and here he goes well what i
like to call this like worthy of
dick clark's american bandstand and he's taking
off now was number one hit three
dm remix you know named patrick and
here he goes casey qasim wouldn't say
i want your sex
when that came out and working
well yeah just by me
oh did he say he would he
would just say that was george michael
with your number two or something like
that he would never say the title
he was also on saved by the
bell and and yet another sign of
how fucking weird it was that they
take shit
well okay easy gay so he was
like oh here to do the top
countdown on the radio play and all
the yeah all these children are excited
to see cats they're in their fifties
diner excited that he was there ah
can i just see the writers' room
please yeah thanks for fucking literally they
never did anything cool show alright here
we go this is patrick patrick cr
arsene
three
i like it
drummer
oh my god yesterday this thanksgiving yesterday
oh sir
yesterday um there's i don't know there's
some guy in my neighborhood the sound
is carrying so well he was practicing
his band with the chili peppers it
was my neighbour certainly was not and
he was practicing his song and so
then mike started like making fun of
him and i was like sure if
he could hear you and he's like
he can't hear us
we were hearing him singing his whole
song if he could hear asthma but
then how do we hear him i
gotta understand yeah i don't understand how
the noise is caring but he was
so he sound like he was auditioning
to be in guster industrial it was
just really usually the way it works
is like something that's louder than another
thing is more audible okay but i
still felt like usually the way i
still felt like i could hear him
so clearly that if we were also
yelling back making fun of him he
could yes probably unless he was making
currently making noise well i thought it
had just stopped and then he actually
was in fact continuing but i was
like with the balls you have to
have your windows open practicing
this song goes one two three
oh no boo yeah and then i
was like oh no you're alone you
don't do the count um that was
me ah i think about my neighbors
what they must hear from me all
the time because i am a ah
a big ah cursor when i'm frustrated
by something wow i would love to
thanks i was in a hotel room
next to you once when you were
cursing a lot
they're gonna go and i wasn't wanting
next to you on when you were
saying someone else oh shit your brain
really like like
oh my lord jesus christ
i'm a silent prayer oh please save
the poor
but i consider like i will be
like god duh
later i'll think they probably heard that
oh my god i just kind of
random person from is making you do
that like is it are the stakes
really low it always like you're like
i dropped my cup nut oh no
a little athletic supporter
and someone need you in the balls
it's
and then i won ten thousand dollars
on television yeah of course um it's
always like trying to put something together
it's trying to do ah something involving
my laptop converting something in me whatever
dropping something and then does your does
draw you know my reaction when i
drop something is always i've
trained myself to do this i say
good
thanks good i didn't want that and
now when you're like really frustrated like
elsa you're putting something together and you're
really frustrated what is janie does she
tried to like help you because i
feel like we have this really with
mike where he was putting together and
she's usually cooking right yeah she's cooking
or taking your shoes off but he's
getting frustrated i was buying getting paid
what if we try this what if
we try it and he's like can
you just leave
leave like i'm like yeah but i'm
like hey can you just leave me
yeah i mean it depends on what
it is she will if it involves
um let's say involves like being locked
out of some fucking seldom used website
or something um she loves getting here
trying to access your cryptocurrency yes
i'm like i you go join three
password tries left god dammit god far
um she loves she loves doing that
kind of stuff but if it's like
if it's building a thing or if
it's something like i'm doing on my
own in my office um she knows
now not to not
to try to help yeah not to
ever say like you okay honey yes
exactly because you're you're fine you're just
like i said if i if i'm
she's like because he used to she's
like i thought you were hurt or
something i was like i will make
an entirely different noise if i'm hurt
that all people whine like a little
but i feel like i was slightly
know if i'm hurt i was like
why don't we just do this later
you know like
cause he was like tired i'm like
close to a slater doesn't matter and
music i wanna fucking you know it's
like he wants to finish it yeah
and it was like it's just like
this annoying little thing and i'm being
more annoying when i think i'm really
de-escalating like i'm like yeah sometimes de-escalating
is escalating yeah i'm learning that funny
like in the vietnam war that your
father probably sure of course
one pale make you be me but
one makes you hungry for ems
yeah i think i say i probably
say god dammit or jesus no i
probably said jesus fucking christ like i
say non-elite probably was cool up to
it because co-op is very expressive when
she's upset do you try to help
her with things with these these types
of
the situations were discussing yeah
if if she's ever yelling she probably
does need help like she's not a
real yeah um like ah type of
person when things are
i'm proud of myself the other day
i still work a sub my toes
so hard like i go in the
door on my toe it hurt so
bad fuck but mike was asleep felt
like right where i open the door
yeah and then i went like i
just want like
yeah just like have like a silent
like reaction but deadly and then later
i was like just so you know
i really could've screamed and i didn't
you welcome up to pay for it
i really wasn't hey
i used to stub my toes when
i was a kid all the time
still made all the bad wear like
shred skin oh i feel like i'm
a big tall awkward weirdo walking around
and scaled up space
see and i just want to say
but you still stub your toes a
lot
i'm always well stumbling joe by the
way has this very specific connotation to
me which is it involves blood like
it's not just oh my god no
i hit my toe on something oh
no my my thing is able to
like walk into the bed corner and
it hurt somebody or i just don't
have my i don't have a sense
of how wide my body is so
just hit my shoulder in a doorframe
like yeah a lot i feel like
i'm not fit
fitting into the space a lot so
i'm always hitting my knees on stuff
and hitting my toes and yeah so
my i have a desk now that
it's a it's a little compact desk
just a tiny desk called a captain's
desk oh it wasn't that just purr
fans and but is that the rank
that you wish you had in life
like if they gave out re happy
with captain if
it gave out ranks for just what
type of person you were yeah captain
is gay guy that's you don't want
that no don't do that granted why
would i be here lieutenant ah you'd
be lieutenant maybe a commodore back swapper
oh she got you yeah she not
only got you
for what would you be and with
all the things in what's that i
don't know what is so much like
what's like for someone who's hanging out
henson swabi wesley crusher wasn't instant use
an instant it was weird to me
and star trek when they started making
the movies and then because they you
know the show was started in the
sixties so then
after a while they're like this guy
would get promoted yeah at some point
so they made you admiral kirk and
it always just sounded weird and i
think he went back to captain we
got knocked down right yeah they ripped
off some of his stars off of
his uniform yeah and threw them into
space and they're still floating out there
that must be human that's it's the
northstar oh and
that's how we got jesus yes because
it's all takes place in the past
actually yeah
laura with ah some ah you don't
care wow i just started thinking about
something why would you start thinking about
a text after respond to them which
one can we respond to it she's
just give us your phone will respond
to anything about a text doctors fault
i just was thinking how am i
gonna respond to that can you can
you respond to it right
now with whatever we say and then
follow it up with oh that was
scott and paul you know that just
wouldn't really do it
yeah come on let's up so no
from me dawg it's not gonna happen
ah what about any other texts you
just let us text anyone randomly from
your phone my guy wow come on
glory and people in your phone would
you actually want to send a text
to right now i would say probably
twenty percent non booking comedy show
related yeah yeah yeah affordable
not you and maybe you know wow
but i mean like if i took
your phone and just like scrolled and
hit something like what are the odds
would be someone you wouldn't want me
to well you know i've had now
an iphone for let's see i got
gave an iphone for know that's embarrassing
i thought you were rich i think
they they they came out with iphones
in two thousand and seven i remember
getting one when i yeah that makes
sense i had one in canada
when cu up and i got engaged
in two thousand and seven and everyone
in canada was like what is that
because they didn't have them up there
yeah yeah um so i've had i've
had it since two thousand and seven
and it's just collected every person who
emails me or number down every ah
i hardly ever go back and like
prune them so yeah i like to
go through and get rid of
people yeah i did my times yeah
i'd do it on your phone love
to do that for you i went
oh you're on mine and i kind
of just go like having talked to
this person in five years users a
dentist hey reach out to me and
i don't know whose number it is
oh yeah i used to go to
him
the butcher of large ma
my dentist i've recommended to so many
people and they would ah as he
would send me five dollars to starbucks
every time i recommend someone only stopped
doing oh i are dentists that we
used to have yeah was also recommended
to me by ah a friend of
ours named bob and ah not oettinger
okay was right
but what was funny was because it
was recommendation i think this dentist knew
like had something in the computer system
of who knew who or whatever um
and so who's zooming who of course
yeah just know why they need to
know to sound friendly he was like
so how's robert
ah because that was his legal name
or whatever and i was like okay
you don't actually know that is so
weird their identities daughter works with him
she's also a dentist oh gee yes
yeah daughter's dentist dr surgeon dot anyway
so he wasn't available last time i
went and she was my dentist and
she's like my agent was so fun
when i was like this is also
having doubts worked on by someone you're
having a dentist who's like my age
like we have like a funny conversation
i had a great time and i
always reality recap we we could've done
that we could've done that and then
i also liked that she um she
had made a joke making fun of
how many people i've referred and how
like i might as well work there
and then i just was like
this is so cool that your dentist
thing in my mind i'm like stink
of death like a father
reality recap yeah oh my god i
just thought it was cool to be
like a person with a job i
guess is what i'm say i was
like oh it's so cool to be
a dentist like you know everything about
that yeah do you have a fantasy
of going back to where i'd me
i know you were only a babysitter
and a movie
car but cry sometimes awesomely pauses even
about the dentist oh well the current
or current dentist we we love um
and there's this one ah this one
guy that janie always gets i never
get janey always guides and he
would always confuse me for a friend
of ours goes to the same dentist
that's crazy yeah paul g tommy like
i don't think we look anything like
yamani but i think he had a
mustache maybe for like a week or
something ah so in this guy's mind
it jose's mind it's like they're the
same mustache joel asked me about our
my friend's wife
plates are doing i used to go
to this what if you really knew
i used to go to this music
in my day to get my haircut
and i one thing i hate like
i love the person who cuts my
hair right now but love i'm in
love with her yeah this yeah sorry
but now i used to go to
just random barbershops in your mouth near
my
house and one thing i can't stand
is when ah they they talk a
lot and and like rest and and
put down the scissors to talk i
think we have discussed we have discussed
you seem very real to me in
my mind yeah but i agree with
you i don't like when well and
i also don't like when a dentist
really wants to fucking get into it
my
this little dental hygienist last time i
was getting my teeth clean was telling
me about her fucking period why mean
no what about it lu like it's
happening right now or what was she
saying about it i was honestly just
going like allows wow
don't get no and she was like
well she cleans your teeth with champ
yeah it really hurt because it ripped
my teeth apart she was just talking
about her getting her period and unlike
how her her period kind of stopped
all that was bad just things that
i was like you know if we
were friends i guess i could see
us having this conversation i just don't
understand
and how we got here and i
have no response and i also just
simply don't want to know when we
were ah cool up and i were
on the phone with our ah ibf
doctor recently ah she was like i
got my pure know she was international
videos that are funny of course
we won ten thousand dollars it was
amazing i think you still get paid
in dollars that's course yeah well but
um you know we were going through
a problem which i won't go into
and saying like well this is these
are the symptoms what's going on and
and the person is treating it very
seriously and saying like well ah you
know it could be this could be
the cause this could be the cause
and then she said you know you
probably just want to wait until her
menzies
wow i burst out loud it was
a serious nation i e i burst
out laughing and cool up was like
what are you laughing i'm like she's
calling immensely she's she's a medical profession
just feel like you don't really have
a date i mean it's very technical
i remember these well you know that
is one of those
those things when you're talking to a
doctor and i'm like should i say
poop or should i say it's my
bowel movements are x y z like
or just like yeah my poop is
thinking that that happened i am a
problem with my pp or like my
tits her know that happened to me
and i think i said i think
i said something in an alarmed the
nurse and then she
he rephrased it as crotch so she's
when she like told the doctor exactly
what it was guy's got a problem
in his junk
xyz oh i think i sell i
didn't say any crude word i just
said like i was trying to describe
exactly what was happening my ding dong
has been
in a good way my slot miserable
i just break my song aches
with desire for you baby
i'm sorry zuckerberg oh my god
alright we're back and it's time for
a three church i'll say it is
scott this is called cafe and this
is submitted by kafe no no no
no they didn't put the accent mark
above the no actually ooh
kafe us it's called k baby
maybe this was my good friend k
baby this is a minute by tania
chen ah and here's how it goes
players a and b are celebrities on
a date play your see is the
waiter a and c know who celebrity
b is and b and c know
who celebrity a
is and it's up for everyone to
give clues to who they are on
a date with when it seems like
the celebrities know who they are they
sign their names on their checks so
basically we'll play it the first time
where paul and i are on a
date lauren is the waiter i will
text loren ah
who who aisle is and then lauren
you can text paul who i okay
does that sound about right it should
be like a famous person ie yeah
right otherwise why are we playing
so i be a famous person or
someone who would score that we don't
know any fictional character know it could
be a fictional character yes but they're
faint i consider them to be famous
but it doesn't have to be a
person doesn't have to be humanoid day
though that i if if we expanded
too much it might take
take too long okay so she's just
a soul living celebrity real it's try
new things keyword live ants gotta be
living gotta be living yeah okay gotta
be living so now i'm thinking of
people who are only dead okay well
don't do that
um okay i just texted paul with
who's scott is okay i'm texting you
lauren who paul is do you have
it got it and so we all
know certain things and we will start
right about now
now
what a wonderful dinner this has been
it really has been amazing in our
our waiter ding dong is so let's
play ding da da i want to
ask you ding dong yeah i don't
know anything about you
ah well i mean how much to
know about me oh my god
wow that was chaotic wow well there's
not much to know about me you
know i'm just a little street rat
who got a job now okay help
you guys get a drink what would
you like well i think you probably
i know you want something fiery you
know maybe something with
cranberry juice and so you hajri i
know that you want a big glass
of wine with ice in it red
wine with ice in it oh yes
please red wine with ice and i
love it yeah that is exactly what
you want or you it can they
turn up the air conditioning i imagine
you must be warm um well sure
given how you're dressed sure
i definitely have too many clothes on
for this date certainly if you know
what i mean it's you know i
wouldn't ask you to change a thing
i just i just wanna make sure
you're comfortable i'm comfortable i'm comfortable usually
wearing this amount of clothes okay alright
although it's it's looks seasonally inappropriate does
that way you think
you're just covered up but congratulations to
you and your new baby thank you
i love having a baby and i
love that it's new i love being
on a date with someone who just
had a baby
it's my first night getting away but
is interesting for both of you to
be on the stage just considering the
age difference well sure horse a lot
of people are gonna look at us
hey there's aides appear to be an
older gentlemen who likes to wear a
lot of clothes and red china sea
appear to be an older gentleman i
could see i'm an older woman yeah
yes i am an older woman it
seems who has a lot of clothes
and likes to drink red wine with
ice cubes to cool myself down and
look i'm young and i just had
a baby meaning i am a proud
mommy but you are also proud mommy
you have your kids i mean they're
adopted and you i'm sure there
we're out of the house but sure
that yeah ah actually something i didn't
know you can bond on that interesting
binding i just never brought it up
on this date i guess our first
date now because a lot of tabloid
stuff gets to misreported are you under
the impression that i had the baby
or that i adopted a baby you
had a baby her partner who um
as our power i hope yeah yeah
no no he's in the picture oh
we're on a date soil oh well
they got married so i do think
that they must have it opened we
have an over time scores yeah once
the baby came well i loved your
by the way your car is so
ah it's it's that sports car you
drove up and
it's like the color of it is
it it matches your ah your hair
it's so it's so interesting so interesting
what you mean by interesting well it's
just you know i don't know whether
you color coordinated it or just you
have a very sporty sports car that
happens to be the color i am
a strong sports car natural i mean
but
be honest does it look natural it
does yeah then yes it is oh
wonderful i think wonderful you know i
should be getting your drinks i'll go
get those and get right back yeah
something fiery the color of her hair
and i'll take that wine with ice
camps which is not helping me oh
well yeah you drink that on ellen
so shut ah okay everyone be also
have your own wine line and this
is why i didn't label you know
you of course i do and i
put ice cubes in it like a
weirdo yeah some weirdos do that i've
seen it happen oh sure no i
went with white wine sir i mean
red i've seen with red and i
think ok here's your wine there's your
nose very red shy
jollies i did like oh yeah and
i just wanted to say cranberry juice
the color of my hair but somehow
you'll be willing to denounce that person
that you worked with look ah woody
allen is ah a terrible ah person
you are doing it
i'm doing what you're announcing him i'm
denouncing him as a terrible person finally
i mean look is good in bed
yes of course look at him but
does that excuse
ah wait a minute i because i
didn't know that oh well yeah didn't
know that it oh yeah maybe i
told my husband you on some level
you knew it my husband colon i
mean colin you don't have a husband
i don't have a husband what i
meant to say is ah that you
adopted your children by yourself and
when you're fifty yeah wait i'm i
thought i was i am who i
was no well what do you think
you are mia farrow nov wow of
an i don't know thank eden i
yeah so of course she's loved with
it of course i slept with woody
allen okay i don't know threw me
i have i don't
remember that i haven't slept villareal but
no but yeah you've worked say i
love working with him yeah even i
know the stories yeah and so do
you know who you are ah i
see you i'm a real flintstones name
about you do i really really do
you know all those names that would
sound good if you were
a character on the flintstones or if
you are not a character on the
flintstones you have a real flintstones type
name anyway
well yeah it's pretty much exactly what
it sounds like yeah it is what
it is as you know you do
you think people like funny you for
your voice i thought it was beautiful
in that one movie where you saying
it was gorgeous thank you thank you
i like singing i have red hair
yeah
all the time oh yeah ever since
i've ah seen you as a young
actress i'm famous for it sure i
mean i wouldn't say you're i mean
you're more famous for your acting your
academy award you would read maybe because
of hair about the town wherein i
don't know as i think lucille ball
got famous just because of her hair
look even though it's just
the hair yep well i don't like
that because she's a big inspiration to
me emma stone yeah that's right
i thought that we might be the
same person for oh that's funny
i always thought i'd have them
i make a trick that would be
a good trick ah greatest trick the
devil ever played my turn to be
on the date yes and what do
you want me to be waiter yeah
we'll just ok rotate that way outta
line text you texts lorne and i'll
text you so what's he telling me
who
oh no no you text me i
text you who lauren is yeah scott
yeah scott many who lawrence you text
me who i told you no no
no no sorry you text me this
is department paul is i text you
who lorne is okay okay so paul
i'm texting you who knows i don't
text anyone so i'm saying paul is
so
yes exactly you don't text anyone paul
you just relax take a breather i
can't wait to read this text oh
man it's gonna be so fucking crazy
when i text it's got me like
text one thing to say is i
thought these people were supposed to be
alive oh you're right okay all right
she gave me a real daddy ooh
why
oh just now yeah i forgot that
we're all um okay so but i
cannot think of a single person who's
alive
who is alive these days
there aren't a lot of people who
are alive i got you one okay
here we go okay
i got it and this is who
lauren is until lauren and i know
who you are and who am i
the way i know i'm the waiter
i know but yeah i'm the rapper
here we go and seen thank you
so much for this lovely dinner i'm
my guy so happy oh hey oh
okay get you any um ah an
amuse-bouche number i would like do you
like appetizers i bet i bet you'd
like something i don't know something a
little ah
the off maybe like ah for a
drink maybe a seltzer
i'm sober you might like seltzer you
might like it in a bottles right
in your face yeah i mean knowing
your background jerry lewis no no why
did you say he's dead too i
don't know that i forgot he was
um kinda you something ah it's so
interesting that you guys are out together
i don't know we're on a date
so i mean
you both have such you have an
interest in comedy so it's great so
one last surprise you certainly have an
interest and you i would say i
would dare say you have an interest
you i think you probably would want
to drink i don't know something like
a whiskey or a beer i don't
know you're just one of the guys
yeah i would imagine maybe just a
beer when i'm just one of the
guys i love beer and
okay i will get you to i
want to sell you a site spread
your face or i'll be right back
guys getting clear back i thought you
would understand that was a joke because
such a big no idea but i
want to reserve yours sir and you
hello thank you and i was good
so i'm a little hungry yeah what's
ah what's the recommended well what like
what do you usually like to eat
as a snack like say when you
were in the writers' room what would
you oh well we love going bagels
and lox one of my larry david
no what's the why are you saying
these weird don't get that joke i
don't either we would have bagels i
mean he's obviously very influenced by you
that he's very influenced by me so
obvious yeah i think i think so
okay and i'm lying forward yeah definitely
but um anyway oh so if you're
you're you
i can't believe it's you've lived such
an amazing life and amazing life but
we have can i get you anything
to eat sir ah yama man and
i i like i'm just one of
the boys yeah i like don't tell
me you don't know what you want
to eat not are you clueless yeah
alright let me go let me surprise
you
guys alright bye i'm a man as
well ah yes we're both men and
that's obvious to us and i i'm
clueless written there's a movie name that
i love that film me two guys
hi i brought you basically i said
i would surprise you
you and all i could think of
his stacking graham crackers in a pile
i'm sorry
for both i'm sorry that's all you
could think of i was like oh
let me try you guys don't cook
the show i went back into the
kitchen that's all that was there and
i was like yeah i also stoop
i feel like this isn't a clue
no it's not it's not a clue
okay i thought that's what i ok
it's just a specific thing that he
felt like the sorry why don't you
give me a clue about me huh
why mean what there's so much to
be said about i mean you have
white hair and i'm balding of course
you are for yeah and i'm so
by the way i'm my name's i'm
sorry about the yeah blank know he
is very dick i think if i'm
so sorry about the recent tragedy with
your best friend you know
no you guys would get lunch here
every day yeah now you're stuck with
this guy over here it's not good
i'm real one of the boys who
look wow
yeah what is my last name why
don't you have a think on it
i mean yeah an older it's hard
to remember things sometimes yeah you don't
know who you are i don't know
i'm still young so i'm figuring it
out do you know can i by
the way can i switch so i
may spray these graham crackers with a
little bit of cologne
i'm just kidding
well i get i get that of
course yeah of course you do well
you know what will panther oh no
i think you'll do like this is
fifty or something kind of yeah now
that it's been awhile i think now
i think that will i think they
should actually go younger and it should
be the next generation's paul rudd of
boys yo just one of the boys
snap
what is my last name i mean
that's well what can i say that
your you know suits from those brothers
looks amazing and you're just babbling just
babbling just those brothers those brothers who
make the suits ah your suit looks
amazing yeah so stop babbling yeah and
babbling your
last name yeah
ah
babbling
raver oh so close brush yeah hey
i can never remember his name ah
this way
whoa what a nightmare that was great
welsh dewi call it was the graham
crackers thing that was not oh that
would just click oh unhelpful that was
i knew it immediately like that's not
a clue he's just doing him i
think we should call it alright all
we shouldn't do one more now let's
call it it's it's been a long
episode it's extra long
episodes
so we're gonna say goodbye to you
just as she
she twist and shape shake twist
did she do the shake do the
twist hey even
e thanks for listening everybody thanks for
listening to remember how to do it
twist and shake freedom usa on instagram
and twitter will be back next week
pie
and i do love you
dushanbe me
shake it up baby
just a shame
ha long bay
can you do the twist
hi law
due to shame
g
tuesday shame
uh