jesus cry
frida yeah we take a quiet roadside
time
ah wow very whisper like an horror
movie and um and horror and rand
horror how's everyone who wasted harder what
does you wrote horror novels like anne
rice eine rind i ran i'm really
brand horror look just change your name
to an if you have any brown
ho
welcome to zarina um allowed to get
a hiss out of lowering yeah this
early in the morning hey let's tell
people what we're doing really we're recording
four episodes in a row goddamn row
yeah so if you don't like two
in a row you're not gonna like
for real or maybe you like that
the most that's what you'll demand from
now that's true then
great that we just did one sunday
a month cranked them out moved it
along destroy friendships destroy their sundays yeah
no longer able to go to church
yeah well once those just out of
a month yeah i know but if
we destroyed thus sundays and made them
break up i'm worried the devil's gonna
get a perry dan oh
ooh
this is how i find out they
only have one great song they'd probably
have a lot of which when you
consider their great song um i consider
harmonia think of the name of it
will be talking about this is oh
here's where the story and they have
a million grades do you know yeah
i know that one i had like
three album my favorite song of theirs
yes if i won we'd see your
island alone in the living room i
want sitting room of course the british
i'm sorry you're telling me that i'm
about to find out that i love
a ton of songs but oh yeah
well don't look at me he said
that they're all great that my ex
girlfriend it was her favorite band wow
well she was in the band
yeah no that's not yeah but it's
a favorite here let's hear a little
bit of i one great
yeah this is how we're getting through
yes
if any sally's just a little picky
did he lie ah somehow my computer's
frozen oh oil is that going to
be bad for what we're doing right
now it's still recording okay great but
i mean it's bad in the sense
of what we're doing right now trying
to listen to the sundays i was
i would love to hear it i
could play it ah a hogan
it's supposedly playing i don't know oh
right eyes how's everyone's morning going so
far oh my gosh so good banana
you had a banana now what was
it brown or yellow nose was it
a classic freedom brown
and don't forget everybody's gotta get out
of the building by three pm
because there is a carbon dioxide leak
and none of those sensors are working
anymore we forgot to change the battery
but you still have eight hours to
get out
yeah
yes yeah man this is what this
show is making it think of song
what is it about she won what
i think it's a shoe buying the
house it's right within the house i
figured it out for the sitting-room she
won the war but it cost her
i know that's the thing about war
scott you are right that's the thing
about warriors not just fun welcome to
three of mine paul
i'm scott oh no and one of
them there because he thought i was
going to talk i never asked if
you want your headphone sets very common
feeling around here i don't want them
turned out that's do you want them
turn it down indeed indeed just a
little um but so how's your sunday
lauren what's going on make sense going
and what is lower in law
abkhaz do you want a sunday this
same thing i do every morning i
got up with holly and we played
in the living room what does playing
like what are you doing like musical
instruments which one we played up the
couch um we should like a marine
and she likes the little xylophone which
coach ah the main
wayne county
the one in that room um scale
of one to ten how comfortable is
that it's actually an a million i
got the best couch i'm not kidding
really splurged on a really nice couch
we somehow we got you thank you
we got good couch like nice looking
cow no not good catch bad couch
yeah they look great but they're not
amazingly comfortable your son goes to get
coffee and the other one comes back
in um if i lie on them
for like a few hours my back
hurts which is bad for a couch
right yeah yeah but this is this
is a pretty state is the plight
of the tall is it not this
is buying out a very long couch
it's a very fluffy
a young coach great oh you got
it from text from tiffany couches tiffany
tesla um it's hi i'm tiffany deal
on mascus inside of it massaging you
play
do you know what i bet he's
bad at massages ah but his terrible
yeah but he always won one who
thinks about oh those ones one yeah
it's like sorry babe i'm back massage
you i'll do you for two seconds
i'm bad at massages thing is rough
because turns out i am bad at
them but i try
pull-up said she was really good at
that when we first started dating and
she turned out she was bad at
them yeah and that was a tough
country she'd recognize that no she knew
i was like hey don't press down
on my spine please ah mike says
i don't i don't do it hard
enough and i'm like i'll use all
my strength in my body and it's
just not use your elbow
right mother no i don't do my
elbow i mean just my hands but
it's not do any do the people's
elbow the people's elbow yes natures oh
no you fools it's a wrestling reference
yeah that's the whole russell doing the
rack johnstown jim sam wow what did
he talk about why did he say
that jane the rack john's town why
did jane say that
because you he would like you know
he would like give ah he would
you like a flying leap and then
hit you with the elbow and he'd
say just wanna be with the people
you call that the people's elbow he
was used very populist wrestler
wow that may that guy retired who
the rock jane the rock vince mcmahon
oh yeah and shame vince mcmahon change
hey i think so i don't know
anything about it he had so many
are we talking about real people yeah
we shall do it he had so
many accusations against my plea i did
not know such thing
and you didn't mention that in his
announce movie didn't say look guys sorry
to the the accusations against me after
one hundred accusations i now have to
retire like what's that what did they
agree when someone just lost a match
goodbye
there's a door that is there a
standard thing that was like they declared
the winner oil a slap on the
floor okay so someone did that next
to him as well you know it
would have been more fluid had i
known exactly what it was i wouldn't
want to be raised by that yes
he was pinning an underling down
laugh the math rita he would be
no his accuser and him down and
then other people's that's right and slap
these things out how do you how
do you like like i don't know
anything about it i'll say that also
that ten more times i don't claim
to know anything i don't either and
i want to keep talking about it
yeah what do we think wrestling is
ah i think it could be
pitiful play let's start there yeah yeah
it is a beautiful play it is
kind of a it's it's a moment
improvised play with beats right and eight
revised in eighth grade a friend of
mine geiger everyone's wearing yeah w w
what lauren when i was an eighth
grader from my head here you were
talking
it's like minute to ah when i
was an eighth grade my friend got
very into w w f and about
epstein but the world wrestling fat better
federation had to reach fetterman feather weight
plane when the world wayne wayne photographs
but um and she always wanted to
watch
we would watch can you smell along
with the rock is cooking and like
all those guys and how do you
not know about the people's elbow because
i didn't really care i just remember
just watching supportively yeah friend um and
it was kind of an interesting i
think i've talked to us before maybe
or just in my life but um
sugarhouse was always really fun and i
loved
going there and um she had little
siblings and they will just find a
better house well don't move on from
that part of it was really fun
about it and this is the part
that now as an adult i see
as being vulnerable not fantastic is that
her mom had gone through divorce recently
so far so there was nothing in
the
nothing in the house so it was
we could run around we could play
we had a big like big yoga
balls bouncing all over the place jump
uh oh okay do it everyone because
you know
just feel like i'm i'll go ahead
and yes looking back i think well
that's too bad but at the time
really fun and my friend was also
allowed to like put whatever she wanted
on her walls and stuff and it
was like you know it was kinda
she decided to put on her walls
magazine cut out some clippings and celebrities
and move the rock yeah yeah yeah
and then we would watch we'd watch
the rock and do
you think she wanted a strong father
figure and that's why she liked the
rock and rest probably yeah no her
dad lived around the corner it was
really no big deal what will be
my father figure puts your blog what
he's cooking
i never did
it was so mirthful she wanted to
rock the suplex her mom oh yes
suplex oh yeah what's that like i
believe it's breslin above yeah it's above
it's the floor bow bozo bluing over
there yeah paul has been fiddling with
ah with chords and stuff for the
past
and paying attention and participating in the
i o c and i don't mean
chords on guitar y o c bring
your own chords yes i had a
um i thought this would this would
be a help this connector which is
connector is bra
wow that was really and it was
giving me um peeking it was like
oh my headphones it's giving me peek
it's giving peaky getting distortion
those headphones are better for you what's
that those oh dear
i said those headphones are better for
you than the ones you usually use
yeah well i i'm using over ear
headphones because i used in years for
an entire day i think i'm going
to be unhappy yeah and i'm gonna
take it out on you guys oh
your buds are are very bad for
you i think oh you're here ear
buds are very bad for you yeah
i've i've
because i've had troubles with your tonight
oh no here we go with scottish
trouble it's tinnitus that's well okay i
said oh my guy said tonight is
to huey lewis and he corrected me
and said tinnitus sorry huey but it's
tonight as no one's ever said tim
i've heard changes before but fuck that
it's tonight i'll be googling it's supposed
to
the ten inches anyway so which would
you rather say i would rather say
tonight is so this time it's so
size all day every day sounds like
you're saying something ridiculous it sounds it
reminds rear dick now reminds us and
rhymes with penis
when i think about my tinnitus i
think
i have minutes of the penis and
it is my penis is too now
people pronounce it ten nights as if
it is a condition such as laryngitis
however it's actually pronounced as if it's
a condition such as yeah that's why
i'm doing it and it just makes
it the english is so strange but
but but maybe malicious
but maybe that's because this is british
website tinnitus and american see when i
first heard someone say tinnitus i assumed
it was a british person like oh
i have tinnitus yeah i don't say
you're ready to taste of the year
but i was after your roll you
know a little bit of tinnitus inside
my little bit a little bit of
data to
a little bit of pettiness in my
here's what i gleaned up all is
i started leanings i started having zubaydah
edit dude dude scott's cleaning his tinnitus
really flared up when he had the
ear buds i started because i went
to ah palm springs once and i
spent all day out in their millions
i've been there so many times you're
not allowed to play music outside in
palm spring right but i
really hit home screen all of hamstrings
wow in the city limits you're not
allowed to play outdoor music and they
will able to turn bnb suffer your
tom spring they will they will have
to go to a hotel and hear
their shitting music yeah right yeah so
it's it's like a neighborhood thing they
will the police will literally come and
find the owners of the place so
do i guess so i was wearing
they'll come and fight like it's like
the child catcher
where is that release coming from butterfly
net yeah to your staff
so i wanted to listen to music
because i was on vacation and your
brandy i was reading i was reading
john hodgkins book and so i put
on my ipod for six hours or
whatever and with earbuds and i then
i started having trouble with my ears
whenever i would podcast he would just
get really for weeks hours
yeah out by the pool that's we're
not talking to anyone that's a lot
not really reading the book but just
lost my eyes glazing over reading the
same sentence four thousand one hundred and
two comprehending anything um but but yeah
so then i started started reading because
my sound person on the friends movie
gave me some headphones was like oh
this will help because i was wearing
earbuds when i was at the monitors
trying to add this crazy too
and why didn't you put on the
over years that's what he gave me
and he was like he gave me
some special overhears and and then the
more i started researching the more i
was like oh shit you're only supposed
to wear like your buds for an
hour like and that's it really or
otherwise damage your hearing anyway so i
would no matter what the volume is
yeah because if you're rollerblading in a
marathon
thank you lauren yeah i mean if
you're on if you're on like an
episode of charlie's angels new roller blading
yeah yeah yeah where your episode of
charlie's angels yeah that's where that happens
and that's only where that happens it's
the most commonplace sure of course but
anyway if you're an opening montage of
somebody being in california and they show
venice beach for two sec
hands sure yeah yeah i would love
to be in one of those man
you can someday how i'll make a
show and i'll put you in it
would you please only in the opening
montage rollerblading you're in the opening montage
which is on the end of every
episode in the exact same opening montage
every time but we don't draw attention
to it and then you get residual
pls don't try and you can you
get residuals hawaii says hey i'm the
same restaurant i had a i had
a friend who who did really yeah
no more can be said about that
well i didn't mean the opening theme
song i mean there's a montage just
a month oh really yeah like people
preparing to go rollers roller blading there's
people like
volleyball the show has started yeah the
new episode of setting the scene the
moderators always yeah no matter why or
why we don't say it's the same
or separate mud yeah matter where the
first scene is lower scenes in an
office we see the people waiting outside
swimming it's just playing volleyball yeah boy
i wish i was in los angeles
right yeah those are daydream they are
always happening
it sounds like a good show it
does show a show so just watch
every single day of my freaking life
um speaking of it'd be watching anything
good i will tell you this i
recently saw a video about baseball in
finland whoa and basically
what happened was a guy from finland
went to america no you know in
the in the early nineteen hundreds or
something one guy only one guy went
until they could only marry to fly
son they sent one yeah there's like
go check out americans so just let
us go we came but only one
was stuck there was no internet oh
yeah make for it back
they're like go write down everything you
see and take a picture yeah in
your mind and draw them this guy
saw some baseball games he was fascinated
by wow came back to finland he's
like there's this stick let's start there
honestly it hits so pretty much like
that really he explained it to the
best of his recollection and well that's
a mess
it's something they tried to play it
it's so they still do play it
the same way their version of it
yeah wastefully based on this guy's aussie
matter how to play yes she's a
wonder here's how base baseball's play was
first of all it's all baseball
based on birnbaum plays what are the
main differences like what are the uses
about everything is different they use a
bat but the the bases are like
a zigzag pattern on it's third base
it's a home run if you weren't
paying attention though you wouldn't probably pick
up the fact that they're in a
square now here's diamond if you weren't
paying a time and bar like baseball
thing
baseball famous last eight hours law yeah
and there's no way you cannot see
the man he couldn't stay because he
had to go investigate the rest of
america i think he got drunk at
the game
that's doubt but it's it's so so
zigzag pattern if you get to third
you're you when you get a point
there's like a big round plate at
home plate that if a circle yeah
it's but it's like it's raised it's
like a like a trash can lid
turned upside down that seems okay it's
so if you there's something about if
you
you get a ball if you throw
the ball in there like i think
you only get three swings that's it
and if you throw the ball onto
the circle plate it's a strike or
something it's why can't i also need
a video it's wow if you did
describe baseball exactly right it still sounds
like what you just said
that's true like like everyone everyone goes
oh okay yeah right around when it
sings about a land on these little
diamond i disagree first of all the
word diamond i think would be extraordinarily
oh yeah diamond but you're also talking
about clubs like baseball clubs don't land
on these little flight a lot of
heart to play that little things
called soup confusing you know but are
not even flat though they're three-dimensional that's
the home plate is famously shaped like
a little house yeah it is famous
yeah it's famous for being the most
house like shape but wouldn't that be
weird thing if someone came back and
said so then they have they have
a little house at the at the
beginning you started our house and it
but that's home
well you would you would yes you'd
say homie wow yeah yeah hearted maybe
just putting it together that it's showing
nowadays i don't think i ever have
really thought that either i might lie
and say i have but i don't
think i have i am sure that
way yeah i don't know a hundred
percent i bet it is wow
it's fun isn't it isn't the obvious
answer is the right one
it's like oc hams razor em so
what actually you owe me is pronounced
dacha so so why isn't first base
shaped like a one second base shape
like well that would be easier thursday
show three so that way are harder
to get on base i think if
it hadn't been a wrote number one
on it cool just
to kind of keep it clean i
like how it's like everyone remembers which
is which i guess it's good that
everyone remembered risers remember the first thing
you do in baseball memorize but you
don't give baseball players enough credit yeah
for memorizing for memorization has there ever
like they go up to the same
places every time when they are in
the field paul has there ever been
a time you're the baseball fanatic here
as there ever been a top really
speak so
soon as there ever been a time
where someone hit the ball and then
start running towards third and was like
no no dude yeah there must have
been bike
see where they doing dizzy bats back
at the busy man why don't they
do that after every game i don't
know at least for like fourth of
july or something yeah you're gonna see
major league players do dizzy
for the all star game due dizzy
bed i love the home run derby
they have yeah exactly if they have
a homerun derby why don't they have
a night of dizzy bats i want
i want dizzy bad night oh also
like make-up be a thing where you
come to the stadium and it's like
it's dizzy bat night and yeah they'd
be the players have to do dizzy
bets before the game
yep
and everyone gets a whipped pie to
the face yes oh wait what a
whipped cream pie and there's the whipped
pie just a whitlow pie that they
whip
like we're gonna work at the highest
bahrain you've ever seen we're gonna have
to pick this up after the break
oh okay because we gotta take a
break thing alright if you say so
here we go goodbye
and we're back did you say i
want some prizes or surprise i want
sur prizes lorna immediately which instagram what
i remember amy
my addiction i have a nice thought
mink guess is five a nice little
sightline on her phone here and it's
like she picked up her phone the
minute we said let's go to a
break so i got a sightline and
that gorgeous boot and i saw this
from boy meets world i will plug
my friend jackie's from boy meets girl
mingus whose may use me waking world
mingus okay yeah my friend danielle fishel
who played to panga on boy meets
world has a new podcast called pod
meets world this is a podcast i
actually i'm finding it fascinating wait is
it because it's a friend of yours
i hope it's a celebrity part of
the television show that they were on
it is but you know what makes
it really good and i i because
i i was
like i'm typically i don't listen to
shows that recap um television television show
stars were actually that they were okay
i don't typically listen to that everyone
could do whatever they want you really
just static mean i do really loud
in my ear buds for six hours
by the pool but what it is
is what makes it too interesting is
it's three of the stars from the
show because they were a child
the actors on it so they're telling
their shedding light on what it was
like when they were like thirteen fifteen
say abuses of course all that stuff
and it's really honest about molesting them
there wasn't a lot of us so
far but i'm saying reappointment know lou
pearlman okay the lou perlman and real
real i just want wanna relay
they're saying there's a lot of abuse
i just want to say let's start
getting real probate
true story but anyway arm really raw
and real and i really like it
and i'm really enjoying it so if
you might be interested in that you
should listen you like things that are
raw and real i do i love
sex a i love to watch raw
porn
like the unedited version yeah i i
just want to see the break i
love watching porn dailies people drinking water
trustee huh see asking questions about logistics
yeah that sounds like a lot of
fun should we end like a long
episode that'll be should we turn this
show to recapping some some television
show that we've all watched i'm trying
to think of yeah totally a show
that you should just read out of
how many bang bang every episode of
the podcast mtv show you'll have eight
thousand episodes i don't remember any of
these and then you'll be in the
grief i'd guess you don't have to
remember you just watch it back and
you talk about watch it back yeah
yes play it on your laptop but
we always did like fake commentaries for
the bank that
tv show episodes it would be for
charles came from yeah it would be
fun to feel like a real commenter
on the dvd or something yeah because
you what was happening i don't remember
neither do i
how many hours have we podcast that's
scary that can individually and cumulative learn
you're gonna get a taste of what
it's like when we do the best
ups for comedy bang bang ah what
do you mean because we do though
we do them all in one day
all one day i'm gonna get a
taste today today yeah yeah yeah i
was like what's going on what am
i doing what am i doing here
i didn't mean it to
be like a threat when you're gonna
get chased of my knuckles exactly yeah
i mean um just to taste i
think you're just gonna be interesting to
watch us you know sort of devolve
into nothingness sure yeah nothingness
it would just be a little puddles
on chairs yeah that miku you ever
buy anything from goop hold on a
second you know what before we get
to goop do you remember when fred
flintstone got yelled at by his boss
and he shrunk no did he become
the size of little magoo alien you
stuck he was petting zoo yeah dub
dubs he was talking to
oh and his boss was chewing him
out and he shrank down to al-maliki
it yes and that's what would happen
on the you know every every episode
now
he would see him trying to get
pointless his morale up so we can
grow what was the point of flintstone
oh it was just never had a
point overly trying to do can i
say no e great comic book writer
mark russell did a twelve issue run
of the flintstones which is incredible
ah you know what i would love
to be in a movie line with
stones that seem fun to act in
it does seem fun um speaking of
goop why did you ask me that
oh i saw some goop like shower
something in our bathroom today and i
was like people are people are still
ordering goop like it's brand first of
all people during your wife your wife
yes i feel like i'm not on
their online tracking everything she orders by
the way and that's really exciting thing
really good for me but you but
you get in the shakeup people are
still buying things just appear i thought
it was like a joke thing know
it's dumb joke while her vagina candle
well i mean just the company that
no i don't think it's a joke
at all it'll be funnier when the
culture was like i'm gonna this is
for fun i'm i thought i did
something for fun recently like a prank
and everyone took it seriously well yeah
she did she she's our practical joker
she put on land like a diaper
that was made out of like gold
and it was like gold leaf diapers
and it was for sale fuck no
no no no no it was a
joke to raise aware
this about how things are not affordable
like that and that's there's like a
diaper she's not the one to make
that joke i don't look i think
we have to get into the ins
and outs of what she was trying
to dano shouldn't which i didn't know
this yeah it gives homeless people hundred
dollars that being said um i have
never ordered anything from goop but i
have spent time on the website and
my friend recently
i told him about something that she
thought i would like from there which
is a a patio umbrella and she
was like i can get you a
discount and i said i'm interested wait
does this gwyneth herself know just a
random var and i can get you
a discounted patio umbrella but i was
wanting to look happy well that's the
thing i haven't looked today so i'm
like well is it still going to
be five trillion dollars because it's goop
so i might not get it but
maybe it's quality i mean there's everything
couple of quality with the difference between
like target and goop oh yeah but
i love target no targets great i
go to target all the frickin top
but sometimes i feel like the stuff
at target is is like oh yeah
you can buy this but in two
years it's going very sure a lot
of it's fast fashion and fast
you know janie haddad tompkins who married
too oh yeah i've heard of her
cheney had a tompkins wow and you've
never even done that one she is
waiting for me to see that
she loves to enter contests sweepstakes things
like that she loves love it but
she loves yeah and one time she
won this ah like portable cabana like
a beach cabana oh and so we
set it up we there was like
one part set it up on the
beach or set it up outside in
your house we set up in the
car where it was
awkward
we set it up on the beat
random there was a rag da
and there was one part that we
we couldn't quite figure out a big
part of that part we couldn't quite
figure out how it came together and
we got it together as best we
could turns out it did not matter
because it was broken oh which we
found out later but then also it
was so fucking windy that this thing
ng almost took off into the sky
like we were we were sitting under
it like sand just blow blowing all
around us but we are you know
out of the sun and then this
thing like flew up in the air
and we had to jump up to
our feet totally shooting rabbit so it
didn't become a web that's wizard of
oz shit that's scary
but the thing was broken and we
i think they sent her they were
going to send her a note so
she we don't have them anymore oh
no do they censor something different or
just be like no that luck she
was like don't worry about me i
won a sweepstakes when i was little
when toys r us and i won
a um is it was
three little pigs house and it was
hopefully a brick oh god i hope
it was the first native cardboard but
oh no but it was bitterly minimum
slogan to you know lifestyles or pig
sized yeah just like me a little
thinker
crawl inside this is when you were
the size of a really fun yeah
but then you grew to be an
adult and put away well my arms
went through both sides of the house
in my legs and i realised they
either had to wear as addressed or
donate it right yeah what did you
decide donate to the garbage
um i killed a giant v in
my home that was congruent maybe a
horn it it had something i could
hear a buzzing from upstairs it was
so it was not a bumble not
a big bumble a queen it was
it was a booth like really loud
and i could it was very big
i could see it like from far
away
oh yeah it might not been under
how did you kill it i don't
it was ever be but i don't
know what style of be it was
killer bee maybe whoa um and i
will be what i didn't because panicking
because he gf obviously with holly i'm
even more concerned about oh yeah has
she ever been stung by no but
i got so maybe like a month
ago oh no jesus i know
yet another reason i want to get
rid of this motherfucker yeah so with
extreme prejudice yeah yeah not in my
not in my house so chain sleep
i where my wife was panicking because
i was i had to act quickly
and there was nothing really around me
so i grabbed a can a glass
candle glass it landed on a screen
on the window holder so i a
glass
a glass candle with a you know
wax in it it's a candle or
you i look up to earth it's
weight of glass and the containers is
a good question ten there's wax inside
with a wick oh i see but
the candle isn't glass it's a scott's
can't come my theme a big long
glass oh sankey
oh shit
good god it's easy to tell though
so i grab a glass candle and
i put it on like you know
like trapping like a cup over the
window and then i had to replicate
out of a book that was kind
of how i said it great use
my foot and like pull it over
i got a journal and then i
ripped out a piece paper and then
i holly wasn't helping and no she
was thank god
god upstairs and so i shoved the
ah paper in and cut off the
stinger like i just happened to trap
it in such a way wow that
it like cut it off it fell
off and then i was basically riding
on wow
like fred florence yeah it was so
humiliated and i threw it outside and
i was so proud i was really
like wow i really just did that
i'm die say no first i will
say first i swatted at it with
a pillow which was kind of crazy
but yeah let's go to moving number
one yeah yeah yeah but um i
was prepared myself also by the way
mike saw two black widow
tos or if you've got to move
killers to manners imam i will say
that when we have spiders in the
house
neither janie or i am big fans
yeah so but what so that's my
job and so what i will do
is ah because the enemy of my
enemy is my friend i will scoop
that i used a manila envelope and
i scoop the spider into the envelope
how and when you you know and
i
open it up you may like spiderman
that's i believe you lost this ah
i all arrived dead and yeah i
like to write i like i will
either if it's on the wall on
the floor whatever scooped up with the
um with the the flap so it
gets in the envelope and then i
i release it outside but often i
will do this without even telling do
you have
of manila's all over the place where
to go wow i do not tell
hovered janie because you don't want her
to think you live in a spider
house yeah well like you can never
know the truth here's one that happened
like the day i was standing in
the kitchen and then i looked down
minding your own business sucking bug crawling
on me on my dress i don't
even know know how how how and
so i went cr
crazy and like flip it up quick
and then it's fine when crease appeared
like where did it go yeah that's
when that happens it's fighter can't deal
with that i'm like where did you
go you'd go lay some eggs so
we're like what's your fucking plan dude
i don't like you had one word
this dress isn't safe but go lay
some eggs on monday i guess cool
inclined e bay
oh cool i've debated telling me this
but i guess there was a lizard
in this room oh lizard yeah it
doesn't do oh tell me out the
lizards and gross yeah love them when
i went to costa rica so funny
they were only a little bikini babies
like an inch yeah yeah yeah i
when i see one scampering around outside
i'm like haha lizard
but like when i went to costa
rica i didn't want it inside they
all they all like while you sleep
there above you on the ceo talks
about this guy's actually horrible yeah i
would not want to but that's also
different lizards those are different types of
lizards i mean i wouldn't be able
to sleep with some types of lizards
in the world hey there's two types
of you and there was you either
because the other ones campers
outside um but yeah there was one
in here and then okay so then
one touch again okay so did she
get it
open the door and shoot i don't
think so yeah and then they would
then there was a big debate about
whether they should tell me oh you
guys read podiums
here's why i don't think we could
douglas debater you have thirty six years
but i think cry himself to sleep
if he knows there was lizard in
here
but here's the thing you can't tell
them here's the one that that ah
that was really bad was in my
inner old place where cool up and
i first lived together oh i went
into my office your plants dead yeah
it is
the plant that i never asked for
i kill plan i killed a plant
that was supposed to get that big
now it looks like some dr seuss
shit yeah it actually is interesting when
you think about it so i walk
i walk into my office and i'm
just stunned because there's a rat nose
i and i know that's a different
story and it just like ran off
not okay and i was like
like did i even see that i
it was so weird to to just
see a rat i had oh no
no no eighty nine from now on
i feel like i care or what
wow would cause this but jane and
i were sitting in the living room
one night and i was i think
it was
was that i was just very tired
because i'm sitting on a couch we
could talk about my couches second sure
um but you're tired so you decide
hey i'll sit on a couch i
get it yeah step number one sit
on the couch she'll she'll make any
difference yeah and so janie is in
this chair we have a recliner in
the living room and i saw ah
like kind of behind her
i saw a what looked like a
rat now just casually like walk across
the bow know and i said
i don't want to alarm but i
want you to get out of that
chair and i want you to come
over here and then i looked all
over for this rat no that did
not exist it so you just log
roll roll on hallucinated no oh no
no ho
but i just can't go under they
go into the tiniest hole yeah i
i'm two stories one is that i
say well i agree
i live guys are gonna kick me
i want to complete my red story
at some point okay that's fine you
can have that goal i once looked
into that for you that had rats
in the walls i come to find
out oh shit i didn't know that
obviously um to your scratchy scratchy yeah
well no i saw poo
oop and and i go oh there's
rat poop and then goes it's lizard
poo i go it's not lizard poop
like he was trying he was trying
to tell us don't be worried it's
a lizard pool mike and i was
like that's ridiculous clown and it turns
out here i'm in the walls and
found him i came to kill them
on your move ah
and he would he locked out i
did not live in this place though
he walked out with was this the
handful of rats by the tail was
this the third place that's what i'm
i didn't see them i did ah
yes rats by new hale yes it
was a very like place with cool
but place yeah not an archer place
no the other thing that was
maybe i told you this story hold
on a second this is mike's account
is handfuls of rats by the tail
there were at least yeah though there
were there were that this guy walked
out from with it with like under
the how ram under the hood but
there were so many no no i'm
not kidding
um okay but anyways um what my
dad was visiting once and this was
ah years ago and we went on
to dinner and then he was like
i gotta tell you something i saw
a big bug in your house because
it was like this big i was
like inches inches long and i was
like why the fuck are you tell
me like it was not
a cockroach but something in that vein
like something just scary okay and i
was like what do you talk about
why why you're telling us now he's
because because he goes i saw this
huge bug and i was like what
happens like i don't know where it
went i was like i hate this
story i wish you never told it
horrible story okay cut to smash an
hour later we're home or watching tv
we're sitting on the couch having a
great time
it turns into the book but it
was me out of the corner of
my eye crawling along the arm of
the couch is right by my eye
is the fucking bug it's huge huge
so they start screaming i'm like like
nah dad is so bad ass he
got up he just grabbed it with
his palm like he does
grabbed his fist and then opened the
door and threw it out the door
it's five and it was on the
lambda like oh we're like stuck on
the couch like he just did it
you i couldn't do it he wanted
to protect you just want to get
off what would you have done that
if you hadn't been there with ur
woody yeah wow no no she's very
um old world in that sense doesn't
give a fuck that's a
thing like our ancestor you shouldn't see
a bug frog window yeah yeah okay
so rat hole on a second when
you see the movie so like a
budding ronnie moon take it
this ceo boom fake it wow no
bow like somebody's regular crawling on them
or something i don't know if i
could do it if i was called
upon to do that oh really what
not well genius like rat i could
deal with these dating only make them
cdi which is not effective
to scare the actor well known yeah
no like here the other cga know
like in the mummy i know i
will lose that i don't see diana
jones inspired but all the bugs were
fake the scraps that's so ah yes
they look superficially doesn't do anything like
my soul as the viewer when you
watch indiana jones and there's a million
spiders everywhere you're like yeah
yes this sucks yeah that's like hey
yeah well was i love practical effects
i do too yeah janie once went
to with her with her mom and
stepdad she went to this ah exhibition
there was some science exhibition or something
and they had but all these kinds
of insects from all over the world
or whatever they did not know what
was in this room
they walked in the hair on jamie's
arms stood up before she even saw
anything what yes she has like spicer
since yourselves i guess so she before
i knew something bad was gonna be
in the room she just like something
was telling her hey don't be in
here oh wow yeah i just got
out when i walked in here oh
alright story so rat alright now i
see this rattling my collusion am i
right or am i hallucinating this rack
because it just yeah wasn't this paul
did not hear you so i so
i was like you know and say
i'll tell my story after you finish
your is my copy the end the
best thing to do in this situation
is ignore it and hope that it
never happens again yeah of course right
and that's what you do so
so i did that for and then
a few weeks so you don't think
you should pick your wife
that's what i did a few weeks
later i come back home there's a
rat again of course and it's campers
away i'm like ok we got to
figure out this priming and i total
people up and she's like this is
your deal exterminator and so i looked
up solutions and i went to home
depot or whatever and the first thing
i tried to do is the humane
situation which is like this glue trap
you
but baits like peanut butter or cheese
right in the middle of this glue
thing and then they get stuck in
it and then there's no more break
off it's just there's still alive in
in the morning you let him out
or whatever i think glue traps and
you wag your finger at them like
oh say you think they're bad i
didn't say something we're just closed behind
it or something no this is
like an out it's it's like it's
literally just like a plate with glue
okay well maybe it's a snap so
yeah so i put it out and
i put the i put the superhero
homewares yeah and
in the morning go outside the the
bait is gone there's like little tiny
feet mark right through it they got
right through it yeah so we're like
ok glues to humane they're fucking survivors
man yeah so i go alright yeah
you gotta give it up to him
you got here he got a landrace
greatest machine yes ah so i said
alright i'm just gonna do the regular
track
ap and put it out there and
sure enough two a m shah kong
i hear just go off and cool
ups like is that that i went
yeah and i got out there and
it's just sitting there in the kitchen
and arms folded like you care to
explain access for
dollar said
like it's a lawsuit yeah yeah
so then extra was recorded deck brake
squatters right i got rid of it
and go up gave me credit for
all of that she's like you you
got the rat and but it's just
so gross think about a wrap feeling
there for like a month or like
every night coming out going hey what's
up here today it's horrible i can't
handle that but you also have to
think like hey do get the message
there's not
here for you yeah we can finally
accept there is every day can't we
make our home getting they're getting everything
they want can we make our homes
like impenetrable i would love from ants
from bugs from i know you open
the doors occasionally from dance to zebras
rise from aardvarks to zebras i mean
we i've probably talked about my fly
killer of course we don't have time
we got
take a break but we gotta love
fly by
and we're back to tells you the
tennis racket that electrocute flies yeah oh
yeah it's honestly pretty fun but it's
pretty darn well it flies well you
play baseball no matter you know i
don't feel what's the worst our our
what our own mosquitoes mosquitoes or hawk
durable let's get rid of all mosquitoes
and there by the way so many
fucking mosquitoes these days in law that
used to never be mosquitoes yeah really
when i move you know yeah we're
not mosquitoes and i remember thinking nobody
came right over here in lumber that
relates yeah from like china or something
like in the last nine years no
yeah yum talk about angina like about
eight yrs
years or so ago there was some
mosquito e batch of lumber they got
shipped here and now we have excuses
but my friends was saying okay well
you know what i've read about the
solution of this is you need to
get a bat house in you know
yeah so he's like like midler used
to sing at the bat house it
was your cat houses ah bath
oh yeah she's sing in court was
that the best was my little one
that was ooh yeah i mean that
was i mean richard pryor he used
to perform there that's right so it's
like this little tiny envelope be looking
thing that you're supposed to put up
in your in the crevice of your
of your house and you sent me
like all of this but that's enough
oh but no bats like live in
them they sleep in them so it's
outside so it's outside right and then
he he sent and then the places
that sell them they say like bats
can eat up to like one thousand
bugs an hour or something right and
so pigs you know what i don't
want that's around me well that's the
thing okay so
then i look up another site and
it says yeah you could eat like
five sandwiches an hour but you don't
you get full
all of this research is dumb they're
not like sitting around there like thousand
bucks two thousand and eight thousand bucks
four thousand bucks they get full after
like an hour and so it's it's
like now you just have bats and
bugs around here now don't want that
i remember going to the brookfield zoo
in chicago which shields has zoo yeah
well we rarely we rarely went to
that zoo because lincoln park zoo is
free
we go there all the time when
goodbye so is free but brookfield zoo
costs money so we went there on
school field trips everyone's well and we
um they remember they have this bat
cave you walk through it it was
dark and there were giant flying over
us i remember specifically if i remember
correctly but i remember this little factoid
that might maybe be true give us
a i don't want it to be
a fact it's a factoid for sure
make sure it's a factoid before you
say should avoid it's a toyed toy
a toy tidy toy to toy it's
a toy um the fact is that
if you threw if you were walking
under the bats in this like cave
or whatever it was you um if
you threw your keys up in the
air they would catch them wow and
did anyone do it but i don't
think they encouraged it but i don't
know i don't know
that's true what if you got like
i don't know how to alarm it
out and you got us a second
set of keys just to test this
out yeah what if a lock to
the watcher
i don't know
okay well it's time for three maybe
someone out there can tell me if
it's true i'll never be able to
figure it out if there's to be
a video of it if it's true
let's send us the video of the
guy running to third lee and send
us a video of a bat catching
the ring of keys while fun houses
ring of keys plays hundred and the
bats going and your reading
ah i see i like that a
lot because i think they've they're so
they're some of the summer they're really
cool i just don't want to see
them in my general eyeline i do
really that's the thing yeah you go
to austin and see all the bats
fly over that i've never seen in
any time i've been what's wrong with
you and why no avoid the thing
you love
i went to carlsbad caverns okay day
i saw joe's three d carl's junior
caverns wow i love him berghaus
okay guys it's time for reacher you
remember the three-tier that we played called
celebrity hunt yeah i liked that one
do you remember how to play it
it's like you think of you you
think of a so someone says the
celebrity and we go hunt and then
you have to come up with a
celebrity who has the same their name
begins with the last letter of the
previous name and it goes until
we can't write the last letter that's
what it is yes ah huh
yeah it's called ah celebrity thirty hunts
like i said yeah and and and
we and we play it and we
play it and and you like it
you like it and you listen to
it and you ask for more like
did you just slay it you just
look it up yeah okay and that
is how we play just how we
play so somebody says celebrity ah the
next person who
has to go hunt we go of
course we go hunt yeah we go
and the next person has to say
another celebrity who b whose name begins
with the last letter of the previous
celebrity yeah oh okay and we're in
a rhythm no it's not because we
just not all knew why like we
don't clapper and you want to keep
it going though you can't just ah
tick around i you can't ah you
gotta get you this fast as you
possibly can yes okay great so yeah
you keep a steady rhythm if you
can let's go i'm glad you're fucking
out okay let's do it go clockwise
alright what are we going well doesn't
understand the stark i always get famous
oh that's right it goes scott paul
laurence scott paul laura
then do it it's lantern and it's
like turning up the volume nods midnight
your six or whatever the yeah i'm
on your sex yeah yeah and you're
not about seven eight yeah yeah seventies
like when you eat attend oh ever
imo i haven't noah my wiki v
rating has gone down so horses
that's happened since i got the boot
on ya by cell of the buddha
oh probably aussie by this time in
my life when does it get hot
tomorrow but oh well that's when does
it get off i haven't been any
question in years okay samantha
alright here we go ready i'll start
samantha who
oh classic show huh we start with
hunt doctor whose first name is samantha
is
oh three hunt antonio bandera is hot
susan sarandon hards natalie portman hans natalie
a earth-moon yeah earth man okay we're
in hot wait what
okay so i started with do the
n maybe i'll get a cheap okay
huh and natalie imbruglia hunt angelina jolie
huns ed norton hi nick nolte lti
ha and edward scissor
huh your instant yeah why does celebrity
know it's real people it's ok so
now so everybody seems going as long
as i can okay no yeah i
know that's how the game should go
a little bit another round right here
we go ready i think it's a
winter challenge so you you start with
e okay ready yeah me outfit
this hunt ellen de generous huh huns
smith will
i'm realised we could comment yes
see okay try again now i'm gonna
start you're gonna start alright i'm gonna
go out of this i can't think
of phone do you go clockwise which
means next scott and the yeah huh
hugh grant huh tim burton and natalie
portman huns nicolas cage hunt edward albee
huh
l and all the whoa wow v
yeah wow be yeah you're right you're
right huh did i tell you i
met him yet he would yeah did
he say it's tinnitus you he worked
with ah he worked with our english
class when he was to continue
but it was anyways alright okay and
jesus so it's the egos to you
ie yep um ready ha ha and
eric stoltz
i'm zealand ah who are exalted good
yeah yeah good so you get dizzy
wright said julie okay okay i'm sorry
why two to three huh zen de
la hoz oh is just me yeah
oh that wasn't okay okay huh zendaya
huh
and alice walker huh
rebecca romain stamos ah yes romaine romaine
okay huh
needs burgas hud's sean connery cause yolanda
hadid huns is yolanda yeah yeah that's
from years ago diane are dina lohan
wow
is real a real glimpse into the
types of celebrities nate berkus hello and
say hi guys nathan fielder hides richard
ruby right
tito jackson huh that's you know jessie
otieno yeah but yeah my tito jackson
oh my t steel oh mind um
nia long huns greg
gregory peck huh
alright let's start alright paul hugo oh
my god um hi hud's jeffrey wright
highs t yeah
sia carrera hods into the ni oita
oh okay ah
eric
person flow when i used to know
ah give it so much doesn't notice
delivery guys
use a real guy you have to
go you have to go up ie
hi eric stonestreet hides ah um you
know yeah
trisha yearwood huh donald duck huh
does it drop scissorhands north carolina s
ago oh my god we're losing c
d d and huh donald trump huh
ah penelope cruz hans zen da ha
ha new game hunt um um alice
cooper hot randy newman hunt
i love it when ah um neat
new lands ah ne thin you're out
huh billion and that's how i picture
it because a rookie because he was
a rookie itself castle castle was just
a comic-con so much the rookie cause
play i couldn't believe it
yeah real rookie cosplay really how do
you know think there would be brown
codes they were just cops lorin what
do you think about the recent dave
cool yay comments is there something regarding
eleven more so oh yeah we gotta
check in with you what did he
say he said that he remembers when
he first heard that song on the
radio and he was like hey this
is a good groove this is cool
and then he was like good
singer too what do you think popeye
and they're like subtle chuck then he
like heard some of the lyrics and
was like wait a minute was this
about me and looked it up and
saw it was atlanta's morissette went out
immediately bought the record and then listen
to the whole thing and realize that
the lyrics were all about him and
he said i think i've really hurt
this
person oh my god that's actually so
sad but he kept silent about it
for all this time for her now
thirty years did he ever say anything
to her not that i think so
i think he contacted i think part
of the stories is contactor and she
was like no prob i think she'd
be like okay shit got twelve trillion
dollars for this because
everyone loves taper didn't go to number
one i'm sure that's the best revenge
yeah a number one is all or
nothing like going to number one after
you break up with someone where did
she go down on him in the
middle of again dinner theater a theater
and i remember what i saw that
when i was younger mouthful of mashed
potatoes when i was working at all
we talked about this i feel like
i have deja vu
when i was in olive garden there
was a couple who was checking key
but hey literally said she had mashed
potatoes that i don't remember how i
was gonna know she was blowing during
dinner what what dinner
a restaurant order
no movie theater hotdog the hottest of
dogs now so switch that meat into
one log do you have a frank
virtues yeah so i'm working at olive
gardens right now i'm sorry more
someone started blowing the guy during dinner
i would think you manderson this below
guy you're a creep i love this
so someone said i'll have the never-ending
salad never breadstick over and brittany breadstick
under the table as i'm blowing and
we were all like walking by going
and because one of the waiter who
in charge of that section it was
a room that didn't have a ton
of people in it and it's not
an olive garden there aren't tablecloths like
your family's so the guys like this
girls blowing this guy under the table
and we would all we all kind
of walk by and she was like
kind of laughing and she was under
the tape is funny it's pretty funny
that's disgusting
there aren't there aren't tablecloths at olive
garden i don't i think you're probably
still maybe there maybe i guess maybe
there were but maybe there's i don't
think there are white i don't think
they're yeah there were really no no
no you'll like they were just table
they're doing this itinerary style picturing my
my most recent olive garden excursion two
hours ago i'm like diary
yeah in the bathroom
before eating yeah just your room i
have a fifty dollar gift card to
olive garden from winning yes we know
aren't you going to take us i
suddenly get you all enough food i'm
just taking a pay difference i'll just
eat the never ending thing is it
called did they call it never-ending it's
all you can eat everlasting breadsticks hospitality
ato
alright goodbye hey mambo hospital italia
okay look we've got some business to
take her yes three team usa gmail
if you want to write to us
freedom usa um on twitter and instagram
if you don't want to write to
us ah our phone number haha haha
in poo yeah i'm gonna call us
if you
you want to just listen to us
hey we like that too you're doing
it the way you're doing it now
or if you wanna listen ad-free if
you're not already go to stitcher premium
or cbp world dot com and also
you know there's gotta be some cruk
terms or somebody has got to be
some crack times i just had one
sensitive for some reason they sent me
literally
one it's just the ignored fun this
was any other day and thought that
too i stitcher i have no idea
they just ignore no request was made
no
i mean i request value in december
i was gonna say did you ever
get the ignored and maybe it was
on back order or something jesse only
thing i could ask for more money
for the show and then that's what
they sent reply
alright goodbye goodbye
ugh