three
duh
oh wasting it live every time
i wanted to that's what i was
proposing that's well we all did didn't
we well no no one did i
ain't looking at you all i was
doing got on the stage under the
spot light with the micro right we
have okay here the studio we have
a little in the corner we have
a little stage that's going to spotlight
in a little little mice my other
show i was hell that's pulling on
the corner
that's folly mccollough come back to threesome
everyone i'm back i'm paul f tompkins
i'm lauren laugh kiss i'm scott
duty guys damn it why did i
let you be laughs yeah um thanks
for listening everyone this is the first
episode that we've recorded since we've been
releasing the oh my god that's so
fun such great feedback from everyone such
great fi thanks for listening thank you
for listening thank you for just
giving us a chance this little guy
thank you for sucking on gelato just
thinking was signal to tell it all
elderly anyone going to little ray's keep
your mouth a small
little did any we haven't really see
it today would enjoy last week's episode
about us to keep your mouse really
small and trying to try to say
words we did we did we do
for endlessly didn't oh wait
well hopefully sound familiar
i've not heard the episode i know
i forget everything i say moments after
that was that was one of our
features it was a fee trade and
la teachers are bonus we don't want
to drive you guys crazy features are
coming later don't worry we got over
thirty it comes at the end my
baby my baby oh my baby
lauren did you have like a grandmother
who'd who had an interesting way of
talking or because every when you when
you you byron allen sounds like such
an obvious guy wish i was by
earlier what did you just buy the
weather channel why yea did god wouldn't
want a american success story i love
it he ll
like built himself up from like he
was a fine comedian what have you
in the eighties and then he had
that talk show where he would ask
leading questions of comedians and then he
bought the weather channel well where do
you get all the money before then
he was on a show called real
people real people right yeah it was
um a sort of it was like
that segment at the end of the
local news but a whole
our of that where it's like here's
a weirdo who does a weird thing
i told the story questions wait one
wasn't it like a pretty low amount
that he paid for the weather channel
like more than like less than you
would think a channel would cost you
to have lapsed into the public domain
yeah watch the other queen who watches
the weather why do you want the
watchman
why do you want to own that
what do you get from that i
don't understand well why would anyone created
if there's nothing i don't know are
they selling it
um no but i told a story
about real people on r e m
i think it must have come out
ah paul just got some startling new
that had to put on his john
lennon says huh that here's what's embarrassing
imo i'm at this new i'm at
the point where said the studio's dark
spontaneous nation lighting which is the nicest
podcast lighting and
and so live-in chef kevin handed me
his phone where he looked up how
much byron allen bought the weather channel
four oh and i'm at an age
now where in this somewhat darkened room
and with maybe the screen not turned
all the way up to it's maximum
brightness united ten upgrade that i need
to put on my glasses the only
glasses i would see on my prescription
sunglass
houses so i look like a weirdo
um who just needs to read good
oldies to look cool to read something
i have to have my old dade
three hundred million dollars of his own
dollars and that's i don't know like
that's a lot of money obviously but
to me that sounds like oh i
wouldn't think you could get it for
that
little like i mean i would think
it would have to be more than
i guess although when you consider like
the like star wars was a billion
that's a third of star wars the
weather channel yeah i guess that's where
you know
a hundred million yeah i guess it's
like like all you need to do
is create three weather channels and you've
created star wars yeah do you think
she's trying to do i think he
might be doing it the weather channel
for starts putting on his own shows
and they're like silly and there's like
droids in them what if he starts
lying about what the weather is oh
my god do we trust byron allen
with
this information i also was watching the
weather thick weather and it was really
soothing like in the morning it was
just like a comforting background noise but
then they were showing the traffic you
know numbers and i was like who
the fuck is tuning in to see
how long it's going to take them
from this like who does right one
there well at some point aren't they
going to phase it out and just
go just check your gps yeah it
feels like yeah it feels like the
whole thing is that now just go
to twitter it's all there yeah but
i also was thinking about how when
i was little everything on tv now
will just say like it's just blanket
just say just gotta tell is this
trip going to take a better twitter
but i see someone i wasted about
my trip to the grocery hey boss
i'm gonna be late just check twitter
a manga worth it
well um i used to watch bob
marianne in the morning on fox ah
marianne books ah fun fucks mary op's
ron and maryann marzano who did have
an affair as far as i wow
that's juicy as far as you remember
i remember like learning that google it
chef and whoa
hey lawrence turn bossy yeah google it
yeah here are three things about that
now and laura and that was like
you went into the mode of being
one of those hosts ah also i
don't think google chengdu government said before
it's like usually make me some breakfast
chef but google little chef um wow
one i always think when i when
i was growing up i would watch
the traffic thing and i was so
confused like who is going from that
specific okay because i'd be like to
to o'hare or something why are you
going to o'hare and you know that
but i never understood that you would
deduct like oh i'm generally going over
there so it'll take forty minutes from
where you wondered why anyone would ever
go to o'hare well because
the traffic to patterns like the way
they describe it on the news it's
like it's forty minutes from the one
ten to okay rain man
she's human atm yeah
huh cause ya i finished doing so
may still works as an insult by
the way coaches manages three year old
thirty year old references
okay okay okay first of all also
i went to go meet baba marianne
and they had a thing where like
bob and rain man oh my god
they had a thing where you could
go meet them and you can bring
a piece of fruit with a face
drawn on it and just do that
position ie and anyone who comes anyone
who can find the office and got
hard
the second they had a thing where
the thing when you could meet with
part of taste of chicago which is
a big food fast sure and they
were sitting on a stage and you
could walk bring up ah a fruit
that you drew a face on anyone's
face or like you did something anything
just like made it funny
you like a clock face even if
you're being a pinhead
from the hellraiser franchise head
oh the hell razer meets bonehead bonehead
i took my brother and i went
and took them ah cantaloupe with a
silly face john and i got down
cantaloupe will surely could you not meet
them if you did not bring the
way to the play store if you
brought the food with a face on
it could you also not meet them
could you just brought back
just did that and no interest oh
ooh what's going on here
just hear me
i mean bob and marianne come on
why who is there your to play
with your fruit with a face on
the cover yes of course i do
but what does that have to do
with any of this
ah well and i think they would
but you have an affair so you
met them what you seek the dan
and i remember so that's a memory
i have i don't know if it's
you or you are jack are you
there married now thank you there okay
marry other people use your memory them
having sex yeah
because i don't think no either for
they knew that they were both married
to other people and they married each
other so it was like oh yeah
okay i always find that interesting when
two people on the local news find
love yeah like this just in love
they always say that just seems that
often i think it's rare well there
was one on cbs or paul real
love i think it's very
there there's um some crying my wife
and i have a marriage of convenience
ah what's convenient about sharing me and
we have to do errands for each
other oh okay i got there i
can be an easy but you still
do her errands you still do her
yeah
ah aaron ha errands
you have to do
guide ah spiv out of date movie
reference
what the guy from the room oh
i didn't think that's what i was
doing what you're doing chicken like i
do around the house that has no
reference point but i do think it
sometimes sounds like um the guy from
ah father of the bride mark short
yeah like character character or just in
general
to my men
what i was asking ah i was
asking about like a grandmother who hasn't
who has a voice because like you
do these like never before you do
voices funky now like trash hong what
did you what
honk or like my comp like the
honk generation but i was asking about
genre whether when you do characters oh
my god it's our first loss sceptics
what are you asking that sometimes you
do characters like eric huh
and jack
a twenty moving it now i get
it you know sometimes you're leaning into
some specific thing no i just wonder
if you're like doing a specific verse
oh um no my gram parents ah
no right rain man i have four
grandparents went to three for my grandfather
judge wagner
um where's joshua after these is he
still with us he's google it schiff
go show his phone can't do it
but just setting on fire i think
he may have passed away setting fire
keep best chess wampler shame what happened
yeah chapel opener
um he died from never having existed
he's an idea though let's judge whopper
he was the original said wampler it's
original oh this is like a reverence
that maybe you don't get he was
the original host of the people's court
ah as opposed to all those other
hosted the people's courts that we can
think of they while they did can
tell they did but one you said
it like it was a dig no
i
i said it as if it's real
zeroes will be fine i said is
like it's not like family feud where
you can go oh re ca listen
i'm telling you so many family feud
it's like it's a death louis steve
harvey the blind smack hey louis c
k oh what that was his next
job that meet what what
if that was his next job though
he's forced he's forced those family yes
i'm saying really tame and he has
to act like he really likes it
that's just i love that to avoid
i avoid going to prison that black
mirror punishment yes exactly he has to
act it has to be like you
cannot be here to tell me right
yeah not even with your eyes right
do you think bill ca
cosby's gonna die in jail i hope
so
i don't think he's gonna die ever
because of all the pudding
who's this
that little skip what if he makes
himself a special potion that he makes
him live forever oh he probably kid
this is edgy stuff i love him
did you did you grow up watching
that show or yes i loved that
show yeah it says i feel sad
because we i mean for every reason
but like the ah the fact that
all of those actors are like they
lose out from what oh and so
do many people from all that he
did write every well yeah i mean
it's certainly
the worst
i no i've quitted his ideas it's
all been talked about i'm saying no
no but i agree like
on the pilot of bang bang there
there's like a guy who has a
couple of lines that we found on
like a sexual predator list four years
later and i was just like well
now that's ruined that oh plotline you
might answer yeah it was my first
touch me
um just kidding but i mean that's
just collateral damage going to edit the
collateral damage certainly it's collapse damn cut
down that damn guy's de um clube
das every good project has some collette
damn
judge orders he saw alive no picture
isn't he dead show like that what
any diet leaned close to the mike
to shit yeah he's i guess she's
like let me get this closer those
for the asr people
do you guys like a s mar
no no i don't wow cool end
of conversation
okay i like it yeah and i
love it no i don't really what
do i consider because because there's many
different things it's not like just any
of those noises works for every working
there anything that makes you a little
lilly felix guess okay because this asr
yeah ah i guess so
um is this asr
i have some pencil shavings here oh
yep is it okay is this a
s m r
yeah do you think anyone wow yes
really i think there's like there like
a white noise app that's like snore
i will say i don't have a
partner and i say write my dad
how's baby i miss you but my
my dear departed dog rocky ah when
we first got him i was shy
shocked by the snoring because i used
to have a girlfriend that snored and
it was really loud yeah yeah and
anyway it would keep him anyway keep
me up at seven i would always
be like isn't her anything you can
do about this i was like twenty
two right twenty two and not very
sensitive i'm just like can't you fucking
fix your snoring um i don't she
never did anything about it as far
as i know but when i did
do something about it she got
rid of that boyfriend yeah she's like
oh keep snoring hello
with a million other yeah oh yeah
laying it on the land but um
but when we got was shocked by
how much he snored him and i
learned to love it because it was
sort of like white noise but it
also let me know that he was
okay and breathing yeah and i was
like oh this is good this is
like a little ah safety blanket
for me of like rockies still alive
yeah my i didn't pass away during
the during the night your cats like
yours it was like maybe i mean
it's like this
that's pretty cute that's it that's a
wow that's some wow oh yeah yes
have you ever as a joke when
you orgasm done a voice like that
like oh baby hello
don't wouldn't it be funny though you
get what i'm saying is let's make
a pang sex why never next time
we knew it oh yeah
let's do it and let's all do
it separately wow what have you but
if you chose one array okay i'm
i wanna know as long as we
agree mine goes hippie
that would be really funny if like
you did it three minutes later the
afterglow is just totally sila you just
um gusta alright you guys aren't up
for it i'm not going to do
it so well why just don't think
sexist joke
can we jerk off and do the
site all right do we have to
vulgar or bark off each other yeah
let me do it privately okay regularly
k do ah swear just so long
okay welcome to privately k probably cable
i'm okay if you have something to
tell me private yeah i remember dell
laser opening your secret is my secret
okay
yes i have a private thing i
went to tell them okay let me
take you off yeah
yeah we'll see
doctor
they're listening to tom for us right
now yeah finer can you know because
i can't i can't
okay well the music's very loud here
i guess it's good to hang up
what an episode a devastating episode of
uhm remember we said it was calm
privately gay privately k um do we
have to go to a break no
eddie what one more minute one more
minute okay what are we going to
do all the time remember when we
all counted two oh my god sixty
fifth
eighteen time we did a lower and
have we got a story for you
this is on the bang bang dvds
it's on the bank bank dvds um
where he kind of family doing a
talkback for the musical episode yes and
me scott
thomas lennon casey willis casey wilson
the end i think that may be
it and and we had a certain
amount of time and and to do
this talkback after the episode too much
time too much time yeah no one
wanted to talk back to us ouch
and we took questions and there were
no more questions and then instead of
just calling going okay thank you i
felt like we needed to fill the
time because it wasn't enough
if we hadn't been you the episode
is only twenty two minutes yeah you'd
only been on stage for the there
was a twenty two minute episode the
talkback was scheduled for two and a
half hours oh my goodness knows like
it was like thirty five minutes for
a twenty five minute episode and after
fifteen minutes no one wants to talk
back yeah so and there was fifteen
minutes left i was like well what
do we do for the
x fifteen minutes you asked how much
time we had left and i think
they said twelve minute twelve minutes and
you said well we could we could
either stop now or we could fill
twelve minutes somehow and i said let's
as andrew luck whoever goes yes herefordshire
nah thomas thompson i were in character
here's the foe that's right he was
the fan i will say harder to
ask questions of characters i think it
would be more fun yeah yeah
yeah la la la
oh it's listening anymore
yeah i don't know i liked the
first episodes that they did then they
came back and they're just yelling and
then you counted and so i said
what we accounted to sixty twelve times
twelve times and the whole audience at
it we the joint know just four
of oh my god but didn't join
doing that we got any here and
there yeah yeah you can see it
on the tv
edu that's really fascinating the thing it
will be it will haunt me forever
that we didn't do it twelve times
i think we did it oh whoops
oh really we didn't do it twelve
times oh that's too bad we should
so sad but i am although a
n do it twelve eight is enough
right what does this raised by tv
oh awesome raffle ooh la la
with la roche lauren did you ever
see that show eight is enough yes
yes but i thought so many times
but i couldn't even tell you what
it's about i remember just a fan
of us more yeah the tezos that
was the blink of mary nitra coach
from growing pains had to spend a
bill which season bowel cancer and nowadays
xd what they did with the goldbergs
two meadows yeah well spit up okay
so did he really i didn't know
myself good for him i'm glad to
hear that ah yeah yeah there's all
sorts of spinoffs nowadays but another name
another i guess girona yes whatever l
a okay that's doesn't count but that's
more of a franchising account well because
i've seen
no one can know it doesn't count
exactly martin lawrence right they take one
character and then kill that character their
own show yeah they don't say there
was like mark harmon never showed up
he never showed up on ah on
ah c s i and it was
like ah hi i'm ah david caruso's
cousin or whatever
i mean they do backdoor pilots on
these shows like c s i miami
was fifty four anyway sure ah but
it's not but it's back in the
day it used to be as if
larry wow you love danson yeah fuck
it here's benson here's the breakout character
let's give him his own show yeah
but then it got weird like mork
and mindy was a forced that was
a backdoor pilot yeah right
or they had unhappy days oh yeah
ruby's yeah they just they were going
to make this show but they just
stuck an alien on happy days for
no reason no it's so crazy i
was just watching the um should save
it for his team but yeah i
was just watching school z ah first
episode of ah hang on mister cooper
and he does a whole thing where
he is the first pet apparently cooper
for show anguish yeah
ya the pile it's mark curry with
the pilot is shot on the growing
pains set because they didn't have them
oh yeah yeah we blame sasha when
he comes out and he's like hey
he starts doing a whole thing and
then alan thicke comes on he's like
what are you doing in my house
and he's like saying your house you're
on things like just kidding i'm alan
thicke you're using my set and they
have this whole conversation about it why
make me
like comfort it's like fifteen minute long
conversation on hulu and then way too
long and then they ah they use
like and they use the whole thing
which is really confusing when you're watching
you kind of do need that and
then at the end he's like i
hope you like to show please keep
watching and like the next week he's
like hi i'm mark kerr you might
not know me but i hope you
like my show i'm doing this show
i mean like does this whole explanation
it's
raised so strange were there's still pictures
of the seaver family on the wall
you know if they turn backwards like
you can't look at this super family
no but it made no sense it
was just just felt uncomfortable because they're
like they're in the different house what
a strange yeah but but it's so
crazy because back in those days i
feel like
the networks used to spend even more
money on things why wouldn't they just
write well the set for the show
and they kept like i think they
were really trying to make it work
by bringing all these actors or designers
i just burped
it would my tim gunn impression make
you burp yeah right to know why
they've got all these actors in to
try to be like oh they're all
from different t j f shows or
whatever like make it comfortable i've done
it for two shows for for david
situation i don't know if you remember
that one were you in it that
bob and david thing we did it
on the the everybody loves raymond said
we
they'll be fun and then for another
show that i did with matt besser
we had to we had to rent
someone said i don't even know whose
it was and you guys say to
be recorded a fifteen minute long conversation
explaining yeah exactly when you guys are
just hanging out there i ever tell
you about the the mork and mindy
backdoor pilot how like excited i was
by it i didn't know who robin
williams
was i saw i was big into
happy days i watched that and then
i had this thing where anything i
ever watched a movie a tv show
or whatever if i was hanging out
with my mom going shopping or whatever
i would i would do the plot
and just explain every single thing that
happened i i'm sure it must have
taken longer than the twenty two minutes
no doubt that it actually was yeah
and we were in a grocery
a store or a hardware storage feels
like a hardware store i don't know
for some reason and detail and i
was and i finally got to the
end and i was like i was
doing every joke that robin williams made
like and then he's like none who
knew which means this country and and
my mom is paying the cashier and
the cash
here's like looks like someone is a
big happy days fan and i felt
like it was condescending in some way
and i felt embarrassed you should have
that is me and i want adults
her children like that no but it's
what they're trying to be oh she's
trying to just include me of like
hey looks like so much but it
was almost like oh i know what
you're doing you're trying to you're trying
to this is how i felt this
is not how no no but that
is how you feel as a kid
oh i see what you're trying to
do you're trying to co-opt happy days
which is like real artist
it's doing a new you're trying to
be as cool as happy days no
i know what you're doing you're doing
happy days you're just doing the plot
of happy days well that when you're
you really never let it go that
that the occur tone that that grown
ups will use when you're a kid
it yeah it is not you always
know that it's condescending i but see
here's the thing i i've never
vw is i don't know if you
guys met him little chi and i've
met kai and i haven't met him
but i saw his signs leading to
his layer he's an exciting little fellow
he loves to dress his spider-man um
and i i hating that tone i
always talked to him like hey kai
how are you how are young fellow
what's going on blah blah blah you
know i talked to him like this
yeah and cool ups like why don't
you talk to him like you know
be nicer to him or something like
i guess the baseline for all adults
talking to any kid is like hi
how are you what's a weird and
you talked to him like a guy
that you share an office with
do you mind give me a little
top-off on this coffee i think kids
like when you talk to them like
they're your save me i think so
too that's how i feel don't don't
like it when you do in no
way does make them feel like you
don't care about kids or something but
like when i was a babysitter i
didn't talk to them like like they're
like that baby voice or something it's
like you just said we've gotta go
let's do it you know it's like
and
most parents don't do that to their
kids i think it's kind of weird
one parents always talk in a baby
voice to their kid to their own
kids yeah but then parents who don't
talk in a baby voice to their
own kids go over and meet someone
else's kids and then it goes yes
law because they can't they're like they
are they're forced to talk to their
own children so much like eco
eagles they can't wait to condescend to
a child like we need to take
a break speaking sunday it was a
long min ah i mean we'll be
right back with more thread huh
three huh um hi we're back push
to me and yeah arm par lef
com i'm scott ocher duty wave in
ah you got somebody you played yourself
played um chef kevin found an article
that lawrence excited about yeah it's about
the um it's about bob and marianne
the host from the fox thing they
okay with bruce around moran anyway
i am excuse anyway it starts from
the tribune it starts quote a hot
cuban babe unquote is how bob surat
described his wife of seventeen years gross
yeah i just said step in and
say gross i hate it when my
husband's objectify their wives in that way
i'm like oh it's really stupid i
love it
do you think it's great do you
really i mean i saw marianne said
i would love being horny
ernie tweaks made you hurry bay when
you go to hardy's in your horny
your high doesn't make me harney good
portman okay wait well she says when
we first met i was kind of
scared of bob who says cuban boise
goes good instincts up in miami and
working because he's an adulterer he's fucking
creep she worked as a news reporter
miami for over a decade everyone was
talking about what a big deal it
was this was going two years and
i was thinking who the hell is
bob surat marciano said they did they
began anchoring together when they began incurring
taylor surat did not speak to her
liquor on air he seriously would not
look at me or talk to me
unless the camera was rolling she said
i'd say how was your weekend and
he'd say save it meaning save the
conversation for the show
yo i was completely focused on like
news has so much time yeah they
just yeah they chatted a lot though
how much what what percentage i mean
i don't know i was a kid
i have no idea what's going on
but it's more like ninety percent judging
so what do what do you and
i never told a news story i
only talk about the
this just in i washed my car
this weekend yeah i was completely focused
on the show and intent on making
sure it was a success that's where
my mind was to show this has
been a reporter on many fucking radio
and tv stations since nineteen eighty blah
blah blah at the suggestion of their
news director marciano asked her out for
breakfast with the goal of bray
aching ice what happened we started having
fun and getting into good conversations about
life we had a lot in common
i had two young children my marriage
was falling apart i was separated and
so was up there okay they didn't
have an affair so well well hold
on i'm just saying that too i'm
now in the eyes of de guise
of the church they did yeah in
the eyes of today's society i guess
today's loose lacks moral yes i think
my under
handing is why i child was very
simple
bulls flags but so do you think
the producer got sick of hearing the
dynamic of this guy go like save
it and things like he was like
don't you actually like get together be
a human being gone right yes you're
where oh weird thinking that that's how
it started and then they fell in
love i don't know have you ever
fallen
i'm in love with someone who's going
to treat me like shit yeah i
mean my childhood but i remember
once i stopped telling my wife to
shut up that's when i really felt
for her because she got to speak
yes she would try to talk to
me and i was like talking to
me like these sounds coming out of
her powerful hey you got someone to
say wow i like the cut of
her jib crusher machine you should go
shomer shay yes some the same you
are the news people scott because yeah
the news people
in your hometown are they still the
same or the a lot of them
still the same it was my hometown
baby so answer the question what their
local orange county people know it's all
really it's all lies you had all
the people um they called the southland
which is like oh yeah yeah wherever
the antenna reaches so it's right there
you know so see
eat like lo no no no it's
it was always ah k m b
so local local no local local
look look look look about you look
yeah there's a lot of that whenever
i go back to philly there's a
lot of the same people are still
on the air or the older you
ya de la rains point to flatfish
let us even on twenty years long
longer than that shtick just should have
carried him through but he doesn't
five investors know he just does it
yeah and and has he has he
ever did point flat hand first dallas
raines yeah he has any internal thought
has ever tried to contact us right
now he never tried to cut well
did you my knowledge to my nose
no no we talked about me invited
him one of the best yes
we kept talking about him during the
the comedy bang bang best doves and
we got to the point where we
were begging him to come on this
please come on there's yeah i would
love to have him on there i'm
telling fritz coleman that he was not
invited fritz coleman must know first cohen
i've lived here since nineteen ninety four
and he's been on the air he's
been on the smc eighty yes at
least crazy
yeah there was the there was the
consumer report guy bo him before bogey
but i remember bogey yeah oh for
bogey yeah there was a guy who
who parlayed it into his own half
hour show about consumer rip offs and
stuff like that i can't remember his
name ma i wanna say marv albert
but i know it's not right i
mean but i want to say it
so
bad all right i'll just say it
marv albert had a show was it
marked consumer
consumer ripoff um but yeah fritz has
been around forever
yeah i don't really mean no
anyway i was surprised that like do
you not check out the local news
when you go home i mean i
guess it's on whatever who would ever
watched the local news my parents watch
it i think but i watch it
too weirdly like i i will have
it on in between figuring out what
i'm gonna do like i like to
start way too you always figure out
what you're gonna do in two ch
mncs and the local news is always
right there in batala but la yeah
like eleven p yeah i'm gonna do
what show am i going to watch
i'm gonna start it on the news
it's like solid base just meat and
i'm gonna roll up from there but
i love like the view i love
those kinds of shit right i can
watch the view every day and i
did for years but
i don't haven't done it lately but
i think it's would you like to
host the view i actually think i
would have fun doing something like that
i think i would but i would
have to it wouldn't be now but
later what i mean yeah oils are
right now but like i imagine like
oh like when i'm like fifty i
can look over the hill when you
feel old enough to start lecturing people
i'd be like i have opinions because
of my life experience should be the
young when you get older you'll understand
that the world works in a different
way than you think it does yeah
well the young people they have now
like meghan mccain who's like she's really
she's put very politically savvy though where
i'm like she brings something specific i'd
bring the ca
comedy
yeah i've thought about it i think
this is sort of like the view
yeah the debbie monopoly that's okay though
because she was like she was like
twenty two though she was the first
one right yeah yeah but everyone made
fun of her for being dumb yeah
but she was so young i mean
yeah everyone's dumb yeah i love what
the mansions the most outta well yeah
i do like that much
what be talking to you seen that
clip of her i don't know if
it was a clip or what both
domes were okay debbie
it was a clip of whoopi like
talking to her um la oh someone
just put your pointing here her like
the bug area you know like okay
yeah yeah and she's just like she'll
just be doing things like i know
like she'll just like respond to them
like she goes off like like on
the air yeah this is a beamer
know she looks crazy because
oh no all have put together that
someone's talking to her but should be
like so you know in the news
justin bieber i'm getting to it i'm
gonna say that we have to go
to break the super it's like she's
saying haunted yeah oh just like a
little because i've never seen it whoa
maybe it was real do you think
patrick swayze
this is a gosar guys now and
he's this is just really ironic just
let me make some clay pots sheesh
made me be complaining i'm gonna make
some people i've never seen that movie
but people think it's really horny right
it's super horn people think it's real
honestly it's a really fun movie i
would say if you're like looking for
something to throw on maybe maybe maybe
we start on the news
start on the news and then i
know your dvd or no scott i
want to warn you there's a mean
ghost in the movie too yeah yeah
imagine chevelle see yeah tm you give
away spoilers i just used to mean
ghost i didn't tell him that he
would daisy i don't know huh i
don't know how i know that that
vince
lynch valley is in it um it's
a great film okay maybe because because
it's a great film maybe jerry maybe
you saw in the in memoriam because
he's no longer with oh that's probably
a senor is given to you isn't
moonlighting wasn't who's a guy from the
train and ghost who's like yeah like
we're talking about free tamper no really
yeah yeah
who did you see of ellis who
did you think you should had jeffrey
tambor no no well who did you
think we were talking about we're talking
about the mean ghost like rick aviles
the guy but i don't want to
give away the movie well there's a
bad guy in the movie
the way there's a bevin wing you
get away now the guy who does
all the shit the domina yeah he's
a ghost well it becomes one while
well everyone becomes one he eventually is
can we just spoil the yeah fucking
like never gonna see it isn't he
eventually he is going for like actually
making a hill or something yeah but
he's gotta go okay i guess
you're right i feel you're saying like
a bad guy like there's a bad
guy think no there's a bad ghost
of a subway yeah yeah that's like
get off my gay but he was
jeffrey tambor esque like i feel like
and i read something where jeffrey tambor
says he people think that's him he's
a tall boardman i mean you know
that's what happens now everyone everyone knows
jeffrey tambor is a me too
i know um you know i mean
going to me too what if what
if dan ackroyd complained about the ghost
and ghostbusters it gives him a blow
job wakes him up by giving him
a ghost blow job it's like no
not in this environment did he come
slimer
onion head aka slimer is this dan
ackroyd come from getting a ghost blow
job yeah i rewatch that movie not
that long ago right i think after
the the anything it sometime reboot came
out yeah you're like let's see the
real versa you probably remember it as
a scary movie yeah i remember yes
i remember hearing were little yes and
i
also remember just being like that's a
good movie damn sure good moon bay
day i got the toys i got
the stuff i started at the news
i got ghostbusters it is a good
movie where my jack i drew a
ghostbuster on danilo by brought it up
to the stage i got to be
babs
charette marianne marciano kumari loving couple jazz
fusion band between babe who can't talk
before i knew new stuff
those rules still in effect in their
home like say the goddamn like to
ask you say that but it's something
i can't ask oh the other news
is coming up on the news we're
not on
news we're not all i want to
watch the news sometimes not just reported
why did you watch ghostbusters recently because
the reboot and i wanted to see
does this hold up as well as
i remember it and it does not
it does yeah i like most things
don't yeah mainly really just when being
like can't believe it and they're like
oh yeah watch the other one is
that fucking radio where it was because
people were were people were saying like
the original ghostbusters classic perfect film roll
it's so you watch it there's a
lot of problems like there's you remember
the song there's as many problems in
the in the new one was ray
parker junior who was saying honestly yeah
he's like i think it's still the
best movie ever but who cares it
was nice the reboot anyway yeah they're
rebooting friday night
lights
she just walks into a movie they're
like they're like reboot of the movie
friday night lights just you're writing the
movie us which was what the tv
show was based on out into fertile
years ago yeah that's cool how could
people have we bought a book yeah
we reboot nobel go reboot a book
you what i am going to reduce
the bible i'd love to talk to
you robin
and done by um that couple who
did things like that who is that
isn't that crazy bob and marianne are
now the good things like that now
you know that couple ah the the
husband is like the guy who produces
all those shows like mark o burnett
yeah yeah oh they were liable just
like a mini series yeah so it's
been done jimmy tell my markers i'm
saying rewriting a book that's already been
written oh yeah yeah yeah a stadium
that is very funny it's exactly the
same thing but no one would ever
do that yeah it would be the
same it'd be very weird i just
wrote a new ah babysitters club the
series same characters different stories i guess
that's been done before in the sense
of like isn't like jack ryan or
whatever some dude took over
for the franchise yeah those are those
are books people that's representing like yeah
babysitter's club is not a good example
are you sticking your hand out like
this to paul i'm dying yeah i
think if you were to rewrite the
original books yes yeah right just rude
i feel like i want to rewrite
huckleberry finn i want ya story one
of our food ramona quimby
yeah
oh you did though it's pretty giusto
sexier last name is quimby like
here comes the hottest guy and i'm
simpsons who do you think is the
most attractive simpsons character ah bart
you said that with such authority i
did think about it like ah really
and then i realized you were joking
i'm actually not bart is the hottest
character please if i had to okay
he's forty now or how long has
he been around wealthy well nineteen eighty
nine so so you consider even though
other show he is still
a child you're thinking because the show
has been don't like me so when
wisdom says he's reached the age of
consent we have a problem with sunrays
by tv a lot because we talk
about hot children that we were attracted
to shorter children yeah absolutely so it's
very different i think bart is the
hottest tina cartoon has more of a
problem with that which isn't ah
if you had to choose between the
two hosts of raised by tv
yeah
ah good see who talks about it
along
um who do you think is the
hottest on come you know where you
know like a babe jumped in my
mind was the arnold wow arnold schwarzenegger
guy oh yeah oh yeah i guess
i'd like a cool dog name
pucci yeah yes that's fucked back cool
if you have to these are my
choices if you had to fuck a
dog if you were like now we
get to it okay like it like
this we've been we've been to argue
about this we also are going around
for such a long time right if
you had to fuck a dog what
it would have to be a cartoon
that's exactly what i was gonna ask
sure like mcgruff yeah oh but girl
is wearing trench coat pervy transpose he's
an adult so there's a clip from
improper human took a bite out of
this on the video podcast network thing
um where we ah something on youtube
we can go look at i'm saying
if anyone cares out there but it's
jon kimberlin and paul rust and then
gambling is
like arguing for fuck for like oh
no this was this was off of
improper humans yes i said i was
and i was i was listening okay
great and ouch ah but it's ah
kind of crazy to watch him argue
for it it's john emily's arguing for
beast yeah what what sparked this debate
ah
i don't know probably just something who
want to talk about it might have
been in the scene or something god
i hope so i think but i
think the conversation was not it was
like i mean in a sense it's
better than like a dildo because a
dildo cannot give consent a living wage
a living being can give consent we
just don't know whether
they are giving consent so that but
the possibilities are fifty fifty they're giving
consent meanwhile a dildo is not giving
cause i still do is made to
give consent oh slavery slavery steely dan
what's that steely dan was a dancer
free bald female nose slavery no well
steely dan famously was talking about this
on bang bang john mulaney was named
after um vidalia wheel coach and naked
lunch yes the book naked let's already
be quickly lead dan yes so if
you are thinking how can i like
the band steely dan le
yes yeah that sucks i like i
like three steely dan songs which was
yeah but no we haven't let's oh
done the dirty work is the best
one dirty work how's our wow fool
do ya dirty work oh pretty good
do ya dirty work no mo um
like i mean it's a good one
i'm saying they have three good songs
um gonna look that up let me
think i like reeling in the years
sounds really years that's the one guy
i mean look at them like hey
i think i'm like oh peggy is
my favorite actually but what about our
favorite hey nineteen
oh go old
lumby and we start i feel like
starts higher and higher hello let's go
back so
a yeah fargo b makes sido one
interval the too high to high
uncle i think pay fine call during
irby
they still die oh nerf balls that
okay yeah it was really good
they give you time to look up
i got over you're looking up i
got actually i really have two good
songs
barry town i don't know okay we
need to take a break oh yeah
taking this out to break his berada
bap bap bap would peg peg okay
what's this about this cool chocolate game
is in july yeah it's about peggy
peggy okay my hobby
so you're begging me now but i'm
gonna pick you later that's the promise
of pegging you're thinking of the simpsons
episode it will do we'll see after
this bye
welcome back wow day welcome back yay
i'm lauren you found something on twitter
you want to talk about yeah yeah
lauren understand you have a topic yeah
trump did something
just check twitter sro trump a champion
bad i feel scared you did a
bad thing on twitter i'm sure that
will be truly the day that this
comes out but true tom this is
from shannon hutchinson at the shannon r
h and she tweeted pictures that she
and her friends ah did that
our recreating our threesome photos and they
did a really amazing job and their
dorm room i can't wait to sue
them out of that dorm room yeah
they released his r i p those
pictures are written i'm very impressed they
did a great job flattered yeah yeah
they're amazing they they one's wearing a
top hat
that's the ones wearing girl food well
just ones all new
ah and if you want to see
some newbies with the top voted twitter
go to my twitter scroll back nine
months
ah do you think the earth is
still here by the time this is
released it's not looking good yeah i'm
hoping you have a feature you know
what i do i do have a
feature write down for now i'm happy
to share this with you good mood
i think i'd better dance now this
this is called how do you do
with few all it stopped who owes
two o's how do you do do
yeah okay alright this it's like duty
hey hey i know i knew you
would think that but it's not okay
your brain always goes there you're the
one who said
first thing in this episode i always
write a recommendation you teams will ah
the i just had been recriminations which
is a reference to ah the show
last comic standing which i had friend
who was who had taken over producing
that shows his company going producing that
show and so they were doing a
ah t's to a break they're going
to go into break and it's like
coming up it was when jay moore
was hosting right and he knew the
house this happens this happens in this
comin up to the o two people
arguing and he said bitter recriminations
yeah there was a bitter recrimination yeah
certainly but did it make you stick
around yeah did ya
also maybe say bitter recriminations in my
head many many guys for years i
mean i remember that that because i
played jay more at death ray at
mbr when that season was on you
played jay moores we did we did
a last comic standing yeah we did
a last comic standing night and i
was j moore in it i just
kept kept repeating
kita da house because i was something
that he said all the time like
if you all keep it ups what's
your feature
how do you do teams will compete
to try so each of us will
be okay now put it in your
own words loosen it up okay like
you know there's three of us yeah
sometimes we're not all together weird separate
odd things yeah this is a hard
just read it um teams will be
to try to get their team to
guess a song by only singing the
word do you might think this game
sounds easy but it's not so easy
when you're on the spot okay and
this is i have to
i feel compelled to include this definitely
one of the funniest adult game night
games i've ever played so wow so
yeah who says this piece of paper
so a piece of paper's playing adult
games at a party yeah and find
it fun this quote is attributed to
know what it is just this piece
of paper too is like william shakespeare
or it says larry king because he's
the one who said that chevallier shiva
we witness each valley because of it
yeah buyer yeah oh yeah oh whatever
because the larry king whatever we should
have said is do you want to
see a show where the performers shit
all the time and their horses yeah
well yeah you know how some shows
keep you awake not this show
yo i make you go right tonight
night the rhythm of the horses we
had a good time watching though i
will sigh but it makes you go
nice expensive um bones i mean i
guess to some people don't wow i
heard about it on a podcast that
someone was saying it costs like three
hundred dollars a ticket that's no i
definitely know because i would not have
been
i heard it costs a bucket of
oats is that not true yes we
need the performance i mean like it
was produced by horse's name so i
think it'll be like one person sings
and i think we're all good singers
and this is gonna be easier as
i think so too and so we're
kind of competing it would be two
people competing yeah sure we chose to
be dewey or should we do it
for time
mm so everyone's competing for the shortest
time
i think it amounts to the same
thing what if we time it and
then we each get points for how
like i'd say i'm guessing and then
we have a minute and you were
with hugo then you go then you
go and whoever gets more out that
doesn't take so long
whoever guy more out that doesn't take
so i think it's easier if we
both try to get like if paul's
doing it we both try to guess
and paul is competing for the shortest
time god okay okay okay wait i'm
committed oh ty is where think you
want so i want to replicate it
as as always sleeping awesome you would
sing poorly and just stretch the timeline
forever which i think everyone knows i
can't you cannot do
yeah i pulled out my calculator app
yeah my my delight by one plus
one plus one plus one sixty okay
um let me find the day so
you're singing any song in the world
and you sound in the world and
we and we will and we're trying
to we're not trying to stretch out
your time we're literally trying to guess
it yeah we want to get it
yeah but you want us to get
it okay
goal is to solve it
let's all get all da oh man
trying to think of a song is
the artist later so of you think
i'm gonna be bad there's over one
hundred songs okay one hundred and eight
songs and i feel you have one
do you wanna do it first um
sure okay well here's the thing yeah
and by the way i know the
audience is loving us figure your name
this is like when i was in
a play
a musical and the choreographer would come
to rehearsal and spend the first hour
figuring out choreography oh god while we
sat and watched her wasting our time
as stupid she didn't want to do
it the night before or the day
before whatever she just wanted to hook
god i gotta go to fucking work
we did this alright paul go first
a knew sunk
can be anything think of your fang
shen b o but you're not supposed
to do a melody right now you
just don't see a melody how was
whatever like doing like the tone like
like the like the drumset hello timbo
that go if you should go first
do do do do like you'd be
like could you could you could be
like if it's like hey dude
be like doo doo
shut down to two doe doo doo
doo doo doo doe doe you're supposed
to have the melody so i was
like doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo did it did to do
yeah okay exactly alright ok ok google
chef alright yeah get it on the
goog chef
you got something okay the here's the
problem yeah all doing it was the
fucking national ah charlie you're such a
patriot i'm like i love this country
think of why of who's who's a
great singer in your fridge just got
key oh okay i want to go
okay ready lauren okay wait i'm on
hold i ready
and the minute you start singing i
press start okay do do do do
do do do do do do i
know i'm saying judy
what's the name of that song and
i'm telling you yeah i should have
kept going usually good guy no no
i guess i stopped when you said
i'm saying or whatever well he was
right when she pointed at me yeah
so five seconds five seconds alright okay
maybe maybe kevin should keep time chef
kevin so i could do it i
could ready no
well yeah but i feel like it's
unfair you shouldn't be distracted and he
would know if maybe we actually do
have to guess the title yeah the
title has to be ready to get
the snow like getting the song is
right cause that's what the whole point
should i bother giving names to songs
okay i want to time it comes
going to okay alright ready yeah here
we go and do do do do
do do da song even saying
i cheated which also the lyrics are
due to na
lauren god because i think i said
todd restaurant again yeah okay your turn
shit alright
flintstones i'm sorry flintstones doo doo doo
dah
ah um um
due to to to do due to
do to do to do do do
do to do to do oh no
still little record yes yeah yeah yeah
it's going i kept thinking of songs
that i'd spoken-word you're right joe is
dr who today yeah doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo yeah ready
doo doo doo
do do do do do i will
always love you
i feel like i like i'm a
recording artist for a cell phone range
alright ready
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo ideally remove co contact engines
boy i wish i wish yes sir
yes yeah it's the name of the
song with stevie wonder i ain't never
knew the name of that song yeah
okay
i think the hard one to even
out my tom's diner okay alright paul
here we go dearly beloved we are
gathered to get through this thing called
life to get this thing called fitter
oh boy this is more entertaining you
actually see the songs as you like
with it's the op switch the fucking
worst i can't i feel like i
blank on stuff like this yeah no
it's hard when all the time it's
like when you're when you're playing what's
games categories or whatever when you have
to think of like an s word
yeah
yeah before for you know a article
of clothing it's like i'm forced to
use socks or whatever yes some
to do that the model stuff yeah
some ruby
and then it was like some diamond
like
you have to it's um
good okay alright alright here we go
here we go right right right right
um fuck you just think it a
rap songs always do a rep
just do a wrap don't even do
dues just like do a radio rap
just make one up
this is there's so many navy huh
who in the world is a musician
because here's the thing you know so
many songs alive i know it's true
it's true i do and do something
you've done at largo do to to
oulu two two two two two
to to to to to to do
to to to to to to to
to to to
this is one of most fun
nah not to do those so long
to do to it
diddy doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo dude dude
dude do do that it
jody
yea who got it you guys got
i like alright alright okay that's a
great song it's a great song i
mean we should also review the songs
after five stars i mean let me
lay down some news for ya oh
okay we had one has this a
good take of a sagas sung by
far
monterrey man guy guy wow okay okay
wait
okay did you do to to to
to to to do do oh ah
dude delineated it dictated dude
oh dear i don't want to wait
alcohol yeah
okay here's mine
do do do do do do do
do do do de jac and nine
do
yeah it's good to dig into his
daughter is on real housewives of beverly
hills teddi mellencamp ooty melon cab to
see inside the lives of are we
doing want one more round chin famous
yeah one more round here we go
paul
okay i think i'll think
you can do this you could do
this
don't do happy birthday dude i almost
did someone
i leave everybody um ahh doo doo
doo doo doo to heaven i'm in
heaven the doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo dah
buddhist no dude no dude who do
you from hamilton king george's song whenever
it's called dude what's the name of
it yeah lauren said oh we have
to do is know the song joins
in the pie okay i didn't realize
that was the tablet dvd oh you'll
maybe be back
check new biddy are you sad now
this game is so low it's humiliating
i love it ah yeah i don't
care we're doing one more yeah so
yeah wow it's the dirt more yeah
you have to go
okay
doo doo doo doo doo doo doe
don't like your face well you know
da da da da da da do
to doh doh doh doh doh doh
doh doh doh doh to dunno do
do do do do de da da
da da
i feel like e t e t
y e t knew this mouth so
i was like dude oh and your
arms are like doing this
i don't know huh i mean okay
well what about is there a chorus
because that's how that works right oh
noo ah most beautiful melodies ever written
dodo dodo dodo don't know
do
no oh ah da levi yes oh
leave on like any show b leave
on the dinner show be a good
man i love elton john yeah elton
john wow i love out to brown
alright ready what if you thought how
albert rau was elton john yeah alton
brown like logan i want to go
to his culture but he never comes
through here i wish he would keep
singing
i love the song but no albums
he put out
i meant the record store he put
out new albums but all the songs
we know
ah alright right here yeah
doo doo doo doo doo doo the
opera
paul gets one more no well you
started so paul to do what i
guess he's right yeah did you say
one more round then i don't know
i want you to do one more
works
but you're the best oh
things like this
yeah me too late my hand oh
no just look at that and maybe
you'll think of a song oh that's
yeah that would be why elton brown
was awesome that's a t-shirt is out
and brown and an elton john costume
negligent on weight a costume of elton
john's or an elton john costume would
be the same yeah yeah it does
if it's if it's the donald duck
costume i guess well he wore a
lot of crazy but you know what
i'm saying is the ice with sandy's
video stamps
yeah he's bald campaign included
because it would not be a costume
that elton john war i'd have to
see the design i'd have seen this
i need you to sing assume no
alright i will sing a song
no due to do my survey shows
guys yeah ways of graham ah dans
ma these days ah
ma ma ma ma re ca ga
j res on de da web ah
from
z zhai
a we'll see you next time i
buy everybody i i miss you sit
back down
uh this has been an era with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com