cleo
oh
ah
um yeah wow we can't believe it
it's another week can we play i
don't know if i mentioned this before
with so many posted on our um
on like a reddit which i don't
always check by the way i typically
don't actually actually cut out the habit
almost entire reddit ago
then it's where you go to love
is that that place because it plays
about stitcher premium yeah
but people were someone speculated that we
recorded a bunch in a row i'll
tell you what we can't we cannot
do more than to it we can't
do more than two one but we
do need can't do more than two
at once due to do new or
we don't always do two at once
do do don't you don't
to note but we're moving but we
do do do do bobbie daughter
da da da da da boo boo
boo plugin to three them for another
week i'm paul
i'm paul
well paul oh paul paul f tompkins
today we are all paul paul f
tompkins paul five tompkins five hundred kin
sa five hundred that's ninety five hundred
indiana jones you're doing it you're almost
there all you you're like ooh away
dr jones dr biden yeah
hey i got there you did a
degrees of dr biden paul do you
dislike it when someone leaves out the
f in your name no no really
sounds like paul tomkins told me no
i don't mind that i don't mind
that you just find they're talking about
right i'm like oscar wilder somebody i
only mind it ah professionally
like if you were at a show
doing a show and was like paul
tomkins you know like it's not paul
tom yes if someone introduced me that
way or if you're billed as that
hat because it comes up on mtb
shopping occasionally yeah also known as paul
tomkins aka
a k f k
f k twigs shiela boof
oh no i'm a twigs currently known
as k c k ah chickens cpa
twin formerly known as twigs do you
know when i first joined twitter my
twitter handle was twitter kim's and i
wish i'd never changed it really yeah
you wish it was still ah yeah
i do i do
ah because it's not because p f
tompkins is not my full name it's
tons small was that too many characters
i think at the time was too
many cars like your your name counted
as part of the machine right yeah
you can i think it's too late
now just because people tell but i
did stag paul the the handle paul
f tompkins
um after that nobody else had it
thank god but thank god oh god
that was a close one i'm so
glad you said that sometimes i wonder
though if i you guys are making
fun of me if i deactivate finally
gets it
couldn't somebody take my name idea i'd
love to take your name a good
questionnaires oh my god the squeal you
through to wedding chicago wow
dearly beloved we are gathered here
like cool up you're up wait you
guys marry each other you've got you've
performed a wedding ceremony i have performed
one wedding ceremony i've performed a few
wedding ceremonies yes i know why you
performed i really hope to never do
that wow i don't like that kind
of attention you know what you get
it done
didn't feel like attention direction i don't
want it feels like a responsibility i
don't want to i don't like that
either i leopard is tough and wedding
i want to be able to be
like i'm in the sort of side
also wherever i want you know can
i just do my own thing i
don't want to have you like to
do your thing yeah was kind of
just badia yeah and you get on
the mic at the receptor say i
like to do me
my thing i would never make a
toast i don't want i don't want
any would never make a toast knows
what i have yeah you have i
just don't like it makes me really
uncomfortable yeah i will see there's a
different kind of nervousness that comes on
you when like for me that is
if i'm doing a live show i'm
usually high
hiding behind a veneer of sarcasm or
whatever but when you have to be
that sets true when you have to
be that sincere in front of people
yeah i haters a little bit of
nervousness of laszlo know now i'm being
judged as myself nah yeah not only
that but you're being judges of the
comedian like it's bo it's like the
people i wasn't being just as a
comedian for the wedding i did
people yeah but i'm saying like if
you're if you got oh i got
mine if you got me to toast
at your friend's wedding no my friend
had a birthday here to be during
my wedding eight shits so bad at
our wedding he was trying to be
so funny as a comedian and he
was trying to be so wanting it
was that bad oh he it's legendary
are there
a i don't remember it is him
eating shit he ate shit felt embarrassed
and then um cool up sister came
up and then destroy it and it's
like because he was trying to our
yeah there's a classic story in the
pro community of somebody doing it but
i can't remember the details so thanks
i love stories about stories
as all my stories are i am
i remember the details i feel i've
i've been there so many times written
they feel so bad i was like
where you you you're reminded of the
feeling you had of this story that
you know oh yeah and then you
bring it up too soon and then
it's like i actually don't actually don't
know anything about stories about my
myself to where i'm just like ah
who are the people that you perform
because i was at one definitely sarah
and gino you were at that one
oh but i didn't get to see
you do it who's that oh that's
right you got there because we surmise
from other friends of ours you have
other free world don't worry i've never
been to a wedding that started that
on time where it was like eight
clock who and wild and it was
literally we got there at eight twenty
five yes and pulled up and they
were exiting da were like fuck drive
around the block they'll see i never
happens that was wild so that's crazy
so who then who were there because
i was at i was at i
feel like i was at laura
millionaire like you were at laura oh
yeah well yeah it was they had
already been married okay okay it was
a new deal thing i did a
ceremony after the after they did it
they had done justice of the peace
one yeah that was the first one
i ever did and i was very
nervous about that and i think i
was trying to be i think i
made it might have taken a true
seriously oh interesting um ah
but then i did so i did
syringe you know i did ah my
friends aaron and cristo
why did mark mcconville and christina roger
oh i've done a few i've done
one baptism too recently what did you
say for the baptism yeah get ready
i had to make it seem religious
but it was not religious gone dunk
this baby
i don't think i would do it
for anyone that i wasn't close with
yeah i don't know absolutely nobody who
hasn't really quest to do it for
for fans or whatever i think it's
too i think it's too big of
a responsibility to do it for someone
you don't know all that well and
i also think that if you're a
fan you should
wouldn't want that you might get someone
you're close with i was once asked
to do it for a couple that
i did not think should be getting
married oh and i need to do
our wedding and
and i said oh by the way
i wanted to do i was not
tall enough i was told today i
was told we want somebody somebody who's
lisa
did did you say no and then
did they get divorced yes wow turned
out to be a real piece of
shit this guy whoa and my friend
ah no
you love him and i was i
felt really bad about it but i
was like i just feel like it
would be wrong god i want oh
this is crazy someone i know no
it's not it's not too much not
i want some gossip guys do you
have any gossip hey if you've got
hot goss about people we don't know
please send to this please send it
in we are starving for gossip there's
nothing going onto a million
emily heller who's very funny comedian writer
um on instagram live said what's what
was the gossip was a big piece
of gossip fries and see her post
about that and that was really fun
and it was fun to just read
these blog essentially blind items about people
you don't know oh but it was
funny to hear the stories some of
them were like oh yeah that happened
at my school too but so
some of them involved murder whoa i
gossip guy resume the other night with
some high school friends i haven't really
been doing any social zooms who just
go to high school
i feel like i i have such
a nice time on a social zoom
but i never do them because i
am on zoom all day yeah that's
how i feel that way too you've
had to do so many shows over
zoom that and now i do my
weekly one which is mizuki is but
at the beginning we did show with
jason manns no not a weekly show
but ah we believe you
oh um because he's by himself and
and you know deservedly so
but we did one paul janey and
caleb and i did one and it
was really fun but now i'm just
like enough of zoom's i don't want
to do it i know i feel
like it's the same thing every time
i do it with someone it's fun
and i'm like oh my god i'm
so like seckerson right yeah or wish
i've had some sex it was boring
oh man
i'm charlie boring sex you're trying to
think of it yeah i don't think
i've ever had boring so i'm trying
to think of is getting me off
oh shit it wasn't boring that's what
i like your head but then it's
if you like it then it's not
boring anymore
but one thing we may have talked
about this before but one thing that
always makes me laugh for some reason
is when people talk about sex as
fun it's really fucking that was fun
like hey man um i had sex
the other night was fun i feel
like it's it's own thing like it's
more than yeah it's like fun it's
just seems like a weird word to
i think make sense
it was really fun
oh but i was gonna say that
my high school friends and i were
trying to come up with some gossip
about people to kind of you know
entertain each other right it's it's hard
to come by it really is we
had a couple little news stories like
recent gossip yeah yeah like because we're
like then like the last time we
did it which was
the beginning of the pandemic we ended
up googling some people on a share
screen which was pretty fun like oh
where's that guy he gives someone like
really random that no one remembers where
no one's been in touch yeah and
then you try to figure what they're
up to i think i think my
college peeve
people i was in college with we
all kept up with each other for
the first ten eleven twelve years and
then thirteen fourteen thirteen fourteen fifteen seventeen
nineteen twenty lives wow we're still in
touch and we're wearing clothes
yeah they are we were all on
a zoom at the beginning of the
quarantine and i don't think there's any
gossip anymore but it used to be
like anytime you'd see anyone from college
you go okay give me the gossip
about this person this person this yeah
well guess what they're doing their due
there this this and now it's just
like everyone's just boring and dewey's an
alcoholic
yeah yeah the the hot items i
feel like in recent years for my
demographic are like imo someone getting divorced
or someone getting engaged someone having a
baby like that's usually the gossip so
it's not that exciting but it's interesting
do you ever think about the the
person
was there somebody in your high school
that when you look when you think
about them now you're like oh i
should have that person i should have
tried to date yeah um like i
didn't think about dating them then but
when i think about the kind of
person they aren't like oh she was
actually really cool i shouldn't try to
date her i feel like i did
have a tendency to like people who
i
like i wasted time like liking weird
people but like people who are wrong
choices yeah but i i had a
good like coy bad boys or you
liked weirdos and you should like normal
people i like to mixture of weirdos
and very normal boring people like norm
core people like just the worst like
lo
more books the worse type where they're
just like not not good or interesting
and they're going to a bar with
george went once and they shouted norm
at him and they slid a beer
over to him immediately and it was
a bar i'd never been into and
he just said thank you and then
drink that does happen to him yeah
all the time alright yeah yeah yeah
famously were
whipped together you were famous
but yeah i just i don't know
if there are people that i'm like
oh i should have
i don't think so not in high
school i in high school i feel
like it was more like i tried
to date a bunch of people and
no one wanted to and then for
me it was like i was i
was hung up on people so like
that was me too there was my
time yeah there was a girl there
we had this on again off again
thing it was very dramatic and very
tumultuous and it was like you know
of course
rss it was like that was my
world at the time yeah that was
everything right and when i think about
now micah little girl was really cool
yeah she was normal and like it
would have been a nice time yeah
go ahead fun sex yeah i will
say maybe i would have checks a
little bit fun at my twentieth reunion
um i will say
say one of the one of my
classmates as i was walking away with
cool up we were just about to
get married ah shouted so like she
was with her friends and was one
of your classmates you were walking with
cool up you just about sorry i'll
say it in order i was walking
away with chua away from one of
my classmates who was with a bunch
of her friends cool ups friends
and she shouted something in me like
like you know why should the couple
likes god you were my backup or
something like that foe fuck you you
are about to get married like you
were in a suit and she was
in a but i don't go
cool i'm never going to get married
in like three months at that point
she is so confusing is it really
cool up and i were going to
get smash the confusing here's started how
did that happen
how it started i was walking away
and no it did not yeah it
was at my reunion
indoor center union there's stories i never
said my twentieth reunion here's how it
started scott goes my shoes were going
in this direction my feet were in
them then keep going up to my
head that's where my face was pointed
in the direction of my shoes because
i was a kilometre about to get
married i was please everyone please write
to lauren to tell her that i
said this was
at my twenty fifth high school and
i are about to get married please
write to laura ingraham ha yes you
cool openai we're about to get married
and i was walking away and my
and this comment my high school video
listeners know oh it's zoran you don't
pay attention to any that's true and
this was the way he told him
fur your brain is broken i know
that but i
you said for luck so i follow
after
first you said i started in media
rez perhaps but yes but before anything
i said this is my twentieth said
please start in situ you said as
i walked away cool up and i
marriage and yeah it's not confusing everyone
knows what i'm saying
oh okay you know it i know
you might give the american people do
it so for everything i ever did
so this broad is like hey scott
you as my backup piece something like
i think she was hoping to come
to the reunion and then i also
had another ah friend or classmate oh
no tell the story now that we're
past the
giveaway know she was hoping to come
to the reunion and where we're like
hookup or something i don't know we're
on the queen mary um oh and
she was like she was kind of
saved them all talk i watched that
i enjoyed it it was fun i
thought i felt that i really liked
where it went yeah yeah england um
but there was another another i don't
know these things are so fraught with
emotion like one one of my classmates
got really drunk and was talking about
her divorce and started crying about her
divorce and i would love to witness
and then intimated like maybe we could
get into a threesome you and the
school while crying me club and her
maybe
yeah the reason many guys suck you
fucking
and then the ten lady guys when
i visit either the ten year everyone
is so like concerned with their place
in the world yes and everyone's kind
of trying to you know like say
say they have more going on than
they actually did have going on i'm
the president um i was actually starting
a sock compass
any i do believe i've just been
nominated for an emmy at the time
so that was nice i nude
but but the greatest was there was
this really popular girl and this kind
of ties into what you're saying really
popular girl in high school who had
everything going on and really pretty and
when i saw her i was like
hey so what's going on she's like
well i don't have a job i
live with my parents and that's my
life right now and she was just
so like telling it like it was
and not trying to put on any
airs i was like she's really cool
was still pretty yeah almost everyone was
at the ten the twentieth where it
starts to get dicey yeah everyone starts
to dice and then we had a
thirty by the way and i i
asked my mutual friend who's a great
love me i go have you heard
anything about a thirty year old a
thirty year reunion for us and he
goes oh let me look into it
oh yeah it's next thursday at one
thirty on a boat
like it was a booze cruise in
the afternoon a week out and tell
anybody you're on thursday yeah so who's
gonna go no i don't who knows
i mean i'm not on facebook so
i don't know whether like everyone knew
about it and i just didn't but
yeah it was bizarre
maybe they'll live on that boat maybe
they too they were just like let's
just celebrate at one thirty
it was really weird anyway w gone
to any years lauren to have you
know and i might have mentioned this
but i um i do feel like
we might have talked about my spanking
pat and let's get it we're shoving
he pops out of the pool
like a commando shit like the lady
is thinking ben and his teeth my
reunion happened and i wasn't invited and
it was i saw something about it
on facebook for my ten year and
i was like huh and then that
was that and i think i wouldn't
have gone so whatever my school was
really big i don't know that i
would have
known most of the people it's hard
to say i haven't i haven't gone
to any i haven't kept in touch
with anyone i don't know really well
there's one there's one guy from my
high school that i i am still
in touch with and that's it and
i just don't feel like i would
have i don't know what we would
talk about
like i don't there's people i can't
remember their names anymore yeah like i
know been a long time and honestly
long long damn it alone
oh wow a taj to graduate high
school my friends on my zoom that
we the fur we had one a
while ago and we talking about some
people we could not remember people's names
and i mean it hasn't been that
you saw in your yearbook yeah but
then i would i don't have them
i don't have them here right but
my friend couldn't remember the guy she
went to prom with
ooh wow i remember it's name and
then we all try to figure it
out and we try to google because
he was like he was only at
our school like a minute and then
we it was how i feel about
the first time i went to prom
i feel really bad but i went
with someone who is hitler
i was nice he needed a day
um no i went with a friend
of mine who i guess had a
crush on me and i didn't know
it until she asked me to prom
and she asked me like this hey
would you do me a favor sure
do me a favor would you owe
you'll go to prom with me i
was like oh boy but i wear
way to do that yeah but i
had i i you know i look
hey it's you know thirty years on
you
more in touch and were better able
to express your feelings yeah i wish
i you'll get there would have meant
i don't think so
but i wish i would have known
how to communicate like oh you know
if you're thinking this hands-on yeah keep
it above the belt in your dreams
yeah i get my kicks above the
waistline sunshine
instead she jim j bullock to me
i think there's i have so many
stories from my past that run like
oh i didn't know how to say
yeah the thing oh right yeah and
be clear absolutely but how how other
way you know what i mean like
i was bad at it all the
way but what's weird is no one
i mean my parents certainly didn't never
teach me how to do that how
are you ever supposed to
no you know i mean from movies
that's actually why i was trying to
do yeah that's why everything was so
fucking yeah it was like why isn't
this working like a movie it's like
the movie actually it goes badly for
a while too yeah so eventually you
will be in love with me
yeah i mean that as parents shouldn't
if you end up being a parent
of a person dropping their shouldn't shouldn't
there be a point where you say
to your child oh by the way
they're going to be situations you're in
where someone who really likes you that
you're not into is going to ask
you out yes i do think here
is
really are good at explaining right i
don't i my parents it was more
like you're not even gonna date so
don't even worry about that kind of
thing yeah i feel like it's like
it's a imagine that it gets better
and better with generations that like the
more in touch we are as we
go through life and like the more
the
mori the next generation that goes to
therapy and the generation after that starts
like utilize what they learned in therapy
like it's like we start to actually
disperse this information in a really usable
way but like i i o heart
i agree with that but i do
think to slow the spread feels very
slow yeah because there's still a lot
of people that are
our clinging to really old fashioned yeah
ways of doing things and it's just
like it's you're perpetuating this dumb shit
that we need to get rid of
yeah um because you think it's a
black and white world and this is
the way things are and it's just
not it's just not that way but
i don't know i i i wish
that i had had
had some guidance in that way because
i just was so bad i was
like i didn't realize until much later
that i was ah like terrible with
stuff like that like so bad and
i don't mean like awkward i mean
like i was i caused pain for
p yeah you know
like i i made things miserable and
and tedious and heavy because yeah you
know that was that was the turmoil
that was going on in me and
like all all i got was like
i remember my mom saying like someday
this won't matter and it's like i
can't you can't someday be this is
the whole world right yeah like
that's not helpful no it's not and
and i i mean i get i
get an impulse though because of course
when you see somebody when you see
kids when i would see like my
nieces or nephews or cousins or whatever
that a younger go through things like
this where my friends kids it's like
you can't believe you wanna you you
have that urge to tell them like
yeah this doesn't
it matter like you're not going to
remember this it's not gonna matter but
it's like they just can't hear it
well there's there's no point in that
because that's they literally can't think beyond
the moment oh this is all they've
experienced and that is the the stakes
are that high and then all the
shit that's happening to them yeah like
physic literally don't even know likely not
in life yes yeah yeah yeah
you didn't either no but i knew
to four o one k was yeah
we see them and you invested in
apple sir
when i was seventeen and tesla
so awesome you're just linear now does
the da
right we'll be right back
and we're back i wanted to say
that yeah the the young lady that
i took to my senior prom yeah
he was noreen
years later we did not keep in
touch years later i saw her name
in the credits of the sopranos she
was on the crew of the sopranos
interesting yeah it was really wild twisting
what you do do you remember the
i don't remember her title but ah
reading the credits so intently on the
sopranos i hope i see marine i
hope i see noreen so such those
reading the cringe
i'd never known her to be interested
in show business it's actually the opposite
that all of a sudden you saw
my eyes drawn to this name very
specific name that i knew yeah huh
that's crazy yeah and did you say
i miss her i did i said
i missed you nori i miss you
you were my platonic prom date um
i found out of a girlfriend passed
away oh it's horrible yeah ah and
we hadn't
kept up so what do you say
now ah on i i i i
found ah you know doing the body
in my living room
right any above it yeah for the
statue i mean i was dead asleep
i woke up
i don't know i don't wanna say
anyway but it wasn't did you find
out like in a weird way no
no no it's just someone told you
okay yeah the normal way and it
was just like a rainbow came to
my door
ah what no fucking way yeah better
get over that
no but it's it's ah it's ah
such ah bummer when i don't know
i go oh yeah you know well
i saw somebody out the reason i
asked how did you find out because
i saw somebody post about someone who
died on instagram and then the person
commented like oh no this is how
i'm finding out
out i was like yeah kind of
horrible yeah i've seen that i feel
like i've seen that a lot i
don't like that um i had a
guy one girlfriend of mine passed away
ah years ago and we had a
terrible relationship it was like a very
ah fraught ah and
it was the sex fun
it was a
news flash new silly just silly we
just have silly said i'm so fun
just to be able to la yeah
we we left all
oh huh
i can't imagine
so with the same huh
haha this is killing me
but either way we're iming having sex
well yeah looks like yeah
i found out in through a text
message somebody texted me and said have
you heard this news you know and
um it was weird because i heard
the news it was a voice voice
mobo it was like where's this going
then it didn't even rhyme and it
was bad news um but i because
our relationship was so bad um and
it was a it was a it
was a really terrible relationship that i
never wanted to be in but i
felt um she it was like one
of those things where all your wrong
buttons are pushed and you feel like
like you have to stay in this
relationship even though you don't want to
be in it and so we were
together for a year a solid year
and it was never like relationship that
i wanted to be in yeah it
was it was weird it was a
weird psychological fuckin crazy like the marshmallow
experiment was like i have patience if
you have a terrible if you're with
me now you're going to
two great relationships later on
um and so i thought like
what i felt weird because i was
like oh wow this isn't affecting me
and yet like i the first thing
that happened was i left my phone
i was in the back of a
cab all of my phone in the
cab never done that before and i
realised like i think there's some stuff
that i'm processing and i don't realize
it's like i knew that i was
somehow processing it but i didn't know
i wasn't conscious of pr
awesome right but i was like something's
going on do you go drunk with
your cousin that happened in this story
because i think it happened after your
mind after allowed need to know why
you're doing ah that one i figured
out i mentioned this when you talked
about bad because it just made me
think about it but i have this
banking pin out ok we'll see someone
died
i was like i like took a
shower but like accidentally left my underwear
on no you told me i was
like really i was just really out
of it haha wow yeah yeah yeah
yeah it say so wow and how
did you do did it take you
getting out to know i realized that
when i was in there but i
was like what it was just like
a we
weird sort of thing what is happening
why am i doing this now mia
was i had to really think about
what i kind of feel nothing about
this and does that make me write
like a weird monster but it was
not it was weird because this is
a person i did not have good
a good connection to do not have
good feelings for
i was never good yeah so it
was like a weird one yeah and
i talked about it on stage once
and then ah our ah we have
a mutual friend april who came up
to me after the show and said
that's not weird when my when my
biological father died a guy who was
never in my life i didn't feel
anything because he was just like
not a part of it like you
would think that right oh which my
father i should feel something but you
didn't because he just wasn't there you
know but she she said she went
through the same thing of like is
does this make me a a serial
killer that i don't have yeah the
yeah yeah yeah yeah interesting yeah but
i mean i think with that that
makes
sense to me to like if you
had only sound that good to me
yeah it wasn't like happy about it
but well but that that you'd go
oh yeah like it's not like you're
you're gonna be like skipping down the
street after you got out of the
cab why wouldn't a skipping i mean
yes it was a gallop i was
whistling are you tipping your top out
to every
ah yes i was i get kids
change said i got a little bit
of good news i got yeah
i like that stuff i got a
little bit of good news i got
it good news
ah death i don't think comes to
resolve scary to talk about it you
don't know we don't know if it
does or doesn't what are you talking
you think there's some people who are
immortal know i just we don't know
if we're going to die i don't
know i don't like it yeah so
you're saying as of now we have
no i've seen numbers other quote
unquote people die i don't know if
it's happening i say your brain preserves
itself don't say this when lawrence wearing
her hale bopp sneakers
um yeah speaking of hell oh no
we just came back from break
speaking of hell up oh shit what
failed top sneakers do you know what's
funny as i did you watch the
documentary on hilltops years no how about
secrets i don't know what we're talking
about going back kool-aid no goi yeah
they did they did drink it was
i don't think it was coolly with
drink some punch or whatever away jim
jones jim jones was when everyone died
with the same stinkers
yes that was hail bob heaven's gate
oh that's what alibaba oh yeah yeah
yeah and there was a document there's
documentary on hbo max right now now
what's it called um i think it's
called heaven's heaven's gate the cult of
cults i think it's called another cold
luckiest i know one time this one
actually is is worth your time it's
it's fascinating area the beach
these documentary what might make you cry
digi documentaries great i'd do it but
what if i don't really care about
the bgm no offense i think you'll
see you next time i think you'll
find their story interesting great i'll watch
it you'll make their about pj's
watch the bee jay's document
that was just on pornhub it's about
bee jay's the restaurant guys getting blowdown
yeah that's what's well they have a
zippy hey we love this so much
let's call our business beaches
oh ah yeah that was one of
the other business acres with chicken
give it to each other via j
yes
yeah
wait wait wait so i want a
cookie now i was gay
um have one why are we talking
him up sneakers and the document or
yeah helm up sneakers i didn't know
what we were talking oh so at
one point they are they're talking about
how it's kind of like in the
media when people's it's older than you
think
like we learned about it in the
nineties you know and um because that's
when the tragedy happened and so that
guy was that it had been around
longer than ever for twenty years since
the fucking challenges yes and people were
in it for that long and it
got it got crazier and crazier as
it went on of like
like like a lot of them do
where first it was it's a ufo
cold and we believe you will float
around in air ufo
and we believe they're they're coming and
and ah we're only meant to be
here for a short time we're supposed
to go to the stars with this
ufo and they started referring to their
bodies as vehicles and saying like this
is this is not truly us like
the soul resides within us but this
ufo is going to take us
to literally heaven that's how we're gonna
get to heaven this ufo is gonna
take us there and there will be
sales in heaven yes exactly um and
so as it went on then all
of a sudden you know part of
the part of the thing was the
two main people one of them died
of cancer and she was like their
deal was
we are immortal and oh so we're
going to go which is great to
say yes because if you're ever not
immortal and you're dead who cares because
you're dead you can't get told off
yeah but if your partner is sticking
around that's the problem then it's like
oh i say to people or more
yeah yeah yeah i would say one
of us is immortal
right so what did the dude who
who was still there say like how
did he cover he had to like
change it and you know explain like
no this is also part of the
plan and but it sounds like the
the difference in this cult was this
guy seemed to really truly believe all
of the stuff and it didn't seem
like he was scamming people
it seemed like this was truly what
he thought okay and so he was
just like everybody else i do adjust
his thoughts oh no yeah so you
say like oh okay well i figured
it out this is why should i
yeah so at one point in the
in the in the dock they talk
about how people were making fun of
this cult after they
he died you know because ha all
the details around his ers all the
dwell but my phasers but it was
was saying get to keep going this
was even even the nines was like
a less sensitive time than now where
people have less empathy i think you
think the nineties people had less empathy
yeah i do because i think there
were i think the majority
of people have less empathy because all
of the details of this were so
outlandish that it was very easy to
to go make china it was very
easy to make fun of them and
they showed like an snl sketch and
i remember tsunami yeah i remember we
did it mister show like we did
it like the second season of mister
show we had a heaven's gate thing
a parody wears on brand yeah absolut
lately but it's like oh my god
i was i was a fucking part
of that but you were in the
documentary i was scared i was going
to be
i really was like as they were
showing things different skin wouldn't sell you
know residuals though
i don't know this was like a
news program i know it was maybe
still what i had to pay sack
so ah ah why wild i think
that if the same thing happened today
i think privately i would probably make
jokes about it to my friends maybe
because the details are so atlantic like
i don't know
i would make comedy out of it
i don't think like ethanol is doing
a sketch about the vow
or are they i don't know it's
been a while since i've why watch
it but i don't think they have
i think comedies for young people when
people don't care about stuff and comedies
for the callow young people that switch
that's what you do you make fun
of those people because you don't think
you have feelings i think i think
of mister show are still around like
not like still going after the nine
s but if like the new version
of it they would they would make
a ah heaven's gate or ah you
know what i mean it's all like
fair game for the yeah for the
young people who don't give a shit
and go wow like dead people probably
yeah i yeah i don't know although
like that that ah the with bob
and david yeah you know it was
sad i don't know it's hard to
judge it's like it was that it
was like trying to figure out does
this feel the same does it feel
like creatively does this feel
all the same and it just a
lot of animals we don't hate as
much stuff these days like yeah back
then back then we would make a
sketch just on something we hated it
would be like oh here's something i
hate let's make fun of it yeah
you know i mean and about four
minutes to help stupid this yeah you
know it's like we don't necessarily
feel that way too
other than you know hey stuff
maybe but i also don't feel the
need to be like this thing i
hate is taking up the world's oxygen
yeah exactly you know it's like bill
hicks ranting about you know fucking ah
insync or whatever some boyband yeah that
he has this you know long rant
about and it's like do you really
give a shit that much like yeah
but i think at the time
time there was so little media that
kind of got made if something like
home improvement were out there you would
hate it oh because it's like
every person i know could do a
show better than this
right and he's the guy who gets
it yeah when you say you feel
like that life is unfair and now
everybody gets a show you're like hey
well i can't complain now i got
home and everyone has one television show
yeah and they can waste it when
they're two years old we already know
if you want to do it when
you're two you can can but you
get another one and it's not going
to win awards your parents also should
like you guys are talking about something
specific and i don't know what you're
talking about on this show the idea
that everyone gets a pilot everyone gets
one pilot my god yes and your
parents should be able to sew to
nyx until you're eight
team should be able to say no
you're not ready for the pilot because
some might be ready their kids my
grandkids really shit some kids are born
stall also some kids some parents shouldn't
force their kids to make their pilot
early yeah you know like here's a
quick stage moms here's a question if
you had a kid and the kid
was a star
like you just could tell you like
this kid is so just just so
outgoing so it's got wonderful would you
let them become a celebrity or would
you be like you have to wait
until you're eighteen this is tough because
everyone says that child stars are not
happy but but that's only because the
famous ones aren't and there probably are
other way
ones that are were perfectly happy and
so i don't know you know i
mean i once on mr show had
to audition a bunch of kids for
a sketch that that i wrote and
um you know and they were all
for the most part like all into
it and we were having a good
time and then one came in and
it was just so bummed
and didn't want to be there and
i was saying okay say you're lying
i remember the wine was it's pumpkin
any and i said an f the
end you have to like laugh and
and hold your mouth like i can't
believe what i just said and he's
just like it's pumpkin any and i
hear him i go you have to
laugh at the end and he's like
i don't feel like it oh boy
i go oh do you not want
to be here he goes not really
i go is your mom may you
you be here he goes yeah i'm
like who's good they're all like four
or five something like that so little
i'm just like oh you should say
you don't want to do it anymore
like if it's not making you happy
but it just is less rough if
my
and they wanted to do it i
mean obviously i was ex
it's fun
i'd say it's hilarious you should do
sure it's a gut buster i do
not buy your laugh um i would
i would have i would definitely give
him like a talk about showbiz yes
and you know blah blah blah um
talk that what we call the talk
here one is a book off the
top
it's because you do want to start
a pilot
you know i think every white parent
has to face this at some point
you
deduct each
if it were a pile it um
but if they if they really i
would you know i would stress like
if you really want to do this
you know supported for islam yeah but
here are the challenges yeah you your
life will
to you you'll have a lot of
attention paid upon you yeah at a
very young age and then you have
so much life to live yeah after
that that it can seem like a
letdown
you know i know somebody i had
that talk with somebody who was it
was a young adult friends the the
sibling of a friend of mine and
ah she was thinking about getting into
comedy and asked me for advice and
i said you know i basically gave
her that talk i was like if
you really make sure you
really want to do this because the
the lows of it are crush bad
they're really bad and you've got to
get used to it you gotta get
be like eventually you don't you don't
think about it so much anymore like
it's it's a weird amount of rejection
that you have to absorb yeah to
a point where it's like suddenly you
won't even run
remember it anymore or you'll be like
oh did i yeah edition for thing
or did i pitch a show yeah
oh they said no oh okay um
yeah oh i guess i didn't get
that job because i never heard back
from those who cares so i'm on
to the next thing i said you
have to really you have to want
to do it so much that you
when you're not making money from it
it's fun like you're you're
enjoying doing it just to do it
and she got into she got into
improv and did it for a little
bit and then got out of it
and it's lowering and i was
and i was like oh okay i
guess she didn't you know didn't yeah
it didn't click for her then she
got back into she got back into
it via writing and is now a
very successful good writer was great never
heard from her again about
got a nice wow
but i always wondered i always wondered
like did did did like that resonate
with her at all anything that i
said wait have i told you this
story that i was like i was
in a very happy for her by
the way yes i was doing pelamis
that she wrote that sopranos episode that
your old girlfriend was misusing and the
old creature of the pelamis class
i was like hey um i'm saudis
what actually happened
i saw a video or i saw
like then an interview did i watched
this interview you did and it was
about it was um sam jones like
i heard oh yeah he's great yeah
and he does stick long form interviews
anyways and she had watched it and
i was like oh cool and then
she was like
she said you said that i can't
remember what i said exactly of course
that i remember anything but she was
like you said that people should stop
doing improv
because there's too many people doing anywhere
and good and that is enabling but
she said that's yeah i thought you
were gonna say it was a joke
but no it isn't
okay i do believe though because my
point was more that people shit on
improv because they see a ton of
bad improv because there's tons of product
people doing it and it's like when
people are really good at it it's
really good and when it's bad i
also think they don't see a ton
of bad improv do you know what
i mean i don't see any i
yeah i saw i saw a ton
about improv well coming i
i think it's stand ups that are
on these writing staffs making fun of
improv that's true too but i mean
i think people like yes yeah but
anyway whatever and i was i was
getting like nervous she's telling me this
because i'm like you don't usually get
confronted with yeah your opinion and then
she was known should do that by
the way she was able to see
whatever you want and no one should
ever call you on it
no and she was like and i
quit improv oh well she goes i
realized that i actually really wasn't having
fun from you saying that and then
i always kind of forcing myself to
do it because i thought i was
supposed to but now i take acting
classes and i love it oh okay
right because that's the point not everyone's
good an improv and it doesn't it's
not the only way to do something
and in many ways
aces it's not the way to do
something like it's a weird route to
getting anything so like you helped this
guy was relieved ultimately but i was
like she might she all she she
actually didn't say at first thought you
were a bitch and then i say
that i appreciate that yes she was
like at first thought you were a
like just a bitch but she was
a first
something like that i was like oh
and then she was like but then
i realized it was because i actually
like didn't really like doing it and
so i was kind of offended that
you said that but then i i'm
not really right for it and i
shouldn't do it and i'm doing acting
class and it's going really well and
i was like that's great but i
also was like oh i'll never look
at you you know her name kate
winslet
we have to take a break we'll
be right back well
oh we're back and guess what it's
time for three teacher whoa yeah we
always do it for ah for ah
for ah good but the hot buggy
and also i just wanna say oh
cool anyone is triggered by me so
saying that you should quit em pro
you don't should quit and probably yeah
but you don't kind of i mean
you don't have to but if it
does bother you think about why that
might come up to learn if you
ever see it in color a bitch
she likes it apparently police don't seem
like you're gonna call her a bitch
but you don't actually go and then
compliment me
that's what she didn't do
ah alright we're gonna play a three
cheer this is called the picnic game
oh it submitted by mathilde g but
i feel like i probably did tell
that story already because i also feel
like i've probably made that identify already
i may remember hearing that story but
but i don't remember anything you've ever
said
nice i think you have something wrong
with you huh
door but let's not step on dorf
on golf dover golf lesson step on
matilda jeez mathilde gee thank you for
submitting a three cheer alright we'll see
you next week all right until then
smiling um he smiled and games ya
know you always ways
naw nee naw jaw and that's when
fans ah
necessarily good here's what she say one
person thinks of a criteria or theme
or category of things that their guests
can bring to the picnic examples things
that are blue things that start with
a round shaped things et cetera god
then the guests start asking if they
can bring specific things to
the picnic if one gets asked to
bring something that fits the criteria the
organizer lets them know they can come
to the picnic does not into this
picnic oh but there's watch out for
this whoa yeah if the thing does
not fit the criteria they can't come
as the game goes on the guest
must try to guess what the criteria
like a shell guess
it's okay no they must they simply
must i want to play must we
must give me the examples are no
yeah you gotta get it okay yeah
okay so are you you thinking of
the thing ah no i was just
reading this shit so wow too bad
fuck okay i have a category okay
so yeah you're the organizer okay hey
lauren what's up hey
yeah having a pick hey i heard
you everything too yeah i would love
to come i have a big sackful
of apples i have apples can i
come
depends and i would love to come
i have a box of depends know
you can't come but you could they
are adult diapers or they used no
you can't go oh wait i mean
i'll use them if you want me
to
i have a firetruck i want to
bring no you cannot come oh i
have and i think you'll probably need
this at the picnic some calamine lotion
nope
um i have a kermit the frog
puppet no huh
i have a liniment oil what's that
pass
i don't know
um i have
depends on the apples apples are either
red or green tea delicious or golden
i have a golden chalice
you can come yes ah i have
some ah hanukkah gelt that's wrapped in
gold foil you can come
i have a spandau ballet cd i
don't their song gold
you can come yes ah i have
a particular brand of pretzel ah it's
getting a little bit away from what
i mean
ah those pretzels rolled and gold you
can't come what with that
and you can't come with that cd
either i don't remorse your sorry comb
i already made plans so let's get
over it can we bring the other
things that we yeah so okay yeah
ah but just try to guess man's
way but i thought a certain point
we you're just supposed to say what
it is like oh yeah guess yeah
is it golden things sort of that's
why it's not right is it gold
things no is it yellow thing yes
oh neighbors
roll gold by the bags in apples
or sometimes yellow true yeah i guess
they're okay cool use diapers yes yellow
alright i have
i have ah
i have something cancer yeah it's a
weird story time to tell you guys
you have a picnic to celebrate okay
i will hey everyone brings something though
i need you to bring something to
my cancer nick i'd like to bring
um this this tv remote
i'm sorry you can't bring your tv
remote i like to bring potato salad
i'm sorry i just i don't want
any potato salad deputy i want to
bring um a jump rope no no
jump ropes unfortunately i'm so sorry i
want to bring fear um i'm sorry
no you have
to be have no breyer yeah i
mean be brave young bull i want
to bring a golf ball no no
golf balls sorry i want to bring
the big cup of spit sorry no
spit oh yeah spit before you get
to the picnic even in a comb
cup
yeah what you just hear the word
spit and you automatically think hey man
don't don't come che me okay
i want to bring a flashlight no
sorry the fuck i wanna bring a
flashlight who i wish but no i
want to bring a chip no no
chips i want to bring a chap
no chap see either sorry i want
to bring a kitten no kittens at
this picnic want to bring a dog
no dogs
either sorry i want to bring um
a best buy shirt
wait to shirt you buy the best
mop the plays where no sorry
i want to bring a crime no
no crime i need this to be
a lawful lawful picnic i want to
bring a steak no steak
i want to bring ah different game
sorry we're playing this one pickering a
chair know what the fuck how are
bring a pool know i want to
coarser i want to bring um a
bottle of water no i want bring
a lake no
called
i want to bring
an inflatable toy no i don't know
if you can use this i wanna
bring a rectangle no you can use
this somewhere in between a pool and
a rectangle want to bring a hot
tub know i mean i want to
make a square
now you're cool alright old again between
a pool and a rectangle remember the
examples he gave trust him remember the
examples he gave the types of things
that i could be thinking which is
literally anything but what was around something
you want to read it again no
i want to bring um a car
no
i do though
you're gonna walk or ah nevermind okay
you're right to your hint and yeah
i was gonna give a hint i
want to bring something fluid now i
want to bring something shaped xherdan way
i know it has nothing to do
with shane okay good whenever something that's
a certain color no i want to
bring something that is a certain hard
or soft
what are all the things that are
between pool and rectangle that especially in
a certain sense what book
oh a dictionary i want to bring
a box of crisp serial please come
to my picnic i want to bring
a queen of course you can go
whatever bring a quick sand yes i
would love quick sandy bring a queer
get used to it
gorgeous wanna bring anything that starts with
q yeah yes sorry i thought that
would be easier but then you never
said martin q it was hard yeah
it was hard it was i think
a better letter okay you turned pool
alright hey guy the letter q on
the list nobody was starting with starting
with
hey yeah so hey guys great news
oh i'm fine cancer-free yes yes and
i met julius really i'm so thank
you doctor i've been fun for you
yeah i'm finally able to tell you
that scott is cancer-free yes now great
that like nick nally wearing new business
okay okay i think we should kind
of
celebrate this business you're gonna like with
the new business oh okay because he's
tied in alright great celebrate scott's catch
a free diagnosis i'm going to have
at my palatial doctor's home a picnic
in the backyard fabulous oh and i'd
like i'd like to invite you provided
you can help out a little bit
of bringing certain things that i need
oh
okay guess i'd like to bring what
you can't come if you can't bring
something that i need i'd like to
bring a palm leaf ah sorry kick
him i would like to bring a
casserole in no okay to use that
i'd like to bring a tomato i'd
rather you didn't i'd like to bring
a baseball don't
i'd like to bring a bed buzz
i'd like to bring a snake don't
do that i'd like to bring a
car i really didn't i'd like to
bring a giant nice i'd like to
bring a doll
i'd like to bring dice nope i'd
like to bring a basketball i wish
it would i'd like to bring an
academy award you can't i'd like to
bring the silver spoon
i'd like to bring a devil nine
i'd like to bring a book yet
i'd like to bring paul newman oof
ah i'd like to bring some popcorn
nope
i'd like to bring
abraham lincoln and i'd like to bring
a kilt know i'd like to bring
a bird ah what about some hair
my preference is no i'd like to
bring sunglasses know about a tuxedo no
i'd like to bring a plant i'm
just looking at things now yeah i
know but no how about something like
a um
like a rubik's cube know i'd like
to bring a fire pit now i'd
like to bring an umbrella know i'd
like to bring zebra now xylophones now
i'd like to bring a trumpet no
okay i don't know if i wanna
come
i i still want to come i
love to bring gladys knight and the
pips nah cheez-its in no although if
you bring those my
take care of the other thing but
no mouse no
take care of the other thing could
i bring smokey robinson and the miracles
though there'll be no music of the
big
wait although pizza not even either you're
gonna play on sonos through the stereo
are gonna be dead silent no conversation
you have nothing to say she's one
of the closest we've gotten but it's
still not it it would take care
of the other thing
cheese cheese realize i can bring an
elephant no recycling bin
that also might help the other thing
but no
can i bring garbage that could possibly
hope the other thing but bottles that
could probably help the other thing i
bring a truck no help with the
other thing
bottles of beer
yeah i mean you can get specific
if you want but could i bring
a person who runs a junkyard
no huh
he's fun still we had sex once
no
he sounds hilarious yeah he's fed um
okay
is this very specific it is a
specific thing yes okay it's not general
it's a specific thing in that category
no it's not a category wow maybe
i should not have done that so
you there's only one thing that we
can say which we can bring yes
oh no you're never sick
you probably should not have done even
some hints oh recycling bin would help
jesus in recycling and a bottom bar
and help urine a wind chime
no and no a homeless person ah
i don't know where you're going but
cheez-its would help a hungry person like
a hungry hippo know
i fucked up
yeah i mean i suppose it is
yeah it's like a category specific okay
so what was it it's ants yeah
yeah you might like insects would have
been yeah a little more general yeah
your stone character at least she's it's
a recycling bin and bottles would heh
and everything was like things we've tracked
track to them yeah yeah
that's hilarious well that's how you play
the picnic it's really is how you
play the game play let's wait no
i'm sorry not to blame
both who look hey within that game
we can change how to play it
and how not to play so you
have all the information you need so
just play this on youtube next time
you have a player you do
can you fucking imagine everybody shut up
okay good
play his entire episode
just this part no they play the
entire thing that was filed that actually
told that story before
last party we went to
alright we did it every day yeah
another one in the books on library
of congress certainly speaking of which i
hope your inauguration day yesterday was good
yeah you had a good time yeah
if you've got an operator yesterday oh
okay oh it was great ballistic i
know one person who's listening who did
she work
um alright we're gonna see next week
we're never leaving you were never leave
we're never gonna keep on gone we'll
see next time we love you love
you
la la la go have sex this
week it's hilarious
uh