three
oh
hey welcome to freedom
oh yeah welcome we're here we're here
scott here hello oh yeah
we're doing it too we're having sex
with each other
whoa are you my love of wiiware
a rubber one
what is this what it's doing it
by elo cool day oh are you
my love of you were a robot
ah one of them says hey no
i think no no the girls the
girls i forget i forget that his
duet he gay people were rubber well
the woman's second aware it
such a good and that's what she
was talking about the female cop duh
know that every female lo female chi
to public doe where a female condom
see you might lose a step where
a female con
welcome to the show
welcome to the show lawrence
i was twenty minutes late yeah oh
that's true
that's also true
um but i had plenty of time
to get warmed up in the car
that's right were you doing your vocal
exercises it's listening to music what were
you listening to on the way here
i decided to do a two thousand
throwback and a listener you realize we're
in the two thousand right now early
two thousand never heard of and i
put
in some guster and some postal service
it was a rule it was a
real throwback which postal service such great
heights so is putting but see i
ended up playing some weird epee that
was all covers
um but i put on guster which
i've listened to since i don't know
probably at least ten years ago and
i it's just so crazy that feeling
when you just start like immediately know
all the words to a song you
haven't heard of millionaires right just as
we're doing right now um
it's roach in the tree tops oh
that's me ginny lauren your voice do
you start yeah i do a trigger
okay any trigger ah subtle comedy ya
wow i still know all the words
to that okay so it's a kid
and though every single word i've listened
that song in ten years um i
put i put on the first song
of this guster album
and i just was so surprised you
know i started to care about guess
i have a few of their songs
oh
don't challenge into it
it's very goofed in black guster does
gust in
girls do
do you like the jayhawks ah not
really i mean i just don't i
mean the jayhawks well what was going
on in your life ten years ago
that guster the j huh he had
happened to you i was ah twenty
two okay isn't drinking a lot holick
i liked guster in haikou
what did you drink when you were
in college like alcohol yeah um no
just beer was vodka soda vodka cranberry
sorry ma just like a real sex
and the city they didn't do that
didn't have things to drink cause cosmo
oh no my cranberry isn't no way
what's there's more ingredients in cosmo cola
was like a type of martini what
did you drink in college what's in
cosmo shaven i drank i started on
beer i didn't drink i didn't drink
until after high school and that i
started with ah drank a lot of
beer or smoked did you ever smoke
sick
six yeah yeah i smoked cloves for
like a sec oh yeah that's really
so good did you ever try cigarette
scott i think i've smoked one or
two in my life not not to
actually do it but just to for
like i don't know if i'm in
a part or something fruit roll over
roll yeah yes and
everyone always saying like hard boiled private
detective every everyone always whenever i would
smoke would say oh you don't smoke
because i was holding it wrong or
something yeah way yeah i don't even
know how one hole lame to like
like you're doing this bad thing wrong
yeah it's like who cares you're not
doing it the cool way alright offer
help rather than say you know clearly
your
bad at what you're doing oh yeah
you don't smoke yeah like what is
the ah you just put it between
your two you're you're looking pussy fingers
right
ah so fingers on to her looking
pushy fingers third is the one that
goes down during a shocker shocker
i report for this one about cocaine
the other day okay i was talking
i had heard a little gossipy story
about someone i knew who was doing
much cocaine and i was like oh
that's so gross and i was telling
this other person ah it's really just
disappointing to me that this person was
doing cocaine because you you see it
as weakness i just think it's
gross to do again and then this
person that i was talking to made
me feel like i was like a
square for that like he was just
like oh it's so fun and i
was like no i don't like that
and i don't think it's cool to
do that and i'm not fun and
it's not cool but i'm not like
against all drugs or something but the
idea of like doing coke in a
restaurant or something like bums me out
i totally agree about cocaine it is
i'm not against i'm not a puritan
about drugs at all and i've done
various drugs but cocaine was one that
never interested me be first of all
the idea of snorting something that's part
of what really is rather oh yeah
i much rather put a needle in
my eyeball but also
so any anytime i'd ever been around
anyone on coke they always seem like
such asshole yeah it just seemed it
didn't seem fun and it seemed like
i it seemed like it was a
thing that high for a a type
of person that i didn't want i
think that's how i feel about ticks
everyone i like not i know a
lot people who i'm friends with who've
done it where i'm like that's not
like part of their identity but people
i know who do it a lot
i typically think are asshole yeah i
yeah i also discovered i also have
a theory about cocaine is in terms
of ah artistry that i think it's
it's a drug that you you that
people
can't come back from when like creative
people is part of their creed seems
like it shears off something in your
brain because people i think people can
come back from booze like they got
back from heroin and still be creative
but people that were like hardcore coke
heads yeah it's usually music people they
they seem to have lost something when
they recover it's interesting like who i'm
an interesting guy
well i wish i could think of
five examples writing wow when you're done
go game music what do you think
about it i've never done it i
think because we paul you and i
maybe grew up in the eighties when
there was so like everything every sitcom
every movie had a big lesson about
cocaine you know just like shows
now are doing it as as if
it's cool real like coke is like
a go to like move like took
kind of up the stakes of situation
using i mean every single movie had
something like you know bright lights big
city less than zero that was all
like the fall from like the first
time as like all fun and and
and then within minutes they're addicted and
yeah you
no so i was always very surprised
when you know i was eighteen i
was hanging out with my friends and
my my friend disappeared into the bathroom
and it came out i was like
oh i did coke um i was
always just surprised by that but yeah
how can you do coke because that's
gonna lead you to always doing right
you know so i have friends now
who talk about it whose go yeah
oh yeah sometimes i'll
do a little coke and it will
be like it's just so strange to
me it's very surprising like you doesn't
it you you're addicted to coconut yeah
really like to do that regularly that
seems i don't know a problem a
friend of mine told me this story
years ago that he was at some
club um and there were the there
was this table
of of ah like persian businessmen these
young guys and they were all like
dressed to the nines and and they
had all these people around the table
and and this is like i guess
the the dawn of bottle service or
whatever oh i loved that year i
want that every time i go out
they should make a movie about the
dawn of bottle service and it
should have apes in it
and so this my my friends female
friend was standing near this table and
one of the guys heard about this
little pipe it would crack huh
like lady saying she was musician
ever
crack oh god crack gary i know
we probably sound like squares though to
pee that's what i'm saying like oh
no i didn't you know maybe like
you know once a year twice a
year i'll do coke yeah that's actually
my my friends have to do it
at the summer and then into it
and christmas time when it's something really
years in summer whatever like twice a
year for deadline christmas
but i was like i'm not lame
for not liking that like i don't
know i feel like i i let
enough things slide in the world that
i think are cool and like everyone
would do it every day why abortions
but i think it's what i think
about people i know well it makes
me feel like bummed out that they
want to do that i'm like oh
no i feel like
there there was one from my alcohol
enough there's right and there's so many
things like there's so many things i
don't fret one guy almost sold me
on it who is somebody that i
trusted and and ah ah it was
not like a coke head but was
like somebody who did had done it
like a few times over the course
of his life
he never went through like a cookie
period but every once in awhile had
done it and enjoyed it and it
was like it's actually a lot of
fun and we should i say oh
you don't know she said we should
there will let's let's like do it
some night you know we'll just get
someone will do it and um and
we never did it yeah but he
was right let's get someone doing three
yeah it was
yeah oh yeah hey can you imagine
if we do it we would have
to
i had a friend who is who
i think is still into drugs now
i want to do it of god
because what a nightmare that recording will
be in how a horrible to listen
back to
everything i had a friend who was
into drugs who i was just talking
about drugs like everything makes me sleepy
yeah i i can't out all pot
every you know every drug just makes
me sleepy i would just want to
sleep so i was like oh man
i wish there was something where you
pick two sleepy drugs right there yeah
i know
i was just like i would like
to i would like to get higher
whatever maybe but although the last time
i got high man it was like
three months ago or something yeah baby
in the microwave
you're wild yeah you gotta do a
p sale but yeah no i just
had to but
i'd too much pot and i just
was like well i don't like being
high i'm going to go to sleep
and then i couldn't go to sleep
and i was like bugging out of
my mind i don't i just don't
like it but i sort of to
my friend i was saying oh you
know i i wish there was something
where i was like oh i could
stay awake and have fun and he
was like try liquid heroin heroin guys
like
i don't think so with the heroin
have a coffee
yeah that will keep you away little
spesso sos from the coffee maker calling
liquid heroin like regret like a crack
like doo doo doo doo liquid i
just want to state again that i'm
not lame everyone i think people think
we're lower the record i'm cool lame
for
or other things i don't know claim
for that although i do wonder if
like there are people who are who
are really into drugs listening to podcasts
i don't know if that intersect i
don't think there's aid for sure this
does it really okay
hey goods right choice about you let
us show the cookies podcasts that you
listen to
i love to cook and listen to
this show what would it be those
pod save america guys or something involved
if you do love doing coke can
you love turning doing coke then turning
on this show i'm sorry that we
killed your buzz the last ten minutes
sorry about the talking about how lame
you are if we killed your buzz
but that conversation get
better coke so i'm saying
hey look i can it
papa i allow ives i think another
element of it just to kind of
add to my reasoning is it's hearing
what people who i know didn't do
those this person i'm not talking about
them but i'm saying didn't do it
really before and now we're doing a
lot right right it's always weird when
someone's in our forties
or something in there like oh i'm
into coke now yeah it just feels
like do that from when you're twenty
on or don't bring it into the
picture yeah or if you have some
job like you're on s and l
yea i won't go
you have to stay up all night
for no yeah i had somebody to
give me a hard time about taking
ah ah ecstasy back when i was
called ecstasy like in my own now
i was in my oils molly or
mbna i was in my i was
in my thirties the first time i
tried it because it was not i
think when i was in high school
cool it was not a thing and
if it was it was like the
very beginning i don't think it was
i don't i never really heard about
it so there were some raves in
like eighty eight that i went to
that i bet people were taking i
think maybe i would see people like
ten years younger than me yeah probably
that was when you would be doing
that in high school right um and
it
it was very popular and right um
so i was telling the story and
the story was not about
not about the first time i tried
this drug story it was was about
me on this drug and this person
who's who's a friend of mine and
i'm not gonna say their name say
they have say their name come on
this is a person who does not
do who's strange person we guess doesn't
do know she's not on-air not on
my not on my friend jesus
yes i'm telling you he drinks a
little wine everyone sorts
used to be watered but hey what
the hell but he this so this
person kept saying wait in your thirties
and i was like yeah and so
anyways like whoa why would you it
seems like that seems really like weird
like you would already use that when
you are younger yeah it's like she
like what she is she she was
older than you are young no younger
than me and wouldn't let it go
to the point where it was like
okay now you're starting to insult me
right yeah it's like that is ridiculous
that you did that that said in
my story i'm i'm probably only talking
about one person who shouldn't do
cause i mean it just evolved now
i'm just saying easy to me it
all started from my feelings whether it
was the sequel to it wasn't me
is is it me is it me
what if i have pretty we'd do
a different interpretation of that song and
he's relieved to find out that it
wasn't was it wasn't me it wasn't
me oh it wasn't me
however did you find me on the
bathroom wasn't wasn't me banging on the
bathroom flooring and i'm out there buck
naked my mom was a teacher for
many years and her an educator yes
and her suit one year they had
talent older school and some students it
was like k through eight so i
don't know like how old they were
but the dogs they'd performed that song
k nine
they performed wasn't me maybe wow i
don't know if it was like kidz
bop version where it was like where
they changed certain lyrics yeah but let
me say this if i understand kids
bop i get it certain songs just
don't don't don't don't do it i
heard kills dough it ah dua lipa
the other day
yeah if you're under him and they
were just saying why they were just
saying it just oh yes yes shevlin
look it up shiv and look it
up look it up kevin barrett in
the ah there was a lip-sync in
our high school lip syncs um which
i used to take part in every
year was really unusual that the one
where you saying ah you said paula
or john is er oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah patter about i know that
was an eighth grade before i got
to high school that was the first
time i ever did one that was
in class but during rescinded there were
there were there were lip syncs every
year like big lips in competition every
year and watching kids lip-sync is brutal
the reason i was gonna suck at
yeah the reason i was going to
talk about is because three girls three
of the like popular girls um did
vanity six nasty girl and they all
dressed in lingerie oh my god and
they did the whole thing of like
i need seven inches like all that
kind of stuff she says and i
still think about that
yeah know it made them change the
the rules of the lip-sync where then
you had to do it for a
teacher before you went on stage so
someone to private show yeah
a guy like you do it me
yeah you do it on stage
oh it creeped us yeah it was
pretty cool it must have been a
so quite a scandal it was it
was scandalous scandalous i'm no but i
do there there was the the one
year my friend josh did devos are
we not men were divo and he
did an incredible tableau of
he had ah like fifteen people on
stage he was he was playing a
professor and he was at a blackboard
with ladki d yeah lab coat de
vigo mortar board
no no more rewards de um stick
definitely stick
um snares with the long ribbon i
think he might have had one of
those yeah but there was like a
blast to that don't have the arms
like ten years oh yeah there was
ah a woman in in like a
cocoon thing that he was watering who
suddenly it was incredibly did this incredible
scene of
i'm with people dancing it was like
you know choreography it was amazing i
was it was i was blown away
by it i was like this is
the most amazing thing i've ever seen
to this day and then hasn't seen
he lost and the high school football
team who listening to super bowl shuffle
shock oh my god and all they
did was they were in
a line and they just honestly they
probably recreated a perfect day that's exactly
what it was i think i prefer
the second the team doing that now
really
if we're from uganda yeah i love
the bearish what if he had had
lingerie on under his lab coat and
yeah it was like duh he was
like look at this a little
all to do with chevron supposed to
look something up i'll tell you whenever
you have let me tell you something
about chevron give us your your detailed
report first yeah whatever whatever it was
we asked you to look okay cosmo
has all the way back no longer
oh my god yeah talking about ah
can't i don't know how to say
cuanto
sro quatro cranberry juice fresh lime juice
and vodka okay so the line i
mean the line would have pretty pretty
close to pretty close well i was
thinking it's five songs like kids bop
was dua lipa new rules new rules
yeah vodka cran would also be on
the rocks and yeah that's true
this is the kidz bop version oh
my god the channel is going down
fourth sorry what this is the fifth
version just listen to it
are you doing right now explain yourself
don't just go huh the drawing going
along kevin certainly understand yourself simply understand
yourself ah yes ah da dams huh
what is this the kidz bop new
rules for oh my god len you'll
pick up the phone your mom is
going to make you clean your room
okay easy are these are these kids
singing or zoo adults trying to sound
like kids this sounds like a dumb
ready nose as a kid you just
give me some
come in
nah he makes it so like nah
buddy know it's weird no i can't
tell if it gets kids
ah he doesn't love me so some
stuff so it's a bizarre twist
to make up the phone you know
is calling tizzy sad and sad and
alone gotta like that day like that
and down again three it was drunk
on the ways fray
meet a bigger friends in london you're
gonna wake up in his bed again
you're gonna meet it with your friends
way but we missed the mark oh
my god oh yeah rewind a little
bit i mean every video is incredible
i realize there was video and logic
kids why are you just turning around
the video now normally it was quite
a reveal it was well done down
again three
zombies friend noisy dude friends in the
nba with you and get
if you're very okay
i liked it it's multiple kids all
looking into the same for what you're
taking yeah the kids are right no
i need the pursues and jumping around
like a candy looking room why and
singing about a fucked up relationship yeah
why are kids bad singers there you
know let me tell you know what
i mean like most kids are like
huh they can't because they barely know
how to like move their body yeah
they're new here's what i was thinking
about the other day i was i
was watching something in the attic kids
like you know catholic choir whatever where
there was a church i was sure
i was just building watching church i
watched this building star watching something what
church the other church i was
no but remember remember how kids like
little boys used to be such amazing
singers they would go through balls off
so because she's just like oh yeah
but how do they convince them today
where unix they were unix lily balls
equals unic i just know balls eagles
unic had this whole ah
just listened to a totally lame where
they were talking about castration and the
two women on it thought that castrating
was chopping off the dick and i
was like wait i think i do
too and i don't i was younger
it's now it's it it's always i
thought it was everything yeah when i
was younger yeah it's always the ball
and chemical castration is just they pour
acid on your balls
and they shrivel up and scream
no but how do they how would
they convince these little boys like hey
you got a good thing going here
let me just say you're sorry
that makes me it's nice to do
it maybe they would just do what
i do they would like in the
middle of the night why we like
just stay in the middle of the
da cut off this little boys oh
and totally lame they were talking about
the moyal who gave the baby herpes
oh and the baby out
cheat oh come the herpes let me
ask you why are you talking about
that now yeah i'm trying to honestly
the part until i started talking huh
in the middle of your said hey
i love you sandy that was i
remember the baby duh herpes parse interesting
and i was like oh you have
them that had okay i better say
well i knew it was gonna get
there so
ouch um anything else chevron that you
add to that was outstanding
ah no see i howard shaggy cute
up for their kids shaggy shaggy cute
up play joints alright may as well
alright we need to go to a
break we have shaggy cute up we
may as well do it we'll be
right back with more freedom no halted
yeah this dance i'm also lucky
bodmin to earn resistance
we're back oh no i mean i
cut your balls off because you're a
really good senior really really good thing
going right now paul you think anything
would change like what i'd be able
to see what i'm like in your
personal level that yeah do you like
probably hello please
hey
you would change just like your soul
would change from just having your personality
whack your balls off as an adult
i don't know i don't think it
would be the from like ah not
like a disease but like just because
someone was like hey wait
now this is unpleasant anyone who is
wouldn't be as soul crushing if someone
just came up if someone killed up
to you it was like i'm gonna
chop the bows up and they did
a movie of your boss you would
never be the same is my point
your life would change well by larry
way if i allowed them to if
i said okay go ahead that's up
to you at that
point someone said i wanna touch your
balls i want you not to want
why can't i take control of the
situation if someone comes up to you
so you have agency you're off but
i say you know what good go
right ahead
now i have some unpleasant news okay
what do you got
we had an episode of the show
know what where
someone was unjustly spanked oh boy and
i feel that there must be consequences
yes semyon yeah or that it was
you shoving was you don't try the
shaggy defense here
now we ask to convene a tribunal
so here's what it is okay so
so it's upon listening talk about it
i was spanked for us for telling
a story that i'd told on a
different podcast and the person who spanked
me heard it on the other podcast
and said that i'd already told it
and he spanked me and that person
what happened with chevron and so there
are a few options that lay before
us we could a spank chevron to
even it out but i don't want
to do a power imbalance
it doesn't feel right it doesn't me
i know i want to get away
with it um but i don't i
don't want to do it so i
wanna get away with it i'm saying
you want to do it and you
get away don't buy that probably but
i'd probably be able to get away
with it okay cute
eric
the other option is you get a
reverse spanking from shevlin wherein he's like
the pen on your ass verse members
just wanted to put a pin up
my ass no huh up here on
the boeing my laser against your sides
but on it goes quickly like whips
it away
i know i don't want that okay
what's what's the other thing that's part
of that is that we can make
it a boomerang and it looks like
you're getting spayed know i'm just boomerang
i'm actually spank that muddies the waters
okay third option i'm just flying by
the cinema paints now also like hamilton
um
sorry what he's hamilton flied but each
season depending like it's flying by the
seat of his pants handsome blade as
they know it it takes pete to
take some balls uncut off balls to
write a musical where someone calls you
handsome
yeah although you could say i'm really
playing the role of someone hands on
helton was hot oh he was sri
was i hot women after myth the
saying you know what according to the
ten dollar bill he's actually a handsome
guy is here let's prove it let's
play but give me ten dollars just
doing dollars
he's got he's got great all we
need a third alshon yeah we need
to serve but i tell you i
have one night i said i thought
we just my message to my pants
oh that's true i thought we'd discussed
one year the way what was the
other one the other one was look
it up in our texture wow am
i right was yeah kevin we just
wasn't here really hamilton was with bay
a
hashtag hamilton was bad i have news
for you hamilton was bay hamilton literally
really hot okay okay never oil into
the ten dollar bill gonna never looked
at a ten dollar bill you ever
jerked off to me it only looked
at i only get hundreds bed um
i jerk off to coins
points lot
okay smash my email
god
my piggy boom
coin in my piggy bank where did
we take so much including okay yeah
okay so we hear okay okay so
it could be my suggestion was you
have to kiss our rings
paul you suggested has to say or
do something embarrassing
yes to score but he needs to
squat against the wall and say me
loves banging mommy okay that's pretty good
we should fill now and then we
decided he should sing hard to sam
sorry by chicago and then i thought
he should saying i'm sorry by alvin
the chipmunks
and then i sent you and you
were you were like what is what
is hard to say i'm sorry and
i sent you a video trying to
get you to open it and it
was and it was never gonna give
you up i'll never be rick rolled
again um everyone saying here's a video
that explains this i feel like people
online were shocked that i'd never been
rick rolled yeah what
so so what do we decide kevin
can you sing can you sing it
all can you carry a tune not
well okay can you sing badly ah
yes do you do using badly yeah
he's gonna go back to me
i think badly and i was like
he's gonna say poorly maybe don't just
say poorly next time i think to
make him sing something as well as
he possibly while he squats and a
quarter while he squats in a corner
i think i just think dua lipa
he's just saying dua lipa he should
sing it along requires singing
bring up the bringing up the lyric
own know when i'm gonna play the
kidz bop version sing it and dance
and we will tape it why don't
we put it out i think we
should get a karaoke version so he
doesn't have a guide vocal i think
i never heard the song can use
a guide but you don't know this
just st just single you you know
it just singing along with it lauren
will tape it singing along with it
singing
along with it stand up sing along
with this standup squat singing along with
his hand up squat c along with
it and then between lyrics you have
to say me like spanking mummy dad
i'm ready out alright go go go
go go go go go go go
nah don't do fake bed bedsit you
have to sing as welling as well
as you can
my law
dansko
yeah
oh pick up the phone dad and
sand along to all save me like
thanking god free me love spanking
if you love spanking mommy
he's liking this too much it's not
a culture
he likes it thank you
hey mikey he likes the attention alright
alright
this is not a proper punishment i
did think it was funny but it
didn't really achieve what yeah he's not
embarrassed enough i feel like this weirdos
on punishable that's the problem shifts i
feel like anything we throw out he's
like i'd like this can i bring
up something from previous episode yeah we
just want to say that i was
indicated
your vindicate i was vindicated um ah
so many people have written that carrots
are good on sandwiches thank everyone and
i was vindicated everyone loves carrots on
sandwiches and and and and and i
was right but you guys wrong and
fainting an indian man in into public
has spoken and i'm in the i'm
in the right and thank you very
much for backing
me all they said was bond me
over and over again no alright a
lot of people were talking about you
wait ah another hamilton joes wort when
we were talking about sandwiches we were
talking about american regular data which we
were talking about american you oh god
yes we were and you know it
yeah
just regular just regular shit but i
know what you mean you can turkey
sandwich or something we weren't sure thing
about but a lot of people have
written said yeah they're good on sandwiches
so thank you so much really appreciate
a lot of people corruption that's insane
yeah so i don't know
felt justified to be a preponderance of
people the captain justified wrote and said
that's nuts and that is hashtag justified
no thank you so much to everyone
out there for saying that i was
right but i love the idea but
i love this is my favorite thing
when when this happens we were saying
the discussion starts as that's not a
reg
killer thing that you put on sandwiches
then it becomes people saying ah the
bond me as if we said there
is no set which that evolves care
right now but that's okay i it's
it's more common in england i will
admit and then set and then someone
was saying that in another in another
country that all subways
have australia i believe australia yes so
anyway thank you so much to the
citizens of the world we would back
me from here yeah and we'll die
here you think so in two weeks
oh no no i get i feel
like i could die anyway
really you'd be okay if you died
in another country and your family could
bring your body i don't want to
because i'd be your family would have
to like bring your like fly your
body home i don't want that to
happen but i'm saying like you're hiking
in australia i don't want i'll never
do that yeah you're never too like
we barely walk around sydney we really
although i personally enjoyed australia i did
too i was i was remembering that
first day we walked around i realized
i'm wearing the wrong shoes because yeah
it fucked up my feet and my
legs were locked up for hours yeah
we did i think we couldn't check
into the hotel yeah yeah right opera
house yeah i was talking about traveling
the
other day with someone who who's traveled
a bit for tours ah who who
has a show here nono mick jagger
it was fun no but i was
saying that every place just seems like
shitty or law that you go to
doesn't
i live in new york new york
is the route re sydney seem like
shitty railway wow sydney she toronto yeah
and that's something
no i don't know like there was
when we went to the ah when
we ate with hanford by the beach
that was that was cool it was
very cool but like somebody bandai be
twenty calls yeah but just walking around
sydney to me was like yeah i've
been in a city i don't know
when you're on tour it's kind of
like yeah i love the time we
had no time it's very different than
when you're traveling so
somewhere and you like you get to
stay there for multiple days yes lord
yeah all the cool thing i think
it is very hard to get the
flavor of the city in a day
yeah yeah totally but it was bad
imagine if you are a mage if
you are going there before sydney's great
imagine if you're from australia and then
you come here and they and you
and you're on tour and for some
reason you're only in van nuys and
then you're like l a suh but
we were in sydney i know but
we only saw a little part of
van nuys of australia
no i do some whenever people come
out here to l a and they
they plan whatever they going to do
around these tourist things like rodeo drive
or whatever i always feel very sorry
for them i know but there is
part of it where you kind of
have to see that and like get
it yeah because you can't just because
it was fertile ground so light can
be like i
get it like it's like you should
l a it's a chill sprawling ridiculous
city that like you might as well
do a bus tour or do something
where you can see a lot of
it i don't know i don't think
it's the worst thing ever i will
also say anyone who thinks that they
need to see rodeo drive when they
come here you absolutely do you definitely
don't so so small yeah you're gonna
drive and wave
yes but it's like you go it's
such a hike fun everywhere probably that
where it's just yeah a bunch of
fancy stores like yeah that i can't
imagine being on one of those tmc
buses those no no it's all i
can think about it would be horrible
but i just follow i've said that
and then we were on that we
were on that double decker bus and
in england it was great we wrote
a double no i wasn't
no you weren't there but but cool
up and i took it around england
and i was like wow this really
makes me like you're on vacation though
no no it was wrong it was
a tour one and then i told
my canford about it and he took
it and said it was great so
i don't know so maybe hands on
the tour it's anybody see legacies or
it's gonna be the best one but
this is where the bombs they had
those bumfights and
you think that's
this is the famous alley where they
had those bumfights
i just think tmc is not the
most reputable there was a guy who
occasionally would show up outside of largo
in the at the by the stage
door and cool it it depending on
who the guest would be an alley
can be creepy oh yeah ab's that
allie's terrifying what ali is not creepy
yeah but that one's got a lot
of traffic of of people who are
not of their right mind they just
shouldn't make alleys anymore right yeah another
solution
i think there's some nice out like
what crime alley primarily where well it
gave yeah chris yeller ca scientologists i
know you know i loved her though
in the eighties i did take sure
she was like summer school and he
knew shown her role yeah she's great
in summer school i love her and
cheers same loved-one cheers yeah ah i'm
chuffed there was
a local church i loved from chairs
i guess alleys are good for what
deliveries we're talking about that's the top
of the lease too alleys are fine
in a non-major cities where you think
alleys should be almost suburban now there's
the only reason to have valley is
in a major city or doesn't have
alleys it doesn't have alleys no
think about it well i guess people
in new york are just fine blocking
streets off like are parking there yeah
wait so yes this guy he would
use from tmc and huge if i
had like a fancy person on my
show he would wait in the alley
for them to come out of the
stage door my god and then they
i think he i don't think he's
ever success
yeah the front but then you would
like fuckin fill me like i'm loaded
up with a quick mag na priest
about the bar it's mortifying and then
like hey paul what do you think
about ah whatever dumb thing was going
on in the new yes i had
one guy follow me at the airport
and he's like he's actually asking about
comedy but i was so annoying shit
i was on tv the other day
i did that just really yes from
the eu and the thirty miles own
just with what you're going to ask
you about that's the mc yeah that's
how that's how far legally paparazzi has
to be or whatever right yeah they
asked me about the between two ferns
oh well i made him go away
and he seemed sad but i think
that what they do is not good
no they've also hurt my feet they're
not helping anything yeah yeah no it's
bad but the guy was nice guy
was nice to him whenever he was
like just do something else with your
job like to know why like just
go staff up on a sitcom
if you need money dam up dude
just step i'm no i mean i
know you don't want to be tied
down you know for that amount of
time but just staff up for a
year maybe they'll make you do it
to your contract
and then you'll be able to develop
happenings
maybe they'll ask you if they can
cut your balls off my haircut your
post you could say yes or no
okay let's take a break perangkat okay
it's yarbrough raggedy apple pie that ray
guy got la vie de la me
lang
welcome back po we're back okay this
is it's time for a feature yes
this one comes from ryan fisher at
sir ruchi hi ryan sir urrutia or
is it serratia it's sir ruchi sir
ruchi
and sarah jan ryan this is the
game called one word impressions someone does
an impression of a well-known figure real
or fictional hashtag real talk or hashtag
mikki vicki i don't know what
okay
oh he's saying a real or fictional
it feels like a doughboys hashtag situation
if it's real do hashtag real talk
if it's fiction you ask hey maybe
we don't make you figgis from do
the right thing yeah yeah yeah yeah
i i usa believe we talked about
it yesterday came up we don't want
a spanking because i was prompted into
it and i fell
like you would be okay you'd be
sitting there wondering what we were talking
about if i didn't tell you thank
you you can only say so back
off shevlin put your spanking pen away
and
i say no it's just so weird
spanking rankings make a weird thing we've
accepted your vow which are lobby on
them yes yeah but you can only
say one word you can repeat the
same word as needed but no new
words only shame if nobody guesses whoever
guesses it gets two points giver gets
one giver goods won giver gets one
okay i don't get it so you
just have to say one word you
can say as many times as you
want but you can't add any more
words to your ration and you and
you have to sound like the person
you're doing an impression right okay great
with so ah in order to do
this impression do you have to sell
like the person
what are you drawing i'm care i'm
not drawing i'm not sure i know
i don't like to take off
okay okay i'm alright so who's who's
starting whispered conversation crypt moment okay um
i'll start like that secret moment i
picked up the spanking pen
wait which isn't spanking bed i don't
know this is that any pen is
a spanking but that's a secret pen
you use for spanking ben do you
i do you
i agree okay i'm talking about probably
okay chicks so you're gonna do one
word okay a one word impression and
you have to guess good is alright
okay here we go
ah
porn
oh la la ah try trump now
face puller
boy
samantha from sex and the city porn
wait this is a person
born
ah okay why would she be saying
porn is it harvey levin from tmc
you stroking your big dick ah yeah
it's someone who's in who's a porn
star ah boy so many likes care
boy born born born someone who's around
porn a lot
stormy daniels
okay it's a man because he keeps
stroking your cock
four
so you're someone who's around pornstars don't
understand who's around for stairs all the
time i don't know porn dads did
oh charlie sheen slaves are dead huh
you might be by the time this
comes
so john holmes huh
hugh hefner yeah
i guess i was thrown by the
impression more than anything well yeah okay
paul gets two points i get one
oh right write it down alright paul
gets two points you get one
i saw playboy bunny drawn on the
table so to my inspiration yeah okay
should i go now alright here we
go ready
somebody jim carrey
my guys can mind a little tricky
go
alright but
alright alright
poor trump
poor oh my bill maher yes ah
okay now is just the word porn
okay okay alright messy wang could only
say that right so it's lauren has
five paul's three i've won okay let
me think alright huh um
okay it makes it harder it does
make it harder um
okay
pawn
joy bahar pullin joan rivers yeah wow
alright lorna six paul and i have
three it's my turn okay um
paw
porn oh my god
ah who's that guy home
it does seem eerily familiar is it
as long as the singer porn
ah home
in my mind yes oh austin powers
well you didn't well you know i
should have said austin powers was it
really austin it was really awesome power
well that's the character ah lorena six
paula's five four alright paul your turn
okay
so many
this can tie us up if i
get it okay
porn ah what's his name
oh um oh and porn verner herzog
oh that's what i was trying to
think of ford
do the do the body though there's
not much to it okay porn porn
porn bill clinton no
that would be i know and poor
horse that would be cheating if i
didn't
um porn porn is hard by the
way it's a hard hard word we
could switch to somebody so okay switched
to somebody with some yeah because some
like guys taught me yeah say somebody
stopped me i forgot but say somebody
stopped me as this person only be
one worth it but that's ok we
were not going oh is it okay
yeah
we're changing it because no one's gonna
get it hey come let's say somebody
stop me somebody stopped me
i like jimmy carter yes ah tied
us all up okay wait there's still
more time six to six to six
oooh the devil's game
stop there yeah i guess so i'm
very frightened right now like i say
huh alright one more round and we'll
see where we're at alright okay
i'm just gonna say somebody somebody okay
and then i have if i have
to i'll add stopping
somebody grover
seven buddy judy tenuta
ah
samadhi miss piggy yeah ah
it works as religion for everyone with
that voice yeah it was almost a
yoda oh wow okay my turn
okay so man draw the mask but
like but it's yoda's phase doing so
stop me somebody
alright
somebody opportunity yes oh this is good
okay oh this is good oh it's
me
play by the way paul paul you
epcam i mean d k i call
you have ten lorna and i have
seven there's no way for either of
us to win you've won already so
so go ahead and do it and
we'll fight for second lauren and i
will fight for second okay alright just
a fun game it's a fun game
you're gonna say somebody
i'm going to say somebody i have
to pick a voice i have to
pick a pick somebody way someone figure
pick somebody say somebody that's what they
that's the that's what this that's what
this feature should be called pick somebody
say somebody pick somebody say somebody pick
somebody say somebody took a little let's
take somebody say somebody pick somebody say
somebody g
wtf to you
it's tough because i keep thinking of
very easy people yeah give us a
a little bit i'm gonna challenge your
initial ah yeah and then we'll expand
it to somebody stop me if we
can't get it okay
pick somebody say somebody picks somebody up
make somebody say something you prevent this
is to stop being in parentheses
somebody charlton heston somebody are you are
you james spader no okay
show buddy
james vader rbi was some show money
doing ultra yeah yeah sure
it's got a very good james spader
as ultron impression because i just watched
ultron and i had a cold and
i was like oh i can talk
like this but that but only for
that day i think because i can't
do it anymore how about that guy
in the bachelor jason who like as
i haven't watched it yet ok but
his nose needs to be broken i'll
do alone or like dug out or
so anyway
like this like i'll just make up
something he said like somebody's funny
like somebody
oh stop me like tony soprano just
crazy i'm like get in there do
something in there dig it out and
do some excavation alright go ahead okay
so show buddy
say somebody stop me now somebody stop
me
wilford brimley no but close don ameche
what someone in the cocoon cast though
no one from the cocoon of nietzsche
telling me he was telling me to
sean
somebody
so murder somebody shot somebody stop me
so they'll over don't ever get i
can't get it i don't think give
us give us ah ee initials initials
yeah g k
george clinton louis j k
just read it
his parents just chose a different issue
louis e k k george night no
i don't know george the guy from
grey's anatomy ah george george snyder the
basketball cody good here no that doesn't
sound george know greg no
giles
oh grant weirdly closer no ah
giffin giffen
so close so is it is a
ga no jay no but i'm saying
the for the yes is ga ga
ga gavin no gap garland
gao gao galaga delgada no no get
get his g ab no gc no
ga d no g gef no g
g keep going but you know g
h i j k l m n
o p q r r grant gar
we're not going ga ga our gar
gar garlic arfield garfield gar garbage garbage
garbage it was garbage
edge ghar ghar ghar gargoyle gargoyle are
a no yeah c d e f
g h i j k l m
n o p q r s r
garrett garrison keeler yes ah don't just
racist garrison
and keeler disgraced garrison keeler oh lauren
i mean what i out a book
of poetry compiled by him we did
learn you won second place i'm thirty
alright congratulations and graduation to paul congratulations
to all of us oh really good
to come in second i want to
make a speech shoving excuse me
impossible without you you q yeah musically
yeah i'm pleased
that this will be our song for
all speeches i just want to say
no thanks to everyone thank you i
want to say by the way thank
you to everyone about the carrots thing
i want a vacation thank you really
understanding the game we loved playing the
game we love playing the game but
i loved being right about carrots even
more and i also loved coming in
second i feel really cool
oh mind the third because i came
in first when it comes to the
carriage thing to beat up the thumb
dance chevron dance yes dance dance know
like you mean it dancin saying here
to clog dancing singing it's like you're
at a club tidewater somebody stand squats
he's not doing any of the things
he commanded ah i will see you
next time bye yeah
does that count
ugh