so no
your studio somewhere good
i so want to go i'm gonna
share with you now morning
oh huh ty bollinger law my god
i was really relaxing while i was
chilling i napped i woke up i
had breakfast i took a shower you
know we always do about an hour
on the show but if we just
talked really fast we could do it
in twenty minutes oh i know no
one would be mad now they could
see us wearing let's do three i'm
really quick we'll be in our room
okay let me know
zip zip zip zip zip http ppb
epa it's been a while since we've
had a challenge to see how fast
we can say so but it has
let's see how fast we can say
what was that tongue twister from last
time the i beg your pardon
we we were doing our vocal warmups
like yeah fuckin roll those baby blues
oh my god i got these eyedrops
oh my god that are i'm not
gonna name the brand oh thank god
but they're um supposed to whiten the
whites of your eyes i often have
veins in my eyes okay but it's
always been like that so i don't
know so but but i swimming thing
i put him in
so so white never see my eyes
so white my life but my eyes
hurt oh it's like deeply yeah there's
something happening and people don't always have
that reaction but i was like i
guess i can't use you check with
your doctor my daughter could use them
oh what am i supposed to dr
yeah i checked with items um i
but having seen a movie recently oh
wow we went my my lovely wife
and i we went to the cinema
and it's one of those cinemas where
you have a recliner and you can
order food and yeah yeah and the
only serie five hamburgers but if i
ever said tracy
five wines right of a ah it
was very popular film opening weekend and
so the only seats that were left
in this theater if we wanted to
see if that day were in the
front row law but you're reclining that
we're highlighting and so we did it
and then during the trailers i was
thinking this was a mistake yeah but
then we just you just adjust
do it yeah but i did notice
and i don't know if i would
have noticed a difference nose hairs know
yeah yeah i saw just double shot
and skirts yo that was i won't
go back wow
um i noticed everybody's eyes were fucking
bloodshot you saw every red bar so
yeah well these jobs are recommended for
being on camera but again i don't
think i can handle it with the
way it hurts us like a dull
ache like that kinda yeah felt like
my eyes are being pushed
i had a friend i was waiting
for somebody inside our anything the veins
and doing something like what is doing
you know how clothing the closing things
move into your brain space i had
a friend who only wanted to sit
in the front row of a movie
because he's like if i go to
a movie i want to i want
to have it just like you know
as big as plastic as possible yeah
it was wow fucking lunatic
stand at the foot of the screen
your weird dad that the food oh
that's green now sit down i actually
saw a movie on opening weekend as
well and my theater it was a
popular movie and manama yeah at the
cinema and i was really popular we
had tickets a month in advance actually
my friend organized this wow very neat
but we had reclining chairs as well
and i thought never again shall i
go to a theater that doesn't offer
this i know i went to oh
nice i i went to pop to
popular movies that came out on the
same day yeah yeah i barb and
hymer did oh shit
and i um i went i went
to one with ah in the morning
with reclining seats and then that second
one without um oh was it the
longer one no no it was not
thinking okay well yeah that's good but
there were class things that's the right
order i think by the way yeah
i think so and on a somewhat
lighter note but it was somewhat lighter
so
moving up and i'm somewhat messages are
still dark dark messages still dog tuxedo
yeah exactly so things maybe portrayed this
one i liked laying back i'll just
say yeah yeah i'll say my bulk
at this theater we ordered because we
were gonna maybe have dinner afterwards um
i'm at a place nearby that we
really like and it was a game-time
decision you didn't know whether you're going
to have dinner no we had kind
of said and then afterwards we'll go
have dinner can i ask without asking
too many personal details was the theater
in your neighborhood or was this in
a different neighborhood the theater and the
restaurant somewhere you don't typically go it's
both the rest of the restaurant the
thi
we are very near each other in
a neighbourhood that is adjacent to ernie
okay okay and so we will come
to figure out yeah yeah jackie morrison
breakfast all day checkbox you get your
tacos gives you tacos thirty five times
per day
and as you remember i was in
a jack in the box for screaming
because my fast food place no longer
serve breakfast oh that's right that's right
but there's did my favorite thing in
that i think you should leave sketches
thirty or fifty five coffees yeah it's
so good i've drive through coffee um
so
so ah we said we were a
little little hungry even though you could
order a full meal there were like
let's just get some popcorn with a
small puddle because i sorta don't like
eating a full meal in the dark
during a movie and then given being
given a bill at the end
you know i kinda like it now
because you can't see anything well yeah
a little bit just like i'm sitting
here trying to cut a salad or
some boy like you you try to
get a salad yeah the the goal
chicken pieces i'm trying to scoop some
soup yeah always get there a little
early have it all done by the
end of previews
okay well that's a goal i've ever
achieved so i don't think they'd drop
you a bill like madam but they
did yeah yeah we're gonna get in
there like here you have alamo they
they know all the dna and yeah
don't talk to you i went to
a different one right right where it's
all on the app yes so you
don't have but it's like you're in
the dark you're handing a fuckin card
you're doing the whole i'm like that's
not what i'm saying to one
where i did you didn't have to
do that dear hey i'm really happy
for you i'm having my complaining saying
wow
we all got slapped um what but
the popcorn i guess because it's like
hey you're in recliner we're gonna make
it a little different than bringing you
in a bowl like you would have
at home oh now that's a metal
bowl that i like but for a
small it was way too much popcorn
wait you change get your on it
was too much yeah and then we
didn't go to ihop corn can really
make you feel paul have you eaten
said yeah no i mean don't go
to dinner no no that's fucked up
i've been back to my home wow
you've just been wandering the street yes
do you ah do you know the
guys i'm eager to see what people
think of being really don't this is
from that like noisy call it's wrong
because god i like
na da da da da what's wrong
is that spring awakening ah frigging away
i just watched a documentary on a
few months ago oh yeah i've i
have that saved in my guide i
didn't know anything about it so i
enjoyed it but i mean leverage in
high school he's like be upset we're
actually seeing the thing so i was
like i watched the documentary but i
think so but i was like um
i think we kind of when am
i ever going
to see this exactly see she was
oh when i saw that the noted
musical sweeney todd the demon barber of
fleet street recently because it's one of
the i had not experiences before where
there were people in a musical that
were famous from another thing and sort
of tracks a different kind of crowd
yeah so people are like cheering for
shit that
normally you would not cheer for the
museu because it's got was named joshua
ball and it's also got a little
boy named josh groban yeah haha yeah
ayton getting mad matter so anyway a
little bit and get mortal shallow adolesc
goodness wrote a shallow a good roll
so he's a singer yeah yeah he
does yeah he he quits himself very
nice amazing i guess he was a
theater kid all these kids with their
believe this actor is a theater
how did that happen
hey but yeah so they're all like
i didn't know if they were all
plucked from you know standard things that
are plucked from obscurity with no background
in the light from dumb shit school
because they were so little there was
so little it was surely oh surely
another so they were born just for
the show i know the show that
was what we were planning to show
we need to get ready with the
strangest thing of all really i have
a cute kid too
yeah please make em que and please
give them a weird name like finn
wolfhard in wolf ah but they would
cheer for the end of a number
like they were at a concert ugh
this i mean as far as that
goes it wasn't as intrusive or annoying
but it was weird when i saw
sing or no six
the setting you saw seven when i
was sixteen when sting sing seven when
you saw sing the james corden pig
no i did not when i saw
six they were cheering like it was
a rock concert and i figured out
was it was because everyone had the
soundtrack yeah i saw six and had
the same experience to the point where
they
were little girls dancing in the aisles
at the end it was so cute
that it's like little nine year olds
oh my god mentioned last year last
week asteroid city the three little girls
in the movie are so fucking oh
they're not in it as much as
i would like they were right or
let's just follow them yeah
yeah home but after the movie who
little ghoul did you danny
the last is he the last adult
man to refer to a woman as
little girl and saw who neil young
yeah i get it bucket did it
i had to burn mice you've already
been baby
pebbles baby
oh every pills movie is good
what do you think the last song
to mention that a girl is seventeen
you go i think sick genre i
heard one the other day it was
really happening for a while there oh
for a long while for a long
while it was was it goes she's
only seventeen
seventy it's like sandra own a winger
it's winner debra was like nineteen eighty
eight eighty nine that was ever around
the last swing never wing or that
would be she should have collaborated she
did she ever meet winger she should
have i'm sure they had a coffee
do you think they're related because the
guy's name is kip winger yeah probably
yeah they probably had a kipper and
we talked about how mike
michael keaton yeah he's his last name
to keaton because he liked diane keaton
and because his real name is michael
douglas right oh but then you're meeting
me yourself have another name of someone
famous but zach was lily sullivan jim
masha michael keane
michael r keaton yeah lily michael keaton
michael beak eating these michael moore referencing
lily sullivan's solo show which is very
funny and if you get a chance
to so funny i'll quit while i'm
behind do we know is she doing
it for like she's just came back
and saw with it but as is
is there like they're trying to do
something for an awesome things
i don't know which oscar i was
talking about though because i'm noticing i
feel like well i guess i know
a handful people who are at edinburgh
this year and like maybe that's a
goal with the solo thing right all
right but that it feels like it
already well she just started doing it
though right
interesting interesting i'd like to do a
solo show yeah you should i don't
should i say not as i want
to do like a character thing yeah
i think yeah wheels yes both at
the same time can you do it
please and you can do it ideal
for nine hundred dollars only i will
tell you off mic about an idea
that i've
had for a long time now and
love to hear yeah
sorry listeners little piss piglets but you
don't get to hear about his piglets
that's right if you have kids there
pepto pink piglets no matter if they've
heard it or not doesn't match right
now it's just right generational trauma oh
alt trauma trauma also generation as well
if you have listened to this show
even once
your pacific yeah it's alright if you've
seen a post we've made about it
near postpone if you've ever walked past
a room where the podcast is playing
your rep is big it's not even
you might be no you are yeah
what are old picks called because we
have piglets for young pigs older aesthetic
a word for an
old people called senior citizens yeah elderly
and your pigs senior pigs you guys
it was right there so early if
you have listened to hell once your
parents are senior pigs
yeah they're dead they're former picks yeah
yeah i've heard today for pigs yep
that's nice have you listened to those
much it's so nice they're so supportive
now
ah supporting the earth are they buried
below are they buried by the way
they're both buried my dad as i
said was cremated and then buried he
was like i'm done you ever visit
their graves know alright that seems i
i never understood that yeah i never
understood that hey it's a place to
reflect
i mean i was it's so funny
anytime you see in a movie and
someone's doing a big monologue yeah talking
to the person it's like you can
do that well yeah we're right you
don't have to make a trip that
i did that in my stand-up oh
yes yes what was it in you
should have told me was the exact
same thing it's like you go visit
a grave and it's like what are
you talk
about like well the dry cleaners around
it again right everything you all as
ideally they can hear you from wherever
you are yeah yeah do you think
though well you know i think it's
nice to spruce up a gravestone i
like that i like that put a
flower on there just calamity hood or
rock for the jewish folk rock rock
rock rock poodle rock i thought
ah i think i'm a cremated guy
yeah we didn't get to that last
time good to know um alright moving
huh
ah could you tell her for me
up dope badoo badoo dupe dupe because
you when you pass i'll call her
and say first thing you want to
be first thing first
for food yes also very sorry for
your loss but scouting
favors or decorations
wait so what do you want to
have your what do you want to
have you want to be you have
your remains buried i would like to
have ah ah mark ah a plaque
of some sort like that can be
seen what about you scott ackerman by
the way welcome with freedom and paul
hi i'm scott i'm lauren and we
talk about how we're going to be
dealt with after we're dead
ah i don't know here's how i
want you to deal with me i
think it is fair i think it's
fair for the people i leave behind
to decide what they want the whole
situation is probably what they're gonna do
whatever the fuck they want anyway i
know it happens so much where somebody
has like a last wish or the
like an instruction or whatever
then they're like yeah what we're not
gonna do this yeah yeah i mean
that interesting i feel like you should
tell yona yeah i feel like you
should honor it too i just think
people what the hell i don't run
roughshod over those requests all the time
right yeah have you registered everything with
your lawyers and all that of like
your will oh yeah but that's such
a that was a weird day yeah
we may
made it light we made jokes of
course we didn't make any news we
no joke no joke in fact you've
got even more syria we got extremely
sorry you are in tears yeah screaming
screaming and renting garments yeah yeah rending
ren ren thinks reading but i like
the idea i rented contracting renting the
way yeah
just update your will i am waiting
for that i had the box delivered
here
um yeah i janie does rent the
runway yeah and i think it's great
i tried it with those because they
do it there's like a version dude
version yeah yeah it's not the same
thing while i was doing newly for
a long time and by the way
if newly ever wants to spawn to
this podcast i would love to do
personal experience
yeah where were you what were you
getting i was doing a lot especially
ah once i realised it was an
option postpartum because my body was changing
i was like i don't keep buying
clothing more beauty your money your mom
had to talk with you yeah body's
going to yeah i know i got
my first period um and i was
getting all sorts of different pants and
shirts and
things dresses and also just things that
are kind of flashy that you don't
really want to wear more than once
but it's fun for a picture and
event and i was i loved it
i just paused it right now but
i'm i'm i'll go back yeah i
also rented a coat for a wedding
that just like looked cool and it's
like the night were turned it's like
that's fun yeah i think it's great
yeah i think it's harder with men's
clothing
yeah i think what we got we
got shirt we got pants we've got
shirt pant jacket jacket there's not as
much like that's all there is fun
to have honestly but it's also the
sizing yeah slightly specific yes because you
can you can wear a dress that
maybe the length would not make that
much of the brains an intro to
write but with your sleeve rice it
doesn't
yeah you'll feel like identive big oh
my god the end of big were
like i'm a boy again but i
had sex with a full grown lady
yeah i mean i know she's haunted
by that forever i can't get past
it well i get past that because
that's my favorite film o k noted
i separates the facts from the fiction
can
what film big big rye i'm saying
the facts being she had sex with
a child the thick shiny yeah no
she didn't it was magic yeah but
it was hot it was magic he
was a grown man at the time
yeah and called it's called making a
wish paul hey i like wishes hey
what would you wish for
if you had just one wish just
one wish yeah
cheeseburger oh my god more moisture like
up but if i had one wish
could i make it something kind of
like blanket like i'll be like i
want everyone in my everyone in my
family to have anything they need for
the rest of life
including myself now like or like okay
everyone i'm feeling it's a mansion one
ah eat these get their all happy
specific then they your mom and dad
everyone oh fuck
okay if you and mike could live
in separate mansions that were right next
door to each other would you do
that ah we've spent a lot of
time in each mansion whatever it was
to to start to hang out to
separate mentally and as you mentioned and
yeah do different stuff like separate mansions
but there was a bedroom connecting the
two yeah i figured you know there's
actually there is a house it there's
a house
bean connection because i'm sure there's two
homes connected by a bridge and you
write and it's like you could have
had a skyway yeah yeah plus you'd
take the sky always a great song
e little zui zui video like any
other play it's great so great to
watch the match i would like to
hear it with an ad like a
ten second ad before it
yardstick alright we have to take a
break okay
and we're back we're back yeah we're
but warwick war biggest here or because
here hey warburg daddy warwick daddy warwick
what
well this is the peril of being
on your phone during hey oh okay
oh my out i just saw something
and sad to say something i had
to do any warm-up something say something
daddy were book from little orphan am
more bucks
we never met i know something happened
i didn't understand and that's why i
kept up to i didn't tell jamie
stop calling me out for yawning on
her i did hear that oh really
she's like do you want a coke
and then just let it go no
i don't want to live and then
she's like because you're yawning and then
you're like why are you so they
don't need to know
stop talking and if we were yawning
constantly whenever we weren't talking all weird
we never stopped talking i was doing
a live show recently in someone on
stage kept yawning and no one was
calling out and economic
someone's gotta say some and i didn't
know the person well enough it was
like an improv show it was ah
not an improv show is more like
a boring play i don't know it
wasn't it wasn't improv but it was
like a thing where it was like
panelists yeah and i was like oh
so keeps going i'm like can we
say something
it's funny we see something yeah um
i there was a show that i
did ah a lot where it was
an improv show and um during the
the downtime when i wasn't i thought
that coaster was cookie the one you
own
great chime in i shut up i
thought that coaster was
shop thompson yeah i thought you had
a bear cookie on the table over
there and i was like what is
bare naked cookies i love that band
it's been one cookie ahead those i
was when i was on when i
was in the back i would be
laughing at stuff that was happening yeah
and then over the course of the
show that would that triggered like a
yawn response in me you laughing made
you yawn because i was laughing a
lot getting a lot of air and
then eventually yes
yeah and i was like you can't
yawn on stage right nevertheless shows we
really know it's really hard when you're
fighting to not yawn the bang bang
in portland we fell asleep string that
island rose portland left lauren terrifying verify
yeah diner die oh my god do
the early shows up for oh my
god i remember you live for your
own age yeah it's a pretty big
say it was but i
didn't get it yeah yeah yeah but
worth it you left for your edition
and then pull and i did the
rest of the show and start falling
asleep during it was so scary so
like while paul would be talking i
would be nodding off sleeping yeah my
god because i was so lazy or
some wire shelves run around yeah so
isn't that the one where we did
andrew lloyd webber's like coronation i think
i do
thing just so we could get on
our feet and like i might have
been like yeah but i don't remember
i don't remember but if that were
like then tim came out and it
was like oh tim came up for
that he has to keep us do
can we ask the audience if we
did a threesome live with they attend
or watch live stream or no we
don't know yet we can't ask can't
do that i won't ask them i
would
all right out i wouldn't take it
off you can ask them questions okay
i'm not going to ask you guys
i yeah yeah because i'm afraid of
the answer i'm afraid too so i'll
just leave it there hey hanging like
a chai you've hanging like a child
yeah you're like yeah hey you like
a chair rocky lego book guitar
da da da da i think i
was doing living on the edge i
don't know that i was driving on
the a o smith yeah aerosmith and
you were doing
tell it to my haw tell me
only one album ah just ah chad
chad chad hanging hanging chad
that is why
deze does disco disco jazz no that's
michael jackson's bad oh sure because art
bad who who really really bad that's
what the backup singer is saying bad
bad really really bad when i heard
that for the first time i could
not believe are you kidding me yeah
they're that bad really really bad really
really bad oh my guy that yeah
it's so bad it's genius it's so
bad it's bad badly really bad oh
weird al should do um you sure
do a parody of bad yeah okay
so i think so but i'm afraid
to tell him i know because it's
kind of like i'm afraid you're too
late
yeah what if he if he did
it today what would it be i
think should be because i'm dad your
dad you know it and then your
dad joint do like norm core yes
dad jokes father's day yeah yeah things
up dad bob's dad bought and you
wonder why making these jokes because i'm
dad yeah yeah let's let's call
come get them on the whole people
and a little high weird oh yeah
i'm using my regular voice oh okay
honey was on the phone oh it's
i think it's got up i yelled
oh i'm not here oh my wife's
not here i was not calling for
her good make sure he knows i'm
not here oh she's really not
here okay i had no interest in
talking to her like she had no
interest talking to you i call your
cell phone i know you did why
would i just why you called me
is lacking from here is your wife
there he's up i'm gonna re release
for the mastery to really quietly so
hell he won't know that i'm here
okay okay talk to molly's is your
wife
find out what he was she's not
i got to talk to her my
daddy's bag some place else he's so
crazy you can hear him yes i
can hear you you're talking i can
hear you okay no no i'm talking
to ah the wall oh painting on
the wall that's a face on it
so i'm talking oh okay are the
eyes moving yeah i've worked with someone
living in your walls
ooh bad rodwell
but she did anyway speaking bad
yeah the michael jackson oh yeah can
you do a parody ooh again ah
where it's dad though and it's all
about dojo because it's now yeah i
mean i'll give it a shot okay
let's hear it because i'm dead yeah
dad you know it really really daddy
do it yeah you did it what
were you doing just now i've done
in the backups i assumed because that's
what they'd say yes really really dad
she is here oh no you picked
up my cell phone extension hi i
just sold that song to mgm studios
making a film based on it based
on something better
so so i that exciting scott book
i'd need to talk to you what
are you pregnant again i'll hang up
through pregnant again i'm pregnant okay it's
a total turn your salary yeah you
know it you know if anything junior
who
oh got him pregnant really really pretty
um it was artificially artificial and so
i who though danny devito uses own
sperm actually watched that video and watch
that movie right before giving birth to
hollywood did you put on my random
pray we should prepare yeah we should
do a scholar and seeing know have
you not seen junior desperate
i'm thirsty forty he's thirsty for that
junior squeeze
he's sitting here with three guys with
weights it's pretty much baby he's supposed
for that junior squeeze for development
we should make a movie where a
hipster docs like it's films like why
they kind of did that with um
things to do in denver where you
when you're dead but we should do
the same it's just i've never seen
that i have any artists or an
smc wow
i haven't seen it i haven't seen
i don't think i will
kind of like i said i was
gonna say something really stupid i wish
there was a channel that just played
good movies all the time but then
i was like well wait i guess
i have all the streamers hbo have
whatever so i'm like i'd be spooked
me feel like i actually need on
hbo you could just put them on
random but i would like to i
would like to feel my favorite
thing i love to just put i'm
sure what they have i was surprised
me say shit typing like no guys
were just like oh yeah yeah like
trust you netflix yeah my pandemic goal
at the beginning was like i'm gonna
only watch like really good movies university
and i put i watched eyes wide
shot i never watched anything else so
it took your your sales it was
a good movie i was like i'm
interested but then i thought i should
watch all these other movies and i
just didn't do it yeah and so
now i'm like i like what i'm
too many batman to watch yeah that's
coming up there is a an app
called canopy which is essentially like the
library's app for movies or whatever it's
like oh free movies and ah there's
a lot of good and interesting choi
choices on there we have added so
many things to this list and that's
all we do is just add things
to the list yeah we never ever
tracked yeah never yeah yeah it's hard
and then so light long enough where
they go away like they're taking off
like oh i guess we'll never see
them guess can be taken away
that's what we say returning yeah i
guess i guess kennedy took it away
what a shit it could have would
have should have
hi i'm ross perot i could have
good guys
they didn't they bring that back ah
to what what's my line was the
one where three people would pretend to
be the the same person yeah oh
yeah woo yeah i were to tell
if someone was pretending they were rosberg
to tell the truth is it to
tell what's what's my line tell it
to my true db i'm looking through
dr ruth
can't wait to hire ruth hello widow
r i p to doctor ruth one
of the original piss pigs she and
clara peller were having a was dr
rosa yeah
she was like very buyout sue johanson
for the canadian doctor ruth sugo sugo
she's a rabid dog yeah she was
a canadian doctor ruth so she said
like sexed up and said a after
yep you put the pianist of agena
a her sex advice stories to smother
me with gravy and curds
are you looking at what to tell
the truth is yeah maybe a celebrity
panel questions contestants in an attempt to
determine the actual person associated with a
story yeah right say that so all
three come out and pretend to be
that person right now let's see what
the fuck a little baby up the
window
yeah oh shit the walk closer to
it now just because i'm just a
little away some the lawn oh she's
on the grassy knoll
hi i'm j f k junior
you know i'm j f k junior
oh what's my line people blindfolded so
there's a famous person and they try
to guess who the famous person oh
god it's and the famous person's like
hi i'm carrie gray they keep their
answers vary yeah brief say choice mason
rowley oh and then the people are
going like
us actor dear yeah what i've heard
of you what have i seen you
in yeah so but you were thinking
of the former right why did this
all kind of fucking gnome and look
look look look look look look look
look look look look look look like
if you could be any animal what
would you okay i have a question
too okay
if i can be a animal yeah
fine i guess
a lion or i mean my favorite
animals graph would you would that be
fun i don't know if i want
toto would be fun but this is
not relaxing things i feel like you're
enjoying themselves yeah but yet they'd have
to say something you're sad over and
just go for yourself out i feel
like maybe i would like to be
i think a lion were pretty cool
male i guess i'd like to be
so maybe you want that lion dick
like something big balls in pennies
you want to be aligned with big
ball so big balls and tennis maybe
a dolphin yeah well that's that sound
so before you because you could yeah
i'd like to be a whale and
i'd like to but i'm against the
law the water yeah you could just
consume like fucking crazy you can be
put into a hotel pool people are
and given more rides people are excited
to see you yeah they're like oh
look at that oh
oh
oh that's every choice huge oh that's
awesome there's more do you want to
be scott wish the wish granter is
coming soon oh the wish granter excuse
roger eve decide um i mean the
wish granter me wants to be something
with opposable thumbs me wants to be
something with opposable thumbs he wants to
be
something with a fucking monkey yeah maybe
a monkey although the raccoon dirty girl
monkeys animals are disgusting hey it was
your question i know i don't want
to be once zebra
why zebra because it's cool you want
a horse
i don't know all the students are
fine i gotta take holiday to the
zoo soon yeah you do yeah you
want to be summing up on that
that time of the month tiny zoo
like you have your period yeah you
want to make the monkeys go crazy
yeah i wanna make this money queasy
yards and yards ago a friend of
mine moved to town he had a
little son who was like a little
toddler
only a little bit older because he
could he could talk therapies um and
i said hey want to take you
guys to the zoo and my firm
is like yeah sure and so we
went to the zoo and the little
boy could not have been less interested
wow anything that was going gets tough
one point we were looking at elephants
and this little child punched me
in the balls to get my attention
oh and then said paul look at
these ants
oh my fuck is getting personal i
found out afterwards that they had just
been to the zoo like a couple
weeks before oh why did you die
only yeah you gotta space it out
keep it in yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah punching the ball should be reserved
for like hey there's a train coming
right at us i i hope no
one does that if there's a train
bearing down on us you don't want
to get
much of the i don't wanna get
punched in a bowl be like oh
my boy here and then you just
like fall to your knees and the
trademarks you over wouldn't be great if
like in the movies you got hit
in the balls you can just get
right up keep do whatever you're doing
yeah or just for once i get
to go oh and then you're back
in action anyway yeah just really take
you out for a long time now
i mean like not good
i i yeah i mean i definitely
think it would be good occasionally if
like someone really goes at it hello
guys
goes at them you know like like
especially when you're young someone will be
yeah boosh right yeah but if like
someone just accidentally swats you or whatever
it's usually like wow okay yeah as
i was saying i mean it it
can linger it's like it's like your
funny bone like that pow yeah because
your dick's the funniest bone you got
yeah it's pretty funny i mean women
laugh at it when i take it
women
alright we have to take break
and we're back well and you know
what it is it's time for three
for three if you would like to
send us a three cheer a little
game we can play write to us
at three am usa gmail dot com
so this is um this is one
and it doesn't even say who submitted
this but maybe we've played it before
i don't know if think it's from
matt producer
you could be from a google goes
oh fuck
fuck i saw ghost freaking y'all fucking
freak this is called fifa for five
second rule okay i was submitted by
tamer okay thanks tamer
and tamir it's t a m e
r okay no accent mark is it
l period tamer
lion lion tamer oh sorry
just tamer i don't know but it
could be tam tam tam know libby
many things that were maybe it could
be anything who knows um so the
object is to name three things in
five seconds player one comes up with
a question like name three famous jennifer's
player two sorry i thought your phone
was a cook oh no
no we'd shut up i thought you
guys were both cookies
and they're a bear cookie no human
you guys both bear cookies and shove
about your bear cookie shovel her your
shows her burning surely there could be
some kind of ten da shocker hi
i'm ross perot sure to have caught
everyone here
i love your cookie
however i thought your cooking because i
should have would have could have eat
you
goodbye forever chap reckoning back to the
great because he saw he's dead right
is that the bachelor great never forget
when a little girl played him on
all that really and a little girl
play howard any little girl know who
ross perot was i even watched it
and we all didn't know and we
all thought it was great yeah yeah
okay um so
the first person goes name three famous
jennifer's then the person we go clockwise
i guess has five seconds to answer
if they succeed they get a point
if they fail then the next person
gets a chance to answer the same
question but they can't reuse any of
the previous person's answers okay
so it's always jennifer's zone
look at me yes
jennifer's um just any category jennifer just
three changes it's not even people it's
got three things okay i like it
yeah okay renae wings so who decides
the category so the person ah player
one does and then ah then i
think we just go around sue decided
category if named three of
that thing through that thing and then
if if they can do it in
five seconds great and if not it's
not the next person yes i can
do it five seconds great they get
a point if not we don't care
yeah okay okay so i'm gonna start
and i'm gonna go to paul we're
going to go clockwise okay and um
i'm gonna count it down in my
head i'm not gonna do it
to you that's fair okay alright so
name three pieces of furniture ah couch
table chair got it lauren name three
types of egg
ostrich chicken sparrow
okay that was close down to why
i don't even know what you meant
i gonna say fry i realized yeah
yeah yeah i was right when i
was ready to actually i was gonna
say brown and then i didn't think
that would have accepted okay okay let's
type of bag okay name three allison's
alison mackey allison
ah al qaeda all i can think
of is someone i used to date
and don't say her name doesn't work
okay i don't get a point okay
no you sure don't alison mackey though
that's awesome mac i think she's like
the girl from nexium yeah yeah that's
why he's trying to think yeah yes
just recently out of prison ms ah
that's it that's what i used today
okay and yeah you branded yeah yeah
oh yeah um name three parts of
the boat
ah stern bow ho nice okay lauren
named three ai colors blue green brown
rice scott named three candies that have
chocolate in them reese's peanut butter cups
tootsie roll hershey's kisses wow
zero so you know that's a risky
choice because it is chocolate but it's
more likely chocolate yeah it's more of
a crayon
oh yes yeah hi name three internet
browsers
oh god oh god coffee is he
stalling for time stoller time wow that's
a day to help them spit right
three internet browsers safari chrome firefox nice
yeah you did it enforced like unbelievably
he did it although we have thought
about yeah awesome show
hello
firefox
okay take a lot of visitors to
the mozilla's
alright lauren name three types of zoo
animals zebra giraffe elephant wow just a
deja vu we've done this oh no
wait no you went to the zoo
asia zoom even someone got mad at
her why she told this story or
cool opted oh wait someone we know
told a story on
i remember this and maybe i even
brought it up on this podcast how
someone got mad at them because they
did it they didn't do it fascinated
it wrong or think little sound familiar
to look into this okay yeah we'll
get our people someone will tell me
um okay what's the category i'm giving
you yeah is um name three three
e
things you find under your sink in
the kitchen ah draino plastic bags the
dishwasher things that you put into the
dishwasher those little yeah me
i'm giving my ah you thought you
had it then you just kept talk
yeah but yeah talk yourself out of
it oh i mean i got my
point okay okay hi paul tide pods
i want to eat the dishwasher pods
name three prime numbers ah one three
nine
nine no i don't know what prem
nine is not as done as nine
seven so yes this one i almost
seven yeah i don't remember what prime
numbers are they can't be divided visible
yeah
cares with for truth and liberty just
i don't get a point actually you
do not see i guess
you get three i guess is not
prime is it no three is yeah
is it yeah one five seven one
three five seven eleven thirteen seventeen oh
boy
three
i hate math amazon prime day paul
it's your turn to give lauren a
category lauren name three fabrics for socks
cashmere wool cotton retailing cashmere i don't
have an interesting like the idea
sweaty little feet and this is what
comfortable right yeah but they make them
truly do i remember being in aspen
colorado when they used to do the
batsman comedy fest and there was the
stores they're insane right and there was
a store that was selling cashmere sheets
that's an likes what do you how
do you clean nose that's what happens
when you shit on them but
what are your dust mites take over
very valid question yeah alright scott named
three brands of headphones bose beats by
dray
and i don't know those are the
only tangible their poe yeah ap also
makes it over the year i have
to forget why i liked them on
air mat over the shoulder boulder holder
by apple yeah those big headphones hold
today
pie apple pie apple by tyco of
course it's like a white visuals
tyco was a toy company and that's
how they would end their commercials oh
like for slot cars or whatever the
announcer would say by tyco of course
wow of course like he thought it
was something else who else could come
up with something so great are gonna
hurt you kid but slot cars a
toy you could use for half an
hour and wounded forever yep slot cars
paul three
quentin tarantino films the hateful eight ah
pulp fiction ah grindhouse la cl spin
note i get i get it you
didn't get it sorry you gotta be
hard on the rolls because otherwise no
one's gonna win i know it wasn't
even tired it's like a titan dishwasher
put that in by the way greenhouse
technically is not a man he was
anyway good death movie called yeah but
he he directed death proof in grindhouse
right but it was a movie i
don't know called grindhouse and he was
one of the director's ladies ladies so
i think it's clearly easier both beautiful
people's republic
all pretty alright good lord with lorin
name three lakes lake michigan lake erie
lake huron
put superior in their interesting yeah sometimes
i don't think i ask people this
a lot and i always think it's
interesting what they're like choices yeah yeah
bell
well you could've i could've we all
can we couldn't have should have would
have hi i'm rob rowe ah scott
yep say so is saying three say
you love me three robin williams character
names ah jeannie
jack ah mister good morning vietnam
you said i cable you get to
mister say most of this is down
yeah yeah yeah i don't know
hi mihai oh yes you um
name three school subjects math history a
spelling
harder than i know spelling isn't really
a main one
it is for a time yeah they're
great depth yeah okay gimme gimme gimme
gimme gimme gimme gimme some more
ah name three famous colleges yale harvard
tuffs
it's famous people know about it
yeah i mean people have heard of
people for name three cities in australia
melbourne ah sydney and perth yeah you
gotta see birth he too because we've
all been there yep we all went
there they didn't have to that was
fine no one was forcing us
dad i'm glad we actually said i'm
sorry pandemic yeah so we are that
aura frame you know yeah and when
pictures come up from that i think
the special time oh i know they're
not sponsoring is still but i think
that warframe is literally the invention that
gives us the most joy i have
honest and my family they're not answering
us anymore no
but i today but they gave us
a bunch of frames and gave one
to my mom and i have one
at my house and we both love
them yeah we won the game of
love comment on the things that pop
up all day every yeah yeah and
my whole family loves them we do
that too it really is enjoyed on
it if they want to give us
ads going to be great and say
it's a good gift yeah really like
yeah it is one of the
my favorite things yeah especially yeah i
feel like if you're looking for gift
for somewhere you can't figure out what
to get yeah yeah yeah it seems
like a thing you'd be like yeah
racial frame but essentially better it's amazing
ones i've apt all memes yes yeah
yes all right anyway alright always meet
to you yeah hi okay um name
three file
sharing services
dropbox reach ribs for good
oh wow you did it
yeah
lauren
name three defunct social media platforms my
space tumblr
friendster
does a tumbler still out there tomboy
it's okay to fund it's bringing defunct
hits bringing the fruity pebble i think
it's denoise for sure i don't know
if it's dry i also know sounds
i don't even i don't need you
anymore well you don't need it because
you're i don't want my point because
i want them to all be really
okay okay scott name three
three um
things you see in the dark
nothing nothing nothing you don't see anything
in the dark just mean slowing eyes
okay the moon stars and street lamps
hi guys a pout about it
alright paul name
three first and last name members of
en sync cool justin timberlake j c
shazam
joey fat one
yeah you got it i honestly i
can never keep straight who instinct in
that actually well who are the members
of backstreet boys no idea what's your
card number the party starter yeah nick
carter oh erin oh that's right yeah
got yeah who has passed away of
course yes oh i didn't know that
nick carter what about deron carter the
party starter don't ok
a term
i go to paul to lauren oakes
um lauren and this is our last
one okay no it's not we can
go for a little okay
name three condiments ketchup mustard mayonnaise
okay okay let's add a layer oh
boy yeah scott
name i don't think i need a
layer no no go ahead doing a
ray romano voice name three eighty sitcoms
oh who's the boss all full house
ray romano
oh da bra
oh valerie is family that because a
child and i'm emily how many times
it took over there was an intermediary
one that you missed val gallery it
was valerie than it was the hogan
family i know we were dating that
we were told there was something in
them that i think there is i
think that person was kidding around i
think i'm kidding around and there's nothing
the hogan family originally called valerie and
then later valley's family the hogans weighed
what that was the last name
yeah it was a win for the
hogans to value family the ho went
valerie
valerie is family the hogans the hogan
family valerie see family the hogans does
not roll off the tongue and allowed
to watch valley's family the hogans yeah
kidd valley family the whole game zone
ah alright yeah i like to layer
yeah add a layer three stars of
valerie family the hogans and with what
layer with the layer of imperial tools
voices sandy duncan's
justin bateman jason bateman the ghost of
valerie
okay yes she haunted the show as
we all know the blanks point fully
points
lauren
you to name
three bridges in the oldest lady voice
you can imagine the golden gate bridge
the brook and bray hedge manhattan branch
she was about to die yeah got
her last words were three bridges ah
that's where all my bones are buried
i mean gold
okay that's terrible my boats was not
interested in going oh please find my
very bones in the style of jack
johnson name
um three types of trees making banana
pancakes oak elm pine making banana think
that's his weirdest song making banana pain
i can't even a single song of
his bubbly toes like i've ever who
were not really yeah yeah bubbly toes
he's a guy who has an answer
go to jail yes so little to
to sing about that he has to
sing about making banana pancakes now maybe
bubbly toes this doesn't make me want
banana pancakes china does should we chastise
banana pancakes banana pancakes bubba lee took
a look at jack johnson boba jack
just bubbly he's probably yeah
yeah probably toes yeah it's a sample
of something that nobody knows that our
eyes are as big as her bubbly
toes on the feet of a queen
of the hundreds of years an ad
for their all covered with tar balls
and after the mega to first to
just make an ad for would make
to make two
hey jack
can't you see that it's just this
has been out of pancakes no okay
no need to go outside why is
this heaven i don't know
i want to hear him singing speaking
speaking of the meg two we saw
a commercial for some muddy ones
ah so there's some jason state the
movie meg too yeah is that the
big toe yeah it looks nice talk
about the big thing the mega may
megatron megatron oh no it might be
for the expendables four know he's a
giant truck okay it's mic too but
the shark is so giant that it's
like yeah why would the sharpie
bothering with any of these things yeah
yeah sure mean it's like yeah if
you saw a peanut on the floor
would you be like wow that was
dumb
wow good huh
yeah okay okay look lauren once yeah
yeah it feels good it feels good
to win your food if everything that
was hoping oh it's all fruity pebbles
maybe um guys that was it she
gets shirts that say it's all fruity
pebbles maybe your free free pebbles baby
yeah who's the fruity pebbles mass
scott flintstones they are for having that
ever happened flintstone they had a charlie
pebbles on the show soon that makes
sense and they're like we gotta get
in which was co-published tab i do
day when you look this up a
dabba doo day will have okay have
a definite oh we have to do
to
time will have a due time we'll
have a gale toe wow
huh
so and oh well my hits the
back of the dinosaurs crackhead some more
um okay look if you wanna write
to us treating those eight g ml
dot com if you wanna call us
hag claims eight if you'd like to
hear ad-free versions of this go to
cbb world dot com come see my
show august fourth dynasty typewriter if it's
not i don't think it's august fourth
yet and um if it
is you can watch the livestream on
video vault and dynasty typewriter dot com
ie i think it's yeah it's if
it's has i think i'd be this
tomorrow com um come see me and
nicole parker at lodge room in highland
park were doing a variety show called
something for everyone just the two of
them with a full band um and
then also ah it's a bubba bubba
bell house um in october um one
show sold out already it's the fourteenth
and fifteenth i think um the fourteen
sold out still tickets for the fifteenth
um bell house in brooklyn my favorite
venue in america please come out and
see us go to paul f tompkins
dot com slash live and i'm at
dynasty typewriter
her with sprague the whisper august nineteenth
doing a live podcast recording and rowdy
screening of mamma mia here we go
again we're gonna watch a movie we're
gonna do a podcast we're gonna sing
along going to be great sounds so
fun sounds so fun we'll see you
there and we'll see you at all
three of those because the three of
us will be at
hell yeah don't worry don't bother me
too much i'm going to be too
busy burning
have you seen me in hell please
just like respect my privacy
bye-bye right
yeah
ugh