three
yeah
me yeah and that's what our theme
song sounds like if you're new here
and we shout along to it we
don't have to but we do jews
kind of thing there's already shouting on
the theme song but we shout over
it
why do we do that by the
way i
you can't ask these questions years in
something because our energy up yeah yeah
i don't think real present centers us
yeah i feel pumped because otherwise something
about whatever i want to think about
i think about sharing i'm thinking so
santa sam thing i think about center
sam thing
stuck in my neighborhood weirdo no one's
really named santa no i know you
would think such a popular guy santa
claus yet no one names their kid
racers my son santa claus santa yeah
people love him he has a great
reputation yeah things never he's known negative
connotation and people named their children jesus
right yeah
so anyway yeah cause come on people
um hi everyone welcome to three adam
let's introduce ourselves right idea scott um
what about you to my right who
are you my name is lauren yourself
yes um and i'm sitting here with
someone to my right yes who are
you though oh i'm an actor and
i'm comedian and
you know we've been doing this podcast
for six years i think this is
our sixth jesus christ as a long
time um and ah yeah i mean
do i'm going to give my credits
yeah every single one
start at the beginning high school place
you can find me on db and
you will be able to learn all
about it and um high school plays
i didn't get into any of them
i've talked about this on the show
that's right by the way this is
number three dems talking about things we've
talked about on the show but yeah
rural part of the yeah all right
and who is that who just said
that hi there my name is paul
f tompkins my home's website is i
m d db dot com
i homepage when you go open your
computer i played the barkeep in oliver
twist in my freshman year than i
played pawnee bill in annie get your
gun my sophomore and which one did
the teacher kissed the student well that
was how specific your eyes i essayed
the role of luther gillis
luther then watched my italian teacher kiss
of contemporary of my that's so she
was a contemporary yes we she was
in my class and years years later
i still think about it now you
don't understand why that was lapsed she
does too you can't even say it
was a different time he was still
a man she was still a child
yeah
yeah my name is scott ackerman and
let's see ah carousel in the ninth
grade i played the star keeper i
was ah jigger that's right ah who's
the villainous person who had lie yes
who got billy bigelow into a lot
of trouble that's right and then he
runs away that's right never to be
seen again everybody never winds up in
heaven up there with billy oradell yeah
that's true maybe he's just not there
ah and ah the reason that the
three of us started doing this podcast
many years ago is we're all comedians
we all went on the comedy bang
bang live tour back in what year
was that even twenty twenty sixteen we
we did every show together we travel
old around the country and two different
countries we went to australia and canada
and england although lauren you didn't go
to england i would have had a
nasal surgery on my deviated septum that
was causing slug like blood to leave
my
from a national not enough blood is
slug like it was just you know
i was scared to get on a
plane and have that start happening it's
a big deal yeah so we all
struck up a friendship and we decided
to do a podcast together you're you're
saying we didn't become friends until the
tour no i think probably halfway through
the tour wow
i think that's true
i think i think no we were
already facing a deepening though i know
i saw each other at our glasses
i there's no turning back from that
i do believe that night two of
the tour we everything got real because
guy because actually we were in the
middle of two shows in boston and
backstage you just like did start downloading
my life problems to i think you're
like look this is
gonna be a boring tour unless we
really get to know each other and
be real with each other sigh there
yeah yeah remember this at all i
was going through a personal life change
yes yes anyway so things got real
between us detailed and we decided to
do this we stopped being polite yes
things started getting real yeah and so
what does this show if you've never
heard it before it's just the three
of us
talking about stories from our life for
yeah we share stories from the the
way past the more recent past and
even things that are to come we
we are we can see the future
well i'm a bit of a soothsayer
they say something sooth we are typically
we're appearing on the show as ourselves
we typically are in ah characters on
other podcasts and some people i know
is from laura and i do many
characters scott does a version of himself
i guess the more annoying
i'm version of myself and even that
show or annoy me wow when i
had the i had that calibration different
yeah she's us so yes it's just
it's just silly it's just it's just
silly we have fun and then at
the end of the show we're going
to play what we call a three-tier
wish don't tell anyone is actually a
game it is a game and sometimes
we play
sometimes we play ek and a lot
of times there are references you might
not get unless you listen back to
oh look we're gonna tell all these
stories again where oh yeah i'm starting
from scratch where we were racing yes
we will tell all the stories again
but new in-jokes we're not going lie
any jokes from the previous six years
off
it's tough but we got to do
it we just did want him just
so that's yeah that's true this is
episode one hundred and eighty two for
new listeners yeah and that's what i
like about the joke is that never
we never even explaining never explained it
down purely an injured from our lives
yeah yeah you no one will ever
know no playing a game that's the
type of joke that we have that
will never excel
thank you
and that's what's fun about friends you
don't need to understand it all to
have a good time listening to the
conversations that's good i think it sounds
great
so let's get into it alright so
we're back you know we've had a
brief hiatus we haven't done an episode
since september with each other wow do
you remember that's long i sort of
remember the last episode we didn't septum
september yeah it was the time huh
but buddy ya buddy ya buddy yeah
what are you doing i don't know
he's just saying badia why are you
seeing body to you guy's body out
of you of course bobby w o
the other body body everybody out to
you that's why we went to the
college ah this is the show turn
my phone off
i thought you'd just want your headphones
you want your entire microphone properties just
connect me from the show um well
unplug me from life temper you know
we've had a lot of oh you
had a story that you tell me
hey i've been saving no kidding drove
me bananas because you and i went
to the bluey house yes okay so
let's let's rewind to say
a what this is rewind after the
first of the year now lawrence
this is three different ways
yeah
lauren and i lauren and i have
children yeah ah not together we not
together that they know of we announced
though on lord's topics quite a few
episodes back we announced the fact that
ah my wife and i had a
child yeah which we'd been trying for
football and i have a lot in
topic yes you have learned over that
important yeah tense yeah well
it's time for lawrence topics one of
our most cherished segment this is a
topic where we only talk about whether
i'm having a baby or someone else
in the room huh
um i am having a baby yay
spring i like to leave it vague
for the strangers of the world and
then you'll just see when it pops
out yeah oh really we're going to
see the video yeah yeah i'm gonna
post that my life has any baby
ever popped out i don't know but
my daughter does say baby's gonna pop
out i will say we're gonna catch
it my
friend his wife was pregnant for the
first time and she scored as far
as he knows
these these secrets you're afraid of and
she said to him oh i feel
like i'm having contractions and you said
oh okay well let's ah let's drive
to the hospital they'd like moses she's
very calm mosey to the car nothing
really weird was happening it was about
a twenty minute drive they drove twenty
minutes they arrived they walked into the
door she had the baby
be immediately wow just like k so
lucky like bobby of the hospital i
practically yeah she just went oh i
think and then they they she just
said like wow it looks like a
tv show where like you where you
get cut off in the writing and
you just you you'll keep talking like
oh i think and then the baby
comes out it's like i guess i
can't finish my sentence like she was
gonna say i think i'm
having the baby but it's like guess
like you know when the shows were
like they write it where it's like
you're like no no no i'm trying
to explain and the person just talks
over you so you don't get it
out and i'm like yeah if you
just kept talking they would have to
hear your explanation that would make sense
and then you the cheapest way because
the the the drama is essentially people
keeping secrets from from each other
and so it's the cheapest way when
someone when a character is like hey
i wanna tell you this thing and
then someone interrupts i'm always frustrating yeah
cause i'm like oh it's so cheap
let's circle back at lee yeah it's
like what are the secrets they're keeping
from each other and like eight is
enough well there's nine of them i
don't know if you knew that is
enough is not a drama exit what
would you classify at us
he's an aid is enough oh no
i'm thinking just the ten of us
by the way this is a big
part of three days holiday knowing shows
from the seventy that's right and lower
knowing shows from the abcs hey i
guess eighty yeah because we're not that
far we shouldn't meet in the e
zo yeah sure yeah now you'd think
family matters urkel yeah obviously did i
did i did i it's funny because
that is a that's an
ah i didn't watch family matters but
of course i knew what it was
it was back in three channel days
these were matters hit you know regarding
this particular family yes and i've i
felt like well that's none of my
business these are family leave me out
of it i'm not in their family
yeah they are family matters thank you
yeah they gave me such a platform
to say that
so anyway laura and i haven't had
a chance to say to you congratulations
oh thanks so you didn't ignore me
when we started till there every time
since this has happened um but that's
so cool if you said it i
don't know if i've actually said congratulations
i've expressed my excitement thanks and happiness
for you it's great why are you
withholding with your congratulations i think that's
a sacred thing and
i don't think you should just like
spread it around like well so you
don't think this deserves it that's fine
and it's on the line it's a
lie and you get a sitter to
me congratulation worthy i don't mean graduating
from school that's congratulations oh you got
me oh no okay so i did
say to my congratulations okay good okay
guys it's compilation
tions to you as well
but so that is happening by the
way in the middle of this in
the middle of opposite sides so we'll
just you know one one week you're
gonna hear lawrence have the baby and
we're not gonna mention it for a
while but that's true because we'll be
banking the episodes ahead of time yeah
yeah what if it happens during a
recording like we get trapped in here
like on a sitcom oh that would
be really
bad yeah that actually really wouldn't like
that yeah would you prefer deliver the
baby near scott cool up but no
what i'm imagining is there's an earthquake
and all the exits and entrances are
blocked yeah i'll just do it myself
you'll tell yourself look at me
that even in a mirror what have
i didn't tell my hands i turned
my head that's fine that's fine
we were to pop out yeah
so we went so we really went
with the blue hills backstory on this
so bluey ui but if you're if
you're not watching children's tv lately blue
is an australian cartoon about a dog
named bluey she's a sheepdog i wasn't
she's a dog keep don't know i
don't need i don't see you know
breed yeah so she's got it's her
mom dad scenario open mind and they
have a very cute it's very good
show it actually is good for adult
adult wow that one of the rare
ones that it's like i have actually
not heard that adults love it many
people i know who do not have
children enjoy bluey yes oh yeah i
actually think that some of it might
go over kids' heads a little bit
they do a lot of things to
nod to adult which is always very
sweet it's like there will often be
like little storylines about the parents who
are like oh it's so touching that
things like getting a divorce cool up
the cries at every time like say
a lot watching the show meanwhile i
sit there angry and stern saying little
amount touch with my emotions a little
trivia about louis riel
there was a real bluey really yes
bluey seven june nineteen ten to fourteen
november nineteen thirty nine was a female
australian cattle dog shepherd last dog was
yeah yeah team twenty nine well here's
the thing no nineteen ten she held
down nine world records any sense she
held the guinness world
record as the oldest dog ever live
we really teed you up for that
and generally i'll die this way he
says it can't be that long she
won the guinness and you actually told
me that the other day that's right
but i yet i didn't remember it
was this part of the yeah is
us not remembering what she was she
was a bit well me she was
surpassed by ah bobby from portugal in
twenty twenty three who
also recently passed away although there is
a there i don't know fred guinness
knows this but there's a lot of
controversy whether that is fred guinness i'd
never mind ah that's a different show
but anyway there's a lot of controversy
as to whether that is a writer
that bobby might not have been that
old but so that's a lie it's
kind of a munchausen situation do you
know what that
means
well like i do know that with
the
a young person had a dog who
was old by proxy learns that that's
with such you mean to ally even
really soaking up a lot of gypsy
rose data recently and enemies regular chosen
syndrome that she was younger than she
was right so i just was kind
of playing off of that that her
age this dog's age
was a mystery given the parents were
saying oh she's old she's all the
whole time she was young how does
this fit in with the mysterious case
i'm gonna tell you grace i have
to catch up there was an update
on that they haven't caught up ah
yeah it's horrible by the way that
whole situation is so dark yeah um
i don't know what it is oh
i don't want to explain it it
rhymes though so it sounds whimsical yeah
you can google that if you care
okay
a bluey bluey is sweet and they
had a pop up house which i
think is still a thing it's it's
moving to chicago soon kinda going up
yeah it's going all over the us
and maybe also because it felt like
people from australia were there like guiding
it yeah a couple of the people
in charge seem oh i didn't catch
that um but so is that it's
basically an immersive experience
that's where you go into blues house
they bring the house from the cartoon
to life and it's you know there's
a kitchen and a television room and
and play houses and bedrooms and all
this kind of and then when you
walk in they say well first of
all when we walked in they put
you in the gift shop which i
was like oh god because it was
it was everything was enticing i couldn't
believe me
what i didn't realize is they don't
you don't and you get shot so
that was a huge mistake but yeah
huge i say how secondly i mean
i was kind of like oh we'll
get to this at the end yes
and then we it just plops you
out into the streets you don't want
to in the middle of ifis stuff
right when you're gonna walk around and
do that and you don't know so
whatever yeah so we we never went
back into by anything but when you
so
when we walked in you said i
said how was your christmas and you
said i actually was sorry about that
i said great and you're like i'm
not going to tell you right now
i want to tell you on the
show i was like when are we
doing the show like i don't know
and i was like so i just
don't get to hear a story now
and then then that was it that
was it yeah so you've been in
suspense this whole time but let's talk
about blue i want a very withholding
he uses like you with your congratulations
well that's i've established why i am
that way but you use it as
a means to control us yeah i
was under your thumb for that so
are you only doing this season of
threesome because you want to hear this
story need to know what it is
but an i'm like doing it because
i need money we went into louis'
what to buy candy okay there's somebody
that's right he says some eye-candy oh
my god i never touched it i
said thank you mom buys were ascot
tie mom but it's not like someone
but hey so so bluey bluey they
let's talk about the blues i want
to because you go in the house
and they say oh bluey and being
are playing hide and seek
you have to find them go in
their house and and you're supposed to
be there for forty five minutes or
so like that's your time and there
is no sign of them okay well
there there is well there is a
sign of things little cartoon yeah they
keep popping up like in a cupboard
in like screens and they'll be like
huh and if you catch a glimpse
of them then they go away
to me that didn't count because fuck
them my child never saw that know
your your child was very upset because
she wanted to find bluey immediately she
was focused on the task they said
you go new item and she likes
hide and seek she's like let's go
find them and then she's like where
are they and she was having some
of them should go we have to
find them where she's going to have
it's a forty five minute thing too
and they're not prepared to have bluey
come out to see you until the
end of it so she was getting
a little frustrated five minutes is a
lot i mean y'all just want a
few louis comes out there slides forty
five point solid solid that's too long
i actually agree i felt that you
should get to end it when
you want to end it i didn't
think that writes that setup is yeah
that's ridiculous because i was like she
never was on board at a certain
point like she really wanted to find
them on a fifteen minute though rotation
where right where they take people out
after forty five minutes and then every
fifteen minutes a new group comes in
and they feel released in a private
room
lm yeah where do you take pictures
and stuff like that which was very
cute yeah um so whole thing was
she had a great time i think
thought like it was stressful a little
bit my child emerald was didn't she
she she knows what blue he is
she really loves the theme song and
that's like she'll watch it maybe but
not knowing what's happening but she loves
the theme song yeah so i think
she was just happy
to be in a place where there
were slides and there were like choices
to play and stuff like that they
they they have like dance contests and
stuff like that like it's it certainly
there's a lot going on state away
from that but i do think that
the holly why are you so ashamed
of your dancing just was like you're
you know it just felt cody because
i dropped like a ballerina i'm
a beautiful dancer prima ballerina yeah but
i lost one that time you've done
all the major roles before you're twenty
one of course you have to um
but being pregnant in this tight space
with a bunch of little germs and
then it was dan thanks for your
children yeah looks like i'm
just gonna move over here yeah because
there are points where everyone was kinda
corralled into one room and it was
like you could just go to a
different room and be alone so it's
like that's great
so in any case he was wrong
was that it sounds when you say
everyone was corralled into this little room
he's younger very grim no it was
it was loud it was like they
were blasting music and doing like crazy
it'd be better crazy to on test
if you are five perfect yeah it
was overwhelming for like they were stacking
like you know all these foam things
and
into statues and stuff liking them knocking
mostly it was work yeah it was
just a ton of stressful to me
so i'll let you know when construction
job i definitely like i was like
i see that monday through friday yeah
i need to i was like you
pushed i was younger i worked for
sure what like when i was starting
out right like i would be like
this would be my this is a
pre baby sitting here
it would be pardoned by the way
to be part of this babysitting and
then movie stuff
so inaccurate but it wasn't that accurate
i also think commercials
wouldn't still do them huh yeah i
still do from time to time when
they pay well sure okay
but the the ah the activity of
leading the kids through this would've been
a side job i went ahead first
right yeah where i would a bit
because it was it seemed pretty fun
and easy for as far if you're
a performer and it's like i bet
it paid pretty decent but at the
end of it at the end of
it we go into a room and
there's bluey and bingo i think and
yes we
yeah sure wasn't that it was another
big lawyer recognized
there was a brown one but we
also can picture with them and i
was highly excited at that point i
think she was but she was also
really confused because they're big they're they're
bigger than they should be and they're
human size she was looking at them
kind of like huh but then she
was excited but in the picture she's
not smiling yes in the picture my
child is also not smiling yeah
but then then cut to two weeks
later she went to a child's birthday
party the other day yesterday where there
was a giant elmo and she's only
been watching sesame street for one calendar
week yeah she blew her mind and
she ran up in the hotel mo
unlike what she did with blue she
was a little reticent about louis she
just hopped down would not let him
go so cute yeah
very cute um so in any case
that teases us up for this story
but we have to take a break
wow i just really quickly yeah do
you think that she was more responsive
to elmo because he seems less powerful
than bluey yeah i think i think
power dynamics were definitely a play
more in control of herself right right
yeah we the almost seems like a
child the bluey that you meet
is hard yes shining marcia to the
touch where i think elma not like
plushie it so it's like a foam
kind of yeah hard so big round
maybe almost fashioned out of cardboard or
something it was it was and then
ah yeah applied with paint it
you know it just wasn't squishy it
wasn't huggy yeah yeah meanwhile oh well
it's just like your raw yeah yeah
pure fluff okay we have to take
a break when we come back this
exciting story of what what happened to
me on christmas eve wow i really
have no idea what it is yeah
you'll be blown away we're gonna take
a break we'll be right back with
more freedom die
and we're back alright now can i
guess what the story is yeah what
if you told the whole thing you
call santa claus you caught them kissing
your mom
yeah and i tied him up and
he's in that room over there oh
but it's funny that that little rat
in that story in that song yeah
it's saying i saw mommy kissing santa
claus like implying that it was the
mommy's idea well also also i think
he's trying to say like mommy was
cheating on daddy there's the other side
of the equation to santa clauses cheating
on mrs tucking and he's fucking your
dad he's cooking your dog cookie your
dad's cooking inside is that the title
um okay so this so we haven't
seen each other oh by the way
lula shire's the episodes of titles yes
so we haven't seen each other as
a group since september ah wow and
we're i'm taking no no i'm sorry
we were we went to dinner and
we had a holiday party at your
house that's right we have the holiday
party so we've seen each other a
bunch and you're a weiss is a
bunch to you twice more though here's
a bunch of bananas two banana yeah
okay more than two banana i'm sorry
don't you not see people bunch usually
two is a lot
this is a lot of times to
see someone between then and then a
great agreed i think
okay so here's what i also saw
your bluey that's right so in between
but i wasn't there or high or
say the costume that would be all
over till we were fucking imagine if
i took off the head and it
was all sh i would show vashem
oh yeah yeah i didn't even know
what my reaction little bit
what oh man i got to greet
your income i gotta figure out how
to do that you need somebody to
do that now yeah yeah we know
so many people have kids now yeah
yeah you would know someone in the
group so just do it yeah whenever
you can and i'm sure you'll notice
that anytime there's a new house verify
their children
but if there's ever a child's birthday
party just there ever is yeah i
mean holly's is probably coming up i
mean in the summer sure the company
can just come by as bluey christmas
is coming up yeah and lauren will
think that mike hired him and mike
will you hire oh like it's like
when jesus says
like when joseph and mary lost our
lord in the temple that's right yes
i always think about that
you what happened on the eve of
christmas okay so ah christmas day umm
we had ah we were going to
have a lot so we're just skipping
right over that story well i know
this is still this is still christmas
yeah my daughter i'm having fun i
understand i'm not
sometimes we get contentious textbook freedom so
on christmas day we were supposed to
have a lot of people over a
lot of family a lot of friends
like to ah yeah a bunch to
people
and um so cool up tends to
go i don't wanna say overboard but
she does a lot when on these
holidays don't say fucking benjamin sure yeah
and she's goldie hawn just a great
host she's a great host using d
she she jumps with the people want
she really she really enjoys it she
really just really
enjoys it but she doesn't farm out
a lot of this other people or
even like order food she wants to
live in farmer that's right he's so
bored
but it's worth it for us yeah
no moderator you just have him out
there in the dell
dude you're getting a dell is what
we said to be higher just like
oh it's perfect heard it was why
he's like i love that reference for
everyone's wife carol runs right around february
once matt remember former mossad remember once
met right
maybe that's the title that might be
this let's go to attract la wrong
food
you know what good they should be
disappointed
so um we go to sleep on
the night before christmas eve oh twas
the night before christmas yes although the
house not a creature was stirring not
even a mouse club has just me
and all through the house not a
creature chimneys was caring and even a
mouse something like that you know what
buyers yeah yeah that's good so before
the night before cool up has
made a big huge to do list
of what she has to do on
christmas eve and it's like to to
the every half hour of like i
need to put this in the oven
at this point wow i don't cook
yeah it's somehow confusing plus i'm horrible
at it plus i have no desire
really the case yeah so we go
to we go to sleep at four
in the morning cool up wakes me
up and says your tinkle bells he's
close close she says why is the
room spinning
what's happening why is the room spinning
oh no and
i think she's having a dream yeah
and so i'm like it's okay honey
it's okay and she's like no no
the room is spinning what's happening and
i'm like oh something actually is wrong
um i wake up we turn on
the light i'm like what's i ask
her to describe what's happening she's
like the entire room is spinning around
me right now um i like look
up on the internet symptoms and and
vertigo comes up and i'm like this
sounds like vertigo to me like you
have an inner ear problem vertigo essentially
is like it's it's the same reason
you get car sickness
if you have in your inner ear
you have like a gyroscope and if
your eyes are not seeing what your
ears are experiencing it's why you get
sick on the harry potter ride or
whatever if i do get sick on
the phone if i went one time
i was like this is the most
nauseating right i mean right around my
arms
they've no not since no like the
first week it was open every single
person who went on it threw up
oh my goodness
okay what the picture just reading a
magazine you're bored yeah so awesome i
order it every week so she's so
lame of you
others cool
so so i looked it up and
i say i think it's vertigo i'm
looking at the symptoms and i see
one of the symptoms is or one
of the things that can happen with
vertigo is having a stroke oh god
and i'm like i think it's just
vertigo i think of you close your
eyes in and go back to sleep
you'll you'll be better
um so she goes back to sleep
ah and then at eight or at
seven in the morning i wake up
with a baby and i'm taking care
of the baby and about nine in
the morning she comes downstairs and i
say how are you feeling and she
says i think we should go to
the urgent care
on christmas christmas eve oh okay yeah
so i say okay i'm trying to
figure out what we do with the
baby we call cool sister who is
able to come over you know that's
really great so we get into the
car and like er how are you
right now she's like it's still is
spinning um so
so i find an urgent care down
the street we go to it we
park um i lead her inside i
sit her down in the waiting room
i go up to the the front
desk sorry this one was she experiencing
she's like kind of crying and and
is has her eyes closed is it
still like everything's spinning for yes okay
so
so i say almost good i check
in and i say hey i tell
the symptoms and they say okay well
are you a kaiser member and i
said no and they go well you
can't be here i swear to god
and since obvious yeah it's it's i
mean everyone knows but it's just so
many things like that yeah so they
say go to the e r down
the street and they showed me a
map and i say okay so i
go back to cool up and i
say hey we have to go to
a different place that's all i say
to her she goes okay and so
i lead her back to the car
and then we find the e r
but they don't
so i need to drop her alright
for an e are so insane so
i need to drop her off so
i say here honey go inside the
you know this is the er go
inside and sit down i'll find parking
and i'll be back parking is three
blocks away what so i like they
do they have a lot that is
full or they just don't have a
dedicated space
people know that the the directions to
the park like there are signs that
say parking this way and then they
don't follow up and say which way
you're supposed to turn after that so
i went i made a right and
it was a left cheek to a
closer lot that's so annoying so anyway
i run back in and i sit
down with cool up and she
says what are we doing here oh
my jesus right and i i start
to freak out yeah and i'm like
we're here for your vertigo honey and
she's crying going to go did you
check in and she goes no and
so i like i'm freaking out and
i'm flip
being out thinking like something's wrong something's
wrong because she doesn't wear shoes so
i go to the front desk and
i explain the situation thinking that they'll
rush someone in there like okay we'll
fill out these forms this is my
experience i literally was bleeding out and
saying to eat by myself and no
one cared it's crazy yeah fuckin no
way helps you
so i'm like can't we like oh
by the way i'm behind someone who's
taking a million years and i'm like
trying to get the person's attention like
this is an emergency but i guess
everything is an emergency in the emergency
yeah but it's like have some urgency
yeah so anyway i fill it i'm
like fuck so i fill it out
super quick and i give it back
and then he needs to make a
call to kaiser
they're like did she ever come in
when her address was such and such
which would have been in literally nineteen
ninety nine oh my god i'm like
maybe that was twenty five years ago
huh you know they call verify like
what does that even have do with
any vow they verify her identity and
they go okay we vet
verified her identity okay and they verify
with her license yeah yeah then they
make a call to the person and
thankfully with urgency and the person comes
right out okay good take her into
the other room and start examining her
and asking her questions and they one
of the questions they ask they say
how old are you honey
and she says um four forty one
ah and i'm like she's forty three
as it's so scary and they're like
okay we're gonna we're gonna take you
and get you checked out because you're
too young to be this confused about
things you know that's rude uh
if you're older we'd give you some
time
so they rushed her into the emergency
room team of doctors comes in starts
asking your questions um and um the
doctor kind of shuts everything down and
just says like this is just vertigo
like we don't need to do the
mres and he goes this is just
vertigo you you
you i know you're worried that you're
having a stroke if you wouldn't know
if you were having you you wouldn't
know that you'd be worried you're having
a stroke he would just have a
stroke and not know it okay that's
interesting so yeah i love that tip
yeah so you never can say i'm
having a stroke and it's real isn't
there something about toast
that's all you're allowed yeah
because it's my toes i can't say
i think that means if not you're
not yeah yeah i do smell toast
i think about edit that you don't
know anything about what's happening to so
he's shutting everything down and and saying
though why were you so confused and
coop says no no you don't understand
i wondered where we were because i
wondered why we left the other place
it's okay so she wasn't confused she
just goes i know i was in
in the yar i just wondered why
we left the previous place and why
we're at this and she just couldn't
communicate she was feeling yeah sick and
she was lying about right well i
say sick i'm guessing i'm like forty
one buy it now i say what
was the deal with the age
two weeks prior she and her best
friends had decided to start lying about
their age huh oh my where they
then went around every time they would
see each other in surprise pop quiz
each other of how old are you
what year were you born i got
your did you graduate teen are you
allowed to tell this
story i think so
ah so
yeah but eject before this
involving her important roos in her life
so so she was legitimately like she
knows she won't like it but it's
gonna cover
studies teacher she legitimately for the previous
two weeks had constantly been asked how
old are you and she had had
to answer quickly forty one forty one
that's so silly
ah
so everything come down they did take
an mri just to be sure i
was gonna say you should still do
that yeah everything i don't like when
they're like now now let's not look
at this no they just say we
have the speed and alacrity with which
they were like trying to do it
everything slowed down okay yeah she's still
like they gave her some something called
antivert which has anti vertigo pills and
stuff and it's been going on
pretty sad just jimmy lift do you
want some do you have vertigo like
pools i'm like it just feels like
the antivert i love feeling normal i'll
avert antivert
well we take some vert first and
then some and i've made vert right
now oh man i'm written so hard
so yeah that was and she was
worried about all the preparations and i
was saying like do you think she
was having like a panic and not
like ah i don't know if vertical
can be a panic attacks candle in
the amount of stress of the things
she had to master are you particularly
stressed in my head and thinking like
yeah it's christmas eve and she has
all this stuff she might say no
because it's like
fun but it's like yeah i'm actually
thinking about forty things and yeah but
also you know it can it can
be like if you have to like
an inner ear cold or something like
that it can it can do it
it's actually way more common than i
think people would think okay asked me
you'll you're the doctor asking me if
i'm particularly stressed are you particularly stressed
always ask me lauren are you particularly
stretch dough
mother fucker
whenever always asked me that one of
the doctor was like and are you
interested if i'm particularly stressed nobody ever
turns back on me and i just
wish someone would say how are you
today whatever every time you had to
go into the everytime you went to
the doctor you had to do the
same examination on the doctor
out of courtesy i like it
yeah they actually know what it was
so cute she went to the doctor
and we were very prepared because she
got like a doctor kit she really
likes and whenever and so she was
like kind of excited and then she
brought her stethoscope to the doctor and
then the the doctor he he said
i told the doctor take a deep
breath and like it was just very
adorable
i didn't tell me to take a
deep breath when she checked my heart
oh yeah yeah and i just said
she's showing that she would not say
it when she was wanting to say
it but she did have a special
posture she was standing with her hand
on her hips let me towards him
and then um yeah at the doctor
she also loves so if you say
how old are you she says five
and she's two and a half
he's like thirty two yeah and a
lot of complications yeah quiz with other
toddlers i mean went to the doctor
the other day got shots was fine
with it yeah didn't even flinch chill
it was happening i think but it's
fast handing her putting her into the
weight thing to get get her weight
she freaked out as a cold no
i think it was just like us
letting her go
which it's holding up yeah this is
cool yeah after the emre they put
her on the weight bold
alright we have to
we'll be right back with a three-tier
welcome back hey everyone we're back it's
still threesome and we are going to
play all three juror that's rye deep
love when we do this and we
love doing it really love it and
do it and we can we can
do we can do it we will
yeah can we don't and we're not
forced to do this it's just that
we can't no one else is here
it's just the three of us yeah
there's their rifles point we change this
whole last part right now and we're
not yeah this room is well lit
and comfortable and we have plenty of
food and water and there aren't like
laser dots on our temples or loser
dogs um this is a this is
an old favourite
we should play that no i love
that next episode how about that um
this is this is called well here's
the thing there's two games that we
play one very similar one is called
purchases will know for the new listener
we played three trayless games that's true
i did not mean to apply that
we only like to gamble either
are basically the same i do like
that yeah because it sounded like that
and it's not no good catch laura
and it could be anything you can
submit a game to us and you
haven't able to game three right three
write to us at ah three dm
usa at gmail dot com and let
us know what three-tier you want to
us to play them you know what
if you want if you ever want
to leave us a voicemail ask for
some advice or something you can call
us at hag claims eight
eight do you explain that that i'm
not after that she'll stay with you
after all after everything is done after
we turned off the recording when you
said that you expect us to say
at the same time no okay that
was my delivery of it every single
one to give him his moment let
him shine yes i always think oh
i'm lee thank you head claims eight
oh emily but i mean
that's the other that's our only extension
yeah claims eight extension oh i'm late
yeah yeah yeah gave me away anyway
we're gonna play switch-hitter pitch it which
is one of the three years that
we play and what this is is
um
two of us play not working check
your network okay
ah
i'm parody of the beatles few of
us do you do that to explain
that that's like one of the most
most ear wired elbows after every song
that was a parody of faith hope
so
i'm doing my own songs now yeah
you should just like wells run dry
oh shit ha ha i was that
parody fat parody is bad
it should be layers i went right
hat hat on my head you know
it i think he should do that
what about that no no because of
newcomers batman yeah zip-top bag because i'm
bad i'm bad i'm batman
ok so two of us are network
executives playing playing network executives we're not
actually network don't send us your ideas
will show just got fired pretending we
have twisted um and then a person
comes in or one of us could
be a network executive and it's a
team which which do you rather play
i think two of us are
network executives and then there's usually we
do and then the third person comes
in we tell them the title of
an existing show we've used i think
family matters we've talked about family matters
we have yeah then the the person
who you're welcome to rewind and listen
for yourself we did talk about the
person pitching the show has to
switch the words in that show's title
usually they'll do the opposite so family
would be like enemies enemy and matters
would be different i think the opposite
of family his friends and you guys
said
but say it's say it's ah it's
their choice to say it's enemies indifference
and they have to pitch a sitcom
or a television show to the ah
to network executives with that title and
then at the end they have to
sing the theme song for that show
righteous truly righteous explanation why love
it alright so who wants to do
one
i want to be an executive i'll
be an executive alright then i'll be
the other thing that's left yes yes
and what does my title yes we
have to give him a title what's
your title is um blossom
okay now i'm gonna report you
i'd go ahead and see if i
care no i'll report you back also
you have something worth thing on me
oh yeah yeah what about these pictures
oh my god how did you get
those i'm sorry my early nights you're
late we went in on this what
do you think of these pictures sandie
shaw law so i opposed with this
it's elmo but it's was my
boyfriend this is supposed to be your
dating elmo and that really elmo it's
costume is this what the point this
is not elmo oh my god oh
hi anyway welcome lie anywhere fly anyway
welcome was that your phil assure him
okay my name's deb hi deb it's
nice to meet you my name's dube
i do have nice to meet you
sir
can i be filled just for the
purposes hey if you want to legally
change your name if you legally change
it in the next six months i'll
allow that you did that i have
the paperwork ready to go i just
have to fill in the new name
and okay you need a witness to
notarize it can i get a witness
i don't know that well a witness
is the same as a notary dube
but ah you could be the witness
i could be the notary deb you
to be a registered notary do which
i am haven't you ever seen my
little stamps okay yeah we don't have
all the time in the world because
why are you wasting our time each
other for different things so um
i need to know what you're getting
calls oh my it's age are high
you haven't live yeah hi h are
awesome stuff yeah i want to report
deb
can i talk to them yeah here
you go my pest-free why did they
clean why are you doing this
because i'm in love with you
yeah i want to say it for
so long and just cheating on elma
with h r pipe size and getting
a text from somebody and h are
you i'm in the middle of a
pitch i need to get this guy
out you'll never believe the boring person
on the phone with right now i'll
call you back okay interesting i love
you click alright okay do you shake
click when you hang
up the phone you just so everyone
in there was because it's her favorite
movie i do love how the remote
kind of changes it's going on kind
of yeah that's part of it i
noticed my one problem with that movie
it didn't change it enough but yeah
kind of like yeah pausing it for
a second okay please please do you
please pitch your picture here looking yeah
we're giving
we have so many slots on too
much money to do this we need
just whatever bullshit you have we don't
really care doesn't even have to be
good just pit yeah oh no that's
what i mean i suspected this was
how things worked hello sharks what i
have for you today is a situation
comedy how did he know we were
sharks and it's called nathan oh seed
see yes and seed is about the
inner life of a seed in an
apple
and you know like santa made it
yes so it's not animated but it
is in the style of a pixar
movie where we see the interior life
of inanimate objects this is a live
action show it's ninety minutes long
ninety minutes that doesn't unusual time it's
the first ninety minute comedy wow well
i mean i guess movies are ninety
minutes
for a tv show i meant okay
i gotta give him it now so
far we have a ninety minutes slot
we have about four hours that we
have to focus just for every night
this is perfect because i have many
other ideas and the longer the better
on so say you have other ideas
yeah well let me get through this
one first well i guess it's like
we got it yeah i get it
i get no no i get seed
oh no maroon no there's more to
it there's more to it deceit go
to school see does go to school
with seeds twin brother seed too because
there's two seeds in the apple oh
there are only two seeds in the
show notes far as i know that's
like if you had a twin named
phil to i do that's it's spice
despite about my
my life oh really so you you
are twins start with that i am
a twin i wish i was an
apple wow okay yeah human life is
too hard and when i dress like
an apple yeah you're all in red
yeah you're wearing a big puffy coat
that's around you know the long thin
hat you are an apple
we'd be dead but yeah that's what
the sign near my apartment says
that's when i first started thinking yes
you're right i wish i was an
apple yeah so seed and seed too
they go to school they play play
together they go on dates together double
dates with other know each other but
yes okay yeah do they go out
with twins i've always thought thought it
was complicated they do and i'll save
you the trouble
yes they do pretend to be each
other oh good that's good huh the
other twins also pretend to be each
other so their data really just girl
yeah that's good yeah that's crazy yeah
that's the situation is yeah you're exactly
right it's crazy yeah that's what makes
this show different it's crazy is that
i heard is that part of the
actual show or is that off camera
all that happy
nz we haven't decided yet because a
lot of big chunk of that show
will be off camera okay do but
the screen goes dark
can you just pause on your questions
for a second because i want to
know if there's a theme song oh
my god of course there is because
because we only do shows with theme
songs it's kind of a set to
work trying to bring back the theme
song a lot of people have skipped
that part now yes or no and
i miss that i miss that a
theme song that would tell you every
thing that the show was about exactly
eve or even just like you know
visuals like survivor used to just be
that was he's saying the saga originally
i could tell i thought it was
i thought he was listening into a
recording now it's his voice but um
yeah we wandering that any give me
just a little more that's right yeah
hey huh he always does this
it's okay to do that
hey yeah you think her
yeah i wrote it it's all gibberish
oh even better
anyway what's your theme song you want
to hear this it goes a little
something like this okay
dab zag these it's almost like a
book out with jackie matt of a
big tree trail gotta go around live
with my best friend who looks just
like ea do do do do do
do i but apple is our goal
to see that i'm not actually an
apple out just as
z thereby aged everybody's got what they
need that proceed that both seed there's
too much in this world that is
greed everybody has to get a low
banner there the do i but apple's
eater how about you because that was
the extended
version that we'd find on spotify but
no that's the short short version yeah
yeah just really ninety minutes deb the
solo song is a full fifteen minutes
long really yeah so it's longer than
stairway to heaven oh yeah and is
there anything on the screen during that
there is a a picture of an
apple and then picture
one apple one picture of one apple
okay then that apple magically splits into
and then you see the two seeds
in there then you zoom in on
the seeds and they say too close
to close and then the camera zooms
back out so smart apple closes again
then you hear the home screen voice
say i'm gonna give her another try
and you have to really listen
close because the theme song is playing
the whole time yeah so the cameras
starts zooming in again you have to
listen close well because it's if you
wanna hear that yeah i guess you
could turn the subtitle how do you
know you want to hear if you
know you can't turn the subtitles on
how do you show will not have
some suit doesn't have sometime oh have
a serious question how do you know
you want to hear it if you
don't know that it's happening know you
can hear something but you
can't decipher what it is unless you're
listening closely because the theme song is
loud i think you should have a
disclaimer that says if you want to
hear what the sort of subtle things
are eating to turn it up or
pay attention should it should that come
before the theme song i think it
just be said in the middle but
loud okay so how about if we
added something in i
and and how about if we added
something like this guy you may have
missed some stuff why don't you rewind
that's pretty good yeah you may have
missed some stuff which everyone yeah cause
that at the end it's no no
so it's right after deb said that
the disclaimer would mean so am i
going to say that disclaimer would you
like to i'd love you can we
hire you i love to have you
do it can you sing a bit
of the song and i'll just do
the disclaimer absolutely everybody knows it
wow if you want to hear things
that are happening just to turn it
up real loud hey gross yeah yeah
change everybody's going to see that your
not strap makes me want to grab
the remote and just rewind yeah right
yeah that makes the show last oh
i'm i gonna get paid for that
i mean you're the ig
executives so you determined what do we
have in the budget let's take a
look a million or so towards that
olfactory in your blackmail oh yeah you
can give you like a bunch of
whether you're blackmailing us or were black
i could if you like yeah sure
yeah let me here here's some pictures
of me thank you yeah oh wait
those are me oh okay yeah i
mean the elmo costume you guys realize
yeah you have the exact same naked
body
we try we're always checking in with
each other every day just say like
hey are your muscles a little bit
bigger moles your stuff everything yes everything
is exactly the same
weak get a tailor to come in
and take our measurements they're always exactly
the same huh yeah we're working on
getting our heads to be the same
yeah i cut my hair like hey
that's been dreaming yeah yeah
and that's ah
replay replays which didn't pitch it and
purchase it saw they're the same game
behind us kind of although we'll play
pitcher friend their song another song can
just do rounds of saying that's right
yes that's true row row row your
boat readily down the street oats
generally by
show us ya know is a nation
a word no i loved it though
who would we all did who are
you doing in that doctor job after
john yes yes dr john was awesome
leon redbone was mr belvedere was he
really i didn't know that strakes on
the china
matter before oh alright drop kick rocker
to the da
the times no one glares no glowing
girls so catterson i don't know oh
awesome no harm hearings yeah turn around
so no one's there according to ah
no arrival alive them all oh man
survival now we just my love i'll
go live yet
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo because i have huge news ooh
no one glare it's what i say
oh okay wait and no one spared
did you say to say that okay
wait no one spare from what the
wrath of khan but sometimes things get
turned around and no one so i
said no
their yea and they know what they're
there for most fans that's that's heavy
i remember there was an episode of
mister belvedere where the older son lost
his virginity that's high weight show it
some do too i never saw any
no i know exactly looks like he
had the cool eighties haircut he started
off with mr t moz sort of
sloppy bleak eighty haircut he looks sort
of like a jamie kennedy type of
dude definitely yeah yeah um i have
to go yeah i'll have to go
we all have to go this is
ain't but um you know we want
to tell you if you want to
reach out to us again you can
reach out to us at three dm
us what is it three the three
days emile dot com follow us on
the soap
chel strydom usa and if you want
to call us it's high claims eight
it's an easy way to remember it
ah hag than the word claims and
then the number eight what do hags
want to do do you want to
say nothing that didn't actually work probably
no that was haha law in right
now this one works fine you just
dial into your phone just hag and
then what a hags wanna do they
want to claim things and how many
of them eight eight always i always
a black guy claims eight you can
call us leave a message for us
you might be able to hear yourself
on this show and for now leave
us alone yeah we'll tell you when
we want to hear from you
um thanks so much for listening to
this first episode of our new season
and we love you we love you
we love you so much ma ma