three
oh and my name of the show
in this show's called freedom folks and
we're here right now recording live from
dodger stadium we are three yellows in
the stadium alone no one is here
and we are screaming guys on top
of our lungs yeah nah guys stop
everything
up everything lauren had announcement that she
wanted to say yes this was this
was previously said she said this right
now where we started the show and
i said stop everything let's start to
show and talk about it gotta get
this on the past topics you guys
are not gonna believe what i saw
on instagram okay so this is on
instagram and i know it wasn't real
she said it was real life i
said
i saw pizza making i saw were
about making you saw pizza making white
i don't think making somebody sick robot
making robot but it's a it's in
rome and it's a vending machine that
makes pizza pizza from scratch it makes
the dough its emissions it down it
puts the sauce it puts the toppings
it bakes it and then it comes
out and it looks pretty good weight
it makes the dough so this is
a blog
process yeah i don't know how long
lady was standing there i don't know
she sped up the video at all
or what but it looks pretty good
and i'd be willing no edit for
fifteen minutes i scrubbed things that were
like shooting edits like in the janet
jackson video you know yeah yes or
our rope fucking nineteen fourteen what was
it that movie
date night two nineteen nine nineteen getting
yellow pudding in the u nine nineteen
going on ninety that movie
oh yeah i love that one i
know what that's a huge oh my
god that's such a mis market body
switch movie extremely old person yes with
a young person yeah that's fucking fun
how young are we talking about i'm
saying i want to see nine and
ninety nine and ninety okaying and ninety
nine year old fights
cells
and a ninety year olds shriveled up
now but maybe nineteen ninety year old
never want to go back
exactly yeah so it would become like
ah like a battle between them where
the nine year old was thirty nine
when rolled like a roll god when
you went like this and you went
like you were gonna clap but that
you didn't wow what what were you
doing i was i was imitating you
was i doing this yeah i mean
we were all just kind of like
doing
lori will start doing that you were
doing that five solid minute okay i'm
not talking to you you weren't answering
i'm not well in the brain i
what i think what would happen is
they that so then the when the
ninety year old finds themselves in the
nineteen year old body or nine year
old they realize i have to
i have to run away i have
to get away because whoever is going
is going to be cheap and be
after me and then it's like a
chase around the world
china it's like it's a mad mad
mad mad world but instead of just
across california in the us well because
treasuries a thing of like the young
person being so excited to be in
the older body because they get to
do things they don't normally do but
i'd be like watching matter no but
i'm saying in in the other ones
where it's like thirteen going on thirty
it's like wow i'm thirty wow i
finally have freedom
to do what i want i have
boobs yeah but then when you're ninety
becoming nineteen then you're like boobs are
down to here while you're just excited
to you know get out on the
town again i can't wait to go
to bed at seven pm yeah i
mean the ninety year old would be
i don't have boobs awesome why would
they not have boobs if it was
a woman double the size
nine year while a nine-year-old that bring
the room down when do when do
we get boobs oh i was about
nineteen ninety no yeah well nine girls
are now women i think we can
be very clear you are the one
who said it you said when do
women get booze huh
because you were saying oh god you
don't know you don't know and now
you know well boobs are new don't
know what boobs are you know
it doesn't know what they are
like when it happens but he doesn't
know what they are just asking that
question alone don't know what the are
that was the thing that bothered me
about the forty year old virgin is
because it came it was inspired by
a sketch they used to do at
second city and they can't already yeah
they kept an original dialogue when he
reveals that he's a virgin to his
poker buddies one of the lines is
yeah i need to you touch a
you touched boobs and they're they're like
bags
of sand and then everybody's like what
but it's like that come on
you can be a virgin and i'm
still kind of assumed that tits are
still have sandbags you get your touch
boobs look i was i was a
nineteen year old virgin and i touched
but my like for boobs but he's
forty four sets he's gone he's never
done anything
yeah moron but they show him in
the later in a later sequence they
show him like his own his almost
attempts at having sex but you gotta
figure the boob got touched before then
the bases i haven't seen that since
it came out at the arclight new
york's of course and my fury remains
undimmed
wow i remember laughing like hell at
that kelly clarkson part
oh right oh i first i thought
you's were saying she was in it
i was like wow these are placing
ellen
is she she yeah i mean has
her own show yeah but she's gonna
do to show and time slot
having an alex sly i love kelly
i think she's so great
one of the best singers in the
world absolutely she's sure of it she's
having something of a i feel like
i've i hear list talking about her
more not i mean because you never
went away but i feel like gradually
people are talking more and more about
their love for her so mixing this
because we're getting to know her more
because now she's in the she's got
a show she's being
herself she's out there talking you know
the best american idol contestant ever and
the first the fir i mean berliner
when furry sang that ah you're all
i need it was just incredible and
we all rooted for her and we
loved her and justin but let's not
forget about justin guarini
let us not forget the runner up
he was the runner-up he was trailer
which is what about ruben studdard usually
it will be teddy bears second runner
up who would be or the runner-up
who would be the real breakout star
yes back someone who is kelly clarkson
she actually was the one to have
the lasting fame but i feel like
for the years after it was always
the second person yeah
yeah because they weren't locked into that
contract yea jennifer hudson was little voted
it was fifth or so my gods
got you you want them daughtry oh
my god yea i secretly likes to
be tree longs sure i met dacha
he was great nice dude
i've met two american idol lists i
think whoa which was i've met david
cook and i play where did you
meet david cook i remember watching via
usb cable springs on v h one's
best week ever oh wow did a
skit together and then um ah oh
what's his name he he he tours
with queen your
things skits pretty loosely i would say
i don't know why i started doing
it and it's making me like it
makes her like to do it because
i just want to make sure because
i felt that it was ironically and
then you gotta to move into jang
that's the problem it's like i remember
when when greg baron started saying hey
man like sammy davis junior to everyone
and then we all just wandered around
saying hey man like
about a year later like everyone just
said it like hey man
yeah normally but we weren't we were
all you know we started with just
saying hey man no we started saying
hey man how much other i kind
of remember that yeah because we all
went to the museum of television and
radio and we saw that rat pack
thing that johnny carson was part of
do you remember that like yeah johnny
carson was replacing summer
one was it sinatra i can't remember
yes and so and then we're dean
martin maybe maybe dean martin or perhaps
joey bishop and then greg perhaps peter
lawford
and greg would just anytime you would
see anyone he'd go hey man and
then we started kind of like imitating
them going here man to people and
then it just it's segue into haymon
yeah it just became a regular greeting
and no one had ever said hey
man before not i mean not in
the nineties this is like ninety think
how much they say now exactly i
say hey ma
man writes you're welcome wow she's so
we should bring back a man hey
man yeah
that i'm gonna come out of cambridge
like times and just like seeing everything
anyway hi man
huh
i haven't seen her in a year
got weird ur
hi mango whoa you hey man girl
amen girl amen girl hey that's a
mature man doe no we should be
the rat pack make the three of
us we should be we should be
the brat pack know what i mean
like we should here's what we should
do we should all go on tour
we each do an hour separate
it right and then we come together
for the last hour it's a four
hour show are you going to do
this way too many hours watching how
many hours you wanna do i wanna
do i want there to be one
hour max switch do fifteen minutes alone
fifteen together what if we all do
our hour at the same time yeah
and people okay we're in different rooms
and people can choose they want to
see
yeah it's like sleep no more yeah
you can wander in more and you're
gonna get you're gonna like coming out
of my eyes into your rooms i'm
gonna i'm gonna have the biggest best
room i like my chances i think
some people don't like mine all navigation
is definitely me then called and scott
yeah
did i become the person you all
like fun
started it yeah it's true you show
what arena you put yourself in that
position we put your story i know
it's good podcasting but it hurts my
feelings oh no honey no no no
no no no no no no no
new year's the difference here's the difference
we don't mean anything by it and
you know that hold
on but when there's people trying to
chime in on it online ah that's
a no no no no and we
don't know if you're that's reserved for
these two to do incessantly when you're
here you're family okay and family can
see whatever the fuck they want about
each other when you're online go fuck
yourself
toyota that's not telling you talk about
um tal john sending ah yeah ok
i'm i pick up todd barry so
todd barry what is he doing entirely
why is it so funny that it's
todd barry to it's very funny to
mention that getting details makes well it's
funny for costa okay here's what happens
to todd barry ah comedian extraordinary
or he was probably doing something on
he's real man he's a man guy
hey man hey man hey um he
he jokingly it's part of his personality
to say to people like to act
like a big celebrity so i think
he was saying he said to tell
john hay on the way to the
airport tomorrow could you send me a
stretch hummer and
in the morning stretch hummer was there
for him and it's just so light
inside like those neon little toy yeah
yeah so funny and then he had
a heated crawl in that i just
think that's hilarious
it's so great you know speaking of
new zealand as we were last week
um ah when we were there we
a bunch of us got in a
in a like an uber type van
to go some place and it was
it was like a party van but
it was way too small so it's
just like all these disco lights and
everything were all crammed in
why do you like too good for
any occasion i love i look i
love party lights we joke around on
here a lot but i love part
of the one thing about paul we
will not and that's the one thing
you want to be serious about right
like for the all the hours we've
done watching in your fifteen minutes that
you would talk about yeah yeah well
because paul is a ted thx
talk yeah and his fifteen minutes my
fifteen minutes are gonna be kind of
like a silent sort of just like
signing autographs and
i love signing autographs and i'll give
notes on scripts that people bring what
if people start to talk will you
what will you do anything or they
can talk i just won't okay will
you acknowledge that they're talking not necessarily
okay that's good and scott when you
give notes or you're gonna read the
scripture just gonna give notes i'm just
gonna give notes by the way it
looks like how fickett
is ah the character names bag glance
on the first page can i say
that the other day i all of
a sudden got excited for christmas
whoa cancel it out of the what
do you mean nice mina y best
one we ever did what do you
mean we just we really are on
a year and a half a mark
what lauren we're at the point where
we didn't just do it yes we're
at the halfway mark exactly sky it
it feels like we just did it
i was just watching wonder woman nineteen
eighty four the other day it feels
like wow that's how i mark christmas
too i did watch it on christmas
and soul i watched that too back
dad my dad went to bed but
if i watched back to back on
christmas we were watching soul mike and
i and um my dad like fell
asleep during i was caught up soul
mike
when the bed we were watching so
mike he did it again remember that
movie soul man yeah well no my
dad is home came back out near
the end of the movie and we
were like sobbing and holding each other
like wow what is this
ah what is this
like watching a cartoon like cry
did he like do you think he
was disappointed like this is what i've
read honest they were like this is
so good that he was like
ah
ah alright so what are we gonna
do for christmas
oh my god yeah i'm very excited
i'm looking forward to ah we should
go to the temple shanta again that
was oh that's right i wasn't like
excited about i didn't get to go
i know we should make reservations and
i thought that since you were not
there last time lauren it we should
probably keep it that way okay that
feels like it
just know
that's the group just jailed no no
no i totally get that i don't
agree with betsy though yeah but just
czar okay and we got all my
random okay scout betsy coming but not
me great alright but we want mike
to come oh okay so i can
still make money so much so mike
and betsy that's a combo so micah
christmas you gotta have em yeah love
betsy betsy's the best um we should
make reservations that's the one fun thing
that's christmas is when you go somewhere
and people do things for you yeah
you gotta pay them but when you
have to do things for other people
oh sky high screw you are a
scrooge yeah janice
oh yeah you're gonna what if you
got seriously if you got visited by
a ghost would change your mind about
anything about it okay only about the
existence of ghost goes that number one
absolutely yeah but like with literally had
your ghost of past present and future
come i think you you'd be pretty
fuckin weirdo and you'd be you'd be
pretty much but put
put on when she goes a dream
unless you were like oh i'm definitely
asleep or oh i don't know i
watched him dudley christian and watched a
muppet christmas carol yeah i remember remit
did you ever watch the song i
said they cut out that i read
that big article about i think i
did the children factories
but the but the some of those
ghosts like the which one is it
that's so creepy that like sort of
creepy probably future yeah i didn't because
i never really seen that movie i've
seen maybe you've never seen any christmas
carol adaptation know i've never really seen
the muppets muppet one maybe once before
you would know i've never seen it
either you would know the future goes
just is the creepiest if you've ever
seen any other just a way that
it was made the puppet is what
i'm talking about not the idea of
it so the construction of the puppet
yeah the the vision that they've had
for what the puppet was because yeah
i've seen christmas carol is one hundred
times like a hundred times
seen it i've seen ample and onstage
a hundred times so leave women scott
you have to believe women i've seen
a hundred times end of story
i was in a one hundred times
i think you were well i mean
i was i did like well of
it well we had a run at
christmas and we didn't want a hundred
times in december
it was exhausting
somebody like saying hello you'd have three
a day every day for the month
plus more i mean we did eight
a week so at least it was
either eight or ten weeks that does
not equal a hundred there's no way
that adds up to one hundred alright
asked me two months say it was
ten a week for a now it's
two that's eighty yeah alright so you
i lied so you lied eighties down
there i got there in august and
what was our error her sing and
i think we i think it started
playing and like right after halloween and
you're bob cratchit i was fred and
oh friend scrooge and young scrooge okay
yeah wow big part who is good
and that's where i met
at my leyva barbuda oh that when
you oh my god i haven't heard
that name in a million years this
league soccer match
matter malaysia was a ah an actress
that we knew way back in the
day we were all like part of
a big um circle of friends and
she was roommates with the hey man
hey marie november and melissa
apparently remember she was roommates with karen
kilgour aref for a while they lived
caring cheers from the airport because malaysia
was like hey my friend needs a
my friend is moving here from satanism
oliva your girlfriend no no no no
no we were friends um but she
she got me into comedies so because
she knew mere mary lynn and karen
coca
i've never once wow like she was
like hey you should do comedy at
the comedy store so she put did
you did you did comedy the comedy
store that's where the comedy the comedy
show
those were the weekly show was that
that where i started yeah yeah windows
ninety five but it was ninety which
it was nineteen ninety five and it
was called windows ninety five for the
next year so i believe that was
marilyn that's kevin craig anton i think
hosted that ah c j put it
succeed and say gee j c j
hosted it with maryland okay well when
i started doing it i
just i just remember
these craig and and ah marilyn sang
some song
and i can't remember what the song
was i just remember the tune because
then i started singing to mary lynn
windows ninety five windows ninety five yo
my baby don't be maybe windows ninety
five and then she started opening the
show with with i remember they would
go windows ninety five windows
and they would dance around st saying
windows ninety five it was i mean
when it was at the comedy store
no one cared because no one from
the comedy store gave a shit but
then when it moved i was in
the belly room upstairs yeah when it
moved to bars then it was bad
because the the bar owners and the
people in the bar would be looking
at going there and what why are
they doing this i'm a sports so
what did you do in that
ah friend of stand i did a
sketch the first time i did it
and went over really well so they
said ah come back in two weeks
and then i did it in two
weeks and that one did really well
and then c j and marilyn were
very nice to say hey you can
do this whenever you want cool yeah
it was very cool and that's where
i got to know everyone i had
sort of meh
but that was where i got to
know all ah a young paul f
tompkins that's right that's right marilyn was
just on doughboys and she was very
funny and i have to listen to
that it was nice because she's in
that movie with mitch
oh that's right yeah oh great yeah
oh awesome i like what you're doing
what restaurant to do um hold on
i gotta think about this girl the
most of the day your memory palace
lauren go into your memory like where
it was i'd make her head law
she's my mom come my way
okay i know it and hey man
your location didn't have i was auntie
anne's yeah edgy ads oh fantastic fantastic
ah yeah they go to the airport
no but but she went to one
that had like none of the good
toppings we should start reviewing restroom
it's on the show yeah let's do
it when i went to men cheese
today and you had your men cheese
today
alright being your men cheese i went
to mentees and um you know the
ice cream place yeah it's a fro-yo
place and in i've lately been having
a craving for some original tart okay
oh and i've been going there kind
of like regularly but i went to
one that i haven't been to and
they
the covert protocols with these places just
it just is such a bummer like
i got i walked in there and
the woman like everything looked like it
was open for me to do it
myself but the woman was like i
have to do it but she seemed
really sad about it and then
i told her what i want but
that's like it would be a cool
job to have a bookstore just stuff
i can't
all the um i think bookstores are
nostalgic okay but all jobs suck i
understand that as carrot top one said
work socks i understand right mine
but anyways they have all the toppings
in little plastic containers and she just
like collected the ones i wanted it
and i like really together later you
don't get with just like put them
on yourself and then they do it
by weight anymore no no it's all
just based on how many toppings you
get and it just and then it
also feels like it feels like covert
you know i mean like it's like
yeah i feel like there's something else
now back to what the way it
was but the other men cheese they
do they put all the toppings on
for you so i didn't know why
this meant she's put them in a
little buckets and all this shit i
don't know look i just missed the
before and i want to go back
to how wow to get back but
you know this is the future this
is what it's like now
it's just like it's just like well
what movies we saw of of what
the future would be everything's in a
little container and that's food now
would you paul would you if you
were on a space ship like the
enterprise sure to for example who would
you like to eat from the food
replicators or would you say no i
would prefer to eat real food daily
here's the thing wait
specifically real food daily yes and only
read your replicator every time
what is daily rule it's a vegan
restaurant oh yeah totally familiar um i
knew what that is here's the thing
the only people that ever come plain
ramen the only people that have many
did some familiar to people like star
trek that ever complained about the replicators
are people who have never encountered one
before
or they're like so incredibly old or
something well so what's a replicator the
replicator just makes me feel like like
a microwave but instead of heating something
up it just makes whatever you want
yes and that sounds good it just
makes it appear but you never hear
like the people on the enterprise saying
oh this foods this fake food sucks
i feel like occasionally there's someone going
like ah it's
it's not the same in the replicator
mostly they say that about booze but
they do say it about booze but
then like if if there's ever a
character like the chief of or not
chief but the deep space nine who
like likes to cook these oh no
you gotta do it yourself it's not
the same in the yeah yeah i
know but that's the they just do
that when they when it's
convenient for them to do that you
know if they made replicators here on
earth would you like say it tasted
fine
and you were like it's nine percent
difference but it's fine what's the like
vitamin quality and all good everything good
like why would i not have that
but wait how often would you eat
with it would you be every day
l meals even a nine percent different
every day every day all meals
so i i could go my little
microwave when i go
working you know whatever and then it
makes it i mean i don't know
if it would do the burger king
brand with vitamins
no i pick that so i'd be
like you'd probably say like burger you'd
probably have to say like smashburger with
this and this with earth burger ah
eleven nike eighty nine earth burger from
huh
oh joerger paw helm how long did
you review your star trek podcasts and
character like a million episodes that show
ah yeah but it's not it's not
a waffle on podcast um it's not
based on the season or anything exactly
yeah it's just it's it's a umbrella
trek is the umbrella um topic but
we talk about all kinds of stuff
so it's
not tied to a specific series yeah
um and we're we're gonna do a
third season where i'm very i'm trying
to turn the show into that show
by talking about star trek on it
every other episode
alright lauren i bet of all are
you are you generally not into sci-fi
stuff at all or is it there
are are there some things that that
period have to be like a baby
switched vials with a nine-year-old for you
they're just totally science-fiction there's some things
i liked that are kind of that
fall into that like i love black
mirror that's like sci-fi
and like i'm like a body switching
sci-fi ball because it has to be
based on science doesn't it sometimes they
can base that's magic well is what
they suffer through a wormhole and suddenly
these yard y'all wormhole ya
yeah the go in the wormhole y'all
did
i'm i'm in the fly the remake
of the fly with jeff goldblum ah
he gets mixed up with the fly
but in the original there was a
little so in the original the fly
there was a guy with a big
fly head and then there was a
little fly with a little guy ahead
yes i'll go in
in their ebay gives a little bit
funny jeff goldblum said was that a
little fly it would be like that
s l sketch i saw recently like
back in i think it was october
november um where there was a fly
on the vice president's head wow because
you knew what they're doing there is
their lampoon
tuning how it really did happen there
like we gotta talk about this because
people saw it happen people thought and
we gotta make them see it again
people said hey look am i nuts
shouldn't have been like a worm or
something just make it something else
and yes it helps get yeah they
were naked ladies like nike says it
has a fly on his head during
the debate yeah noone fresno you're like
how are they gonna lampoon this suddenly
it's like hey mike pence you have
a worm on your head
i like this idea like like doing
a parody of real life yeah like
kick like i don't need to know
exactly what happened i saw that i
want to see a worm on his
head yes a sketch about the titanic
but it's made out of ice and
crashes into a bit woodburn ore he
has like a squirrel on his head
and everyone's like the fuck
and it just sitting there and then
it's like yeah i mean i understand
how people would be like to fuck
if a shark has a flaw that
is like other woodland animals yeah just
to go like oh that word data
but i think it's what i think
flies what about you like in cinderella
when the flies help or make them
now that would be good it would
be good that would be good to
fly meets cinderella that would be like
if cinderella if you did like a
parody a cinderella she was like in
a garbage can finally they're going to
parody cinderella have you heard about this
i'd love to see her in a
garbage can yeah i'd put her in
there right now i don't remind see
ooh
yeah that reminds me of when neil
and paul paul russ and neil campbell
um not neil armstrong and paul newman
i went to go see their ah
ah i think a sketch show that
they were rehearsing or maybe i was
going to be in it or something
like that and they did a james
bond sketch and they they years later
they were like it was so funny
when you said to us finally james
bond is being parodied
so funny
they loved it when i would insult
them
oh okay yeah is that your perception
yeah you don't think they're being sarcastic
oh loved it
but neil did he love it too
i don't know he's inscrutable will never
go tar to read it's hard to
read truly is hard to read neil
who knows what's going on with that
guy i saw him eat like a
bowl of chocolate pudding in his face
never chocolate buddy no but the mouth
please did you say
first you say then you do it
and wonder when he'll pass out pass
on
to his reward
the gates of heaven st peter's like
bo
i'm waiting for you do i think
the sweet impression of you do you
think st peter calls you by your
first name when you go to heaven
if you're famous does he have to
check the only of your famous
yeah it's kinda like that overly familiar
thing of like oh to bill
you got it
podcast famous though
but he he must have in the
book there must be everybody's first n
last name i mean probably male first
names yeah tiny middle on security with
what's going on these days
awoke
oh hey listening to show some whoa
alright
we have to take a break bye
for now cya
and we're back hi i'm back too
i would like to mention that i
am back i would like to mention
that i'm back and we see we
need a little container yum yum yum
when we do the show finally together
again we should do it back-to-back
ah what do you mean like we
don't look at each other yeah in
a tree in a trio of back-to-back
where we don't see each other you
know so that we can keep an
eye out so we drew to see
each other oh keep an eye out
for insurance now you're talking why don't
we do a meerkat sour one of
us is above the horizon and looking
out for predators the other two are
hunkered down behind the hill yeah i'm
gonna be on the lookout
your neighbor who's mad at you i
don't know if the neighbors matter if
he's a listener hey we love you
what if he is a listener he
doesn't make the connection between you and
the show and the weirdos and oh
my god thank you along with my
stupid neighbour now i'm going to relax
with my favorite podcast
oh i really really do the story
the other side of it well duh
so mad at us and we were
recording his favorite show
i'm probably a bad neighbor who knows
now i don't think you are basing
that on who have no idea
what do you do that's good wow
because if you're not good you're bad
is keep yourself it keeps it well
keep to myself i don't go dog
man anyone's doors are real killer i
don't say like hey man my hair
man my plants
hey on my plants need more sun
man
and what would your neighbor have just
say both
i don't know how i'm gonna need
you to move your houseman my plan
is kicking a sudden man
like
we talking
so doing that voice here for everyone
i know we've got our differences matter
but lemme alright i'll turn down the
music that if you
hey man i know we never met
before but can you move your house
my plants get some sunlight
ah by the way coin can we
talk about
lord did i were commiserating the other
day and paul you your die often
dreamliner on the text chain but about
the descriptions of the videos
i love them wait i got read
some of theirs so there's no we
just us
he's consistent yeah there's this is the
zone map says show couldn't figure it
but we did discuss naps absolutely okay
let me just go back to yeah
scott paul lauren discuss easter
yeah already i'm out if i saw
that i'd be out immediately
funny story their quarantine phases and celebrities
they could be friends with
why stop listening to this show why
we're getting the god paul lorne discuss
their dreams monopoly and
ship clips
yeah cool yeah why chip
ah yeah la loi this ghost clones
gender reveal parties and unnecessary holidays i
mean i want actually sounds okay it's
interesting adam hammill yeah okay um just
got porn discuss driving murder
murder drag thing it's funny murder mystery
dinner theme what did we talk about
town whenever we could talk about when
it came to driving do we do
it
joshua said he's very proud of these
yeah yeah okay they are very norm
core he's trying to make them yeah
boring sounding as pop pop ska paul
now and just got road rage garden
gnomes and stovepipe
ah but here's what he's what oh
lordy okay is
hell no
woof woof oh wait i gotta go
sees me one second oh okay
alright alright scott alright what's up
i mean we can mention that she
doesn't have a dog we gotta mention
this
now she's talking just talking to her
imaginary dog she's saying i didn't know
you were coming home she thinks the
dog has a job what kind of
job does she think this dog who's
kind of job does she think it's
just dog guys i don't understand anyway
fun here's what i'll say about the
the mansion this about the the the
descriptions i think they're great because they
don't
give any jokes away and sometimes descriptions
for podcasts will give away things that
are like why now if it's frustrating
to me i agree i agree no
it's nice it's nice to have no
idea what's going to happen but they
do make me laugh i now am
in tariff any layer on just like
here here's what i'm like less less
this guy paul morin discuss
laurens topics sesame sesame street and the
electric sli it's just ah just like
is this show three minutes ah running
time must be a mistake maybe they
just record a lot of dead air
so putting
and i think it was episode we
discuss other episodes
they discussed episode descriptions as this one
is the scott poem lauren discuss fast
food bad haircuts and prank calls and
then we have scott following because dining
out postcode naps and mariah
mariah and we're all married yeah what
do i mean i don't know anything
about ryan's and like one friend is
honored
no one friend is a lie
why knowing the dwan grinding thing
ah there should be like this one
where we discuss billie eilish star trek
and gray hair
all of the same dogs know this
is the one that really got me
when i texted scott scott paul lorne
discuss having lots of siblings beanie babies
and combs
holmes what did we say about combs
yeah that really made me laugh there
should be a ray of fur friends
oh um you can say you just
want to make friends on there but
you know what i mean like i
think episode they're all lying though yeah
of course somebody ending that occur also
like saying basically
fuck filth
ah
skills things things i'd like to
the way to total filth you want
an app more for making friends with
guys yeah there should be a like
a right and not facebook not my
space just like oh you swipe through
and go this this dude looks cool
yeah we should we should go to
a ball game together is boring
ah
see this is how the show works
i throw out an idea that i
obviously don't believe
for comedy you may right and then
insults me and i take it
hi i'm lauren laughs i think it's
a good name for the app it's
really funny
yeah
this is the latest that we've ever
recorded maybe well except for a live
episode yeah it's like alright just measure
dark almost solely that the sun is
still beaming through
ah
oh if we can talk about i
did jokingly um talk about with josh
we should do a slumber party episode
where we were twit we locked the
door wrong
q would we run out of things
to talk about i mean i feel
like we do on this i mean
guitar for twenty four hours just the
three of us know we can talk
about chrome's paul i mean doughboys just
did it but yeah but they had
guests know i know we'd have to
we we could never have a guess
we'd have to do restaurant roundup well
yeah we have to start meaning absolutely
of course my trends
those trends lawrence topics you would have
to know how they repay down again
yeah i mean it can have a
new topic what you're bringing in another
time oh okay i tug i two
in a
i think you should be able to
revisit old topics yeah yeah yeah as
if they're new yeah so we we
have josh compile a list of all
the boring us shit we've already talked
about and then we just talk about
those things what if we have the
same terry okay let's talk about combs
though because i don't remember talking about
colmes i do want to get serious
about combs i used to go in
every picture day i remember that we
know
oh this is that what we talked
about i think that's what we talked
about and i think do we talk
about the switchblade i don't remember ever
sharing that with another living soul i
used to get whenever i feel like
that rings a bell for me that
zombie yeah and i think i may
have talked about how it was a
popular birthday gift i'll tell you we're
like what yeah or something do you
use comes now
no i use a horse comb i'm
a brush man
what's a horse karaj man it's ah
it's one of those it's like circular
and has a bunch of spikes oh
that's switched over that it was it's
really good for my hair obviously not
right now because i you think you're
here to reg lots of body lately
i've noticed that while it's longer than
the i got one of those covert
haircuts on my porch and and got
to
we're gonna follow up on a haircut
where she was like how's it going
out hey did you hear start to
grow again no did did you like
your haircut
joe box i'm now i feel like
i've i feel like you know in
the moment you say it you always
say it because you always say because
you're there in the moment but it
was nice to receive a text the
next day like will did you like
it though like is still looking yeah
i think there's like it's such a
hard thing for me at least when
i get a haircut and i i
kind
i don't like it but i'm like
i i know it's gonna look better
when i wash it and stuff and
i like i don't i don't like
how they styled it or whatever exactly
and then i feel like self-conscious and
weird and then i leave and i'm
like i don't even know who i
am anymore and then sometimes i'll see
pictures of myself with my haircut at
like some event or something that i
went to it after i'm like it's
not even me
me like this even looks like me
when someone does my hair it's like
just like the way that it is
when it just been freshly cut and
done it's a whole different thing i
remember it very reward you there was
like we moved onto haircuts by the
way from combs that just well there
was only so much to say about
comes there was a barber doodle that
used to like put stuff in my
hair after the hair
cut without telling me he was gonna
do that like also put a bunch
of gel in there i'm like what
the fuck your shadow i don't look
like this scott thinks it was come
like sadat you're you're like like there's
something about mary sort of situation no
like that dentist who is doing it
while it's it's not a good story
i tend to look at lawrence look
at oh well we talked about topics
next day so i'm going dentist come
ah tell us what comes up some
story to come story okay drilled at
the dentist sex denton rural column j
jailing out this is this dentist tales
the legend of the common born
i just thought i'd tell you off
my job three form i just read
porn
so i just i don't want to
see this iconic in in the description
but i just want to say i
just learned something i could just put
the most random things together just and
and read a story about it someone
that was just
i'm dumb i was expecting them him
i was expecting to find that i
thought if anything is around audio random
man why don't but i don't know
but i put story that's well there
you go that's why i'm doing so
but put squirt in there no come
on
if it were done to sexual assault
there's too many things that will come
up yeah really yeah
there was a story of a dentist
that impregnated women right oh when they
were out yeah yeah yeah god even
sick cose we don't know you wouldn't
have gotten pregnant is that noise lawrence
computer his
yeah it's so weird how it does
that but my mic doesn't appear to
be picking is your computer making a
pizza and make a pimp says ah
man my goodness would you say you
eat that you if you were in
italy you would eat that pizza circling
back like you made italy you would
eat that pizza ye
yes or no even if there was
a pizza restaurant right next door that
was delicious even if the robot had
hands and he didn't know wash i
think i would try it like as
one of those sort of random things
in the middle of the day late
night saying you know but i but
the best food ever isn't italy to
be it would feel silly to be
getting a pizza vending machine but also
when you're
traveling in other countries it's like really
fun to have vending machine food because
it's different i'm just saying that we
were on tour and remember all the
times that we've been out of luck
because every restaurant is closed yeah how
else really working out the hotel how
to how to pizza machine that would
be awesome that would be kind of
hang that it will never happen in
america because we can't be trusted
with a pizza robot what do you
mean because they will use it for
verb war they would never put a
pizza making vending machine on the street
anywhere and i feel like don't think
that would just never happen because we
were just told why they put redbox
in front of seven eleven do they
still yeah i think i don't know
i haven't been to redbox is very
good like a dvd way to measure
yourself
you can measure yourself i go to
seven eleven sell toys when you walk
in because there's that that numbers on
the side that are like yeah how
much you've grown since you came here
last exactly
how would i know i write my
name next in my eyes because they're
so used to getting rob scott they
have a height marker on the bar
so i think that's interesting so that
when is that way when you rob
a seven eleven year like get on
the ground and count to one hundred
until i leave on a stick to
and you tell the camera don't look
at me don't you fucking look at
me
yeah i don't like i don't like
to face
it's a reference to this boy's life
oh okay yeah very terrible referendum which
boy tobias boy yeah i'm sure we've
talked about this when you have things
about this boy's life have i felt
maybe you and i have i don't
know you're wanting i'm gonna give you
a topic that we've never ever seen
a sunday sick
who's got a story about a frog
fraud oh i do this is like
if i was a psychic and ah
like ah i like a group of
people i feel like someone here got
a story about a frog i'm getting
a g over here yeah i feel
like i've told it before well what
is your frog story yeah but extremes
give us the highlights oh well that
that story did i tell you that
one about the frog
falling on me yeah twice yeah okay
so but i did i tell you
the reason why i screamed is because
when i scared because i'm just a
euro but when i was twelve i've
i've told you about one of my
first jobs delivering the orange county register
that's written i was a paper boy
and um i used to deliver at
the apartments on one neat huh
and couldn't be less germinate into the
story or one eight in orange that's
where it was oh thank god and
so i so that was one of
my places the whole apartment complex i
had to deliver the dam and one
day
i don't know what happened but i
went into the i was riding my
bike i went into the apartment complex
and i was attacked by hundreds of
frogs
whites
if it was i've never seen ground
anything like it ever since they're on
the ground jumping out everywhere they it
was not an apartment complex that had
frogs all the time but one day
i don't know if it just rained
or something but hundreds of frogs they
were covering the sidewalk you couldn't ride
your bike
like they were just covering every side
i was how did you not see
and or hear them before you got
up there i mean did i hear
a ribbit once or twice as i
was writing my book bike up to
the apartment complex sure you didn't hear
like a chorus of two hundred rabbits
it was the i've i don't know
what it is
i've never seen anything like it it
was so nuts it was like magnolia
it's like magnolia or something like i
was gonna say fucking everywhere and jumping
out at me and jumping on me
and stuff and so it gave me
like a frog phobia wow oh i
don't like that for you yeah so
when that frog so ya cool up
laps and winning that
frog frog jumping on me right i
can't remember if this is a story
that we just have talked about paul
but no i don't think i've heard
this when we went to yosemite oh
wait this is another story yeah so
sorry all for scott's lily pad this
is where he tells all the sad
stories he has from one to the
next we went to we went to
yosemite and the law
long and short of it is i
opened the front door one day and
a frog jumped on my hand that
was on the doorknob open how big
of a frog are we talking about
ah probably in not incredibly big probably
silver dollar
okay okay so not the biggest frog
in the world just like a silver
dollar tiny frog and landed on my
i was opening the door landed on
my hand i looked at it and
let out apparently according to klopp a
scream that she thought a woman was
being terrorized outside
and i brian took it off
and then went inside and told her
what had happened and she laughed at
me and then the next day i
came back to the apartment that were
not apartment but the house we were
renting i turned the doorknob again and
the same frog jumped on my hand
to see crossing guard the sog and
so what i figured out was the
frogs like home or something
it was right above the doorknob and
if you like turn the doorknob it
would it would make vibrations or something
where he would or would get scared
into a jump down oh right huh
my god so maybe william of course
holos it maybe it was two frogs
and you helped them get down from
a place they couldn't get down from
this true okay that's they were like
ok at least we kinda halfway
a yeah um can i say that
i while i don't think it's it's
great that cool op laughs at you
and your fears you did take her
to several terror events when you were
dating younger guys whether she told you
she did not like that guy with
butter oh the past close but a
devil mask
you had to join the devil that
man was or you did by the
devils you always use the devil bets
to oh you know ah you're an
interesting couple sure yeah hey when we
went on vacation recently did i use
the devil mask ever as far as
you know not as far as i
do but on your bag every day
i'm terrible sleep though
so i feel like humidity and i
think i may have done it i'm
do you ever frog story lauren um
i don't really have one well i
mean i dissected a frog in school
like oh so did i yeah so
great winner when when are they going
to stop doing that it's right well
did you also dissect a pig yeah
a windy baby would be big and
we did horeb
oh the pig is the pig is
really fucked up because it's like very
human feeling yeah yeah um but i
will the reason i thought of frogs
is because this morning the first thing
i looked at my phone when i
woke up was tick tock my friend
sent me and it was the most
disgusting thing i've ever seen
and it was this frog
someone's like she's filming her pool and
there's like the string of like two
black strings a really long going like
the middle of the pool to this
stairs and on the stairs there's this
frog and it's like dead and it
has these strings command was ass and
then she starts pulling on them oh
and then the frogs are it's like
coming back to life a little bit
so she takes it out and she
puts it on
like a log and she starts pulling
the strings with gloves on now
and it's so gross
and then it goes on it goes
on for a long time and she
doesn't know what it is and then
she has these two follow up videos
and there's all these people commenting and
basically it was this poisonous cane frog
or something and it was having babies
and they're poisonous and they are toxic
to humans and dogs or whatever i
don't know she had dogs they were
people were worried that the dog was
gonna eat
eat a frog or something
anyway it was the sickest thing i've
ever seen and it was like seven
thirty am i was like this is
how you start my fucking day with
this starter to start my day
she sent it to me huh and
that was my day way who said
to to the woman my friend mariah
smith i'm alright i don't do that
oh send that bad early notion that
that early that's night was really harrowing
it sounds truly disgusting it honestly was
sick as hell wow
of paul any rock stories before we
go to break man i wish herrmann
my wish man i wish i like
to rock someday man i'd love to
see a frog i've never seen a
rock in my life man what's up
like a mannequin from all right well
let's let's take a break then and
we'll come back with a reacher okay
and we're back hi we're back high
it's time for three cheer this one
is called hitting the post we've done
it once before and everyone loved it
so much that we're gonna do it
again
please cut
yeah
this was submitted by john combat who
credits dave shameka from stop podcasting yourself
for the idea one person chooses a
song and plays it from their phone
without saying what it is another person
has to improvise over the beginning of
the song as a radio host right
up until the lyrics start the closer
the improviser times the natural end of
their monologue to the beginning of the
lyrics the better if the improviser steps
in
lyrics they lose so let's do it
who wants to go first
i'll i'll play the song if great
huh
yeah paul you wanna go oh i
forgot we play the song for other
people right yeah yeah ah yeah i'll
go first yeah okay here we go
fly one five we got it coming
down it's almost traffic time and that's
when the zombies come out so everybody
be sure to hide under your bed
because you will not live to see
the morning but if you do be
sure to enter our contest if you
are the thirty
loud pretty good that was the song
was that broken by depeche mode
broken spanish mood i'll play a song
first got
here we go stay ready
well my mother-in-law's real bats she's visiting
us all weekend long and all i
really want to do is drop her
off the face of the earth if
you have any suggestions please call me
here at the ready to breathe me
anymore
shit sleep slow do you sleep you
say in my volume all the way
up ooh ooh i know i'll play
song forlorn you ready okay
to to to the the the
and once again we are live from
great america all summer long we're bringing
the hits from under the roller coasters
if y'all wanna get ready get a
good ca kinda cool to get a
ticket
ah so well knowing that you knew
how to do it i discourse the
immortal you make my dreams come true
by philly's own hollow notes philly zone
here we go ready paul yes
we're looking at eighty nine degrees for
the rest of the year that's right
i just heard from the weather people
and they have sealed it at eighty
nine so get ready to take off
your jacket a hand roll up your
sleeves because it's going to be pretty
pleasant out there
and i love
and i think about you every night
please don't leave me
i'm talking to one person out there
and she knows who she is
oh yeah that was good well i
wonder by the smiths oh my
okay
okay this is now oh it's me
that's you who that you
okay i'm ready
sometimes i get a phone call and
i don't know who it is and
so i pick up the phone and
i say hello grandma is this you
and it's never heard but it always
ends up being a really interesting person
that i love to talk to and
i've made a lot of new friends
this way so grandma fifty shot once
so great
ma
the end that was cheerleader by omi
right loughran here we go
the ghost came back everyone i want
you to know he's back and he
is still living in the home with
me but i'm doing everything i can
get rid of him we've got a
ghostbuster coming back on the show next
week to give me a nice long
interview and hopefully get me out of
this mess once again i can't wait
to meet that nice person who's going
to make my life better
once and for all that is the
person who will help me is a
ghostbuster i look you know and i'm
sorry i can tell you guys about
this stuff but if you guys are
my friends
pretty good yeah tuesday morning by the
pogues pogues alright one more paul here
we go ready yeah
hey everybody are you still having that
same dream that we've all been having
i know our water has been poisoned
i just found out because my uncle
works for the government i can't say
in what branch okay he's a mail
carrier
oreo speedwagon don't let him go lio
what a fun game i knew one
more yes i thought we were doing
one round yeah okay scott
you know sometimes i'll take a look
at old pictures and i'll say to
myself hey who is that cool guy
never really grew up and then i'll
realize wait a minute no it's me
and i did grow up anyway this
kind of ties into the song and
why i want to play for all
you listeners out there never grow up
always be the young guy that you
see in those old pictures
because this is the songs it's
that was circle the drain by soccer
mommy soccer mommy soccer bali that's a
fun name wellesley law rather have going
to get one for laura in here
okay okay
oh right
e yeah okay
as one apologize for my previous guest
was this network does not stand by
any of the things that were just
said i'm not previous segment in fact
were adamantly opposed to them and um
i just think that out that is
no reflection of me or any of
my cohosts what that man just came
in here and said we actually don't
know who that was but we're working
on getting him out of the building
hopefully
before we all get attacked we'll see
what happens already then have a good
day oh look
i was late on that was a
cover of the chain by the high
women all the high women oh it's
very much like the original i know
it's a pretty faithful cover yeah you're
allowed women
well guys that was fun it really
was that was fun
very hard not to play that game
every time i know it's a fun
game yeah it really is it rose
well what is it here whatever we'll
talk about next time yeah what a
wind down save up your save up
your topics guy save up your topics
been a blast i love this episode
i hope to catch y'all next week
i have just as much
energy now as i did when i
started recording i'm having a great time
all the time
remember our t-shirts or whatever we oh
yeah shirts go to wag pawed sweet
home go to the store and get
a little get a little crook we
got shyam gochujang cuckoos robo we have
some ah we have another teacher in
the works that i
are very curious to see who will
buy it me too we want to
swim on you we want to a
new baby show us the picture okay
we want to see restitution okay shows
take a picture and show the shape
just take a cab published to picture
insurance just take a picture and show
us please click show so please do
it please do it please
alright we'll see you next time bye
bye-bye
uh