nice to see
oh my glitter notice that i was
hooting like a little owl like an
i actually did hear what an outlet
now let's yeah i was actually just
going to plug a plug into because
he made a turkey noise what medea
plugs are the alec her things tom
from ah frannie my my dog
i had some issues last week oh
no and i had to give her
a bland diet and i was just
sad to give her now jon jones
and amory she loves indian food she
loves it but i had to yeah
it's calming down no spice yet mild
spice she just want chili pepper i
gotta make her
some like boiled chicken and some like
and rice and some like um ground
turkey was an option so i did
that and i'm telling you the ground
turkey when i open up that hierarchs
it couldn't smell more like a fart
if it tried it is the gross
ground turkey in general smells like i
don't even want particular i don't know
because i've never made ground turkey i
don't so i don't you've never ground
your own turkey nah no i haven't
you don't even have a grinder in
your house yeah you're not even on
grinder now you're not any lower sing
a bunch of birds yeah i know
but anyway it smells so fucking gross
just but i think thanks for that
update okay i want i just had
to share that i've an updo
eight as well okay i can't whistle
anymore anymore what you mean by such
it here i read this
you're just you're here just to this
does yes
today i was called upon ah to
whistle in a voice recording and when
i went to do it i you
don't make the sound of whistler's whistle
shy this is like my bird trauma
oh yeah yeah that's the best but
that is not good yeah you're not
good i used to use fabled yeah
yeah yeah what do you think change
do you need more wickedness in your
mouth oh um i don't know i
don't know what it is my mouth
does not feel dry well let me
put something in there yeah wow that's
how you treat my update yeah so
oh oh i come to you with
an update about music i can
make with my mouth
just like biz markie
i was whistling the brady bunch theme
for holly and she was loving it
really yeah she really liked to know
what did it michelle ah everybody loves
her response she was just so excited
that she was trying to whistle to
oh yes yes like oh we all
can you hawk a look and get
like
like really wet in there that's serious
just just be like what and then
go
wait
oof because i have too much bitmap
everyone's wild get into a great groove
in the shower where i'd like my
whistling is really loud and you will
in the shower sometimes after i started
me to do such a thing after
i saw west side story for some
reason i think i was whistling cool
like for half an hour and it
just sounded time it sounded so good
so long
time to whistle also that's a long
shower i was like this is professional
great well no i took it longer
because i was like this whistling is
too good you stayed in the shower
because you enjoying your whistling choice on
someone who sticks are just were a
perpetual drought
look this was after the big rainfall
oh man my shower was collected when
the raid and you had buckets all
at your feet like to water your
plants you may even a rain barrel
yeah
um i have to issue a correction
or upto right yeah but i was
informed by a very kind listener and
let me tell you just see your
list if you're a listener you can
be kind when you speak to us
online sure and many of you are
um everyone's smiles so most of our
most of our pigs are wonderful yeah
i love our beautiful little guys out
there yeah
um someone told me that the food
instagram that i plugged in the last
episode is one that i follow to
learn about what i should do oh
no they're racist the their their antivaccine
and yeah yeah there which which faxes
um oh i think it's just mumps
oh okay okay yeah i'm kind of
up to you
um but no i ah they said
that i probably wouldn't align with the
values of this person and in truth
i don't they also suggested a different
food thing to follow i'm not going
to plug that one because i don't
even know you got that's a good
one exactly you have to vet these
and yes some awful reason yourself now
sir all i was really getting out
of that account was like you
no don't buy doritos buy these chips
if you want to have a healthy
day or whatever you know what go
ahead plug it ya know i'm not
good i mean it's i be sick
when you plug doritos well i love
the stuff doritos all right has flawless
politics um look and if we were
gonna get into it the eminem
ems the imams they're obviously back look
look look
lauryn are you embarrassed i'm actually not
because i've got no regrets i don't
know no i remember yeah i don't
really i don't care and i did
fall further little trick and we talked
about this paul we are both on
tv i say with ashley rae great
fun tv podcast we're talking about all
the super bowl commercials if you wanna
hear that you all check it out
yeah all three hundred and every single
one i honestly think we tend to
talk about the upfield one twice seventy
five percent there were three good felts
there were three while three spots that
i saw i think i only saw
two i only saw one and i
maybe there's only two i don't know
but i saw i miss one that
was longer you saw an extended cut
so farage a funny line in it
about cultural approach
preach oh no i've seen that one
the one but the night was the
long one maybe there was a short
there was definitely short one where there
like an garfield or what's the name
garfield read goodfellow commercial ah go and
he goes hi i'm greg and then
they cut it then there was a
wound or the other so i was
confused that wasn't a local commercial i
know that was local site and like
everyone i'm sure yeah wow
yeah it seemed that yeah yeah yeah
but anyways the imams are back um
go ooh appropriate
are you buying for a role next
month so you got a good build
i worked with you once you did
i i was on the ouch that
terrible show you did result oh he
did read i as well he yeah
because you'd take over no using here
he was the original i think andy
levy was the writer i'm not sure
but greg greg gut feld was
the host okay and strangely enough i
was booked on with gavin mcinnes
creator ruby road politics aligning
there's a funny story one clip out
there of me on who go on
to show with these two enjoy hoo
boy well alright also be the least
funny person in the room
it was so funny because my i
think my p r person just like
sold it to me like hey there's
to show that we book a lot
of comedians on it's on fox is
that okay i was like yeah i
don't care like thinking it was fox
fox whatever this is how disgusting comedians
are because they really will like anything
it doesn't matter what please get me
on tv
my quest for fame the whole eisele
will be filled
um yeah well speaking of that i
i can't say what it is yet
but i will be on a game
show again oh very excited wait you
are on i like that you're hearing
yea yeah huh you were on the
pyramid i mean you're literally gonna happen
um
my pyramid never aired i don't know
maybe it's gonna i don't know how
when they air them or what's happening
but i know i don't think it
ever aired if they don't air the
the winners don't get the money that
can't be true that's true it's not
really joe that's because i was winning
also hard for my people i mean
they really gets to me that's a
clause in it and i remember a
friend of mine um one
on a game show anyone like two
hundred and fifty thousand dollars or something
like that and he was just praying
it got on the air and that
they didn't cancel the games it was
one of those nighttime game show easy
he was like god because they don't
get paid unless it actually do think
they have a plan just game game
shows in general to not air a
batch of them i think if a
show
gets cancelled that's their protection in order
to like save money essentially like well
if we got cancelled we're not going
to pay out every single oh but
i don't know if it's cancelled i
i it's kind of funny that it's
like well i was like fuck you
nobody thought yeah i mean i actually
find that astounding um yeah it was
something i
never knew about until like i said
my friend won and then he was
just like yeah you don't get paid
unless ersa did it air it finally
aired things like oh thank god but
it was like one of these i
think it was the game shows that
was like during the millionaire craze yeah
who wants to be a millionaire was
doing so well like a bunch of
competitors that stuff anyway one of these
things where it was like oh my
god if it may get cancelled
it might not i don't remember the
other shows of that era i tried
out the likes of quiz show yeah
i tried out for one but i
don't remember what was called it was
on fox i don't remember i don't
know um i took i went down
into quiz and all i read i
checked huh yeah right
good good folks big conch
look felled we love you you're really
funny good felled we love you guys
have you watched your show no it's
astonishing because the audience he hasn't audience
in studio that's they're not laughing yeah
every joke just like dykes goodfellow we're
not better than you though
it felt were not better than you
know we are i don't even know
what yes i have said oh i
said it on the podcast i'm saying
it here i don't know what that
show is and i i thought the
commercial was local and i'm just learning
and i'm so and gut felt i'm
learning about you i could fill
yeah i'm gonna learn everything i can
learn about you online and get to
know you you know just you're socially
ok here's do you think this is
funny this joke i've noted okay my
pronouns are go fuck slash yourself yeah
yeah like yeah because ah because of
because because everything so woke everything is
woke roseanne
going back thank god and she announced
by saying my pronouns are kiss my
ass pretty good pretty good pretty good
oh wait i'm sure they can million
times you could say yes my ass
said they wanted to kiss my ass
and kiss my ass wanting to go
how it was kiss kiss last kiss
said my said i don't know i'm
already lost so that my ass is
the possessive or the idea that anyone
now would do one of those jokes
because it is yeah it's right but
because there's a there's a community of
people out there who are real
love it every time bad every time
go it's good it really is true
though it's like you can make the
same joke like endless variations on the
same because they will love it yeah
just got aquaman story
your memoir i got felt we love
you and felt we let i'm so
committed to learning all about you and
i'm still will try yeah so you're
the best but that said if god
felt word to call us tomorrow we're
on a plane absolutely we're on this
show to pay respect in new york
we saw
stand on the shoulders of god i
believe it's in new york at least
his last show was yeah man it's
filmed on the ground that's what it
feels like yeah like miles underground
in a missile silo you to claim
down many many layers latter no elevator
we don't yeah we shot no you
shut up underground well that's oh i
was there yeah yeah yeah that was
fun i was it was fun it
was fun right by the airport there
was one a great area
i didn't i don't remember like
somewhere afterward you should you shout would
have been amazing you should go every
day every single day like burbank yeah
you float who've burbank to l a
slow to burbank but you flow to
bring a photobook i know a couple
hundred dollars is cheaper guess yeah because
what's going on with the planes these
days so
many in the going up and dad
are going up going down summer like
going in a straight line yeah some
are completely full summer not yeah it's
crazy like i'm now food chain stuff
that's going on there going up or
they're going down a booty judge
question
ooty judge
booty judge that that guy booty judge
haunt
um when's the last plane ride that
you took you took one recently didn't
you where did you go you go
to chicago i did wear but what
does it go anywhere sooner yeah went
home for christmas that's what it was
yeah yeah i wasn't being up there
in the friendly skies well you know
i saw i saw was that i
saw white puffy clouds that i saw
blue blue blue air
err yeah
um no but here it wasn't me
it was their foes beautiful i'm i
have a couple of trips coming up
that i'm excited about some actual girls
trips oh really yeah okay you're march
and april you know assuming schedules all
work out and everything yeah um magic
my couple places show in vegas i
got to see magic how many girls
i see them dick swinging um one
will just be me an arden and
then another one's birthday trip for my
friend where i think there's i don't
know how many committed to the trip
but there were like seven people invited
and this is a out of town
true yes wow jamie has a yearly
girls trip which i think is very
nice well i heard about it on
your podcast and by the way also
heard the shout out that i'm one
of your listeners and it was like
standing right indeed i am um hey
i thought her trips idea sounded so
nice to go to palm springs every
year yeah and it just seemed like
so so nice to have that tradition
i really i felt that way about
because a bunch of us went out
of town for ah rob pupils bachelor
party a while ago before we got
married
obviously um and it was so fun
and they were like thirty of us
in ohi and just like swimming in
the pool and throwing balls like a
big house or reading house yeah throwing
balls at each other like football you
know like trying to catch a ball
while jumping in the pool oh that
teske social you know and there was
ever
yeah everybody always watching me watching you
yeah watching for managing the daddy lets
me
you're throwing pennies for each other yeah
testicle he's a bomb
but i was like it sucks that
you have to wait for a friend
to get married and you can only
do that like theirs we should have
a brand you don't you don't have
to do that when yeah i like
his retreat every year something like that
oh yeah yeah not but not call
it that yeah now with the same
not robbed no he's the only one
no
call it that because that's the that's
what my church called it oop growing
up the men's retreat
the idea of a bunch of like
christian man getting together like god let's
really talk about our faith guys sometimes
i tell if my yeah right yeah
yeah oh wow yeah well i will
you do about that i looked at
a woman's leg
i was thinking about where i went
to summer camp every year at forest
home and in redwoods california sounds like
a cemetery um no nothing used to
be yes you like it was oh
thank you i'll sneeze over there just
one just had a lot one out
yea okay but um that there were
cabins everywhere except for when
you were caught what ages was it
oh it was it was first through
fifth grade or sixth grade
slipped out in the ground no in
tps in what they called indian village
oh and the place is still around
i wonder if you can still do
that or is it like goodfellow said
cultural appropriation i don't think it's called
tps in the indian what did you
call it what it was called indian
village you can still call things teepees
okay but because what i'm saying if
they have a daughter or your tv
but they have teepees and nobody involved
is an indigenous person doesn't that seem
appropriate like that is appropriation yes okay
like dressing up as a knight and
chainmail i'm saying that's my culture i'm
saying do they
they care
oh indigenous people no no the the
christian oh christian summer climate they don't
know they no no no i um
i when i was when i was
a kid it's a very native american
themed all the time that is true
when i was little we may have
we made like native american like art
in stuff while we were there yeah
when i was little we would too
the y m c a had a
program called indian guides and indian princess
yes and dads and daughters dads and
sons indian guides and dads and daughters
was indian princesses and i mean you
know of course appropriation decide really nice
bonding with fathers and daughters yeah it
was very sweet we would go so
i'd be like all these dads and
all these daughters and you go to
to you go camping or you go
to like ah like there was one
time we went like we all stated
a castle and they're all just bunk
beds and it was weird and then
like there's like a princess who had
bunk beds and a shower things who
even knows who even knows but they
were just weird locations there'd be little
events welcome tobacco and it was really
funny and it was very sweet and
when i think back to that i'm
like i'm
very like touched that like my dad
did that with both extremes yeah this
was we yeah i think he loved
you did these i think i love
you so what about zo of bread
dough
just put your printer
and you're an indian guy so he
was the guide i i i don't
know why but wouldn't that be both
times it would be called because like
the the guy dads and sons is
called indian guy that's just indian guides
yeah the dads and daughters called indian
princess i feel like it is a
guide or i guess
yes my dad is just there but
i feel like this was also indian
guides was also a thing at my
church growing up as well it wasn't
what is it why does the religious
are no i don't know my yeah
let's see why youth m men cd
cooperation a
are you going to say something worse
amen
oh amen it is religious yes young
man cooperation hey man yeah my summer
camp i went to was called st
john neumann but i don't remember there
being any religious aspect to it like
i don't think we i don't think
there's any church service i don't think
there was like grace before meals or
anything it was just a ne
a yeah there was nothing religious with
show look the what activities but i'm
just wondering if the whole place was
religious or not but what was that
what was that fascination with why so
many religious places had like oh let's
make it indian themed native american i
didn't feel like we made a number
of chirps or things i think it
was exciting thing yeah yeah yeah like
romance
fantasizing the outdoors yeah but they could've
made it like pioneers but they were
like yeah let's make it indians because
it's mystical yes
good times we honor them whose way
to honor the native americans so that's
definitely like blackface was honoring some black
people i had somebody make tried to
make that argument to me why years
ago yes yes my god those its
attribute was a tribute to black people
that's psychotic well i mean yeah don't
oh oh nah nah i mean to
be fair no
i guess i could see
why don't we talk about something dumber
oh here's the dome
i don't know if you've done that
you had something like no i just
meant like you know rather than you
know debating appropriation i haven't yet bad
we're not debating it and they were
just discussing i don't think anyone's for
no we're not but what does your
bag new bag because i finally had
to admit after having the you do
you remember my old bag was a
leatherback let's talk about that
and didn't memorize your bag no of
course you memorize it was brown i
could see if you saw every week
for a year
i am familiar having a riser up
here that went down with all you
opening the flop yeah sure and it
was brown leather i have that bag
for i want to say ten fifteen
years and wow happen i finally had
to admit i hate that bag wow
finally oh good for you i but
i liked the way you tell it
so
so much i didn't have the heart
to tell but you went along just
right and i'm good trash i ended
it in the dark and then that's
impressive you did it for so you
use it for so long i want
to do like so bad you didn't
like punctuality the way look let's look
at this bad it's a canvas messenger
slashes so much small what do you
call it stop messenger messenger babe yeah
but it's an
it's not a broader body it's it's
a vertical it's a vertical rectangle so
it's not this i guess you could
call it a merce i don't know
is it do you keep your market
in there yeah
i have several like you one of
my glovebox i have a red markin
for saint patrick's day they said market
ah merkin ah so ah fucking where
did you find yeah at sea i
found it on amazon dot com wow
okay yeah amazing i went looking with
ah specific specifi news canada please sure
i want to look at it here
it goes that's a good amazon guy
it's a good bag i mean it's
you know axed cotton another twenty dollars
and jeff bezos his pocket do you
think he still gets money yeah people
by showing them yeah every day why
wouldn't he just thankful i feel like
he's not part of the company anymore
is that not true i think he
i haven't heard that i don't want
to go on record but i
he is going to happen you gotta
go on deep background gotta go to
court
say it to his face i thought
you weren't allowed there
but let me look it up that's
a good it's a good bag call
congratulations on your new purchase and hope
it makes you feel good but do
you know that feeling of like i
want this thing to work so if
it happens with clothes all the time
yes oh my god yeah but i'm
getting you hold onto a thing you're
like oh it looks so good but
not on me there's stuff in this
very room that i'm like i'm like
yeah can we see no
one user when you when you let
yourself finally throat of every single use
go no no no and i mean
that's her way something yesterday that i
was like oh thank god i finally
did it oh my god what was
i looked at i don't want to
say oh wait can i say something
i was all your i tell ya
she says she
want to say sometimes okay starting to
google is jeff bezos still connected to
amazon the first three things that come
up when yes i've been is jeff
is jeff the killer real
i don't know who just killed
i like ray he's not real oh
my god is jeff probst married and
is jeff dunham married
to one of his puppets
so what are the answers
on all of ah says n slash
a oh my god and then i
pull it just just basis the first
thing comes up is is jeff bezos
a jew jesus i i don't understand
what i wanted to say was i
was doing a big purge and i
was getting rid of a lot of
um like things that we had for
a big plastic things that she outgrew
that i don't like gate that i
never was able to use like anything
someone gave it to me i'm like
okay i was going to put outside
my neighbor has a baby so they
were like oh great they were taking
like a
a bunch of the stuff that we
were parting with that we didn't think
we didn't worry me as well but
yeah but you don't need all my
trash whether we like your note this
is an easy way by the way
we're just getting rid of a lot
of the zero through six oh yeah
there are three to six months oh
i see it happened so fast yeah
well so it was great because i
was like i was holding on to
so many
things thinking maybe i'll want it later
and then just i finally admitted about
a lot of these things i don't
want it but then it was great
because my neighbor was like oh we
could use all this stuff so it
was like it felt very purposeful like
i was agreed i don't need to
have it anymore and you can use
it right now and then do whatever
you want that's my point is we
should only make one of every thing
everything yeah we all just really like
community like wow yeah as a tangent
i just joined this like by purge
cell group helped me mom high and
it's like giving away or selling for
like five dollars like kid stuff and
i'm like so excited about it i'm
like i wanna do more of that
instead of buying all this stuff new
but um i i put outside this
i had this lamp like i had
a set of lamps that i had
kind of keeping forever that i really
didn't have a spot for
is it a nice quality lamp and
is getting kind of dirty and i
was calling out whatever like i just
put it i was kinda just trying
to go just stop holding on to
everything just put it outside someone will
come and take it cause you know
people just going on the street they'll
take if it's good trash and my
fucking neighbor took different neighbor not these
know nothing you know this other guy
took my fucking knee being
he told me he's a junk collector
okay the lamp isn't junk actually kind
of well i'll tell you he and
his son have this business he says
he's always feigning he was standing looking
at my pile of stuff and he
was kind of like i collect junk
so does so and so and so
he's kind of mentioned people on the
street and i don't know them but
he's like they also liked to catch
him so he's like can i have
this canvas is kind of taking comics
down i was like have that do
whatever you want
i don't care at all that he
wanted to take this stuff what i
do care about is that he has
left his piles of stuff in front
of his house and now my stuff
is in his piles and i look
at it every day and i'm so
annoyed because i'm like because you want
to get rid of it i'm like
i want to now i see that
i never see every day and i'm
either like give it back because now
i'm like i think i could make
it work yeah or
or just put it into a you
it's it's getting ruined by the elements
like i'm like i don't understand and
then i had this frame like of
this art that we kind of took
apart and then there was his frame
and we were like mike was gonna
break it up and he's like honestly
but this man has now taken that
and is using it as a sort
of gate that he has to get
around every day but it's like not
useful at all in that way it
has queued polls know he was like
an art p a canvas oh but
it has like it has a huge
holes in it it wouldn't protect nothing
going in or out yeah and now
that's there and i'm looking at that
every day going like this is actually
mister obama because i was trying to
get rid of stuff and now i'm
like this man is keeping it on
and
showing me every day that you think
he's trying to recreate the inside of
your home in his yard from the
inside out and really walking around like
oh
thanks it's actually really maddening alright we
have to take it okay
alright we're back and we're back jeff
bezos is the executive he is the
executive chairman now he's hbc he is
no exact he's no longer the emperor
yourselves
oh boy
he's no longer the president no longer
the ceo he's the executive chairman what
about the i don't care about that
what about the previous three questions okay
let's find out if jeff the killer
i didn't know who that is and
you know everything i yell killer tell
me now call me now did you
watch that documentary always doesn't go anywhere
which won the clio miss cleo oh
no well that's disappointing oh if anyone
wants to hear the revealed if you
don't want to you could hit you
get hit for fifteen seconds if you
don't want to hear that twist
first i guess if this starting she's
dead now she's a lesbian who cares
was that it that was like a
big twist at some point i went
i don't care i never thought about
our sexuality i'm more intrigued about if
she's scamming it was like it was
such a weird like we're saying like
like this nice ending with her having
a girlfriend was so
so yeah it's weird it's like they
got into this they just had to
do this documentary in a day yeah
like oh there's no story here oh
shit
oh she's got a hot girlfriend jeff
the killer is a fictional character in
the online horror fiction sub genre creepypasta
he is depicted as a pale noiseless
man o black hair and a joker
esque grin okay i'm scared i'm scared
i'm scared well you known for his
pre murder catchphrase go to sleep
you don't think so i'm scared jeff
the killer origin history at dictionary dot
com why
thanks dick slice the dotcom dictionary getting
involved and jumping killer leave the dictionary
out of it he's a definition of
a killer oh yeah here's another question
where is jeff the killer live
is jeff a serial killer
i love him i need to know
about it now yeah it's me jack
is your family good as this creepypasta
a children's world you know how would
i know
meaning the people so maybe it's been
googled a ton because there's a lot
of kids wondering if jeff is real
it must be right right yeah yeah
yeah is somebody asked quora is just
to kill a real and still alive
can you imagine having google as a
child i would have known of everything
i know elephant penises it's sweet somebody
answered yes jeff the killer is real
and whether or not he is alive
i don't know he was lasting in
twenty eleven that being said no one
really knows if he is alive but
i think he still might be okay
that's just good area that's scary it's
good
an answer good answer good answer answer
but i went around when it came
show you gotta be yeah you'll have
to wait and see what game show
could you be on wheel of fortune
probably argument is a kick oh i
would love to do as a cake
check out this is this case i'm
not going to touch you
you will have connected you are to
my body you will not trick me
into touching you again
yeah
ah well i'll watch the other before
sunrise movies yeah but i want to
do deal with you oh really oh
but we can do i'm like yeah
space it out yeah and i'm tom
marino yeah you want nine years but
me yeah yeah we should every nine
years
so if you type in it is
jeff probes you get married then you
get is jeff pope sick sick like
what where i mean we're all like
today creeping towards death is that what
they mean
he he's been married a couple of
times sorry couple of times he was
married only right from nineteen ninety six
to two thousand and one didn't work
out this is pre survived while survivors
started in two thousand yeah oh so
then he was like i don't need
you anymore shine right amos now shelly
wrong for me and then he's now
he's
bill married to lisa ann russell as
of twenty eleven i'm so relationship we
love you we love you in goodfellas
going on twelve i love you ayres
lovely lady and you know what else
i think i love jeff the killer
too well i'm i'm attracted to him
based on the description and like smiles
i like to i think that's nice
plus no six fewer muscles have a
smile garden
face instead of a frown yes right
no knows he can't smell like your
gubbio or fart is jeff dunham merit
he can smell my ground turkey
is jeff dunham larry he's also been
married twice you might be a redneck
if you married johanna he was married
to paige done different guy
but but still true yeah he's married
to paige dunham from nineteen ninety four
twenty ten a gram he's been married
to alright murdoch since twenty twelve that's
great censure is of jeff is with
him and ahmed the terrorists could they
great i forgot about the night it's
great
look i just have a picture by
myself now get ahmed in there oh
my god i'm really happy for the
killers married
it'd be tough because he would cause
to be going honey go to sleep
and he's like yeah don't murder me
try to think of have any reality
recap yeah ma million dollar listing is
really great this season i will throw
that on there oh yeah a switch
my tv providers no longer have well
let's talk about that not
right now but i'd love to know
more about later um it doesn't say
if he's married but it does say
he is an adolescent serial killer and
registered creepypasta he kills rats on the
registration register creepypasta so if you move
into a neighborhood in europe registered creepy
policy you have to go door to
door and tell everyone i am a
creepy boston ah also going to sleep
have you ever gotten me though is
an adult oh thank guys and i
listen to his a serial killer but
shouldn't you be thanking god if you
did get it because there are probably
i pretty much think everyone's a pervert
and stay away from that yeah yeah
good yeah um jeff was disfigured after
being set on fire while fighting a
gang of bill bullies had lost his
saturday key losses
saturday when he was being set on
fire it burned data boundaries no fighting
the bully yeah but loses said i've
tried several fire i'm going crazy over
here it's honestly so stressful it's oh
my god wait how was did you
go to the did you go to
the valentine's pickleball game know i know
i have a baby okay well
a collection of maybe you have a
nanny
on a weekend my dear for a
special things such as a pickleball tournament
and that i don't care about okay
well that's their right yeah how's i'm
going to do with your child ah
no i did not i would it
looks fun i didn't go um and
why didn't you go well because i
you know i sort of i was
sort of like i have a child
yeah
and what about well you know what
actually don't know i think about pickleball
but then jessica message me and she's
like why weren't you courtside next time
and then i said you know what
next time i would be courtside yeah
i would i would love to dress
up in the outfits club had an
amazing gucci and is there enough people
that it was sold out yeah but
the okay i mean what do mean
everyone would be where i feel like
you're letting this
this friend group balu yeah i'm scared
of them you are you you've talks
about how you admire them i do
admire them but i don't think you
want their kind of tough love i'm
i'm scared i'm scared and ready never
making you pee places no i mean
honestly i felt honored that she said
i should have been there i've i
felt like you know i'm not
i'm not main friend group here i'm
kind of like tertiary just to get
your sporting care i'm a supporting character
in their lives one hundred percent yeah
but i'm like i'm like a sort
of co-star like a gum i have
two lines every ten episodes you're twenty
eight on the call sheet um so
you think gunther is probably held with
having to hold down was gotten through
guns and gun i don't know gun
caution
and probably even twelve who's seven hell
through eleven they appear on the show
early i think okay so you think
he's like number six no seven six
of my luck he's number seven i
love doing who else could pause and
a friends call sheet we have run
it here let me look janie was
a was jamie
on that i saw the clip i
love that yeah we went to you
know james michael tyler who played gunther
died um yeah yeah i ah i
guess during quarantine um and we went
to his memorial service wow hollywood forever
and it was wonderful that's nice it
was real it was like one of
those it was a real celebration it
was outdoors
it was a beautiful day yeah it
was like music play like he he
said he wanted his he knew he
was gonna die and he wanted his
service to be a big party and
it really was it was a wanting
to base and like you know this
is a person i never met in
my life but to i felt very
privileged to witness the outpouring of love
that
was that was being ah ah that
was on display and this you think
you'll get one ah
a funeral like oh i only think
about it every day if you ever
died five i don't know that you
would i think your funeral would be
really fun i think it would be
yeah i think it would be people
laughing ivy league guys
there yeah and hold me to that
i'm going to have a man selling
ice cream if you owe make sure
that because i will die at you
because i'm younger that's right and you're
a woman yeah here's what i have
found a friends with benefits call sheet
i will look at that number one
ryan hansen what toes that he's ah
he was in veronica mo
but i mean that's not the same
movie i'm thinking of ashton kutcher and
no i don't think this is a
a movie i think he's efficient
money's okay ah and then i would
need my glasses so you were just
looking up call sheets while i looked
at friends call sheet now yeah let
me see friends here's your new friends
call sheet jennifer aniston dare we go
here's an x-files call sheet who whoo
whistle it where's the rat man on
here i clicked on i clicked on
what i thought was the x-files call
sheet and here's what popped up ah
gotcha i gotcha that's a nice guy
you don't rick roll a walt disney
nineteen thirty s horse
i fucking got you fucking got me
aren't you glad that you do this
show so you know what rick roll
against i love it i never would
have known i so yeah i just
bounce back i do feel like i
have i'm i'm a what am ill
that was not me i gotta take
my pill that's apparently now because everything
is going through my computer when we
record if i get a text apparently
that happens we know but you do
not disturb you just touch the screen
of that oh i press mute oh
it looked like you were touch i
was like that doesn't work that way
sweetheart
wow hey dear i'm just gonna meet
you poe come to find a principle
i didn't it was there's too much
the word friends is too general yeah
that's that's a note for that show
yeah i had infringed sheet but i
do think i'm twenty eight on the
call sheet if not lower on the
deep dive friends yeah um but i
but i would be happy to be
like a sort of think easter egg
at the gallon tines pickup alternate who
do you think beats you oh plenty
of people i mean like okay if
we're if we're gonna do a call
sheet for their friend group absolutely yeah
ok let's see so i mean i
don't want to put a number one
because i feel like that's that's they're
gonna come i know i know people
who want to be number well i
think they should and want to be
number one but number one would be
june casey up diana not diane that's
june um jessica figure it out on
friends i wonder maybe it's just alphabetical
order that's what we have to do
probably can't all be number one so
like i bet courtney cox's number one
because of hoody zing v nupur radius
fame who do you think would be
number one on the deep dive friends
group pod or call sheet anything like
i'm probably gonna go with june because
i feel like she would make she's
the one who wants it the yeah
she would make it has yeah yeah
yeah then we're going to i'm going
to put i'm gonna elbow everyone out
for
or that then you think it should
be alphabetical from that point forward i
mean i'm like we got casey we
got we got jessica we have cool
up then we have our next players
we have elizabeth lane we have danielle
you can set them to be supporting
characters no i just mean they're not
i would say yeah if we're going
for who's getting those top spots they're
gonna say they're getting those tops weird
do they talk about us like this
no yeah personally they don't they don't
care about us at all and that's
the whole point o madman gif of
course i don't think about you at
all yeah yeah well i could go
on but i won't i'll make my
own call sheet and i'll send it
around yeah send it to them see
how they react i think it's a
great idea to make call sheets for
every friend group you can think of
and then they everything you
invite pitch to be there called they
should have a call sheet for all
of their events and then they tell
all time and wardrobe oh my yes
and they have a stylist theme and
they have the makeup and hair they
don't call your hair and woke up
i wouldn't be shocked they had that
for the downtime and just pick up
alternative should safety orientation i love the
idea of a call sheet for a
party yeah zero actually kind of cute
if it was like a tv themed
than somebody's gonna take it seriously though
like why am i number seventeen yeah
right yeah you can't get get caught
up in the numbers i'm happy to
be too
absolutely i love when you're on a
show you guest on a show that's
been on for a million years and
you're like your number ah five hundred
and two yeah i'm um orange is
the new black i was like number
forty one there were so many sort
of so many people so many amazing
people
so fun i've never been on a
show wow how does that feel in
your heart that
sarah silverman program yes i was on
that twice two different characters show you
to call sheet i'm sure sure about
i bet we did but i don't
even know how they just told you
to show up tomorrow and like it
so much that show was like yeah
you are already there yes like so
you're in this somebody said yes so
much of that show was just trying
to figure out show business from
people not giving us any clues but
honestly that's how it is i think
across the board there's no one explaining
anything and you just you have to
show up and hope you figure something
out that's life baby yeah yeah that
is life yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know what i was thinking about
um tell us i drove past a
jack in the box and i was
thinking about how you were
talking about jack-in-the-box and that fry situation
that was carl's junior but thank you
so much for thinking of me oh
damn i appreciate that i mean writes
it all memorized because it's gonna sound
just like my brain is even more
just centered on myself because i was
thinking about how i forgot that i
was in a jack-in-the-box commercial and i
was thinking why didn't i ever think
of that thing that was because you
were saying carl's jr the entire year
yeah what did you did you play
jack no i didn't i was um
the premise of international check the premise
of the commercial i didn't check em
you directed the commercial well he did
oh because the the guy with the
voice yeah right to all the commercials
that's what a sweet remember and kindler
talking about that that guy casting himself
and he's like i don't know i
just keep
hearing this voice and specific voice is
it's like someone like gemma yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah jeopardy produce yeah i
love how it's italy one is shutdown
well the to replace alex trebek of
the the producer of the show reilly
cast himself was so crazy yeah that
was really funny um the premise of
my commercial
was that they were finally serving breakfast
all day and other people where i
was worse for me
i was in the drive thru as
long with many other cars as we
were experiencing going to our other fast
food places and finding that they no
longer serve breakfast so i'm screaming and
sobbing in my car because they don't
serve breakfast sh and your lunatic and
i've been saying and then it was
opera music playing over us in slow-mo
we all screamed and cried in the
cars
and then they're like don't worry we
have it all day and how do
you feel about it after feel great
you feel good yeah worthwhile worth your
time i was absolutely worth my time
yes yes it was one step to
quitting babysitting
so from babysitting to jack-in-the-box yeah we
should at least we now have an
intermediate step yeah
what did you what was your favorite
super bowl commercial my favorite one god
paul do we decided on favorite i
think i liked the will farrow one
the most because i like i like
farah that was the list i loved
one i loved the dunkin donuts one
was funny i actually didn't see that
one right i have to say the
thing no i thought it was funny
you're not allow
loud to say he didn't think that
ah can i tell you something wrong
in the voice back in i'm gonna
say my late twenties early thirties ah
when i was
dream kingdom all the time do we
get drunken one bill makes you every
na na oh we all do we
all my go to when i was
drunk was to get two breakfast sandwiches
from jack in the box so and
maybe if i was lucky i wouldn't
eat both of them that night maybe
there'll be one of the morning yeah
that's a good try to as often
as not i already both yeah yeah
yeah i got drunk the other night
and congratulation and it was to the
point where i was worried i was
going to throw up in the uber
on the way oh no dang i
was but i focused and i was
fine you were driving an uber i
was right afterwards yeah and i go
got home and we sort of let
me see the back of your head
why what does it look like i
think you drove me in your upper
ah back of me you pass the
ox at that site
ah
i just the killer over yoda did
that thing where i kind of like
go to sleep i stumbled around my
house making decisions like how many pretzel
absolutely those here i'm gonna do this
so yeah and then like i actually
went to bed with my makeup about
which i never do and you so
good the morning i looked beautiful and
i look up and
the joker takes makeup off islanders a
good question he seems to have nice
skin i think i was getting really
crackly i honestly other than the heath
ledger version i thought his face was
naturally like yes i thought so too
cause autism asking to um anyway it
was fun it was fun time actually
was like really had a great night
what can you say what the occasion
was
i went to a housewarming party um
yeah i'm house yeah it was one
house it was fun and it was
a fun mix of people that don't
always see so it was a lot
of nice convos nice yeah he's like
yeah you time to hear any gossip
me think um
yeah okay we have to take a
break lord's gonna tell us the gossip
we'll we'll be right back tell us
a gossip
oh yeah
ah that was that happy hours snuck
up on me gotta love d drinking
you love ny j gay okay show
yeah we looked for lawrence o jack-in-the-box
commercial and instead yeah we found via
a video where she's making fun of
drunk driving cat i don't know i
don't know
it's an old web series so typing
in jack in the box breakfast all
day you get a lot of people
reviewing jack in the box maybe you
there's so many there's so many what
what could be the difference in any
of the things that they're saying i
really don't know i this commercial might
be hard to find i found the
youtube link it is now unavailable really
yeah day one sorry no longer available
because the youtube account so
associated with this video has been terminated
oh god wow execution style with extreme
prejudice so sorry sorry everyone you can't
see it but you know what that's
for the best shouldn't everything be online
all the time agreed yeah i don't
i mean i think every anyway i'll
be online all the things everything should
be deleted
we'll start over okay i think that
seems better why don't i do everything
to porn up yeah it's everybody knows
huh hello bump name yeah we all
love it
it's the number one place to find
everything out there but that new batgirl
movie up there manolo is a time
for three char oh yeah well gee
or a voicemail what do you want
o voicemail let's do a voice million
were my little snack here and if
you would like to call us you
can call us at ah hag claims
eight
ah alright so let's see how do
i do this oh boy you should
have a full size or no but
they're okay here's the problem he put
them all in one file okay alright
i'm skipping into this one alright here
we go it's freedom boys i don't
have a funny ques
question okay bye was just no that's
good alright i like it when it's
not funny yeah it's written boys i
don't have a funny question i was
just curious if any of you ever
have like anxiety or if you've ever
had like a panic attack on c
stage while performing ham how you go
about hiding it or how you deal
with it
yeah i don't know just curious if
you guys ever have to deal with
it like my thank oh baie baie
thank you so much you know it's
hard when you're on stage and you
start getting nervous or so because like
your your breathing gets really shallow and
it's very difficult to do the necessary
thing because you're you're expected to talk
like i'm talking about when you're doing
standup yeah if suddenly you start getting
like a fucking bombing and you start
getting nervous it's very difficult to keep
recover because your breathing is getting like
more shallow and but you have you
have to be talking yeah at the
same time so the best thing you
can do is put yourself in a
mind state where you don't give a
shit before
yeah i i've never i don't think
i've ever had a panic attack on
stage or something but i've definitely felt
like anxious i never i don't know
i don't know i feel like although
i've bombed plenty i don't know that
it ever felt
panicky in that way it felt more
like you just have to keep going
it it just jumping you had good
material my my materials like i did
not oh my my memory of that
feeling like from the earliest days when
it was when i did not have
the the the skills that i have
now was
that it just felt bad it felt
like scary like oh no this is
it just felt humiliating yeah like this
is bad and i have to keep
an i can't just leave that to
say it's more just like it feels
bad but it's not um might your
brains aware that it's yeah bad you
just can't stop of course you have
to keep going of course the famous
say
story and you could hear it on
laboring under delusions of my one of
my albums um about doing a new
year's eve show where people threw ice
at me wow but i still did
my time wow and then realized later
i probably could have left and no
one would have said anything while the
other part of fun by the way
that was carried the other part of
your question was have you ever had
a panic attack
and no i don't think i ever
had i've had one or maybe two
i would know it right again say
it wasn't during the show was it
i'm having it right now you look
great i know see i can keep
it
um no it was horrible um i
don't want to speak about that okay
thanks for your question yeah yours ah
this is shannon i think here we
go
hi scott hi lauren in no particular
order but we do it it was
noted i was calling because i got
into a big argument with my boyfriend
because i was buying a gift certificate
for someone from a restaurants and he
invited that person along to go get
it what why and he did not
see the problem in there and see
arguments wow um sorry i want to
back i want to be known i
know you draw i forbid a thing
to think that if you're getting a
gift for someone the person that gifted
for moving shouldn't be there during the
time of the gift getting okay love
you bye you may yeah he's
is totally wrong why would you invite
that person it seems weird take him
watch you buy the thing and then
you handed to them maybe that's their
kink where you kink shaming this guy
i don't i think she probably would
sad if it was as king he
wants to watch you buy this
it's like kuk my guess it does
but it also is a great tv
show i took my gift i feel
like as a person who gives the
gift it does sort of achievements cheapens
it for them yeah you know it
doesn't feel special it feels like first
of all that person had to do
the errand of going to the place
because why not just give me money
yeah we're going here today
gether yeah why don't you just buy
it for me here's my question why
is this a fight like why could
i think because i can't utilize it
why this is a fight know why
why if you ask like my why
do you want to do that and
he can't explain it then you have
a communication problem or this person cannot
communicate like if you're like you're saying
what we have here
there is a failure my question also
was the three of us did they
go have food or no they just
went to the restaurant to buy the
gift card then they were going to
go do something else together like that's
that's insane like you can't bring the
person on the errand of their own
also yeah you can say that's unacceptable
to me and say like oh no
i wanted this to be a secret
so the person can come in the
ca
car as long as we keep it
a secret yeah i'm going to think
i think great way to avoid a
fight is to say things like that's
unacceptable to me yeah yeah i know
but keep it real know but what
i guess what i'm trying to say
paul is like don't be afraid to
say your own feelings about how you
feel about something that i agree with
that and where your boundaries are well
it sounds like she did not have
an issue with that
yeah right yeah it's like great yeah
huh anyway drop him well we settled
that one um here this is natalie
okay
hello hi love their all latest thank
um like me to go ramos to
tell jury duty story no we did
and then i hadn't promised that hurts
oh it's an opportunity to give a
jury duty stories go ooh hello
possible there are stories we haven't told
already ah if we didn't talk about
dirge i must have missed an episode
i got jury duty once when i
was without actually went to other times
i deferred it and they didn't call
me or you know what i did
know one more recently i called in
trying to go and then they just
kept saying i wasn't needed until it
ran
out and then i wasn't needed like
i actually was doing my due diligence
yeah but i got jury duty when
i was like twenty one or something
and i was in chicago and i
went and i remember i went and
sat and there and just like i
had like my book and my snacks
and then i filled out some forms
they they didn't they never interviewed me
and then i was sent home and
that was the end
there you go yeah how are you
i have gone twice ah one time
i went and i got um excused
because they prefaced it by saying this
is gonna be a long trial so
um you gotta get your affairs in
order and it was during pilot season
this is right out a will
this was back when i yeah you
might die here no longer
your future grandchildren by the way you're
all going to end up liking each
other but um and ah it was
this this was back when i was
a working actor it was pilot season
and i was like i had to
write out a letter and say this
is the time of year where i
try to find work there's also the
the back of the days when there
was a
pilot seats yeah right and um i
can't i you know if i don't
get it if i don't get a
job within this time i probably won't
get a job right and i was
mortified i was like this judge is
gonna yell at me oh yeah you
think you are better than league judges
love to yellow and so i had
to wait through uh
um you know ah selection or something
i don't know enough through selection but
there was another address of the judge
gave to everybody and then afterwards said
ah that i was excused and i
was so relieved and then the second
time i did it i was chosen
and i sat on a trial and
real bummer
the trial ah i think we've you
and i made some yeah yeah yeah
and ah it was a lasted about
a week and it ended
it ended in a hung jury and
we were all dismissed why any jury
with you as a hung jury yeah
thank you i just remembered i had
a court date years ago and totally
forgot la la i think from one
of my car accidents but i'm trying
to remember everyone one no i went
i was like i think it was
in high school and i had to
go to court with my dad
and then they like made me feel
really bad and i was like i've
seen your dad took you to this
native american things and he took you
to court yeah right yeah yeah big
better got and i had the judge
had to like i talked to them
about what i did and what happened
and then they told me what i
had to dukes had to go to
drive driving school or yes yes yes
yeah and then you go to comedy
traffic school this whole areas of
and i was i felt so ashamed
and horrible and scared sure yeah it's
terrifying yeah okay i was so terrified
when i was i'm i know i've
told the story before but i got
arrested for smoking on the subway when
i was like eighteen yell and i
was issued a court date and i
didn't go yeah and then mail
i'll start coming the house saying a
benchwarmer has been issued for your arrest
and my mom is saying what is
this and i'm like wow i don't
know it's crazy that she not know
you smoked is that why you want
to keep it secret i was just
showing that she knew i smoked but
i did not tell her that i
was arrested yeah and then um i
tried to go one day i think
i tried to go on the day
and i couldn't find the building
yeah
and this is before google this is
before google and before i knew any
fucking thing yeah and i just then
i just did go like yeah i
just didn't go that such then yeah
and i got like like you i
can't find it forget it i've got
a few more summonses but that was
like how i dealt with things was
like just total shutdown yeah i can't
this is too
a bit much for me mine yeah
and emotions i'm just not going to
deal yeah just actually deal happens when
it goes away and guess what it
did wow because i feel like i
would have gone into some bill about
i'm like can you help me but
did it hang over and arrested did
it hang over your life for like
eight years where you constantly thought about
because i know i had a warrant
i think i
thought about it for probably a year
and then nothing happened and it kind
of went away and i was like
this is such i think also was
a short but people like they're not
gonna fuckin right right try to find
you in a red yeah yeah i
had a warrant for probably seven years
or something like that for like a
speeding ticket or whatever where i same
thing i couldn't find the courthouse like
and it just
ended up not going your ineptitude saved
you both both yeah no but my
thing is anytime i drove i would
competence my cowardice they came through anytime
i drove i was so paranoid about
it of like getting pulled over the
them calling the warrant than they impound
my car yeah jail for years for
years and years and years and years
and then fine
only i i went in and dealt
with it one day and it was
like the the judge i went before
the judge yeah and it was it
took me like a half hour he
basically like called me up and said
ah why didn't you deal with this
i said i don't know and he
said ok well i'm gonna reduce the
the thing and you reduce it down
to one hundred i was like i
didn't have the money he reduced down
to a one hundred buck
it was like alright get out of
here it was like so simple wow
that i was like why have i
been under this law a massive cloud
for years and years when i could've
just taken care of it then you
also hear shit like you know you
go you go there and the cop
won't show up and yes dismissed yeah
but that's like my thing yeah cop
the other thing i read is when
no
couples you're over and uses radar you're
supposed to say and when was the
last time that was calibrated sir
and after write it on the tickler
of i don't know i'm doing just
my cup had to show because i
had to go to drivers i love
with people's advices to be an asshole
to the gulf yeah oh my god
i know you say to him is
you pay his salary while also we
should just say don't talk to cops
don't ever give them any donuts or
any of their questions that's right um
so my one jury do
rudy story was i the same thing
i kept deferring because like i remember
shark tail at the time i'm like
literally the movies opening i can't do
this and they're like well you have
to do it at some point i
was like yeah but now oh and
they're like no you can defer okay
let's do um but the last time
i did it was ah in burbank
and have i not told
this story but i don't know apparently
we haven't i got there was a
group of a hundred of us and
first of all my hundred scott ottomans
yes it's crazy and the person on
trial was me oh no was jeff
the killer of the jury
but um so there was the they
got a hundred and they were looking
for i think they were looking for
like either twenty four you know because
the twelve alternates or that's sixty or
something like it so my friend who
was a judge said hey when you're
filling out the form of like all
your information and it as
you do for a living write down
every single thing you do like podcaster
ah
you know actor like every single job
or hobby you have because then you
look like an insane robbie yeah you
said you look like an insane person
to the judge and they'll get rid
of you right oh so i did
that
and then they that actually sells yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's why it sounds
unhinged and like you make no money
doing any of the things but in
these days of the side hustle oh
it's absolutely they used to be but
so i did that but it's but
it didn't they didn't get rid of
me and so this is a two-day
thing um so the first
day they passed out these like badges
and the judge admonished everyone who says
you are going to need these badges
every single time you come in here
and if you do not this is
the most important thing in your life
if you do not have this badge
when you come in you are going
to be chewed out by me from
the machine right so everyone like had
to had to
i have these with curse words yeah
yeah like kill you lose long in
a row you feel jeff ross style
it's gonna be like a caricature artist
on the boardwalk so that so that
was how we started and then did
you lose it oh let me get
to this i like to jump ahead
so we hear what the
the trial is going to be about
the what it's what the type of
thing it's gonna cover and he starts
interviewing people ah numerically i was number
sixty something right he starts with number
one and he starts just interviewing people
um saying like here's what the trial
is going to cover will you have
a problem being impart
chel and it was very interesting because
people immediately like if you they didn't
want on the jury they would go
like yeah i would have trouble being
impartial it was very interesting because the
judge kept steering them into out of
politeness they felt like they couldn't because
he's like no you could be yeah
he kept steering them into like going
like yeah you're right i can do
it i can do yeah and there
was only one guy who was like
absolutely not i cannot be impartial and
he he interviewed him for fifteen minutes
going but if this happened surely you
could put aside those things no i
would never be able to do that
i cannot be impartial in this story
and finally after fifteen minutes of just
excruciating things he goes alright you're free
to go and i was like damn
guy actually like withstood fifteen minutes of
reeling yeah he did it yeah so
ah i so i get picked by
the way this is the day that
i wrote that letter for you i
don't know if you remember this with
your old manager um i don't on
my lunch break your old ten year
old manager called me to write an
email
on your behalf and well i want
out of that later i only had
a forty five minute lunch break wanna
hear i wrote i wrote an email
for you um but um so cool
up picks me up in her car
which is a pristine car has nothing
at no trashing or anything like that
um we we get home she picks
me up because we're going to
to a restaurant we go to the
restaurant we go home and then i'm
looking to go to the next day
i'm looking for this badge and i
can't find it and i'm like hey
cool op can you look in your
car for the badge because i can't
find this badge she looks in it
it goes it's not here i've looked
everywhere for it it's not here i
go i fucking in trouble
so i go the next day and
this judge like you have to have
the badge to get into the room
and who doesn't have the badge doesn't
get in the room and and so
like i get put off to the
side and he just tears into me
and he's like what did i tell
you yesterday that you had to have
this badge what happened to it i
said i'm just like more
defied because the other thing is another
juror like recognized me it was like
i'm such a big fan now i'm
being like shoot out in front of
a fan i'm like i lost it
sir
a your honor whatever i call you
and he and he just like yells
at me for a while i'm just
like sitting there taking going fuck fuck
fuck fuck fuck so ah they they
get all the people they need before
they ever get up to sixty whatever
and so we're all like go at
the end of the second day um
just having curiosity i go to clubs
car is sitting right there
look
how did she miss it i don't
know
ah xin not see that coming at
all oh my god wow do you
think the person who called and left
this message was the one who saw
you get chewed out and wants to
tell that story you said promise me
years ago that you would tell a
story about jury duty it was so
emasculating i'm a i'm a forty whatever
your old man being yelled at by
another forty year old man for losing
a piece of paper that's been laminate
that sucks oh and then the other
thing was ah as i'm leaving i
see a little wall of celebrities who
have done jury duty and there's weird
al going that shouldn't be
celebrated isn't that weird yeah yeah um
well duh right time for this episode
who's your judge friend is it judy
yeah alright i beat on her leg
once you start it's raining i know
i told her it was p okay
thank god
i don't make the mistake
we have to go but look if
you're still listening to this you're probably
in for the long haul right yeah
yeah thank you for sticking it out
this is our last episode and ah
until next week and oh yeah we
should say until next yeah um but
this is this is our final episode
until we come back next week yeah
see
series finale of episodes that end now
yes series finale of this week's episodes
oh okay and um we love you
for listening if you would like to
cuddle if you ever listen to one
of these episodes the last two minutes
or so lawrence on her phone looking
catching up on emails guy
step so that's it i hear lawrence
cooldown period yeah respect i need it
badly um but freedom usa you'd like
to call us it is of course
hag claims eight the course and ah
three m usa gmail dot com if
you wanna send us a three-tier idea
of a little game we can play
ah we're through to usa on the
socials app
and if you'd like to listen to
ad-free versions of this podcast you can
do so at stitcher premium or cvb
world dot com
and until next time remember
eap
and shooting the breeze is ebay better
than hang it up by
uh