three
eighteen d
oh yeah and now reader
oh wow mimi oh yeah yeah church
church take me to church buy one
get one free back to back
happy if you could buy a church
and get one free would you yeah
of course why not how much is
the first one well how much could
buying a church possibly be hundred dollars
thousand
i'd say max we're looking at two
fifty
hi everyone welcome to three of them
i'm scott i'm paul i'm lauren and
there's no mistaking this is three what
can we say this is freedom i
mean geez you're not losing anything else
this podcast has a certain vision is
a three-day
i'm dealing with postnasal drip which of
course you know i'm dealing with pre
nasal drip but it's coming any second
now yeah thirty is freaky
barrett is pre nasal drip bloop um
why would it's very annoying because you
know i was sick last week right
it's not covered right and this is
the like last remaining like thing that
wants to happen inside of my body
and it's very annoying well i mean
you're also pregnant well okay i just
mean my nose not praying you do
have
one remaining thing in your body that
is happening there's also this thing called
pregnancy rhinitis oh where you can have
a stuffy nose for no reason which
i have had a lot of it's
really annoying is rhinitis is that a
fancy term for stuffy nose yeah it's
it it's so crazy that the stupid
anything related to the nose they call
it rhino stuff it's like it's like
oh my god stop insulting
me yeah because the fuckin got him
in the morning i got born on
my fucking face seca bucket which came
first the rhino rhino for nose or
rhino for the mount for the for
the mountain or the monster sir you
as monsters right oscars his allies just
may as well be mosques some animals
are absolutely montoya rhinoceros yes that's one
rancho raf drive moms they're beautiful but
munster ufo monsters yeah give monsters exist
beautiful monsters like the jinx robert
still a monster i always think was
gonna go outta those people making that
documentary must have just been christ humpy
like when tiger woods nevada oh hey
that's the best fucking shit but then
i heard that was kind of fabricated
don't do this to me i'm sorry
i want you to know the truth
i
or news ai
so nobody ever got murdered this guy
just this was a fun character that
created um a couple weeks ago i
went fourteen days less light less than
a week ago we went on a
babymoon trip oh where did you go
to santa barbara but we were also
swim there the yesterday
all weekend oh really yeah we just
went there yesterday all weekend yep the
full can share about that i i
was there for the santa barbara international
film festival because i had a film
in the festival called another happy day
when you were there for the biff
yes and then we made it abating
them because i was looking to schedule
a babymoon and i was like it's
getting
too close to the wire can to
be better can do i gotta make
this one gonna make one better yeah
one thing one thing and it was
great and we went to the zoo
and the zoo there did you go
this time we didn't we passed it
and and cool ups said to me
why did we go to the zoo
that time i said i don't like
right before you have a kid why
did we is that because you're saying
you didn't have a kid no we
just when we were one yeah we
didn't have a kid but it was
real i mean it was twenty some
odd years ago and we were like
why did we go to go to
the zoo in another city that's fun
but i um did in fact well
i did well i'm now i have
two had you just seen mandated you
have to go to the zoo every
city you go i have time they're
legally have to go to the zoo
illegally have to take
yeah also wait this is with holly
yeah we did a whole thing um
we have nobody to take care for
if we were to i would
people refuse right they're like oh i
we we like being with her you
know it's really not because a few
people were very like you brought your
baby on your babymoon and i was
like where else am i supposed to
do i mean this is first of
all this is what's going on we
already have one so second of all
i like her and i want to
show her places and she had a
great time she actually loved the
trip so much we rented an airbnb
and she was like running around the
whole time chasing franny or dog and
it was like you brought the dogs
to this we did the actuators that's
weird they did the whole thing and
she was she when we was time
to go so i don't want to
go home my level trip so much
this week and the festival was also
very good what have you said that's
great because we're living here which
then say okay find your own way
home i think she'd be fine just
leave her there
um but it was a great weekend
it was really nice did like four
nights and um how many days one
one day pieces kept coming home and
going back to for the night and
i was just outside the city limits
i popped up to do these festival
q and a's and whatnot which was
really fun questions were you asked
well i was asked many questions but
how do you memorize all the line
yeah a lot of people wondering that
and they just did not understand the
movie is a postpartum depression comedy and
so a lot of the conversation is
surrounding postpartum depression but a lot of
people sharing from the audience which is
really their own story yeah
ways they related were there people that
saw you pregnant and they said you
how's the opposite of what you're lying
you don't know what it is there
was no year ahead there was actually
a lot of oh now you're about
to see what i'm like asian easy
as it ages
yeah bad
you're required anytime you work for happy
medicine to do that i put out
my ticket
tell me about one time i had
an audition at the happy madison studios
or whatever and um i forget what
it was for oh was it for
that i was to play you don't
have to go where it was for
the tv show gay robot that was
dry yeah oh yeah it was that
it was made or it was a
pile
i don't remember if it was made
ah i think it was i i
don't know it'll be because there's always
a movie this was the pilot it
was something he was doing in his
act yes yeah and he would do
the character this was a pilot and
i z i c looks like it
was a pilot when i got there
the oh good i'm saying thank you
for the kind of didn't continue on
to be a stowaway i've seen new
information
this was a pilot
list of pilot as a tv movie
which i find very weird i auditioned
for this after i was kind of
told like the edition was a mere
formality meaning that they were going to
give you the part not yeah not
that it was like we're obligated to
audition you but you're never gonna get
the part yeah it was like no
no no this is like yeah don't
worry about it and then of course
i
not impart um love that but i
remember being had that happen in the
waiting room of course why do people
open their mouth i say everyone's already
saying yeah everyone's talking about how to
you yeah yeah yeah oh great yeah
and then i don't get it oh
why did anyone say i forgot other
people were also talking about this other
person yeah and they were the ones
who make the decision so yeah i
um but i wow
not to interject but i but here
we go yeah but i hated when
people would do that around me where
they would like promise people jobs it's
crazy yeah there's just so early yeah
yeah so what to the point where
i do the opposite where i'm always
like you'll never get the i know
yeah thanks i'll never you will never
work you're a terrible actor i hate
your work
no but i had friends who would
do that all the time where it
was like oh your show is ordered
and then they go hey you're gonna
work for me you're gonna work for
me you're gonna work for me you're
gonna work for me and me and
then get the budget and it's like
you could only afford to have no
control and then and then they would
never talk to the person that they
said they were gonna hire the person
is always like why did yeah yeah
it's so weird yeah
well anyways so i'm in the i
get to the waiting room and it's
full of people who do and there's
nowhere to sit and there was technically
one place you could sit but a
dog was sitting there what oops adam
sandler's those meat ball oh well hey
he's should have it was that like
a test of like if you tell
me ball to get off the
chair then you imagine going in and
telling someone else's dog to move yeah
to take dog itself like not going
to the person in the office but
hey get out of the yeah yeah
that would be a test of being
an asshole yeah but you would have
gotten the part of you unless yeah
because they will respect the pastor was
well like oh god he
he'll do that to us if we
don't hire anyone to be an executive
producer credit to them what happened um
so then i auditioned it did not
go well and i didn't at the
role so then what happened
so then they didn't just show did
not go and i think it was
you because i should have been made
as it wasn't me but then what
happened then um just up to now
like every day oh i went to
sleep okay
i woke up three weeks ago oh
okay yeah actually you were in a
coma in two weeks time oh my
como yeah you did so many three
dogs go about kobe he's talking about
his girlfriend being keeps calling her a
coma oh no she's just in a
coma girlfriend in a coma go vertical
ma ma
okay ah how one's no oh no
oh morrissey we know you suck now
before easily you do a parody of
your own song guma in a coma
what did you do in santa barbara
we just it was a total like
let's get away for a couple of
days because i can't sleep why because
you know how previously on three-day and
we talked about how we take turns
monitoring the baby when it's my turn
i turned down the monitor really low
because anything will wake me up and
i don't want to wake cool up
i'm from korea monitors taking care of
it why do you have to
yeah no but i turned down so
low because any any noise no matter
how low will wake me up i
don't want cool up to be well
yeah ooh but when cool off it's
her turn she turns it up all
the way because she sleeps so deeply
that this system i think you gotta
figure this out you need to her
bedroom style so
so pretty much every single day i'm
woken up um but she was just
like you're you're really tired yeah i
know but i'm glad about sometimes by
light sometimes i sound
yeah it's like every single day i
get woken i know and you think
like can i just could just skip
one day can i oh can you
fucking imagine i have no worst snoring
right now a day just be asleep
for one whole day i was thinking
about when i was sick or would
pretend to be sick when i was
young school's not that bad but it
was just like
it'll be amazing to go but but
but just thinking about it when i
was like i was i counter that
it is that bad yeah it's like
it sucks yes like when your school
famously said something when you're five or
six because i remember i remember that
sucks yeah i remember one time just
pretending to have learned gyrus
and when you were that young when
i was that when i was sick
that would could be like i can't
talk just so i can skip school
and watch tv all day yeah that's
great and i remember the the i'm
sure i've talked about this but um
i'm not gonna apologize for it but
the pbx pledge drive was on as
best i remember them saying like you
have to call in you have to
call it
like cds like headlines or the new
pbx yes dr but as a big
i shouted to my mom in the
kitchen i'm like we have to call
in and she came and yeah your
voice that was like oh oh as
if she didn't already know we have
to save them but it's so funny
to like get to
catch you like that so so fun
but but a belated congratulations you played
yourself you so much i just wanna
say i have the worst snores in
the world right now and i don't
know about you do i don't know
about it all and they're coming up
like up oil i was thinking about
this why doesn't snoring wake you up
i don't know how is it partly
because my brother
are used to snore like fucking crazy
like yeah rattle the windows and i'm
like how is he yeah he's he's
closer to it than any he's like
a white noise machine yeah like you're
just like enjoying it should be that
way for everyone yeah right kind of
right i sleep through the rain my
gas sector storing i know sewing is
horrible i was in a relationship with
someone who snores and it it it
did sort of become like a white
noise machine after a while i mean
sometimes it was super loud he would
wake me up and i nudge or
what he doesn't adjust me from time
to time i haven't been wearing those
nasal strips yas and those don't always
really do it sometimes it seems like
it's working in other times it's not
in the know know like me
just cut off your nose okay despite
my face despite your face ah let's
not divulge into chaos here okay the
thing i quoting yes someone said that
qian traders oh yeah everyone wants someone
will say and coo up and i
will look at each other and say
like that didn't make sense yeah yeah
i love one so
i i really hate when people say
it happens a lot on like reality
tv testimonials like we're will say like
so much like me like him and
me is like it's like you think
you just like wow what are you
saying him it was the langley and
when i had to go get him
and me his breakfast like yeah it's
just like saying oh just stop
that stuff doesn't the only thing that
bothers me is when people get expressions
wrong and the and the only reason
it bothers me is because of course
i know what they mean it's not
that it's not that i feel like
they're being precise precisely that some expressions
are really good and it's like you're
funny cherish them like what's an example
if you can think of what it
might be hard to think of
you know what a classic one is
buck naked and people say butt naked
yes yeah it doesn't make any fucking
sense while you're while you're fucking naked
it actually makes more sense than buck
naked no it doesn't because buck naked
originated from buck rogers that one episode
where he was naked
which was rare because in the twenty
four time chinese originated no no many
there's so many colors i thought it
was because you buck your clothes up
like a horse
that's interesting i'd like to try know
really think that paul i think it's
because you just come off no i
think it's because you're naked as a
book you're you're up close okay but
why bunk why not every animal gray
question frog naked dog
i know some dogs wear clothes oh
true some dogs were close but have
you ever seen frogs wearing clothes never
fucking toad looks famously can you know
what they actually look good they're doing
i'll they have styles books are very
sweet and calm yeah that's oh there's
new show let somebody who and there's
new show
oh wrote on a new frog and
toad cartoon i heard that now here's
what i'm looking like any luck mr
toad yeah like of wild ride fame
yeah that's not the same thing as
frog and toad mr toad is on
crack cocaine have you been on the
ride wherever it is you gotta know
that it's scared right is too wild
it's so
scary they they tell you though they
tell you what you want mister chose
mild right honey when you get in
the fishing line option seat would you
like wilder mile they ask yeah
like when you order chicken
if you just smiled right it's literally
ten seconds just go just go any
circle then you get out and if
you choose wild you have to sign
your soul to the devil yeah yeah
and they will take it and then
the end she has it would you
yeah would you sign your soul to
the devil if that was the only
way to get into disneyland um no
no
are you sure what a way to
get out of disneyland then yes now
i know that be there forever i
live in the apartment where walt disney
lived above the firehouse yeah do you
think if so there it is i
saw something about a good day i
don't know what i was watching and
it's a security camera
he's gonna rink him thought about that
always goofy going ooh
um i the whole selling your soul
i don't know what taylor
here's the thing when you have one
you're not really aware of it it
kind of feels like take it or
leave it i don't know if i
have one but once it's gone yeah
i want those grams baby don't take
those grams for me yeah instagrams yeah
oh you mean the seven how many
uses for seven grams i think it's
more than seven how many grams what
is that movie where it's like i
thought was seven i thought was like
twenty four seven grams is a chinese
restaurant in tustin california was eleven grass
all souls exclusively i'm yes sean penn
grams twenty
one graham i'm very nice yeah ams
that's right of courses that many gram
i'm keeping them i'm keeping my grams
you want all your grams yeah i
don't even wanna go to heaven i
want to i want to say my
rotting corpse
be fun wouldn't it of course it
would
what wouldn't be fun about your soul
having fun inside your dead body yeah
i would a ball yeah so if
only if you get buried with your
soul it just gets trapped
i imagine right yeah just there's a
school of thought that you don't want
to be cremate creamy cream green bay
ruminated because what if i don't crave
it ain't me what if we don't
have sensors to pick it up okay
star trek what if i said that
intentional centaurs but what if ah you
could feel things when you're
dead horrible and you're sitting there you're
unable to move or communicate but you
can feel things and then they're like
now let's put you in the eight
that's the that's not gonna happen that's
the basis for a sci-fi thing that
dead people can feel everything like there's
a star trek thing there's an episode
about this that's terrible
what i'm trying to remember earlier like
captain picard was bald
the word gay you seem tough but
he was really a pussy i need
you to know canonically a captain picard
is a virgin why did he say
that though that was like
totally do some sometimes leave a voicemail
charlie please let everyone know
out of your salt i mean gabba
who's done over the shirt stuff
his oh shit
not someone else's please let everyone know
toddy like she's supposed to tell this
as keeper of the new flee she
was gonna do some event and he
was there and i started doing it
then i think
alright we have to stick break
whack for my grandma grandma quebec um
so wait how was santa barbara oh
it was good i i built here
like you i wouldn't let you off
the hook i just need to i
wasn't so was it so so the
first night cool was like you know
your re
the tired all the time what if
we got at town and so the
first night i was like i'm probably
not that tired um i went to
sleep at nine thirty and woke up
at eight wow
were you in your own room no
no but season five but without without
just the the guns monitor on it
just allowed me well now what did
did she stay was was amy here
what happened i don't want else so
that's why that's why no ah my
sister-in-law came together
yeah so she was on monitor duty
yes and thankfully because this was a
weekend where she was coughing a lot
in up quite a bit oh good
eating them to comfort her yeah
the worst part of parenting no it
was good we we just hung out
at the hotel on on one day
we went to town and went to
the funk zone that's right we went
to the funk zone i crowd of
it i googled better on my end
up there not oh you would know
okay so yeah i feel you definitely
no if you ended up at the
funk zone well i was like in
some area but i but i was
it funky
what is it i wasn't zone today
miss out so the funk zone it
appears to be santa barbara's attempt to
create a neighborhood of sound good it's
a little more boho chic i guess
then santa barbara is because you know
some farmers slash santa barbara is very
like
old people and and then college kids
yeah but there is a lot of
beautiful nature so this was a it's
called the funk the funk zone yeah
this was a neighborhood of googling like
where to go shopping especially popped up
it was like like three blocks filled
with ah a lot of women with
giant huh
hudson babies one okay so like i
would have if not fitted but kind
of fun if you view yourself as
as a cool parent you know this
is where you you like go to
eat and go to shop and there
were a lot of like wine tasting
hours and stuff this one o'clock somewhere
i don't know if i was there
they felt like that in other places
too
it was why everywhere i feel like
if you could replace this called the
funk so i mean will never forget
it yeah there there were there were
high street signs everywhere that said you
were entering the bow is that true
yes i definitely owe there and there
there was a store that had funk
zone sweatshirts and cool up was threatening
to
buy me one threatening um and i
said i feel like she better just
shut up row by the switcher this
looks also some yeah i you know
i looked at this i didn't care
because i saw this picture and it's
the same picture i see now and
it's like a store that has like
cool colored file cabinets and i'm like
no yeah we bought twenty file cabine
fun funky yeah i'm just like very
funk i don't care but interesting nobody
was also can't drink wine and that's
getting in the way of like a
lot a lot of your normal daily
activities like if i was going to
stroll around some cool neighborhood anything in
the way of me blacking out i
would have why no it was it
was it was kind of like we
we just hung out and then were
like well let's go to the wine
taste
thing thing i will say okay so
we went to a wine the wine
tasting thing if you've ever been one
of these it's like you get you
know five classes for twenty five dollars
a piece or whatever so we had
the first two are great third one
tasted like water literally like water we
we both went this has zero taste
to it so wince
when the person comes and goes how
did you enjoy that wine and we
look at each other like should we
just say great you're having tricked should
we just say fine and let it
go or whatever but i was like
to be honest it had no flavor
it was just like water and she
kind of went huh yeah not for
everyone huh
just wanna like i feel like that's
an opportunity service wise to go talk
to your owner and say like i
think we got a bad batch or
something yeah at the very least show
tasted like water taste this you say
this should have been like did it
smell like curious about now it just
it has no trouble pouring it out
of the bottle
it couldn't come out because there was
a stopper so i was a little
like
if don't ask the question unless you
want it unless you're prepared to deal
with the reality that answer i think
if you are only three given information
like that you should be curious and
say really i never got anywhere everyone
i'm not gonna not for everyone and
tastes like orangey like orange that's not
for everyone yes i'm not a wine
snob at all the only time
this is something like this has ever
happened to me as we went into
a wine bar or one proletariat yeah
exactly and ah now being a server
i was taught about wine that i
was like why do people you know
why trouble smell the smell the corps
why do they smell it all that
kind of stuff and they and it's
not they say it's not to
to judge the wine whether it's good
or bad it's just to see if
it is taste vinegary and has zachary
has already gone off yes yes so
so we were in this wine bar
they delivered our wine i tasted it
it was the only time in my
life where i was like oh this
is this is a problem and i
sent it back and the person argued
with me oh right yeah yeah and
said wow and said that it wasn't
true and i was like but see
oh my gosh i was just out
so when i was in santa barbara
i went with my friend after i
think our movie thing and very unspecific
after screening and she has us troops
kinda i didn't want to go to
the barber should have gone
chicago we were thinking about that time
we went a couple of years ago
that was fun yeah we think we
left our exploding kittens deck house we
had one we had to borrow it
oh no we've seen got okay no
we bought it after
anyway your story really and you start
your majesty on the bug floating in
her y ou and i was like
get another one and then she thought
like rude but i was like does
this even once asked why there's a
bug in it you have one glass
of wine a life and they did
replace it but then i'm like you
can't do that everywhere properly but it
was like empty and it was like
murmur let's get another glass eye one
time which was sort of mildly and
jovially shamed for being ah for having
a bug in my wine by home
at an outdoor event by some some
friends of my some friends who are
shaming oh friends jays they're making fun
of you for having a bug in
it or
for caring that for carrying that there
was a bug huh because we were
outside oh we were in some honoring
no bug just taken out whenever anyone
out there can build things we were
inside and there was a bug and
i'm like you know that flies like
land on shit right yeah i do
hate mosquitoes drink blood right yeah that's
fucking crazy like the things these
fucking things put in their mouth this
is the omen i was drinking them
yeah this is the only thing mosquitos
can eat blood it's like yeah lucky
there's no flaw dude there's like doughnuts
out there it's like other drinking blood
like fries something else actually for example
i was just saw something about polar
bears or they've been having to forage
because of global warming and they have
a bird
herbs and stuff normally wouldn't do that
i'm like if you're so mosquito let's
just say there's no blood yeah so
you just don't eat yeah you don't
even like right pivot and like find
something else it yeah pivot
a
david schwimmer wasn't a clip from shark
tank that i was watching last night
he was supporting pancake mix and he
was supporting was happy i just wanted
to come out and support liberties have
their show shark tank update on this
guy and and and they showed chinese
should i take by the way i
should update
not just on the people who they
have business with but on everyone i
want to see updates on everybody yeah
um i hate sharks thanks so much
oh i watch all time for sharks
well let's talk about that but so
let's unpack the day they show this
guy who is now like making millions
off his pancake mix business but they
show they show his pitch and and
randomly david schwimmer they cut to david
berlin this thinking makes is so good
and then he's in the room and
then he then they don't show me
a attached swimmer to this pitch and
this guy is an actress
chicago's like he probably does plays with
game shot but i'm like this is
fascinating just like they just popped in
one line of him being like i
love this pan mix it's really really
good and then it just like he
was gone and they never mentioned like
he's friends with him or whatever like
i hadn't seen an episode i didn't
know sharks bring it up like there
was a tremor you were just shown
being an old clip and then gonna
look at the guy which is going
like schwimmer pancakes segment how successful businesses
oh look wrong we'll be okay sir
on instagram long table pancakes the best
damn pancakes and waffles i've ever had
but now we're promoting it long table
on shark tom not like i'm against
it the hell is happening with schwimmer
in these pancakes why is he eating
so many p
flew to l a or lives here
yeah and ah way to the shore
tank studios that's the weirdest part
i stood there god i love you
i guess ah like how many times
do you have pancakes a year do
you know what i can't make pancakes
i'm terrible at eight i can see
that well what's what's wrong i'm i'm
actually this isn't you know you don't
want about i need to you need
long-term i mean i am wondering if
i do i need one table if
you want i need to fake sponsor
our show because i
i love pancakes that's right but i'll
make like four hundred duds and then
i'll have like one giving my kid
little kid you helped to be able
to wyoming chosen ones old how is
it yeah well not for me
when you say are you making the
mix wrong or are you cooking reading
them wrong and how do you do
that wrong is you it's like they're
gooey and doing it in the tub
tells me so you're not getting my
ma but they're getting burnt maybe you're
too high so i should put it
on a really low but way longer
than i think maybe
i don't know i'm not a pancake
i want to try it because i'm
not claiming oh my dad's gonna come
in town and maybe i'll make i
don't know how to make pancakes here's
all i know i got me old
pipe like a meal fiddle when it
comes up like i kicked on the
cradle
i bet your dad tell you how
i kinda wanna grill yeah well yeah
you should get a grill i anytime
i make eggs i'm always thinking about
the one-time my dad taught me anything
now the one time something else he
was like ok this is how you
gotta like you know scrape you gotta
you gotta do the edges cook so
you gotta like go out just like
scr
ambled eggs this is any kind of
any kind of url an omelette or
whatever so like literally i think of
him telling me this every single time
i ever yeah it's just you know
it's interesting how the brain yeah hold
on yeah yeah i wish it would
let go and then it could be
a piece i wish my brain was
separate and i could leave it ajar
would just like to look at it
yeah i one time i'd like to
look at him i wish i could
get there he's up there you can't
deny it yeah i would love to
take them out of there just plop
them on the table and just get
a good long look your brain yeah
but what would you be able to
see without him in your head
fuck
can i say that long table is
still in business why are companies only
continuing to grow i know they made
one point two five and less six
percents a decision they've made let's only
grow from selling grow the company has
gone on to expand it's product line
offering new limited edition pancake and waffle
mixes such as short-run ginger cookie flavor
bland okay well
while we're just promoting random things another
shark taking almost this almost same i'm
gonna get another cat it was a
and i kind of went anyway but
it was a litter that detects ph
imbalances so if your cat is sick
it will tell you so you want
to buy some cats well my cat
had kidney problems at the end and
i would have known that so
sooner rye rye rye is very interesting
and they also have pee pads for
dogs you could piss on and see
if you have a youtube ai
yeah it turns out you d i
piss out a few beds for dogs
that do the same thing which is
really that's very helpful as helpful tips
thought of dogs getting beauties i'm sure
they do or is to do detox
kit
chlamydia c disease and herpes chlamydia i
don't know i guess anybody can write
i think it happens to the best
few fuckin enough i don't know i
don't know if dogs ah oh no
lawrence tipped over dogs love to use
condoms let's see
i think the complete silence as we
look yeah like okay here's why i
don't like shark tank okay tell us
i don't really talk the stds shit
yes answered i don't like the sharks
themselves i don't like the way they
talk to people and about mr wonder
i fucking hate that guy so much
you know he's he's my my
most hated ones that's where the shark
tank guys is now they are on
all these ads as themselves going like
this is a good product this is
a good product if you're so successful
why do you have to do these
ads or is it just purely make
hay while i try to be part
of the deal right no it's not
ads for stuff that they've oh they're
they're like you know hi it's mister
wonderful and i'm you know talking about
this thing it's just money it's just
like because i'm sure they get gobs
of money to give an endorsement because
at that point why do you care
just get just pile it on yeah
yeah you're already a soulless creep
and we'll get back to shark tank
in a minute but we don't have
another app that i saw recently was
was you know the person from flip-flop
the christina hall she's oh what's that
she always the divorce company else i
don't like about it it was the
divorced couple you had terek or taraba
yeah and she they got divorce
first they still continue doing the show
or whatever me saw but so she's
she won't get custody of flip delgado
shiplap
but but so she's doing an ad
for showers or something right and he's
doing bad
but this is how the commercial starts
she walks in and goes hi it's
kristina again
this is like my problem with curse
this is my problem with curious george
books what do you mean waiting again
setting up well yeah alright like we've
never spoken also like on love is
blind she goes i'm an esl ah
ha obviously i'm nicholas j and you
just go obvious obviously i'm nicholas shade
that's bold it's
just like well that obviously she's been
a son obviously this is love is
blind and obviously i just wasn't like
that's so but it seemed to me
like it was the it wasn't hurt
doing it it was the producer of
the commercial kind of wanting to be
like yeah sure you're always talking to
her right it's just another example of
this she's always i guess
writing us into thinking that like she's
always around or something i don't know
it was very strange very odd hi
it's kristina again here's what else i
don't like about shark okay and i've
just realised this now the fact that
it's on video makes it somehow worse
mean on video was like on film
like newhart yeah or like top chef
for you know like shows like that
like there's a lot of them that
are kind of
of finish you know it's like a
stage presentation yeah there's it's like to
live feeling it's too like yeah i
don't i don't like it i don't
like shark tank okay i think i
get i don't like watching the presentations
of these dumb people the worst part
of it is is you have a
million dollar idea and you yeah i
want to go on but yeah you
hate the shows and you think
eating all your own money into it
yeah and your ideas why a tank
for sharks yeah so plus rails
i see pie chart
so your ideas what a giant tank
for all these sharks yeah sometimes i
find interesting when they go off on
somebody or like sometimes they'll be like
really though like like let's say for
instance like the person challenges the offer
yeah yeah sometimes they allow them to
do that but other times they go
you're gonna of
well what because when they when they
don't allow it there's so condescending to
the people and it's like i this
is a really like your idea is
so stupid and here we are offering
you money for your yeah counteracting yea
i'm like don't they have the right
to be like i'd rather give you
twenty five percent and thirty three percent
or whatever and like yeah the shark
is like no
no no and it's like or that
i'm not interested or like there'll be
like the persons challenging it and then
like the other sharks were already out
or you shouldn't be doing that you
shouldn't be you should they should let
us be judged but you know what
else it's like i want to be
sure there's a thing where so the
person gives her presentation like yeah but
ah who wants this why do they
you know who cares what it's like
well why is this purse
being on the show like i don't
want this is unpleasant to watch i
already find it pleasant so usually you
don't like like american idol when they
would have bad singers on they would
i hated that yeah well that was
the only reason anyone watched that was
a different time i feel where there
was a different time i don't feel
that we as a culture want to
do that the same way we did
twenty years
ago where it was like funny now
i feel like it's really known and
they still do it the notional veda
american idols have feel good show now
where everyone who comes on has like
the inspirational story i feel we've gone
so far on the other side that
it would be fresh again to have
a simon being like you saw the
last shark tank i saw is money
he's good you used to suck
into the
come out and say like oh yeah
you heard all the king terror book
and they would sometimes be like what
are we even doing here and get
mad at the producers like this because
the producers are intentionally saying yeah yes
people who suck like you know why
yeah newsday here the producer
you're one of the people enjoying funny
like when you're leading that person in
your clinic now he's gonna hate that
we watched some shark tank in a
hotel room and um there was this
so you hate us so much you're
watching a hotel rooms just waiting to
go to hell to watch their tv
we went on to check the hotel
to watch it
um ah
learn dropped an orange it's amanda um
i don't care
so so this woman it was two
women that had this um this ah
new ah baby changing station like the
kind you have like public restroom yes
exactly and the idea was that this
was a self cleaning station so after
you install in restrooms or that you
would one would bring no no
installed in restrooms and you you know
you close the lid before you use
it and then it was china charges
the thing and it was great idea
but and they pointed out
yeah but you're not going to be
able to get the people that need
to buy it to buy it like
for for the for the people that
would use it like a lot is
yes but the bud for like an
airport or a restaurant or a mall
or whatever it's too expensive it's too
expensive so they're not going to buy
it right and that was interesting at
least
first but it sucked to watch these
women's we told like your dreams are
not a good idea whatever i don't
know i just i really don't like
it i find it very unpleasant you
know a lot of men's rooms still
don't have baby changing stations and that's
insane but someone was i think it
was eric swalwell or whatever so sorry
saying maybe
rocky from mask i think the texas
um was saying that they were original
marty mcfly i think they were gonna
try to leak like make it make
a law where every bathroom every public
restroom had to have a baby cham
station that was like that's to some
i mean these little tiny ones
and like tiny restaurants come on i
mean tiny restaurant of course i have
a tiny one like for a tiny
baby yeah i feel like if your
baby's big don't go in there it's
kind of the same as having a
toilet like it's another type of person
who needs a place to change their
name i though i have a toilet
but i'm saying like i wanna see
me
yeah well by your idea we have
toilets
okay alright we have to take a
break
and we're back and you know what
time it is what time is it
paul i love saying these words it's
time to play three sher wo three
terrific game that we'd like to play
you send them in and three day
we let
alright it's alright i understand i was
trying to help i know i gotta
say wow i get why you did
um if you would like to send
us a three shirt to play on
the show ah because you get to
listen to us play why are we
doing this why do we do what
let them submit know why don't we
have three cheers ah well it's always
been a huge part of the show
it's everyone's favorite part of the show
so that's why people are like well
hey we want
you truly want to change it no
no you go no nothing will ever
fly okay it's like asking why does
david schwimmer like pancakes because they're good
because the best ones ever had
that's why hi it's kristina again
um if you'd like says thresher why
don't you write to us at three
mm us eight nhl dot com and
send us a game like game you
play the car a parlor game if
you're old fashioned in that way um
and we'll play it like this one
that was sent to us by kevin
h kevin
an h being very cagey about that
last hi kevin maybe he's an alcoholic
maybe it's hitler
that would be a drag that would
be such a bummer that would be
do remember hill street blues the tv
show i do yeah guy with a
pipe
ah oh yeah james be sticking he
was just like july guy ordinary people
oh he was that i believe never
seen it palsy
ugh you should have a mom no
we already did that and you see
um ah but there was a there
was a list you haven't seen so
why don't you i'm busy there was
a storyline at some point where was
the cops was going was was trying
to be the agent to this comedian
and the comedian was played by terry
kiser bernie of universities okay and he
had a talk in that early years
or is he dead from thinking the
very first movie he talks before he
dies right yeah i don't recall many
topics like dying and then that's it
he talks to the very end of
the second
to say we all had a lot
of fun but nowadays save my everybody's
somebody's writing letters to me saying here
he really did
but so the s so the this
comedian had narcolepsy and would fall asleep
on stage oh is that part of
the bit but then his name also
was vic hitler junior oh i remember
this yes i remember this dream
this is his stage name that was
the characters real real name remember every
american zika hitler junior i started watching
la law because i'd never seen any
episode so i've watched the ten episodes
of the first season sancho tele law
bom bom bom bom bom oh huh
okay
huh yes when i was thinking but
um i find a dell twenty fascinating
the corbin bernstein pale because it was
really good in a pilot for him
to do be a divorce lawyer and
they got to do like cd knees
giving terrible advice and all that and
then they ran out of storylines i
think three episodes in of him being
a divorce lawyer so they turned him
into an effort
payment
my god he's like i'm really getting
into entertainment law but it's not an
entertainment law business right it's a just
lawyer l a law business so it's
really weird to have one entertainment law
guy i don't remember anything about that
show ah the what butterfly was butterfly
the venus venus venus butterfly
remember you know this is laura know
some sex things yeah so so what
the kind of nebbishy guy is told
a sex technique called the sex neque
sex nephews called the venus butterfly or
whatever it's like this you put your
legs behind you the soldier drive women
crazy
easy or whatever and then he tries
it on jill ikenberry that night whom
he was actually married to so it's
not weird oh in real life yeah
and realised only characters are allowed to
do it and yes
so cut to the aftermath of it
and she's like i've never had anyone
do anything like that to me and
he's like well i live to do
it again sometime anyway who cares about
what happens afterwards but every bagel in
tinman everyone was oh that's right everyone
was like my roommate bagel um roommate
brow
and it parties ah but everyone was
like what is the venus butterfly what
is what is the venus but what
is it they made it up yeah
yeah and but they but when you
assume that yeah it's some sort of
oral sex weirdos alright okay i think
it's where the guy puts his legs
behind his head and then he like
kind of
crawls or other robots but yeah scoots
around those yeah it's like something out
of hereditary just but i think it
is alright thank you kevin h for
submitting this my name is parentheses and
i like my name is the first
introduces themselves to the second as a
memorable character simply by saying my name
is example my name is john
smith and i like swimming splash splash
but it's not memorable
watch
yes bad examples is what i just
said do you remember my name is
something like splash splash john smith john
smith you remember okay red container milk
stick but okay so it's memorable in
that said man bursting camera woman tv
it's not like my name is napoleon
dynamite and i like doing the dance
on stage honestly
it can be that okay go on
the show were the same thing every
time i like my name is john
smith like swimming wouldn't be much of
a working
the second player introduces both the first
character and themselves to the throw rye
he was going to be name his
name is john smith and he likes
swimming splash clash my name is taylor
swift and like eating apples chomp chomp
okay named new characters continue to be
introduced like this in a circle until
someone is forgotten nails are so hard
let's dreams are so hard yeah but
that's why you make the memorable okay
let's do it oh they have to
because john smith i don't think is
a memorable name unless you're it's a
fucking example dude named that and then
it is
if you met somebody named john smith
you would not forget it because the
name is so yeah bland apologies to
any john smith ah apologies to most
john smith's not not all you're right
some of them gotta be dicks right
it reminds me of teachers' lounge when
you know like every when people come
on bang bang everyone picks like a
crazy name you know and so i
picked jim smith to be the care
but then his name is actually gymnasiums
and it's smithsonian because he was born
into bayesian in the smithsonian did that
just come out or you planned up
i can't remember i bet you play
your little devil i don't know alright
but ah alright the forgotten character then
wins a point and begins introducing themselves
to a new circle new circle new
circle of friends like do this with
us
saying we found a friend there's multiple
circles i think they would start a
new or were able to pull the
audience they see what you're saying what
can you can pull the audience yeah
i mean that's only there i'm calling
that okay good yeah my name is
oprah winfrey and i love bread huh
home pong
her name is oprah winfrey and she
loves bread home pump my name is
georgina willen hema
and i love
riding my tricycle we aren't we aren't
we
her name is georgina wilhelmina and she
likes riding her tricycle we don't worry
my name is canuto ba doodle and
i like it because you write
ooh i just wasn't my as well
it's just no my previous reducing me
and me him and me to you
i wasn't listening to what you just
said because i was really worried that
you would wait do i say oh
wait a minute i don't know why
i was confused on as well but
it's like it's like what's it's like
you only remember one thing so then
i'm introduce
icing everyone re you oprah winfrey and
will amina menino
to you who aren't now you're a
new person yeah okay alright let's start
over yeah because because i hate this
ah you kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding
my name's jazzy pass and i love
pez click click
her name is jazzy pass and she
likes pez click click and my name
is ah
ingrid ah jones and i love bags
crinkle crinkle
her name is ngo and shows bags
crinkle crinkle and her name is jazzy
paths she loves pets click click my
name of course is tommy noodles and
i love dynamite by bang his name
is tommy noodles he loves dynamite bang
bang her name is fuck i literally
have no fucking love bags ingrid jones
you didn't know
what she'll ingrid jones chefs bags crinkle
crinkle and her name is jessie pads
and she loves pez click click and
my name
i've forgotten everyone so zester stallone and
i love rocky run run
i guess he did run up the
steps he famously his name is sylvester
stallone and he was rocky run run
this dude is someone i don't have
any idea has never introduced himself to
me so why should i even know
his no good loophole
oh my name is ingrid jones ah
loves bags crinkle crinkle and this is
jazzy pez passing as busy his busy
pitch and loves pez click click because
and then my name is wharton be
through the verge
this sucks what ah what about what
about we do i'm going on a
picnic and i'm bringing and then you
do oh no not this
famously i get this but it's alphabetical
abc okay i don't remember remind us
how to do it again she said
we're gonna picnic and i'm bringing a
an apple then you say i want
to pay between apple and a monroe
i'm gonna pick bigger apple banana and
a cancel can i just say very
quickly sorry apologies to kevin h
yeah it's for you boy
yeah work out was really hard it
was really hard it's a great idea
but eighteen but we couldn't do it
maybe paul you are right that it
was just that it should have just
been the two people why is easier
with more people oh yeah because you're
hearing your heated more time read i
feel like they played this an asteroid
city um i'm always trying to play
that
we yes um alright so but that
was legit that was actually my friend
there was no sound yeah right started
us off with the i think this
game would have been better with one
different than us who were not as
hungry yeah yeah we are very hungry
right i'm ready to eat alright so
do you wanna try the picnic thing
yeah i'm
going on a picnic and i'm bringing
apple sauce i'm going on a picnic
and how do i phrase this and
i'm bringing apple sauce and i'm bringing
apple sauce and banana bread
or double beam i'm going in a
picnic and i'm bringing applesauce money and
a bread and corn on the cob
i'm going to make emery applesauce banana
bread corn on the cob and um
dicks
i'm going out
she is hungry
i'm going on a picnic and i'm
bringing applesauce banana bread corn on the
cob dicks and egg salad
going on a picnic and i'm bringing
apple sauce banana bread corn on the
cob dicks egg salad and fire i'm
going on a picnic i bring applesauce
banana bread corn on the cob dicks
egg salad fire and grover from sesame
street i'm going on a picnic i'm
bringing apple sauce been
nana bread corn on the cobs dicks
egg salad fire grover from sesame street
and ah why can i not think
of any word that starts with age
you got him
a hoverboard i'm going on a picnic
i'm bringing apple sauce banana bread corn
on the cob dicks egg salad fire
grover from sesame street
hoverboard please one and
i me oh i'm going on a
picnic and i'm bringing applesauce banana bread
corn on the cob dicks
thanks clearing your throat just exactly just
to get ready make salad egg salad
fire salad grover from sesame street hoverboard
and i
and
jelly beans black only
i'm going on a picnic i'm bringing
applesauce banana bread corn on the cob
dicks egg salad fire ah grover from
sesame street a hoverboard i me
jelly beans black only and can issues
a million things coming amazon's been integrated
corluka up
d excess
exile it fire grover from sesame street
a hoverboard and i jelly beans black
only ah conditions and
land o'lakes margarine i'm going on a
picnic i'm bringing ample sauce banana bread
cornell kolb dicks exhale lid fire grover
for sesame street
hoverboard i'm me jelly beans black only
conditions land o'lakes butter
what land the lakes butter land the
lakes but tom j ah hello
marjorie marjorie yeah that should count because
you said the l part lead character
as we were playing the santa likes
margarine and um and mackenzie phillips memoir
double ams i'm going on a picnic
i'm bringing apple sauce
saas banana bread corn on the cob
dicks egg salad fire grover from sesame
street hoverboard i me ah jelly beans
black only conditions land lakes margarine and
mackenzie phillips's memoir am
and nothing else
i'm going to picnic yeah ah i'm
bringing apples thank you sauce
oh and sauce for ah banana bread
corn on the cob dicks egg salad
fire group for sesame street hoverboard ny
jelly beans black only ah conditions linda
likes margarine and the kennedy phyllis memoir
ah nothing else oh
i'm going to pick i'm bringing apples
husband in but could the cup dicks
exile
go for the cheap hoverboard i mean
jelly beans black only condition men like
spurgeon
mackenzie phillips memoir nothing else oh penises
i'm going on a picnic i'm bringing
applesauce banana bread corn on the cob
dicks egg salad fire grover from sesame
street hoverboard ny
jelly beans black only conditions landlady margarine
mackenzie phillips memoir nothing else oh penises
ah what's up to the oh yeah
and quilts
i have been in business and bringing
episodes
episode episodes
episode seven fifty episodes but in a
big corner the curb takes each other's
fire groups as street have a burden
i call the beans black licks my
dream nothing else oh bean aziz ah
quilts and
oh ragu
i'm going to put com bringing applesauce
banana bread cola coke dicks
solid fire grow from saucers straight from
abroad
i mean till the beans black holo
kind of shoes linda looks mom because
it will swim well nothing else oh
penises quilts ragu and of course snakeskin
i'm i'm kind of picnic
bringing up assad's been outta road corluka
six hallowed fuh grover from sesame street
e lead hoverboard ny me
jellybeans like only can issue lakes margarine
mackenzie phillips sm whoa nothing else oh
quilts rgu snakeskin and timeout magazine
time out new york
is that what this cause
i'm simply going in a picnic and
i'm bringing episodes i've been in a
bread cone on the cobe ah deeks
is allowed day a how you say
fire a grover from assessments tribal and
have a board and i
in a jeremy bracco lee like moran
they make lovely memoir a nothing at
all beans
quills raghu a snake's gown tumult new
york magazine ah balloon oh no umbrella
wow kong i feel seen
i'm going on a picnic i'm bringing
applesauce banana bread cornell called dick's solid
fire of a row grover processors to
the hoverboard i made jelly beans black
oline conditioners lender legs murdering mackenzie phelps
memoir nothing else oh penises cool
oil swag ooh snakeskin timeout new york
balloon i mean umbrella
and uh victrola
i'm going to picnic and bring more
to getting your apple sauce red corn
on the cob dicks egg salad fire
grover from sesame street hoverboard i e
jelly beans black only can issues land
lakes margarine mackenzie phillips memoir nothing else
oh penises quilts ragu snakes
akin timeout new york magazine balloons i
mean umbrella ah victrola and wild an
hour episodes
many
half of one wow
episodes
i'm going on a picnic i'm bringing
apple sauce banana bread corn on the
cob dicks esq salad fire grover from
sesame street hoverboard ny jellybeans black only
the conditions linda lake's margarine mackenzie phillips
memoir nothing else oh peanut
aces
quilts rgu snake skin timeout new york
um the balloons i mean umbrella ah
victrola ah wild and out half an
episode ah and an x-ray of my
yeah
i'm going over on a pig i
don't know i don't know how to
ram i'm bringing
applesauce banana bread corn on the cob
dicks egg salad fire
grover from sesame street hoverboard i me
jellybeans black only conditions lund are like
smarter in mackenzie phillips wilmore nothing else
oh penises
quilts ragu
snakeskin timeout new york
balloons i remember allies um victrola
wild note episode
extra of my leg
yak blood
home scott
ah going on a picnic and i'm
bringing apple sauce banana bread
cow deck exactly fire grows from sesame
street loverboy ny me generally means yeah
only commission is black lakes larger red
mackenzie phillips ny yes oh p s
well ready to stay
skin type out
yeah
wow yeah extra ah well now now
ow ow my leg
yeah and a zombie of zero moscow
oh we were too good at that
nobody messed up and everyone was great
well i love us and i love
the listeners and ah thank you for
listening to us if you would like
to if you want a three cheer
you wanna say well your body's um
so only if you want those two
things listen you gotta get to three
mmmm eps because that is where that
additional content where we answer your voicemail
three other wheels every other week and
it it gives a little prompt of
things to talk about it's a lot
of fun it's a little mini sort
of three and you can find
those at cb world and apple podcast
premium that's right and also don't forget
about three visiting on the choose that
as our older episodes vintage classic episodes
coming out from bow and the bay
whoa
put it back also if you want
to write to us write to us
at three m usa gmail and leave
us a voicemail it had claims eight
dot com i think that's really at
lorne that's all i got yep and
until then cya smell ya lima you
smell ya later beta back