about how the
nah but three huh
i'm not picking up some saturate
the name of the show oh that
is the name of the show and
we are the people that make the
show happen mine this misdemeanor ellie i'm
missy misdemeanor elliott to the second time
the c misdemeanor elliott the third coming
to you live we are a family
of missy misdemeanor elliott and we are
proud to give you this podcast just
together we're a felony
that's right three minutes meters racetrack you
ever been stung by a jellyfish ah
no no you want to yeah i've
desperately because i have one yes yes
throw one at him well i just
want someone to pee on me it's
apparently the solution just everyone knows i
recently learned that actually doesn't do any
so stop doing who freak was the
person who suggests
did it in the first prankster
i gotta piss on you that'll solve
it
in your face but i mean i
really read that's not a thing that
i you i mean look i hear
you say that because people really i
have no idea where i heard say
a jellyfish stings you okay okay there's
nothing around for miles and miles someone
says like look let me try to
the whole pissing on you thing you're
telling me you're going to
say like no i read this not
a thing i mean horrible pain i
would like but don't try piss on
me for sure just to see who
would you let piss on mike well
if it was ah it depends on
who i was with you know if
it was with someone that i reviled
i probably wouldn't want them to piss
makes wi we have got someone wrote
well yeah maybe like we got lost
on a road trip and were
we're stuck in the middle of nowhere
we fell in the ocean and i
got a jellyfish thing and then i
hate that person and i'm so sick
of them and then they would go
along and piss on you and go
i'm gonna fucking kick your ass but
someone's like for a movie it's cry
every second good movie someone that you're
like feel medium about like oh they're
not my friend there mike pence i'd
ask them to put their piss in
a cup and then i'd pour it
on
on myself i'll take care of this
thank you well i can your own
piss not doing if well it's i
don't know if that's the case not
always easy to get the piss to
where it needs to that's so well
for years a little easier dear well
i guess if i get stuck on
my ankle i could just pee right
on that yeah what if but if
you gotta suck on your hand you
could pee on that
what could you know no my hand
can't reach oh no you've never wiped
i love this how can you not
be i couldn't pay my own but
i could yeah my back what if
you're upside down
i guess i'd have to hang upside
down p hope that it runs if
you were trapped way if you were
trapped by someone who kidnapped you with
a hung you upside down you would
have to pee on your own bag
to get the jellyfish sing-off now there's
no jellyfish just push them out so
they let you go yeah um she's
crazy well i mean take a beating
for a second
ah yeah this this is older ones
that happened a month ago let's let's
get into old business and yeah okay
i was having a delightful time at
disneyland you are stung at disneyland that's
the worry was on my i kind
of felt me on my hand and
i looked down on a b which
is kind of live showing like a
yellowjacket a big a big big
fluffy but not a bumblebee just because
you offer it was ah it wasn't
a i feel like you're inventing a
category of be it was a thick
b o thick which was to see
ya to season two e's and i
started slapping onto my nephew i was
like wow trying to get it off
like using him as like lev
bridge to kick it off my hand
and then it was literally sticking it's
fucking ass into me as i was
doing that and stinging me and it
was horrible and it really more than
once no it's just send me really
hard and then the stinger was in
my hand this is why you like
always always carry a flower i guess
it's a bumblebee i did have a
little ball on the end i don't
know it's the abdomen
you always carry a flower because that
way you can lure the bee to
the flower and i shit on that
yeah anyway it was kind of dramatic
but everything was fine but it's one
of those flowers that squirts water so
that when it lands on it you
just scored it to be as humiliate
oh that's funny and should shrink down
it gets even smaller than a b
what is smaller than to be nothing
i hit they have one thing why
the iodine know the idea that these
that's it that bumblebee inner they currently
thin yeah the idea that bumblebees their
big move is to sting but then
they it kills them i know like
there's
just die away but is that not
true of all these no i don't
think so really i felt all bees
yellow jackets continue and be like huh
i sort of think that's why it
was a yellow jacket that i killed
in my home recently
um because it looks different that's really
evil it had a really evil advocating
yellow i'm gonna chemical what a yellow
jacket is because i thought i told
you the story of when i was
running on those checks and like those
woodchips i thought i got stung by
a million yellowjackets you think the show
will pop up first and your google
search while i typed in yellow j
w
c k r y e let's see
me okay and it said yellowjacket now
here i'm looking at it it's yep
yep that's definitely definitely what i got
like you know why we go looks
like you're standing people oh yeah i
think so evil energy tonight hate looks
so me they love soda it's sick
it's fucking bow they love sweet that
when we were in love so yeah
look and see if they can sting
and remain alive because i think they
came when we were in thailand we
we were in our hotel room and
we pulled the drapes and right outside
the window hanging from the above balcony
was the most giant probably
he as big as your torso like
hive it's big length torso yeah that's
multiple feet can i just say it
was but but but bulbous oh my
gosh thank you so much
alright so real quickly so it was
a hive hanging outside the window honey
bee yes she's die after stinging no
other bee now that actually pisses me
off that's i used a picture of
a honeybee okay honey so what what
is it about the honeybee that makes
them die because they're filled with honey
there's so full of honey they're like
kill me
i beg maybe a little misery hey
do oh i know you'll make it
i eat it was definitely a honeybee
that stung me at disneyland it was
furry it was kind of fluffy and
it did die when it's after it
was on the ground writhing in agony
anything it's stinger that it wasted on
my hand than what i thought so
bumblebee can stay
you and keep on living or is
a bumblebee just another name bumpy like
i yell i thought of naming a
puppy i thought of bumblebee was the
same as a honeybee well that's what
i'm asking right now yeah if i
would ever listened to me
i crying out for your attention okay
look honey i said honeybee same as
bumblebee i say hey honeybee same as
bumble me okay okay but there are
different um the honeybee looks like this
and i'm bumblebee looks like this huh
you see me
sort of a yellow but it's it's
more mixed brown sort of like black
bumblebee straight up very thick yellow very
thick black very thick yellow and very
fluffy indeed and like so much better
that sting war new honeybee that's a
little meaner than the bumblebee like so
what does the wonders of all these
years are very far
away okay is a bumblebee the one
that doesn't appall and they look similar
though they do look similar but the
signs to us muted colors so upset
honeybee said that's a hell yeah why
would father ever listen to this show
like the bumblebee is more black with
pops of yellow whereas the just awesome
color is like kind of brown because
the yellows bixby into the black
yeah fun yeah um so i got
something i don't want any of them
around i guess sung by honeybee because
i remember the stinger in my arm
with like the little ball on it
that was abdul yeah that yeah that's
so gross it's gross i've been stung
by shay sick three times i think
really in my life free only three
once when i was
ten or so
and you don't know at that point
if you're allergic or not so they
tell you to go to the office
go to the nurse school nurse was
the school nurse do all day are
they busy only you know thank you
all fucking day they put that's our
healthcare sign ice cubes into brown paper
towels put them into sandwich bags and
tie them up to be i really
wonder though like you have to be
there
they're an on calling sure the people
coming in all fucking day joe how
many times i went to the nurse
just complaining for all the time i
like my head hurts because i don't
like math you're abusing the system this
is why i had really put my
head oh what her percentage of school
nurses cases that they take on are
fake like kids trying to get my
head
that really did hurt fifty so only
because i hated it so much i'm
gonna say ninety five percent ninety five
percent right how think about that jaw
i don't think i ever went to
the school nurse but first of all
in my google or other we had
one it can be done there all
the time yeah but that's think about
that being your job where ninety five
percent of the people you talked to
are bullshitter you thank you for accepting
my statistical
i know it's kind of sweet of
them to like humor the kids yeah
but you gotta know every time someone
walks in they're like fuck here comes
another lie or schoolers i would send
the kids home every single time yeah
we're looking to share like they cut
the finger i think you're spending you
also should go home yeah but what
okay well girl they made their decision
i'm childfree by choice
baby i'm sure everywhere was at what
level of care
c f b c childfree by choice
it's a community it's it it's a
committee a community of lonely pasted dedicated
world we have each other we get
together we talk about is we don't
have kids and have sex yeah with
okay we also have sex with each
other
and try to make these everybody yeah
and it never happens we're all lying
and we're desperately sad you're right so
what at what level of care our
school nurses authorized to give their alleged
surgery they're allowed to do bring they
can make decisions but they can't close
them up
but like if someone cuts off their
hand i think they call nine one
one nine hundred and eleven
oh it was
sure fuckin head they're happy in shop
class there had to be a school
nurse just sitting there waiting for people
to come and a spray i just
shot it in woodshop and i um
i made a few things that were
really wonderful you know it was really
good at it yeah i made a
puzzle i mean yeah jigsaw you know
what's great about a puzzle
is that when you make it it's
always right like it is it's not
like good or bad it's like you
just cut it however you want and
then the guy that fits together than
somebody else's problem yeah yeah exactly i
made a little bit harsh how many
were using some of the puzzle sorry
how many pieces in this puzzle i
bet you it was probably nine
you know like oh well you're working
with er yeah i never got to
do it i never got to do
it yeah we yeah have we work
with the jigsaw to make a jigsaw
puzzle but she didn't say jigsaw but
i can still just smell the woodshop
now i made a wooden sudoku what
about those those puzzles you know where
there it's eight things in a nine
whole thing and you you know slide
puzzle you
know what i like has been there's
there's a game that we have that's
really fun i would like to recommend
it it's called color coup and it's
like sudoku but colors so it's it's
basically a it's a i'm gonna be
like i explained baseball it's a wooden
tray that has little scooped out little
divots and we're basically where
there'd be a number on a stoke
ooh there's a hole and you put
a colored ball and you can't have
the same color going in the st
you know i mean the same amount
of squares xo so it's very yeah
sleeper per box yes and then nine
boxes interesting and it's really fun i
actually don't like sudoku but i like
this so do you start with colors
already in there or you have to
you have to construct hey it gives
you puzzles so like you have to
set it up to look like the
picture and then you have to solve
it now i wasn't listening to how
this game is played because i was
thinking of something else which i want
to share with you fine this was
a thing that i forgot to include
in the description of finnish baseball okay
which is this is while from a
previous episode yes which episodes were so
a little business
so the the batting helmets that they
wear look like the helmets that they
put on babies when their heads need
to be reshaped in finland yeah wow
maybe they all i mean finland maybe
they know hotheads and generals maybe they
know more about how it should really
be it's part of their national identity
yeah
if you're listening to us region and
we just hit
i don't apologize for my accent work
which was flawless i'm assuming yeah
um what are you thinking about color
cu why do you like that instead
of sudoku because it's colors instead of
numbers that's the only thing i don't
know for some reason well i've never
really i've only tried to doku a
couple times and felt very like i
don't really get what i'm doing here
messing it up it's the exact same
as color i know but i actually
i was looking at color coup yesterday
going maybe i would be good at
sudoku if i could do this you
probably would because it's not edition or
anything like that it's literally just and
i mean exactly what you're doing with
it is it's just that um sudoku
numbers yeah yeah but you're not adding
them together you have never seen one
of each in each row and and
and align or whatever you call it
yeah up in each box in each
line
vertically and horizontally horizontally ammo boxes lines
and rows yeah about yeah it's two
inches which one would you prefer they
get
boxes i think the boxes yeah i
know it isn't row
contained you know and it's like it
makes me feel bad for the numbers
i do feel bad um but i
love the game into fun game and
i recommend it as a fun little
like you know sort of put it
on the dining room table like revisiting
comeback or sit down for a night
of fun with here you know friend
is this a game in a box
it's in a bar
fox i think it'd be hard to
put it down walk away revisit like
yeah i'm doing a game i want
to finish i agree you gonna finish
get you you know i also used
to really love doing puzzles i was
looking at all my puzzles that i
was obsessed with pre panic and pandemic
times and i was like that's that's
a different world for me yeah
you're no longer into puzzles well with
a baby not only are the pieces
crazy she'll they'll get law she'll put
them in their mouth yeah the i
don't have time to sit there and
when i'm done at the end of
the day i don't fucking do a
puzzle yeah you want to be you
want to blame this on ray plays
up absolutely smoking style i want to
put all her toys because she was
like taking all the
or you know she was hogging them
all day and it's like i didn't
get to do it oh no does
she have a favorite toy um she
really isn't a musical instrument right now
and then she likes to um crawl
around like holding things so she likes
to hold the ah she'll get in
get attached to one thing at a
time but like she loves water bottle
tops like from like my reusable water
bottle
oh and she also has to to
be fair i got her like a
bunch of um big magnets that she
could safely play with on the fridge
that had her heighten and she really
likes that didn't let her say oh
you told me she handed out the
word satan right yeah she used these
animals and spell out the words safe
and it was actually amazing ache yes
tarantula as it made a lot of
sense yeah hi mark
ah finally given n animal and an
animal um nerve nerve damage
there's gotta be one i used to
know or wall narrow law used to
have a book that had you know
a children's book those children's books for
every letter hadn't had one letter had
one and then i bet you for
anna was norwell i remember a book
when i was a kid that i
saw it was
advertised on tv and my mom got
it for us and it was a
book ah that used essentially like pictograms
to help you memorize the state capitals
oh my my works on it during
the pandemic actually did you really yeah
how did you do we got we
got to a point where we knew
them all and we knew where all
the states work because there are some
states that i just have never really
retained exactly which ones which like yeah
what
the capital of california sacramento whoa she
does know all i know what's capital
chicago huh oh
ah
but here's the thing i remember that
book and it was very like it
with the the idea is it would
it would be an illustration and then
like a little sentence that was like
a story that would help you remember
like a mnemonic device yes so like
i remember there was for indianapolis there
was a it was a picture of
a flag
poll with like a native american
laying on it horizontally on the top
and like the the percentage was
indian ah taking a nap on a
pole no less so you would remember
indianapolis look at work because i remember
where only one or about oh i
don't remember any of this it's honestly
the weird native american could ever do
um alright guys i love that book
though but i don't i'm i'm mad
that i don't remember i wish you
still had it i wish they would
give us copies of um what did
you give his copies of recently the
book of les oh yeah the book
of lists paul lod paul and i
want to say i remember every gig
ever remember these commercials i don't think
you would remember them but so i
said this the other day i was
like coop did you give me this
she's like i don't know
it's like you forget yeah there was
this commercial when i was growing up
that was called it was it was
for a i do not say like
that you did i was chandler show
number commercial shimmer myself there is a
commercial
comer there was a commercial there was
a commercial comercial there was a commercial
for um this of french learning ah
law called muzzy i think and it
would it would be like this it's
sort of a cartoon of these like
little like and i was like uhm
duh it was like i'm learning french
and it's like he would watch this
familiar yeah dude talk going keep going
and i just remember continue and i
would play all the time i would
think i owe muzzy and i had
never won huh
have the opportunity to use it but
you would think of it as a
font family like a friend it was
comforting commercial it's even can find it
alright i think i've talked to you
guys about chisholm bob chisholm bob i
hope so
chisholm bob was a ah and if
for the listener is about talking about
this before sorry take a break take
a breather fanatical break two minutes oh
i'm assuming it will be two minutes
it was a way of counting room
and it's the way we know which
is and bob
like you would put your hands on
the table and somebody would give you
like a long multiplication or am i
just like a long math problem like
this times this minus this divided by
this whatever and so these kids would
be like tapping their fingers on the
tables on the table to come up
with the answer i never quite
understood how it worked but it was
a very brief thing that was supposed
to like like the the commercial was
as if this is gonna revolution like
revolutionize yeah and it did not really
catch on i sort of remember this
and the tapping of the fingers was
part of it of like okay if
you tap this because you have ten
fingers usually well eight
in to play the muncie covers alright
yeah we go through you're taking a
picture of me you're all your phone
isn't shooting
just imagine these jesus chris that's french
they're speaking no these children aren't french
and they're american and they've acquired their
amazing new language skills i've got the
range the remarkable new videos printers children
developed by the original casting corporation imagined
bringing up the language skills children learn
a second language
and bridge for sure
come near me jokey forward to like
videos which will become very deliberate tv
shows or train another language becomes fun
you'll leave them strong and begin speaking
and understanding their new language from the
very first new language unique method msg
outcomes with four videos to audios what
did it come with before it's good
you know you're introducing this for the
first time so don't act this a
lot of information muzzy now comes with
four videos two cassettes a parent's guide
you can understand what your kids are
saying about about of cigarettes are like
we have to take a break by
i am her back and me thinking
about that animal making me think ego
by edible book reminds me of z
zebra in remind me of when i
when when i went to the doctor
with my mother and this doctor it
was a children's doctor and pediatrician pediatrician
sure good
one had a ton it like you'd
go in every office had paintings of
zebras for some reason i guess because
their women delay you to delight you
but they were not delightful they were
not like fun children's pictures like brightly
colored they were like literally like oil
painting like well-done paintings of zebras and
stuff like that
that you know like it sounds nice
so and you're complaining so i just
remember well done i think kids would
say to the doctor sir well done
these are actually these are not like
for the high level really for a
higher level these are wasted on me
frankly
but i just remember we waited so
long for the doctor that i was
trying to come up with riddles and
i was making my mom laugh so
hard oh because like and i remember
one of them being um why did
the because it was some zebras going
on probably noah's ark or whatever they
were like going up a ramp on
a boat it was like why did
it was all in all zebras noah's
ark
hey i have an old zebra flood
fuck all you
like cyprus and that's it so like
but one of my rules is why
why did the zebra go on the
boat my mom was like why because
it wanted to go see and she
like cried like that's good yeah i
think there's something very sweet about that
and that your mom was going like
this child who i brought into the
world has made me laugh so choose
thinking and i am the first of
many here's chosen bob he will make
so many laugh
i am choosing my debbie and they're
going to show you an amazing system
for calculating math coaches
korean word which means finger calculation oh
it can turn a child's fingers into
a kek you've got to use better
branding okay brad here's your three times
been fred macmurray well just just yes
choosing bop is history and word but
don't use it here
that's right my favorite just zipped third
and two i feel like i did
this i figured it out or something
i just when i was a kid
you never figured this out plus can
i see the video while you play
it minus twelve i feel like this
is also based on blackjack card counties
yeah how card counting is like it's
not like you're sitting there going like
oh ah four queens three a's yeah
it's like i actually don't know how
card counting war it's like don't either
rain man it's a math fucking god
him when i drop some matches on
the floor you freak shit yeah definitely
matches
it's like hey man it's like you
you you go minus ten for every
jack or every face cards it's like
you're you're trying to get to zero
all the time i'd never quite i
think the reason i don't understand is
because i immediately glaze over when it's
explained to me yeah well that's everything
yeah to be fair from dumb
chisholm up choose bop but such is
mob things so we can use that
for the jitterbug game yeah yeah i
feel like i saw that isn't top
of everything jitterbug figured out exactly what
it was i'm trying to hold on
a second laundry you know some new
business are you proposing that from now
on we play jitterbug we instead call
it chisholm bob yes alright i
second scott and i think we should
call it chisholm but i'm i'm muzzy
i
that's the name of the game yeah
the money doesn't come into play but
we do chisel up in a french
accent she came up by me gave
up okay here's what he's in bub
she's envelop here's the chisholm box set
of french accents scott we need you
to we need you to vote on
this i abstained present alright well the
majority has it so so it's
it's about my muzzy and a french
accent chisholm bye bye bye mozzie is
the name of the game and then
we chant chisholm bop and french action
there you go yes ok here's here's
how it works you have two hands
on the table okay your left-hand knows
what your right hand is doing yes
so it can't wash it you're the
four fingers are ten
and your thumb is fifty
your right hand the forefingers are one
already lost each finger ten ten ten
ten five hundred and fifty for the
thumb and then on the right hand
it's one one one one and then
five the thumb is five the thumb
is five and then basically you put
fifty on the other hand i forgot
about the sex basically like on your
chisholm when young when
you get a question whatever fingers are
on the table you then counted out
you'll like you put the corresponding finger
on the table let's try that goes
bonnie finger on the table you know
give me a gimme gimme just ah
this plus this okay yeah jan plus
ten wait listen it's just card counting
isn't bob this is jim bob okay
twenty because i have to have these
two ten it also i know that
i was twenty i have these two
ten fingers up but give me something
any of us i know you know
you have giving theories this plus this
way okay fifteen plus seven plus nine
fifty fucked
there's no way he's gonna get this
fifteen plus seven fifteen plus seven plus
nine oh shit how do you do
this okay not knowing how do you
do the seven and the nine with
your chisholm ma you need to go
you should go piece by piece if
i go fifteen fifteen so i put
the ten down in the five uboot
the window and enter the last seven
but i don't have enough but i'm
sorry
how did that help you understand it
to get the rest of that dive
because whatever you whatever fingers you have
on the table at the end of
the problem you're the end of the
day but here's what it is is
what the answer is no because you
because you're still adding it up at
the end of the fucking day you're
going ten plus years i think it
means like one finger is like the
first
ten this week this week be ten
twenty thirty forty fifty so then if
it was f i got to attend
my pp and now i know that
that's in the tens this is how
they get you to admit if because
it starts arguments yes if you ain't
gotta buy it if it was if
it was twenty i'd put on my
second thing i bet in the break
in between episodes i bet you can
figure this out
and we can be we can be
a man i'm gonna google chisholm above
remembering long division how hard it was
for me when i was first learning
it yeah heart like i my brain
just shut short division you're like hey
she's called finger math yeah it's a
korean words korean we're being finger math
finger calculations
but i but have i ever used
long division probably
really me plus you divided by janie
i don't trust that you don't trust
that sort of stressing me out what
just seemed stressed out actually we're gonna
we're gonna figure out she's about oh
you're gonna you're gonna teach it to
holly are at holly samuel learn not
only what numbers are but what she's
drop is i can't wait to she
has like a favorite stuffy that she
care
i know she doesn't have that yet
i'm trying to push one i love
but it's not working yeah so jewish
like looks at it and looks at
you yeah she she will hold a
stuffed animal for like moments but like
not shown so she's not invested in
stuffed animals like shit like his friends
she likes she sees them as toby
around and she likes when they kiss
her in
stuff but when these doesn't when you
make them with yeah oh when you're
okay yeah they don't do it themselves
and and you didn't like catching killing
your life likes ah to hold them
like a second but she she's more
like she actually still care on hard
objects i loved the footage of everyone
saying happy birthday to her in her
first birthday i
and she's just looking like
what is why are you why would
anyone do this really was so confused
and does not eat the cupcake the
first time it was confusing easy what
do you think oh second time they
get it right yeah second time they're
like oh this is this happened a
year ago yeah we'll see in the
second time they realised this is for
me this is about me yeah i
don't know and third time it's like
old hat is like edyta yeah yeah
yeah yeah
where's the cake for the time it's
like yes fifth time it's like i
think i'm actually into this six times
like whoa wait what was this again
seven time i'm into it again eight-time
i'm getting older i'm kind of aware
of my mortality nighttime just like the
first time yeah tell i'm happening double
dizzy's wherein baby yeah and that's some
year that's when you
really take ownership of your birth and
you make it hap yeah yeah yeah
your birthday and made it happen man
birthdays i'd yeah you just had one
you weren't going to suggest selling uber
no no i know better than that
lea michele is joining funny girl on
my birthday and i thought that's a
birthday that's a birthday when i saw
september
six on the poster i thought that's
a birth that whole story is so
crazy and the fact that yeah michelle
and beanie feldstein of the same agent
is wild i just learned that yeah
like as details of the story kept
coming out it just got nuttier and
nuttier will be as completely ignoring it
on social media she's acting like she's
taking the high road
we'd be talking about real people
i'm just curious what's going on i'd
love to know more ios i want
to hurt somebody but i have to
sign up to read it i want
fuck this i'm so sick of that
i love that that immediately your interest
evaporates yeah when they're like that i've
signed up didn't like know are watching
for video i just i think it's
my first time
a web site that month i should
get it for free if i go
again have me sign up speaking of
commercials oh boy i wanna shout out
my favorite commercial running on the mlb
app right now but mlb network because
you know they baseball games as we've
discussed are very long and they still
games are very long du da da
da and they show you this
same ads over and over and over
again like itv or at the stadium
no on on the mlb network oh
you're watching tv and sometimes it's you
don't notice it it's just wallpaper just
fades in the background if something has
a song it can be extremely annoying
um but everyone's wrong you get one
that's like i don't mind seeing this
a thousand times and there's a commercial
for
i believe it's for kiya and it's
skeletons going on a date and it
says whatcha these are very cute cartoon
skeletons and they're going on a date
do you think a skeleton needs to
date another skeleton or could they data
human than be like look we both
have the skeletal it'll never work out
it'll even think that the person who
made it up was like skeleton
in key ah skeletons okay so it
scales with skeletons obviously forgot to do
the homework the night before yeah yeah
i got into the media like a
fuck ya ki kya kya skeleton skeleton
to come up with commercial then what
it's for there have been times where
like make his model yeah please i
need fifteen jeanette
eric commercials on my desk tomorrow
there are times we're making like watching
basketball and all that come in then
i'm like oh what is this commercial
oh weird and he's like the fact
that you don't know this commercial like
you're so lucky yeah i've seen this
five trillion times same thing on basket
but then it's also it depending on
what team you're watching you might get
different a different you might you there's
an overlap of the same
commercials because i are there regional is
that what it is the regional kind
of thing well i don't know because
because no they're not they're not tied
to like the region of the other
teams they're just like you know what
for all different things huh um and
so like my friend julia lives around
the corner from me and she's a
red sox fan and so we talk
all the time about the commercials that
we're sick of
and the commercials that are okay oh
and so i'll say like she hasn't
seen that the key skeleton commercial huh
what what it's like on this one
yet
yeah they go with a bone they
they i get it very smart laura
very smart that's the kind of readily
what else wow my mom will your
mommy trisha
cracked up until tears came running there
i do the skeletons bone it's three
skeletons and one three on a day
one is clarice some one's a butler
yeah he's a chauffeur and a butler
he drives the skeletons in the key
and they're in the bathroom dr gruber
situation well but here's the thing they
get takeout from a drive through
another skeleton quirky is this commercial i'm
just going to take out bones is
like a filet of fish and it's
like bread they're not eating scale keep
telling me but i have to google
what they look like they're very cute
and so wearing hats or clothes one
of those they are wearing clothes
and so one of them oh it's
sort of like ah ah
yeah wear those settings but i was
gonna say because sugar almost a sugar
skull but they're not decorated that they're
very cool-looking yeah sort of like pixar
ish yeah exactly so it's it's like
a more cartoony than cocoa yeah so
it's a commercial for this fast food
place no it's not scott and you
know that it's not i know but
i want to see
that was pretty cool that would have
been interesting if you had so they
own it they go they get take
out and then they drive to like
a place where there's like a like
a sort of a hill that's overlooking
a city oh like they go oh
yes and the and the the chauffeur
now he sets up a table and
a tablecloth and everything sets the table
for them and then they sit down
to have their
and there's no talking and there's no
name to be thanks the butler i
don't think they kiss they do not
think the butler it's his job to
say thank you with a check that's
right that's what that skeleton body is
for so um do they pay with
threads instead of money like as everything
related to
then with threads instead of money you
know everything into their nitty gritty of
how skeletons get through the day well
i want it this is world we
don't see the unit of currency i
mean they have a very short amount
of time to establish this world yeah
you know what i mean and are
they in a realistic yeah or to
cartoon as well it's a cartridge well
but it looks real is it see
through
no it's not see through scott
so what if i want the one
from the commercial you have to live
in the cartoon
see that's what's so far only brad
pitt has been able to do what
if i want this guy's yeah
ah i guess send away box tops
did you ever send away for a
little monkey oh yes dear goodwin oh
wait i see monkeys i did not
not only another little teacup monkey know
you could send away for those um
he kept monks back in the long
day ago let me look at but
if you ever get the x-ray glasses
second the low doggo i never got
the extra glasses
i was always fascinated by them though
i know that picture made it look
incredible we all know they don't work
of the guy staring at his own
hey yeah but it basically what is
it it's just like makes everything air
like yeah darling zap monkey eighty nine
nine i must have been expensive at
the time this squirrel monkey makes an
adorable pet and companion almost human with
it's warm eyes your family will love
who what
weird these young monkeys grow about twelve
inches high eats same flute as you
and even likes lollipop into perspective simple
to care for and train free cage
free leather collar and leash free toy
and instructions included live delivery guarantee oil
options only eighty nine
eighty five express collect mail check or
money order to eight nine eighty five
to animal farm send monkey tzu here
there's a lot of these ads so
so did anyone get one and it
was like had to have a monkey
let's find out everyone got them they
flush them down the toilet and when
i'm able to live monkeys this was
in the early seventy s
hold on so this is before when
harry met sally yeah yeah that's your
oh that's your demarcation of time okay
so ninety eighty eighty nine eighty eight
okay it's b wu h m s
got it h m s pinafore need
the wifi because this is really going
slow but anyways in the seventies
s wait it's harry met sally pinafore
do it try to get on an
outside zone okay so for coffee groups
of the sixties and beyond the ads
are mail order items for sometimes just
as intriguing as a superhero actually interrupted
x-ray goggles sea monkeys of course the
last page they weren't interrupt um
and then this is in two thousand
and eight a man named gernot who's
bobby hill told comic book resources dot
com is sorted tale of a mail
order monkey mishap who sorted oh no
so he spotted the app the live
monkey um he got the monkey okay
so it came in a little cardboard
box i'm i mean i'm se
being so alive monkey it was helming
to the size of a shoe box
except it was higher and had a
little chicken wire screen window in it
there was a cutout all you could
see if he looked in there was
his face she carried the monkey home
and brought it to his basement where
he expected to join his menagerie of
robertson gerbils where i've been settle in
the monkey began using the plumbing this
is a jungle gym
em what the monkey began gnawing on
his arm like a drill press can
i pause why he had twenty eight
stitches can i pause here one second
to say ah just having gerbils and
rabbits is not a menagerie it's not
at all in a basement and what
do you consider a menagerie i mean
at least three animals i would say
at least four deletes for yes
i'd say ten oh my god to
read this to you over you nope
didn't know you don't
okay good so okay so he had
twenty eight stitches from the thing eating
him the drill press bites surprisingly his
parents let him to keep the monkey
which he named chipper books and trial
and error gave him some rudimentary knowledge
of how to care for peanuts and
seedless white groups were appealing bananas were
not chipper also enjoy writing on the
back of the family's border colleague how
cowboys style who the fuck is sending
but why does all these monkeys descend
when chipper was about five years old
he died suddenly oh god he suspected
a possible wasp sting but could never
be sure did he interview all the
wasps and neighborhoods one that was for
oh my god
and anyway people say that they the
defense counsel says dave sorry to bother
you thank you australian i'm ok so
oh well i wanna say one more
thing where were you
so this was a big this was
a big moment in the sixties and
seventies where one hundred and seventy three
thousand squirrel monkeys were important to the
u s from peru and colombia seven
where they would household be a private
dealers or comics and magazine ads including
the warren whore publications that creepy and
the eerie so people were just selling
these by the boatload wow and the
butler
god oh my god so one time
this guy had a monkey that he
got from a comic book and they
kept it in a crib and the
aunt reached her arm between the bars
of the bed to smooth the an
ant to sue the animals nerves aware
where harm could go in a monkey
can come out said tate and outcomes
pepe and a monkey who believes is
about to go
to the next beyond and pit go
to the next beyond and panic jumps
out into escape bites the first in
franchise and what is that that is
my aunt's pendulous breast
this guy's creepy pinwheel is due rest
come on dude
ah okay well so you're telling me
you never got a monkey from catalog
people say
people say but load because somebody was
dumb and didn't understand that it was
boatload right well i used to stare
when people say butt naked instead of
buck mike and i could yeah maybe
buttoning is accurate but there is a
butler just naked a boatload of something
does exist it's dumb butt naked funny
i don't think so
alright look we have to take a
break no we don't yes i
name and it's three your time
and um we're gonna play oh what
is it cause it's oh la la
hey whoa beautiful day i got wooed
of all fee
everything's weighing my words called actor's nightmare
and we played it a few times
it's where and we're playing it today
because we're we're here in my office
and i have plays here and offices
full of plays he's always working on
a new one it's informed he has
little nights where he sets up he
he puts a cover over the pool
makes like a stage and then he
goes out there and so i felt
this man yeah then puts the cover
over it yeah
i don't my it i don't want
to cut the lotion it puts the
cover
but um
this is where we do
this is where we do a scene
where one of us has a play
in there yeah and we that one
of us reads lines from the play
and then the other two are supposed
to improv around it and i don't
know whether we're they do we're just
gonna pick this one i think it's
one on one one on one why
don't we do a two on one
it sounds messy but okay let's do
it okay so i just opened i'm
i just opened it to a random
place or am i supposed to just
do one character i'm sure i just
picked one character yes all right okay
um i don't know how okay well
we switch off no
i think one person should yeah we've
done this on stage before and i
think all three of us did we
did it toronto the one to the
one time but i'm saying do we
switch off so if you are the
one reading the lines i think just
ember i'll just jump in whenever you
guys like yeah okay yeah alright alright
alright no you start to see
i'll start it yeah gary comrades right
martin absolutely i never say anything otherwise
hey don't speak for me i'm martin
and you see what i mean martin
he's special right yeah i'm not special
i'm unique you are special and i
love
you gravity decency smarts his strength is
as the strength of ten because his
heart is pure and he's a roy
boy one hundred percent i was gonna
say that ah the fact that you're
a roy boy you love roy orbison
and yeah sunglass i love as saying
like you have that bowl cut i
can't see his eyes and i like
administering jos a married man martin
no when excitingly i married my cousin
with a wife she doesn't dare go
to dc and so joe cannot go
and keeps us dangling oh i forgot
your wife could see anymore because she's
my cousin we've seen that kind of
thing before avonlea these men and their
wives yeah i mean jerry
a six was a big day look
so that's her birthday so she wanted
something really special sure so yeah well
i watched from the car oh yeah
now no i'm talking about generally sick
now january sixth eightieth you fucking of
phuket yeah right now you're coming away
read came today
oh the mail okay so you have
a bill here while you bought a
lot of porn on amazon you have
printed bills into your house you're telling
me wait and fedex said they try
to deliver a monkey to you but
you weren't home a letter from the
new york state bar association martin they're
gonna try and just bar me oh
are they congrats this you wanted this
you have one time why martin
because you were wearing those gorilla suits
to court you were trying to get
fired and disbarred and really hated their
crop and the whole establishment their little
rules they will yeah you have to
break them in order to get fired
camp or can't get to spar without
breaking a few rules because i know
no rules because i don't see the
law's a dead and arbitrary collection of
antiquated dictum
thou shall thou shalt not not you
know because i know the laws apply
ebl breathing sweating organ because because oshie
i disagree i see the law as
all those things that you just said
that you don't see them as i
see the laws one thing what do
you see it as it's the thing
that kind of controls
as us in the best way like
i love it like i feel like
because i know the law i know
what i can and can't do yeah
well there's that
so you agree okay so i don't
know what you're fucking talking about i'm
deeply ashamed oh goody
yeah you should shrink down to the
size of nothing
not so damp please sorry i you
deserve that dampness and more i'll deny
it was alone i got a damp
ass pussy filmic she's got no paperwork
can prove a fucking thing i can
prove it
i'll tell you what you could do
i'm about to be tried joe by
a jury that is not a jury
of my peers okay who is it
topic just environment committee genteel gentlemen country
club men i offend them to these
men i'm what martin some sort of
filthy little troll hey hey well i
mean i do go to a country
club and you do live under a
bridge
ah well i would know you do
know you do know fancy lawyers these
disbarment committee lawyers fancy lawyers with fancy
corporate clients and complicated cases rye they're
not law so fancy just go to
dinner i feel like it's like what
are we debating yeah we're gonna be
late for a reservation know of course
it's not without the light of the
sun joe these cases in the fancy
lawyers who represent them will wither and
die you need to eat dinner yeah
you're going nuts
a well placed friend someone the justice
department say can turn off the sun
to your brain for a minute we
want to eat and hang out with
you our friend who we know so
well we don't care about your job
yeah it looks like you're a hard
thing but just let it go let's
have some everlasting breadsticks cast a deep
shadow on my behalf what are you
fucking talking about yeah make them shiver
in the cold
oh okay yes now i get it
literally we have to block out the
sun okay it's fine let's do it
if they overstep they would fear that
yeah i see that you're talking about
the servers at the restaurant yes that
like if they like you know how
sometimes when they sit down with you
to take your order yeah it's a
little too much yes yeah they fear
that you do
yeah i do yeah thanks for the
backlash campbell route i was losing his
mind he's hungry he is hungry he's
typical unethical he's angry would you excuse
us martin sure
take a walk martin for real yeah
i said sure you know what i
read something online like a tweet or
something and somebody said that they thought
hangry meant horny and angry so they
always like why people telling me that
they're hangry since your husband know but
it is something to take a walk
martin oh best i'm gonna do is
turn around and close my eyes
unethical are you trying to buy here
you are you trying to embarrass me
in front of my friend we're not
i'm we're not more friends than i
am friends with him joining me like
so it's not like boy you're embarrassing
really something what the fuck do you
think this is sunday school i don't
think it's
hey look i'm joe thought it was
sunday school why would you curse in
front of them this route this is
gastric juices churning this is zines and
acids since yesterday was what they did
yes say you're hungry okay so hungry
you're horny and angry and you think
you're what
i'm martin that's what i think above
that i'm not above martin i m
martin above alive is what dead in
the cloud alive is what what it
was finger said i'm like that doesn't
say you're sitting here hungry yeah great
they smell i'm weak you're hungry you
want blood this time oh god
okay look i think you should let
them disbar you i think you've got
to let it go we gotta do
something else you know you always wanted
to be an elephant trainer just try
it how hard could it be oh
martin's back yeah
have tarried around and sure nice try
joe
joe but huh
amen
oh not the sunday school now he's
getting religious yeah amen
heading into the play angels in america
is out what that was yeah angels
in america hills in america roy cohn
is oh no he's the worst he's
terrible i cut out a few words
that he that began oh no that
began ah patino playing these historical figures
yeah like chee paterno
though ah and doctor diff um what's
ebitda because we want porky and do
you want to do one paul i
have a different play yeah give me
a plate okay here we go i'm
tossing it to you oh good toss
you got it you got it lauren
how did you or paul how did
you feel two people doing it at
the same time was just totally yeah
yes funny
alright let's write learn and i will
be
playing he's gonna open to a random
page and pick a character
and lauren and i will be the
improvisers what are you doing here bub
oh i'm sorry i i broke into
your apartment because i was looking for
the diamonds that you keep sorry i
what i the diamonds you know your
your big yeah i guess it's like
a velvet bag but let me look
i gotta know i gotta look at
it to know do i want it
oh i'm sure you want it they're
very valuable but
oh and i bet you're wondering who
this is i am his kid yeah
i could make baby sandino ren dino
couldn't get a babysitter sorry anyways i'm
really i'm very i'm pretty chill is
embarrassing for us both but please i
beg of you i'm pretty lucky in
prison i probably want it what i'm
saying is what i'm saying if it's
worth anything yeah
they're priceless diamonds i mean that's why
we're trying to steal something anyways the
question is but what it's just like
everything else money like every other fucking
thing where you are native was his
name were you ah i was at
the rave why what's his name horus
horace you have um anything i don't
play with like what were you with
the riff games is flesh
yeah user is don't know why we
put the riff
without my permission teach teach was there
not teach i told you you are
not supposed to go anywhere with ease
took me there what the fuck does
that mean well what kind of a
bad guy in the back of his
motorcycle i bet yeah he's got that
mullet and the motorcycle and he's really
you just hang onto the back of
the mullet yeah i just grip it
with both hands what date is it
that don't
i mean shit it's june first come
i told you i told you that
you couldn't do this in may come
on bobby what's important in a coin
ah i mean look honestly yeah the
the president at you know what condition
it's in oh okay okay so who
cares hey i got to
quarters here these are um will give
you these two chords if you let
us go ooh yeah they're both ninety
two's they're shiny as all hell never
been used i haven't been in circulation
i got them straight from a dealer
the book is like you use it
like an indicator i mean right off
the silver pieces so on oh god
he's touching coins again yeah look ah
okay here why am i
just i'll just distract distracted
well look about belly roll little rebel
a little bit
oh no well what do you want
for the coin two dollars it's not
that much of a markup okay well
look at him sure look it up
i mean it's like it's a quarter
it's two quarters i only got to
the corner oh i got a shy
dad she's yeah you gotta help me
out should i distract him yeah do
a dance okay do you
duly lifted dude but you got an
idea about you got an idea you
can deviate from i mean yeah it's
kind of a my little take on
ballet it's kinda my little pony ish
watch this yeah hey everybody but it'll
be even better
he was a fucking sucker bob horace
hey don't talk about my sucker worse
easy job
my guess first of all she's a
woman not a woman yet well yeah
that's not true yeah oddities bob freak
oddities of nature what are we talking
about here the silver the silvers may
be three times face you want fifteen
cents for it
you said two dollars fifteen cents is
kinda lowballing also okay what do you
want for it two dollars yeah what's
a quarter let me see it look
at it shiny never been used no
brain circulation yeah to look in the
goddamn forget it forget it don't let
me see it oh me i'll hide
it behind your ear look over there
that was
credit where did you learn magic i
learned it from watching you tube
say i do magic all the time
and you've never ever wanted to watch
me do it the book gives us
ideas bob the book gives us a
basis for comparison we'll be talking the
bible we're human beings we can talk
we can negotiate you can this you
need money what do you mean i'm
out who cares i want to sell
diamonds but you i'm not selling the
quarters dad it's over would look just
take a neat about
take us to jail okay horace take
us to jail we want to go
to jail and take on dad and
ah they were going to play cards
oh hey oh yeah i think we're
just always constantly shooting began rigging rendering
the awesome like that look he's gonna
take us to jail if we don't
play cards we finally will play a
game
will play ghost chair oh goldfish go
fish teach in me and fletcher what
time is it ah teach and fletcher
coming over i don't want them hanging
out with her what some call rocking
time is fifteen am god you fucking
dad time for a heist i guess
yeah i'm get a phone but no
you would be a church
do you know what time it is
ten fifteen a m damn right you're
late ah well i mean you're a
little early usually you sit there praying
for about an hour after church in
your watch broke yeah well i know
i tell my dad he's just got
for me just go you that watch
that was an expensive super late
put it under the car and let
your watch free yesterday
so you've had it for three hundred
and sixty four days and it just
broke yeah well you look at it
you want to know your watch broke
all you gotta do is look at
it well i mean yeah i guess
you can hear the crunch sound too
yeah you give to me last june
first i broke it yesterday yeah why
nowadays
are you high right now i'm i'm
hungry
okay when you're horny and angry look
i i can take care of one
of those ah the angry barton let
me give you your antidepressants
you're going around without a watch so
why two gives a fuck not that
important well it's just it it meant
a lot to me no i didn't
you got it from the apple store
yeah i thought you were gonna give
it to your email a lot and
they were gonna give it to their
time an heirloom i understand it's it's
kind of yeah but whatever can be
paying you to do a thing
torres i expect to know where or
when por are you talking to teach
on the phone right now tell that
little shit i don't want him hanging
around my daughter i love teach there's
no fucking nerves involved in this teach
give teach a message get teach a
mess you know give them give me
tell you what if i see him
i'm gonna spank him i don't like
it i'm sure you don't yeah he's
not gonna like it yes do you
sleep in this relieve him alone i'm
not gonna eat teach alone he's leaving
he's bothering my daughter he's leave him
alone hey you're right he's
not that bad of a kid look
i'm just scared i'm scared rillington i'm
scared that you're growing up too fast
watch me grow
how did you do that you're ten
feet tall i'm growing out of the
house
you'll let me grab onto your hair
co came in
who teach the end the end was
so long before dawn had another line
alright here's the problem with requests that
are at plant which was american buffalo
by david may may and thank you
for a second pauses and ums and
uhs yes um the problem with three
people is that it
it becomes what here's what's better about
it being two people okay is that
you're forced to make it more of
a conversation right then when the other
two people have your own conversation that
has nothing to do with the other
person then it's not as much i
feel like it's not as much fun
to follow do you want to do
this to one more day one more
about
i only have two here but i
tried if i thought your your office
was filled with plays therein the they're
over there and i'd have to walk
but i'll i'll walk here
yeah it's gotta be a different style
okay okay i am i will say
i am starving well we're almost to
the end of this episode i'm you
made your bed raul you got here
too late you're right you know you're
right because i wish you'd gotten here
twenty minutes earlier we'd were eating lunch
right now you're right that's a vast
fact facts dear
but i had to feed my daughter
okay i'm gonna throw you lauren i'm
gonna throw you this one okay okay
here we go i thought he found
woah i love it and catch it
um ok thanks so much here's how
i can work with three people i
think okay how is it the two
people who don't have the tradeoff responded
okay let's finance just think about this
play last night
what were you thinking about
i used it in something i wrote
um mature chicago
what is what did you say the
thing we have to do we're just
going to switch off will switch off
responding to you yes ah alright expand
the beginning are you going to the
beginning well meaning of a scene so
exciting artists like it might just be
one lungs and
um
reading that word ah is another david
mann
ah okay
you fucking build it men come okay
but it's harder to do than you're
thinking you're absolutely right i mean i
have an opinion too i think that
it's actually easier
they have
say it they have stinky cheese looks
look like when they build your business
then you can't fucking turn around and
slave them treat them like children fuck
them up the ass leave them to
fend for themselves no no you're absolutely
right and i want to tell you
something ah before you tell me something
i want to call h r i'm
really i wanna tell you what somebody
should
should do well what they should do
is figure out a way to build
it it faster someone should stand up
and strike back who like the empire
somebody me should do something to them
okay well look i feel like this
is getting punitive at this point something
to pay them back
someone someone should hurt that murray and
mitch know that's what he meant by
punitive yes yeah i'm uncomfortable with this
kind of revenge kind of business dealing
how do something to hurt them where
they live you're scaring me right now
this is very scary to someone should
rob the office whoa that's what i'm
saying
we were if we were that kind
of guys to knock it off and
trash that joint looks like robbery and
take the fucking led leads out of
the files go to jerry graff
jerry graff is he the guy he's
got he's like really short and he's
like two feet tall he's two feet
tall he's always smoking a cigar well
could we get for them i don't
know buck a throw buck a half
a throw i don't know hey who
knows what they're worth what do they
pay for them all told must be
three bucks a throw i don't know
i had a miller
one of them once and they paid
me five dollars so i don't think
there is valuable is what you're thinking
the glen gary the premium leads i'd
say we've got five thousand five five
thousand leads that's a lot for plaid
yes yeah no i agree i mean
you said it yes and i'm saying
it right after you yes
yeah well because i worked for him
oh that's right you had a little
apron on and the paper had oh
no what do you mean have i
talked to him about this yeah you
worked to the cornell gonna stick place
the hotdog on a stick now we're
just we're just know it was corn
it was corn dog were just speaking
about it as an idea it's funny
me because it's a hotdog on a
stick but it's actually a corn dog
you think it would be like cornell
gonna stick but instead like you don't
get there and get like literally just
a hotdog on a stick yes you
know what i mean yeah chiggers so
you agree that you work there no
so you disagree that you didn't work
there no so you agree to disagree
that
you didn't work there when you worked
there as a robbery no oh i
see so you you never took anything
not even one free hotdog hey everyone
takes every not actually know oh wait
a minute no no no it wasn't
a hotdog on a stick it was
horns julius no not actually it was
orange julius on a stick
rick what did i say you haven't
said anything about it i just were
looking at those old pictures of you
that you showed us yes you wouldn't
tell what i said not actually the
fuck you care george we're just talking
george is just asking to clear up
your hot dog business yes yes we
sell hotdogs i think
it would be instructional for us to
know how many you sold per year
that's right it's a crime it is
a crime and it's also very safe
so you did steal hot dogs and
you got away with it that's right
i want hot dogs then have i
said that you kind of implied that
you could get us out did i
say that yes you i mean you
may as well have is that what
i said
it's heavily implied in what you did
what did he say he buy them
i mean ah yes i bought them
because you caught me stealing them and
i you made me pay for them
but i didn't want to yes i
would also buy them i would buy
hotdogs yes a buck a shot ah
i feel like you can get them
cheaper at the market however
they are that's the deal a buck
a throw five thousand dollars split it
half and half if they're cooked a
dollar seems reasonable if they're raw i'm
gonna say seventy five cents yes twenty
five hundred a piece one night's work
on the job with graff working the
premium leads that's too much for hot
dogs twenty five hundred a piece is
that what i said
it's what you literally just said twenty
five hundred a piece he would take
you on yes you want me to
fight him i'm not going to he's
this is my dear friend i'm not
gonna fight yes it is george yes
it's a big decision and a big
reward it's a big reward for one
night's work but it's gotta be tonight
don't i have a say in whether
or not he fights me what what
the leads oh the
oh you want me to fight the
leads that's right the guys are moving
them downtown after the thirtieth marine mitch
after the contest that's right marion mitch
are the leads in the play yeah
and you're where you want him to
fight them so that we can take
their place you me now i'm doing
it you ah i don't think he
should do it i mean i'm so
much stronger than him you have to
go in you have to get the
leads i'm very scared of both mitch
and murray because they're so handsome yes
i mean they're broadway quality actors i
know it's just community theater but it's
not something for nothing george i took
in on this you have to go
that's your thing i've made the deal
with graff
i can't go i can't go in
i've spoken on this too much i've
got a big mouth the fuckin leads
etc blah blah blah the fucking tight
ass company
right if this deals with george that's
one thing i don't want to be
part of this i don't want to
take on the murray there too handsome
i'll get nervous and start stuttering what
will they know that i stole the
leads items steal the leads i'm going
to the movies tonight with a friend
and then i'm going to the como
inn why did they go to graph
i got a better deal period let
him prove something they can't prove anything
that's not the case i thought you
wanted us to be
eat up the mitch and murray you
want us to steal that like kidnap
them yes oh that's i think that's
a crime yes well i don't see
how you profit off of oh yes
george
okay so i guess the ransom is
how you'd listen to this i have
an alibi i'm going to the como
inn y y place gets robbed they're
going to come looking for me why
because i probably did it are you
going to turn me in georgia are
you going to turn me you know
i'm not gonna turn you in i'm
gonna turn myself in because i'm out
i don't want any part of the
state come to you you're going to
turn me in yes
i am they're gonna come to everyone
okay sure but look i don't want
to star in in this broadway you
know revival of funny girl that much
you would enjoy just what i'm talking
to you answer me they come to
you you're gonna turn me in
me because i already said that i'm
going to are you sure he's sure
i'm sure we're all sure that we
don't want any part of this and
listen to this i have to get
those leads tonight at something i have
to do if i'm not at the
movies if i'm not eating over at
the end if you don't do this
than i have to come in here
okay so ah
it seems like you're going to the
movies and then we're supposed to kidnap
mitch and murray and then you need
an alibi i don't understand and rob
the place we're gonna rob the backstage
funny girl revival of all their props
and they take me then they're gonna
ask me or my accomplices
well but i mean we would not
be the accomplices we would just be
doing it because you're at the movies
absolutely what now that you say it
out loud i think this plan is
good seen ah alright that's it that's
it we deaths it we did it
listen three more stay hungry yeah
oh hungry and angry and we're all
horny and angry um were three damiana
say at gmail dot com if you
wanna write to us and something we
are also ah haha info on the
phone if you want leave us a
voicemail um we are three m usa
on twitter and instagram and if you
would like to listen to ad-free versions
of this show you can go to
sicher pr
premium or cbp world dot com and
you know what just keep being awesome
you guys are so awesome we do
love you it's true we love you
you're awesome we just want you to
listen to us and listen we're about
to eat so whatever you're doing why
don't you eat at the same time
and then it's like we're eating together
yeah
yeah it's like we're having one sleep
one routine goodbye
a