nah
three
agreed
freedom is the name of the show
and that tow it goes freedom is
a thing did you guys notice that
i snuck one in before i did
a little bit but i did it
at the same time so like i
got a real listen i snuck into
the very last libby reboot let me
rewind okay but really sweet huh
freedom
now hold on i heard it that
time that was before the second one
yeah you said it was at the
very end listen to go now threesome
oh wow comey oh yeah there was
yeah that was much sooner than you
think yeah interesting everytime like but you
know the grim specter of death oh
i thought you were gonna say the
grinch and then i was like grinch
comes sooner the grinch comes earlier and
earlier every year he's kind of like
trying to get those trees were putting
them up earlier you don't mean
helloween grid we're kind of saying it's
tree time and she was getting he
was in our village november first why
i'm like tapping his foot and it's
like do we look get the relations
oh yeah things they don't say about
the grinches how much he loves other
holidays and just oh my god he
loves them oh and he's very nice
about them like he loves valentine st
patrick for the party is yeah
everybody yeah you sir he does hide
rotten eggs which is just a little
yeah it's like an obviously will be
guy no i love that but he's
just so fun but anyways the year's
most fourth of july parties are great
he's very patriotic i love well he
loves america yeah he dies himself red
white and blue
how can you die yours your green
how do you tell yourself oh it's
like dice chair well yeah because green
is a combination of you should just
ask him you should ask him or
her stylist yeah let me call okay
okay call now ulu hi is this
the bridge yeah day look with the
branches get rid of just steal christmas
it's like the hits people put other
decorations earlier and earlier anyway what can
i do you for ah how do
you okay so you're green i dye
yourself red white and blue oh you
do i do i'm standing up and
saluting right now you're standing up and
saluting or saluting both so you're in
a saloon but your saying
yep absolutely look up drug
i have a drinking problem it's only
ten in the morning where you are
where you're up in the north pole
oh you're in whoville habit hawaii so
it's seven o cita
can i talk to him ah yeah
here's more let me give you the
phone grantee lord hi okay so i
was thinking it's getting really close to
fourth of july where are you planning
to have your party this because i
kind of got a plan if i'm
gonna fly or not well my place
is a fucking best so i know
because the renovations and everything revision of
their charitable the saw to the backyard
so
so ah can't do it there so
i thought lot why don't we just
all beat up at a park okay
what's the saying oh sorry he said
for forthright that was bigger okay hey
you're on speaker hey whoa are you
saying lord yeah i was saying this
your fourth of july is going to
be at a park no i was
gonna kind of argue again
ernst just pushed back a little bit
because i heard about the idea yeah
i know i'm and and this is
my response i feel that there's going
to be a lot of people doing
that at parks we're not going to
have our own space you know and
what i like is the freedom we
have around you to be our true
selves oh and i feel like maybe
you should write like an air bnb
okay i was the skatepark oh
i've been practicing my ali me too
and my kick flips yeah that we
could put hot dogs at the top
of the river rolled down to the
bud okay that's all i thought the
hotdogs were like a lure to get
us to actually do the trick so
we could grab the hot dogs on
our way down so you're on the
other just for tricks okay so we're
gonna roll him down the hill into
the buns yeah he ended about the
buns are waiting like
i-beam the clean the whole thing before
at least before after that's actually a
good idea well probably not before and
after okay also there's gonna be a
bunch of oily seabirds so bring a
bunch of dawn dishwashing liquid oh okay
that is the one that cuts through
the grease the best yeah takes screws
out of your way okay so we'll
do that alright to which k
part way with like what state it
ah it's going to be in colorado
oh and you want us to we're
gonna be singing proud to be american
proud to be proud to be american
he's got to be an american that's
right by lee greenwood so yeah we're
doing that as like a sort of
performance insult it's like streaming say oh
we saying i hope you die
dance as well can we add that
it's good can we sing to you
i hope you dance and then you
do a little dance yeah and you
know what roles going to see dominic
the christmas doggy well that's random right
no i just guess i'm thinking about
carbine okay but how much you hate
it so why would you feel why
do you want us to sing a
song about it if people don't understand
misunderstood i don't hate christmas i love
it
that's why i steal it every year
it's like oh you want yourself he's
mad i you covet it for me
oh hey oh do not disturb who
texted you tell us what they said
someone from high school it really so
high school chicks what did they say
something something about yeah i don't know
getting together like okay something about getting
together wow okay
ooh he's got a whole secret life
yeah i'm still friends with everybody i
do at school who did you know
or there is high class is grinches
species are your name both sound like
yoda yeah yoda's species today sky i
just feel like we should keep doing
the show like i don't mean to
cut come off but right yeah i
got a job like during the show
three of them like we're
in the shithole rachel has forty oh
yeah we're here wow paused diarrhea he's
not here
yeah he's not one hundred match what
happened to me
if i don't ball he's probably going
over cool yes he is the most
solid poops of anyone you know right
yes
well hey bridge it's been a great
time talking to you it's great did
you get my package i did thank
you so good i started like a
bunch of kanji oh christmas candy all
candy from california and colorado he liked
kang he always can't get california casey
but i think that it's actually become
a lawyer yeah send himself whatever i
missed it so
looks like reese's peanut butter cups snickers
and so i think you can get
it there yeah
i don't know
you miss california because of the candy
biz california getty and lord will send
me okay i do send him a
lot but i just i always kinda
think it's bullshit but i do send
it you know it's so many times
at the top i've never taught you
anything he put a tom frond you're
you're not one of these people who
requires gifts in order to be your
friend got it all
you have to be like i need
a big part of that is i'm
just gonna steal it at christmas i'm
so right but i do think your
love language is gifts it is both
accepting them and stealing like them yeah
so getting them to step out of
the bathroom hey paul is you how's
your poop is it solid
hey i gotta go oh okay sorry
hey paul you're back oh yeah i'll
go heels sorry yeah yeah i put
on my goat shoes why are you
in some sort of like saturn costume
for a play you mean your seder
seder you're afraid to be anti-semitic wow
ah hey we were just talking to
the grid for a really long time
oh my god it was really long
you don't be rude i mean you
didn't does not know when to leave
the phone keep on asking me where
i need to haul because that just
means he was gone along time as
what i'm saying well i see it
wasn't that long you were gone and
totally read thank you i'm normal
everything about me is normal okay okay
yeah you're the most normal person i
know yeah think you're great you're very
average yeah there's something um can i
ever say something yeah yeah tell a
sunny friday um to my yaf mike
setup fun date for us we went
to the law firm
phil and saw a psycho with my
bow wow and it was so fun
and i've never seen psycho hey we're
gonna need some extra violence yeah yeah
you really were working over time but
we were like in the second row
so we're very close to the orchestra
it was really fun to get to
watch them up close and look kind
of trading just like him you can't
hear the orcas
ultra well enough sometimes you know i've
never been there oh okay great but
it was great
this was a walter disney concert hall
yeah dude all that oh yeah the
acoustics are really good yeah i guess
go to the ball and they have
like oh well yeah like the orchestra
playing with a yellow yolo so yeah
the orchestra's just basically like a really
low keyboard and i'm like no i
want that thing pump i feel like
the orchestra in those instances is protesting
because
like this we don't write music using
zak yeah i think so they're they're
making a big show of their point
aiming their instruments yeah they're mining and
then they're pointing at the electric guitars
and zoom size down that's right yeah
yeah i think the only other one
of those i've seen is for that
documentary jane about er um jane goodall
um hello they have they had an
orc
no one it was like an event
for it but orchestra of gorillas it
was like impressive it was like the
premiere of that documentary something and she
was there and then they had an
orchestra blah but it was because it's
just random music right less impactful to
me than to have so they did
the entire score they just played a
few songs into the
whole thing you won't be fun is
to see like an episode of ah
reality tv with a full orchestra yeah
i love it when it goes to
poo poo poo doo doo doo and
doing that on this without really percussion
instruments when that would be as a
question
anyway psychos like being yeah i didn't
know you like that whole monologue at
the end where yes i loved yeah
yeah yeah yeah i love we have
to explain this because it's the sixties
yeah they explain why the why that
guy if you haven't seen psycho yeah
i won't even tell you actually because
i don't want you everyday although i
guess i kinda already knew
whalers just from living in the world
but yeah you'd never see it right
yeah we should but it's like soylent
green it was so good yeah i
was like this is such a gift
for lauren hasn't seen i know um
i have a little i have a
little hollywood story about psycho oh wow
um when the so hitchcock had portly
direct
actor himself by the way this way
this was an adverse like you know
this was an answer on the people
magazine oh really they were like what
portly director we were like shots fired
people if you don't know what i'm
talking about my instagram last week i
was staying in a big hubbub at
an air bnb limping out at an
air bnb and they
had a people magazine board game we
opened and it had been unopened and
it came out in nineteen eighty four
and it was trivial pursuit of all
like entertainment questions that were very important
to people at nineteen eighty four that
we had no idea what the answers
were it's so funny it's such a
dumb idea to make such a specific
game like it's right i think they
fire you don't
trivial pursuit was like so big we
yeah get in on this and it's
a lulu but they they mentioned they're
like what portly director when you're like
what the fuck is people magazine why
is that the first thing they talk
about what famous direct yeah really anyway
so that's why i mentioned so he
is he's ah he wants to have
a he's going over ah stuff for
sound effects
um gao or the different movie def
no way for the director was doing
yeah okay thanks that's so
and so we had a bunch of
ah hughes with the fully people he
had a bunch of melons this is
for the stabbing sound whoa she's a
bunch of middlewich all different kinds of
millage and squeal the person has a
a knife and they're just jabbing into
different yellen's and after they go like
down the rove you know nine
different melons ah hitchcock takes a moment
then goes
kasab huh
me say this album as a melon
ah did you think it was a
magic spell
sabo gonzaga cuz oh yea squish squish
with me i don't know but i
um really i liked that you don't
see the people being stabbed like the
name yeah right yeah yeah that was
great i always think that's ah that's
a really cool thing when a day
vector can make it so that you
see a thing in your mind that
was not yeah oh no show in
scream five i did like when the
knife went right into the person's face
oh yeah that wasn't saying but wait
i also have to say i never
understood that norman bates was like a
cutie pie nice guy
oh is that what they're sort of
making him out to be well i
think the whole way through he's just
like he then gets weirder as it
goes on but i didn't know i
i've never known anything about this movie
so i thought when i hear that
name i think it's like creepy you
know yeah yeah yeah because in the
shot for shot remake that gus van
zandt did with vince vaughn as norman
bates oh hey
notably saw in the theater yeah so
did i know that but they the
the additions are very weird because like
the the one of the only additions
that they do at shot for shot
but one of the only additive things
they do is norman bates in the
first scene i think jerking off to
a hole in the wall yeah he's
like spy on somebody and drinking
yeah yeah but i said interesting addition
i don't think i'd seen the original
a long time and i do have
to say when i saw that shot
for shot remake i was like wow
this i mean it is very i
gotta watch that really do now that
i'm a big psycho head yeah i'd
go psycho you're like okay you know
there's many sequels to psycho i don't
know that you're not bad i've
ever seen it yeah i think they're
not but did they do three they
did psycho two and three i don't
know about psycho for the voyage home
that's a star trek yeah um by
the okay so we're talking about places
we went to i wanted to bring
this up i went ok i went
to portland that's a place is not
wrong so far okay and i did
ah the show livewire which yeah about
you a lot they said you're really
great on it and they play love
doing that show the band played the
freedom
song when i walked down wow that's
also that's cute and i did not
recognize it okay um but because live
band was playing it's yes my band
and they were very nice about them
afterwards and i said did you notice
it was the freedom song and you're
like no i was so nervous i
couldn't even hear
over the chattering of my teeth um
but on the way back ah i
get on the plane and i have
the window seat nice yeah that's all
i wanted to say oh my god
that's amazing i'm so happy for you
so i have the window seat and
i like my dome piece against that
wall
please events why you picked on it
gets i wasn't going to say that
speedy
no world was i gonna say that
so i get to my row and
there's just the guy in the middle
seat who is already boarded and i
give skin over sweet customary polite like
hi i'm you know in the in
the window seat yes i what i
do is when i see those people
in the middle seat i go up
to them and i'm like i'm like
put my bag over the thing and
then i'm getting ready and then ah
right as i'm sitting down i look
over at i'm gonna go
like sucks to be you yeah yeah
that's a good technique choose your seat
earlier stupid yeah yeah so this guy
this guy point to the window seat
and i go hi i'm there and
he goes oh did you want me
to scoot down so you can lie
ah i'm just like the fucking bulls
ah yeah i love it what a
hilarious attempt
so good so crazy oh would you
like this horrible scene
oh the only thing better is if
he just did it like yeah i
was like sorry so sorry let me
move to this one it was so
funny i just laughed i would ah
that's because oh okay get out of
the i couldn't blow it was great
it's amazing it's awesome that's amazing amazing
stuff does
amazing um so the other travel thing
that happened was we went to tell
us there's gonna be two there's to
travel thing all right i'm not really
ready it's not a travel tip how
i knew what you were going to
go to a place that's how this
started you really took advantage of that
setup so you just wanted me to
say what the place i went to
yeah that's what i was prepare
cared for so we went to oh
hi this weekend first is a second
place oh my god worse yet so
you're just all over thy lamb i
land from this experience with this middle
seat guy and i had to go
oh hi forty five minutes later wow
so that's how quickly yeah last time
around festering around that's a real fast
turnaround going from one
a place to the next yes yeah
so it's the first time that we've
traveled with emi ah what was that
again she she was a little thing
in this wing yeah you saw her
oh were yeah yeah because i remember
thinking i'm glad that swing is getting
some use well i thought cool i've
got really little
a mixture of grew up and you've
got really little we both got really
little combiners honey i shrunk me
yeah he's drunk midi well honey i
shrunk myself so did you all of
those i think so i know he's
drunk the kids i mean i blame
y'all this it's honey we shrunk ourselves
because it's all yeah it is you're
right yeah scott hasn't seen any any
of those oh well human dna yeah
you gotta do the whole month of
those know but i do like the
first one okay we'll do it
i'm not available you see just three
episodes back you were saying you had
nothing but time that's not what i
said think the latter looking for stuff
to do like you did i must
have been being facetious the last time
i was at universal studios they had
the honey i shrunk the kids ride
yeah and
it was a while ago then yeah
that was i went to that when
i was like oh no it was
that um i went to that at
disney world but they had universal i
thought it was i was like universal
maybe it is yes it was disney
when they it took the place of
captain eo okay idea disney world when
i was little those only time ever
went to a disney place and we
were running raindrops going boop boop and
then the kodak film
lm yeah and that sprays you and
stuff well here's what i remember is
that it was three d yeah yeah
and first i was startled by they
say something is ah running around there's
like rats or something like that like
shoot-out air at your ankles and everything
yeah that's startling i was like yeah
that was going and then um at
some point a snake is coming out
of the screen right and i actually
like leaned back i love it i
live bucket it really got me your
perhaps our commercial fi that's how many
back because voting and like there's a
whole audience yeah duh yeah fat joe
when you see a snake coming out
of this league
lee joe oh that's right thirty prefers
um anyway so we up to no
high which i've only been there for
a day like the day i drove
up and down so i don't i
don't i've really got to explore it
but it seems nice it's very nice
of their ah but it was the
first time we'd ever traveled so lot
of furs
erste slew a lot of setup you
know if figuring out a lot of
stuff but with and then we it
wasn't the first time we've been to
a restaurant know i know i know
okay because up and i had a
date at a restaurant early on yeah
okay um but what g e liar
you know our first date was at
sushi and tap right no i don't
memorize these things i don't memorize anything
when to show so someone said we
got we get mind wiped after after
every episode yeah i liked we're gonna
hold it split between peep
apple saying ah they tell the same
stories every episode and other people saying
i do listen to the episodes multiple
times right so right so maybe we
sound like we're telling it a lot
yeah okay but sushi and tap if
you or don't memorize the sushi and
it's beer that's what you think note
sushi and tap dancing waiters know it's
nice
fucking kidding me i was aware he
never talks about this it was in
the valley it's now rocked by you
rockin sushi it's it did not ask
shit yeah sushi dan rockin sushi that's
so nineties it was it was ninety
nine yeah isn't a nineties to have
tap dancing as part of a gimmick
of a restaurant yeah i've talked about
it before
but i remember going to twins the
restaurant new york where all the waiter
for twins and i'm like yeah nineties
thing you could do i don't know
why we've talked about we've talked about
how they cover their shift although yeah
do you remember march twenty one twelve
one oh those restaurant in new york
that was just science fiction theme oh
cool with no but like yeah no
no i guess this franchise red planet
it was just like you know like
a space where there aliens yes there
were aliens not eighties there was a
restaurant in chicago that i'm remembering i
went to as a kid where you
think you wear your pajamas and you
get it was all serial it was
like a serial oh yeah i've heard
about this place no
yearning i was a kid and i
can't yeah i mean i was in
my pajamas and my doll was in
her pajamas and you know there's a
good picture
by the way i see the yeah
e t s extra trust extra trippy
oh actually no he's so extra otis
because he's terrestrial but he just takes
it to the limit he's so extra
and he's just so extra law each
i remember hanging out with him and
saying ichi could you not be so
extra tonight yeah he's an e t
two x
yeah i was like yes exact date
so it's e t t
t d it's very palin drama he
loves palindromes he does very fellow drama
darla it's so palindrome eighty my name
is adam um ah e d bad
about no i always remember the book
when growing up that we had to
read it was called hannah is a
palindrome ah
oh no what it was you had
to re-imagine to dan oh no i'm
no they did not hey look we
ought to take a break oh wow
i'm back i want to tell the
conclusion of this i saw here write
your rats
and then i've got a fun surprise
for everyone oh well right back
and we're back okay now previously we
used the end of the story that
takes place in restaurants and the beginning
of the surprise yeah obviously what happened
to know hey well we was everything
i thought the beginning was what do
i do right okay so we we
had been we had been to one
one restaurant with e d we've been
to one restaurant with me before but
she she and it was where we
walked down to a local restaurant and
we had her in her stroller the
entire time she was just like chill
and she didn't eat or anything she
since then she has started to eat
food so we took her to our
first restaurant chicken
sometimes um hold the big turkey leg
epic medieval
renaissance weird turkey like um so we
we went to a restaurant and we
said can we have a high chair
and first-time for the high chair at
a restaurant see i don't even know
that i've done that oh really yeah
we've only had it we've only taken
her to a couple restaurants okay yeah
so he isn't a regular cherished candidacy
that she just stands on the chairs
or we hold her still she wants
to move around so much so yeah
but yeah so we fucker so cool
up takes the stroller out i put
her in the high chair cool off
comes back in and i'm looking at
the sudan we've never done this before
i'm looking at the situation and i
i think to myself oh those coffee
the cups that the waitress just filled
full of coffee are probably too close
to her and as i reach out
to to push them aside she grabs
wow
dumps it on herself and then throws
it on the floor she burning she
it was luckily enough time had passed
oh my sense to come and she
only got like part of it on
her she started crying but we took
off a marginal scare took off yeah
it was more scared yeah we took
off dining she was crying weeping for
this coffee it's on the wall
udon screwed
she was i've never heard she didn't
screw up or that but no there
wasn't that much on her and it
wasn't that hot but it was all
overflow and the it didn't break or
whatever but he was like oh okay
so we need to move everything out
of her way i know before she
ever sits down because the first thing
she's going to do is grab the
first thing that's in front of her
oh well holly broke my comps
after yesterday no that was pretty sad
what does she do she there it
was so i had bought myself a
treat at clare v which is a
store that i like oh yeah absolutely
free food it was a no it's
a purse company they i mean it's
a brand they make um these fun
like plastic chain link things you can
like attached to your bag like a
decoration
and i was like i'm gonna get
that i got that and then she
was running around with it every day
since i got it and i was
kind of just gonna link that's annoying
because it's not like a toy right
now it's a theme you sm i
think yeah but i kept letting her
do it and then yesterday i said
impaired you yesterday it was like
she really shouldn't be playing with that
and i did take it away and
then she headed again i should just
put it in the closet she had
it again and then put them whenever
right now it's of fine and then
we're on my computer on face time
with my mom and then me and
holly and then she we we hung
up and i was like i was
about to be on the computer and
then she just wow
whacked the plastic thing against my screen
it immediately oh the screen the scream
and oh yeah my gosh so instantaneous
it's like i couldn't believe it she
didn't hit that hard like it was
she was right next to it and
just like she's like indiana jones did
i guess and i was have you
seen that movie i have like aware
she used to whip right eye
i started to say i cried which
was i think i was already right
there anyway and they are all like
yeah we're all just right winger millisecond
away and then i was crying and
then i was like hey i love
you very much yeah
did you explain why she was wrong
i didn't thank her i didn't explain
anything to her i just took it
away and then i was just like
fucking fuck and then um then last
night mike was like backing it up
in the whole screen went black backing
it up meaning like putting gas yeah
he was just like backing his ass
up against the window and then you
wanted to show you what we've learned
and then the screen went black
but um he's going to get it
fixed today so it was oh my
god anyway i was really sad but
it's like that's how quickly that's how
quickly it can all gen even like
she also likes my hair straightener i
have this like oh my car shader
and she's like hair hair and then
she like likes like carried around again
it's very small and i don't really
care it's cheap
but then when it's on and she
wants to grab it i'm like panicking
yeah so yeah you know it's that
i saw i saw some instagram video
where it was a baby sitting on
a one a sofa and they put
like a toy and then some household
object next to it and the baby
would go for the household object every
time yeah yeah
yeah i she am
emmy just wants like any anything like
she wants remotes showing our mostar's so
big we've got helping her own remote
oh you can order one on on
she like it or just don't want
the real she'd like it worked for
a long time at that age like
it worked for a while because she
was still interested if you put it
out like right you can put a
label on it so it just you
don't get confused
right right we also it's an actual
remote yeah we just bought on amazon
for like six bucks just like a
tv remote and that does it say
kids remote or no tv no regulation
no batteries yeah just put it down
right yeah yeah it's a good decoy
yeah for a while and then eventually
she realised that we hadn't talked about
that one yeah assholes yeah i'm part
of this family too
yeah it's the grabbing so so so
it was it was a good learning
experience because then the next day we
went to a brunch and before she
sat down and that's clear to everything
out of the way didn't take anything
for granted like she knows not to
grab them yeah you just push her
further away from the table you just
have her
across the room yeah at someone else's
you leave her at home
honestly i i i enjoy when you
mimed that she dumped the coffee yourself
you mimed that she liked tipped it
over the top of her head like
like like absolutely on purpose here it's
what i do with this
yeah it was so scary stressful very
stressful and scary and every you know
the people at the restaurant were very
nice ah but the people in the
restaurant were all looking at us like
these fucking i didn't like when people
judge each other with children i like
it in court well yeah i love
that i love that yeah divorce over
that
oh yeah visitation yeah are you guys
ready for a little something called taste
test i think i am wow so
i have to taste bitter want save
one for the next episode and do
one now yeah yeah okay okay um
taste test and you might have already
had this idea like two different things
one is a flavor of liqueur
roy that mike is obsessed with it
i whoa okay now it's a test
to see whether you were the we
hit here's here's what i got here's
what i learned from ah you know
what i would do yeah that's not
ok you're not a lacroix person right
i do drink lacroix but not i'm
not obsessed and i often won't finish
can okay
hi mike made it out like you
oh well he likes to kind of
you know make that the reason i
might yeah like suzanne right that's not
going to be a big man on
but i know outcast actually kind of
like other i like i like sparkling
waters but i don't think sparkling waters
i don't really like sparkling water say
this word limoncello yeah see cello okay
so yeah this joe buck's janey loves
this one
mike oh my god i cringed yeah
yeah yeah yeah alright okay so we've
paul and i both opened it we're
going to to propose a toast each
other
smell smells good smells like a sugary
lemon
it's pleasant i think it's good you
like it it's actually had people over
a couple different times where they tried
at different people and some people said
they did not like it and really
actually hated it had a muscle through
it and i wow really hate it
as well he thought i was gonna
be very excited but then
then now you both like it now
it's like lemon with a it's it's
not as tart as limited it's like
a sweet lip it feels like it
has vanilla and yeah yes and i
know i love reminds me manila away
for oh and that really bothers me
or you don't like vanilla i like
vanilla banana drink because you're so let's
name the vanilla things you like
um cake
cookies icing um ice cream checks hey
she's yeah sorry it took me a
while to get there ettrick i love
extract
vanilla extract is my favorite extract um
being um yeah ah jacks yeah like
sure why not just mish super plane
why is nick wagner would save vanilla
is a flavor you know is a
flavor yeah i love it i never
appreciated vanilla until someone was talking about
vanilla wafers once and saying like vanilla
because i always thought was plain it
was like a right but yeah we're
playing but it's it's i love vanilla
yeah okay so you love this i
by the way it's taking everything i
can to pronounce it vanilla and not
what about vanilla venality is what i
grew up vanilla vanilla yeah like did
you also say milk no okay i
didn't i never heard that i moved
out here malc malc milk do want
the second taste test you talked about
that martin luther king of course
now malcolm
multiple of art do you want the
second taste tested ie wow let's wait
on it because i'm enjoying this one
i agree i can still take data
it's it's an edible thing it's early
there's a little bit of an aftertaste
and that's the problem yeah it's very
perfuming too this is a great tease
for next episode because i was really
worried no one was going to listen
to the guy now so yeah we
kind of obviously were telling a lot
about stories today if
you thought drinking was interesting wait till
you hear eating on a mic um
yeah my problem with with sparkling water
is first of all i don't like
the texture of sparkling water the bubbles
in your throat i don't it's not
like i check when i like a
soda like a carbonated beverage yeah but
there's something about mineral water
oh god he's floating up to this
guy oh no i'm charlie i always
ate a roof
with a fan in it um yeah
i just it doesn't do it for
me i don't i find it like
it makes me thirstier than yeah i
don't know it doesn't quench my thirst
like yeah i've actually googled this oh
like i've googled is the square kilometre
dozen chapters and what did it say
i don't remember yeah let's go
get ah does spot our clean water
hydrates you but i also don't like
the um yes the flavor carbonated water
will hydrate just as well as still
water or it's what you're doing you're
not gonna like run a marathon i'm
like yeah don't er no it wouldn't
feel like it cause you're also going
like i'm burping and farting and suzanne
i'm turned into a slightly acidic ph
a slightly acidic pig it's a little
portly
but i also don't like the the
slight flavoring yeah because it just makes
me want something was full flavor yeah
yeah yeah and i'm jealous because people
love this shit oh i know i
love it i know it's not about
lacroix because here's something okay recently oh
yeah if you read i think it's
on the can i don't tax
where it says innocent and this is
that on the or is it just
a box like this since i got
a file it says it on the
can okay there's an exclamation mark read
it where it goes like ruggiero you're
spilling
oh you're spilling oh no wait we're
supposed to read what all that i
want to see the word innocent there's
no further information it basically says like
zero calories equals innocent with an exclamation
and i always think this is is
a zero okay it's zero calories zero
sweetener zero sodium equals innocent
exclamation oh i see it goes all
the way around and i just have
a problem with that because i feel
like we're gonna in twenty years they're
gonna go oh and that was a
really bad drink for everyone because i
want a hundred just doing like innocent
yeah and also how does it have
zero of everything i never understood that
yeah okay how how is it possible
that something has zero of any of
the things yeah this is cancer
water that's kind of what i'm saying
yeah yeah yeah yeah who knows here's
because flavored sparkling water is now the
default yeah everywhere you go yeah i
was at a friend's birthday party on
saturday and he offered me a drink
and it was daytime so i didn't
want to like wine or anything
and i said do you have like
a soda and he goes what do
you like do like like cola or
like yeah that would be fine would
you like a cola what you've this
is not a conversation that a human
being has had with another human being
it sounds like you're two weeks late
can i believe you said do like
doing a cola what kind of soda
did you yeah well here hola here's
this would probably explain it okay because
he's from mars he comes
twenty fifteen he comes back and he
has three sparkling waters because i realize
oh he thinks that's cola well he
hasn't he doesn't know what he doesn't
have soda in the house right i
see so he's like any while he
doesn't drink soda right and so he
just pulled a cola flavored water knows
not it was like i have these
and i said oh you know what
i'm good yeah i'll just be dry
and you documented his hand i said
i'll just have water yeah and so
i don't have that you said i
already made one trip for you
and then he ordered me out of
his house wow um but then he
he's all kind of soda usually like
and i'm like i don't know like
coke or whatever you've never heard of
and then never know
but it's asking me my preference and
then like a half hour later his
wife comes in the house with a
six pack of co ny so i
know but he sent her out i
felt bad i felt like i don't
like coke that much you're like i
don't yeah i was found to not
have it yeah water is fine yeah
i've but i felt really bad
they that they felt bad yeah they
didn't have a thing that i wanted
and now they're gonna have this six
pack that they're dealing with for like
ever know they tore that people tore
through it oh really oh people like
cool like oh yeah i know i
that happened to me though the other
day when there was a guest here
who's like p r person was like
make sure there's a diet coke for
them and
get this request like the night before
i'm like i don't have diet coke
of the house like feel free to
bring your own you know that's just
you're gonna run out to the store
but you but we should we all
should have at least one coke and
one diet coke in the house at
all times so my mom loves diet
coke and i do stock the fridge
before she arrives because otherwise we have
to go get it and then
i have to go do that so
it's like i gotta have it ready
to go always have coke zero in
the fridge yeah the little cans i
don't always have coke to be clear
i actually don't oh no that was
clear that was crystal-clear like the way
that you oh i got it so
you know what i haven't basically i
stopped drinking coke when i was in
high school i mean in college
because i started getting headaches from the
huge things of it that i would
fill up in the food yeah school
thing whatever and ah are you drinking
fountain yeah i would because i could
get my free refills and i'd just
like i'm drinking this whole fucking day
and then um i started headache sounds
like let me just quit cold turkey
and then i basically never had it
again except for you know a sip
here and there
and when i have it now i'm
like this is so good yeah first
first i would have it and go
oh it's really syrupy like when i
first came back yeah and the first
one but then now i'm like if
i'm sometimes you just really in the
mood for a coke what would make
a coke taste better
like um get rid of the bubbles
i don't think it needs to taste
better i think it's great just corn
syrup i love drinking corn i glug
that to cora i love raw corn
wow i love corn i love to
drink corn there i said it but
you know how likes you'll create it
you'll drink a coke and oh my
god he admit
you'll drink a coconut anyway they won't
quench your thirst you'll be like justice
thirsty afterward i've not had that experience
oh really yeah but they sell it
like it's like oh quench your thirst
oh it's i wouldn't say a thirst
quencher i wouldn't say it is you
know you're living let me look it
up it's not me thirsty or sheer
thirst sometimes he goes for me rewatching
i think you should leave which is
so funny and it was actually the
first thing i was giving birth i
like i think partly it was like
the first thing i watched her to
give me ten minutes after well like
once i was bringing in the room
i put it on and i was
like cracking i think it was like
so high from every but it's also
very funny and then when rewatching it
now when it's so funny
and every like i had forgotten so
many funny things from it but yeah
um there's just rewatching the genre only
that where he's at dinner and this
is like my favorite he's like yeah
it's like i forgot to lie
so okay look sparkling soft drinks okay
look contained between eighty five percent and
ninety nine percent water which means they
can help quench thirst and count towards
your recommended daily fluid intake so it's
one percent brown
i'm just sounds a lot like buying
that
oh oops from earlier shahada hey
grant was talking about i'm not out
anything like that fucking guy he was
obsessed with crunch blame it on the
grace yeah
ah alright it wasn't rebecca
and we're back oh the grinch is
back oh he's not just the branch
the branch the grinches bag dog holes
oh wow robot all are seeing love
that was like wow this is a
very good blow the bitch the attending
ah benches back yeah now what was
that tongue about um um bom bomp
she's lump it's in she's in my
head i mean eighty meaning namely it's
about someone who sits alone in a
boggy marsh totally emotionless except for her
heart i know because i'm like what
is that
mud float up into her pajamas and
she totally confused all the passing proud
to say as a child i love
this song and that makes sense because
it's definitely a goof troop nothing makes
sense sign for children like that's just
what that is huh
but it rocks is it from rocks
my cock song would you say it's
true how many cocks do you have
well not anymore
okay would you say you saved twenty
six yeah goof troop corps is group
trooper is your garage if your patrol
little of the burgers it puts the
lotion in the basket and it gets
the hose if you if okay so
if every time you add checks your
penis fell off and you had to
grow it back for two weeks with
digital never have sex again well i
think animals have that situ
tion i would because sex is great
oh that's right
i think you could last two weeks
without with your wife when you are
house when you think about how disgusting
sex is i know the idea of
it what you're doing i talked about
this on a previous episode that unfortunately
cool up listened to and she's like
oh really sexist no because you said
naked bodies are all disgusting well yeah
she was like and then jackie's ca
commented something about that and i think
it was in the sense that like
whole quote or whatever and then coop
was like this offends me
yeah she's fine but the idea is
we're still together we worked it out
when you break it down yeah it's
like kissing is discussing oh everything crazy
about these things no but it's like
that's why they the creator in his
infinite wisdom made it feel so good
yeah and he made us that's the
thing he made us in his
his image which means he has a
rock-hard cock oh all the time why
is that uncle how does that say
about god go what if god ah
huh
caucus butter ah alright paul do we
oh shit do we have a reacher
yeah we do sorry guys sorry everyone
sorry it's that time of the game
i mean show it's that time of
the time the time of the month
where we play the show gives me
a team
alright um this is submitted by rochelle
collins hey rochelle and some mal producer
who referred to himself as matt producer
which i really enjoy like that just
up so we're not confused he suggested
the title three h one storytellers like
like three h one bori
tellers is that a parody of that
yeah it's already three one for each
other and it's like scotus to me
like the for each club yes that's
right god it's a parody of many
things it's good guy wow that's clever
one person is a musician at a
live concert telling the story behind the
next song they're about to play the
other two people have to guess the
real
artist and song title based on the
meetup oh that's fun i like that
say it one more time because i
wasn't tracking okay i'll say a lot
of the people in the back okay
thank you rattle your jewelry ah ah
this is three each one storytellers where
the fuck did it go i got
that much so you tell the story
behind this
song is if you're like doing your
v h one behind the museum storytelling
whatever yeah and then we have to
guess what the song is okay it's
done that she got real song until
the story of it yeah love it
i'm gonna look at my phone to
find a song i'm gonna look at
lawrence phone to find the song she's
looking up i'm going to look at
the ground and just think about my
life
and how great it is not good
oh and and do we play the
song about about that afterwards yeah i
guess you ok i think that must
be nice transitioned the next one
we could do that we could do
that all right um do anyone want
to go first no because i haven't
found yes and no one wants to
okay
okay i okay i got i got
one this coffee is chicory
carmel i believe is oh well alright
we all do i'm gonna do one
yes
i'm not doing an impression of the
person no of course i'm just making
that clear because yeah yeah you know
don't just add yeah degrees agreed i
thought we agreed no protections you and
you want off doing if you want
to play it yeah you're done okay
and to just lowers riding the ox
yeah ok okay so
so this song it was so first
of all thank you all for being
so excited about it because it is
one of the last one i've done
or you are we allowed to talk
back yeah hi hi thanks for inviting
okay not anymore shout did you amy
yes thank you um so this song
was a song where it was really
about like a master fee so exorbitant
how i wanted more than anything you
listening to him i just had this
urge in my body to like move
my body but not only by myself
so i think that that was
something that came to me as like
maybe this is a universal feeling that
you know when when the sun goes
down and all these things start happening
i just really want that feeling that
when my body moves around the room
to the music or whatever space i'm
in
and i can do that so either
a room or whatever space you might
be yes and i would like to
ideally my preference would be to do
that activity
not solo
well whitney when you say you wanna
dance with somebody and you sing it
what the fuck does that mean oh
this is what she means
haha wow ooh where why how wow
one of the great wounds
alright
i gave that fade out i turned
it off thanks um i was fun
i didn't know how else to describe
it by the way it made me
very happy when i was in ohio
this weekend and i heard we were
out of market and i heard tears
for fears ah outside before we came
in on playing on the speaker and
i arrived right at the moment
in in where it goes to data
data data huh banner and then the
guy goes yeah do you know that
part of the song no i don't
either it's one of the greatest yes
because it's off rhythm sort of it's
not it's an award part right i
love i just love going yeah he's
just had a pilot stephanie i believe
we asked them about that
that when they were on bang bang
alright okay i'm fierce or something yeah
they were great they were on the
tv show yeah i guess they were
with the pirate greater yeah wow they're
so nice and wednesday we're on the
tv show a week later they came
up to me and they're like we
can't stop talking like the banister that's
awesome
i saw them do like ah more
recent there's like a there was a
video going around of them singing some
other oh yeah they have a new
album yeah that's what it was yeah
but was so fun to see them
and they were like so great
alright are you ready yes yes
hey everyone thanks so much for coming
you may be wondering why i brought
you all here i think it's a
concert oh you thought it was a
murder made someone's oil that was one
of the murderers i had to pay
oh so you got oh you got
a ticket to perform dress like this
okay so you're just a butler yeah
but then why are you wearing a
full football uniform
of the backstory for the butler
we were encouraged to embellish i think
you have the right i actually lucked
out i gotta go i'm sorry i
shouldn't be a cigarette if you like
it'll stick around if you like my
music somebody's gonna cry because you're already
in tell us about the song
okay this is about this is about
a friend of mine
he
he's in the arts and he's an
actor he he was in a little
movie called the big short
and i just loved his work so
much i love the way he chewed
gum and ah he was just so
interesting to me i said oh i
gotta write a song about him so
i went and interviewed him and ah
talk to him about his life and
he was ah he had a very
difficult
lt relationship with his father and ah
ah one day
he was with his father and his
father just ah ah
took his not his right hand but
his other one and just swung at
him and and hit him left and
it surprised gum it surprised him so
much and then he went on to
star in succession he's a real he's
a method actor and he's he's he's
incredible
jeremy by pearl jam yeah huh oh
shit ever over i'll forgive you please
look grubby here solgar clo rose removed
it's fun to sing in a weird
way it is but don't you always
wonder what certain singers were like did
you just decide to start doing that
yeah it's interesting because you hear him
talking he's eddie vedder is the one
here talking louder oh are you
welcome back charles o mountain toe ah
he's chewing a mention in that zone
know it he chews gum in the
soft jeremy strong oh he's in that
i've never seen that film i don't
remember him in that movie that's the
first place i ever saw him i
do remember here is that like how
is this actor chewing
damn his entire performance alright love with
his mouth open i like watching him
yeah so will
hi hail and thank you all non
impression by the way okay i want
to thank you all for being do
you do impressions some do the grinch
ah oh a terrible really bad we
know how you do de niro's how
will or could you milk me ah
how's your day
maybe de niro he just had a
baby
oh i thought you meant i was
my baby dear impression do a baby
nero gretchen
will you talk to lee but say
gugu gaga yeah babies thought i was
going to i was going to say
gugu gaga you cut me off he
listed i'm so happy okay thanks for
your concert by oh there's more to
it i owe even the first song
oh wait sorry sounds what kind of
culture do you think it was if
i was you doing baby janeiro brazil
we were
excited i wish
anyway ah ah this next saw the
results of the first saga it's very
important to me it's sort of about
time in a way when someone tells
you ah
what time it is and you think
well
is it that time now or does
anybody really know what time it is
by schoharie scba by chicago but no
i'm talking about my songs clocks by
coldplay
the song paul definitely notes yeah it's
be funny if you think that you
know i went to one aa recording
of saturday night live and the musical
guest was coldplay oh wow who's the
host was come on fuckin jon hamm
and coldplay did three songs yeah and
sometimes we liked that boy
better than having too many sketches because
the sketches aren't always great i would
like to see what moore's good i
never happens three songs it did it's
only reserved for huge musical artists like
youtube paul mccartney coldplay i've never noticed
that anyway this song is pearl jam
this song is removed
the bow girl this talk is about
questioning things okay questioning time
ah it's about it's about being unhappy
and is there someone tells you hey
hold on there and you're like well
i'm i don't want to hold on
anymore
what things would be better dao
cat stevens is that you know it's
not being paul mccartney you said paul
mccartney this is weird you guys came
to my counselor i thought you know
why we heard this was impressive meeting
said amy hero said anonymous concert
and we thought it was anonymous the
with the babies nero with the guy
fawkes mask okay okay oh so time
time time what does die it's about
somebody sega you know hey it's going
to you know what you stop you
don't have to wait for you the
bangles and or
simon and garfunkel lew two guesses at
once they sang the same side or
they did but you're rumble oh how
about cyndi lauper time after time about
her
this who do you like like what
artists do you like oh i like
somebody artists but bd like myself what
about us about just which is by
the kings who does that some ah
pink floyd does not so i'm thinking
this song macanese with the concept of
time in a whiny way
in a while anyway but are you
bob dylan nope
talk more about the lyrics is the
weirdest content of the play joel
stuff like joseph guessing artist talk about
the lyrics aloud we'll talk about the
lyrics the lyrics involve you know
who i am where i come from
who my parents are perhaps maybe who
my father is um it's about is
this about is ah i mean isn't
a matter of senator clay have um
like this about a receptacle that you
could put i'll talk gonna do the
songs please i wish ah i knew
what
you should do the concert and yeah
okay my career is this about a
receptacle you can put time in no
it's that this is about it's not
time in a bottle
damn i mean in part yes it
was it is this about a certain
feline being in a cradle that's what
i've been trying to get at i
could remember yeah it's not okay this
is croce let me know if you
both doesn't the cradle isn't jim croce
do cocaine cradles messages yes it's right
that someone else did
no also very cheap at their show
shape it well also the version i
know is ralph from the muppet and
the ralph's in the greener with the
surf spoon of but this is also
about maybe going out to you think
you're gonna find some satisfaction there but
that you don't really make the most
rolling steps on you is this
this icona pop
i wish it were let's just hear
that little song here it goes
oh and how alone is national news
now
ah ma ma ma ma ma ma
ma ma ma ma went obama obama
easy to find a bag bang baby
wow son
a wow
china's civil criminal
lasagna of nothing but wow i am
you man new to love girls wow
heard about a girl used to be
so fun you know and now he's
a stone drag i like his new
character though
what's his new character
the new moore's oh i thought maybe
he'd evolved once more
well that we did the feature did
we do it because check-in swimmers okay
do one more do one more we
don't we don't want to do what's
the song about time
oh but this clocks by coldplay excuse
me i just finished my constant growth
ah dangle dangle dongle dolce codigo guy
glee maybe geneva
where's the branch getting out here goo
gai grid see if i could save
time and a bottle the thursday bed
i'd like to do
well that's gonna be it for this
episode couple of things yeah then let's
say housekeeping was getting the sounds scheming
um are we allowed to play this
that's yeah okay who's gonna stop us
chris martin i'd like to see him
try on one second each huge tall
and jabbing real it's her turn off
off so he just got way hotter
um the answers is treating you well
i guess like johnson's down by the
way i also saw keanu reeves cash
plus plane and maybe fifteen years ago
saying and he was very sweet joy
with videos
i love it oh you run
between two ferns oh that's right well
i didn't bring it up either at
tower video when i'm old oh yeah
right and what did he rent i
don't remember that's hardly recall do shit
a written it down yeah and kept
the paper forever and never written it
down into your i don't think i
waited on him but i did come
up
and get an autograph for someone who
was a huge fail really yes that's
fine i read this new worry about
him that a person's either mother or
grandmother who was like ninety it's a
riddle
um is a huge keanu reeves fan
and the the person like the sun
or the gander own people old people
come on that's ours the son or
the grandson would only be fair to
people that are your contemporaries in aid
yeah was not really a huge fan
but he saw keanu reeves at a
diner or something and came up to
him and said hey my
is this i don't do this personally
but my grandmother is eighty nine years
old and it just loves your movies
so much ah do you mind if
i take a picture of you and
he was like do you modify color
and like chatted on the phone with
or fifteen minutes old lady how are
you doing hey hey
dining room i was leaving at the
counter ice to y'all to read their
tea he's like hey he called i
know i had to die
alright look here's the deal
if you're gonna give us a voicemail
apparently some of you have been leaving
long ass voice mails oh resume two
minutes in longer we're here man and
that's where we're hearing we are never
going to listen to them but our
mat our producer has to listen to
them yeah and he has made a
request please keep these under thirty seconds
where you say your name and then
you ask a question then you're gone
yeah that's that's
a reasonable request yeah but also throw
in a compliment yeah and what is
the number of that that people call
just call hag claims eight yes now
the other thing he wants us to
say about three years
ah what are some of your favorite
games to play with friends ooh good
call yeah some yeah like car games
yeah or hanging around games um that
would be cool to get some of
those okay we're looking for that classic
minister's cat feel yeah or a botticelli
let's bring back minister's house
i wrote wrote a truly what what
was the name of it it was
about a celli what it is by
telly in the version i know but
oh ah i'm gonna look at botticelli
is jackson pollock a really know it's
there's a wikipedia for it called botticelli
botticelli is a guessing game where one
person or team thinks
of a famous person reveals the initial
letter of their name and then answers
yes or no question wait there was
some other game we played that had
like an italian name that was not
that was a different game but was
known by this weird name that i'd
never heard before i don't know interesting
we'll never find out we'll never find
out but speaking of finding out things
if you want to find out
how to listen to ad-free episodes of
this show listen to them at stitcher
premium or at cb world and if
you have ah follow us on instagram
which is three at three am usa
and then if you want to send
us an email paul what is that
three dm usa at gmail dot com
lauren you have anything to
add i can't wait to see what
your guys are going to send in
that was like paula abdul when she
sounded all nuts on the news
i gotta look that up oh it's
good okay well let's add up ah
in between episodes and by the time
he listened to the next episode we'll
all have seen it i think a
will be will be dead by the
time you listen to the next episode
we'll all be dead if you're hearing
this episode i'm dead
alright bye bye bye
uh