yeah
um and three them to you and
to us all read mt you and
we are there what do you um
it's freedom day rather other day my
dad grandpa
my dear grandpa yeah oh welcome back
to three of them to show you
i'm paul f tompkins i'm lauren lucas
and i'm the show three to your
show the show came alive yes hello
everyone it's scott's body it's adapting di
di di di di di di di
di di
yeah atp like not even a parody
of the hustle it's adapting that would
be fun in a in a monster
movie where it's like an alien and
then it learns how to do things
that when it comes down to the
hustle and it does the hustle and
then the scientists are like it's adapting
do do do do do do do
do one season i'll be sure to
say it's elect
eric okay were you trying to say
that
why would you say that i mean
that's what i was parodying but i
didn't sing the hustle it's it's electric
it's electric um doo doo doo doo
doo
to to to to do do do
do do it's electric boogie woogie
wow can't explain it it's electric did
it in any boogie woogie woogie you
don't know that so many electric slide
eighty aber wait it has words yeah
why those words who can't explain it
it's electric boogie woogie we want it
and they know it had words i
didn't do it
yes i don't think i've ever been
at a place where they've played the
actual song oh my god never went
never been to a wedding
in your example are mitzvah they people
people dance it but i don't think
they danced so there was no music
they just say now we'll be chilling
a couple of coughs
ah alright everyone knows time for us
to do the electric slide everyone be
quiet shut the fuck up
um i don't i don't we we
may have talked about this before i
don't know how to do it i
guess people learned it in gym class
i was always astonished at how people
all knew it when i would go
to a wedding or something i don't
know how to do either but we
should learn how to do it shouldn't
let the three of us should do
it here and of course we know
how to do it i don't know
how to do it know how to
do it i do
okay well how did you learn it
um school dances bar mitzvahs things like
that i mean i went to many
i think it was mostly environment so
situation cause i went to a lot
of bar and bat mitzvahs when i
was in middle school i did not
know it was a bar mitzvah ah
staple well i know that at least
in my experience there's like you know
often
times a sort of bar mitzvah um
hype person who will teach the kids
the dances and you do it all
zachary is at it's own job like
they're just hired for that yeah they
might i once had a character that
was based on this um not that
anyone cares but um
so i've thought but nobody cares in
character i hate you okay um but
anyways they i think they do like
party you know party pump up sort
of thing and like go and you
sure yeah um have you ever been
to a bar mitzvah and whenever have
party oh that makes things party
that's true you do parties um i
i'm going to a my neighborhood was
all ah i think there was like
one jewish family in my neighborhood um
everybody was either catholic or protestant um
and i did not and i went
to catholic schools so all my friends
were were catolica yeah
yeah i guess you're both wrong in
your religious um i had a couple
of jewish friends but i don't think
i knew them in junior high i
think i got to know them in
high school so i wouldn't have gone
to their apartments i went to my
cousins when i was like an adult
wow two or something did you you
might be too i think you'd probably
be too young to remember this lauren
and scott this might be
on the edge for you but there
was a p s a edge me
that ran for years i for for
a little while i guess on on
um maybe they ran saturday mornings when
kids were watching cartoons note it was
it was well you do scott because
it might help you put it in
place in time okay okay alright huh
lauren is just me know are you
quitting not i'm going i'm jumping into
lauren's furious right now i'm jumping in
the pool too
um it was a it was a
p essay about to teach kids about
racism very briefly your calm and quickly
it was it was con it was
saying it's not good don't do it
yeah it was a little it was
a white grandfather and his white grandson
and a fishing boat and they're fishing
and ah the little boy
boy says grandpa what's a racist and
the grass look at the mayor the
grant well look into the water don't
spoil it the grandpa says ah why
do you ask and he says well
my black friend tommy says that i'm
a racist oh cigarettes pretty much as
well if you call him your black
friend then that is rape
just oh that's a good dsa yeah
but it's so funny that the the
the grandpa is like yeah you are
one i signed with your friends so
i take this
i mean and you'll never change this
of course this isn't my my memories
ah transcription of it you know and
i'm sure yeah i think real life
think you're like the simpsons but yeah
and also
interesting take because i like usually it's
the grandpa who yeah exactly it would
be like my listen i didn't fight
and w w two to have a
bigot for a grandson you piece of
shit
you're no better they like chinese my
friend thinks you are a bigot or
a racist who your black friend yes
see grandma grandpa you're not supposed to
say it i've got some words for
him
i was just watching this um
my documentary it's not i was praying
to never say a word before
don't think that it was one i
mean it kind of was i was
sort of like a dateline but not
dateline you know you know just a
little special around your estimate street failures
of sesame street and i kept trying
to watch like which years which fifty
i think the first fifty and yeah
mike i'm like why do you want
to watch awareness they skipped the first
year and just did the last few
yeah exactly ah he just was like
i don't wanna watch that every time
i try to put on he's like
why are you trying to watch that
and i was like i just think
it might be interesting and then he
just kinda like
of course it would be just like
really not interested in it but i
will say i think there's an actual
documentary about sesame street that probably is
way more interesting it wasn't that interesting
i think he was kind of right
because it was kind of just predicting
the future he was just not interested
in it while it was happening i
think both he didn't actually see any
moment of it but i oh well
when the commercial came on for it
i was like i got
to record that i got to see
that and then he's like why and
i was like i don't know i
want to see that and i don't
know
but it's just some story now i
know there was something i was gonna
say oh i'm sorry it's a strange
thing to question it it's been on
for fifty years it was four it
was such a groundbreaking more missional thing
in our child and every like how
many generations of children like why is
that interesting why would you want to
do something like this
so there's a perk though that i
thought was really interesting that they had
um there was a a he scene
that was cut from sesame street where
they had spent a lot of money
on this episode and trying to make
this happen and and had a lot
of specialists come in to discuss this
topic and i was all about divorce
and it was snuffling up i guess
his little sister finally get divorced from
big bird yeah there and then i'm
snubbing his dad who's like with a
big scuffle up a guest wearing a
tie and sunglasses or something glasses and
he's like what to see it he
takes the kids to their house and
like we're home and then they're like
let's go inside and he's thinking they
don't know
i don't live here anymore
all the worst way to break a
divorce though so don't you are there
any new he's like don't you remember
i don't live here anymore oh and
then they said that the kids they
tested it on some kids and they
were all so confused and sad watching
it it's simply the way you're saying
it sounds confusing except for one kid
who was like well they didn't show
the whole thing with like how it
was explained fully but it seems like
there's a better way to deal with
the topic of divorce than that particular
execution of like hey kids your home
well no i don't think there as
well i think there was more to
it it was more to it come
and i also think that it was
relatable because it's like if you're a
little kid getting dropped off between homes
like it's probably confusing and then you
have this little girl's like being reminded
like no i don't i don't go
inside there anymore
and then these kids were so hurt
by this this video that they showed
that they didn't air it but then
the people making it were really upset
because they had put in so much
time and effort not pleased eric please
air and they send know who who
allows upset the the grips or the
puppet tear the the muppets ears
oh the third they're still called puppeteers
i believe i feel like they're called
something special
ah well
paul rolled his eyes really hard slow
burrard i'm sure you heard it it
was like ah sound but i just
thought oh my god that show is
so educational and so interesting and like
to that's such an interesting episode to
have but now they're they're trying to
um meanwhile
i'm talking about r f k assassination
yeah he got into a lot of
shit on his show did he think
it was a conspiracy yeah you knew
all about conspiracy and you said documentary
about him mister rogers yeah it was
yeah when i've i have not been
able to watch yet because i know
it's going to make me cry
yeah so i'm gonna use it and
work on them and i've never i
i can't start now but how many
do you need all that water in
your body
it's most of my body is walking
a lot of people don't know paul
lives in a desert i live out
of decry doesn't like i can't afford
to cry i can afford to cry
this note it sounds like went oh
guys
boo boo hoo hoo hoo this talking
about sesame street though leads me to
an interesting topic which we have not
discussed fingers crossed on this show
is this one of your topics this
well i think it should be part
of lawrence not scott ackerman streets on
parade know you just name every street
you've ever been on come on do
it okay there's lexington that's where you
start
it was where i went to junior
high oh my guy
um no this is lawrence topics alright
well i have to help helping she's
never talked about it on this show
and i thought that we maybe we
should talk about okay we can address
it finally once and for all well
look um look look here's the deal
we may have to cut this because
it's too traumatic for kids
um i'm very happy because i'm pregnant
yay from the device oh threesome baby
no ah the father
but if for anyone out there who
is wondering why we're on zoom that's
a huge part of it so yes
yeah gotcha
transition to zoom because first of all
you we can only do one episode
at a time and setting up the
oh yeah when we're doing two episodes
at a time outside and then i
found that after both times doing that
i was extremely exhausted i had a
headache all night long
oh nine long hey k
um so i requested that we moved
to zoom and you know it's just
been so great for me ever since
so i was outvoted i said i
don't care i'm not pregnant so why
should i have to do zoom um
but low scots outvoted me so we
are a democracy i know i voted
that you should get pregnant yes and
i'm trying so try i'm trying yeah
i'm been injecting myself with so many
things
lauren this is great great news we
have known for a little while longer
than the public yes and we've danced
around it in previous episodes we like
dancing around the raindrops with your pregnancy
talk we've come so close to talking
about we badge right up to the
eve
edged ourselves right up to the edge
and now this hilarious release um it
can finally talk about it lawrence what's
it like it's so so first of
all i'm so i'm so excited and
happy for you and i can't wait
to meet little baby lap kiss on
castle
that's what i'm gonna call her i
was doing this girl is a girl
girl why not only talked about that
have we no we haven't i have
it anyway
scare saw jesse ellis god when when
you and mike got married did he
like turn to the crowdsale castle takes
queen
yeah
oh my everyone applauded i was like
oh you're so cool that would be
yeah
huh
i mean oh my does love chess
but that's a bridge too far he
does love his ah now you don't
have to i'm not asking you to
tell me but ah the but do
you have a name we do have
a name it's actually been um interesting
because um yeah nobody knows the name
except me and my
mike and um at my mom has
been trying to guess it for a
while which i had to just like
i will never say it so we
have to stop this but um she
had a lot of interesting guesses to
throw out there what was the worst
one
they weren't really weird they just weren't
really names that i would probably pick
like she said like danielle and i
was like no man yell like daniel's
a fine name i'm just like doesn't
that seem random for me to maybe
die now i don't know um i
was just a random she was coming
at me with like bella ella daddy
yeah la bella gela kela lulla
until something sounds right but we have
said it accidentally in front of a
couple of people and then they didn't
hear it was ah the perfect rye
i know my friend was over helping
us move some furniture
ooh oh you oh my friend bill
william bill for sure yeah um and
that we said put it in sounds
you know we said the name i
put it in so it says room
and then aw a minute later he
goes we did you just say it
and we're like yeah and he was
like oh my god i didn't hear
when it was ah
and then like due to the d
set in front of someone i was
like you gotta watch that tongue
secret but that means that means you
guys are saying it yourselves to your
to each other so much yeah it's
like it's just second nature to say
as if she's already here it's becoming
a casualty i feel like i use
it like half the time but it's
very vulnerable yeah
also because i feel like you want
to get used to the idea of
the name make sure you like it
when you say it out loud because
it is such a commitment to name
somebody do you have a backup name
just just come down and you're like
you don't look like a tonya slapping
know i have no idea i have
no other ideas so it's kind of
this user can i
ask is the name based on like
you you thought the danielle was so
random because why would you do it
so it says to me that the
name is based upon someone in your
life previously well that's so interesting because
it's actually not and so i think
you're right that the name is about
as random as danielle oh but
like it might as well be any
name but um it's not this the
name is not um half not not
something in your family not something there's
a knot in the fertile name ah
nah oh a middleman to and you
say the first middle name old-time right
no no no no no i say
say her full name
so this is great i had a
question yeah been meaning to ask you
about this yeah okay how much would
i have to pay you for you
to act like big sue for the
first two years
huh love with the makeup and everything
so she thinks that's who you are
the first two years so fuck down
i can't imagine how disturbing healthy and
not the moment i take off the
makeup i'm just needing she's like be
taken seriously how like tasers say how
much would you do it for if
if you were really
gonna pay me yeah i would do
it for twenty five million dollars would
you really do it for twenty five
i wouldn't do that
ah i we're gonna get question what
is the what is your advice to
fuck it's like oil yeah that's like
i guess i would take a billion
dollars but i would feel really bad
i think it would be fun after
a while like you know you'd be
waiting for the you know it's not
a gender reveal it's like an identity
reveal party oh why aren't billionaires doing
shit like this like yeah i'm saying
i will give you a one half
of your land dollars to do this
fucked up thing were like wow we
just want to sell our birthdays like
does anyone on my birthday yeah instead
you on musk is out there
dig killing it on our ship although
killing it on this of course i
will i gotta be fair he was
terrific i didn't watch it i saw
one skit i did laugh a few
times what you want out of me
i don't know i'm only a month
out at this point
yeah that's the hormones
so those are funny because people have
thought i was high multiple times since
we've been recording and i do think
i'm laughing more i think there's like
some i think i'm like laughing harder
and more during this time yeah how
is it how has it been for
you this like physically and mentally and
i guess emotional and spiritual everything my
god just like logically
physically it's been pretty good i'm just
you know very grateful to be in
this position so i feel like that's
playing a huge role in my response
to any physical ailments that i have
i really don't mind any of it
um so i you know i have
the i have aches and pains my
back hurts and can't sleep and whatever
you're shit back your pussy in your
neck back pussy greg hall hurt but
i don't care because i'm just so
excited so that's been nice and um
i think most of it is just
like wrapping my head around the fact
that it's really happening like i think
that's the part that i'm um you
know working on every day he's been
doing more and more realist time goes
on and i mean by the time
anyone's listening to this it's very soon
um imminent but
right now even feels like it soon
so yeah yeah like is this some
did you from like when you were
a kid did you want to be
upset
did you want to be have sex
did you want to be
yes i always wanted to be a
mom so it feels like something that
i've just always wanted and i'm why
why can i ask in ah and
this is not just about you particularly
if i mean i'm always interested when
i hear like people have wanted to
be mom since they were kids since
they were little what is it about
being a mom that when you're so
young and
and what is it about being a
mom that's like appealing yeah it's interesting
because i feel like i you know
i think people will say like little
girls imagine their wedding and stuff i'd
never like thought about anything like that
and castle teams queen
like that never crossed my mind but
i always assumed i would get married
and assumed i would have a family
but i think so much of that
is based on like if you if
you grow up feeling that way it's
a lot to do with your family
life and your parents and like what
you see emulated you know before you
are what you want to emulate
and i'm so i feel like i
always kind of assumed that would all
happen but in my head i feel
like being a mom just seems like
i always want to be a caretaker
and teach somebody and like have that
relationship and that's always been something that's
important to me i even i mean
it as being a little kid it's
like a sort of abstract idea
idea but like little babies like baby
dolls you know it's too weird it's
like a neat it's very strange
yeah i don't cool up
she i don't think she wants to
be a mom because she had the
greatest relationship with her mom right she
maybe that's chart how the inspiration to
she had to take care of her
sisters growing home when they were really
young so i think she always was
a caretaker when she was really young
you know what i mean so i
think so maybe that makes sense yeah
yeah i didn't
have to take care of anyone but
i what i wanted to when i
was younger i just assumed i would
have kids i was because i was
religious and i was just like the
natural order you know and it was
a long thank-you to have like eight
the same way that
that your parents had a bone i
think i i think i thought i
would have i don't know that i
ever fixed a number in my mind
i don't think i think when i
when i thought about it i didn't
imagine like a huge family like that
yeah um i think i just thought
like there would be a vague amount
of children that i would have you
know can i add
ask did that did did that coincide
with you wanting to be in show
business like or did it divert or
diverge when you suddenly start thinking about
show business wasn't like oh maybe i
don't have the kids anymore or do
you know what i mean i yeah
i do but i don't know that
i could i could i don't know
that i held both idee
ideas in my mind at the same
time you know you're a one guy
he's got to talk mind and one
at a time i do everyday and
comedy was the track he was ah
this is your bio pic
a true hollywood story and then mike
is seeing a commercial saying why is
that why would anyone watch this um
i i think it was like i
cause i when i was a kid
i of course i wanted to be
in show business but i don't that's
not
when you don't know anybody who is
in show business it's not really real
it always feels like a dream it
doesn't feel like a a goal you
know it just feels like that will
be great and as you like when
you're a little kid you you picture
yourself doing that but then as you
get older and you start thinking about
the concept of having a job
job and having to take care of
yourself and so on and so forth
i don't it was not a real
viable thing to me until i started
doing it until i started doing open
mics yeah even that was like because
a friend invited me to do it
and i don't know if i ever
really would have thought about it as
like oh that's that's a thing that
you can actually do for a living
yeah
so so so you were at what
point did you say oh i'm ah
the whole kid thing is not going
to be something i do without was
that when you actually got married to
the particular person i don't want to
give away your name that you're married
to mrs tompkins um it's it's before
it was before like when we started
when we got sick
arius and then you you have to
say about series i was waiting oh
me how he could possibly know he
found the second thing didn't happen
what's o j j and you get
a serious j gene um that was
when i was when i was doing
open mics there was a bar around
the corner from our home club me
and my pals the fudge bar this
because it's around the corner
oh no
this place called molly's though he used
to go to um that had a
video jukebox oh cool that had maybe
six songs and one of the songs
and this got the guy that used
to manage the club when he would
come hang out with us he would
always put that song on jane's getting
serious
as with the other five some guy
and there were guys in gorilla suits
at some point um and when the
guys in the gorilla suits are come
on this guy that put the video
on would say there's my boys and
then you would go there's my boy
yeah and so you'd see these gorillas
and you'd say i'm not going to
have kids
because i want to fuck them instead
ah
when janie and i got serious that
we started talking about that and realize
that
put the bar in the bottom of
the phone why are you putting the
screen up grandpa for the bottom of
it he's holding this clean up to
the micro folks
this is jane's getting serious
drizzy
who is this ah it is a
little guy by the name one of
his own honestly john astley of course
not rick ghastly yeah you got john
rolled really not related not related i
believe he's american jobs suck to have
what do i that you know trying
to make music at the same time
as summer
on the same last name everyone thinks
you're their brother your bad like the
same year i feel like like nineteen
eighty eight or so
yeah they think that you shouldn't have
done this well like sean cassidy was
related to david cao stephen cassidy but
i'm like but no one who cared
more who to hear more about you
know because everyone into sean cassidy was
us big time absolutely then when they
both were i feel like david cassidy
was
much bigger because the partridge family yeah
shaun was such a huge it was
because people did you run ron and
yeah number one hits and stuff okay
i sit corrected
on my fat ass
back to lawrence pregnancy about paul's journey
okay well that was dirty smollett i
really was like um it was a
difficult thing to figure out because you
feel like you're not allowed first of
all you feel like you're not allowed
to say
you don't want to have kids because
that i don't know that seems like
a monstrous thing to say to some
people um and will really don't especially
i don't know if it's different for
men but i have some female friends
who don't want kids and people just
don't believe them they're like you'll change
your mind i've heard that so many
times but what's funny is nobody says
that to us nobodies
ever said that to like me
but also we got married when we
got married we were i was forty
i was forty one and janie was
um in her thirty in her late
thirties and so it wasn't always forty
one jamie's in early thirties
ah but it shows the painful paul
has to breathe through this whole entire
early it was i feel like that's
easier to skirt past that question at
that point because yeah you're like yea
it's fine we don't we can we
can't we don't have to it's like
it doesn't have to be ah it's
not when you're like getting married at
twenty four and everyone's like so
oh yeah okay yes main course of
course but that's interesting and so did
janie i mean you don't have to
get into this if you don't want
to but did she know that already
about herself that she didn't want to
do that no we kind of when
we got together we were both we
were both on the fence about it
we're both on the fence about it
but knowing that well if we're gonna
do this we'd have
to make a decision about it very
soon you know um and then we
just never really we just never really
talked about it that much and every
once in a while it would come
up and it would be like do
we want this where you know and
then we finally just likes came out
and said it like no this is
not a thing
the same time to do yea to
what yeah i don't think we want
to do
um but i think there must be
some like real comfort in knowing that
well there is challenging that it's like
the idea of just going like i
know that i don't want that it's
just but whichever decision you make you
always think about the other decision yeah
and you know for me it's like
for me it's like i really
i love kids i don't know how
good a dad i would be i
think that i disagree now i mean
who cares but you know because i
mean do what you wanna do in
your life but i think you we
would be a great dad i think
i'd be very loving but i don't
need a good granddad i think i'd
be a great-granddaughter can you just skip
that i think well the way i
i feel now is like i have
i have these young friends and i
like feeling like the father of adult
children yeah like i'm proud yeah oh
yeah so that makes a lot of
sense yeah that's gonna work too oh
my god yeah they'd have to get
used to you yelling and cursing when
when like sitting down around the house
but there is something about that actually
just saw a twitter thread um yesterday
from jack something new on twitter yeah
it was a newer way can we
pause
no new tweets coming every few minutes
the computers um jack hay posted about
being i love her i'd love to
tweet on sister sister and she was
like when i was initially you know
auditioning or offered the role or whatever
issues like i didn't see myself as
being a mother i was like two
young and sexy to be somebody's mom
so i don't wanna take the role
but then by taking the part i
understood i started to understand how amazing
it feels to mentor young girls and
to be somebody that can teach them
and they can look up to them
and i think that's so cool it's
like it's a interesting relationship to have
to be able to be like someone's
older mentor and
and be able to be there for
them and like not everyone is successful
tv show and be a mentor to
someone yeah i mean it's amazing i
just have to assume on comedy bang
bang nobody got men toward my you
know ah and i by the way
i said successful tv
yes the coffee
um well this is great we have
to take a break but i want
to get i wanted to even deeper
on this sagan or in we sick
big pregnancy episode we come back about
my vasectomy hey did you really write
back no
and we're back and lorin still blue
you are still pregnant nothing changed nothing
changed in the break during the break
and feeling good i didn't move at
all
ah good oh we're worried we're gonna
do i know those were low impact
break yeah um so it's it's coming
up your your your whole life is
about to change although it has changed
already but now it's going to change
ah even further yes and
what do you think is going to
like have have you i had a
friend who was about to have a
baby who insisted that nothing in his
life was going to change i don't
believe that at all you don't believe
that i have this friend i don't
believe you have a friend
i know i don't believe that nothing
will change i believe everything will change
third who would you i mean did
of course fucking talking about but i'm
gonna go talk to this guy he
did that but still like such a
like chill attitude where like you think
you're just gonna be able to like
juma just chill through it and it's
like yeah ie kill okay so this
this
a person was going to be in
a show i was doing and i
was like how many hey there man
it was a stage show and i
was like hey you know we're we're
premiering the week after you have the
baby because he he announced he's having
the baby and he was like oh
and attention everyone he was like it's
fine eating eating i'll nothing i don't
think anything's going to change and then
the
day after he had the baby he
called me up and was like ah
okay so i gotta drop out of
that show ah this is like crazier
than i thought yeah literally had never
seen a baby
like how did they what and like
i'm sure his wife or partner was
like you can't just leave me yeah
from that extreme of thinking oh nothing's
gonna change to like totally planning out
what your life is going to be
like where are you in the i
think i kind of fall in the
middle i'm very um i'm trying to
take everything really day by day which
i think i've done really successfully during
this time i turn out to get
ahead of myself um but there's like
been certain points where i felt like
okay maybe i should get ahead of
myself a little bit like because you
know talking to other pregnant people i
feel like they would have more things
figured out that i did or something
and i'm like oh i don't know
any i don't know the answer
that question i guess i should look
that up or these are previously pregnant
people or no people who are currently
pregnant like where kirt briggs i was
where there's a makeup artist that i
work with and she's pregnant and like
ah on basically like a cup just
a couple of weeks ahead of me
and um we were working on something
together in this other way
woman was like asking us like oh
where are you going to deliver and
all this stuff and i was like
at the time i had no idea
so like there's moments like that where
i feel like oh my day by
day um sense is maybe not great
for like actually feeling less anxious like
i think sometimes it helps me feel
anxious but then sometimes it's nice to
have a plan so i'm getting to
the point now where i'm like
planning more for like the things that
are more imminent but
in terms of like my life changing
i'm just trying to take off from
work like we're trying to we're trying
to record these episodes in advance and
i'm doing that with newcomers and anything
i can get done beforehand would be
great so that i can just feel
like i can just be in the
moment and see what happens but i
don't know i don't have any plans
about like getting a nanny
any are doing anything i don't know
i don't know what's going to happen
it seems like a lot to figure
out paul's piss all left is upset
because he thought he was going to
be the nanny
ah close my door and also i
get scared of miami's because many mcphee
one oh she's ugly she's highly wrought
on the news forget about it oh
she's the anti-money mary poppins that's right
as we've discussed but i think i'm
getting into that mindset now like wanting
to have everything so
set and ready to go and that's
feeling that's making me feel better and
i started taking some online classes it's
weird i mean it's like covert and
everything are some classes or class yeah
labor class like labor and delivery and
then they also will cover labour and
the tories um yeah they're also going
to cover labour no thanks and whatnot
like what to expect
when when you're expecting exactly what i'm
reading that i mean are you doing
like breathing like lamar's shit and all
that of stuff i don't really i
haven't gotten to that part of the
videos yeah also the bill cosby ah
chunk on it about the you know
it's been a while since i listen
to a bill cosby joke it's it's
you gotta breathe
middle of mars i think is kind
of dated but i think there's still
breathing techniques that they use that now
looks le mans and it's faster yeah
lamar's actually for men
ah let's go bars lamar he's this
guy who taught i said a harsh
hi i'm lamar
you're here now
a brief first go
well there's all these things like hypnobirthing
and what have you breathe is exactly
like that by the way ou all
day i don't think just like by
just my regular breathing that sells all
day would anyone ever want to be
around wait tell me about hip know
hypnobirthing i haven't fully explored it but
i there's a friend of mine from
high school who i was reconnecting
with an instagram a little bit because
she's also due around the same time
as me and she's had a baby
before so she was just giving me
a lot of tips and info and
she was going on about hypnobirthing which
i i need to really look into
but this is part of the thing
of my my taking a day by
day as i'm like i don't really
want to look at all that right
now it feels kind of intense to
like learn about all that right now
but then i'm like i should
learn about that but i think it's
about keeping your mentality really calm and
like um focused and not not getting
anxious during the process and so it's
techniques to keep yourself i would think
that it would be like making you
think you're a chicken and then you
just you just learned you think you're
laying an egg yeah and it's easy
p
to think chicken labor is hard
i mean
yeah i don't know no i think
i think it's probably really easy so
it's a question for the room they
were worried about every day i don't
think it's like of the table
score they just kinda go you know
what i think is weird though is
like the shell forming inside the body
yeah but i mean that's another thing
about having a baby that's crazy it's
just how much i have there's no
show you know i have a bunch
of apps that i follow every day
to check
on yeah please tell me what's going
on yeah twitter zero yeah
it's just crazy to go like the
baby's brain is getting more wrinkles to
be able to oh yeah worse thoughts
and i'm like where's like every week
they send you a new like hey
here's what's going yes and so there's
a new toe like yeah well the
baby's the baby's foot today yeah cuz
amy's footprint is as big as a
swedish fish today
a whoa
and they just tell you random shit
like the other day the fist was
the size of a tater tot i
was like
is it always just shit that makes
you feel hungry um well that does
work for me anytime i hear anyone
talking about anything i've wanted a hotdog
for so long you can't have hot
dogs and now can arise when you're
pregnant no they're full of garbage yeah
not only is it like she'd rationed
no one hey but yeah kind of
that's some other sort of thing like
and may
maybe after you're pregnant too don't but
i was listening to doughboys and they
were talking about hotdogs and i was
like oh my god i need the
hotdogs i'm so mad hot dog i
love hot i love hotdogs for something
that i hardly ever have i really
do love them so much i told
you about how i was just staring
at a hot dog chart it says
that was the big smile on my
face
oh that was a dick
ah are you talking about turtle the
show's nail on our face it was
national hotdog day and someone tweeted like
a picture of like thirty six different
hot dogs styles from around the world
and you're just like i was just
like look and we were in with
strangely enough we were in a doctor's
office at
and i had a big smile on
my face and lips like what are
you looking at it was like hotdogs
and she's like i'm rethinking everything ever
whenever janey asks me what i'm looking
at on my phone if i'm like
smiling or laugh at something it's always
she only ever asks when it is
something that requires so much backstory and
explanation and i'm like i did thai
guy gotcha oh my god yeah years
ago there was
yeah that's a michael be like what
are you looking like if i ever
have the sound on he's like what's
that i'm like nobody it's nothing like
he's like nothing it's never good you
internet who gives us you don't need
to know but then i tell him
and he's like i don't care that
and so here we go you know
because first i think so it's always
all over again i think sometimes co-op
makes noi
noises because she wants me to ask
so it'll be yeah like totally
la directed sort of at me so
i'll go what are you looking at
and then she'll tell me and i
at this point i'm just like ignoring
it ignoring wow
ignore nord and by the way the
ignored giblets solo finally trying to shoot
charms she turned suzy i was really
worried oh i was so i was
just quivering in my boots i hope
they've restocked those shoe charms by now
yeah who knows at this point um
so
do you love me oh i will
say i love my shoe terms and
i love my crocs and they make
my feet look really small oh have
your feet expanded in the yeah
big fat feet now so just so
just ever so slightly but um but
but my eye you know if you
go got my wiki feed emphasize ten
i'm not i'm not ashamed and they
make my feet look like they're probably
size six i mean you know from
the top at least oh and yours
are like they're a little platform me
right yeah i love the platform i
love mine still haven't come in yet
i have the old i'm still waiting
on mine too what would you order
him from
amazon but you know i press click
and then they were like okay they're
coming in four weeks huh ah that's
a cancer i yeah yeah i come
so do you think this baby will
have benjamin button disease like is it
gonna come out an old man and
you know i really hope not
do we know that it's a disease
maybe it's just more of a condition
it's an aspect or an advantage sure
the benjamin button advantage you know that
wouldn't be ideal i guess are you
happy that it's a girl i'm very
happy that it's a girl that's my
dream so makes sense to me
and and mrs laccase ah interest probably
very excited very excited yes this is
this is not the first grandchild this
is no yeah i have two nephews
so but they're the first girl yeah
so that'll be fun and you know
girl stuff is so much more fun
than boys stuff
yeah toys everything or you or your
parents planning on coming out when yes
around the earth or yeah beforehand this
is like i'm trying to figure out
and i don't know if it's gonna
come out yeah of their marriage is
over
ah so we've just been waiting for
this my god i'd be fairly interesting
um this is our agenda we're both
yea i would be so by that
i mean
um i guess i'd be like cool
ah um
but yeah i'm planning to have them
come out but this is what i'm
i'm curious about and you know probably
by the but maybe by the time
it comes out i'll still be waiting
for some advice so if anyone out
there has had a child what are
you as curious as the case of
benjamin button
yeah i know there isn't a different
way can we make that an expression
man i'm just curious in the case
of music but it's a bit long
regarding this matter
in re
but i'm i'm trying to decide how
soon i want them to come out
and how long i want them to
stay because i really i mean i
like my parents i like having them
in my house some nights now yeah
we have consulted on about it did
his come stay no yours there
wow they do sick of real ah
no one else's parents would be the
worst now what do you mean it's
just so our friends' parents come down
like hey no ah ah their parents
stayed a few doors down from me
for a while and so they related
how
many doors would you say about three
but they rented a place to stay
so yeah yeah yeah because it's just
not my plan my plan was to
have them stay with me because it's
just kind of how we wrote that
also happens yeah you just talked to
tell john and you'll get a good
idea of like around when they got
really sick wow yeah because i feel
like there's a part of you know
i've heard people say like you really
want to soak up the time
and then other people are like like
like without them i just share with
just your partner and your baby and
then the other people are like no
you really want help and i feel
like i'm gonna want help but i
don't know why i wouldn't take that
offer yeah yeah yeah yeah because there's
so much to do in general that
like the idea of someone just doing
the dishes and laundry and you know
being there give me advice is really
yeah that also
seems very natural to me you know
and yeah i mean like it seems
like it would be a very comforting
presence to have somebody you know to
have your your your parents who have
been through this and they understand and
you know what i mean yeah i
think so what age do they go
to boarding school for you the kids
yeah like two until they were two
or one
ship em off nine months a year
and you'll have a wet nurse right
oh my god yeah she's been getting
her tinies already and ah i mean
is that is that concept is somebody
who is capable of lactating that it's
that they never stop there they're always
nursing so their breasts
never stop producing milk that i've found
my king
huh jesus
but i mean i don't think that's
a thing anymore is it at least
in america i can't get it i
mean i don't know maybe for super
celebrities oh my god hiring a wet
nurse seems like so extreme
did madonna madonna had a wet nurse
yeah change if anyone if anyone she
never changed a diaper that's the she
didn't yeah she and she and eddie
murphy were both like yeah i've not
i've never done that shit about any
when you're that rich why would you
but that's so wrong because it's you
know touch baby no one was that's
your personal baby and you were trying
to
tell me how cute i would think
my dog shifts work
oh just thinking about it and there's
so few that offends me that that
you would be a parent to never
ever change a diaper it sends a
weird message i think it's like did
it wasn't this i mean there was
a child for a while you were
disgusting know they will remember but it
wasn't didn't donald trump to the he's
never done that i feel like that
was the course oh of course
i'm sure he like bragged about it
yeah yeah so you're gonna change all
the diapers i'd like to do you're
going the other way fifty percent fifty
percent who's gonna do the other fifty
because mike i'm hoping to imply the
process is what a cook
he's got he's gonna tom sawyer his
way out of doing it so yeah
because guys seventy two hours man this
sure is fun change in these diapers
i love it he's never changed a
diaper though and i mean i as
we know my career was babysitting before
i became a movie star and high
ah i've changed thousands of diapers diaper
yeah i mean i think a lot
of men you know you never really
had the opportunity a couple of when
my sister was young but it has
been so long that i don't remember
anything about it and probably diaper technologies
totally changed since then nineteen year old
empty world safety pinning it
with like a cloth or some thing
i think i had to do pins
at the tab so now it's is
very different now it's less hastened acres
i remember when i was like tabs
yeah when i was young i remember
we had those safety pins ah with
like the little ducks ducks yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh were they were they
plastic or were they
point no they were metal pins they're
metal yeah and it must have been
like only one company made pins because
everyone had the ones with the ducks
yeah yeah yeah like you back back
when we were young back when paul
and i were young like people would
corner the market on that type of
thing now there's so much choice for
every single thing that exists but that's
really it was like that one company
you would make it because they would
have the factory that could put the
parts together you know like i guess
that still happens like the the the
sort of kleenex effect we're all tissues
get called kleenex rain or xerox or
whatever but like what does it happen
with now like roomba
i guess there's other robotic vacuums but
it doesn't seem as it doesn't seem
as ah prevalent anymore yeah yeah
yeah i was just i was just
watching this is us last night catching
up and um i was a few
episodes behind were like this was us
this was them but they ah they
you know they flash back and forth
in time as i've explained and there's
like there's like a whole because now
love the characters are having babies on
the show
and then they flashed back to when
they're dead was alive and he was
taking care of them as babies and
all the stuff em so they showed
the diapers and stuff in this i
guess it was the eight seventies eighties
their toes ninety one two thousand and
eight minutes probably seventies and they have
all this baby powder which is now
like a base
likely illegal like baby powder is like
is it so i didn't know i
didn't know that well johnson and johnson
had this whole thing where they were
like um yeah for causing cancer with
these products because you put the right
decision you know but china and but
this like a couple a couple of
years ago right yeah i remember this
so in my i don't either it
must be
powders that are fine but in my
mind i'm like you never do that
i think i was a baby powder
baby i'm sure of course yeah well
that's why you're so dense
well imagine how smart you could be
i know i shouldn't say this to
a pregnant woman but fuck you
but there's so many things that changed
so much actually i was this is
i almost want to mention this last
week but i didn't want to bring
up my pregnancy but i saw this
um thing on my apple you talk
about god i i'm happy to never
know what i want no i don't
know but i will say i will
say i was like it's kind of
in great that we haven't brought it
up because we it's just not a
topic it's kind of right
and i don't want to be the
person who only talks were still in
lawrence topics by the way yeah and
this is my exodus is facts but
the app that i was looking at
was like explaining how much has changed
in pregnancy in like thirty years and
the things are so crazy it was
not that long ago that like the
maternity leave was like a new idea
like there's like just so many there's
so many things like that that have
changed
am even just like with the style
of cribs and crib bumpers and when
i was a baby i almost died
of sids which is sudden infant death
syndrome
wait and you know what what was
what was the situation i was saved
well it's a you know it's it's
a family lower story that is um
like a rashomon where everyone has a
different take no there's one take and
it's been trailer show
i was a baby and um obviously
and my brother was three and we
lived in an apartment building when my
aunt my uncle lived in the apartment
below us and he was having a
party so my parents went downstairs to
the party and we were upstairs in
the crib sleeping and then my mom
had a sudden
feeling that my um great grandmother was
speaking to her and telling her to
check on me wow and wow she
ran upstairs and i was not breathing
and then i don't remember the end
of the story this is how all
my stories go but ah i should
get the details it all worked out
i don't remember if there was an
ampule
science or what happened or if i
just started again when she moved me
or what happened but houses but i
had blankets and stuff you know because
in that time there was not considered
bad yeah and um now you're not
supposed to have anything in the crib
it's just a sheet on the thing
you can't have a bumper you can't
have any sort of cloth not even
a sophie no sofa
oh who would have been in the
wrong messy i know see that what
changed history
oh no literally who would it have
been dvd
i actually i'll let the sun come
up kind of know but i'm like
whoa you know who is joy i
know who was first choice oh who
turned it down they were busy with
the project but it was a celebrity
so you need third choice of who
did well i guess i guess i
will but maybe they wouldn't been busy
if you know
all the world oh that's true yeah
if you weren't around the butterfly effect
of me not being here means that
the show they run me out of
existed rise oh my god will you
tell us off mike who that person
was okay um have you ever worked
on something and then been told fifty
you got the job that you are
the second or third choice i don't
know if i think i've
i'm known that but i don't know
if i have like been told that
directly but i've also known i've had
it happen where i turn something down
and then my friend takes it and
i just never say a word of
absolutely never say a word but isn't
that always kind of weird when you're
like oh wow and then you like
watch the thing like this i would've
been doing yeah
and i made a mistake and then
my grid
well there's always that fear like oh
man i don't wanna watch that thing
because what if it's really amazing and
i'm like pissed that i said now
or whatever but i've got a few
like last minute offers are like hey
would you like to do this job
and i'm like yeah okay and it
starts tomorrow and i'm like well i
guess i wasn't oh yes i've had
that happen with this one specific thing
that kept
asking me to do it like the
day before and i was getting offended
like i was like stop asking me
the day before to do this thing
like yeah like it feels like rude
at that point and does that too
yeah i don't know if you know
if someone always canceling i'm gonna go
while she is she's around and it's
like any negative oh now i remember
this person but not
when i'm not when i'm conceiving of
this yeah
scott scott and i don't yeah i
don't get offered anything
he's like on mine sweeper ah um
we have to we have to take
another break we'll be right back with
i hold on a second scott now
we have to tank we have to
take a break we have to take
a break everybody
we're back and it's time for three
cheshire well everybody we are back and
it's time for three-tier i just wanted
to say we are back and it
is time for eighth the reacher this
is the part of the show where
we play a game and this feature
featuring the three of us or a
three-tier if you will and that any
code word for gay
game oh right um this was submitted
by kristin kelly someone with two first
names and she can't decide which one
goes first and it's called it's not
what it looks like okay and here's
what happens two of us are ah
well the three of us do a
scene one person
man walks in on the other two
in the middle of a compromising or
embarrassing situation and then the other two
have to try to come up with
a plausible excuse for what's happening so
i would say the person walking in
should say oh my god you guys
are doing this this and this and
then the other two yes come up
with the the
the excuse of why it's happening now
saying a groot okay so since fantastic
why don't we launch into this i
like this i think it sounds terrific
and i see we're all going to
have a very good time good to
me this sounds good to me why
don't born and it's good journey
why don't learn and i will will
team up and then paul you come
in on us okay great marvel team-up
great yep the thing and it's got
um in marvel team-up the thing would
always i don't even care okay
alright just coming home open up the
door expect to see normal things and
stranger things oh my god what are
you two doing up on those library
ladders and your
god swords in your hands you are
making from the waist up and you
are covered in chocolate pudding
okay look okay this obviously this looks
weird hey buddy buddy buddy i can
explain buddy decides now what it looks
like well yours is not what it
looks like i mean this looks crazy
to you but it's obvious but man
ding dong what's up ladies who were
essentially we we had heard ah like
all these books that were
we're on the ladders for right we're
selling them and we we wanted it
to sound good so we said they
were going to be half off so
we're cutting all the books in half
we're cutting in half and so obviously
we want to be half off with
our clothes that we were like kind
of unthinking mirroring the books you know
like putting these are kind of like
the pudding sort of this thing where
it's like we're wondering sure that we
don't
get any stains on any of the
books so like we cover ourselves in
putting we put we put all the
stains on ourselves just so that we
say they wouldn't be on the books
yeah and and it makes us extra
carefully see yeah but we're gonna make
you a ton of money by selling
all these books of yours so aren't
you happy about that i mean that
does sound good
so it's cool right yep let me
just get my shirt off and i'll
join ya
oh oh yeah my visitor right i
think i get this so i won
that one um well let's see
sentence um ok i'm gonna do it
and you guys are going to be
the team okay okay
da da da da da coming home
i'm just coming home ain't no unlucky
my door opening the door walking through
the house and go in the kitchen
oh oh my god pause scott hi
hello guys we didn't expect you home
engdahl he is okay wait you guys
open my dishwasher polished straddling the door
sitting on it which doesn't look like
it's gonna hold um scott's got his
head hanging out the window and his
butt is stuck in the window like
he's trying to get free and like
winnie the pooh winnie the pooh and
then you guys have scattered granola all
over the floor and you are both
covered in piss now this is not
what it looks like it's okay i
don't know like i could understand that
you would take a look at this
kind of situation and be aghast at
what it looks like but it certainly
is not that
he certainly said your home is very
unsafe and so what we were trying
to do was figure out a sort
of ah security system that you could
do every night first ah i was
going to get in the dishwasher you
know um to to be able to
surprise fees surprise ya
exactly i would know if they were
coming because i would hear the crunch
of the granola yeah on the floor
now and now i know what i
was doing was i was i was
planning an escape route in case you
surprised the burglar but the burglar is
not incapacitated i was trying to get
out this window here yes
and i found that i couldn't fit
so i was like you know what
this needs another level so i can
wriggle out of this window so paul
why don't you piss on me yes
and which he did because we didn't
have any we didn't want to use
up your butter know he was maybe
he likes and then you're probably wondering
why i pissed then on paul and
paul a little boy yeah well
because you know it's like yawning it's
it's contagious said someone pisses you and
then you have done biscuits someone else
yeah no i had that happen for
sure trickle down yeah literal guys yeah
so sweet and thoughtful of you i'm
really so grateful i was with the
whole time we were doing were like
lauren's going gonna love this they're gonna
love this abduction you don't mind that
place right no i actually think that
it looks like he figured out how
a robber would do it so the
safety guy yeah good people are getting
the dishwasher me yeah to wait and
tolbert go there
good guy won that one okay good
job learn you truly did alright you
and paul parry it was close though
okay okay
you do tend to go into work
gone to work go to i'm not
a jerk i'm going to work and
just change the lineup it'll oh all
the way to the top floor cause
and the bowels oh yeah getting out
that elevate ah go into my corner
office opening up that door right of
our work oh what's this
paul and ding dong what's up players
what are you guys doing underneath my
glass desk
you've unplugged my computer you've taken all
of my plants and you've dumped them
out onto the floor you have opened
up all of the windows you have
taken cranberries and you've arranged them in
a big what are these letters i
don't even know what this is spelling
because you haven't quite finished it what
is all this weird oh my god
i know it looks like and it's
not that it is not what it
looks like oh my god well first
of all what do you think it
looks like by the way yeah i
don't know because i mean these are
such disparate things
to be honest i'm just i'm more
startled that you broke into my office
which is the weirdest thing well wait
till you hear yes exactly there's a
totally logical explanation so basically we were
really pissed at you and we decided
to come in here in kind of
just fuck shit up so we broke
all your plants we put cranberries spelling
they're gonna spell fuck you scott i
don't know if you how it was
so hard to figure it
out but it's oh well i say
fuck you scott i said let's make
it really quiet here we'll throw the
windows open ah lawrence said let's throw
his computer out the window i just
plugged it um to see if time
could fly yeah yeah that's what we're
trying to jesus christ
so wait so you're just pissed at
me yeah yeah we were very angry
we hate you and so we are
trying to ruin your shit oh okay
seem to work i thought we're gonna
get away with it but you walked
in just at the wrong time okay
yeah what it is it's because you
you sing everything you do
do and it's just because you're the
boss nobody can say browns palin ding
dong see my friends pile and bing
dolly c and so guys i mean
that's like so you still think we're
your friends even though we just did
all this stuff my best friends pile
ending down your weird and diluted and
i don't know why you're the boss
this kind of jump out this little
window it done about this later oh
my god this worked great thing hey
he just killed himself yeah is that
what we wanted we i mean are
you having second thoughts about this while
i did back damn it
what rubber band around my waist or
the head over anyways around your waist
has certainly did oh my thing now
my best friend my other best friend
oh what's it
you guys are fire bird what does
wait a second what for what idiot
you fucking kid i'm sorry i won't
do it i want yeah that's right
you let me kiss each
no
oh we don't like you like that
you don't like you like that how
do you like me my thing oh
my god wow right now i don't
feel bad oh shit rubber band again
timid
oh okay i won that one oh
yeah yeah you did you ultimately you
did yeah that was fun squeaker congrats
thank you to kristin kelly thank you
christian kelly thank you kristin da li
um guys that's gonna be it for
this episode i'll say this is a
big one and i'm sure less
it's funny and then there usually but
what are you going to do but
people like the drama this is a
dramedy podcast and i don't think they
realize that yeah comedy podcasts like arachnophobia
anything can happen at any time yeah
and mommy doesn't we're gonna come back
next week don't you worry about that
don't you worry your stones you hurry
bad say idiots
i'll be back next week love yeah
um by hey
uh