three
princeton princeton free trade
a
oh good times we've had screaming together
yeah oh no and now lorell bed
no shame hailed the cromer know a
crown like a king's crown yeah looking
on from somewhere with my mouth owed
to you know like chains of air
yeah
do you know what it's like a
piece of air just like a piece
cube of air
um have used you watch the bachelor
have used you yesterday you were texting
meter i know i was going to
bring it up and say we're all
blodget wrote yeah yeah i haven't watched
a single episode but i did tune
in for the finale wow which was
something i said to myself at the
start that i might tune in for
the finale just to see your you
aren't absolutely honestly that was plenty no
te
because you got it i got it
i got whatever one's deal was yeah
give you a lot of information and
next story every previously on the bachelor
yeah yeah so i was yeah see
during the finale and it was it
was very it was just very almost
annoying enough just to watch the end
when you see the way people get
hurt like why why doesn't everyone when
they're watching sports why don't
they just watch the last sixty sec
well yeah i understand only sound watching
sports yeah watched the last sixty i
want because that's when it's all decided
basketball games if it's not it is
not close in the last sixty seconds
why do you even watch it anyway
so just only watch sports that is
close yeah last sixty seconds and then
it'll be really exciting for sixty
the second big lollipop
i like to lick it and it's
actually been like for like sucks down
pretty far um yeah it was very
sad though the girl who got rejected
that was just rough i mean of
course it's fun not so anyone's name
and not know what's going on and
yeah i think on the way about
everything yeah in life yeah i don't
wanna know anyone's name at all i
don't know yeah right
ality recap yeah are you watching love
is blind new season yes i just
started it and it's fascinating can i
say we had dinner with some friends
of ours recently who that's like your
own little reality show oh my gosh
anyone film eight were all filming while
putting our phones aging together and make
i'm not gonna i'm gonna assume it's
gonna have you're gonna
hire an editor i'm gonna put all
the send all this stuff on a
big hunger put all four phone hard
bag together but yeah fridge and see
what happens yeah yeah um yeah really
cool these were two people when we
were having that part of ah life
now which now is very common where
you talk about what you're watching or
whatever yeah yeah they surprised us
these were not people i ever thought
would say this they're watching love is
blind it has permeated the culture and
it is getting to people who wouldn't
normally do you think i'm gonna end
up watching this show i think it's
worth it for you to throw an
episode one and just why don't you
watch episode one right now they'd be
okay okay right for you
gonna be like no time has passed
at all why don't we let's watch
it alone right yeah it works watch
it let's turn on
hey so welcome to the pub do
you live here e b have i
lived here come out sure
ah um it's pretty fun but but
you know one thing that i think
comes up a lot online about it
is like why is everyone all done
up when they're sitting in a pot
and the purse because they're on camera
i know but wouldn't it be nice
whoa knew that nice if they weren't
jobs yeah
just to see them in their normal
casual clothes no makeup don't worry about
your hair whatever it because it's and
that's to me that's the sexiest way
a woman can be is just in
swear i live in woman's disgusting yeah
and because you're smelling bad uncomfortable for
no reason and like a short dress
and high heels and stuff you don't
need to be doing it a weird
empty yeah
there was a commercial where
i forget what it was maybe for
like fares to be something not please
okay okay rest in peace pillar but
this was for some shipping company or
something and then um it concluded with
the idea was it's so easy it's
you know it's all done so fast
you don't have to worry about anything
and there's a while you want
send a package i'm just constantly worrying
until it gets there and packages for
four days straight packages freaked me out
ma'am just i can't sleep oh my
god i have stretchered about packages but
so this so this woman is doing
a video and voice-over if you're not
in the bay is sad to tell
you guys and then and that's a
voice
it goes over the image but yeah
can't see the action i know all
voices technically are over the images but
this is an unrelated look at voice
yeah like god yeah i got you
i don't think voice modes coming out
of people you think of them as
being over the image of the purse
of the image silently mouthing along yeah
so this voice over saying
at the end and then you're on
the couch in your comfy pants and
the way she said comfy pants it
sounded like puffy pants to me woe
and i heard that way for the
longest time i was like why is
puffy puffy pants and you i bet
you're thinking like puffy pants must be
a thing and you're like people are
talking about that i know yeah yeah
i need to get puffy pants and
then janie said oh no she's saying
comfy pants and then i was just
like mad because yeah it was like
she was like her it was like
yourself had hurt or i won and
the world yeah it was like one
of those earworms you get that's not
a song yeah but it's just like
a person saying a thing yeah that's
fun that said we should mm
make threesome puffy pants okay okay what
are they this is a good question
we have the year we die we
are the ones in charge you will
be the architects of the puffy pants
look no one's gotta be sort of
like a like a puffy coat like
north face sort of like what the
pope for all the bones yaga yeah
so so
so yeah pants like that now can
they be elected to you but yeah
maybe above the knee can the hem
be above then why would you know
who's putting on puffy pants that are
above the knee puffy caprica lay on
the couch above the o above the
knee i think you're putting on full
losers' shorts those are showing you're right
you're right
down below length wide leg wide leg
they shouldn't be tight no coffee yeah
right okay so what color are though
any and how do they have every
color of the rainbow how did people
know that radio blocking on anything that
i purchase yeah
such that fucking dog
these are the types of people red
yellow black white v ed we're all
gonna make blue polka dots
these days boy anything goes oh my
god um i watched a documentary that
was really good really good about about
love being blind
it was broken up into eight hours
it's called the volcano have you heard
of this there was a volcanic eruption
in twenty nineteen in new zealand that
was actually terrifying keo to two people
who are around it or yeah and
yeah and to everyone but many people
were injured and hong encore
terrified lori rings were terrified but we
didn't know about it really here's what
i'll tell you i learned about this
i had heard about it somewhere and
then i heard about it again so
that's what drew me to watch three
times usually to yeah in order for
something to solidify yeah i heard opioids
puffy pants puffy pants look on they
appeared i heard it referenced on a
podcast i think and then i
heard it on rosie o'donnell has a
new podcast that i was listening to
and her guess was rory kennedy who's
a documentary filmmaker oh you listening to
podcasts that aren't this yeah i know
we've thought about that before but i
will do it and i listened i
remember when you said scott och don't
want your live yeah yeah it was
crying yeah
but anyway worry kennedy made the documentary
and so i was like well let
me show you can't say rory kennedy
she's a documentary filmmaker it's very sad
but she's also a kennedy oh kennedy
kennedy yeah haha ah yeah and the
first thing people think over they think
of kennedy it's the story well because
rosie was like
why didn't i hear about this and
then she was kind of spending she
didn't really hear about at the time
she was like touche balls still ah
rosie on the podcast she does throw
them like into the mic every kind
of few words you hear like a
soft thump yeah foosball um and ah
anyway whooosh it was said that there
was a lot of stuff could get
an american news cycle at that point
so it wasn't really
we breaking through much but then it's
crazy when you i think it's i
recommend it's on netflix and it's just
a wild i don't want to give
you know tell you the whole story
because long as it's probably an hour
and a half and what was the
time we get that down to about
forty five minutes um you can if
you just skip around i guess that's
a little bit disrespectful shy skip around
in order
or make it like pulp fiction i
would say watch the first forty five
and then you then stop to watch
just stop yeah yeah okay cool
um no watch the whole thing it
was really good what was the timeframe
i don't want to twenty nineteen twenty
and twenty nineteen was not long before
the pandemic though so i think it
was like chaos oh because it was
all like the because people were like
always
get ready we're saying there's a lot
of trump stuff at that time that
was actually the yes yes yes um
but it's really rather available mobile it
was extremely tourist going to um visit
a volcano like ah yeah i mean
how many how many times this has
happened to you you go on vacation
to
your volcano well yeah you go on
a vacation so it's so like sort
of excursion that you know we could
just like that in hawaii when we
were wanting to go on a helicopter
ride it's right it's just something that
went awry but the core four didn't
yeah we didn't want to go outdoor
no we did not want and then
they ended up being cancelled right the
helicopter we hear something to wendy yeah
i don't think anyone
yeah haven't noticed it's when we had
a nice dinner we had a nice
conversation and we run the caution that
was a great night was a great
night yeah because because cool up the
core for of course if you don't
know it's cool ah no that wasn't
they want to see the man a
raise or whatever yeah yes yes yeah
we didn't want to do that yes
what ended up happening yeah we didn't
want i think
only for people who went up went
to do the helicopter right that was
a different story because i think that
was child john nora tim and the
snore for sure
oh my god i have to texted
that i know it's eight years too
late
i talk to every day with these
people it's right and there's no sexual
advantage lunch from one trip that we
ought to be yeah you agree isn't
it kind of impressive that we have
a text chain that's still going this
whole time yeah and then it's led
to we have those nice dinners now
yeah so yearly tradition which is really
nice here's here's what people should do
if they're listening yeah
next random people you'll get a great
friendship out of it you'll go to
dinner with them start a group chain
with people that's how we met because
we consider someday random people people don't
know how we met it's strange i
don't think we've ever talked about no
we met on but we all text
each other by accident so i texted
my best friends and family and invited
them to thanks
giving turns out actually was texting all
of you guys yeah yeah we did
the exact same thing yes at the
same time and so we all showed
up and we all like where our
friends and family yeah and it took
us like five hours until we figured
out that they were coming yeah and
it was like a twilight zone where
we were all in a room together
and we were one by one
we are getting suspicious and accusing each
other thing yep yeah it turned out
we were all in heaven yeah and
it sucked so we came back down
here to earth
and we started this podcast
and the rest is history yep it
is her story or the history okay
or history either so some room for
it to be history
why there still has to be room
for it to be history okay yeah
jesus and defending men euro euro miserably
activists no archie love men
and i want them to have whatever
they want on which by the way
everything yeah i love excited for it
just like that season i'm so excited
when does that come out i don't
know but i saw one of those
hbo trailers where it's like here's all
the shit that's coming up are you
serious as a trailer now there's just
like so little like little scenes of
everything because i saw like wang dong
until we've taught
oct but i think that photos of
aden and kerry in the street now
just like hey what's going to happen
john corbett i was like why was
the d j on what's going to
happen exposure all things i've not seen
big fat greek wedding you don't remember
him from lucky the billboard said to
do big fat greek wedding for your
pod okay let's do it i
whatever when do you have a weekend
free i don't do podcasts on the
weekend okay so we'll do it tomorrow
good role models we make that a
rule it's not a rule that i
have but i should make that it's
an unspoken um that i break huh
yeah exactly i feel yeah speak a
lot that's a that's a classic though
for you to throw up on there
yeah
do it to throw up during what
i'm gonna throw up on the on
the old oh yeah yeah alright will
do apple will do it at some
point in the next two weeks no
we won't you will know you have
to if you bring it up that's
not three show your duty bound but
i have like eight already that i'm
on the list i know and you
haven't even followed up on a single
one oh
sorry it's my oh but she can't
i'm not gonna initiate yeah oh we
got bored here i need to be
more aggressive when do you think that
i should call you like can we
record your podcast i really wanna hear
ya
that's how a book of every shown
and people call me and say plea
please do one this week oh are
you going to people just calling are
you going to release a podcast i
really hope you do i wouldn't i
would never record another episode but people
too many people begged me to do
yeah wow are you ever gonna have
either one of us some cvb fm
or you i would love it like
you have
enough time with us with this well
i would love it i don't like
to bother you to do stuff oh
yes you do
a bunch of stuff that you could
sign right behind me oh it's always
signing i know i have like what's
in there now i have ah seven
hundred books i have designed jesus is
so fucking wrong with you so feel
free to join those page in sorts
for the book yeah it's really just
these little guard yeah they paste them
into the books what's the a
a for aquaman no that's kind of
ah it's the company yeah anyway the
company we keep ah
you're talking in your sleep the buckle
well with this episode is out it
will be out in like ten days
from then because this episode comes out
on the thirteenth it comes out on
the twenty fifth twelve days from now
ah oh my god well then everyone
won't get into the episode yes the
twelve days of the book i mean
only going to sign
those yeah no i'm just looking at
them but i would love to have
getting them out you paul read the
fm i was actually thinking about it
this morning i would love to do
it yeah it'd be great i really
enjoy the show oh great wow um
and lauren and i wasn't i mean
i fast forward through your monologue yeah
but everybody everyone does
lauren i'm not gonna bother you to
do it's great
yeah we all we have so many
well see i love to do it
i'd love to do it i'd love
to do whatever you want um i
want to try that oh i like
to do podcasts and um you you
you're getting more back into this i
yeah man yeah i'm getting because you
had two babies for a while yeah
yeah holly and yeah my nicole with
the
the other show that we had new
comers was a lot and someone's doing
a podcast really is a lot especially
one where you have to watch three
hour movie that's what really gets yeah
yeah they were all three hour movie
now except for the title so i
mentioned this on doughboys but chris colfer
who i met at naomi peregrine's wedding
suggested that man for the next
last season and i actually thought that
made sense though because once you do
an episode for every episode of the
television show yeah we would
everything else is a diamond ni episode
three years if i'm guessing that's why
it was like brady episodes i just
crushed that was easy the shit that
that lasted in three channel days it's
while i'm like this is a big
hit everybody watched it it was three
three seasons but you want to know
how many episodes they did
oh yes ten h or something guess
oh i mean ten each so thirty
my ex sure that was seventy but
i'm saying thirty you're saying thirty what
what's three seasons um probably automatic way
more over i'm gonna say yeah i'll
say like seventy no i'm going to
say a hundred you're saying okay but
you can't go over ninety
so you're saying ninety you're saying seventy
one yeah
one hundred and twenty learn you in
three years if you do one hundred
and eight with sixty in one season
it would make sense for telling me
ten
it's sixty episodes of the season here's
what i think happened it was it
was like they did one season of
thirty four it was so pop and
became such a like phenomenon season of
thirty four they've ended sixty and then
they only did twenty six the third
season it got cancelled so i think
like everyone was over it but wow
that's nuts yeah yeah oh do you
like
that would drive me crazy to do
bettman i've seen some well every every
episode of this of the batman series
is exactly this i'm not doing every
episode of the batman series i'm due
maybe one of the of the series
now you got what no no you
should do the bem is the sixty
six movie because that's yeah it's a
nightmare that man movies because otherwise they
were getting the batman cartoon yeah
that gives you all of the batman
of that area that you need so
you do the sixty six pounds hard
it sounds har eighty nine ninety you
two or one whichever it was then
ninety five ninety seven and then the
three ah more for nolan's and then
the reason when you have nine episodes
right there and then you could do
a cartoon here
there if you want to want to
do erotic fanfiction which we loved your
sleep to me that sounds like a
drag to me it doesn't i mean
the entire thing is hard season i
ever had was the tyler perry season
yeah because varietals fun the problem with
the batman idea is that first of
all he's a weird guy
he's weird but it's also there's a
lot of resetting the character and going
very training someone else anyway i'm story
yeah yeah yeah yeah plus it's like
well what if you just did one
of each of the directors
sixty six batman then do a tim
burton the new schumacher well could hear
well one man and then do what
could pair with batman visit matt nice
roget so and so and you do
like the batman thing and you like
this you do batman superman so that
you owe because i forgot oh rewiring
but man superman fuck around
odd i've been seeing that constantly when
batman v superman came out oh my
god it was in my head all
the time fuck fuck it around i
just don't know you could do batman
superman because then you have you can
do like one of each of the
directors of batman you could do one
of the of the directors of superman
and then meet up with batman v
superman i mean that's kind of key
cute we'll see i mean it sounds
hard catanzaro couldn't why are you even
bother ah the fans want all the
hand we love the fans now you
know because when we don't i don't
know i mean like it's either that
or i do some improv or something
huh
are you looking for stuff to do
um i don't know i don't know
if that's true or not i mean
i'm i'm available if that's what you
mean but i don't know that i'm
looking to just add things to the
plate i want like yeah i want
some fun things to happen but i
don't know why don't you come babysit
see i already babysit all day and
that's ok
um um yeah well well look if
you have your podcast ideas so send
them to ah three music gym help
yeah or are you think i'd say
for me to see where your value
to me is submit my ideas to
you yeah yeah yeah and i'll judge
alright we have to take a break
by
and we're back yeah we really are
naturally you're welcome back to the most
listenable podcast a real page turner yeah
yeah like you wanna hear every second
you're like when you're listening to one
second you wonder what's going to happen
in the next usually with podcasts i
listen and after one second i turn
off
off i go do i wanna list
yeah you could have cod and then
i played another second i usually hear
her i'll hear the theme song and
then i'll hear like how they say
hello and then from that i'm kind
of deciding and then i might read
the list of like who the guest
is sometimes i'll talk to friends i'll
say did you like this should i
continue past this one second yeah yeah
i've been biggie on my podcast group
where we all
i'll listen to the same podcast and
then we discuss it at the same
time yeah yeah we all just talk
at the same time and i do
a podcast about the podcast oh no
no no no no ain't the experiment
yeah we will all listen to a
podcast and then we do a different
podcast we get together ever mention the
other each to your own podcast about
other things yeah and then you layer
m on top of yeah people hate
it yeah okay yeah it's unreasonable um
whatever teaching shame about what what what
i remember watching speaking of page turners
i remember h davis of course always
speaking we saw and heard in subtask
yeah still under a bridge way she
saw a couple of weeks tiktok and
hey joe want you to understand that
mr putin would like the schedule that
we placed out for you it's under
discussion we could just upload negotiation me
really really happy to hear you know
we won't give you any more but
we can give you less know it
won't change but we ask us what
you don't like about it and if
you don't like it your other alternative
is to lumping yeah lumpy like
like it or lump it whoa what
does that mean oh laura and laura
i know love it are listed you
don't know like it or lump it
no other listed by the way they
all just want to stay in their
place they're all looking just for innovations
yeah you know what i mean so
like it's really bad because at the
end they're building up the suspense of
like is the guy who to
took them to three empty houses gonna
get to and they never do because
they all died man in the ring
hate each other so much do they
really know i mean like but they
always have fake forever fake fight oh
well wait till you see what i've
done with the laundry and then at
the end where at the end when
they're recapping it's like he's like wow
you did such a good job of
course they stayed and she's like well
i bet
you you know showed him some good
places you know but yeah there was
everyone this but they definitely get it
i'll never need oh you think oh
the shit out of each other yeah
like hydrogen in that every house so
this you get horny watching the show
i don't get hard but i know
that they do yeah he ascribed i
get horny i know they don't
wow so you're real jack spreads he
gets horny no matter what he's watching
just tv with visuals and images he
kind of is just crazy all the
blood just rushes yeah i would absolutely
suck yeah like no matter what you
watched the news you can never try
the family i wish i could shut
off where my head where i'm always
singing yeah in my head i'm cut
is constantly a song we stop true
yes i like i recently was like
stop oh stop and then i sat
there and was like it don't do
it it's boring yeah it's like i'm
bored
um i did find out that like
an acd symptom and then i was
like okay this is another point lori
d you with eighty what are you
how so are totally i gotta i
gotta shit i gotta get this check
i think idea to get checked i
got checked out i got it's real
resemble a test have you i think
they hit you with a bat and
see
and then you have the ability then
yeah yeah and that's awesome i am
curious though because i have heard of
people when they take the medication and
huh wow yeah amazing i can do
all these things like that's cool i
just feel like my i can't finish
shit i can't have a hard time
finishing so unless it's like a
super stupid thing oh i'm really good
at that i can scroll on my
little groups and all my things all
night long yeah yeah yeah but have
i have i ah digitized a bunch
of dvds you bet your ass yeah
you digitize all your old performances right
yeah last night i was like i
gotta organize my stickers you know i
think there's a couple of
trousers over there for me like yeah
they're right there on that chair i
see them from where when i was
like in in the middle of like
oh i gotta figure out stuff i
don't fit in anymore and i'll i'll
take it out of my class because
that's what you had idea there's too
many too many times where i'm in
my closet going like oh i'll wear
that and then i put it on
yeah i don't fit anymore and it
makes me sad so yeah get it
all
out i just did the same thing
yeah yeah but those those i think
they've been sitting there for now six
months oh okay i'd never finished that
yeah that's frustrating i've shit in my
office just draped over a chair yeah
oh yeah well my thing is i'll
move things to just certain location yes
so it's like oh say can we
go yeah sort of the same location
and that's where it's getting out of
control yeah
but i yeah do you know what
i got because i forgot this was
a thing and then a friend of
mine mentioned it that they were doing
it on instagram is to vacuum seal
vacuum pack clothes oh so you put
don't wear yes she put em in
a bag then you have this little
vacuum attachment sucks all the air out
so it makes it into
like a pink lat little pancake pink
and then what do you do it
again then you can store it and
it takes up less room but so
you could put on it like the
size and you're like whatever this is
exactly like winter yeah if you don't
have yes yes it took close to
precise will ever be that size again
though should we just get writing i
will you will i was close
couple of years ago and then i
put the weight ball back on i
was close and then i broke the
ankle all my ribs are actually wider
from having a baby so let's change
a lot of my ribs are wiser
i was gonna say rib cage is
wide oh she came through your mouth
that's right you are rally holding from
carrying her she's ten pounds almost is
what it is yeah they they actually
do they can't there are exercises you
can do with with like i saw
it on instagram i was like i
should do this every day for instead
you just watched it yeah do it
at all um borja like you know
pulling bands like at different angles to
kind of like get your ribs kind
of like to go in a little
more you can't give them back to
what they were but did you go
in like a tube
and like crawl through a like across
space maybe we can stack everything could
happen yeah what if you sleep in
a bunch of bungee cords i do
that already okay yeah i just get
tang i forgot i forgot it's sort
of an amelia bedelia kinda did you
say tangled because i mean oh you're
all scott has no this guy seen
i've watched that one oh we should
do
do it for scholars and i don't
want to why shouldn't i do it
yeah what the fuck what we want
to talk about you what finally she
asked me about his experience making you
know what would that be like what
was your character who's the little drunk
guy with the lease on the tv
show too yeah aren't you yeah yeah
let's admit it and oh my god
they have a tv show
you're this guy yeah that's yeah it's
by the way she just showed him
a picture of himself and that's you
you're this guy that's me too this
is your wiki
and that's you that says about
right
alright paul will do well will you
do it as the character though no
because you can't do it okay i
understand legally i could probably get in
trouble ah um i won't do it
yeah i'll just i'll give you a
date okay but i about somewhere before
sudden rise we're going to do that
we're gonna do that a year from
when we did the first one are
you serious yeah right well she'll be
thirteen years later something or ten years
yeah i don't want to wait that
long well this one doesn't make any
sense why because while it's nice it's
a nice round number one
what do you want cool hand luke
next
um so we'll do three episodes before
that okay i'm not real quick you
guys for the smart fans out there
because my mustache whoa actually feels good
right here's mine i saw a sound
article is with a video it said
here's what asr does to your brain
rain now that sounds sinister but it's
very like this tickles it yeah but
it probably makes it better right i
don't know if it's better i mean
you either have that or you don't
write you either have that reaction or
you don't yeah that's the trip to
phobia or whatever right you the scene
three things three eyes it's used i
like yes people don't like a babbling
ball people don't like that yeah yeah
people yeah people don't like that so
here's like smell like real weird hey
apple hey tim apple which by the
way
come on tim cook
and he doesn't cook apples instead he
makes phones are not cooking apples every
day dude one wizard email tim cook
and you think he should cook apple
yes it said he makes phones yeah
he makes phone or apple did you
ever in school make one of those
things where you're like put like cloves
into like a little
oh hell yeah you poke co into
an apple yeah so i didn't go
like grade school that cigarettes robert smith
as my instructor i hate this i
hate the smell soil is shallow co
my roommate college was a co we
haven't done is roommate ah what was
it called roommate roundup no
restaurant roundup but i will say very
very few and far between i didn't
have ah i was actually afraid because
i knew that when you inhaled them
they had like shards of glass in
it or something i was like shards
of something and say like i mean
that's not literal but like something was
really bad clothes that you shouldn't actually
inhale into your lungs let me look
as i ever heard okay maybe my
rye which should you not inhale cloves
but that's because burning clubs releases a
chemical called eugenol a topical anesthetic used
by dentists to numb the mau yes
for smokers inhaling clove smoke means numbing
the throat which allows them to breathe
the smoking more
ah good thing it's the opposite oh
it's it's good
oh that's okay i'm fine that's i
think that's why i don't like clothes
i forgot it's because that dentist office
but i think i like to use
that anymore
i mean not if i'm making i
remember that smell from when i was
a kid and it was yeah horrifying
and i thought they smelled good well
you're insane i saw a bunch of
college frenzy of the night and i
was just so surprised it was like
they're still smoking all of them says
while to me too it's crazy i
was just like really thirty years later
i don't think i have ah
any friends from that time who sells
maybe one yeah they all we went
to see a play and then everyone
like you know before the plays like
oh we gotta hurry and banana like
an intermission we're like oh that's like
very gen x of them yeah it's
really used to smoke yeah and my
me and my pals from that era
yeah yeah and i just i assume
boom anytime i see someone i'm assume
like oh yeah you put that away
in your twenties or whatever yeah but
i can't put also that's the hardest
thing to quit so it's like if
you're kind of like this kind of
fun you keep doing it forever well
yeah but the thing if it i
mean i don't smoke cigarettes i don't
really know i mean i don't see
cigarettes yeah okay yeah
okay yeah it's okay
but cool i brought up also it
may it may be in appetite ah
suppress suppress welford and make sure maybe
they're just smoking socially as an appetite
yeah maybe they're all smoking together because
they're all back together yeah it could
be i don't know i shouldn't be
so judgment but i just was like
no it's more surprising because it's like
a lot people quit by now the
stuff around smoking about
what about quitting appetite suppressant all that
stuff is it's pretty much all bullshit
you know i mean it doesn't people
should stay appetite i mean it's more
that it makes more but to eat
taste like an ash yeah exactly yeah
yeah yeah it's dated to smoke people
are more afraid that if they quit
they're gonna put on weight which is
true like you will as you need
to fill the hole
yoga your mouth but i but when
i quit i did not like start
eating everything in sight and i was
going to the gym
sorry
it's just a classic joke structure i
think absolutely i don't believe it um
and i still gained weight i didn't
really yeah i still gained weight i
it's just ah ah ah wasn't gregory
like getting up to go outside too
young five fourteen five fewer steps ah
but quitting sm i think quitting smoking
because you everyone is told it's the
hardest thing to quit like yeah requip
and heroin it's like well because you
can't buy heroin on the court you
know yes stone you should you should
you should only buy heroin in the
store yes i yeah you're gonna say
you dated smokers i didn't always write
i didn't really buy
bother me actually but if you get
him more you get used to it
i feel like but it is an
adjustment yeah like whoa now when i
think about i just got level i
can't believe it's different i felt like
smoking a little house versus smoking outside
yeah like it would i just remember
you saying oh yeah yeah is just
but but i feel like human beings
i wanna make out so bad that
it should just overlook yeah yeah it's
true you know i mean it's just
like oh i just i don't care
how disgusting okay sir yeah
roll it around but it's actually one
of those things where i sort of
feel like i don't like to i
try not to like control the person
i'm with where like if you want
that's my desired habit but i feel
i will say i really like you
have to quit that and i feel
like i was always like whatever and
if they they wanted to quit i
will say when when you
knew you weren't in it for the
long haul
when cool up and i started dating
i found a packet packet right or
pack a package about the packet and
packet of crisps no i found a
pack of cigarettes in like our tool
twenty still cuts and i was like
what are these doing here and i
said not here not in the house
and and she was like
oh it's just a social yeah i
was like socially whatever it's like ah
yeah nah that was the one thing
i was like controlling but this is
cool up yeah i've never seen him
with a cigarette oh because this was
so she was saying because you because
of you yeah i cut we were
talking about it yesterday and she was
like you wouldn't let me smoke and
i'm like article edge goes yeah i
mean yeah it's just because i'm nice
smoking no yeah it's good to not
obviously i mean we try we tried
to not smoke in front of her
so that she would haven't been role
model but she just picks it up
from the tv or something yeah yeah
yeah i remember once making people mad
on twitter when i said if you
didn't show characters smoking in movies and
tv you wouldn't miss it and then
then and that's that's literally all i
meant it's like yeah right you wouldn't
you don't think like you aren't at
least smoking and people like what you're
trying to control our well you're madman
and i'm like i don't care if
you if you didn't see people smoking
may never you or you wouldn't have
thought why aren't they yeah it be
weird if you thought that there yeah
marvel comics in the early two thousands
the editor in chief joe quesada decided
to get rid of any character smoking
because characters who smoked it was all
wolverine and nick fury and they were
all to show how badass they were
you know and same thing everyone was
like up in arms this is part
of what verine character
and all that kind of stuff and
now twenty years later i'll go back
and read like early ones and it'll
look strange to me yeah they're smoking
yeah you know what i mean like
comic book yeah it's like such ah
it's yes ah wolverine man yeah does
it yeah it's weirder that grants a
lot of managers fists yeah yeah that's
he's wearing a leotard
yeah like he needs to smoke he
looks cool yeah it's true but it's
you truly don't like yeah you can
get all upset about i remember i
was sort of upset because i was
waiting tables i'd be upset too yeah
i was like i want to be
a movie star
um but but when they did the
no smoking allowed in restaurants law i
remember i was like briefly upset about
that because i was like well you
know people come in here really good
time and i'm waiting tables and you
know what if they don't come in
or whatever but like no like twenty
years later no one gives a shit
yeah right yeah yeah um here's a
funny thing
about wolverine yeah i think that is
sometimes so so say the same thing
what are you gonna say he has
this ah this is j opposite by
the way was that james is his
real name anyway because those things logan
well that's his his his the name
that he has gone by until he
got his memory back his name is
james howlett and he forgot huh
how let the moon oh shit know
what i haven't had that guy that's
really what that but yes i'll have
the moonlit wow at the moon yeah
wow jacqueline howlett james how let the
moon howl at wow so he's got
the big curved points on his costume
yeah and then you
take that thing off and there's that
way too you know but did it
did the costume make his hair that
well you know if you're gonna take
off your cake if you were to
take off your baseball hat your hair
would be in shape because opera with
river there yeah oh my god logo
that was so gross
needed addition oh like alright we have
zuckerberg
and we're back and it's time for
three church here it is this is
called kind of like name that tune
but with only two lyrics and no
betting submitted by paul burgess with the
fun part of name that tune is
the bedding well there's no but
i mean the fun part is going
to vegas as the gambling right
oh no i just like going there
you don't see shows or anything no
just like wow you're week you know
i just wandered around like casino that's
the best part taking in the sights
yeah inhaling smoke and people watching where
that all stuff about smoking in the
last thing we didn't mean it no
we mostly news grades very cool yeah
and do it
i don't want people doing i just
think we'll be really good at this
okay oh yeah this is you being
honest yeah i honestly think that why
no cap everything i've said before yeah
it was a cap
player has x amount of time so
we have to dead ass okay yeah
wow
to think of songs they can sing
only two lyrics of to be recognisable
i e it's been and and oh
two words not to lyrics yeah two
words well this was written by an
idiot and
this is a tale told by an
idiot full of sound and fury signifying
nothing we can't hate on paul for
submitting this and paul is a great
person and it was mountain and i
i will always love you ground control
it's like okay and i is much
more than two notes that makes it
a good choice to lyrics not lie
too late to work too
notes two words of the lyrics caveat
title lyrics are out you can't sing
staying alive hey macarena white wedding that
apt for can probably go ah
yeah he says up your ugly guard
again or the i from anti is
in the title of i will always
love you i miss the point of
the game be cool player poems as
many songs as pay a bad amount
of time in x amount of time
each so we can say okay so
we basically took thirty seconds
each correct answer from other two players
earns a point i guess it could
be a team game like pictionary but
with these three two guessing honestly and
for fun should work ok so let's
just do two guessing and one and
we'll just try guess we'll all just
take it this means we can okay
yeah i'm here great i'll don't care
either
it's hard to think of songs though
so you'll see there's happy no that's
a lyric happy it's in the title
shit to you yeah
i got one okay alright let's maybe
we hint maybe we can't time it
and try to like go fast it's
whoever has won just do yeah okay
ready yeah yeah oh look
oh look
yeah that's what i just did ah
look wait what is the game ah
look to scores lyrics of a song
yeah yeah you got it wage the
first two it's well no no it's
anytime tending to your exact okay good
then i'm doing it right you're doing
it right i'm just trying to see
oh little
look is it look or it's what
i just did never thought you were
maybe a little flat so i'm trying
to figure out the exact randy jackson
choosing your new dog ah oh look
look because you're around ya look oh
look la yeah i look or allah
ah ah look i just don't know
this i don't know i haven't tried
this
shall i continue yeah yeah well use
one look at
oh look at
i don't know good one more one
more i'm just gonna go no keep
going because i'm about to get into
the jags one more i'll look at
the westerns guys have one more note
before i get into okay to take
give us one more ah look at
all the bow may be blown that
was pretty cool
ankle angle be cool okay alright my
word my my turn now my version
of oh
wear it
wear it or we're aware and we
are at where at where at yes
w e r where it is it
w e pasha r h e r
e where oh you're not doing this
where at where at where it
where at where at i'll give you
the third okay yeah where at least
where it where at least where at
least at least
ah shit where l is duh
where at least i where at least
i know wow hey wow man
okay i'm on it whereas lisa
ooh i'm for a game yeah ok
don't make
dough make
and the dome make another one
in other words okay in other words
i'm i'm waiting for confirmation from paul
yes i can from sorry i forgot
i was in the ca
don't make it hey gee yea his
dad diggers ah sha yeah good bad
oh ferry member
dandy huh then you can fight to
make it bad bad ah no ah
no no no no no no
hey jude
no no no
no nah nah hey jude to to
to to to to to to to
to no no no no no no
no
nah nah nah hey jude
what
never ever ask questions
ah okay whew anyway
but you have one yeah okay
i know i know
it was all title i was trying
to be the next line um um
she said
she's said
she said he said shins she see
she she's said
um dead she said
are you writing a song yeah you
guys wanna i like it on this
i like i'm dead she said drop
dead fred
it's good to go go to bed
go to bed okay this is good
like oh my god that reminds me
a killer jeffrey just go to sleep
yeah kimi lost ooh so it's a
creepy song for halloween men could be
back on our word yeah she said
oh
i get what she said is the
title right before she said yeah she's
said oh you
last that cheese hey hello you
oh a radar member out about that
was oh yeah okay let me think
let me think about everything one everything
hey
i don't know if you can guess
this
whose broad broad stripes and bright stars
yep that you're joking yes ah okay
where are you
colin
were you
next i mean other word yeah
where are you all done
where you are
does it neal isn't neil young no
just the ears where you are although
he'd be great singing the song he
would be great singing that song yeah
that is where you are
up
why where you are up where you
are up
a stay
no stay no are you gonna play
the stand i'm looking for in a
place where you know phase
oh
he said around my it might be
it might be whatever the website what
you it's what you not where you
oh my god wow you're like a
hanging chad what you are
um what you want
a manga
and up above
what you are wrinkle to a little
yeah suh world so high famous pop
song black dagger i got one no
it's my turn spencer spencer spencer okay
you did jump my turn last time
you did this you did oh my
word oh i didn't know that
obviously
me and mrs mrs jones so we
have a thi me and my little
monkey me and my shadow what if
that was it meanwhile lucky less i've
never heard that song like well your
singing it perfectly remember it can't be
it's not in the title yeah me
and mrs know i mean the sensor
xuan zang it is a good son
it jones knows me mrs jones they
added the me and wow i like
great choice because i'm sure you remember
absolutely next word
me and you come with me and
we'll see him in awareness of your
imagination okay i'm gonna do you call
germany it's bow from what you did
take in spo and me mr jones
yeah yeah mass
star jones and me see it's weird
mr jason guy from there jones oh
my god those are about the same
people there in the mister jones verse
this fuckin guy keeps mr jones busy
while this other guy while me is
fucking his way me is fucking his
wife
like ah
i didn't know me did that i
didn't only do that either
oh my god alright well i feel
like that wraps up the show it
does that was really fun if you'd
like anyway right lol you ladies pop
your pussy like this so it's interesting
to words
i don't know the melody not to
excellent command
i also that if you would like
to what there's some
there's a way to stop this
there's some holes in this house there's
some hoes in this house said sort
of fide free zone
yeah you would like to switch the
teacher right to freedom usa gmail dot
com and tell us what the three-tier
is and just tell us tell us
what it is yeah let's don't ask
a signal little story i have a
great time doing whatever you're doing the
rest of your day you'd like to
leave us a voicemail we didn't read
voicemails we didn't listen to the voicemail
ooh maybe we will next time ah
why did you call us it heg
claims eight picture of a newspaper headline
hag claims in the number eight also
if anyone wants to write it like
we talk on the show about what
we have been doing with our lives
true we want to hear about what
you're doing so if you want to
send us one of those like christmas
letters that your family says so yeah
yeah it's like all folded up and
it's like three pages front and back
just send us like what's going on
in your life yeah yeah a picture
nobody wanted to be in yeah no
we're not going to read it but
we're not going to talk about it
but we want to know what's happening
with you yeah yeah well yeah we're
not going to read it but we
do want to know what's happening with
you we're not gonna get out loud
we want
on mic oh yeah we're gonna we're
gonna read it to ourselves we're never
going to mention it on the show
but we wanna know what's happening with
you and what's happening with everyone in
your family and try to ride him
in that jovial kind of like yeah
way that that sort of is like
we can tell there's tension but we
don't know like it's been quite a
year yeah yeah um and also we
want to know we want to know
like how
you're doing we want to know the
name of your first pet we want
your mother's maiden name wow oh a
model of your first car address that
you used to live on yes you
know your grade school yeah send us
all those things and oh and also
you're so security yes it will see
your passwords at the movies we'll see
you at the movies remember
or we're going to be out at
the movies every day this week and
the movies if you find us you
get to tag us and we'll give
you a sticker that's right we just
tag us get a sticker we have
hundreds of stickers that we've been trying
to give away and no one wants
them so i have developed back problems
from carrying sticker i know you have
yeah they're all hunched over yeah seven
sticking stickers my back and i have
a rash yeah
yeah so if you say no just
leave food back yeah we're gonna be
seeing five movies today if i let
x seven days just see us and
look i'll even tell you what theater
we're gonna be oh yeah amc burbank
thirteen burbank thirteen we're gonna be there
at thirteen we're gonna watch five movies
a day just if you see us
every days we'll give you tag us
you have to you have to physically
come over
over and tag us on the bud
on the pc somewhere else do not
do that just about just just on
the but yeah if you see us
at the movies and look and we
can't be getting concessions know gotta watch
get us in the theater while we're
yeah guess i'll never go to that
theater again but the mc thirty or
so people will come slap my ass
we're gonna miss a sticker we're gonna
be there
for one week watching five movies a
day obviously the space tool but did
the same five movies every day well
i mean there were thirteen screen there's
thirty three but whenever some more than
once yeah we're going to see five
the first they're all be different yeah
five different ones the next day then
we're gonna see three new ones into
old
yeah
yeah so and so forth i haven't
worked for b so yeah please do
come
because you tag us on the ass
we'll give you what tags matter paul
in the ass say hello to me
from afar lauren do it right on
the nose
it's a boo we gotta get rid
of these stickers guys yes so sick
of these stickers yes wait how are
they taking us
with their with their touch yeah yeah
yeah it's like yeah you're right you're
yeah okay yeah exactly yeah and paige
davis has a few more days to
respond another couple of weeks i think
the sand is running out to pay
and we and look we know tax
day is coming up
make sure you you can write this
podcast off listening to this podcast yeah
when your tax you can write us
off like i've written you too
alright goodbye everyone i
uh