three
if you'd like to make a call
please hang up and dial three
ah there is a bug in here
yeah listeners ah yes that's right would
you sweat this place oh why are
you talking about the plan use
voters
last the plan boss there's a bug
in here boss boss buh aren't saying
nonsense until she puts her phone down
this is how i'm engaged while meeting
my do not disturb for y'all i'll
put it in my purse while i'm
less i have to google your put
it in your boots well put it
in my purse unless i have to
google no one thought that accept no
one thought that you fats but i
said it because i thought well i
guess yeah oh no oh whoa
da da da three years yeah hey
goodbye i'm embarrassed to say that it
up i'm gay oh i'm embarrassed to
say that we all saying that at
my high school graduation you should be
embarrassed i admire it we smiling um
like
spontaneously it broke out and all of
the graduates arrived how could you not
of course i'm not saying we choreographed
no but i'm saying if somebody starts
it of course everyone was gonna join
i mean i joined one yourself but
even though you are being flamed and
i tell you and i know you
started
you are being wood-fired i'm being like
um i filled more i feel now
let's shut that door for sound vacuum
packed it's funny it wasn't open a
second ago i guess there's a there's
a ghost in here what if it's
just a big fly
it helps like choosing
yeah fly leading you guys are like
yeah that's so gross got what flies
fly killer that's like a tennis racket
that electrocute them yes ah which makes
you feel like you're getting exercise while
killing so it's really to sleep over
but every once in a while and
i don't think flies deserve life i
don't feel bad
huh but i everyone's so well i
feel like studios definitely don't well it's
kind of insane when you kill a
fly with this thing and then it
doesn't immediately die and goes like it
starts to like smoke up and then
you have to eat it what you
have knows it's a smell so delicious
it's been cool it's meat yeah it's
way now it's a waste to throw
it away
it's just protein was just approaching just
eat it idiot speeds eyes see give
nah goodbye yum when you remember that
tv show best week ever that i
did absolutely ambrosia every day um when
i hosted it it lasted for a
year and then it was very obvious
that the show was not coming back
even though they wouldn't say that it
was cafe hey
they would just avert their your gaze
oh yeah you ever talked to them
and so i want we had in
the script the cameras will just turn
off spontaneously
be like we're out of here spun
daniel turnoff should keep talking um i
had in the script that i would
the last thing that i would say
right down the barrel of the camera
was see you in hell and then
the fuckin this producer that we had
was like no you can't say that
it was clearly because he was still
gonna work there and he was worried
it was going to turn the story
because he was religious
i won't be there he yeah he
was like you don't say this isn't
actually going to heaven so why you're
telling a lie which is the same
exact um speaking of which sins hurt
yes indeed hurt scott on ah good
christian fun podcast oh yeah i did
that that was really fun i just
met the the two hosts ah when
they were
on my other shoulder tackle i'm talking
about ah passion of the christ and
so i was on their show and
it was a good conversation i felt
like talking all about yeah that's a
fun show i've done that show i
have to yeah i was the last
thing they said i completed the threesome
trifecta that's great and being on it
i was like you could ask me
five years ago i would
i'm like i'm not holding out reading
i don't give a shit i remember
five years ago you were like i'm
not doing any podcasts that aren't all
about me yeah well then i finally
was like okay me and or jesus
that's a good concession it's decent yeah
did you learn anything new about these
diese nutzen idea like i did and
i meant to talk
about it today and then i forgot
oh okay yeah i would wish for
what you learned or forgot to talk
about today i forgot what i learned
i'm talking right now about it
like you were talking about it it's
a job half done yeah that's perfect
yeah perfect that's absolutely perfect it's absolutely
perfect so you so so what did
you say instead of see you in
hell
by i honestly can't remember
and that's the end of a season
made a laid back formula
i can't wait till they reboot the
show without me one day which they
did and then that didn't last either
oh yeah did years later no i
don't think so i think less at
the same time who was on that
i don't owe as much of new
comedians that i was not familiar with
i never saw it i never too
painful yeah you can't go back there
couldn't do it
no no no whoever is hosting no
you shut up now i don't watch
that either you know what if they
regulated that i would just pop it
they scrubbed that from the internet like
there's no videos there no you can't
even see anything expertly scrubbed i'm like
i'm a little confused by that because
there are things that i think should
be scrubbed and arm yeah sure i'll
just get rid of some like show
that was like whatever and then just
like erased weird leaning how did that
happen netflow
looks like scrubs one of their own
shows that oh yeah is on netflix
yeah why not just have it on
there forever like who cares and it's
bandwidth may yeah but the idea that
it might gain an audience later like
a show you didn't didn't perform well
in star tile what's like the things
i'll never be able to find the
spotify algorithm has made the most popular
pavement song this weird
rd b-side i think like that ah
the and there was an article about
i don't recall why that particular song
became the most popular pavement song but
now they play it in concert and
everyone's like yeah because everyone's heard that
sounds so weird algorithm did this algorithm
see we need to be afraid we
do is the algorithm just listening it's
know constantly afraid we need to free
all the time the flout
your heart rate rising at all and
sleep yeah the more enslaved because you
can control it's going guys been having
the worst sleep lately really waking up
all the time and what do you
do as you are so go back
to sleep pretty quickly okay good but
it's like several times during the night
just wake up and then i like
turn over and then i fall back
saying like okay i feel this
bed i'm i'm here in my floating
in space the other the other day
when we were in vegas i took
a nap and janie happens there stays
there paul yeah it's so i'm bringing
the coach am i i'm bringing the
um taking a nap and because my
sleep so bad immediately after we recorded
the episode
only not long after naps can be
the ice napkins i nap and now
i'm useful and how why would he
wouldn't be anti-china i just didn't never
like thinking up i always felt kind
of sick when i woke up like
i had that for the longest time
but it's now i feel great it's
it's time it's the timing of it
and making sure you get the right
amount i took two and a half
hour one yesterday because i wake up
super
they say twenty is perfect but i'm
more of a forty five minute guy
yeah but there are times there are
times where i'm just sitting there and
i'm like i start feeling dizzy and
tingly and i'm like it's time to
nab him yeah just like in it's
so great we knew yeah i tried
to relent i know will try to
let god yeah
i like maps really until recently like
the last few years so it's no
wonder why you look so tired until
just this last i know i know
and everything changed you looked exhausted until
recently it was every time either of
us talked so suddenly looks exhausted if
you think micro natural came out of
my eyes aziz my eyes you see
me
i mean your eyes huh
i don't even know why i just
thought that racism at these come out
of your eyes
this is how you think what you're
reading a cartoon disease are coming out
of the eyes you think when you're
reading a cartoon and you're right you
think when you're reading a cartoon i
read cartoon now let me get the
sri you think when you're reading a
cartoon do you think cartoons are not
read their their scheduled
it sounds weird to say reading a
cartoon does it's wrong what okay what
is right watch them i want to
well also what is love my derby
wait so i'm taking a nap right
yeah in the bed next to me
she's reading a book yeah i won't
take a nap in solidarity with you
because she said she was going to
and then she slips out and read
a book i woke up and i
think in the split second
between sleep and awake i forgot that
she was in the bed next to
me and i screamed i did kind
of shit
like i like bolted upright it was
yeah and i was like why did
that i took me a while to
figure out what happened yeah like what
i do yeah it's weird when you
like hear yourself do something when you're
asleep yes i told you about the
plain one that i was honorary screamed
on the plane
thanks so i think okay i apologize
to anyone if i'm repeating this but
basically i don't i fell asleep with
my ipod on your eye open okay
yeah that's my eyes buds open one
i pod open in the other i-pod
in your pocket of many miss ipods
you still use yours well they they
now i
ipods you have more storage than phones
but now phones have more storage than
ipods and they discontinued ipods used to
have more storage the phones but now
phones twenty four bucks are big hits
yeah i pod where that's what plays
my music and my cars it's like
we're using the phone for so many
things i don't really care but i'm
just like consolidating it onto so i
like being a new phone
just came out never like so much
storage i'm like this is great but
you know what i'm i would sort
of household items in there and i
guess i could just use like when
i pad for this but like i
would sort of like to have a
spotify device oh a whole device just
for spotify it's like saying why don't
you just buy a second phone hey
you know what i liked about the
ipod i really enjoyed the clicks on
the
but i like robin when you're trying
to drive and you reach down to
fast-forward to song but you have to
look down now to press the right
button because there's no click or there's
no like tactile yeah but actually i
think we have talked about this but
i know exactly where my thumb goes
on the fuckin phone because i'm not
at all goddamn day because it's depressed
and yes it's
hey depressed i'm on my phone old
ah anyway so i'm on the plane
and i go to sleep with my
ipod on and a song with a
super slow fade-out occurs and i just
drift into the deepest slumber and then
a really fast song starts after that
song and it's
it scares me awake where i don't
know what's happening and then i see
two people next to me and i
guess as part of my dream i
thought they were people i thought i
was in my house there were people
in my house looking at me on
the bed or something he's grieve get
out with
and which makes it
it would be a great tactic for
the people who break into your home
and everyone on the plane looks at
me including the two people next to
me and i went i apologize i
was having a weird dream but i
didn't know what was happening and they
just were like glared at me you
can't be mad at oh ravenna scary
so lane right um and pablo frightened
because it was one of those things
right like oh i'm in my bed
and i wake up and to start
i
felt like i was in like a
science fiction show or something where two
people looking at me it's very own
material in a human zoo yeah i
love to sleep on the twenty six
but there's something very vulnerable about it
when you're sleeping on the plane it's
like yeah yeah you don't know what
you're doing you don't know i could
sailing camp doing anything be moving where
you're going i'm drooling and like you
know yeah and n
anyone can see it and everyone sees
everyone turns and looks you're talking about
every segment fighting the the people that
can actually our name cross my mind
but yeah for sure what's funny is
that there's very few people that can
see you on the plane it's true
but in certain areas of the plane
such as first-class there's people who go
i mean i've never been so i
don't know
oh wow right when i'm in first
class i fall asleep immediately and then
everyone in the the loser parade who
goes no thankfully i'm playing i'll pass
on planes now they shut shut down
them going into our bathrooms ah it's
such a fucked up thing
you're not allowed to use just any
bathroom it's fucking crazy
let people use the bathroom scott and
i are silent
i am by the way um for
all you people out there who want
to be upset about that ah i
wanna look i learned my lesson
to show for her for work purposes
they have to they literally have yeah
i know i will because you demanded
and it's in your bag says i'm
saying from either side of it oh
yeah because i've been in the situation
flown coach five i'm like really yeah
we'll continue to i'm a coach and
both of the bathrooms are full and
it's like can i please just go
in it is crazy when you have
to weigh your news
ben your li ho is through the
running in the front yeah you wanna
go in the front you're going hey
the right coach in the back they've
gone from my party the drug i
will i will remember the life coach
criteria yeah australia ah you had a
first-class seat which you're entitled to your
wife paid for it yeah i mean
that's that's what you're entitled
yeah and i was in the absolut
area of the plane which was fine
but it was i literally didn't stand
up for nineteen hours i like got
into a ball your ex to somewhere
you can sleep really easily on planes
you were saying that is true i
just curled up into all and i
just fell asleep for as long as
possible do you feel so vulnerable because
you're curled up in a ball like
a potato
oh bug see yeah and they look
like someone might think tatum
they'll just like the run at the
seat when we went to italy i
was i was in coach and it
was just like trying to sleep excuse
oh my gosh totally i believe you
mean yes eataly mario batali is eataly
yeah looks like a country in a
way it's very it's ah you know
those seats are horrible they're they're not
good and it's not easy to sleep
it's me and it just ruins
you're the whole first day that you're
in another yeah i have to have
my neck pillow and i have to
like but i debate whether i prefer
window or aisle because window i can
curl up and just go into the
wind into the window yes i've always
preferred aisle but but now if you
have to sleep on a plane yeah
you don't want to can't do it
without a window no because then people
are going to step over you wake
you up i would rather
or be woken up and wake somebody
also from aisle all the way yeah
you would rather be woken up the
wings imo i'd rather move for someone
else than have to ask somebody to
move for me okay yeah i don't
really i guess i feel the same
about either option i feel bad either
way so i don't like i can't
decide well yeah there's no either way
it sucks yeah so it's which side
of the sick do
one of the flying is just bad
all around what do you remember the
first time you ever took a plane
um ever rode on a plane i
guess no yes i mean i guess
maybe my monster here to visit my
sister who lived in redondo beaches here
today glue your first time
i was like why gonna try it
so i went to burbank and i
said drop me off at l a
x i'm trying to think that's why
beggars airport you guys are like custom
destination just anywhere just give me a
pod yeah sure but okay so you
came out here to visit your sister
yeah yeah yeah that was my first
i wanna plane what was your sister
doing here she was
was pursuing the arts at the time
we charts the black arts the the
entertainment arts oh darkens and not potions
to town tongs in the town oh
two duties in the d on that
trip i saw the band billion the
billy viren and the mediators person do
anything they wanting whoa da yes he
did but if i
told you his moma what would you
give if i told you i don't
think you're good
penny
a hey buddy will you give your
hand yeah hey baby fuck you that's
right that's how we do it in
america yeah that was vaguely familiar we're
not having a hay penny where did
you
where did you see them i can't
remember the name of the venue oh
okay i can't remember the name of
the venue it might not be here
anymore but it might be ms lamar
who knows and so what in what
year was that it was your first
plane and nineteen eighty four was an
it was an olympic year i also
went to the groundlings to see a
show with phil hartman wow he did
add a casual mystery chance about
yes that's very i saw and i'm
sure i told you i saw a
standup show at the improv which included
our ceo hall whoa wait so hell
rick overton i was a santander sa
phone what word was mt and you
took a trip to visit my sister
in redondo beach the first flight was
you were a team i was a
team that's
i was a tree ma'am i was
a teen really it was a sluggish
team thirteen i believe flew to new
york ah this is the one vacation
that i took as a child john
hurt yep thirty we went to new
york and then traveled all around to
to from maine down to virginia washington
dc all that kind of stuff oh
wow whoa whoa what about the philadelphia
via atlanta l a we went to
philly yeah okay yeah as i recall
um but yeah i remember they it
was night so those nineteen eighty three
and they showed my favorite year on
the on the projector screen a like
erected the whole screen got about that
and everyone's smoking on the plane and
all
because everyone people didn't want to yeah
everyone was cigarettes in your mouth as
he boarded but they were even if
they weren't you know i mean yeah
exactly killed at sure dove ah you
know i i can't believe the number
of people that it's very strange to
me because when i stopped smoking i
never looked back like i never
craving for it again i never desired
it again and knowing people i feel
like i meet more people who are
like i miss it i will smoke
again i think most people miss it
it's so while i can't get my
head around that yeah well that's good
that you have that right i'm vs
because when i was when i was
ready to quit smoking it was just
it had become disgusting to me and
i was still doing it
yeah like i don't want to do
this anymore yeah one of those things
i'm glad i never took up same
that's the one thing i would change
and you're the only thing you would
change everything else is like hey that's
the fuckin school hard knocks you know
what i mean you make you're done
you make your dumb mistakes but smoking
is like the amount of money and
health issues and
and whatever that i that i wasted
on that dumb thing i wish i'd
never done it do you think do
you well no i'm not gonna i
think yeah you are then i can
therefore
ah oh by the way oh tell
us paw delays this oh by the
way with paul of tonkin yes about
how you are
oh by the way i'm great
um after we recorded last week in
las vegas you were in las vegas
than what i did go i did
go to the roulette table i did
put down one hundred dollars and i
did bet on black wow and dan
landon green no way when you texas
one of the more rare ones hey
yeah
yeah what what is green green is
the double zero baby oh it's a
double zero yeah never bet on gree
yeah i don't like betting a most
unlucky the honesty felt like it honestly
felt like oh this is just rig
just someone with this guy he wants
me ray you like took one look
at you like let's draw
drive this guy out of the sea
think black riders fifty fifty but it's
really not it's really not what is
it forty eight forty eight two or
something how many cars aren't there like
two double zero spots where i said
forty eight i thought it was just
was talking i thought forty nine forty
nine two will you please stop saying
numbers forty seven forty eight forty eight
forty four definitely
up north definitely right man
if he said definitely i'm definitely a
man
yeah i'm definitely gay man but he
wasn't mean
was the other guy right man i
don't cruise his reign my side opening
night and don't remember a single signs
man because his name was raymond and
ah you said raymond couldn't say yeah
you're definitely a man i'm changing it
you're definitely really frankenstein did you have
to yeah it's a frankenstein everyone thinks
it doesn't hoffman is the titular rayman
your delivery of that reminded me of
ah an ex girlfriend of mine oh
thank you once one just like
you see you see people like scott
in a wig
sorry shoes was beautiful to draw new
oh this is um she met albert
brooks at this some like fancy event
or something and she said oh actually
um i saw your brother ah recently
and our books it was you wearing
a uniform
agree because brother was super dave osborne
was wearing a unit thank you super
dave osborne during the guy from i'm
going to try to find you the
guy from ah
kurt is it yeah exactly see what
else yeah yeah passed away yeah and
he was on bang bang and ah
an interesting guy oh
i remember this from your appearance on
that podcast that your mom was a
fan of the bang bang tv show
oh yes she she takes wonderful every
episode that necessarily come up on this
podcast know on the guy saying how
we never discussed
not just likes to focus on the
negative yeah yeah i know you're all
out of a writing and writing blindly
into cars they they ended like they
hated mister show but they but
oh but they liked that one what
are you shaking your hand there buddy
oh water cap what were the names
of those awkward seekers chuy's over the
culture guys jaws shark jaws jaws was
the meilleurs okay my feet were narrow
so i had to buy sharks everyone
knew every everyone know but they looked
the same no nevada a slightly different
picture
and everyone pointed at my feet and
said those are girls shoes you're a
girl well cool yeah it is cool
sounds good to me absolutely sounds good
to me
yeah dude it rocks up in here
laura when you were little were you
enamored of the olsen twins like when
you would see what's your name on
full house going like okay dude were
you like this i got that high
into my thirties you know i call
if i was you know at the
time going like oh she's cute i
just loved the show yeah i loved
all the characters you want
families in science should be to live
in the house they lived in as
a huge beautiful house would it would
it have been like did it ever
make you say oh i wanna move
to sanford because he was seven times
i wasn't i you know oh often
wondered what that would be like but
they didn't really show much san francisco
ever in that show they went to
disney everyone that was the only real
time never went and that wasn't just
obviously so
ever showed you know going in the
opening tenderloin in the opening credits they
show the hill right that's died on
they never go to abbot kinney but
i did once walk over to the
full house the house that's in the
venice yeah yeah when i was visiting
yeah you're thinking of hay is they
never would do the higher stake what
they never went to haight ashbury that's
hey that says the glendale galleria yeah
it sounds baseball shame same thing yeah
um i i did go see the
house the full house house when i
was in san francisco on station people
sterling and
it was bit of a hike and
um when i got there a lot
of people were taking photos and it
and it was really fun to see
it honestly yeah they painted the door
different color i was like you know
what all here's why this year too
i feel yeah if you buy a
house that is a famous iconic house
keeping away the same different tinctures anyway
it's just disappointing
going to see it yeah different light
have to photoshop their picture yeah like
the home alone houses in wilmette not
right right my where i am the
father of the bride one is around
and i went to that i wish
i loved and the peewee house which
it's um looking pretty rough i would
say but i think there are a
few reasons but yeah you should biden
len live there yeah brady
on child's get out and run various
for a tv show yes they did
like talking about all show i don't
know but i'll recap yeah yeah i
thought that's such a fun idea although
like actors came back to like be
a part of it and stuff but
angling for their own shows yeah wait
all the all the brady bunch yeah
the kids density like
renovated the house and then it was
like they showed the they rent all
of all six came back ah maybe
only five okay i don't think they
renovated it to look like the actual
house from the show because inside but
then yeah thanks yeah who lives there
like what do you do with that
while they were gonna air b and
do it as an expensive air bnb
or something good i would totally say
that where like
you can stay yeah it would be
so fun let's all stay there wait
if that would be hilarious either for
one night and in record shows and
if we see a ghost would have
one of the ghost the ghost of
the heard robert reid yeah that goes
to the uk day today it's these
two like not writing character videos the
character i thought was the guy who
built the house that we'd be sitting
oh he was an architect
no plan here ever talk about building
his own house or was he just
like yeah i bought this but i'm
an architect or witty only do high-rises
i don't think we saw his blueprints
very week we suffered once you once
i think they went to disney right
well someone used me everyone goes into
and just went full houseman disney they
always go there they always go there
or
hawaii they used to anybody why why
and that's why they had that grow
in and oh kin or totem that
was bad luck ooh surfing yeah so
you when you were growing up i'm
i want to get back to an
earlier question when you're growing up in
chicago you please show that geschwind
up you acceptable um when you're growing
up in chicago was there was there
any tv show where you're like that's
where i want to live or was
it all just los angeles because there
were show business there no i always
wanted to live in new york and
then any show that was in new
york i thought was really cool like
friends deals i never thought about living
someplace else oh i'd kill
always wanted to live in new york
but mostly when i was in high
school that's when it really solidified that
i was like i gotta be with
it but let's send a big city
i think i was too cowardly to
imagine ever moving out of philadelphia yeah
and did that trip to redondo make
you go like oh i could see
la being a viable oh we didn't
really you were like so cowardly to
imagine it and yet you like billy
vera's everywhere oh that was listening
athletes never well eventually i did that
you will eventually i i had to
put away childish things yeah man yeah
but i was scared when i moved
here it was like i'd never i
i to to do something that huge
and not have any conception of what
it was like yeah i was lucky
enough i grew up in orange county
so i knew where you know the
universal amphitheater was
chinese unit basically er fra that was
up from l a but you are
killing people or whatever been there yes
but it still seemed no it's a
whole different world but because i really
come i remember yeah my roommate was
a friend of mine from down in
orange county and he moved to the
valley and he was like yeah i'm
moving to a
of death yeah oh god because like
i'm moving to l a i'm like
oh cool and i couldn't even conceptualize
where one would move to an la
and he's like yeah i mean the
valley and i was like what's that
really i didn't i didn't have to
stay okay well then it's a whole
new world i feel like when i
would picture new york in high school
before i mean i'd been there on
a family trip but when i'd picture
living there i would just picture time
square it's a good think of like
where one of the apartment would be
like in what you are saying yeah
right yeah um but my friends and
my university man i went to visit
her when i was a senior she
was two years older than me and
seventy nine yeah yeah
and that was really fun because then
she got to see what her life
was like oh what was it like
it was just so fun she was
living in the dorm and it was
like she's moving in the statue of
liberty so cool like you know all
her friends like going out at night
for you know street food and like
just being out and about and having
five street fighters
you better choose only people spines out
yeah finishing ham etc
ah so then that was a great
trip and i was so happy my
mom let me go do that because
i got to fly by myself and
go see what i came here when
i was a teenager i still had
that um that ah just irrational um
dislike of california that people
will that anywhere out to your staff
yeah yeah yeah yeah i know people
like i mean i remember that as
well growing up i like l a
had so many stereotypes about it that
were negative that i never really thought
about it do you think everyone talked
like this dude yeah that was like
where's the beach like the californians
man oh ya it's actually british people
doing american accents like i'll authorities celestials
the holy oil of rose yoran even
after i've lived here yeah that's your
way in yeah over on yoran
i saw two things the the real
world season six i think when they
were in seattle that made me go
like oh man seattle would be cool
to live in and it was before
i'd ever been that i went to
seattle world made it look cool because
because they're right there out here yeah
yeah it was it was really cool
and then i went to the piers
and everything i'm like oh okay which
season was that that was irene and
david where are the
me my baby oh no they they
just did a reunion did you watch
reality recap yeah well i did not
even who slapped her i want even
star stephen swaps yeah wave is actually
kind of cool now it was reality
rehab right yeah have you seen the
paramount plus series where they get to
cast together okay yeah the the new
orleans one is supposed to be really
haven't watched it yet i've watched it
it
there's one ah cast member that makes
me very uncomfortable because she seems studying
something else ah
having some sort of mental illness crisis
yeah oh dear but she's definitely self
being polite
but um but it is very good
it's it's yeah it's interesting for season
with new york and i really was
enjoying it yeah that one was very
fascinating season two made me depressed because
it was the la cast and it
seemed everyone was having the exact same
arguments that they had twenty five years
ago and i was like do people
ever change and
even in this new new orleans one
it's kind of like the the super
religious guy is still super religious but
don't you think that because they were
on that show together which like really
was i'm very confused as to whether
this is a new cast know it's
the old csx national united last guys
into the same house or whatever
god if they can get the same
yeah but who had the same idea
and so we don't know if they
can get the same every season to
that could not every place was gone
okay so that was similar don't you
feel like because because i think this
is rather than saying they don't change
i feel like if they were on
a show together and the personalities clash
whatever way and it was on tv
and that was before there was a
lot of reality tv and this was
a huge
i'd show that everyone saw and so
you're talking talking about that for the
rest of your life yeah i probably
hold onto a lot of those things
and go like oh there's this fucking
guy again for the last thirty years
i've been hearing about how i didn't
say the right thing when you did
that yes i would love the my
point i think with how people don't
change is like they get that out
of the way kind of early where
everyone like
like hashes out their issues of what
happened on the show than they either
forgive each other whatever i'm saying after
that point they then just start repeating
their actions from the books from the
old season or they have the exact
same arguments that they had in the
old season the exact same way that
is weird and the people fly off
the handle in the exact same way
they used to
no one seems to have matured i
think it's different for this new new
orleans season where people have like grown
and there's a new new orleans yeah
godly orleans i gotta go no not
there's not a new cast he's saying
a new thing there's a new city
yeah yeah oh hey did my these
clouding around huh taking a break ever
yeah we gotta take a break huh
i was like just realised we were
talking yeah that's alright goodbye goodbye goodbye
goodbye goodbye my guy
and we're back oh no no what
are you typing loren loren has phone
lauren has phone even keep talking you
have phone honey duffy mahoney do you
have phone
what's wrong you had you haven't even
not touched your phone
for your phone gets cold
oh my god okay i'm here i've
only seen season one of the real
world and then that season with como
mad maybe even tonight that's the new
orleans one yeah that's the new orleans
yeah and they're back orleans that was
new orleans that season hey timberlake's i
don't remember any aspect of new orleans
or any or whatever city it was
i don't remember any aspect of there's
a spiky haired super religious christian who
is still still looks staged at the
religion the super religious christian i remember
from that season was a more odd
girl yes the mormon jilly but she's
not have spiky hair no no no
no gentleman has spiky like bleach dinnerware
to religioso yeah anyway
too many i don't remember him at
all let them chalk talk to each
other yeah he's still remember her and
david he's still very religious and in
fact when pressed about so do you
think that gay people ah are human
beings human beings he's like this interview
is over
wow so wow not even like a
prepared answer why are people so over
it people are really bad people it's
nuts the mormon girl is no longer
mormon but she's the one that i
fear for her oh no she needed
the guiding she needed jotting light of
religion johnson said his name was
joseph smith joseph that's right you and
your hat look your facts yeah he
looked in his hat and i thought
you're doing miller's crossing lines with an
accent it's like i'm doing a parody
of that i see because oh it's
always good we explain our jokes he
would have his peep stones and he
would have this one keep stuff explained
peep stones to us what did you
try to say
the infinity stones when i tried to
sit down
twitter peeps wedding yeah i don't know
this story oh okay i have mormon
ah rabbi about infinity i have more
blood called about that but beautiful beautiful
glove will have you watched the last
one hundred and i yeah the what
is it infinity war yep yes i
just watched last night i will not
be speaking on this getting one
funny is that all questions should be
directed to newcomer when you see um
like ah the replica are you doing
any glow like that to ask newcomers
when you just when you see the
like replica you can buy the infinity
glove yeah whatever it looks exactly like
the like right now that's honestly don't
know i think that's the best part
billion anyone this gourd
exactly they've successfully replicated full gems yeah
it looks like plastic i want them
yeah yeah but if i had to
have anything i would want that it's
interesting that those those didn't take off
the way that sometimes like fashion from
a movie or something everyone will strike
oh like everyone's gonna start wearing that
yeah like like like as as a
fashion scale michael jackson but yeah i
think because
you could make anything like your head
was
yeah
nice
nightmare sleep
a plane and there's two michael jackson
standing around and staring at me like
hey they have to look good together
to make change in one glove
to make
one glow hey what the fuck were
we oh so joseph smith yeah tell
us about peep stones he i cannot
decorate the beach where heaps he was
getting these messages that only he was
allowed to see they were like right
on so i have heard that they're
written on stones with marker or like
the probably marker yeah because it was
like the one year fifteen
eighteen hundred or something oh yeah yeah
it's a very young religion it's young
and you do don ross um and
he would he would like look from
what i remember and yeah he didn't
believe mormonism explained by paul f tompkins
i'm wrong about this yeah this is
not dreary history this is easy just
go to wake up sober hazy summer
learn about what you want to learn
about yeah everyone but if i'm wrong
you can certainly look it up and
you can sue him will even say
that i take all lawsuits over be
getting this wrong
if you can give it a core
with this i have added i look
forward to reading that this is a
challenge um and ah ah so he
the reason why um yeah it's very
hard to get past the scammy nature
of this religion is that joseph smith
is like god
god is communicating to me ah he's
giving me these messages on these stones
and i only i can look at
them everybody's like okay yeah sounds good
to me yeah well that's what they
say
many many religious yes feels like they
come back to something like that yes
yes yes right um so that was
it oh or so i've heard peeps
and they were called peace zone i
believe they are called peeps oh well
that's very silly wow it's adores that
what peeps are named after yeah yes
that's what he's there are mormon candy
yeah made by mormons for mormons every
time
leave by you you just know he
just saw peeps inside his hat and
he's like um the stones say he
just like was like panicking and making
something oh seven and three-quarters i should
be allowed to have five wives
that's such a flex when you're doing
religion you're like yeah i'm allowed to
fuck everyone yeah and you are not
ah you know what if you guys
can do it sure good yeah i
mean hey god wants this sister wives
were entering camp theresa no fascinating program
flows engagements and divorces happening in that
film no way
a divorces of this destroy fiddler says
fitted on living people leaving because the
struggle will you make of these systems
lesion on my daughter's wedding day hasn't
oh by the way the offer yeah
how's what today's miles can i do
some of my offer million precious please
okay
so this is my good one oh
ready hey ready what's going on with
you today ready ready get out of
my office ready rumpelstiltskin
oh yeah he was great godfather right
of the battalion of the grad hey
you know butter up a guy like
you stumbled back is how you do
it you go the gig another week
of the league of escape from the
regular world that the show that offers
so crazy it's low yeah cool i've
told them it's a little bit here
miniseries it's cool i will be in
the other room just laughing at how
craig
easy it sounds because everyone's doing the
most extreme accents i can absolutely so
ribisi is they're going like oh yeah
west brom lie why watch don't you
go back
i'd make an otago rock band okay
miles teller's like blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah is the exact
same cadence for every lee's miles teller's
acting in this movie like he won
a contest to be and he did
not want to win yes exactly because
his wife entered it is like far
this is for her and he's so
good in top gun
when she's in it we showed up
played any playing marlon brando no he's
playing the producer of the movie it's
all a story it's based on yeah
okay i didn't know anything so he
it's so weird because he has the
exact same cadence for everyone says blah
blah blah blah but yeah blah blah
blah blah blah and then you've got
the other guy going ready let's go
with you ready for this graph few
good plays robert evans legendary producer
her and he's having the time of
his life his time is english she
is the most fun yeah he's you've
seen him he's been in he's been
ilion thing he's beating matthew good woody
allen's match pulling yeah man
there was a scene in that movie
where bunk going over the net today
is the forty love you know it's
slum he there's a scene in that
movie where
it puts the polygons
wow a trifecta yeah man you've got
i know who that is he good
ready ready what is it going to
enjoy something you haven't got the guy's
name pierre smith fire major or use
my major minor major or submit ursa
major ursa major money ursula from the
little mermaid
and there's like some scene that's going
on that is clearly improvised there's three
people in the scene in a woody
allen movie and a woody allen movie
you can just tell by the way
they're talking yeah and it's like you
can see i think he was on
major drugs at this point like he
was doing heroin jonathan oh yea and
so he
he's he tries to like get in
on the medallion prophet fifty third now
they're pretending like he's not there it's
very weird oh very very i just
saw a post about the before sunrise
trilogy which i love i still have
not seen them i want to cover
them on the show well ready you
gotta watch ready you gotta watch the
oh but for sunrise i saw a
post about arise even better and now
we're going in between psoriasis never before
it's not really richard
days so like richard linklater's there was
zero percent improv in the movies interesting
zero person i was really surprised because
they have a very natural flow yeah
they're good actors so they're fantastic actors
it's without a doubt two three of
the best movies ever made wow i
got damn we would want you behind
on the table which spoken scott hasn't
seen talking about em um mm
maybe whenever you do it depends on
when you do it whenever you have
a free moment then okay i only
wanna do the first one okay let's
find good boundaries go down
we'll we'll talk about that ah another
time great more deep ready ah huh
i just cannot watch the show without
saying ruddy over no i love him
so much he's really funny in it
but it's the craziest accent show i've
seen yeah so long yeah and cool
up will just be howling with laughter
listening to she can't eve
can he pick out what they're saying
but she's just like these accents what
are they doing i want to see
a little bit just to know it's
really good have you ever done an
accent and in anything you have would
you do homes um no i didn't
speak in that film for at all
but allying the end when i was
american that was one good party i
know you have time
somebody speak a movie you got to
have him talk at the very i
did speak at the end and say
i was just kidding um let me
in the face i just like my
son i have something with an accent
coming out oh wow wow um and
the ugly but it was by like
that but like the movie yeah bio
oh pig
if there was a biopic about that
person i don't even know who it
is but ah like that and they
called it by like the well
they called it like that i'm all-in
yeah but it's like kolam get tina
turner biopic malignant belinda what if they
came to you and they said look
lauren we have an offer for you
we are not gonna tell you how
much it is where i'm going to
tell you the extent of your role
we're not going to tell you where
it shoots well we can tell you
is this movie is called belinda
here's what i would i mean hey
i can't probably say who's making you
have to at least somehow into making
like there should be some reason to
want to do it i can give
you a rain but for the art
you want but just know that told
by later but i have no other
information from one dollar to eighty million
one dollar scale to three million dollars
okay and then the question i have
is
problem either one skill while legged duh
i interesting is why would you do
it if you as long as you
didn't have to say about like that
or i think it was that the
additive in theory i would want to
be the one saying lay down but
yeah practice i think you'd be better
if i was in because i'm sure
be ripped to shred here's what i'm
gonna tell you
that's not algae doesn't um here's what
i can tell you everyone in the
movie says it at one point but
only one character will say it in
the final cut oh so it's like
whoever is the best yeah it's a
bake-off it's about like deaf like deaf
metal yeah okay fine i'll do it
we've somehow yes we've
fashioned script yeah we fashioned the script
somehow so that everyone gets to say
this line on their land to make
sense but yeah so that we can
cut all of the yes
only people
reflect says the same line in their
dialogue never in the same scene
that's that's great do you ever have
a house that you made up in
your mind that you pictured in a
book that you read that you um
remember why do i know i know
you do that that i pictured in
a book that i read okay for
example right now i just just think
you're mostly written a book was just
see what this house that i made
up when i was reading a book
and i you know made up with
the house look like
whose house and i was just thinking
about the house just now randomly problems
in my head and i don't know
why but what was it the book
was called nothing to see here and
it's actually a fantastic book i zipped
right through it everyone tell you it's
about because there's a twist and i
didn't read the summary on the flap
and i was so happy i didn't
because i didn't know it
gonna have it the twist is there
was something to see yeah there was
something to see and it doesn't they
braid it on the fucking book which
i thought was kind of crazy because
it's a fun twist yeah yeah marketing
but anyway i just picture i made
up this like beautiful mansion with this
like pool that that the describing the
book and i just pictured in my
mind that i don't know why you
know when things just popping my memory
but it's not a memory that is
a
one question if you ever walked into
a house that looked exactly like that
would you be like holy shit this
is the place yeah and then what
would you do i'd start screaming and
breaking everything
i remember when i was a kid
a series of books ah that were
sort of narnia like but it was
these kids ended up in this world
that was like basically like a chessboard
you know like i sorta remember the
a yeah and um chess for dummies
right yeah
google story was real dough and the
boy was the person reading
no i just open it up and
there was like a mirror pages you're
the dummy yeah all the dummies books
have that and i really love gsu
i love the books again i don't
remember a ton of details about when
to save it this way and then
they'll be the real dummy hey lillian
hellman when those dummies books to see
if there is a mirror because they
don't know
that naropa yeah and then they turn
the page here's the real mirror and
then you you actually defend here oh
and by the way post malone did
you see that cover i posted of
him saying better man no i did
not i saw i saw that you
posted that i saw what the song
was and i was like i don't
like the original oh i love that
song okay but i loved this kids
i never
i heard him saying i was like
what's going on i was so surprised
by some good yeah i loved it
i liked post-mortem and he was great
he he also did some nirvana covered
we went on the coat spree watching
youtube videos i like his humor what
were they sprite commercials thirties phone i
don't know i don't think i've seen
that you know what if you look
closely at the tattoos on his face
their terms and conditions
yeah and and then if you turn
it inside out but it says may
apply it's a map to treasure oh
wow if you look at it inside
out yeah you could say oh that's
right it's on you man yeah don't
do that don't do that to both
host but i feel like i can
see there was like a castle in
that series of books that i feel
like i can still see even though
i remember
for yeah details yeah yeah it's weird
took a memory that you made up
the mind is very funny isn't it
in mind interesting thing with all the
lines and real goofy little too rough
ah down bound but um save it
for later and oh girl jam at
all pearl jam i mean i know
jerome s booker other great wonder you
know why i like him because they
tell stories with the song yeah like
harry chapman now they'll pause the song
in the middle
just tell a story yeah bedtime story
it's getting better
asleep in chance huh let's take a
break
that's ah
you should cover your next show they
were one of the last would be
fucking rad do you think people will
lose their shit yeah oh my god
if you sang a pearl jam song
at your next show people would love
that they would be like what when
rubbing their eyes and going like am
i watching pearl jam
you know what there's less program started
to suck my legs and i think
it's i think it's audio safe
um there's a song i think it's
audioslave and it goes like to be
lou alone you do not have out
now familiar and i was so surprised
by the song because i thought it
would be because you're playing no i'm
not exactly that when you just did
like hardcore music but oh yeah no
i know which one's self-esteem song and
the audience we are watching this like
old nineties concert and the audience was
like
with the high thousand singing or whatever
to oh the audience was in their
nose ah hold video online of the
concert and the audience was like crying
at the sung and i was like
he's seem like self-esteem and like being
yourself and it's just like so surprising
because i hear the name like like
that taddeo helicopter i see i'm not
thinking i'm gonna get something
like that obviously showed me it was
cool to be weird dumb not i'm
trying to trying to find the what
did you just don't know what i
mean
i'm trying to find the song oh
no wow wow wow wow wow i
have a we find it what's called
be yourself by audio so be yourself
here we go the full title is
beresford by audioslave yeah it was two
thousand and five songs so i was
wrong with when i said the counts
oh shit he's got the oxcart that's
why they call him scotty ox
this that's why they do that
so be yourself this is be yourself
by audioslave mm i'm not hearing it
oh there it is here we go
hey audioslave fans just as juneteenth approaches
we'd like to remember
ah you observe it on a monday
this month
bees go well you have to play
the glass so ah so
whoa that was true those listener and
me and me ah no it i
don't know now i never will we're
gonna see here lazy good par alright
alright here we go you want me
fast-forward yeah i don't care play the
chorus alright here we go right
this is how i felt when we
were talking about songs to make us
cry yeah and then my song it
was a more of a build yeah
we just listen to the very first
part of it's not fair i seem
like i'm i have mental problems yeah
there we went a little bit
yeah well
here we go kick it
last two jobs
no way jesus every day guy resides
in sigh
a good moser
to make eighty
children's
uh i'm using like all of my
brain
a way out
ah
anyway anyway i was surprised to say
the least and post malone surprised me
as well you think you wanna hear
a little bit of that should i
do you want anyone you can do
this yeah yeah yeah yeah
let me throw me the dongle
give it a real swing like he's
doing
yeah you do you will love it
it is great yeah so
ah funny dude do you know what
i think that is funnier than the
when somebody reaches for the car door
handle you dry e pull-up oh yeah
this i hate that one but my
brother drove over my oh dear i
like it what how no my wife
has been my way if i
oh no my wife was like god
fucking hell it's okay is you know
hey is it eight o'clock at night
guys that's how it feels this time
for bed go i can play it
i'm sorry i know maybe i could
play i'll play it i'll send you
a dm oh sliding their baby like
i could play it i can buy
it play it
prep can play it i can play
i'm gonna play i can play it
come on with me on my blade
alright we make good and we gotta
take break
no gao there were back and don't
call me daughter ever don't call me
guess what it's time for pronouns are
brother father
don't come you don't owe when i
say something you know like please the
dome we want you to say things
this is one-third your show the love
it if you'd say so just i
would say less yeah to mean really
i really want to say last and
not interrupt you all the time but
you're not saying anything
this is true
a quick shout out to a podcast
that i've recently started listening to n
w t i'm devouring yeah this guy
this guy don't listen the first focus
going on with um ah podcast called
three bean salad which is three hey
there three british supervise well yeah here's
the thing there are three british comedians
and they have a topic that they
discuss this is like
lawrence topics week yeah some similar what's
funny is there like a ah a
version of us where they listen to
each other no support no way no
we support various people at certain times
a story mission wait what's the alliances
are formed that you recommended to me
that my celebrity crush don't
gleason was on though he was on
it yeah you wrote you sent it
to me it was like a show
where they talked about food oh off
menu yeah yes i liked it a
lot yes it's really interesting but also
hosted by two very funny british comedians
james yeah that was we get it
you're an anglo file well maybe why
don't you just move over so
see do you think i am do
you think i am an anglophile there's
this like phenomenon that children start to
speak with a british accent if they
watch a lot of pep i've heard
a lot of wet peppa pig it's
a dorsch cartoon and they get addicted
to it and then they start speaking
like because that's how they're learning how
to speak it's interesting because i used
to watch a lot of pbx as
a kid because my parents used to
watch oh yeah
tapi piggies pig this pig um but
that's how i would watch a lot
of like upstairs downstairs and and various
english stuff and so i grew up
like kind of really able to do
like english accents because of that and
then i lost it all but i
feel the same way yeah but it
was really instructional when i was a
kid just constantly like learning how
everyone in the world talked yeah and
him being able to imitate it i
sometimes wonder if i were able to
do a scripted thing in an accent
would i be better at it than
i was better at improv i was
better at it in scripted because i
had to do a memory carol yeah
the word yeah you say more than
once and you literally can do like
the vowel substitutions in your script and
stuff like that because they have
different vowels yeah yeah everywhere all the
consonants though sometimes they swap em sometimes
the v instead of th it's right
rough so do you have three teacher
heavy have i got a three times
you are three cha daddy um
disgusting that is going to bring it
at this bringing us three child is
going to bring us violet crumble
um i made my notes in a
different color so i could find it
easy smart oh you're so smart and
yet you're still not saying it clever
girl she's a very clear guess she's
a very clever go to chi is
a dinosaur
i'm sorry about that is over lots
of raptor goes damn oh can i
just say i'm in bentley's new music
video and the music video is great
and so is the song and it's
called parents get high if you want
are you telling us you know i'm
telling the audience i've seen little promos
for yeah it's fun
i've seen i've think i've seen an
advert for that you've heard of it
oh wow right pepper that'll do peppa
pig
all right nah it'll do you remember
this guy k p o he is
like enough with this guy he's our
worst
suddenly our worst enemy he's our biggest
threat he's our biggest fan and our
worst enemy oh right i said he
oh he's submitted i just said threat
he submitted a survey
oh you guys feel like we're having
one of our patented disagreements very very
american one of your patented oswald's um
he this guy k p he submitted
this three-tier patrol it was we all
know him as kitchen we all know
him as kitchen patrol he's appealing spuds
he's like paw patrol but if it
was a kitchen instead yeah oh now
i
get a a like if a blender
had a hat on oh now lean
if you're if you're a blender
so he submitted this to nature called
press junket and we were like there's
a lot of problems with this yeah
we had notes let's get a lot
of notes and we said ah you
know work on this and recent right
into the mike
it was funny because you turned away
from it until the audible part yeah
you're right there was there was a
panelist best week ever panels before the
hosted version that killed it the first
time um who yawned during a take
and like did not like didn't stop
like didn't say i'm sorry let me
do this but just gone through
as if that was gonna make it
to air and it's like this is
a television show there was a this
person posted on ah the online yell
i just mentioned data but i didn't
have a pen or paper so she
signed my notes app and just typed
zendaya into this person's that's funny but
yeah she did it ah
well the same thing is about to
happen to me as soon as we
stop recording oh she just did it
on my ah
ah
yeah i got on
okay so k p so maybe just
mitts total killer waste space
i wouldn't go that way i think
we saw the potential in him he
was not he was only talking out
of the gate it was like no
copy this needs work go back yeah
go backward yeah back there guy goes
skip back he goes to us for
whip back yeah well either jack to
the drawing board yeah and so then
he comes back because one
one of our notes was what's the
big prize because he said there was
a big prize that you went yeah
then it gets back to us finally
last week alright here's here's his initial
submission ah one person is a movie
star doing a press junket for a
made-up movie one person is an interviewer
from a random local news station and
the other person is the stars handler
trying to keep the interview on track
i actually think it's a good game
well why no we didn't it needed
something more because it wasn't necessarily a
game for sure you know what i
mean yeah and so then he comes
back different chain came in at three
oh we shut down just shut the
fuck oh and asked discuss touch we
certainly don't ah then he comes back
with this
for three minutes when this is him
or is this you kev this is
all him you never made any suggestions
right and you never will yeah hear
me god kevin by the way had
to learn sign language in order to
communicate with us because we don't want
him on mic yes so and you're
doing a good job and you did
it just by watching kota stop saying
i love you so you know anything
they said in kota and that's it
i love that he just knows the
dialogue from the script from movie until
the end he has to work every
conversation into that he wants to be
a singer i guess
time to go out on the boat
tonight timer set for three minutes one
players in a lwv hollywood bad boy
or girl doing a press junket for
their new movie one players they're stressed
out publicist and the third is an
entertainment reporter the actor has a silly
rumor going around about them example tried
to grow weird disease growing out of
my eyeballs right now amen yeah the
caesar slower
dude the rumors decided ahead of time
by the reporters only and is only
known by a publicist and reporter hazard
the reporter is slyly trying to get
the scoop from the actor button hope
a bubble says destroy obama
you knew you were going to yeah
sometimes honestly that's a good description of
their job but yes hamas
yeah bye bye sis says i almost
shut down when i'm done i'm done
for my career you've been driving law
but i said oh baba baba gotta
walk on goober and get my car
by bus yeah i can't go already
over driver drive my car and you
drive you
where you can drag my main main
main male guys five stars yeah wait
hoopers driving your look weird out i
love you normally love your work yeah
first of all why is the person
that's giving him notes all the time
well we gotta we gotta talk about
oubre you can drive my reporter is
trying to get the scoop from the
actor but the publicists are trying to
stop them and keep the interview about
the movie the person playing the actor
improvises the title their character and all
the other details of the movie if
the interviewer can slide and get the
actor to say the rumor within the
three minutes they win the big prize
okay that that was the original
that was original and i said what's
the big prize okay and he like
got us all go sassy yeah it'll
take more like that's a prize of
course i had to play it wasn't
just suggested some modification okay so what
you've you've you've taken over k p's
job and let's hear it if he's
not going to step up to the
plate you're going to pinch hit okay
the the there's two rumors what the
reporter and it comes up with a
rumor no and the publicist comes up
with a rumor oh okay both are
told to the actor what so the
reporter and the publicist are thinking it's
two different rumors and the reporters trying
to get the information about why
one of them but the publicist just
trying to stop the other one yes
trying to stop both yes so the
i think yes trend will stop trying
stop but don't really what you're trying
to do is figure out what's going
on okay and so the actor hole
has all the knowledge yeah and is
miss and you know obviously is trying
to keep the the other two from
knowing great what the secrets are let's
do so you have to get your
own way
what your what your the secret that
you're trying to stop if you're the
publicist you have to guess what that
secret this is like the opposite of
k p this is p k this
is so good let's do this okay
so pretty kickass let's just yeah let's
just be patient sb assign tasks and
explain it again yeah two who are
tell us who we are well as
as someone who would like to hold
all the cards who feels good about
that i think
think scott okay i'll hold all the
cards you need be the agony actor
yeah speak the speech i pray you
as it comes typically off the ton
oh god
think tipping life and dango which being
the light fandango reaction to shakespeare oh
yeah this guy again that guy the
bard yeah i've heard hard these nuts
yeah i'm a little over the source
material you these nuts alright let's go
subset ever gonna end no because
i wish it would
we're going long over time and we
have another one to do my friend
all right she know everyone will hate
me
i think the second one is always
the second one i don't think it
works for loopier um people like the
even numbered ones and not the odd
numbered ones that is how it breaks
out oh we only did one in
las vegas so now we're broken the
cycle we broke a little shy cool
okay hey true believers broken guys sex
shows like stanley with the
the nevermind can't ryan was saying well
last night
simply take it over half of santa
clauses duty yeah here the rally's only
gifts on christmas eve
you'll be delivered no rye
okay i'm already really familiar with his
work you're the publicist yeah thank you
but direct all questions to newcomer here
the public shall your eye on about
mate you're the hubbub yeah i'm the
damn full reporter okay i'm gonna hop
up guys are gonna text me okay
so you text us the rumors oh
you make up the rumor
or like compete with those apps i
thought it was the opposite we know
it was we change okay oh okay
so he will tell wait each maybe
it is yeah that's what i thought
forgot already lost oh so so you
text him yeah tucking rumor you know
both rumors and then how did they
get out we're trying to draw it
out but he or
am i trying to not eat but
you know one of the no but
i think would be more sensitively or
saying things that get him to go
did i fucking guinea pig you know
i mean like that's but that's the
usual way we do guy paul's you
know one of the secrets your trying
to draw hour and if you go
to jersey mighty you're not going to
have it mike's way you know you're
always gonna have we're doing
paul's game we do all switch mike's
way yeah crunch
oil vinegar salt pepper sea grudge and
just say crunch oh but man what
jersey mike was really wow their jersey
you gotta do cover back you gotta
do got it on that you got
you got
okay alright so paul's way i'm trying
to find out what what loin is
secret and i and i'm trying to
to sort of just i'm just talking
okay this is what you do best
yeah just talking not thinking yeah ok
here we go oh are you mad
no but just beginning
here we go
he mad and by the way i
haven't done yet one thing i'm supposed
to do i insulted you and i
was like what it means i mean
you know i'm just waiting for your
text and it's about you yeah okay
if this fictional actor that i'm portraying
know okay delete delete mel gibson you
don't wanna hear any rumors that we've
heard what have you heard something about
me know okay oh my god
they're totally silent right now as their
text me these rumors
oh my god i got something from
jason maneuvers before you guys see
is it over now it's some some
marvel news i'll be reporting on newcomers
yeah
okay got it i got one from
paul i've not gotten one from laura
and it hasn't gone hasn't gone it's
my signal even the wifi doesn't work
on my phone i as well i
think three or four bars lorin yeah
and i want i will trade off
giving details about the movie okay okay
i'm still waiting for lauren
do you want to show me yeah
don't show their dojo lauren is sacred
okay it'll probably go through eventually okay
if you forget got it alright on
the reporter right yeah i'm the hypothesis
hey how much how long is this
oh i think it's gonna be like
twenty can you cut it down to
twenty three i can make it three
i think hi guys hi brenda hi
gay greatest thing is so much for
saying yeah today yeah why did you
call me brenda
you know i was calling your publicist
brenda oh because that's your name yeah
so i was looking at the wrong
people saying hello obviously yeah well you
have your ray bans on so we
couldn't even tell oh i'm so sorry
i didn't realize i'm really sorry you're
fat in black no no no no
because you're wearing a black sea and
you have an alien idled in your
arm i know i'm wearing a black
suit
oot i know i'm wearing sunglasses i
know of an alien cradle my arms
but there's a logical explanation for all
this i just don't have the time
to get into it i understand we
only have fifty minutes yeah it's actually
bringing it we're we're on a bit
of a time crunch she's gonna eat
for lunches so we're going down to
three machines to eat for lunch yeah
okay that's interesting i have four stomachs
like going out in three minutes so
what publicists what publication are you with
published sisters chic
i'm right yeah i'm with backstage northwest
oh okay wow arena okay so what
does this wow a lot of people
in general it's yogurt that's yeah alright
okay yeah um great so let's get
right into it if you can you
ready yes absolutely thank you brenda okay
yeah so limp um yeah very excited
about this picture
you so much yeah and i imagine
the holy spirit it's never been done
before on screen it's the first and
people think people play god people played
a lot of people played jesus yeah
well so it's funny brenda that you
mentioned um that you have to eat
for lunches because ah i understand you
ah forgive me if this is in
polite but you're you're kind of a
hungry boy aren't you
it was exactly irvin said to me
he certainly hasn't you're never hungry or
thirsty for new innovations new innovation yeah
really because you seem like a very
traditional kind of guy but what what
are these new innovations well you know
just contraptions
and things you know contraptions yeah such
as
you know electric stirring sticks stuff like
electric stirring sticks yeah
keep you who has who has the
wrist strength this will be great for
your interview keep going on these days
you know to keep going on this
yeah you want to talk about the
for lunch ask him more about the
the sticks and things you want me
to know about this isn't that what
well we don't know what you want
because you've never made it clear
ah i thought i'm trying to get
him to say the thing that i
texted them
no i'm trying to figure out the
thing that you texted him you're trying
to figure out the thing that i
texted okay okay here we go
i mean yeah i am hungry ah
a lot of times yes i am
a hungry boy yeah yeah yeah yeah
especially right now i think more people
know that recently than did before i'm
sorry did you um glimmer did you
eat something that you shouldn't have eaten
i don't think that it's illegal to
eat who's doing what to really come
back who's doing the inner
vw here that would be illegally legal
at me so that's why ozzy osborne
is in jail right now okay well
i thought because he's fighting for his
life did you eat something like um
like a tongue or something oh my
oh we don't have to talk about
that let's talk about the ah the
the movie now everybody's in this oh
oh it's a star studded affair it
seems like the um we've got ten
romney yeah jennifer connelly i was gonna
make a comparison but oh please i
don't think anyone with i think i
think all the stars have my favorite
initials though in the really yeah so
quentin isn't it cute
ah yeah and ah ah a line
from the movie coraline is deep yeah
this song is fun is definitely yeah
vv sure yeah or v yes i
mean yeah anyway yeah go juicy v
yeah that's some way that's the way
the bird
i mean ooh wow when i hear
those when i hear those initials well
it's like excuse me yeah hue v
c what about it who can
is this movie why you sleep i
don't know when i hear those initials
i just triggered something in me
ooh god what a triggers like a
sort of narcoleptic reaction sort of it
seems like an entire yeah i've we
may have to wrap this up like
you keep saying those sounds like from
what you so do you have some
sort of condition perhaps um check to
see what condition my condition isn't say
i mean it's it's definitely something that
i
can't serve an unhealthy habit somebody i
need to do yeah is it something
you're comfortable that's talking about britain i
am comfortable it's i mean it's a
rumor but i think we could squash
it right now yeah sure so what
people are saying yeah is that ah
you fall asleep watching qvc that i
can't you can't sleep unless
as you want ain't gay gay gay
ah and then what i heard is
that you ate guinea pigs bow ding
ding ding ding
it's not illegal it's not illegal it
tastes good do it not only it's
like a little freedom lie
why would it be like that
oh excuse me i have to burp
ah ro ross cleaning two one two
four three six nine every time you
throw up you recite the phonebook
sorry just what what i eat is
coming back up o ralph's cleaning so
you you ate like do like a
cleaning solution are you sure shaky pizza
are you sure two three menus is
okay to talk about this in front
of her i mean are you willing
to go not sure but i'm not
talking
in front of her i've just can't
control my burping because i had such
a big lunch so recently on set
a lot of people discovered something about
you and maybe you didn't want them
to know about this yeah unfortunately you
were the one who inadvertently let them
know well it's oh it's one of
those things where you know the sound
person should have been ah
making sure this didn't happen obviously you
want to trust them but you can't
always can you can always so i
should i should i should double check
these things yeah but oh god excuse
me
ernie's plumbing eight one six nine three
two five a sound like tourette's but
it's the phone
forget it
yeah it didn't work it didn't look
like tomatoes it was that i left
my mic on while eating a phone
book in my trailer i said you
ate the phonebook know so you're ripping
up the phonebook is it your birthday
and anniversary of the fog implies that
you ate it no we're not playing
implied here we're playing we're playing a
faulty game yeah didn't
work so who's who who weren't best
f t or k p that was
my fault i'll take full response you're
going to take the blame there's something
about the games and me it doesn't
work
it just doesn't work you know i
find games to be tricky little things
but we'll get it next time we'll
get it next time hey we'll get
an exit game good game good game
good game good game good game she
chased him he was really funny as
in professional baseball games the teams do
that themselves do they really yes after
a professional baseball game i was going
to see the teams
line up separately and they'll go to
all i'm saying good game to each
other i was watching the challenge not
any other team oh idea i was
watching the challenge the other day and
someone got eliminated smacked the the his
competitor in the butt and i was
like when did that start like what
the first guy to do that must
have been so scared to it be
like it all comes down to
the second guy's accepting of it yeah
well that's what it is the first
guy yeah also been like really wanna
touch this guy's pot but i need
an excuse what if
i'm congratulating them on the game they'll
see i think that's inexorably tied into
sports i think you're making it something
similar and so bored and i think
i think we gotta move it'll she's
reaching into her purse for her phone
okay i thought oh my gosh she's
got a taser know like i know
who's eating
uh