sorry
oh right
wait about three days or three days
ah ma did you catch that i
was doing old school sort of no
you didn't care share play well not
carriageway away but like animation like i'm
i'm a big i'm making tunes i
do that voice that i did three
then the three that sounds interesting in
turp but
what i was doing was you remember
how when they were the song if
they wanted to like jazz it up
a little bit they would take something
that already existed and they were the
speed it up or slow it down
yeah give us one example like through
rogue
dance and i sped it up i
would fifth yep thrift freedom
what if we put freedom onto existing
so everybody can come to tibet
back to back
freedom
but rid of
kevin kevin's love like no kevin's a
bop and ally love kevin
just texted us i've never actually heard
a song and that was really good
is this what song is
will love to three and this is
what three dm is definitely yeah two
and a half people going nuts this
crappy way we want to call you
and a half person maybe i'm the
first i'm a woman
she would channel two points yes tom
law barrowman and why is that song
so funny grey day but remembered able
from from let's go girls let's go
to that riff which is hilarious it's
camp it is kind of canvas yeah
oh we have a man shirt shorts
girls
ah that would be very hard about
is great it's really funny cap did
you see her show her come out
with harry styles i saw clips of
that hey so um a clip but
i didn't click it oh why didn't
you look because i was just like
can't do this right on computer now
so yeah more like i'm dad and
i forgot seeing god da scene there
is
clip is almost the same as watching
it i felt like you get maybe
what happened was movie poster i'm like
i got it yeah yeah i invited
doctor strange if i see the idea
of a tour of ten years doctor
strange and you see movie poster yeah
i say i look at my boyfriend
like i guess doctor crichton sorry not
okay we hate to take over you
hey yeah no yea nah you gotta
apologize you through each down even bother
who
news one gives a flying tiny little
uglier bottle more into the microphone that
was great welcome to three of mine
i it's raining it's raining so you
say raining a roaring fire hey it's
raining oh my god this fires are
hitting yeah scott waking up on a
rainy day next cu up he's just
sitting there for a long time
she finally opened your eyes and goes
high it's raining
it's fading
ah speaking of sleeps yes lately did
you get tell me i i oh
my god i've been horribly lost for
you even get into your story and
before i hear about that whatever with
your sleep study the results yeah here's
the thing between the time i booked
a sleep study and the time the
sleep study actually happened
i lost a lot of weight and
so i was no longer having the
issues that i was having i kind
of knew as i got there at
ten pm yeah he's putting the stickers
on and you're like this is the
weirdest romero ever been yeah it was
like so did you sleep it's actually
been okay lately yeah noisy like get
out of here you nut but only
said that internally to my oh so
you send it to my mother you
think you guys will see what happen
i did the sleep study it was
fine but i really was you were
like asleep the whole time they were
like so you're just one of those
creeps who wants to come what we
watch
up mature while i watch you wear
it why were you to er ja
vu
okay wait and so you slept horribly
last night and also what about sleep
um i've been waking up in the
middle of the night lately
because my house is on fire um
i will i will be having a
dream and then i will start talking
in my sleep yeah but like i
know the secrets that you get so
weird when i'm talking to myself yeah
i know them
that's such a funny idea to chris
i've first of all i wouldn't tell
the person i'd be like oh no
the seeker i know because that's what
it would make some secret but the
fact that when you're talking in your
sleep like you hear the secrets that
you yeah the seat goes out to
gail bow when you're talking in yesterday
for three days
a bed and i go to sleep
shapes
bethe woozy many-body my tiny little paisley
i love songs like that that have
a sort of nursery rhyme cadence
so no texts from kevin that is
sung to
so too is oh ding ding dong
to meet her
that's a good song um if i
know chrome believable as a good sign
yeah yeah chrome believe bo
i love thinking of a band like
that when that gets licensed they're like
okay you know you just go whatever
yeah yeah i mean they're all like
twenty year olds mack came by yeah
okay right zulu sure i die it's
free money weasel no we
pauly shore and sina man cinemax you
can study
baby i wake up so speaking alice
zaragoza no no no i'm like saying
thing but here's the weird part is
like and and like sometimes i like
sit up like i'm i'm like it's
like i'm living the dream in real
life yeah and i'll say something but
i'm weirdly immediately conscious that i am
in my
my bedroom and ah janie is there
sleeping and so i i speak out
loud but i to it and like
a quiet voice what did you say
and then i sort of wake up
all the way oh well it'll just
be it's mundane things it's like i'm
i'm talking to somebody in the dream
and it goes in the jack and
then
that's on monday the name pickles me
to be a journey doors yeah it
was like shit like that yeah like
thank you for coming
i'll see you later like whatever
that's why you see janey after six
thank you scott c okay i just
tell you i sit there every time
i see you later
oh my god we talk about the
show last night yes last night i
met someone i had met before competitive
i knew he's gonna say yeah i
get very competitive we owe any show
called comedian uus family feud with teams
of comedians i love games and i
do very competitive and yeah that's the
fun of games personally i think
if the games are just fun oh
i do pause getting annoyed by me
i was i was not annoyed i
just never know good good i was
i kind of because you you you
displayed it early on like backstage yeah
and i was like oh okay yeah
and it was fun watching you try
to not appear competitive like you would
like
you're you are trying to control your
face just trying to pull it back
a few times because i i want
everyone to be competitive i want i
like the energy when people are all
wanting to win but then i was
like you're doing a comedy show like
we found this out with the match
game soon we were doing when you're
doing the comedy show like three quarters
of the comedians will not care at
all totally only care about if they're
getting laughs
oh totally like gameplay i felt like
everybody cared during i felt like during
were trying to meet new people don't
want to want to win but um
i have many examples in my life
of getting very competitive especially with people
i don't really know and like too
much i think it's really fun but
i go i later will wonder oh
did they think that was annoying because
i don't care
her in the moment and i just
like having fun to me that is
like the joy of the game is
like i want to beat you right
yeah that makes fun of me for
the way i play what is it
called the exploding kittens no no that's
just one but ah what's the one
where ah you know like ah there's
oh mafia yeah mafia yeah because like
i i'm super competitive to the point
where i will i'll if i'm not
mafia i will say look here's the
thing i'm never gonna lie to you
i am not mafia
and if i am mafia i promised
to say mafia and then i'll actually
do it when i'm mafia i'll go
hey guys i got my age when
we were in hawaii i go and
i nora did it for oh yeah
that was newer but i was very
compelled
our do not seem to be competitive
she was like once out of the
game my thing is i'd rather like
i don't i get so competitive i'll
just like lie to take everyone down
like in a game like that like
i'm like i know that he's in
the mafia because i saw this and
like not true at all i'll just
like
there really is nothing more satisfying then
i saw him open his eyes when
you look when you allude being named
mafia and you've been mafia the whole
time and yeah everyone always votes each
other out and yeah there's nothing more
sad is nothing like it i discovered
on that trip that i like to
be the the like the narrator
yeah the thing yeah it's really fun
yeah i got it that i think
it's really fun but also to watch
it being played is more fun to
me than play oh that makes total
sense yeah then you have the bird's
idea of who's button what like i
kind of like when i get eliminated
early and then i can watch everybody
else i have the knowledge of what
of who's yeah it's fun can we
talk about some of the the answers
on family feud because family yeah it's
like the funniest show and like it
they pull one hundred people and get
the most popular answers and the answers
are always so weird but also what's
funny is that sometimes the answer has
only been said by four people or
something yeah like well that's not really
an answer but the question will there
were a couple that i thought were
really fun one was what something you
find in your lover or your spouse's
pocket poop mom okay not on their
ah which is weird because i could
i would not like what's your next
guess if you had some number okay
like condom yeah that was i was
up there but i did guess yeah
um condom phone number which i did
guess it was anymore answer
somebody else's someone else's phone number yeah
that's up there um i guess that
was the number two yeah there you
go and that's great pocket rockets were
saying pocket rocket excuse you um but
then there were some that were like
so we're like so stephanie alamos my
team and she's so funny and she
always has she always says a different
perspective on things than anyone else
you never know what she's gonna say
so i think she's like one of
the funniest people but in the games
then it was her turn and she's
like trash gum wrappers and she was
like gum wrappers tissue nobody said you
have to get more specific she went
any kind of trash yeah that's even
less resin ah you're widening out yeah
and that didn't count that got an
x but that on the leader board
or whatever whatever it's called scoreboard there
was a category that basically what it
was like used tissue or something which
i was like why she swam to
she didn't take issue i fucked up
yeah why fucked oh i did why
would someone not want to find a
use i mean it's like i guess
it's annoying in the laundry well i
guess
rose like con like it's like used
as a condom yeah no or no
no i think i think devils pockets
that person is like
you know imagining a universe where they're
going through people's pockets to take stuff
out of there put it in the
laundry or something like yeah it's like
oh god i gotta grow like used
tissue on my right jack you know
what i mean so it's just people
interpreting the question then later my team
played against an audience team and the
question we were busy being allowed backstage
during that portion yeah which i'm sure
was
actually more fun possibly it was a
lot of fun but i i was
kind of thinking while we were back
there like i bet they can hear
us she didn't notice that janie in
the audience said we could hear ya
why don't you notice it ah i
was too busy focusing on the game
but i'm losing to the audience did
lose yeah i did
um but the question was what's something
you say to your lover that you
also say to your dog oh oh
um sits neil
open your mouth i'll see you later
thanks for coming along see you later
well the guy on the other team
was the first one to guess and
he said good girl and then that
was number one good girls good boy
and then our team sitting home and
it was on there i was like
this is sick this is sickness but
you know river butcher made an interesting
point which i had never thought about
it this way before that the poll
might
not be i'm gonna ask you a
question you just give me the answer
that comes your mind it might be
like a multiple choice thing where they
write down a bunch of things and
then say which of these do you
think is i don't know no no
it's no thanks so i think it's
because some of these things are fucking
weird but because you know why it
doesn't add up to a hundred ah
all the time is because like they
don't
accept any answer it's it's just like
either one or two people saying something
so there are you know there are
times when someone just says like one
person says something crazy and then they
don't you know put yes so that's
why i believe it's not multiple but
okay so like for the what don't
you want to find and people but
don't like the dog thing nobody's saying
good girl i think
hundred people say ah good girl good
boy because
but see you wanna treat that was
on there too said wan chee no
one's hungry slash wanted treat question
dickey others today julie's zippy if there
are enough similar ones they combine them
into one yeah so it's not the
wording yeah but i mean it's like
asking so asking your partner if they're
hungry is not the same thing as
asking a dog if they want to
treat but see but if your partner
or is being a collar and a
leash and you only need the mo
oh well also you want to treat
it sometimes you can say it like
desert like hey you want to treat
to know you know and it's not
no one has ever either i don't
think people are saying to other humans
do you want to treat them choice
i'm gonna say it every day to
go wanting to make it true yeah
my theory
just like this one treat one tree
until a grieving hungry one lady cheat
what were the other ones always the
dogs that they they step on the
little buttons to go to many things
one was i love you and you're
so cute go to bed those are
the only two that works those make
sense yeah go to go to bed
bad
you say that i mean not all
the buns to cool off code to
go to bed you're tired you're tired
and you're not having designer dollar you
go outside you i got inside p
um that's what you say no i'm
asking you right now oh yeah we
go to the bar together to go
to the park yeah that's something that
you say to both absolutely no way
the party it to i always say
these things but then i take jamie
to the vet
in the chop over balls
ah good theory it was really fun
it was really fun i could've plays
a i could a late night yeah
jackie snell who hosted and put it
together he's terrific we get lauren i
got to assemble our teams i had
a bestselling osco ah solomon georgio river
butcher and that's it because i'm the
number five
i was panicking that i forgot somebody
and i had joey greer stephanie allen
um art and marine and lorna smith
and it was very very yeah it
was a fun group so it wasn't
really his room and also you mentioned
that solomons said we should be playing
yeah um we should be doing stuff
like this like canadian
should be doing more should be the
only thing is it was very involved
like i was like there was a
lot of preparation for the game when
the match came stuff we used to
do yeah it was it was very
involved jimmy had to do the brunt
of the work jimmy pardo hosted but
also totally somebody's got to do that
but not easy to do and i
want to show up yeah jerry yeah
i think we should be doing it
all the time and somebody should be
responsible
for us yeah comedian jeopardy
interesting actually it was david really have
to dumb down the questions with me
umm yeah for you i go
let me know because you probably want
the questions to be able to be
setups for like jokes a bit more
too because i have to be funny
yeah like yeah you'd have to blow
some of your answers on joking what
are the games that would be best
suited to comedy this i thought was
good family because there was there's room
around hollywood squares of course the way
the way i want to build that
set though hollow or solid pewter so
funny with like how you're getting ready
to say your answer and the answers
are dumb so it's like that's naturally
funny and then you can riff off
of that but there's a lot of
room around the game play to to
have hollywood squares match camera both the
same where you can say a joke
answer first and then go no no
no my
real answer yeah you know to help
the person should do hollywood squares and
well we could we get in square
we could do it at my place
where everyone just like it's three stories
and everyone just yells out one window
that sounds
that actually would be really fun do
you know what we should market this
and if you want us to come
to your house if you have the
house that's appropriate for this we'll come
in three story high windows or a
garage can be one of them or
know the outside you could say i'm
a poor showing the ground outside and
then two windows above yeah yeah exam
lately they just have to be higher
than someone sitting down if he wants
to come we'll do it for free
look will travel anywhere for free we
will pay for travel on that set
where was the host and the contestants
they were like off to the side
yeah they up when they raised up
a little bit like an a mid-level
with the middle of the dough know
they were kind of level with the
bottom level
wild wild stuff what i think about
it it makes me crazy that it
would be very strange if they were
as high as the top level yeah
looking down at yeah yeah yeah yeah
um yeah let's do it let's see
yeah let's do it tomorrow
actually i recently played a hundred thousand
dollar pyramid which will be airing at
some point yes i'm so jealous because
that's the one show that i've wanted
to go on forever and they ask
you and they never ask me because
i am not in movie i like
that one could be very even as
gonna say no one could work because
yeah you just need the titles of
the
thing yeah someone could easily make that
yeah we have the board game too
that we would oh yeah the the
home game as the sky but i
used to have a screen with the
things that the audience can watch the
titles and then when you're playing the
game and they can only see one
side you know yeah and you need
somebody going huh
yeah and just that's the time ticking
down yeah you'll be the clock all
those famous clip from when louder sounds
of someone giving a clue just like
huh i was like i don't know
this reward i'm doing for every category
noises
i would like to actually do that
though very charming calorie actually hey
you won't be able to talk laugh
yeah cool
it's impressive i wouldn't my jimmy pardo
lying used to party when i used
to tape the pyramid ah and then
he would he would face tape the
pure of mind that your time is
kevin's hand
like it and he would he would
have his back to the tv and
i would have it on mute and
i would like do the clues one
at a time and ten try to
you know i just practice for the
day that we ended up on pyramid
and neither of us will because oh
and when you do it they do
a practice round with you in like
a little you know room beforehand and
it would that was so far little
so really it's at the airport right
like where they interrogate people yeah they
kept i kept saying like this is
game show right so can i put
my clothes back on
things i wanna put back on clothes
i'll wear clothes for the actual show
ah good stuff i'm guy can't wait
to see on the pier but you've
been on millionaire i want i would
love to daddy
i've been on pyramid i literally said
to my agents when my when i
got off the comedy bang big tv
show they were all okay ignite you
find that you're finally available to do
stuff ah what kind of tv shows
do you want to do i said
can you just get me on pyramid
yeah yeah it's ever been i can't
go alright i'm sorry who hosts it
oh michael strahan
yeah yeah he was great he's very
nice and i was thinking like he's
a host on like he or he
was um kelly and michael for yeah
well wow i'm like that prepares you
for anything yeah you can roll with
any i mean really all that shit
because you're talking live on tv every
morning about nothing to the most boring
people i actually love
okay i guess you know what so
sue me i enjoy that obey so
i'll see you in court
your honor you can't wait for discovery
can you oh wait
the company you keep is anybody watching
the the staircase i haven't started yet
but i'm really excited my friend number
sam original yeah honestly i'm gonna check
out that makeup yeah skip the fucking
thing and just watch the original question
originally yeah nothing is more compelling than
well no other things the original howling
well said guy no i'm glad you
told me you have
have to watch that but i do
want to watch the show because i
think one i haven't watched the original
a long time so i'm excited yeah
and a long time oh damn series
lonely lonely lonely and so good only
earth is doing a better job than
i thought he would write but i
think they put on netflix which bill
marks whatever man it's available as i'm
trying whatever man
when can i see this this came
up last night the goal of them
to make that joe vs carroll thing
when it's like so wait he fights
valentina one channel yeah spoiler here wins
against chao the thing yeah the dramatization
of it oh no one watched it
it's like why were you guys think
they greenlit it when it was like
everyone was
talking about that for that yeah can
be right or they started making it
right when it was we all watched
it and we all regretted watching it
and we agreed we would not talk
about it again the one i liked
though was ah the i'm all i
can think it was dragonball z what's
the skateboarding one palsy
what is it josh brown and z
boys dogtown and z boys that i
saw the fictionalized version of that first
and thought it was great and then
went back and watch the the documentary
and thought that was great too and
i was like they're equally good but
then people to do the reverse were
like what's the point of this that's
kind of the camp that i'm in
that now camp i am okay
the definition of camp is sim law
the the trend of them just making
a dramatized version of all these true
crime things just feels like it's not
what i don't go on to see
people dress up though isn't it i
think that's worn off for me anyway
really it's like the the novelty of
seeing people play these real life people
is like
if there's over what about six sinatra
in the offer
i'm actually enjoying this and i'm enjoying
the offer i caught up on paul
paul and i were texting because i
knew he was watching it and that
was twenty minutes in going this is
terrible right and i was like no
i like it so i kept i
haven't seen that ad but the sinatra
guy is ludicrous use it there are
so many people in this thing that
were in band of brothers that it
has to be intentional
a has to be it has to
be intentional couldn't they have gone connor
roughly let ratliff and they're let live
like yeah right lift carnal lat lyfe
hey i'm sinatra ghana here i don't
mind you making this movie about me
chum
it was a really good impression that's
of the guy on the office is
connor if he was on the show
i didn't know where it was going
wrong yeah they should have caught a
ratliff sinatra why it would have been
exactly like the guy's dead eyes to
blue
oh god we have to take a
break over here i don't care
and we're back we're back talks about
secrets by the way yeah we've talked
about recurring dreams before right yes i've
been having those again the same house
that i'm trying to flip and all
that i've been having them lately about
ah before i learned to drive i
rode my bike all over l a
yeah and i had class
epic story of you riding on the
sidewalk trash man and i'm done yes
and i had a basket a dog
right um and um story again you
almost hit someone we've already told us
to on this podcast oh yeah tell
me again i want to hear a
damn liddy guy we love it i
was riding my bike
a six mile ride my bicycle industry
to move now do do what i
thought a holiday was not old man's
feet my man
you look down for us huh oh
no those are my yeah my v
of course i ride my bike barefoot
famous forth that hurts um i was
derived to like move your car and
you don't put shoes on yeah and
it feels very weird ticket to an
errand without shoes oh that's
really i just go where are you
living just to mix up pick something
up at someone's house or something like
that and you're just driving like a
mile too far to good honestly cray
gets too far to go because i
always think about because i'm like even
if i'm just wearing sandals i'm like
what if i get arrested for whatever
reason and i have to jam the
sandal oh shoo have you ever left
the house without your ah yo
or driver's license and it feels very
dangerous i always feel like it's crazy
and i like mike's always like oh
it's not that we were done i'm
like no that's correct this is gonna
be the time when you didn't have
one for years this is the thing
because you're allowed to do this you'd
just be like oh yeah i didn't
i don't have it on me they
go oh and you didn't carry get
it next time so yeah wow i
always find we are all
white here so yeah this is a
warning
um so in your car put your
hands anywhere you like so you you
your your riding bike you saw some
guy no i saw a guy with
little feet
i was riding down the street
i was i was on franklin um
i was headed toward a street the
usb i think beautiful town and ah
as i was pedaling along on the
sidewalk somebody was coming out of a
doorway on the street with a little
dog and they like kind of ah
i was going too fast and they
were coming out right
i'm gonna get you in your league
fuckin ignoring i fucking slammed on the
brakes and like you know sleep stick
around
oh no and this the jandy stan
this yeah it's a fruit stand don't
crash into this window this area two
guys they're still mad at me um
yeah yeah i just spilled it so
this young woman with her dog she
yelled at me and said you're not
allowed to drive ah you're not allowed
to ride your bike on the sidewalk
and i fucking stopped and i said
you're not allowed to walk around with
your dog off the leash and then
she went are you full of tough
huh i love to recover yeah huh
forgot how yeah that's the last time
i'm telling you by the way i
thought that you also like what i
remember from the original telling was that
you wrote a little bit and interred
around and came back and yelled at
her was that not the case know
this i like kept going and then
she yelled that and i stopped and
then you came back to her yeah
yeah great well i didn't know yeah
nobody like to drive
new actor gets like use your feet
on the sidewalk huh
yeah i know you're in here huh
yeah
sharply get a robot that dog when
i see people walking their dog without
lease on franklin or nin stuff like
that is stressful it's so straight and
i was ah i was pulling in
here the other day just the other
day and um i started to make
to turn into the parking lot and
there was a dog off leash and
the dog start coming to the car
and i
like just put on the brakes laos
i was your dog on and um
and the owner looks at me like
i was crazy for stopping in the
middle of the street in case the
dog daniels me of the street you
know like you don't know what why
don't you do that your crazy for
stopping in the street
do do when my dog is off
leash we did it
we have to end the podcast right
now yeah it was goodbye really we're
never gonna beat it thanks for coming
guys see listen to me
yeah oh yeah really what the fuck
oh so my recurring dream now oh
my fucking is that i am because
my bike was only it was a
cruiser bike didn't have any speed so
it was really fun to to ride
around but when i had to go
back home
it was all uphill because i lived
on beachwood canyon
so you so all so this name
ira this is your highest number that
was my past and my recurring dream
is i am far from home oh
i have to not only ride my
bike home but it's all appeal and
i'm like carrying stuff oh no it's
incredibly stressful and then this is a
new one that i've been having lately
where i am
i am in i'm at a studio
like one of the studios in town
and i can't get out like every
turn i take is not the exit
of the studio last night i'd want
to had it was so fucking stressful
where there were multiple things stopping me
along the way like so many like
to fill up some kind of
forum or something like you couldn't remember
the numbers right yeah it was it
was it was maddening it was mad
i've only i've now had to ah
stress dreams about the tour
yeah necessary just one is constant one
was yes and one one was ah
oh i haven't booked anyone for tonight
show no guess and then the other
one was oh no i haven't recorded
enough podcast before i leave
that's stressful stuff stressful stuff ben relatable
isn't a relatable to all of you
people out there to have strength like
repetitive stress worse i do i i
also often have the actor's nightmare yes
yeah yeah i had a crazy one
where it was like basically hamilton and
i was in it and i was
like so panicked and what's weird about
the wind i have that
that these days is like before it
was like oh shit i haven't gotten
the script yet okay we'll keep the
script off stage all yeah go take
peaks in in-between you and now it's
just like i have that dream sometimes
it's like the script isn't here and
i go yeah it'll be fine like
well like all just bravo around yeah
that would be really good and show
but you feel that way but i
feel that way in the dream of
like i don't need to worry stress
about it that means something positive i'm
sure yeah i've been having dreams were
they're just so vivid that i want
to go back into them and like
say i was zoning out and mike
was like are you depressed and i
was like no i'm actually thinking my
dream and wishing that i was inside
it which maybe is depressing but it
sounds good
down the road i just liked my
grey hates this reality are you depressed
yeah i saw you looking off into
space you depressed one of those things
your dog and your partner and are
you doing oh my dream i had
this like elaborate sort of basement den
in my house and
like you garbage and like had cool
stairs shards yeah they need it and
i was just like just i liked
i liked being in it and then
i was pictured myself being i had
a dream like that where it was
a stage um that had all this
ah like it had like trees and
greenery growing out of it and it
looks so cool and i woke up
and i was like i wanted to
be real so bad yeah yeah yeah
i hate when it's just not real
that you picture in your mind i
don't like when i make a thing
up and it's not real i agree
yeah but i don't feel that way
and what i noticed this morning trying
to get back to sleep is that
i i can't if if i pretend
to be someone else i think because
they've i pretend to be asleep cool
off since no if i were to
if like if i'll sit there thinking
about things that i'm doing or like
things that i'm supposed to do or
whatever i can never go back to
sleep because it stresses me out my
heart starts to race but if i
like think of a movie that i
saw the
night before something and pretend i'm the
person and just even do the scenes
that were in the movie i will
suddenly like start to dream and those
scenes will blend into dreams and stuff
like that so it's like a way
to calm the homeless like myself dreaming
it sounds like you turn the light
on and see if it's real in
your dreamy no i'm definitely not lucid
and it's just a way to get
me back to sleep
i'm not thinking about myself as does
heartbreak feel good in a place like
that it does yes somehow so if
i were to pretend to be her
and and go like ok i'm about
to film oh you don't know retirement
are you the person she broke up
with y ou nicole kidman what about
her you she's been talking about it
heartbreak feeling good in theaters yeah
got it i'm caught up but if
i were to be like god i
can't so i gotta stop thinking about
my own troubles i'll go like oh
okay i don't know but it's been
ah something i've been kicking for the
yeah fuckin half hour earning a footrest
is it a footrest looks like a
footrest why would someone want that i'm
curious oh my god is this
a squatty potties
anything is quite a buddy yeah but
your feet up a bunch of books
i have a squatty potty and let
me just tell ya it's good hey
can i tell you something speaking of
a bunch of books
yeah the bible
i did it i found you guys
the law the book of i can't
read it just to key or they
don't have the same cover its know
i bought two of those books you
must give them back and tell they
were like textbooks one seems to be
flatter district these to my other podcasts
as well this is like this data
so i used to have this and
was his name trying to start like
the one there was an app that
lena dunham and the guy from genova
yeah tried to start where it was
list it's called liz yes like anyone
to just do because it's just like
it was like homework like a whole
yeah like
okay someone sober and memorable articles ever
insured this is literally why they made
that up i bet you a million
dollars now of course this is what
it's now of course i've inscribed these
books to you both and also you
have
okay i'll chew three to nine oh
no i didn't mean lauren please read
every word of this book and think
of me with every single word love
p f t here's my dear scott
how are you
taking
associate editor fern brian fatness assistant sadness
assistant editors wait listen look at how
elizabeth is spelled listen to this is
really crazy a little of this e
l i z so far so good
yeah e b e t h e
wadi lizzie be why there's so many
okay now
bear in mind this is nineteen seventy
seven what what do you think the
most v most memorable memorable that's not
really what do you think is the
most expensive thing ever insured is this
family feud is it betty grable legs
there are legs on this list but
that's number four say thanks fred de
sam o the hands
nz of laura mars famous surgeon the
ass of j lo this isn't nineteen
seventy so they not she was just
born and they just that's gross assassin
bronze hey yeah the san francisco oakland
bay bridge for forty million dollar so
i'm like okay gene kelly's eleven greatest
dancers of the past why me no
yeah i picked these yeah dancer yes
i forgot that some of these were
like buying celebrities or whatever yeah alright
who are now that's cool do this
gene kelly picked these dancers of the
most famous dancers in film history gene
kelly came off the broadway stage at
thirty to star in such
physical hits has anchors away the pirates
singing in the rain and american in
paris and brigadoon he also directed numerous
films among them yo and hello dolly
he received i don't know ga je
li g i g o t
guizhou he received a special guy guard
for his innovative contributions to the dance
in movies one salaam to master juba
three is a dora duncan
for nijinsky
alright here's here's here's a better list
twelve most commonly used words in written
english the number one with a bullet
oh yeah double it
number three is
number seven r
not on the list what
is one unless one what what who
oh what's number two number two is
oh
wow and the number for feeling this
vague in the books i'm boring number
four is a little word known as
ah the seven greatest numbers from one
to seven number one thirty four
eighteen drinks named after people or peoples
ah the shirley temple of course and
the dirty shirley is the drink of
the summer from what surely time ran
there and i did read shirley temple
stuff on there too tom collin was
fuck calls for number eight harvey wall
banger ah sir real harvey well-being so
we got the aleks
zander we got the bennett in your
team we got the bloody mary we
got urban bronx cocktail dom perignon gibson
gimlet gin rickey grog harvey wall banger
sorry to tell you i was wow
kickapoo jim kickapoo joy juice whoa that's
a fun name manhattan cocktail martini miki
finn rob roy scotch and tom collins
to hum cuts
tom causes really low yeah sorry drink
that everyone drinks now okay here's ten
tough challenge oyster know that then other
than peter piper picked a peck of
pickled peppers whoa number one the toughest
i guess or just a ten tough
the sixth sick wait the six okay
six sheep focus sixth sheep's sick start
over the sixth start over you can't
even reach it slow the sixth sick
sheik's sixth sheep start over why i
didn't understand
i do one i ain't crazy me
right yeah this is my book but
i want but yes more fun stuff
okay
while we all know that so much
rubber baby buggy bumper
robert huth
robert downey junior bobby jedi junior rubber
baby buggy bumpers robert downey junior baby
she se yeah
tony junior babies this great where you
only see his legs thinking steamer sunk
the thinking steamer sunk the stinking scene
visit the stinking rhythm gleeson toy boat
for troy beja mezzo i knew it
he is music isn't if a three
month truth is the truth the truth
is this is it if it chooses
a truce
truth is the truth tuesday two three
month jews getting a moses supposes zeroes
what page you want and that's let's
see if the pages match up one
hundred and sixty one
if you know if you stick a
stock of liquor in your locker is
it slick to stick a lock upon
your stock or some joker who is
slickers going to trick you of your
liquor if you fail to lock your
liquor with a lock someone's easy wow
that one's pretty easy i love that
one i'm gonna say it before everything
i ever do
oh shocking well i guess this was
nineteen seventy four but
and black people that are ok
ten countries twenty eight
la ten kinds one has the highest
percent of men and women lived to
be eighty five years old oh i
hope it's my country doing this of
the u s oh sweet land of
liberty and numbers are crazy low and
it's like four years for men they're
really low and for women they're much
higher so like it says for men
the top city top country is puerto
rico
twenty one point six percent amendment be
eighty five but on the women's list
it's only thirty percent but like only
teen percents in these men's categories tell
us tell us where we go iceland
albania sweden norway netherlands denmark canada israel
greece for women it's puerto rico canada
sweden netherlands norway france u s well
done mr lowe and only eighty
five this is nineteen seventy four it's
like things have changed so much i
would say the percentage has people now
are higher yeah you right
lower whenever you want listen this one
peter cornell's ten favorite dinner guests from
all history who's peter cornell okay well
he'd probably tell us yeah i'm an
english biographer critic and poet peter cornell
was educated at bylaw college bilal oxford
he edited cornhill magazine and presently
the hill magazine presently joint editor of
history today his books are read worldwide
among them byron the years of fame
blah blah blah um so i guess
this is like ten people he just
would want to invite to dinner by
the way this is an exclusive mark
blah blah blah blah blah for the
book of lists was he the guy
that invented this ca
concept of of people who history but
listen to who's number one is john
wilkes
not the guy you're thinking of okay
it's just a different guy wait king
henry the eighth second wife anne boleyn
had three breasts and wore long sleeves
dyed her six fingers which i had
two dicks for those three breasts
i see why did see why did
why the fuck didn't i say bugs
you said what the six on broadway
that's like about henry the eighth vocal
six wives whoa and they're like the
the premises that they're all pop stars
and they're like competing to be like
the number one pop star whatever they
sing their story about their like their
their peril with him or whatever it
was really fun but anne boleyn and
never was in that well i saw
ghost lady mentioned or three tits or
six fingers i don't think so i
should have yeah i saw ghost which
features the song i'm henry the eighth
i am yeah and he's saying it
six times interesting i think that's a
sign sign sign everywhere a sign yes
so this isn't movie site
signs and how stupid it was but
it was a big sign yeah yeah
right i mean the whole water thing
is so dumb it's also he just
ripped off a prayer for owen meany
yeah i will never stop saying and
then he also his previous movie was
all about a guy who is whose
water was the weakness so it's like
this guy had a break because the
weak ne anytime bruce willis fell
all in a pool he was like
ah and although i don't remember anything
yeah so it's like what the ending
what the fuck does this guy have
against water i hey if you're listening
out there m night tell us what
why you hate water we'd like to
know it's just a couple of how
about low heels of a high takes
place on a beach this dude i
haven't seen that one i'm
seeing it's it's kind of worth seeing
if you're on next i'm going to
play look for it i thought we
might do it first scott doesn't seem
we've talked about i'm so sorry for
i know really sucks i've got to
watch these a terrible movie tonight boy
which one can you say i can't
say because it's down the line a
bit i'm sure put in the chat
i'll put it into chat you can
you can you can
sixty ka bo bo bo yeah
whoa
bum bum bum bum bum bum nine
upstairs my name's bueller i'm the guy
and i don't go to school or
i go out and do what i
want i ride in a car that's
not my dad's i will boo anything
with my girlfriend her name sloan and
guess my girlfriend mr eddie i'm the
king of the hotdog king of chicago
time to go to school tomorrow i'm
sick again my name's katherine i'm depressed
maybe i guess i gotta get dress
i'll wear my hockey jersey as we
go to the museum but i like
to see some paintings and that's the
place you see him but i think
ferris is a very good guy but
i sometimes doubt
does he have i in my four
good things i don't know the core
is go away through the window my
dad my dad he's got a beam
probably killed myself if you saw the
sequel the sequel to ferris bueller's day
off and the future huh succession boom
i think that your rapping was better
than mine
if that's also great you're better than
mine no but i felt really confident
today in a way that i never
do yeah remember the rep the rep
you did for the first audition i
loved that guy like i was talking
about you're running a trump and you
couldn't get one line out without laughing
that's like saying right
zach was like i love it yeah
i wish i'd gotten an audition i
would've laughed all the way through it
alright we have singer barry goldberg
hey we're back and guys are good
friend k p kitchen patrol himself okay
this guy's been on thin ice yeah
this guy's been on our ass for
the past he's been on our ass
and our shit list and thin ice
all three it's like wow
when you go to four corners and
you try to get one hand and
one foot in each of the states
one foot
anyway it's over three cheer it is
the three choices segment where we do
at the end and this is k
p ok so k p look if
you if this is your first episode
welcome we love you we love all
three-time listeners obviously do oh yes but
if you're
if you're new to the show k
p if you're a new love you
already here hey happy birthday
what he's doing you made a great
choice start listening to this episode they
never heard one yeah this on every
episode someone's first and last oh they
don't know it's their last until they
realised they haven't listened to the launch
yeah exactly oh i thought you were
gonna say they don't know what's their
last because they're going to die and
that's the only way that someone could
stop listening to this week aspiration
do a remake of the ring or
whatever it was where it's the videotape
that makes people but it's a podcast
ring make that's a really good yeah
and it's like three white guys talking
can i ask why did the videotaping
even have to have anything on it
i don't know i mean if the
act of watching it was what cursed
you want to just have a still
friend that said you're cursed
yeah or like a guy sitting down
in front of the camera go hey
if you're watching this what were the
images it was like it's like a
little girl in a well or something
zoom away it wasn't who watches you
choose to work the shipping news
was it wasn't it clues as to
what they had to solve in order
to to get out of the precarious
situation they were i don't remember i
just remember she crawled out of the
tv and it was scary because i'm
not supposed be able to do well
yeah there wasn't well like that you
don't like crawling out of the tv
it scares mall why don't you crawl
out of the tv and see how
just fun it is
okay i'll try right now are all
in new york tv and died
bow bow bow bow anyway so k
p has just look if this is
your first episode it's so hard to
explain kpi yeah there's so much lore
she's to go you go but you
gotta start from the beginning yeah super
ep even though he didn't want episode
one we didn't talk about him until
two episodes ago but it sets it
up i feel like like yeah it
all leads up to k p
is and why he is yeah but
if you don't care that's also fine
that's totally fine but we'll catch you
up right now kpi's some dude hey
guess what if you shut this off
right now nevertheless again i don't give
a fuck hey it doesn't effect it'll
hurt your wow you just tell us
pulse lying i'm so k p sent
us this ah lai k p sent
us something for three ch or file
well um ah so a submission of
which is like the x-files but not
scary yeah although it's like one of
the funny episodes of the x-files yeah
exactly like one that ah who wrote
those charles nelson reilly yeah the nelson
riley one yeah jose chung's from outer
space yeah exactly so he sent a
three-tier to us and we thought we
were
reading capiz but we were reading someone
else's and that's so we we fucked
over k p hard hard and it
was funny it was fun soul usually
alan hardy guy i feel like i
got hung out to dry actually why
like you we throw you under the
bus on that one like not do
this and then i was like saying
we're not doing it i guess we
are guys we very sure i was
like okay i guess for you still
mad about this i'm just bringing it
up to explain pitcher is day the
problem is that the three of us
never speak off mike and so this
is where we have to sort this
stuff out yeah yeah yeah so anyway
so then the following week we were
like okay we're gonna do capiz and
then we read it and we're like
no we're not gonna do that because
it's bad no but k p
will not be deterred because we told
k p on that episode we said
kpi this one needs a little tweak
needs a little punch up so k
p to kpi's credit be too there's
two of them mp jo no yellow
two k b squared yeah to his
credit k p ah does he give
his actual name or maybe hippie
is katie thomas um anyway so he'd
be punched it up i haven't read
this i just saw he punched it
up and we're gonna decide live in
the moment whether we're gonna do it
or an absolutely nuts here okay this
is junk it there's a timer set
for three minutes and eternity when it
comes to stuff like this truly yeah
truly so what
so long so but we'll see one
player is an aloof hollywood bad boy
slash bad girl doing a press junket
for their new movie than one players
they're stressed out publicist and the third
is an entertainment reporter but ah the
ctr has a silly rumor going around
about them example a roma tried to
grow weed in the jungle at rainforest
cafe that would be silly you're right
people know the ceiling yeah that's decided
on ahead of time by the reporter
and is only known by the publicist
and the reporter so the actor has
no idea what this rumours the reporter
is slyly trying to get the scoop
from the actor but the publicist is
trying to stop them and keep the
interview about the movie the person playing
the actor improvises the title character and
all the other details of the movie
if the interviewer can slyly get the
actor to say the rumor within the
three minutes they win the big prize
which we got decide on the big
prize i'll give this book away
i'm kidding i'm kidding paw
i think that i admit it i
think oh my god he admitted i
think this is a good improvement but
he didn't say what the big prizes
and so i'm saying right now i
don't want to do it what if
the big prizes we get to meet
k p no
maybe i never want to meet you
and if you ever try to meet
me it's gonna be bad you ever
try to meet me on stage chris
rock style or dave chappelle sta ah
what have i whatever the dave chappelle
somebody germany russia must ai tim at
the hollywood bowl with the hollywood bowl
listen with a gun with a knife
on it a gun rep oh no
oh no i've gone yeah now i've
gone yeah yeah it's darts but they
didn't get hurt did he owe the
person who restaurant stage got hurt for
sure no doubt i didn't see the
clip nor have i know you saw
there was a clip though right i
did yeah so we wanna just go
to seeing the clip do we want
to do this or do we not
want to do this i think we
may i
i think we have to legally legally
we have to we have to do
it this week nope let's just do
it and who's going to be the
actor who's gonna be the really like
the thing to do is to kick
this down the road kick the can
down the road for k p yeah
it sucks because you talked a long
time telling us how dr long time
doctor longtime what what i think is
great
it is this becomes it's own segment
before the three whether we decide to
do cpz they are not exact right
we don't have to do a piece
thing alright okay maybe next week what
do i do and said i don't
know
i was given ah i was sent
to us here a physical game wow
my god this was sent to us
by someone named zan toward the magician
and this is a game called conversation
the game it's a little pack of
cards and here's how it works
is the freedom boys and closes the
game on me with my friends called
conversation the game the rules are as
follows every card has a conversational rule
that must be followed pick a card
set a timer for two minutes again
incredibly long amount of time and either
a hide it from other players so
you follow the rule and they get
your card example lauren has only asked
questions she's only allowed
to speak to the players in the
form of question when the timer goes
off scott and paul try to guess
the rule okay okay i like it
tip if a card looks like it
won't be fun skip it i like
to sew right like this tip put
it at the bottom of the deck
for later here's another way to play
put it on your forehead headbands style
so it's in from yourself but other
player
urs follow you like these get your
own clan style it's h e a
d b a n d z and
then with a little trademark symbol okay
i like this less um example paul
has flirt scott laura must flirt with
him when the timer goes off he
guesses his own rule that sounds better
than the other one i have yeah
yeah okay i liked it better and
we don't have to we don't have
to do it in ahead head
banned because we don't own any headbands
for added fun players can look through
the deck and assign each other cards
okay let's try this let's try the
second one and we'll just put it
up to our heads longtime listener first
time writer love the show centaur the
magician santa or the magician canal crumpled
this up and throw it away are
you sure okay yeah alright by the
way we got this long
time ago speaking of go listeners and
then the pandemic happens so we couldn't
play games in person even when we
were in the backyard we could yeah
true yeah okay so where oh no
now you gotta unwrap oh no they're
already right only that i previously unwrapped
previously on threesome i took the liberty
of comparing one of these earlier like
we've never met paul
lra alright so now are you still
just put one up to your head
my head and then you do the
thing yeah yeah eating me into guessing
what it is yeah i think so
yes i do do you wanna do
it to your head first no okay
then lauren will get your risotto know
i respect you you know what it's
not a good one
skip it it was the first one
and i got excited are we ready
yeah who's timing i should we do
it for two minutes do we do
it for one minute ah let's do
it for two and see how we
feel okay um and don't hit lap
i will not hit hello hey
elena take cool off duh hey alright
yeah alright you got that dude who
donated to do we take turns right
yeah we picked her okay great and
go
hey
how are you doing i'm good
um
ah
where do you go today
i don't know i have amnesia
when did you get that hat
am i a suspect for a murder
no
just make it a conversation
so
why are you here today i mean
we don't usually see you um i
guess i just thought today was the
day in my schedule
um
where were you last night
am i being interrogated
my late
okay
i i have to ask
what's your mother's maiden name
um
bingo
also plausibly
what are the last four digits of
your social who's seven to one
ah okay
what's your childhood pet's name i forgot
my password
right you can fly
i'm saying a premier airlines credit card
ah no what was it take a
look at the guard sigh heavily once
per turn okay yeah that's really gives
good info as to what it can
be what it can be yeah yeah
yeah okay okay give me that deck
did two minutes feel like too long
or was out know that guys already
everyone is good i wouldn't never have
gotten
that i didn't really get yeah could
be i was gonna go over the
top with sighing um
this last time but i didn't get
to it just really try to bring
home i'm not supposed to because i
was showing you i didn't see paul
was doing oh paul's doing oh i
do now oh god okay now i
do
so paul um
i guess what i want to know
is are you happy with your situation
yeah i think so i think so
it doesn't feel like that to me
you think i'm unhappy i do
i mean could you be happier yeah
sure
i sometimes i think about you i
think about what what could be right
worry that you're not happy
i mean yeah i think you could
be happier definitely but i think you
could be happier yes i do do
i not think you can be up
here i don't know i don't think
he could be happier i owe you
don't think that no i don't i
hate to see
but paul what i really wanted you
to know when i came out to
participate yeah like you don't do what
i really want you show me guess
sweetie pie to guess what's going on
because i brought you here for a
certain rate i i feel like i
know what it is okay say don't
make eye contact no
so paul something else it's definitely something
else and we need you to know
what is shaky read every time yeah
is which doesn't translate on guys
ah let's find one that would work
on the pod move your head while
you talk it says but we were
we were really going for it it
was good it was good okay can
you read it oh my how did
you know i could you squinted that's
how i read okay
okay isn't it weird how it works
and just hold it here know we
know honestly i never thought about this
before but it did help when i
squinted to read that oh good yeah
so weird i can see better alright
me i'm young yet
yeah oh yeah she did it i
do once in a while it's always
unexpected is always voted what dive oh
my god this happened over christmas i
was ah we were at her mom's
house and i was in the other
room and i had to blow my
nose and i'm now
for a blockchain it was very loudly
and i ha and i heard janie
other room sang to her mom did
you hear that and from the other
room i went yay yay here
wow alright so her mom's really learning
what an asshole you are oh she
knew
humam me oh that's just a conflict
with her exactly i don't give a
fuck i'd walk around nude in front
of her
you'd think over family member but this
is yeah let's do it it's alright
here we go hey you started the
timer i have to do that
so what did you do before you
fell asleep blessing
i was played a little mario kart
oh okay
what's the worst thing you've ever done
to another human being
i meant to ask you
um told a white lie too that's
crazy i forgot to ask something to
it's been i was just wondering like
what you jerk off to
i meant to ask you that i
last lost i saw you i forgot
huh yeah certain plotlines of downton abbey
certain ones probably not the newspaper when
it was boring
um
lifetime what have you put in your
rectum
um usually just whatever comes out of
it you put your doctor innovation yeah
you feel like it fell out it's
you're like oh this is where this
belong yeah what was like something that
wouldn't take a time you just really
embarrassed years i mean just tell us
about a really embarrassing thing that happened
to you that we couldn't stop thinking
about um well one time i was
walking down to a little stoop of
three stairs and i
um tripped on the middle stair and
i fell on my little butt
ah oh right um what does cool
look like naked um like have you
ever seen like those renaissance pictures of
beautiful women naked so what do you
guys do when she's naked
so is this just asking me embarrassing
questions okay intrusive injuries injuries yeah okay
also was like you all you both
were looking up enough to this ah
to the right before you and then
in the middle would look me in
the eye so that's like a minute
and for a minute i thought it
was up because we were we were
formulating the questions because we were flying
were lying tech technically lying which is
create
tion yeah good stuff and let's hear
that alarm right now
almost at the post
well that was great that was fun
thank you xl tar santos estore so
so now i mean you got on
crump oh i don't believe about
damn damn damn damn down to do
duty ma'am and no ma'am thank you
relieve a booth huh
oh ah hickory hickory dock thank you
against a zant tour zander the magician
where you're from i wonder the planet
irks cabal okay
um thank you for listening and we're
gonna go back into our little holes
yes and then six more weeks of
winter we finally have a phone number
and the phone number is haha input
haha law in us ha ha l
a input yeah four two four two
five two four six
seventeen again that number is four two
four two five two four six seven
eight better known as haha la input
la la neighborhood and why are we
calling why do we have a phone
number we forgot the reason we want
phone number please don't call about somebody
the last thing we want you to
call that number haha input yeah hi
ma input and um look you know
follow us at three dm usa on
all your social media and and write
to us at three am usa gmail
dot com
i could leave three years on the
on then i think phone number i
don't know why should we even want
it why did i want to remember
i don't know but um hey if
you want to listen to the archives
and to ad-free episodes head on over
to stitcher premium or cb world dot
com and for lauren and for paul
f tompkins good night
hi everybody
yeah good nye and sienna i'm on
good night viet nam
a