oh but
i yelled three to a mountain howard
gonna do it again
yeah i've done it twice and i
think i owe one more in me
ah molly zowie so to do you
were
i'm still trying to figure out exactly
what they said do you remember why
just tried to do the theme song
live that one live show that we
did yeah what applewood did not work
why what happened i don't use scarce
got away from doing another live show
is always begging him to do yes
i think we maybe we did not
properly explain what needed to happen oh
or maybe
yeah they started it without telling telling
us and it just started when three
am and then we oh yeah three
two yeah interesting he just don't remember
some stuff and you just keep going
but isn't it interesting how you do
remember some stuff yeah keep going yes
yes yes yes what did i think
of the other day i was like
why do i still remember that it
sounds like he forgot oh yeah
i think yeah we shade table alive
show i think so too please thanks
so too maybe when we did look
yes dynasty typewriter look we we could
do a tour as well but it's
a tall order with this bbc tall
order and by the way that's why
the tour was so jam packed for
the comedy baseball tour
are full of fun but it was
why we did so many shows and
so because he was like a last-minute
thing of like oh okay the baby's
going okay let's do his chores we
went on tour i think we could
do like one weekend here okay few
weeks when we come a few weeks
no momentum maybe we can also quite
simply do a live show and stream
it and you know have fun and
make some money and honestly that sounds
why do you
say no i know what's your fucking
deal he's like i'm trying hard to
get really bad they trying to get
you for a long time well it's
very hard i'm going to set the
date
save the date what is it it's
going to be december thirty first to
be yankee light to all three nb
in the new year and it's gonna
be closer than you think speaking of
holiday i'm pressured to shop as as
we all are by consumerism speaking of
holidays where are we getting all the
banks giving yeah i mentioned new year's
eve oh you're smearing i'm holiday
it's thanksgiving today special thanksgiving episode of
three's oh yeah yeah there to gather
to say more phrases wow that's a
deep cut yeah thanks ma'am umm
what are you doing for this thanksgiving
oh and doing today i simply don't
celebrate thanksgiving really as a protest against
well i do feel now that i
agree with you that it's mostly been
that over the years it hasn't meant
that much to me and i've kind
of just let it yeah i mean
has there ever been a person alive
even nowadays who like celebrates thanks
gave me like oh thank god that
like this country exist oh there's some
peoples and then that it's all about
family yeah i stopped going home for
that holiday and so then mike and
i kind of we like to travel
this would happen this year but we
went to we were in japan and
things we were in germany in germany
and i've been in london on thanksgiving
i
like to just be other places yeah
but not this year but not this
year we're gonna just be with holly
to holly's second thanksgiving i don't recall
what happened last year um but i'll
probably try to cook a little dress
her up like a turkey he's not
like you know i like the parade
it's it's hard to dress your baby
like don't dodge the question did you
dress up like a turkey it's hard
i like the parade it's hard to
do this lawrence was here you know
it i like to pray you accidentally
put holly in the oven thinking it
was the taree yeah yeah you wanna
acid and she was so juicy yeah
um no i just don't really care
so thanks you it's just not some
end because your family other than celebrate
and they get together you always know
what i mean you ever seen los
angeles yeah
you're with mike and holly all the
time and then we had to pandemics
things young very anti-climatic it's like i
met kim chi mak
and i um i should probably well
it's gonna be low key i'm like
maybe well maybe we'll hang out and
watch loki don't watch loki it's fun
i lost looks real mike hates parades
and i like grey macy's parade is
what yeah the the i hate brains
but i do watch i'd love to
i love to get up and watch
the what's gonna deal what's the deal
with chris the hollywood christmas parade okay
just toy
toys for tots like a weirdo right-wing
christian organization i don't know but wait
because they're on every single person in
every single person who's on that parade
is like erik estrada dean cain like
all these like weirdos right what are
you doing for thanksgiving it's emeralds first
her first and i don't know if
she's gonna understand it but we're gonna
draw
we'll probably get it i think she'll
understand and she'll understand the pros and
cons pros
he she may sit this one out
yeah um maybe given what i know
she's like i just am not ready
to make a decision about us her
grandparents will be there that's very nice
and special um that is three of
this home will be there wow that's
right okay three full grandparents hearing you
yeah yeah in the same room so
that's interesting so that's interesting oh this
has never happened yeah dad is like
wanting to tell me they've always missed
they've always missed each other yeah the
point where you thought one of them
was pretending to be it was a
downrigger situation yeah it was a doubtfire
situation that much time together that would
be so weird if your if your
dad
i'd just like your mom i would
use like mrs doubtfire things like like
your marella you thought you had to
parry i feel it's cool op's mom
does a yup okay one of them
i just think it's nice that your
dad was dressing up as your mom
yeah you thought you had two parents
but it always ever since you were
a kid who'd been your dad and
then your dad leaves the room and
dress
this up like a mom and comes
back in just because it's like a
two parent household is more stable i
mean you could you could get away
with it for a while when they're
when they're babies with just a wig
you sure what you want to be
that elaborate me some blush and while
i'm saying you don't like there's so
little you don't have to be that
elaborate with it but if you want
your voice you need to say how
would you want yeah i get old
order of gorgeous hollywood is playing with
my blush brush today and he let
her have it but then she was
dragging it all over the bathroom floor
and the kitchen oh goodbye to the
post yeah it was just like this
is this is yours now yeah yeah
what do you let you can't let
her play with everything right but she
gets fixated on something is it like
it was sort of like it's kind
of i was getting ready so i
was kinda like yeah here just take
this it's kind of soft and you're
painting everything with it and then like
just getting all sorts of new bacteria
because i certainly don't wash it enough
to begin with or you know to
play with mixed gun um
i mean yeah you know superbowl he
talks about that gun all just be
very clear he doesn't have a gun
we do he says i keep it
in the drunk drawer and what it's
to look there
the drunk don't the judge dog jars
the group i said with god yeah
um like judah rock drunk junk dry
no but i mean i like the
idea though like this is stuff like
throw in there when i'm drunk i've
been using it i just throw it
in and i look at the end
of the year are you surprised by
how many people you know that do
have a gun
ah you know what i don't at
this point i don't know how many
people that is i don't know exactly
because i know definitely there's a few
people that i i definitely know i'm
trying remember the last most surprised where
somebody told me i was like really
yeah yeah i think people should be
allowed one and they should not be
assault weapons so yeah obviously
look we can all agree guns they're
great and what a great invention and
certainly we need them i mean we
all agree that go pew pew could
not agree more
i actually disagree you say that they
don't know you
yeah good job were you happy when
you are able to imitate a gun
of course i was yeah how did
you see that elated i do that
it's really you're like yeah you're you're
clenching your deals together and then forcing
air out of your larynx but then
something's going on with your tongue bill
nye or yeah he's literally the science
guy i'm like um i remember once
in an interview with gds rasulo really
the science guy jimmy gruffalo they asked
her like some dumb question
and like what's the what's the biggest
difference between you know male comedy and
female comedy or something and she said
i don't really know that there's that
much of a difference i guess men
are better at making gun sounds interesting
what's true is it true that's honestly
my big takeaway from comedy bang bang
women are
as funny as men but men make
better gun sounds yeah interesting sometimes just
a simple absolutely wow was just a
simple um what
zubin yeah i already ran over to
go where else close close knit with
janie here's well where i used to
go home for thanksgiving as well and
then stopped that after a while because
i was also going on for christmas
traveling at that time that's oh we've
talked about ah thanksgivings too close to
christmas way some hey
a i forget which episode it is
we reorder the holidays it was i
think really great actually what i yeah
i'm thinking about this some kind of
a fresh way i don't think this
is how i thought about this the
same thing we have at this time
halloween is at the end of october
november has thanksgiving three weeks until then
you have christmas actually
my thinking is we need one at
the end of every month that's good
and different where you want you want
a good one like halloween thanksgiving christmas
every month yeah here's what i'm thinking
i really would like that the other
day because halloween thanksgiving and halloween and
christmas the two main ones where you
celebrate it all month long
i'm like you start at the beginning
of the month you put out decorations
yeah yeah yeah thanksgiving giving you bought
some knowing okay whatever oh leave some
leaves from your where's your whore know
plenty but like st patrick's day it's
well middle of the month the one
thing i would say is virus july
fourth you get flags american flags for
quieted
a month before yeah maybe a month
before but then there yeah but it's
like i don't listen i think that
one should count as a good one
because it's got you got fireworks if
you do it right you like it
because your birthdays buy it yeah but
actually i would say i always loved
fourth of july fireworks but let's put
it at the end of the month
though in your plan because then you
have to look forward
two yeah july thirty first independence day
is as the end of the month
so those are the four good ones
i think okay but what what would
be a good holiday like what do
you like about these holidays like it's
going to be different because halloween you
can't just replicate halloween of like halloween
to season of the witch it's gotta
be like you can't just read you
can't just go
dread i watched there and only three
but go walking me and it was
really good which one the first one
the the original yeah yeah i had
seen it before but i also forgot
everything about it and i thought it
was fun but what what was scary
what do you what would you like
to have a holiday have i would
like okay well you know what you're
like hello existing havas great question you
phrase
xd it i just was in canada
and they have a new holiday that
the government decided called family day oh
yeah they were like yeah yeah go
a long time without a holiday so
the government said we needed a one
here and that was family day i
mean what how sweet could something possibly
be what do you do what are
you supposed to do shoot i assume
you hang out with your family okay
or they're trapping say although we're talking
about like shooting ways today with family
there's always a trap or two oh
yeah johnny john educationally what john m
d says february twentieth and let's see
february twenty okay so this is good
although valid down times day
should that count and make it february
twenty eight i actually think it's too
close to valentine's data actually ok so
manziel stupid i know we've already gone
over this i love the holiday but
alcohol is okay on family day many
people plan and take part in activities
aimed at the whole family these include
visiting art exhibitions watching movies sneering outdoor
ice rinks playing board games taking part
in craft active
cities
okay activities there's gotta be some way
to decorate it you know what i
mean gotta be and also not all
of canada celebrates nearly two thirds of
canadians reside in a province that observes
a statutory holiday canada get your shit
together we assessed your holiday the wood
on the third monday of february
tuesday february twenty eighth it's it's always
a day it's always a monday that's
because you can have a three day
weekend yeah that's nice i like that
i think it's really thoughtful although you
say you don't get the day off
like valentine saying it's hard to make
love
with your whole family oh wow
they got all in the same room
no really nasty dot all the same
time everyone is a different room valentine's
day has the hearts st patrick's day
as the shamrocks
ah thanksgiving the turkey and the and
all the vegetables so what are you
gonna do what do you do on
family day like you have the i
think things like you make like a
little stick figure like things turns and
say you love each other tell me
about your thanksgiving too is it's excuse
tell me two things giving us just
a little curious this shit we
we we have usually been at home
for thanksgiving um sometimes we'll be with
friends sometimes while friends move at our
place um we spent one thanksgiving alone
and it was kind of great yeah
that's the thing once we discovered how
fun it was yes not make any
sort of pressure on the situation we
really yeah oh this is awesome
it was no pressure we have faith
stealing food now and that's what it
was just the two of you just
you i made a full turnkey just
for you yeah we made the same
amount that you usually would have for
thanksgiving dinner free audio cable yeah um
but this year finds us in philadelphia
oh because out of philly home of
the phillies the eagles the flyers the
u
union um um and to what end
are you there i'll tell you oh
i just i just did some shows
in umm ah brooklyn the bell house
to some varieties and i thought it's
the weekend but i'm just looking what
are you doing my face was my
turtleneck
legs looked weird you had your turtleneck
robbie williams channel journos i had a
dana carvey stout turtle turtle um and
ah so i decided well why don't
i haven't been feeling a while so
why don't we take the train down
will stay in philly for a week
after the show we can do get
a hotel or an air bnb when
you get a ho
hotel um it's tough because my family
is all in the suburbs right but
there's not a lot of hotel options
out there or you're going to be
spending thanksgiving though with family members well
the thing i don't know you haven't
alerted them i will be oh i
have oh i have and my sister
ruth who traditionally has hosted
thanksgiving has said oh i won't be
in town interesting i said well maybe
we could all get like a dinner
you know earlier before in the week
before you go and she goes that
sounds great
nobody has said well here's what we're
doing maybe everyone's psyched that thanksgiving is
coming doing without ruth maybe they are
making them go over to her house
no no no that's scott but maybe
you know what no wedding what are
we going to do we get to
kind of be free to not do
lands right like one one's like what
would my dream baby i
wanna go to the you only get
one chinese only get so many thanksgivings
so true you know so true bestie
but at the same time the pressure
of having to do one every year
is like maybe this year they're kind
of like let's take one boy they
might just tell me
though ah she works for she works
for a travel agency should go and
she's like oh shit shit what if
i did this she fucking thinks that's
exactly it she travels all over the
place like oh i think i could
do that yeah it's really cool that's
cool wow yeah um that's actually awesome
well that's gonna be fun so you
might have like a philly cheese steak
imo or hoagie might we might we
might go to wawa for things that
i don't know it's funny that i
don't i still don't know i guess
i have to really come out and
ask them hey does anyone have any
plants and their shit i asked
yeah family text chain yes and so
you could ask on that or how
would you i can see approach don't
ask them that when you call someone
personally and ask call oh why are
you interested in the process because i'm
curious how people communicate i would text
we are no where on a what's
our robot oh encrypt is that true
no wonder what's up there because ah
my one of my
sisters lives in germany i love that
awe of wunderbar
yeah did she end up living in
germany we are ideal yeah she moved
from philadelphia this is my oldest sister
oldest person there are a lot of
nazis she
though she could stay in america oh
that's right um she moved first franglais
or philadelphia to first to allentown were
to follow ging to bid on knowing
if you're listening to the song exactly
yeah that's the sound of metal hitting
metal by the way yeah that's right
yeah that's um and then she
from the song from the song allentown
do you know i had a memory
recently of staying at her staying overnight
at her apartment downtown philadelphia
and um she had a guy stay
over one night huh okay it was
getting a little don't don't tell him
don't tell mom that he stayed over
how old were you like ok i
was i don't know how i will
do see though
she was eleven
yeah she had her own apartment it
was her teacher i mean she was
very precocious um how she must have
been in her early twenties okay yeah
that age word still is like look
i know i'm an adult i can
do whatever i want i am doing
what i was religious at that time
right you know she didn't want to
deal with the whole of course um
um but yeah i forgotten about that
yeah but i kinda remember her apartment
it was very i remember being i
remember thinking it was so cool
to to have a living space in
the city yeah oh yeah it's awesome
yeah there was it like that apartment
in flashdance where it's like a whole
like the whole city block yeah it
was just a hole and then wait
she went to germany no then she
went to get sex with this one
guy yeah just like i went to
turbine i got to do everything
she moved to um redondo beach california
i do know that my neck of
the woods but but does she have
a job that took her to germany
i'm getting to it why seems like
too you will forever cherish you ask
how did she end up in germany
well i kind of incurious when someone
moves to our country how they make
it happen you want to rephrase
and i'm trying to show did she
come there with a work visa or
how did she make it happen where
she was able to be in this
country i think giving you the whole
goddamn thing mister police and you're gonna
like it okay
redondo beach it's thanked ninety four she
meets a guy
she meets a guy from new zealand
they started a relationship hoi hoi i'm
a k i do i'm absolutely why
he sounds so easy okay oh hi
nah my wife is deaf boy off
life um so then they moved to
london together wow okay how did that
that's not germany they wonder how you
can be an ex pat
i'm trying these greenies fucking tell really
well she's living she's not pad anymore
like oh my god
that's so literally oh okay so then
ah they started a business together in
london called friends in london which was
for tra travelers they would come to
london it was like it was a
little bit ahead of it's time that
they would be like a sort of
concierge service for you cool to see
rt of do what a concierge service
does exactly yeah theater tickets um
russian ship did not last oh remain
friends wow yeah he's honestly but she
loved living in london and so she
stayed there
she got a job you know all
that somehow she i don't i she
went through all the stuff you have
to go through i guess to staff
it was a little i think it
was a little time to test the
difficultly administers it's perfect
all the money she's like what are
these jewish employee who has two thumbs
and no money
no mummy
i mean do you think she's a
mummy now i hope so i hope
so i hope so mr nader romeo's
they're all mummies i hope everyone's because
it's like coop everyone's oh mummy tutu
in common you know she wouldn't god
didn't come and come and alien two
people fart at the same time david
to in common
very good very good they'd be a
good like laffey taffy joke
good what happens when two mummies a
good one or typical one are we
what do you call it when two
mummies fart at the same time two
in common suit in common how you
spell it though you have to spend
you'd have to spell like tooting common
and and then sees i think it
only works common if they only worked
out loud yeah you say it a
lot once you read it lauren
that's how it gets you gotta read
right that's how the oral tradition continues
i don't think laffey taffy jokes are
beings yeah right ave yeah are we
a germany yet no because we were
coming up on a branch so she's
in lungi she is itself taken off
she is also a singer and so
she's singing ah well python's perfect example
i love close oh um very good
so she is singing with like this
more essentially like a ah you know
like a party or an event orchestra
you know like this this this big
band you were hire out for
a huge event she's vocalist and she
both thing everyone in the family things
except for my little brother so you
could have a little bit of a
orcas your family we're gonna have a
family band if we wanted to i'd
actually like to see that who wouldn't
want to see a middle age know
an elderly family and what have you
guys own for our freedom to no
variety
yeah the right tobia family reunion yes
sing a song together do you know
caitlin tarver did that with her family
really yes yes yes i had them
all single one of her tracks wow
that's amazing so like she was in
the wainwright's did that to a family
of talented singers it's just
amazing it's fun um so then she's
in this band she starts a relationship
with the drummer of this band but
boom boom boom boom men will take
ailing around the world that's what i'm
hearing what men yeah if you get
involved with a man help with a
guy you're in a new country by
morning well they lived in
lucky they lived in london for many
years yeah then they got married and
they moved to junior abroad that kind
of thing that caught on fire
it's nice to be sad but i
think he's nailing every single thing press
a button that each
exactly yeah so then that of course
the sound of the fisher price barn
door
a great something a bleat i love
it so much yeah i used to
open and close the door all the
funding time i love trying to like
really slow it down and a bitcoin
for the feel like i'm worried we've
talked about this but i love the
turning it upside down and a move
oh that loud does little canisters yeah
that was so late why is it
so great twenty satisfying how was it
made satisfying oh no one knows you
know like actual cow in there so
they get married they moved to ah
munich
that's paul how much song to take
break
but some awful i think should take
the break so my problem i think
we're taking a break we'll be back
and we're back paul finish this tip
store they get divorced no yeah congratulation
to have a child they're going after
ride yeah no longer a broderick that's
not a thing i can't give you
that one they should when you get
divorced they should play the da da
grant thornton backwards to scenario it makes
you like your eyes back in your
head yeah i'm satan comedy i'm here
ha en suisse co satan satan everyone
so scared of him but he can't
even like appear unless you do like
certain things let's get on base like
little red little devil it's like a
red little rich arizona skin
if somebody lives in literally hell hell
it's like dude get an apartment you
go on house hunters and get whatever
you want yes you choose to live
there yeah nothing here anyway yeah okay
ahead so they get divorced they do
have they do have that kid field
child how did he feel about the
divorce how losing
felt good right
i feel like he was still pretty
little so it wasn't totally yeah i
think he was under ten did the
dad ever do a mrs doubtfire where
he dressed up like doesn't serve this
day and everyone knows the same it's
mortifying that's really stressful yeah because you
can't make job because he's dealt fires
about you dress up as his own
wife yes you know i'm saying that
would be a good version of a
few
he when your brother-in-law does mrs doubtfire
you can't stop him because if you
sort of like try to acknowledge what's
happening he will just fucking violent it's
sort of like waking someone up for
me yeah guy person his own wife
like thinking he's fooling his children so
bad just throwing another because he
does it every night just see it
i'm cool enough
you're high on your face like that's
normal so she ah he moved the
husband the has been moved to berlin
and she stayed in munich and she
loves it she loves living germany's awesome
yeah she's never been i keep saying
just say no so great i'm never
with their own may i also ask
i'll go to munich is she
yeah let's do it together i actually
went there right before the payment maybe
my sister opened for the show is
she i don't know your sister we
had a headphone is she also there
because she doesn't want to take the
kid too far away from well no
he's like he's in his twenties now
still
oh shit oh oh i mean he
can even arrange that by himself where's
he live
he was living at university
um i think he's back in munich
now okay i'm not sure like this
he's actually won the whatsapp there are
tomkins all over the world from two
places i love it looks at germany
appear clean was i love whatsapp is
such a big crew for me it's
just me mike and my brother and
his wife well this is my me
and all my siblings while not all
my siblings siblings and other story me
and my sibling come through tom tom
cruise tom cruise huh some gruesome person
plus ah simply some cruise tom cruise
some great some cruise
send it up but now it's part
of the get's race siblings tom cruise
so it's tom cruise tom cruise
when you make a mistake you weave
it into the pattern when you make
a mistake this is how you make
up a state beautiful faces with cracks
have leaves of gold yeah that's beautiful
thing yeah i'd like to go like
i keep saying that but i never
i think joining your next big trip
how long would it should be
sounds like great time really sure how
long is the flight i don't remember
too much yeah i think it's if
it was two hours two hours it's
probably ten but you stand the whole
time right um you have to stand
and you have to have your eyes
wide open there's no shutting blinking and
ah that's it wow
do they feel like spraying thing in
your eyeballs to keep them wet sausages
oh i guess i can't just dangle
them my dad by the way who's
in the aerospace industry oh yeah it
was oh we're talking about like what's
next for for you know airplane travel
or whatever like how do you get
five oh wait is it called aerospace
as if it's just arrow and this
is called aerosmith because they couldn't get
the rights to aero space i think
so too both of you
i think that's a cheat if you
if you're just a helicopter dude you're
not in space i read that the
show arrow was it was meant to
be a e r o like the
candy bar and they misspelled it in
there like holy shit now we have
to justify this guy's got to shoot
arrows do you know what i have
a friend who in shop
class or whatever it was you know
million years ago this dum dum the
use bow arrow and she's a r
r o w he's like well right
and he made himself a belt that
said aerosmith ah i agree like the
kurt bucy comic absolutely incorrect that's how
it's spelled oh i wrote something called
aerosmith that's it was the guy who
made arrows
bs i don't i don't know what
the actual plot of it was but
this like get very bright right in
my eyes or i just move into
it's path i think he moved into
his pow worried about you um but
we worried about you too okay so
my dad and i were talking about
what's next for for flights and how
do they get faster and he was
saying this is his theory that
they that's basically it won't be planes
necessarily but they will shoot and you'll
you get onto a rocket no one
will want it will shoot up into
the air and come down at any
place and come down because the the
earth will have rotated it'll take like
an hour
our to get to germany or whatever
i love that idea now you're in
just because it takes less time oh
wait you just go straight up in
the air go straight up in the
air hanging out there for hour you
just know you don't hang out huh
yeah i've explosions and deaths
the scientist smiling you're so excited about
it like the joe ward is rubbing
your hands together
dollar signs and loud ticks are losing
your signing a petition to elect you
for congress so you can happen back
notice if the law is going to
be opposition leader tenable to ever talk
to your dad about chem trails trails
is that one kim kardashian farts
like putin kevin
her and kanye have a dean cover
mummies
because we got to finally talk about
kanye well first let's talk about chem
trails i think it would dovetail nicely
okay what what it tells me about
kim charles do you know about kim
trans i do i know that people
believe in them that it's sort of
one of those conspiracy theory yes and
you know like those white lines in
the sky white lines run
through my mind yeah yeah people say
that that's what no camara his contract
ah you know a lot of guys
all i know is i think it's
a conspiracy theory right because there's a
conspiracy theory and the the theory as
i understand it is that ah it's
how all of the world's governments keep
us docile oh like those little dust
in the air it's kind of like
causing me to like yeah breathe into
the rag a little bit
or even to it like like the
recommend rag like you guys did into
the government bags that's my favorite song
the government's right yeah so i e
that body that that government rag the
idea that the government was like how
do we keep people from rising up
against us why don't we just have
planes just sort of crop dust yeah
like leave these trails everywhere and keep
everyone just pretty what about us you
see it oh no people can see
it yeah they'll just can you imagine
just people some people just have very
interesting belief system well it's enjoyed that
because it is a neutral as possible
if you look at semi recent events
it only took a few hundred people
almost overthrow the government so it's like
there's millions of millions here we could
do whatever we wanted and yet we
don't because of fucking chem trails good
but starting to come around on this
way
way to keep them ways of course
spray vinegar okay so oh yes kind
of like how you smell like vinegar
all the time um i'm sure i
don't know what you mean so if
you spray vinegar it'll eventually waft up
to the sky just know it does
well dissipates in your immediate area oh
so it's actually the white lines aren't
really as far away as it is
it's down in my mind
and the white lines are up there
but then all the shit comes down
settle down i'm just like a puppy
zine wizard of oz yes thank you
excuse you what in the fuck
what happened got an alert a purple
alert glass breaking heard
hi house oh is anyone home i
was laughing until i heard the my
house in my office address is really
weird and you should definitely have someone
check that out hi glass breaking in
my house i will definitely send that
oh i'm sure cool i've got it
but oh maybe someone oh no you
know there's a refrigerator guy who is
is going to be working on the
refrigerator down there sounds like he's probably
yes to and you're frederick's behind glass
so yeah only using case of emergencies
as what you're getting fixed could you
take the glass off we're starving
um lawrence i answer your question yeah
why don't people just wear masks oh
masterwork that's oh only going to her
oh that's right yes that's how we
here at cova just spray vinegar but
there are videos on youtube that people
extreme vinegars why have you been doing
that because i wanted to preserve myself
for marriage mummification yes i could eventually
i was too common with my lover
here's the thing if you want to
be a mummy just spray vinegar on
yourself a bunch well you put the
paper well let the tub with vinegar
and then yeah yada yada yada yada
yada yada yada yada and mummification
how do you want to do you
want to be cremated or do you
want to be why did you ask
me this once a season i have
a will have you you have a
oh we have a will can i
be in this lovely um yeah what
do you want a dollar um you
don't really need my dollar twenty nine
like this using the age old question
i'd like you to give me one
hundred dollars in the will
l just right now know how much
you have me right now i think
i probably have like six dollars or
some would you give me sixty dollars
now would you give me fifty know
but i love i think having cash
is what we're missing this in our
generation yes this this is so give
me fortune like being buried
with cash like because ice i think
we yeah i think you will need
to have cash on that in there
i agree that's why i'm saying give
me forty i can't give it to
you right now i need it when
in your will would i need it
would you please will to me something
that would naturally go to mike but
just give it to my bra collection
election
these are the ones you never wear
right is it just in the glass
case yeah i just kind of like
old-fashioned interesting recent case of sagging yeah
vintage brass bra funko pops yeah um
no you know it's already a done
deal i'd have to in a few
years time when i go to edit
it again i will leave you something
okay thank you leave us both
but it's they already did all the
work of finalizing yeah i know you
have a notary yeah i think ours
was very vague where it was like
well i didn't include like all my
objects yeah we were just included a
few this stuff goes to them like
that goddamn we i hopefully we're not
going to go at the same time
because then that complicates that ball
oh we did all three of us
yeah now it's that's why i don't
want to go on tour with you
here right we can't help in the
same places but hell you're like he's
bringing out the door we just want
to do one live show at home
i know idiot he just
oh oh come on you are my
freebie next how did you know i
was talking about you wait wait are
we talking about match
please come back to what you were
just saying yeah what about it what
about was
huh by the way i've gotten confirmed
final episode i've gotten confirmation that it's
the freezer repair man wonderful so episodes
were so happy now so wait would
do even have time so happiness we
have enough time to go back to
lawrence topics well a little more about
this if you want to start a
story inspired by yada yada i do
have a little more time i love
to hear
yada yada
okay what do you want here you
wanna hear about the actual bill there
yes i wanna hear that story okay
heard the story birth excited so okay
so when it was like hey five
centimeters yeah it's going down this down
down baby they said ah to us
at emerald sun going down i am
naming na na na may me
um they said do you want to
go get lunch and come back so
we went to it so exciting that
were you just buzzing it was a
little like okay it's a waking honey
the whole time it was kind of
like we'd been beaten into submission right
ticket like excitement for excitement purposes of
like for two weeks just like it's
not happening so yeah now it's
like is it happening i don't know
so we went to red lobster which
was across the street to caress red
lobster it's good and so now we
think maybe on her birthday we go
to red lobster every oh but we
went to red lobster and that was
at eleven thirty we we got back
by twelve thirty then we our lunch
shh sure a sensible hour yeah went
up into a hospital and we had
to we had to like sign some
stuff and all that kind of stuff
so that's maybe another hour it's one
thirty and then ah our surrogate husband
is there and they only allow t
is he's he's like who are you
ooh faithful i go away for two
seconds how many losers in my baby
two people are allowed to know he
has to leave i have to leave
wow it's better that he is there
because like i'm getting to he needs
to coach her through right all of
this happened he's pulling your leg
oh like there was a doula of
her was like okay yeah hold her
legs open because she's like i wanna
be shot she don't give me back
today so he's there so let's see
he's there in cool up as there
and i have to go so i
must have been crazy for you so
i picture you like like you know
window eating red lobster
breaking into a lab billboard so basically
i am now in the situation that
like you see in the old classic
movies when there's a pregnancy where right
because the men was we're always waiting
men were always in the waiting room
so i'm basically like hanging out in
the hospital all afternoon fun on my
phone and then my
one phone is about to die fine
so i go out into the car
and just like shill in the car
all day and all night it sounds
like heaven how long did it go
on um so
by the way i have we we
supposedly the the process is when the
baby is delivered we then get ah
our own room like the babies taken
to a room and that you know
that's when they get the stork yeah
train stork they hang it on the
beak and then it walks into your
oxen yeah exactly yeah that would be
really cool when the noise he makes
is like
i learned they do it i guess
she was gonna go for it without
thinking and then that's when i don't
think i know it it's all about
that comes so ah so i'm just
in the situation where i'm like you
know doing the difficult pacing the the
waiting room and like i feel like
i need to have cigars for everyone
there something but so ah
at at nine thirty p m um
i hit post meridian post meridian i
get a text from collab saying it's
going down and so i'm gathering and
like there's all this stuff that i
need to take up to the room
and it's only me so it's like
two giant armfuls of staff hollering books
so
yeah i'm but the tax ah
impacts a teacher about puberty now so
i have like just i'm like okay
i'll i'll get all the stuff i
go i go to the end the
the entrance is closed now unless you're
going in for a specific purpose so
i basically gather two armfuls of stuff
at nine thirty pm and um i'm
there by the end
lawrence ready for it um ten twenty
two is when it happens twenty two
twenty two huh and i just i
just get a text she's here huh
and then a half hour goes by
just standing outside with shani outside with
this stuff but also like
like is there a problem write something
they know that's the last thing you
hear that's just she's here rod and
then a half hour and then i
get a picture and i'm like okay
did she come up should i come
up anyway another couple hours goes by
the torture and it after midnight around
twelve thirty it's like okay you can
come up
now so i was i mean if
you can say what was the delay
or oh they have to do like
certain tests and stuff like that because
that was why you weren't allowed to
go there yeah doing all those things
they're not moving her to the room
right okay yeah okay because you're supposed
to be in that separate round bubble
blog that so i definitely got your
questions i definitely got i had always
assumed i would be there and what
it would be like the whole deal
right
cool i've got all that and i
got just basically the typical you know
like nineteen sixties man for yeah where
it's like oh here the baby's here
i'll run up to the room saying
yeah leave the bar
but that's great that cool i've got
to watch that yes it was very
good to shoot and she's got some
videos so that's great i think i've
been er the nurses all likes took
her phone and took oh pictures and
stuff like that it was very nice
but then they just like we get
the room and and we don't know
or doing they're in and they're just
basically like here's your baby good night
yeah
yeah take care of it and you're
like oh what how that's crazy yep
anyway so wow so did you stay
overnight there stayed overnight there and ah
would have maybe stayed one more night
ah but this is not a hotel
sir
no no we were pressing to go
but i keep calling the hospital the
hotel and vice versa true we want
to go home but yeah so you've
been but they were like maybe one
more night but then we finally got
clear delete you have to watch all
these videos and stuff on an i
they bring in an i-pad they're like
watch these videos before you can go
i guess it was like one rick
ass
we'll please be honest
briquettes yeah um about how to like
certain things ie thing how to take
care of yeah oh yeah yeah awesome
safety they're there kind of data they
remember the ones that i watch um
yeah the safety elements but like the
sort of like someone someone like style
that was it was good but yeah
anyway so we got a member there
were only two genders
ok we got home the next night
and that's and yeah so that's is
are there any details that you want
to know about that i've left um
well i guess my first question is
what was it like the first night
when you were home like did you
feel like oh my god i can't
believe it like what was your emotional
ah because the night before
for you know it was one of
those like every two hours week yeah
it was just like sheer just exhaustion
just like and we had to drive
home from riverside which that it was
actually kind of nerve wracking to be
in the car cool i fell asleep
i she was like i'm going to
be the backseat i'm gonna be making
sure that that everything's alright with emerald
and then then i drove and then
i found out later just loud
she just knows she just fell asleep
right away oh she's fine yeah ah
yeah so it's you know i don't
know it's been a bit of an
adjustment sure sure sure sure said yes
and now i think you told me
you take pictures of her all day
and then you at night you look
at
the pictures that is the picture know
that cool up does definitely she's like
all i do after ah you know
when we go to bed as i
sit there in bed for awhile just
looking at all the pictures on to
it so fun um it's yeah that's
very nice so cute she's very cute
um she's like a perfect little clone
of cool up yes yeah although she's
starting to look more and more like
me really wish she would not act
like you this isn't she's starring una
said yeah um alright we have some
beautiful break
me and your bad
oh yellow they come right away yeah
dial did it ever come back in
style ah no no yet he didn't
say when
i saw that guy in person one
time oh cool that guy from twin
peaks it was very exciting yeah yeah
yeah yeah the cat and fiddle oh
wow that's i hear that's a good
restaurant now i went there a long
time is it this is not the
same place though right
ah oh wait they need to know
that there is a new oh iou
i have not been there i have
not been like on that street and
i can't we were on that street
last night and we passed in clubs
why that's a restaurant that was in
santa monica or something that the second
location is now in they moved to
brick by brick o second location brick
by oprah says never go to a
single location it's true
um so very quickly the yadda yadda
ya
i was in a development deal back
when that was a thing nice and
i got paired with these two writers
to essentially write a sitcom pilot based
on my standup i loved back when
that was a thing i love everything
i'm hearing and these juices drinks eight
beers every show yeah it was about
a guy who drink apes every show
oh
yes slim yeah yeah every other page
drinks another beer
another one another one another one i
mean the best music and these people
and i did not get along oh
no um ah we had different ideas
about what was funny and what was
not fun well that's already rough and
they were like the pros right so
i was like the dumb comedian who
didn't know the show to doing um
except i i
new submit and you know what's funny
yeah yeah and so we clashed a
lot and i could tell that they
just despised me yeah um and they
kept wanting to back then i did
not drive they kept wanting to meet
um as far where they had a
boat and they always wanted to meet
oh come on yeah just so insane
and
in a boat they had a boat
anytime you go by the water yeah
that's already way too far and then
you go oh yeah sure yo ma
you're done marina del rey no no
no no no had to go down
rich no mother fuck and then here's
what we did was we just sat
on the boat in the dock it
was like i thought on the yeah
like gonna go out on the water
i was like if we're
if we're gonna do that yeah that
sounds fun you can use sitting at
the dock event like yeah i'm just
sitting at the dock and and you
know like there's no shot this is
beautiful this is not like a like
a huge luxury boat you know i
mean there's an we're sitting on a
molded plastic waste your life yeah yeah
there's an implied thing when you're working
with someone is that you meet
halfway yes exactly the between two ferns
movie would say let's meet halfway and
then pick a place ten minutes from
his house yeah of course so i
had coffee with you guys and like
westwood yes sir year so the thing
does not go years later they're working
with a friend of mine on according
to jim yeah
and when your friend jim belushi
please don't make me name bro
but they were telling the story of
working with me no not knowing that
he knew he no no we would
they say you so that you never
heard of a menu never will wow
hearing that story they've talked about what
an asshole i was and then after
that store name yeah yeah yeah and
my friend just going oh huh oh
i'll take it all in and take
it all in so then a year
after that or so i run into
the guy the husband of this team
has been a lifetime always lie because
been a while while there and all
they can afford is a shitty boat
well they couldn't afford it for long
because they eventually had to
i love them for them but he
he was like being so fucking phony
with me and he kept saying it's
good to see you and i wouldn't
say it back yeah and he kept
like saying it's good to see you
and i was with other people and
i feel like i was like yes
i am seeing yes but the
name of their boat was the yadda
yadda spelled y h t a but
it was not a yacht ooh that's
why it was ah it was a
reference to another sitcom that they didn't
work oh they did not work this
is more about this but they break
up i highly recommend the show episode
i'm sure they're still together and are
they dead i'm sure they're still together
i'm sure
are there still alive like daily and
later we talk about the show episodes
just for the quick reference yeah i
love that show it's so funny change
a huge episodes so good if you
need to show out there and you
want something funny that's the show for
you i haven't been writing tv husband
wife writing duo that's kinda the premise
that matt leblanc plays like a version
of himself it's very funny yeah love
it
yeah classic tv people advice about do
you want to vote no i don't
want to be on the water ever
i get seasick if you could walk
on water would you
sure do you think you will get
seasick if you walked on it probably
that's the thing if you if you
could walk on water would people like
walk to england ah yes they would
absolutely you would just walk everywhere that
broader connects something to the other thing
obviously
obviously doesn't wanna hear one about paul
does paul wants a vote paul wants
about so bad i would call once
but i would love a boat you
have to be so you have to
have so much fucking money when there's
such a boo i dated this are
a waste of money if you have
the money to keep it up
yeah nothing is a waste of money
if you have the money as well
then what are we talking about it's
still a waste
so history will note if you have
that money that's what i'm saying yeah
and i said yesterday showing it because
it doesn't affect you at all it's
not a waste of money if you
like it and use it and you
can afford it i think it's a
waste of money if you're saying like
again avoid this but i'm gonna do
it and i'm not going to use
it
that's a waste of money
um i dated in high school i
dated somebody who i did post it
seems always talking about girls never mentioned
these always signs that girl but she
her family had this boat and it
was like the best boat situation i
think because it was in huntington harbour
they got into best book
um but where basically it's just like
you can travel around this very serene
water that's by everyone's houses and just
these like that's almost so good and
stuff like that it was like ok
i like this but then what for
someone's birthday once someone in co-op's friend
group rented a boat for like oh
let's go out on the water for
thing everyone sees it immediately
or just not worth that no no
no no i'm really iraqi people onto
a boat believe i've talked about it
on our show before but jamie and
i rented a boat in south carolina
a couple of years ago and it
was so much like we would want
to know because you what is it
common placid though and like ah yeah
i mean you're going out and like
the it's not like a lake so
there is it's the river
or it's the intercoastal waterway okay and
there's certain places like you cannot go
over there and you can't go over
there and you have to be really
mindful of how um how deep you
are because if you go too shallow
you run into ground that's a big
fuckin deal and so there's all kinds
of monitors and things like that like
little nightmares but things that monitor your
not seeing it's not like video monitors
but there's you know there there's all
kinds of gauges and shit like that
you have to be aware of and
i i like that part of it
too but you you pick it up
very quickly yeah you know and you
when once you get the hang of
it it's really really fun it's great
i can't wait to do it again
and they shouldn't be letting people do
it why don't you go jump in
a lake
you know what maybe i will relax
you're at the lake how is that
an insult by the way go jump
in a lake oh yeah jump it's
like hey sounds fun but you're saying
it's someone fully clothed that's the implication
it's yeah but like you said like
got a wallet not against the rules
to take your clothes off no no
it is there's go jumping lake implies
all europe shit will get ruined to
your shoes
i only know this means i don't
care what that's why that's why it's
a bad thing to say it means
i don't care what you do just
get out of my sight about go
suck an egg that's nasty maybe it's
that's go as far away from me
as possible which includes the water that's
just go jumping you know what i
mean like only say if you're near
a sago jump in a lake you
don't save that like some people say
that like go jump in the lake
who says that no one saying that
like people well they might say it
like bell like says all times she
says go jump in the little jump
in this lake oof hey alright we
have to play this three-tier yeah you're
coming back that you are going to
lead us right into it like no
other way to say yeah i got
confused about time but we couldn't leave
the thread hanging because it came up
before the break and people dripping phantom
wacha and fifty times lol phantom thread
okay this is a three year we've
played before we haven't done it in
a while and i'm very pleased to
bring it back it's called hey fred
schneider this is an old improv warmup
where you say you stand around in
circle you're clapping you say hey fred
schneider what are you doing and then
somebody has to come up with a
thing that fred schneider is doing and
the classic french knight or voids love
it so much it's fun and nothing
but alright nothing but fun let's do
it and we all say hey fred
schneider what are you doing yeah same
time yeah yeah and then we go
around the show we don't speak circle
at all no we never speed up
if if anything we slowed down how
many times are we saying it before
someone has to make up one i
think one just wants yeah yeah
weiss what's the clap i forget the
rhythm but fred schneider what are you
doing right there hey fred schneider what
are you doing hey fred schneider's yeah
yeah it was hey fridge snyder what
are you thinking you're wrong
i'm wrong you're wrong you're wrong i'm
wrong you're wrong i'm wrong i'm wrong
someone gotta bring their fists in their
hand and it's all down here from
you hey fred schneider what are you
doing hey schneider what are you doing
o putting some ketchup on my hotting
ng dog hey fred schneider what are
you doing going to the dentist for
my free clean you loud i can't
the cops are july yeah process what's
happening yeah let's a little that's still
too you have the loudest class yes
now i'm beautiful it's my beautiful hand
yeah it's it's your princely
put your hands together likely i like
this
so yeah you can play it like
a liquid those weird country instruments okay
hey first-time what are you doing okay
oh fred schneider what are you doing
i'm going to oh ben up my
own chase bay hey fred schneider what
are you doing walking down the street
like a chick
chicken with a head hey schneider what
are you doing trying to learn the
rules of baseball so i can play
hey the french writer what are you
doing test driving cars with no rove's
hey fred schneider what are you doing
going after finland the land of the
finns hey
hey shiner what are you doing poor
and catch up on my dear wife
hey for schneider what are you doing
counting the feathers in my new po
hey fred schneider what are you doing
go into the beach and looked in
at a crab hey guys i hear
that's an
only you do buying twitter for forty
four billion a fresh writer what are
you doing paying my fee to verify
hey fred schneider well what are you
doing storming the caf beto with some
good friends hey fr schneider what are
you doing
catch an olap procon and squeezing the
life out of it hey jay schneider
what are you doing catch it a
gu said squeezing the life out of
that hey fred schneider are you doing
catch a big foot and becoming friends
hey what are you doing shaving off
my
hair and realizing i'm the big foot
hey fred schneider what are you doing
i just see my pants till they
fit real ty hey schneider why are
you doing sending a valentine to drag
yo la hey fred schneider what are
you doing ending the song right now
alright yeah wow i was here what
are you doing i love it my
hands are tingling my hands are tingling
and i'm i put myself with my
wedding ring oh lesson for next time
yeah it is but i will retain
it get a divorce
so you don't have that race i
made a vow i like
it isn't weird that you make this
vow and then half the people just
go like yeah i forget yeah
kind of greatest option it's it's fucking
great a great option great backdoor option
yeah i think they shouldn't make it
so definitive in the vows i think
i should unless you get more eggs
do you want to do this
alright well this was a great time
because it was ha i'm with you
all i'll be back gang happy thanksgiving
i hope said if you're like trying
to avoid your loved ones today and
listening to us that everything's cool with
you ah if your loved ones are
listening to this with you there keepers
yeah
wow and if they're saying this is
stupid why are you listening to it
kick them in the fucking balls kick
them in the balls of that yeah
another for that i love that
but guys if you want to follow
us on social media it's at threesome
us a yeah we're proudly american yeah
i'm a medica
and medica you can write to us
i forgot what the what the three
of them he was a gmail dot
com that's what he asked and send
us a three-tier ideas and if you
want to hear ad-free episodes of this
you can hear them at stitcher premium
and also cvb world dot com oh
and roman remember scott i know what
you're
to say i'm so glad i was
thinking the same thing okay what i
remember the wait i know what you
were just going to say lauren so
he stayed at the same time yeah
three to one remember that only the
poseidon adventure burgers
no see what i was gonna say
is we're re-releasing all of the old
episodes we you know what we call
it of everything of every of every
podcast happy we're doing doing know there's
a lot of words just podcast hey
guys just podcast mozilla and so jump
to happy days i was like we
gotta happen welcome to night vale holy
show ever
happy days happy yeah you sound fifty
so it was the first show um
no we're re-releasing old episodes of freedom
so you can and we call it
three three visit three visits three visiting
three visiting revisiting knowledge news because it's
on tuesday nanotubes and tuesday will re-release
another ad in the fifties and i
was a child who did
i understand ty day use me really
did it a little bit so anytime
you saw anything said in the past
you were like what is option when
they already reruns you know so like
so like this is from the wonder
years i thought kind of wasn't i
just i sort of thought but it's
never was the fifties by the way
it's good it's never been a big
day it never has been
but i thought and it never will
be the fifth city at the distinguish
well i swear fish world's gonna end
in twenty forty nine o slater owner
so please listen to the episodes they're
coming out every every tuesday listen to
will will release episodes this you know
last tuesday we're gonna release them this
tuesday three visits three visitors on the
tube i don't know what three visiting
own
see you there
uh