three
z z z z
oh wow
three three months from now i'm really
done with doing what you were going
to do it
tweet me to wait wait wait wait
when we're down we should like the
budweiser frog three what are the budweiser
frog to say i don't even remember
it really it's a budweiser they said
budweiser yes i want the budweiser frogs
it sure was
why why do you think a commercial
like that right now what have you
are forced to be called whatever you
said like gollum like you're like racist
to gollum sega la yeah that's why
his name was gone because you made
that noise y'all um yeah actually it's
because he's when i actually know this
deeply that way
when um andy circus would swallow in
character it sounded like golem and he
made that part of his thing you
made that part of his p o
m his original name was spiegel because
he was a guy and he got
to ah ho
hopeful about that ring and he became
nasty here's the thing about lord of
the rings and i know you've discussed
this the way welcome this freedom paul's
talking welcome to ridden paul's talk
the person who said paul is talking
first with scott and the person who
pointed that out is lauren yep and
that's the three of us and we're
together three them and now we're gonna
wear em three boys where the pretzel
gang of course that's that's where the
peanut butter m and m crew yeah
okay a pretzel game f k ah
peta but a f k uh
love of the theme of guys well
i think we're aka not f k
formerly known as yeah i don't say
yeah no no we're um familiarly known
as have many titles like familiarly known
yeah what a difficult thing to say
familiarly known as all the riddle gang
them peanut butter boys
you entitled t k is no butter
in boys
titled t k that i never knew
it until the breeders put out their
record it was called title t k
but oh it's like where you fit
what you're gonna fill in to come
is and it's yeah why is it
a k because i guess tc doesn't
look makes you think like taking care
come see you em i have no
idea
what even though that one's how it's
really spelled ceo emmy i don't know
when i read the word ceo i
mean i think c u m
no matter what the kind of better
wait what were you gonna say when
somebody says oh i think come
when somebody says gum i think come
on
all i think um and when somebody
says three am i think three codes
you asked me if i wanted to
come and coke
come in my coke um so he's
saying well yeah what were you saying
i wonder what i was saying
i want lord of the rings oh
yeah yeah oh yeah so when i
was when i was a kid i
read all those books first i read
the hobbit then i read the three
the trilogy how did you get interested
in them was it the cartoon or
you know the rank and you know
what i don't it was i think
it was rankin bass but it was
it was ralph bakshi was that the
enemy ralph bakshi yeah
but i just watched it all i
think i read the book first and
i don't know who turned me onto
that but i remember reading it and
loved it i really like a bunch
of times where you ended dungeons and
dragons or anything i wasn't really i
want anything i of natalie or no
not really not strongly that was it
for me like i was probably more
into sci-fi as a kid than i
wasn't a fantasy
um that was kind of the extent
of my fantasy was section of cycle
hobbit the fiction that's right i'm a
science science denyer you take something a
little bit true and you make a
little bit fun you take something a
little bit truly they had a little
things like cars like swords they exist
right but what if they were lasers
i just want to alien for the
first time so it's a little bit
swiftly oh it's a little alien
little bit of sci-fi especially the part
about that that's like a monster from
another planet and spaceships like the pile
with all like being themselves and i'm
like this is real but here's the
thing about the hobbit vs the lord
of the rings and this is why
it's become so like in in hearing
you talk about the hobbit movies which
i think i only ever saw the
first
one i was so mad that ah
because i didn't realize it was going
to be a trilogy as well oh
really and it was so they added
all this darkness to it that wasn't
in the book and it really bothered
my old friend
darkness he says a little by the
way oh shit
tom hi back ah was that it's
like so j r r tolkien writes
this book and it it does well
and then he's like i'm gonna retrofit
this this element of the book to
become this incredibly dark thing that in
the in the original book was just
like
it turns you invisible what's in that
the the original book was the habit
was the habit okay and so when
when you're reading this book where bilbo
puts all right it's just kinda cool
where it's like ooh he's just like
oh nobody can see me and then
in the in the in the books
in the subsequent books the trilogy frodo
puts on the ring and it's like
is honourable fuckin change comes over him
it's like this horrible nightmare world yeah
it's like saying yes yeah but so
then i sort of understand that if
you're going to adapt the lord of
the rings first and you're like this
is such a huge success we'll go
back and do the hobbit but now
there's this
established world for people that maybe never
read the books that it's like well
i see so they they added i
never saw these so they added the
darkness to the hobby yes they they're
anytime anyone put it put a ring
on put a ring on it um
they then saw the of the the
zombies or whatever there i honestly can't
remember what happens when
puts the ring on the habit look
why in the ha why don't we
talk to the expert over here well
looking at it right now let's be
clear i will have mixed up all
of the movies into one mush sure
but there's what happens when frodo puts
on the ring is that he is
going into this kind of disturbing world
yeah everything is like black and white
like he's invisible but everything
that isn't habana i think he can
like get away with stuff but like
they're still scary so it doesn't yeah
fun yeah but in the first cartoon
first cartoon is the only one that
i saw unliked i remember i remember
going like oh that's fun like this
is a fun thing yes a fun
story fine i don't like it yeah
it probably doesn't but i'm
coming to it as an adult i
think maybe as a kid i would
have medicaid i was like oh what
a fun story like he falls in
that and i'm paraphrasing the story obviously
i'm not reading this currently but he
falls in a hole and sees a
weirdo and then puts on a ring
the place was like every page of
j r r tolkien the hobbit stars
so he falls
in the holy see's a weirdo
huh and we watched the toyota it's
right by the way it starts with
that line so freaky slowing he flowed
say ooh he's arguably yeah yeah so
he falls at all these weird i
actually think that is not a bad
opening line for a book so i
agree the whole and caesar were down
so he falls all because you're wearing
my attention you're wondering who's he yes
are they midst versus is the narrator
telling a story in the real media
rez who knows yeah book that started
with
so so he falls in a hole
and this is a weird concept to
weirdo it's not about i mean opening
lines and books are really hard and
i do a punch up on that
yeah anyway he falls an old season
anyway not bad i got a better
one okay i punched up yeah however
he falls in a hole and sees
a weirdo can i punch it up
yeah therefore he falls
in a hole and she's a weirdo
okay can i punch it up yeah
thusly he falls in a haunting weirdo
seems like you're just doing synonyms for
bunching up yeah moreover he falls in
a hole he's a weirdo moreover it's
such a word you would use it
a school paper like sound like you're
smart or yeah there was a rover
thus someone played me a tape and
i bet yeah funny
it's going to be a teacher and
your kid gives you like the student
who's your favourite it's a moral moreover
guys selenium
just just write it in plain language
stop trying to sound smart i know
you didn't ever say moreover thus did
you ever hear that tape or or
mutual friend played of the guy the
english actor mutual friend jeffrey epstein
i remember when we were on the
ground he played that video huh guys
go see this
so does this english actor saying how
and ever do you remember this at
all i don't want to say who
it is it sounds familiar but instead
of saying however this english actor was
trying to sound smart or so but
he's like how endeavour high and the
chameleon interview it was no it was
a secretly taped thing that's why i
can't say what
i'll tell you now i remember exactly
what it is yeah the person didn't
even know they're being taped and they
were talking like that yeah yeah how
endeavour that's bad
ah recorded some moment they didn't know
no i will say i don't think
that your eyes started turning i really
i got scared like have i done
that i am recording is no you
know i don't play said for how
long
months i've i've recorded someone on the
phone before yes i think it was
illegal i didn't do anything toll ville
were doing las vegas or new york
then it was okay i was so
so basically cool up cool up was
was in a big dispute with a
sickly coup law
up was in a dispute with her
landlords really fell in a hole it's
all weirdo
she then moved to an apartment basically
she fell wholesale facebook shop i thought
wow this is you and that's good
basically trying to carter boy basically she
figured out how come a car drove
away
so she she got to do it
dispute with their landlord over her deposit
or something like that and where her
landlord wasn't going to give her the
deposit back i mean she was owed
it or whatever you don't say that
to cool up no no no but
so so i said you know i'm
gonna call her but i'm going to
tape record the conversation so that we
have it in case
anything goes weird but what i found
was i said oh hey by the
way i'm tape recording this conversation and
she was so nervous she went ah
yeah oh okay i am too that
cheat that it totally resolved the situation
wow oh my gosh a good tactic
yeah and so it's a really good
tactic if you're ever in it just
cute to go like oh by the
way i'm tape recording this conversation just
for you know it really shows you
feel pretty confident you're right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah but not to get
into the vow yeah oh boy
oh okay how's this already sleep talked
about basically falling into a hole and
seeing a weirdo yes exactly what happened
those people hold i do kind of
want to watch seduce wood on starz
which i heard is the way better
version of the vow which tells much
more of the story but i'm also
kind of like i don't really want
to hear any more about this this
this my girl this entire king are
things i feel like i would much
rather know that people
talking about it than watching i wish
i had watched tiger king i wish
i could take that back yeah you
can look man we were outside working
outside the king and all his works
and we were desperate for entertainment and
normal work and it was right there
and it was what i'm not gonna
watch it what am i gonna watch
but with the vow i sort of
have this theory that because
it came out if you've only watch
the island it's only information you know
it came out that there's way worse
stuff even than that that this man
has done a while now he's in
jail for life and it's very deserved
but in the in the show he's
recorded all the time and he's had
people recording all the times like they're
tape recording every conversation they have filming
it so there's
tons of footage of him just waxing
poetic was fucking bullshit by the way
i truly would be like you make
no sense like there were so many
times where someone could have easily still
challenged anything he was saying because yeah
but he claims to be the smartest
person in the world like there's truly
like he's delusional but it's good for
a documentary though to constantly be recording
wow but my point is that
this should start doing this okay fine
so we can we can talk a
bit about this well honestly like i
am at a point on the comedy
bang bang tv shows like this would
making the show would be really fast
yeah we should i wish we could
hire a crew to like follow us
around while we make an episode or
whatever ah to put it as an
extra on one of the ways but
like so
but then bruce springsteen is constantly recording
every aspect of his amazing every album
well i just watched his really good
documentary letter to you about his new
record it's like springs he's listening it
was really good but but it seems
like every album he's made the like
a camera crew comes in and there's
all this amazing food does feel like
you know oh
from even the old day even the
old days oh and you know and
it's like cheese should just get away
i'm like yeah just anyway good well
i just wanted to say that i
felt like it might have been one
of his manipulative tactics to record all
of the possible stuff and be like
i'm always on recording and then the
second the cameras go off he's literally
having sex with children
it sound like doing more flying thing
yeah oh um that
that like it's as if he's kind
of set it up to be like
look i'm an open book i have
a video of everything i've ever done
and then of course there's this really
dark backstory yeah why did where are
the people who fell into it dumb
like do they explain that my yeah
you gotta watch this because like what
what's your name from smallville alison she's
off her rocker wow yeah
yeah so it's just a bunch of
really believes in the sun she's it's
a couple lunatics in other words like
like a lot of times you feel
bad for people like oh they're not
all lunatics or only they're all people
who were in need of something until
they were susceptible to cold which i
i yeah i don't think that's like
i'm a psionic or swing know but
i'm saying they get to toe to
real there but for the grace of
god
so swept in and swept up in
it that they don't realize it's weird
but i think one of the things
that's weird about the vow is that
by the time it is you know
they realize how messed up it was
and all this stuff they still think
the cult stuff was good like they're
still kind of going like him with
the teachings and like all the things
we learned and like these my my
show
sashes and it's like no no no
it was all that yes well connected
to the bat yeah but if something
makes someone feel better that part of
it might be good i mean like
you look at scientology like although we
don't want to be talking about that
probably on a recording i don't even
know anything about it really i haven't
really watched things or or
for any religion mormonism or sure we're
having system early or like people who
like you know like even like the
long island medium where it's like if
therapy think oh this makes me feel
better but there is
kind of a different thing than those
things yeah although i will say that
when in growing up i was thinking
about this the other day that um
my parents like didn't believe in therapy
and so when it looked like someone
in my family needed it they were
like well only if it's a christian
therapist what am
and and it's just like ah but
now i think they would be like
it's such a different time than nineteen
eighty five yeah i do think people
nowadays i think people to be like
oh yeah that's fine i think it's
the same you don't think i think
it's pretty much the same except for
phones hey i think that's it the
tvs are flatter you have to admit
yeah nah my house anyway you have
we are now
around tv baby round the sphere why
don't they make spherical tds so you
can watch it from anywhere in your
room
that's what a flat one is
okay why do you think the sphere
is flat ma used to do the
earth but um you could watch a
flat tv from anywhere in the room
scouts it introduce you to the mechanics
running into walls so triumphantly he's arguing
that you can't see a flat screen
tv from anywhere in the room where
can see it from behind
but you can find it from behind
the wall a sphere you could i'm
saying if you're like have you ever
gone you're saying you hit a wall
that the tv is on to do
something and you can't sure but i
mean it still say sure like archer
who's lorne it's chore got close to
the wall you have to go up
and do a thing i'm saying
i'm twenty three so can't see what
happened on the show and so you
gotta shoot fears that are lowered like
disco balls in the center of your
room to squabbles just starting to scope
when i make a p essay yeah
please um actually it's about secretly recording
people because i just saw this instagram
please do it
i thought was worth sharing the knowledge
because this woman realised she's being filmed
in her air bnb and the camera
looked like a phone charger plug where
you plug your usb into the wall
and you see there's a little um
microchip inside it dang and it's you
i'm taking a little microchip that's redundant
a teeny tiny little like their gigantic
microchip
but anyway you can tell if that
is when because when you turn up
over the the thing there's like a
little hole for like i mean this
is a friend of yours knows a
woman i saw on instagram and everyone
was sharing it associate she was recording
people know she was singing rbi and
realized oh after all you know spending
a few days there oh my god
she's being onboarded yeah the cops did
nothing about it because she
she's on that person's property and it's
kind of like the laws are confuses
things you can then that guy's air
bnb was removed but that doesn't really
resolve that it's crazy i mean these
microchips are so small you gotta we
gotta hit it or you gotta hit
in your house
he's got em hidden everywhere have microchips
gotten too small
nine eleven you see the nine nine
eleven gc that boston news report on
on video game machines popping up everywhere
in boston this is from nineteen eighty
two i think and it was ah
i think i think dan rather it
was national news it was a national
story but it was set in boston
like dan rather introduced it and it
was
like talking about how um there were
i'm getting the math wrong but there
are like a hundred thousand million one
hundred thousand people in boston and there
are forty thousand video game machines like
like the the ratio was that doesn't
make and and and they're like their
ratios
they're everywhere and so they were introducing
laws to get rid of them in
certain properties and then these people's excuses
were like you know old old women
have the right to go do their
laundry and a laundry mat and not
be ah not be being made fun
of by these punks who are sitting
there on the on playing the video
games
that was the reasoning for it i'm
like oh when i was a kid
i loved going to a laundromat to
play defender and make fun of old
ladies yep
look at i do it a lottery
but it was why are you watching
cause you're almost dead it was it
was never about hey these video games
are a waste of time or they're
sapping people's brains it was always about
the types of people who were congregating
playing yeah the bus it's always about
punk spikes every complaint in the city
hall is always about punks they're saying
i hate the queen
yeah and
this god save the queen at one
point they said it sarcastic oh is
that sarcasm i've never known with it
when do you think the queen of
england will die oh my word lauren
doesn't care who gets it after her
is it prince charles charles he's in
line but the the conventional wisdom is
that he's going to refuse the throne
why oh really i didn't know that
yeah that he doesn't want to be
king is why wouldn't he it's like
kid so i'm gonna be a few
more years he's finally going to start
his acting career
oh god i don't know well it's
strange it's seventy oh i guess somebody
was way older when princess diana got
married to him in the eighties it
seemed like he was going to be
king soon yeah everyone thought she's just
held on yeah longest longest reigning monarch
really yes she okay c b seventy
one and and she's ninety
four
dang but prince philip he doesn't become
any no no wait so if he
abdicates ninety charles who gets remains a
living corpse you ever sailed charles abdicates
then i guess it's one of the
one of the sons one of his
sons william yeah no harry loved yeah
wouldn't while harry would be he would
to be king i think if william
died right but i mean he's he's
out of the out of it he
left what about that married like woman
what about our friend from the luisa
rey and there have a netflix deal
do they live here yeah something moved
to canada they have a naming here
they both maybe get yourself a girl
who can do both
canada and the usa but what was
better friendly oliva nail wouldn't you say
oh no he's a spare it's like
it's the um i apologize to our
friends in england i'd know nothing about
the monarchy the line of succession i
believe goes generation to generation it only
moves laterally oh if someone dies
as if the if the air dies
right okay i live in montecito okay
wow i'm just telling you what's cool
see them i'd love to go visit
them
think dong but just a couple hours
away got the perfect thing she got
to marry printshop the royal wedding she
had a royal wedding she got to
be royalty and then they she gets
to be an actor she's always wanting
later do you think she's gonna continue
acting she was doing a voiceover in
a disney documentary about no offense nice
nice about pro elephants or anti elephants
it's pro what's the tree zones on
an expos a about the law is
there two hours of that documentaries based
on if you feel different parts of
the elephant you think it's something different
like a snake in a like in
a haunted house they did get you
don't they don't know that that older
of the terribly blind man three by
three times an hour
elephants sitting in a hundred house and
you walk in he goes a snake
and then you touch the next part
of grapes
yeah you're touching off the table
i think there would be cantaloupes
testicle crazy supposed to be highs i
oh okay
i can't imagine touching an elephant's eyes
and touching a bowl full of little
testicles
ooh i lead shook when he laughed
like a bowlful of little testicles
what is it though it's the you
the the feet you think is a
tree is that what it is some
like that look i don't know i
can strong because the snake and the
the ears are like my touching fans
i thought it was all animals but
i don't remember
yeah i don't know anyway it's a
great old parable it's a great old
pair you really should read it it's
so fun to g o p what
are you reading lauren you're on your
phone i was looking at elephant parable
oh the parable of the blind men
and an elephant originated okay so let's
see there's a cartoon and my breakdown
little faster okay an elephant
like the snake actually no it's a
tree stump what are you saying it's
like a sheath of leather you're all
wrong it's actually like a little furry
mouse is that the testicles so the
idea is if you're not seeing the
whole thing you don't get the whole
picture yeah exactly like if you're only
yeah and also the listener line people
are unreliable narrator
just stand on or off into any
wonder why stevie wonder is not narrating
any documentary rely on about him i
was in the standup is deon cole
standup clip those on on instagram stevie
wonder stole the girl he was with
deon cole yeah interesting they he brought
her to a stevie wonder show and
then she went back because
we want to talk to her and
then she came out of sixty needs
me and then she gave him cab
fares whoa for stevie gay needs me
i saw stevie recently within the last
couple of years in it was me
and a bunch of people and we
were like is that stevie wonder because
i think he shaved and we were
like we think it's stevie wonder or
it could be a guy who re
really looks like stevie wonder and it
was it took us about a half
an hour until we all decided with
seventy five percent certainty was stevie wonder
and and what was this person doing
ah saying superstition yeah on a concert
stage he was kind of waving his
head so i decide who is stevie
wonder concert it's that stevie wonder
that guy looks like stevie wonder am
i don't laugh at me is this
weird that cat looks like stevie wonder
i know i feel so crazy because
honestly that guy looks like see and
i don't i'm not trying i don't
know it might not be it's right
there the name but he looks like
him i wonder is it stevie wanda
wander so what was the man doing
remember
a fish called wanda where he's like
yeah wanda and then he's in court
and everyone is wondering why he said
that because he's not supposed to know
jamie lee curtis so because wanda wanda
i wonder what would be the i
don't remember that i haven't seen that
movie since it came out itself i
started watching it and i was like
this is what this is what does
do you think it was about a
fish i think i always thought it
was soap dish which i've also never
said oh i was so confused that
it was like do you think is
soap dish soap that oh shit for
the future
does lord because i can name so
many things i've never seen soap dish
i've never seen soap i've never seen
really a fish called wanda i guess
i did start to watch it but
i got bored soap was a big
thing when i was a kid it
was very scandal a show yeah and
we were we were like the only
kids that we knew that were allowed
yeah we were not allowed to watch
it and was
is it a drama comedy it's a
comedy comparative oh yeah apparently it's a
movie or a show it was a
television show but and it was a
once a week thing wasn't i'm like
yeah mary hartman
yeah it was because mary hartman was
like five days a week was oh
that's right that was weird it's not
weird um but ah it was a
once a week thing and billy crystal
played a gay character i think that
was a big reason why you know
oh yeah watch it yes yes yes
um but benson
is a spin off of it benson
was the butler benson doug benson is
this doug benson please oh right yeah
i know i'm wrong but all i
can think of is that ted danson
show oh dance yeah checker becker becker
did you ever see the video of
the guy i know this guy the
guy dancing to the becker theme for
an hour
know what is what is the becker
theme they didn't even tell you it
is the most generic sort of nineties
sitcom theme there's no words to thank
my weight my name exactly my atlanta
ga
by the way judge judy
her theme she's so fucking smart because
her theme is just public domain like
like classical music she didn't even want
to pay for things she says with
any mentor yeah it's like
oh becker
uh
ah i mean how can you listen
to this and nothing becker
um this is the judge judy theme
song there's no rick roll us i
won't didn't i do it to you
the other day yeah did over a
text chain okay this is the judge
judy why is it not playing oh
i need to turn up because you're
stupid
diana oh yeah
but wait
isn't that walter murphy's a fifth of
beethoven
well it's beethoven yeah it's not the
rewarding of walter murphy's okay beethoven if
that makes it like he he took
classical music and did i know what
he did
so i mean she paid for this
recording just like you know what i
liked that sit the beethoven do that
well i don't even think it was
a an aesthetic choice like larry david
doing the curb your enthusiasm thing where
it's like i like that piece of
music i think it's funny that's that's
a public domain i think those are
like rare like killer tracks
ks the curb music is all like
like you can just buy it online
why yeah yeah yeah yeah that's but
i think he just likes that i
think he liked that piece of music
because he was like that says what
i want to say about the show
judge judy i think doesn't want to
pay a royalty every time her show
is on the air so she took
public
domain music and paid someone like i
mean it's five hundred dollars to make
that recording of it i mean so
it's was essentially walter murphy's fifth of
beethoven without the thing that walter murphy
added to it right yeah i think
um attitudes f k throwing shay yes
had public domain yes tune because i
was here at on other things every
yeah so it was the thing
i'm for the sloppy boys sketch show
not always the birthday boys yeah my
god and there's also something else though
like even like an ad or something
that i heard i would happen to
us on the bang bang television show
where because because i was very involved
in the scoring of the thing like
i and we would constantly be looking
for music tracks i'd go this one
doesn't work let's find something
being sort of like this so i
spent a lot of time on that
i would get to know every track
that was used on everything and i
would notice them pop up in of
in advertisements a lot and wow have
i talked to you about um the
kate the baby's cry from arthur the
cartoon no this was like an obsession
of mine i'm clenching my fist by
the way oh yeah it's your
arthur finn nah um well when i
was a kid i noticed that the
baby always cried the same way out
every episode and then i started an
i i'm just noticed like why she
always has this cry it's like this
this this like little bit like wow
yeah and then i started if what
you're gonna put your chair in
paul is moving his entire body the
sun is killing me i um how
started hearing another things and then i
looked it up and it's basically like
the wilhelm scream but it's a cry
right so is it see this is
i got very upset at our editors
for putting the will because i didn't
know what the will haim scream was
what if anyone
there doesn't know is that it's this
one specific line from a cowboy movie
i think yeah from back in the
thirties where someone goes oh and then
you'll it's like a finn basically free
thing you can use so everyone who
is in is like an inside joke
and so we my editors put it
in three times in one sketch and
i didn't know what it was so
i just was like one scale yeah
so i was just like oh okay
they're like putting in screams then after
the episode went up there were like
huh we we used the will i'm
screamed for that and i was like
you gotta tell me stuff like this
right like because now there's like weird
jokes a joke you don't know yeah
i didn't i didn't want anyway yeah
but the baby thing is real and
i um someone i someone who we
talk about a podcast
it linked me to this there's like
a hey that baby while me see
if i can figure it out but
you know we can't have you on
your phone and paul moving share at
the same time there i'll have to
talk continuously or there is some sort
of are your toe paul does anyone
care get back on my can tell
us about your toe i just hit
my toe with the chair know there
is a um
sort of database of this stuff these
sound effects and like it's a whole
it's a whole world okay it's a
whole thing new let me hear to
shut your ears let's see if this
is right
ah
was that arthur maybe it is but
the sign exactly right but oh no
that might be copyrighted compare was shit
oh shit please don't sue us please
don't do us the sound effects ascap
please also there's a whole youtube thing
that i did watch at some point
about this cry and it's on reddit
you're bored
while i also did a whole body
tiger
you got deep into i did a
show years ago with ah karen kilgour
aref and eben schlyter called voice-overs the
top which was alive show that we
did
we did it sort of thrilling adventure
hour style but way before that show
where we held the scripts we did
like a radio play and it was
about a married um couple who were
both ah voiceover artist and amateur detectives
and so they use their voiceover skills
to solve crimes but all the crimes
were they were not they
they were like these delusional people and
they weren't real crimes um but we
had a lot of sound effects that
eben would play on on a laptop
one of the sound effects was a
door opening hey yes that i've heard
in so many things so many rays
honest
really really annoying when you start to
notice yes well and that's what i
mean about the cry like it's not
that i want to dive deep on
this it's that i can't help it
because when i hear it i feel
cuckoo bananas because i know it's that
baby from cartoon but it's also i
forgot real kid in a sitcom and
it's this it's just it's just forgot
what movie it was but there's like
a director like
spielberg who essentially said hey we need
to start recording our own sound effects
of like guns and stuff for this
movie because every movie had just been
using the sound effects library for guns
for so long then they were like
no it's like nineteen eighty four let's
record new stuff and it's so sound
like
nothing yeah well like so any movie
pre eighty five or eighty six just
has these like oh like slacks for
oh yeah you know i shot my
gun alright we need to take a
break shot my gun we'll be right
back
ah
we're back we're back we're back look
we are definitely back you can't say
we are not back if you said
we weren't you'd be wrong you're a
liar you're a goddamn liar what are
you like that why are you like
why are you like that did you
ever see the movie ah was called
ah
kurt russell's wife gets abducted by a
trucker overboard no
oh wait oh i thought you're talking
about goldie you mean his wife in
the movie yeah
i couldn't think of a goldie onward
corrosive wife i call any actress by
their husbands wife tim robbins girlfriend ah
um he and think about them never
getting married and goldie hawn and well
like galleons married
i think they are married but they
never did look it up lori look
normally
hey can i say laurie that's so
weird no they're not married they're not
married but she's been married twice before
maybe that's why yeah can i say
well i'm thinking of it a story
i wanted or a fact i wanted
to tell in our last episode when
we were talking about weddings and the
fact that how short it was right
after i see the thing that i
wanted to see
a oh no well i'm think you
wanna hear her run for never getting
married brought up the essure
i would have been long divorced if
i'd been married marriages an interesting psychological
thing if you need to feel bound
to someone that it's important to be
married if you have independent if you're
out of money in a sense of
independency like your independence there's something psychological
about not being married because it gives
you the freedom to make decisions one
way or the other who dat that's
called the hot it's called associate got
married right she's married two times and
she married done for him
because of all those reasons but it
should be you know that's the reasons
for me totally know it sounds really
like the only people present things like
that where it's like they know everything
that their nose in other words shakira
shakira won't marry her longtime boyfriend here
shakira well okay well we're going to
say um so in this movie actually
sucking
too bad go ahead talk about the
movie i'll tell the thing that i
was gonna tell while i'm talking about
the movie so this movie guy kurt
russell's married to this lady they're on
the road um their car breaks down
or something do duty you're just trying
to figure out what what movie it
is this trucker know this
this trucker of ducks the wife carell
says to get his wife back breakdown
breakdown thanks right down so he at
one point he gets in the cab
of this truck and he's got a
knife i think it's a fucking butter
knife that's not a knife
this is
so you talking to me he you
talking to me
e
one buddy drops the knife on the
floor of the cab the truck cab
the noise is so loud it's just
a butter knife that drops on a
carpeted car carpet did but instead is
like clang i dunno it's so fucking
loud like you expect the driver of
the cabinet what what is my cab
mike was doing it like like secretly
he accidentally dropped the knife and supposed
to be a tense moment like oh
oh you dropped the knife but the
noise is so loud you think the
tense moment is well surely that guy
heard that yeah it's fucking right it
was like reverberating throughout this truck i
think like the sound people go overboard
sometimes and i'm sure somebody got another
call mihai movie overboard not another one
the same one you mentioned because that's
right section when you know a pair
look i love right away she's amazing
just watched just becomes her yeah i
did too on your recommendation yeah i
love to have you see then yeah
i loved it i never seen my
whole life and it's funny because when
i would go to the video store
i was kind of freaked out by
the cover and like she's holding her
head in her hand or something um
so i never really got what it
was and it's so hilarious they're also
funny and it's
a real female comedy which i know
loved it it's good i went to
her house once you did where was
it like it's not aware why wouldn't
we rush limbaugh it's my it's my
question but i mean it's my films
i film film something with kerr russell
you can see it online it was
the we are the world thing and
so i went to their houses when
the second commissary you were like we
should
i don't know we are the worst
together ah
okay so so based on your house
really cool ah yeah looked
um how could it suck
ah so crete walls mundo perjure everyone
wearing straitjackets now looks like poo
i was locked up for fifteen years
there
getting critical
so bat based on my d j
how weird it was that he thought
my wedding was friday night so we
had eight um but um this is
a story based on how the d
will know just spin off story know
it just i thought of this i
was like oh i want to talk
about this way forgot so the weirdest
the weirdest lie i ever told to
two a turd and it was at
your wedding huh i do i do
quote um no but i was i
was trying to get out of seeing
my wife ah this this may y
o read sally he really goes oh
hi
he goes way over what he says
my wife it it really made me
laugh in a movie where he goes
it's funny now
hey i was like glad to have
you but i think he is really
brilliant his speech he made recently was
so amazing i shared that aware it
was but i thought it was really
interesting that the speech convention yes i
won't get to make a speech yeah
yeah alright everyone in the world tops
your choice and so every good civil
your own half an hour or two
ninety last forever cats here we go
give me a break i did once
do a bit where i just saying
give me a break over and over
again until people got mad and then
got happy again and got mad again
i kind of love those things yeah
it's online unfortunately oh check out r
of fortunately and jimmy carter's baby it's
cold outside similar also keep going until
we just
we we just saying i really can't
stay baby it's cold outside and then
i go i really can't stay oh
baby it's cold outside i really can't
stay here so we just keep saying
oh and then after that okay
um okay so the weirdest catch on
the weirdest lie and i and i
didn't know anything about weddings because i
think i was too young what even
is this thing but i didn't i
didn't know how they worked or whatever
but seems acquainted so this this this
girl i was dating was saying hey
do you want to hang out sunday
night when you were dating a girl
but you didn't know anything about wedding
things
you think you have to know about
weddings if you're dating engage upon kissing
you got to know about the wedding
part why because you are basically signing
how are we talking about i'm like
twenty five or something no mean you
didn't know about that what do you
what do you mean never been to
a wedding i'm not saying i don't
know what a wedding is what you
say
wow you saying scott you're all over
the place i'm saying he's my pho
jumbo took how many episodes and he's
very pissed pause and reasonably handsome okay
um thank you but you know how
you know how at our wedding there
were two people you're not to say
you gotta stop saying that because
people get comfy and cool up in
my wedding i remember how there were
i love when janey says my wedding
in front of me yeah yeah or
my house yeah oh boy that one
gets me i it's called the da
the bedroom my room oh camping in
my room
i don't know why
you know how at at cool up
in my wedding shoes to people who
wanted to bring women that they'd met
on facebook yes yes yes ah well
wedding crashers know they were people who
invited me they invited an error or
they they got a hold of us
and said hey can we bring these
two girls we met on facebook who
were flying in like to hang out
with us over the
over the weekend and i was like
no and they they were like well
we're just not gonna come then they
were like you know like unreasonable about
or unreasonable about it because they were
young and then they got older and
one of them got married and was
like oh by the way i cannot
believe i did that to you because
now they know about wedding yeah that's
what i'm talking about is i
like twenty five and didn't really you
know i'd been to weddings but had
never thought about them for myself so
i had no idea they had a
kid they are what are windows into
yeah i never thought about their the
months that they occur in or gene
vi but borat so this one was
like do you want to hang out
with me sunday night and i was
like oh
oh i can't i'm going to a
wedding and she was like a wedding
on a sunday night
and i was like oh shit did
they not happen on sunday nights i'd
never really thought about it like hood
it could but like no one ever
does yeah sure so i was like
oh yeah get there and traditional i
guess and they just thought sunday it
was cheaper i guess to do it
and then i got caught in this
like web of lies where i really
never
like no wedding no i wasn't going
to a wedding i was just flying
over till i was just trying to
come up with an excuse got the
premise yeah like to
i know can you imagine such a
thing happening on the show
well yeah do it you're sitting there
looking like i'm crazy when i'm talking
and you're the one who is forgot
now it is forgetting things crazy
or is being twenty five it's hey
if there's a wedding on a sunday
crazy you're not ya
you're when you say you're cute because
guilty i'm looking at the time right
now
ah how far in are we forty
two minutes or so we are but
yeah that's pretty good your audience is
screaming at their pods right oh you're
forty joe manager honey you're not know
but i wanted to tell the story
in order to ask you what are
some of the
lies that you have got and gotten
like caught because they were so noisy
jesus oh my god i feel like
when i was a kid
i feel like i lied a lot
i like it a lot as a
little kid but i feel like i
got away with it but i also
think nobody cared like i will watch
my nephew lie and i'm just like
that's such a lie it's so obvious
yeah but i don't need to argue
it i don't carefully so when i
think back to myself lying as a
kid i'm like i probably probably everyone
knew but then
then it didn't matter but i want
my big lie that i told to
people at school and it's so silly
that i did this because as you
know i have many names so that's
interesting enough we're talking two yells above
lucifer if he's so but when you're
at school and people like what's your
middle name but then i have a
story of myeloma
a middle name's laura my name is
dorothea lorna la gra blah blah and
then when i was in like first
or second grade i added in that
i had two more muslims my name
was dorothea lorna libra elizabeth ellen lap
kiss and i said that the nurses
were named elizabeth anne allen oh i
wanted to like the nurses when
your parents gave away my yeah and
they wanted to honor them yes oh
interest i had a fake middle name
story to oh what was it i
would tell people that my middle name
was five
was because i was born because i
had all five times i just whole
thing where it's i said my parents
after my older brother was born my
parents didn't think they could have any
more kids and then ah they had
i was surprise um and i was
born the fifth child five days late
at five in the morning and it
is that stuff sure wow i was
boring
i was the fifth child yes oh
okay not five days later well paul
learned the apfs did for five i
think like seven am something like that
two hours earlier and i said yeah
i've stood for five and most people
believed it it's such a strange believed
it live and why would you lie
about it that yeah i would imagine
being like because i didn't it was
also because i didn't i never prompted
it
always when people ask ray what does
the f stanford was it ally in
order to make yourself seem more interesting
or yeah it was also something that
just amused me to do when i
was a kid my friend told me
that there was a secret hole in
her closet or you don't use that
closet well thank god of course where
you can go
go to another land where where there
were like elves and like magical thing
where you get this fucking idea and
i truly believe i was like oh
my god it's cool it was this
your friend cs lewis yeah well i'm
sure she got the idea right but
at the time i was just like
i want to go in but but
the door goes away
what an amazing thing to like read
a book and then say i'm gonna
say that happened to me
i feel like kids do that all
the time i think i at one
point was humming ah the def leppard
song photograph or something as i had
to walk two miles to school so
i on the road a graph on
the two miles i remember the two
miles yeah i remember exactly where i
was what intersects
when i was at i was like
kind of humming photograph going full dog
raf i turned to my friend i
said i just wrote this song
because you're deaf leopard
i was like whoops i had a
roommate who was dating this guy and
they they have like sort of a
tumultuous relationship and then she dumped him
and then he wrote her ah this
he's like i wrote the song for
you and it turned out to be
an existing song right this is a
squid and the whale wow yeah plot
by the way which i love and
it was like yeah ravi kumar no
one in the well that i remembered
i was mortified so more because oh
we've all done it and it was
just of little book i just talked
about on our youtube show about writing
poems and and stealing verses i heard
him cop to that
yeah while isn't funny what like as
a teen yeah to like women he
liked and they'd be like oh my
gosh you're so you know incredible but
one of the songs that he did
that with was very strange oh yeah
it was song lyrics and he said
they were poems yeah and then i
found it very odd that somebody would
read that it was like a weird
song same effect by just saying like
i heard these lyrics and thought of
oh my god eggs i wanna be
yes that would be like was i
remember these two people in drama who
were dating and he wrote out the
ah or no she did it she
wrote the smiths lyrics ah it's not
like any other love this one is
different because it's us and and wrote
it and like presented it to him
and by the way he was
secretly gay and awe and dating this
woman as a cover and she liked
him more than you know it was
all like a very tour thing but
there was one that i just thought
of like a really weird lie where
when i was i think i was
five i think are like neighbor friend
had a playboy magazine
and like showed it to us on
the way home from school or something
jesus and my brother and i and
so i've yeah at five and so
like like we tore out one of
the pictures or whatever i was like
i'm gonna look at this later we'll
be back to ya later and i
remember like going like oh i can't
have my pair
fancy this i'll put it under my
shirt sure my t-shirt does a piece
of a magazine yeah like a page
from magazine put it under my shirt
and she'll never know but i'm wearing
like a tight t-shirt and so i
didn't even know what year that photograph
yeah and that's why i started singing
it every time i knew it makes
me nobody so i'm so my mom
says do you guys not know that
song oh what what is it who
is it it gets nickelback or yelling
i believe it is no thanks um
so my mom says what what does
that paper you have under your shirt
oh so tidied model
and i don't know how this worked
but i said homework ah and she
went okay and didn't ask to see
it why would i have homework under
my shirt but that was a close
that is before the merce had been
invented
what did you carry your things in
at school shirts i don't think i
don't think i even had homework until
i was like ten or eleven oh
you were that little oh my god
that's really i was five or whatever
oh i'd be looking at that paper
if you were five give me that
yeah isn't it weird i don't know
why she bought it i was thinking
that the other day like how did
she not just go do you ever
think there's times your parent
like are letting you get away with
it like when they're one hundred percent
okay this person's high know my password
that i can't deal with this no
my parents were very like if you
lie about anything
we're going to have a talk yeah
yeah so i mean holy hill pretty
much like i do think like engines
envy your yours anger there's something kind
of like nice about the idea that
your mom probably would not be the
case with her but if she kinda
was like i feel like there's something
secret right there well lemme lemme have
also know she would i mean there
were
they were the type of people who
are like searching my room when i
went to camp suisse you know like
i remember you expect that to happen
and you hid stuff for life here's
oh here's one that was terrible like
oh no that said fuck you snoop
i love that my mother would put
notes like that in his drawer because
i always would go in his drawers
no yeah and then i i mean
he would put one that was like
get out of this drawer or something
but then i love it get out
of this room one time i found
that i love just like what we
lived high times when your socks away
but i remember i went to ah
okay so the first time i ever
drank alcohol i drink at my friend's
house like a shot and i was
like yeah this is horrible
and but then i went to a
party when i was fourteen where we
had it must have been wine coolers
and i got drunk and i was
like oh this is okay maybe it
was fifteen sven i was like i
want to experiment with this so i
i hung out outside the grocery store
and i asked a guy like an
older guy hey do you mind buying
me
me a thing of wine coolers old
thing you know and here's the money
and two people said no go away
and then the third was like yeah
sure fine and i hung out outside
he bought me a six pack of
wine coolers bottles and james i remember
and i went back to my room
and drank them to kind of like
try to feel the effects of completion
i know this story and so but
then i i and and i couldn't
even drink all six the same day
or whenever i think i drank two
at a time i was like do
i feel drunk and my feet like
trying to figure it out but i
couldn't get rid of the the bottles
because my parents would have seen them
when they took the garbage
cans out or whatever so i was
like alright i'm gonna i'll put these
in like i'll leave these in my
closet and i'll think of them another
day i'll try to figure out the
solution another day why not think of
them another well also i couldn't sneak
them out anywhere because my parents are
always looking at me kid logic like
i'll just put that in here and
eventually that'll go there's probably a bomb
in your shirt probably sometime through a
sandwich
i wanna eat in my closet and
i found it it was just green
why remember my brother hid his bong
in the garage in a place in
the garage the other bongs yes specifically
ciders yeah
no but i but that was that
was a way to do it of
like don't keep anything in your room
because my parents would search the rooms
so it's like he kept his bong
in the garage somewhere but there were
probably a million ways around this problem
that i wasn't thinking of but i
just put them in and then i
went to summer camp and then in
the middle of summer camp i was
there for a week i all of
a sudden we
and oh fuck they're gonna search my
room my bed while i'm gone i
have those six bottles there and sure
enough like the minute i went back
i was looking for clues on their
faces they picked me up and they
were like okay we're gonna talk to
you by the way and oh my
god it's just a mun yeah just
another lie
eg huge long six hour conversation of
like am i an alcoholic am i
you know and i was like no
i just i got where did you
get it yeah where did you get
it how did you who purchased it
for you all this kind of stuff
and then are you an alcoholic are
you doing this all the time all
this it may just crying going no
i
try to walk inside it's just oh
so many of those types of ah
horrible conversations with my parents well i
think i've told you this one but
when my friend and i had a
party secretly when her dad went out
of town and then it was really
fun and this was in high school
and we threw all the stuff way
like four houses down in the towers
down
and then like the person who lived
there saw the receipt from domino's and
saw the phone number and address oh
what a fuckin so like you nar
can like it was let it happen
like google's garbage those o boxes i
have pizza yeah here we didn't beer
probably
mike's hard lemonade well yeah you do
do you just go like oh someone
used my trash can to throw it
i definitely wouldn't be thinking i'm going
to be a detective about this and
get to the bio how a kid
had a party but i also just
would think who gives a fuck yeah
who he's one single fuck that said
i i've never had a kid i
don't even know if kids do this
anymore do they do they
like hang out and try to get
adults to buy them booze is that
still i know there's like a sting
where
like cops will try to try to
do it for teenagers and then like
arrest the teenagers i don't know that's
so much that people i can't imagine
people still sitting outside of seven love
yeah waiting but i feel like there's
ways to get a hookup like now
yeah the internet or like whatever like
you know that's all my figure two
but i can't i
i've never so it's never happened to
me and i don't know what i
would do like if a kid out
yeah me to buy them i probably
would say no just because it's like
you don't want to get involved in
that yeah because you never know i
like you know you don't want to
be the person who's like buying like
contributing to but i think you go
i'll buy you some skittles
please come again
and and you get arrested for that
alright we need zuckerberg we'll be right
back
and we're back and lauren you have
a three cheer that you were in
i here's what i'm hearing sky extra
extra creature okay i'm a little stranger
but yeah i do this was based
off of yummy ponies suggestion i'm embarrassed
that's okay i'm not really i'm just
a
a little it's called indochina where are
you hiding
just like nervous it's called instrumentals each
person goes around and mimics the sound
of an instrument and everyone else to
try to guess what it is i
think this is like the fruit of
the loom the fruit of my loins
is fruit of the loom or we
tried hurry of fruit of my loins
this was vegetables so did you toothless
vegetables yes
alright scott make an instrument sound but
a memory leak
down one wheel and it's just your
wow wait one sounds like a note
that's what i think that's what all
of your arms is a good suggestion
yeah that's what i think is hard
about it and boom boom but don't
get to me
one notes were moving her arms one
no care where the timing just right
yeah i wanna go first sorry go
ahead
huh
oboe
oh wait no the big alien spaceship
in close encounters
this
wow
who knows that's why it's hard a
flute okay no okay i'll try i'll
try to add
ooh
you just singing so bicycle horn
doorbell
okay watch my face
watch why
watching your face is giving a hint
what is not i promise you are
you acting like you're blowing into something
are you imagining what what they if
they were alive i'd virtue
this whoa
krugman has us ah sort of emotion
that's that's that can ah
violin yes oh god god you nailed
it now it's your turn okay think
triangle sure
ah
huh
oh
no guitar nope
ah
do it again
base nope
keyboard nope
your watch my face rochford okay
oh no
here i don't like that
huh oh my
harmonica nope
i don't know true drum no drum
come on it's definitely a drum clarinet
no
is it a woodwind nope
this is a discussion ring no is
the string instrument there's strings piano ferryman
nope oh piano night grey clever what
very clever clever about what that's not
easy what do you think of when
you think of string ah well it
is not a viola i i didn't
say that it wasn't i said very
clever asshole now
oh ah cello no i don't oh
i don't know where tracing anything did
i stop you guys yeah does that
mean i'm winning yeah i guess banjo
oh company you know
okay my turn that's what i think
of what i think of ding ding
ding living bing bing bing bing bing
bing that's the song i mean mainly
mainly mainly mainly hey man i'm going
to hear somebody mentally mentally mentally ready
yes
some symbol no
sandbag falling in the ocean yes no
but brushes on the drums piece
o p sh o
ah you are close with a person
close to the cymbal hi-hat know that's
assemble tambourine yes o p sh plea
she a chance because i went and
then i was like well it really
has some music to it peach alright
one more for me
bow mean bass drum no no no
no no no timpani yes timpani
dna i can't think of the word
timpani without hearing ed mcmahon saying it
sure timpani do you know that is
yeah i don't know jerry lewis telethon
anytime they would talk about the total
of money they raised at mcmahon who
was the co-host or announcer would say
benet
and then they go during the amendment
and wow and and forty five million
eight hundred billion no three trillion dollars
chant that's not how it goes okay
let's hear it i am alright
oh because ooh yes well you didn't
one i did i gave yeah that
should this should be over this chanel
yeah she over no it's not
didn't say whether or not i'm just
saying it's not alright you want the
backup game do your time ah sure
okay this game is called sinking story
and it comes from toba roni each
host takes certain starting roy double row
the starter story and the others try
to go along with it by saying
the same word at the same time
so basically we tried to say
tell a story at the same time
so all three of us are trying
to tell a story okay sure you
could just i feel like the time
for one round yeah yeah
or we're sorry we're all trying to
say the same words at the same
time yeah but let's say the one
person will say the first okay i'll
say the first word okay moreover i
knew i was coming he yeah o
da mo as ah weirdo thus
slee he guys far as bow hey
more over he saw oh da
first hernandez like a good guy pullover
right that was fun who who kate
who came up with that toblerone toblerone
e you know moroni that's very difficult
with three people it's very hard yeah
and we're all spaced out too that's
true we are so far away from
each other we're on different property you
has to move your hat property hot
property another family name
so stars while it was normal i
think it's norm macdonald's impression of ed
mcmahon hot property
oh it's from star search yeah yeah
yeah i feel like it is i
don't know well yeah it was fun
this is fine was fun we had
fun um a little bit attention in
the middle from you yeah i felt
tense because of what you were doing
were radiating tension yes yeah we because
of your actions which i had a
great time performing and i enjoyed witnessing
alright we'll see you next time rangers
and focus three trims yes three team
usa on twitter and instagram since creatures
have their skill creatures to r e
to unheard episodes if you want to
sign up for stitcher premium there's two
more that you haven't heard unheard an
unheard
of their they're just sitting there so
sign up for stitcher premium and ah
get them and go fuck yourself okay
bye bye my
a