three
three da hae wow we yelled it
today as a very special yeah today
is a very special day da da
da da da
birthday it's paul perry hi i'm paul
birthday do you need a cake i
have ton it's come to my birthday
cake warehouse everyone just assumes it's my
birthday my last person anyway oh wow
name birthday good last name so good
just her birthday mrs birthday like some
people have lessening i think some people
have
lesson christmas yeah is changing yeah oh
hollywood of course oh of course hopefully
the smile jimmy chicago it's really your
last name is hollywood jimmy chicago
i'm just making people have chucky new
york ronald oklahoma
if there is a ronald oklahoma out
there please be our fan we want
to hear from your last name is
birthday colin right now for a big
price call and right now
send us a letter while you dictated
on the phone hi everyone welcome to
three-term welcome to three of mine paul
it's my birthday i'm scott it's not
my birthday and i'm worried it's not
my birthday but it recently was so
kind of feels like it is true
although you know what six days ago
is my birthday and i'm like it's
very much not my birthday anymore it's
over we all say happy birthday to
you
i don't know i know i did
what do you mean did you say
happy birthday did i know yeah yeah
yeah i run the chain or some
yeah yeah i do everyone acknowledged my
special day that feels like a million
years does it was literally six days
ago and it feels like i was
i was one hundred years ago one
hundred and ten now oh my god
i was ten last you look great
thank you so huge ten last week
yeah
yeah we've always assumed you are in
your twenties thirty so i was twenty
years old i think when we first
met and it's like a one two
three shorter thing yeah you were like
an old soul yeah for sure zero
yes yes um wait what the fuck
okay so two entities on lawrence birthday
wished her happy birthday
on instagram two and two oh one
was ah star trek on parallel plus
yes because i'm on that show would
show star trek and star trek lower
decks of drink
lower deck okay we're decks and i
play a blue creature and sinus pandora
you just track every single person who's
on that show and wish them happy
birthday cares so that was what he
was worried about well because it was
it was ah star trek on plus
and also dynasty typewriter the theater that
you guys for me yeah yeah now
as of this recording yeah neither star
trek on plus yes okay yeah not
only that but star trek four
a motor takeout before most people yeah
early in the morning go star trek
on plus and the main star trek
account they were lying on me you
know what sartre was mourning for my
birthday elements was the first post i
got and i was like they're on
top they're on top of this shit
wow appreciate that and i respect it
and i'm an an delorean
excuse me i'm the guy washing florian
definitely don't say that i'm an i'm
an an dory named um jen that's
right okay and i'm doreen gen and
you're blue and you have antennae yes
so star wars has blue people yeah
mentioning stores we're talking about star trek
because that ah sige cad bane is
blue that's true countering is blue i
wonder if they're the same
race yeah for sure
um yeah because they're both but listening
on like but here's landing rock good
point so as goodfellas was really blue
in that
um but here's the thing as of
this recording i've yet to be wished
a happy birthday by dennis to typewriter
and what i like him what's happening
now is that there's no way they
can hear this no this will be
they can't this guy tip to do
that they're still in there still in
the running to wish me happy birthday
but here's my theory
star trek has a list of every
single person who's on it and what
their birthday is and they just roll
it out every single day it's like
a checklist for whoever runs that account
yeah dynasty what else do they have
to do dynasty typewriter happened to see
a bunch of people wishing lauren and
happy birthday that day no let me
tell you something maybe dynasty typewriter puts
out a calendar every oh they do
have everyone's birthday on it and people
first of all they
will post about should i look now
yeah look yeah you gotta make sure
he got cancer now and forever hold
my peace yeah forever hold your pee
oh no that's horrible yes penis dna
xy how did they do they wish
you happy birthday in stories it was
a story huh wasn't a main if
you get a main i'm gonna
fuckin go crazy
this is what i immediately sameness one
on the whole birthday i so i
sent those to her and i said
okay if i don't get one of
these i'm fury it was really threatening
and it actually kinda ruined my day
can i just say i'm haven't done
yet
and i'm sorry to hear it jason
over they still yeah certainly not over
it is merely ten twenty four am
i gotta say neither of those places
wish me a happy birthday on my
part that makes so much sense it
does make a lesson
um can i just say really didn't
wish me happy birthday the pentagon i
didn't hear anything from the queen oh
i have some bad news breaking ah
my birthday it was still good news
can i just say
still good news good news quick life
value
she's she's gonna die about five days
later yeah today and then one day
bed can i just say really quickly
that really quick how quick oh i
don't wanna say it to you want
to time you know i don't because
i want the information to be retired
i'll say it once and i'll say
it faster okay hold on i'm good
time you time you saying if the
regular way okay this is good and
then we'll see how fast you can
do
don't press lap alright read please no
press a lot even though my last
name is huh alright here we go
and yeah okay paul and i have
a show coming up and it's on
september twenty fourth dynasty typewriter you can
see it in-person or you can watch
a live stream and you can watch
the live stream anytime you want and
you can go with the tickets dynasty
typewriter dot com
that it yeah so you weren't talking
to us you were talking about listener
yeah you said it like oh i
have something to say to both of
us so you know when someone's listening
they might think that i they would
be interested in whatever i'm gonna say
it is very hard to tell because
lauren never looks at us when she
try to look up the whole time
she looks up the whole time we're
recording alright that was thirteen and fellow
i'll second sort of like a
nope situation um okay alright now i'm
asking you to it ready okay and
go pawn image analyzer is ah two
point seven five a big part of
speaking quickly is getting your tongue in
there about
paul and michelle everybody for today's neighbor
to watch live sports online or watch
in person
now can i tell you about my
fantastic team yeah okay this i cannot
bless you whiteness nice i don't care
i want god to bless you i
don't want that for that it was
a cough i don't want that for
that
i this is the best birthday gift
i could have woken up to wow
history i don't want to say it
held back i held many last night
i was hanging out at your house
lord wow you and mike wow and
holly oh and holly and i were
getting along like nobody's biz wow she
was i was making her
laugh and she was talking wow she's
like i would say things just lying
repeat down the road laugh aw don't
ruin this for me she's so amazing
but then i got to take care
of her for a night wow hey
do you want to
i didn't do or even better three
years
three years i just gotta go ya
gotta get cigarettes soon to get a
massage can you take her for three
years
and then um we were i was
taking care of her we were playing
this sort of virtual reality video oculus
haha well it was like a red
dead redemption kind of thing but there
was no shooting you just had to
find things kissing so she's like
like instead of shooting you're like look
i love you scott what who had
the dream because i don't know anymore
martin luther maybe it was oh okay
i go oh he has already had
a dream you so you had the
barry m l k but this dream
teamers shah died dream
and so then we were playing red
dead it was like the end of
the dentures having so much to learn
yes and she's finding all the things
and then later we were we were
at ah like whatever place we were
staying at and we were in the
the this was not your house you
are no good as a
a second locations like some other place
and then she was asleep in the
bed with the covers up and ah
and so the people that manage this
place these two women came over to
me and said did you read to
her and i said yes he did
yes and they're like okay alright just
wanna make sure
you're not just playing video
exactly yeah yeah yeah yeah look at
some paper it was the best there
was the best rio que na team
ah that's so nice it made me
very happy
yeah she's changing so much fun i
saw on one of your private stores
yeah umm anyway private stories that show
oh i mean ah i think i
dream this do um the dreams and
you reply recycle around my eyes
she was like being funny she is
being funny she's like doing yeah she
knows that she's doing good laugh yeah
yeah yeah really bit um where she
first was like sipping water and then
like going like like spitting it out
at me and then and then she
just like put her face up like
my name i kinda like grandpa face
she knew it was funny it was
so cute it was ready
like cognizance that her parents are improv
royalty you know i think she does
gather you know um i think that's
there she i mean she honestly thought
about it and we laughed last night
to do an improv show mike and
i together or first nights we've only
had a few outings yeah yeah and
this was very exciting actually i was
kind of like wow i can't leave
doing this i'm tired and then we
had a fun time and it's a
really fun set was just holy shit
no this was um convoy show huh
we got like twenty minutes yeah it
was nice and there's really fun and
i was like like you know i
don't even know my point just that
it felt good to be on stage
it felt like an improv show you
know it's been hard with all the
theaters being shut down
down and now we're finding these new
little theaters and now um you know
what some of our places we coming
back but like the to be at
these kind of random spots this is
john s theatre oh um and so
that was cool it was like a
little bit a new place like doing
something different and with my can we
have fun and that's great yeah and
did i'm glad did you warm up
like doing zip-top saw we
zip zap zoop yes um we we
no we um we literally did nothing
we watched just walked out on watch
the team before us and then we
got up yeah wow that's a good
warmup to watch the team before it's
just fun and you kind of go
here's what we're working with this is
kind of suggestion they got this they
like this i think we're okay with
just how we're gonna get to see
you actually do it though you know
that's the thing
it's like i need her to see
that because i want i need her
to understand so as soon as we
can get her to theater you know
it's hard because her bedtime is right
around the time i go on stage
so um we'll just have to see
yeah that's that's definitely imminent yeah it
isn't i do think about the both
of you of like how do you
explain what mommy and daddy does for
a living like you know i mean
it is weird how do you explain
what mommy and daddy is it's weird
because i think being an actor such
a weird job for a person and
podcast normal podcaster i don't think you
can you explain what's happening right how
do you explain what we do mommy
has to go into a room and
talk with her
tell stories play a game at the
end and you're not trying with me
ah do you think it'll ever be
three and a half them with her
o three dom and a little lady
yes and the ghost in the corner
no ho garber cut out of scope
oh okay
i can't wait yeah um for the
cardboard cutout yeah yeah everything else is
like seven seven i ordered that while
you leave and then there's the cardboard
and with the whole no talking oh
see also we can do it every
walk to it
put a pencil throwing okay sure
i know you can get behind it
and then you can pretend you were
talking you put your lyrics you want
to do we all do whatever we
want oh okay okay but she has
no lips it's just a hole and
then you put your lips through it
yes okay yeah yeah yeah okay actually
more things like that i would probably
grab like zucchini and just shove it
down
oh my god speaking of zucchini wow
what paul i think you've seen my
instagram i got to meet that tortoise
idea i heard about this i don't
i don't know what now who is
he or she and what is the
sits were they right for our friend's
bread and dana one day they find
in their backyard they just moved to
a new place which is very ah
full of wildlife there's like a bear
that terrorists i know brewed by the
way that is actually too scary
buying some video but i now live
near where a bear goes i think
that's not okay the woods yeah yeah
oh okay they both go there but
yeah the both shit in the woods
right side by side why does it
own the bears keloids is that a
joke
some people it's like never mind i
don't know it and i'd love to
learn know you don't want to know
my story okay that it's based on
two different things does a bear shit
in the woods is the pope catholic
and people conflate them and say does
the pope shit i knew it's happened
isn't that funny and aren't we having
fun i love it and i think
people when they make jokes they're so
funny and it's so good
and i would have asked holly's first
joke that and she's just she thinks
you came up in the woods if
she came up with that actually be
impressed anyway what if she came up
with it and fifteen i still wouldn't
be impressed and i think you know
good mom yeah i think you have
to go like you're funny you know
it's just he came up with that
like if you didn't if you never
heard that
then i'm then i would be like
obama you didn't come up with that
what if holly who's that from you
remember obama said you didn't build that
oh yeah what if hollywood would have
holly i wanna know more says it
and says i came up with that
but you can tell she's lying then
i'll go you know what you like
your eyes are darting back and forth
like yeah i just made that
great joke i just made
i still think that would be funny
though that would be funny actually i
tell you when i was like ten
or got it has to be like
twelve i think you did yeah and
then we have ah there's there's absolutely
no chance you haven't yes but i
was i was i remember i was
biking home with a bunch of friends
from junior high so i had any
covered your eyes and
um i sat hey guys let's all
shut our eyes i sang a song
that was like so had some of
the lyrics to deaf leopards pyromaniac but
i changed them or something i romania
pyromania or playroom while he says i'm
a pyromaniac so i maybe it is
yeah in the albums by romania yeah
but
many things about him being singular yeah
but hi romania yeah go the album
ty very model of a modern me
radioshack it works scans but i think
i sang i sang like one lyric
from pyromania and one of my own
or something i said i came up
with that in my friend went oh
pyromania oh yeah
show me the lie once wait what
but you are trying to fool them
no i just in my head i
kind of came up with the song
but i was like i think one
of these lyrics is kind of familiar
whatever oh so you thought you made
it up i've stood up blind as
a kid i would just say i
like remember lana yeah i remember lying
yeah wait so let me talk about
the twa yes
so i say it in french no
way
so he wanders he wanders into their
yard this massive tortoise that is actually
quite alarming it's what asshole funny and
i learned this from doing the neighborhood
listen because we do all these next
posts it's such a common thing that
these big slow creatures run run away
ended up in people's yard they're packed
their pets yeah they don't want to
be like i always wonder that about
if our if our doors were open
would our dogs just go like fuck
it i have added here and just
like wow maybe on purpose yeah but
you know what i mean like if
they're like this is my fucking chance
i think they would escape i think
they would be like
if i want to see the great
wide world yeah also want to go
home and get food no that's happened
but i just bought it but you
know what i mean like but i
do tortoises they actually want to leave
and don't want they don't do like
a new homeward bound but it's like
a dog a cat and a tortoise
and they have to wait for the
tortoise constantly yeah you know many animals
were harmed in the making of that
film
oh i thought it was milo and
otis okay
what about a homer down where it's
a turtle a scorpion went down i
thought it was my own notice because
it was filmed in japan and they
don't have the swan maybe both they
did not i don't know what they
have now but they did not have
the same as y benji went to
japan did he go to japan i
think it's another everyone heirs did the
bad news bears definitely wait hey we're
all
all harmed there the whole point of
benji goes japan is benjy goes to
japan yeah it's like the tree it's
like a two hour movie he like
goes to the airport tourist and goes
through customs ah i think you're um
i think you're right or do you
after doing my day approximately thirty seconds
of research homeward bound um that's the
michael j fox yes sally field and
somebody i didn't remember yeah rally field
somewhere around britain
xy wrote and i think mom from
forrest gump the mom from mrs doubtfire
the mom from lincoln the future mom
from j mom of the flag ah
i loudly linked to field is incredible
mrs fields we call her sally fields
sally field but when she makes the
cookie she's mrs fields since you put
two people in the basket girl she
gets the hood yes
he's amazing that clip from mrs doubtfire
when she's like the whole time the
whole time the whole time you know
so good levels a little that's just
the part the moment but launched over
and over again i watched yeah like
china person is going like clips and
it's a it's a clip that they
love movies are essentially clips
yeah they're all a bunch of girls
all put together in order yeah and
i watched that one clip a few
times you know right right i meant
i watched soap dish for the first
time i saw yeah that's right we've
talked to newbie i'm talking about me
on my new told me i should
watch some show yes so you guys
stand by it you gotta stop but
let me say this because i don't
think i said this before see eh
every scene is like one second too
long oh no you didn't wave the
wedge director that's so i'm sure everyone
knew a one thousand one and it
could have been cut off exactly yeah
it's all great people but the direction
of it sometimes because i'm sally field
who is great yeah sometimes is like
comes off as very pami in a
bag
good way because they didn't cut she
probably yeah because that's a good lesson
for actors like always do it won't
stay in at one second longer than
you think you should but that's what
you shouldn't do because because it's in
there and use it said bailout one
second before and go alright so she
yeah yeah i'll cut all your small
pathetic ten-day kind of cold cuts oh
god i uncle cuts
give me some bible what have you
ended every scene thing i went cold
gas
but
yeah okay we gotta cut some of
these like merkel we can't cut all
of them i'll cough like brando in
apocalypse now like if you're trying to
buy the flow of the you are
trying to fuck with the director you
hated them so now every time you
you did something you just putting the
island coconuts and there's never let them
have failed take except for the one
you lie
liked yeah guys we have to take
a break i don't call cool that's
i want cold gattaca dot lie my
other brothers can't deny they wanna go
walk soon with the cold cut wasted
cold cut waste were back and around
having your face who gets wrong in
your face so guys this is the
first episode since we all came back
you're petting them nice know there's your
betting though maybe there's a bug that
i'm trying to kind of bug i
couldn't tell if it was a what
do you call adventure saga or a
bad one fruit fly
they're all bad okay was it a
fruit fly this is the first all
bugs are bastards
maybe absolutely i agree with great for
rhyme schemes oh but great for bugs
and ladybugs and lightning bow wow not
too good bugs there's one way of
jail maybe some lightning but you can't
say there are some good bugs yeah
you have to say all don't let
a few bad bugs spoil the whole
bug barrel know you're real
oh
he's like ladybugs lives matter it's like
okay dude we're gonna have this conversation
every day i guess it's your breath
in bug one get away with it
thin bug line around my ankles fighting
me know i know i kind of
bond check out one right on my
real nar this morning we didn't use
to have a man we used to
have like it was like within the
last ten years right yeah it was
that because
bunch of lumber from china right we
talked about this week we harry thrilled
there were no mosquitoes anyhoo anyways so
this is the first time we've seen
each other since we were away for
six weeks and yeah we were spraying
the same topics i know so so
tell us how chicago was more chicano
well my god your coffers are long
fantastic i had the best time
i was shooting a movie called another
happy day you can follow it on
instagram at another know this is a
sequel to happy day yet simple happy
happy days but it's just another one
more mister cee yeah i do and
it's back in time great-granddaughter it's basically
she time travels to now and so
she's young but now and she's like
video game
james exactly this is a lot like
that jukebox that fancy would do it's
a postpartum depression comedy and little that
is
fuck yourself but no but i feel
really exciting that um i feel very
proud of what we did it was
really fun i you know course you
have no idea who's going to turn
out but but for me it was
a good experience and i got to
work with my friend from high school
who is the writer director she's a
couple of years older than me but
i always admired her i didn't know
that aspect yeah
yeah know that's why we shot in
our hometown and she is such a
great director so it was really fun
i had to like cry a lot
and do a lot of emotional stuff
but i really enjoy what did you
think about us yeah just like how
much
um and then i just enjoyed being
home for the whole time it was
really nice a lot of time for
holidays build my family yeah and i
liked being in chicago i like working
in chicago and driving around and getting
to go wow my favorite spots and
and see how much everything's changed and
that was fine how much are weird
well like where i was like where
i first did improve what i was
in high school it was like such
a close place it's a fucking fun
shop it's so it's a really original
location was bought out by a huge
um what's the word february
this like company buy the entire block
basically made like these cuckoo block of
fudge
there's condos and there's shops beneath and
this is around the corners it is
around the corner from where baseball is
made it's like common space oh yeah
rayfield is right there and then there's
kill one's fudge and it's pretty depressing
because it's so corporate now like that
area was very it was like full
of cops handle large thing and it
was
like bars and just like raucous and
like things start with b a r
yeah and it was i it was
just a fun c type barbarella you
don't mean like his barbershop the streets
are all like people are christian people
but i know when you stumble into
an improv theater and then watch like
amazing performances and it was
like a special time and then to
see it to totally nothing is kind
of crazy course they open a new
io like in a different area within
the last few years but that also
now has been taken over by new
person so it's all like everything's changing
so much with that whole world absolutely
weird um but that area bummed me
out because it got so corporate in
like a really of course everything if
you haven't left and what has stayed
the same i think it would have
you know if i brought my energy
to that um but anyway it's really
fun to home you could chain yourself
to some buildings you know what i
mean i think i would have you
know that's definitely my type of protesting
yeah um how in yourself how is
your um it was good did you
miss me ah we did miss you
yes
ah sharp sharp-eyed fans will know that
i wore my loren lukas pin i
was very flattered by that thank you
i don't have one so i didn't
wear wow
rolf dot corn never sent it to
you but corn dot com oh my
god everyone's too obsessed with the corn
kid we've got i know my second
videos diminishing i didn't see the second
one i'm going i'm seeing the first
one don't know who he first is
great there's a little kid loves charming
he's his sweet little boy i don't
want it he calls it what did
you call the tube with the knobs
ah fine it's great huh huh
i have i have talks like one
of our characters i've a startling story
from the knobs thank you oh what
he calls out adjusting the and by
the way how's your freaking ankle oh
well i get the results of the
mri after week and what do you
mean i came back they checked it
out there like you need an mri
i may need
i was totally thinking there'd be no
problem with your ankle no so i
love for the show so come back
ah not for next next week because
we're doing we're taking it right after
this one but for our season premiere
i'll have surgery probably a huge news
about my ankle oh so you're saying
us motherfucker on the tour we had
to carry him onto the stage
ys does that yeah well but this
time he he really liked gave it
a day yeah yeah anything cool just
flopping around yeah yeah you're hearing me
like jesus and jesus christ yeah hey
no godspell oh my god this i
don't know i noticed homeward bound today
depends on production um but we had
a good time i have a startling
stories homeward bound ma notice situation
i've a startling story certainly story from
the road you can't conflate homeward bound
by its but you can't complain you
can't conflate godspell with jesus christ superstar
sing little easier to conflate i think
i think that is shit moves around
hammerman shirt walking around and talking i
just meant from the cruelty apart okay
fine
yeah because my own notice is so
they went through like five miles and
four odors because yeah like they drowned
them right there like threw one off
a cliff anyone did a bad deck
what did what a horrific into the
day when they may have felt really
sad i'm sure a lot of people
were if narrated by dudley moore dick
ish from santa claus the movie that's
correct wow
okay so startling story from the road
clause you've got a startling story from
the row all you know this one
oh so i won't be startled but
i haven't i haven't told this on
any podcast so are you guys excited
to get a debut i'm extremely at
rest so when i get startled this
going to be huge okay so extremely
addressed we were on the east coast
and i don't know if you were
tracking some of the videos for this
half and i just kind of pop
in and see are they having fun
okay okay seems like they aren't kinda
hurts yeah back off a little bit
doing so huh yeah no modifier yeah
oh so nobody's saying my name or
anything okay that's cool man yeah no
um the audiences enchanting thinking it's me
and thank god i do
you think that in chicago when i
introduced clarissa
okay i thought it was going to
be really wanted to do the show
and i was i could not get
coven it would done the whole thing
yeah so ah try you try as
hard as you could to get out
to get coven yeah yeah so we're
we're on the east coast and if
you saw one of the videos in
hartford connecticut is that right ryan gaul
switched pants with an audience idea
i do not go her connecticut bonus
two way where did we go where
did we have ted leo ah that
was in providence providence providence rhode island
rhode island oh okay write um you
might have talked about the sun staff
hawkins hey er no i think i
heard about the pants thing okay no
this is a story i've never told
before okay on any podcast i told
it no he didn't
okay he doesn't know that
this is my story story you know
it but you kind of went huh
yeah alright so i do this second
wave startled me as you gave no
got no reaction from okay guy by
the way i'm gonna find the picture
while i'm talking okay i don't know
where i want this pants off no
it's not but so so it was
that where the the pants happened yeah
don't underpants oh providence ri providence yeah
okay so i think so we get
to profit
science is that where we know little
state in the union maybe it was
maybe it was up in in portland
maine portland man i remember say no
no okay so no he did that
in in in in wherever it was
providence because tos there yes okay so
we did that shout out to ted
his birthday was yesterday happy birth never
forget same with ben lee never
forget yes so we did that and
then we musicians birthday september eleventh so
we did that and then we we
aimee mann's was the never forget fuck
you both it's an elaborate gown
you oh well you know why he's
trying to get a chill it's actually
oh it's actually a fuck you bow
i can't believe i'm joining him fuck
you bow and the subject of the
champ fuck you bo
yeah so the next day we get
on what we think are two trains
too and instead it was an airplane
we think our two trains yes we
thought we were taking two trains like
you're not at the same time that's
everyone's no we're not going to be
straddling the interracial what you said motherfucker
you said we got on what we
thought to train obviously i'm picturing you
both in to train someone was saying
the other you're waving you're saying hope
i see you there i know this
is hurting you like
trade routes how you spoke i don't
want to do the show da kid
oh no i can't even do one
more episode oh really oh no we
haven't gone try to get all the
money oh no one hundred or so
yours no i want to give your
money huh
oh because it's your fault no okay
we get on a train not the
h train paul warrington new york city
but we get on a train and
then we think we're getting on another
train and it turns out what paul
to be a bus instead i'm sorry
i can't believe this i'm sorry how
did you get on no no no
no no
i am shocked i didn't realize that's
the story you were telling like no
that's the beginning of this haul but
i'm already shocked you got on a
train but it was a bus now
i don't understand how it's physically possible
know i'm syria today if i make
yeah we had we were supposed to
have a connecting you're just to train
to be an asshole no actually because
once i started talking i understood but
yeah
yeah so we thought we were gonna
get off one train and onto another
train but hey you get off there
like actually it's that bus over there
you're like oh shit there's about ten
minutes before we got off the first
train someone looked at their ticket more
closely and said this says bus and
who bucked it well i don't want
to throw anyone under that bus that
we took but it was the baker
um so anyway ah so so we
get on this bus it's it's and
and the bus ride was fine i
think it's actually quicker i guess then
a train was from where to where
from ah boston to is that right
to providence was at boston that we
went back to yeah yeah we went
back to boston then we went up
to yeah ah
maine portland no actually i i don't
mind the bus but the bus the
train is fun the train is fun
and the bus the bus the wears
you out a little best is marty
are sick you know yes is more
car so you don't have as much
like the train you have so much
more room and everything so anyway we
can just click and clack and true
we get on this cool get on
this bus we get we get to
the hotel paul and i are exhausted
but this is one
of the rare days that we have
like time for a nap before we
have to go because most of the
days we would get into the city
and then it was like okay let
paul and i would have to get
dressed into the q and a right
after and also sign a hundred posts
yeah wow so this was one of
the rare cities where we got there
early enough quick sidebar yeah i meant
to do this i'm so mad that
i didn't i wanted to do a
video like a time lapse
most of us sky posters get to
these venues and was just the two
of us sitting side by side
inciting the posters assembly line while we
would sign them at the same time
yeah and then and then slide them
aside and i meant to get a
video and i'm mad that i didn't
do i'm sorry we could still sign
email while i can imagine that actually
really well
so in any case we get to
the hotel in maine providence maine right
yeah yes and i get into the
hotel and i just basically like take
out my sound machine get my sleep
mask on take off my shorts throw
him on the ground see my hands
conk out for an hour right yeah
and then
then the alarm goes off i get
up i go to the theater it's
really you know scrambling to get there
right and i hate that feeling of
like oh snap i think i do
show yeah do the show comeback conk
out again until the morning i wake
up in the morning and i'm like
fully cognizant and aware for the first
time and we have to
yeah we have to go to cleveland
the next day right but we have
ah some time and i'm looking around
the room and i'm just packing stuff
up what happened and what do i
see on the floor of the hotel
room oh god what's it going to
be pants a pair of
grey sweats
that you don't like that i do
not own no no no no no
no no and this is why i
bring up the pants that rights swapped
i thought that he snuck into the
hotel i wouldn't think could a pair
of pants on the floor of my
hotel oh wait that's not what happened
these were left over from the previous
guest i noticed them but i didn't
notice them because
someone came in or somebody told with
you yes silk tail styles yeah cocktail
style duck and they took their pants
off too we ever been snuggled with
ducktales style it's when you have three
in a bed
but
i've never been to hell to hotel
room with something like this just plain
an enduring dirty pair of sweats has
been lying on the ground that's actually
so fucking gross that's really berlin had
a really scary story where she was
staying in edinburgh and like she had
something appear in her bathroom during her
state where it was some there appears
a pair of boxers
hers appeared and like it was not
there ever she's like i would have
seen that right i was there for
days and then they're there on the
hanging on the bathroom door something and
she was like this is so unsettling
and she switched rooms and was right
it's like what does this mean like
it's just i have a story like
this to not happen to me it
happened to my friend marco
jackson we with the thrilling venture airy
went to australia and we this was
our first stop we checked into this
hotel um and we're exhausted because it's
a you know flights a million hours
but you throw a shrimp on the
barbie i'm gonna go we had to
yeah i mean you know i had
a giant barrel veer
is this in australian sydney but you
and mark winther the thrilling adventure hour
oh sorry i know that we went
there when you were
you know when what a great time
it was anyways so we so we
check into the hotel and um the
ah mark tells us the story then
when he gets in the elevator to
go up to his room the elevator
was like kind of stalling out like
it was going up and then kind
of stopping and then going up and
so i'd like never do it again
on this thing he
gets to the room and he calls
down and he says hey just so
you know like this elevators messed up
you know so you want to check
it out and like oh well thanks
to this thank you very much exactly
so he takes a nap
then he wakes up and he finds
this ah spongy yellow lightbulb like ah
like a dog toy almost
yes like a stress ball sort of
yeah exactly that says like
you know the elect you know something
about the electrical department of the hotel
or something like that thank you whatever
and he's like looking at this thing
and it came from weasley he he
goes right that off while he was
he goes down to the front desk
and he says hey ah this was
in my room while i was somebody
put this in my room and i
was asleep and prisma
that's like yeah that was the electrical
department they wanted to say thank you
for letting us know about the elevator
know why the hell he said i
was asleep and the first counter is
like is that is that not good
like think about it if it was
you and you were asleep and range
person in the room happy i use
sleeping it really makes me think about
like hell to get anything too yeah
yeah that's fucking weird but yeah that's
why you gotta do the latch and
so our mutual friend our mutual friend
julie after that story bought like a
bunch of lightbulbs like that
to like plan did she never did
it oh but then mark and i
did a show in portland and she
gave i said you gotta give me
one
and so i had to leave before
he did and i put it in
his coat pocket in the in the
dressing room and was like i pray
to god he doesn't discover this until
he yeah tell right end he didn't
and it was great huh and what
did he did he think it was
you was oh yeah he did and
he sent me a picture of it
he goes you son of a bitch
and i'm like whoa where'd that come
from
i instantly shifted blame to
like just like a fuckin carla she
she must have done this she had
a connection with wow and i was
like great
wow so is he going to listen
to this and know it was you
know okay when you get to listen
to this area sit oh my god
i'm so like the one nobody listeners
i don't think josh puts him out
i think he just like oh by
the way we're really gentle and cheese
oh yeah kevin's not here we're back
with josh we're back with josh we're
back with jaw for today
only for today but only for today
show only photo h only photo h
only if any other stories from the
road
whew
when that was about it we had
three oh can i tell a story
from from two second hand
holly loves the beach ah she loves
the sand and hello you are getting
more and more perfect when you like
about it she has no fear i
thought i just was worried oh she
might like those teachers same winter she
was wearing a no fear shirt and
like big dog pants or something but
she was like
she you know the first day we
went she was like touching the sand
on my lap and like not crawling
around and the next time just crawling
all over the place going right into
the water right back out with some
chicago or the aspect oh so there's
a chick oh yeah so aligns the
whole city i know the lake does
i didn't realize that there was like
it has beaches beautiful
beaches and so does chicago um and
that's why the motto of chicago's relax
you're at the lake yeah we see
it all the time their state flag
is one of those posters it's like
ah leah lake vibes is our state
flag like i'm um but she loved
santos so happy it was so huge
you know any sand
she ate some of the first time
again she didn't do it the next
time that's like pretty amazed so now
do you feel like you have to
go to the beach here even zoo
animals everywhere anyway yeah it's like i
hate going to i mean i like
being at the beach but i hate
the process and also to locks drive
the baby for like an hour you
get out to the water then drive
back for an hour like you're asking
a lot we would want growing up
i can't wait
when she was fifteen we were fifteen
minutes from the beach so yeah we
were it was better but it still
was like a big day where it
was like yeah i had to put
on sunscreen and it would always get
my eyes and try
she was very casual um there's so
many beaches and even stands very like
you can just right stumbled over to
one and enjoy yourself so it's like
really we did it all the time
in the summer but here i'm like
i you'd have to live by the
beach too yeah exactly yeah for us
if if you don't know california i'm
sure you think that we all just
live on the beach well of course
we're wearing all neon right now
and we are in the middle of
a volleyball game on the beach or
stop to record the land of fruits
and nuts but no it's such a
pain it's so annoying i think when
you move here you think you'll go
by the water lieutenant like i didn't
see the ocean the whole pandemic no
you literally have to live by the
beach on the west side and who
wants to do that unless you're super
rich yeah sure shadows obviously yeah
yeah yeah it was a malibu over
to your house when i'm gonna go
there i went there for i tried
to tell you this for a summer
i went there with ah no more
than summer was like for a year
me and some friends would boogie board
and we would go to point dume
oh yeah boo and it was really
fun we would like make a whole
day of it'll go every sunday fun
boogie boarding is really fun yeah i
know but if
you're a surfer you look down on
it i know bow it's got good
branding doesn't it like boogie board it's
pretty good a like whoever came up
with that is just like i'm gonna
call it something really fun yeah and
it is it's super fun buggy board
have you ever been surfing know i
would i would never i would never
my list of things i never never
i would also be way too scared
to
fall and i just i don't like
it the list of things i've never
going to do is just like growing
yeah basically like i know like i'm
just like designed to it before i
die it is funny that it's a
thing that i never appeal to me
in any way yeah you know what
i mean like the idea of balancing
on it like i said i can
understand why it is exciting for me
people that do it yeah but i
don't feel a pull to do that
in any way i agree i and
it's cool it's fine yeah yeah it
looks cool looks fun but it's weird
to know like oh that's a that's
a cool thing i don't want to
do it at all yeah yeah for
sure skydiving i don't want to do
no interest and i really don't want
to go in a helicopter i wouldn't
mind going to helicopter
i really don't also don't want to
drive in a car never never okay
well you gotta try problem in hawaii
we were like no law some of
us we guys gonna go in the
helicopter when we were going i wasn't
i wasn't i said yeah i said
no we were gonna do some other
fucking thing when janey and i went
years ago and ah oh i've told
this story where alright alright let's take
break
and we're back it's time for you
and this is the part of the
show where we play a fun game
but we call it a reacher i
know but let's call a team no
no i wasn't correcting oh okay i
was in the audience yeah first we
said we should have a feature yeah
scott said that and we took that
to mean game
how does he don't know what else
it could mean well i guess i
meant or i feel like this is
like when we talk about our favorite
celebrity yeah be anything yeah that's what
i sort of meant when i pitched
we talk about our favorite celebrity yeah
yeah yeah no that brought up like
oh my god such a good cake
it's ahead
it's not a hake it's a hamburger
it's an actual hambone that came from
the victor business bakery happy birthday i
mean take the two yeah oh let's
just rip it happy bahais oh gd
pi gonna like them send the bitches
yeah happy birthday
data yeah oh yeah oh yeah it's
a special hamburger day wait mccoy oh
yeah well you know what if you
forgot new year no oh traditionally on
a birthday wish before you get to
use this tremendous that's tremendous cake thank
you
guys this was your doing ah
no no scott scott came in with
his hamburger i had already had the
croissant yeah we separately we didn't dependently
had plans for you is that sweet
it's
yes it's very sweet
when i saw this paul i was
just like this is kind of freak
him out he's gonna be like is
this guy he's like i'm having a
psychotic break you're like you're like us
the show is kay is i'm like
i'm like one of the people on
the show is it kay yeah you're
giving mikey day right now
it gives you mikey dave i'm giving
mikey day is cake so it's a
good look yeah
playing a guy you don't even know
what flavor it is but i bet
it's good for hamburger yeah remember guy
who got pie tastes like shit huh
ah
okay no way have we all recorded
the show number i know we did
it on your birthday yeah the chocolate
chips and whip cream have we i
don't think that we've done it i
don't know if we've been on loud
at sea was trifling exchange don't know
that i would have agreed to yeah
because you like to clear your sky
do i do you you have your
birthday month no actually i very
how much don't i have my birthday
day and i like to do my
thing yeah yeah but what isn't everyone
this is one of the central doesn't
like to do it that's right oh
no that's your birthday and you're like
who gives a shit yeah i mean
this is fun for me to see
you guys huh
no it's fine of course fun i
didn't know were reassuring ourselves it's this
is fun right fun for people to
listen to what people enjoy like the
podcast of course
um ok so let's do the reacher
this is called name that abc and
it was submitted by ronnie not robbie
williams thank you ronnie williams thank you
those are cute candles too actually kills
are pretty cute this is pretty good
alright so we listen to them we
think of a song the song singer
replaces the lyrics with the
abcs yes which is the alphabet in
america which we could go through these
right yeah we know b c well
yeah right yes o e f e
is before all yeah always yeah obviously
i always go before f that's how
you remember it i j edge in
chateau remember good g h i j
yeah
a clean look clean low clem ca
come kick count cam it
ha jail and yeah kalman o p
kill menno pay q and hung kuna
thank you the best letter of all
the storm arse arse too tough
weeks weeks who is week sees weeks
is yeah because there we go yeah
sure i go so that's the american
alphabet that was good so that was
good how do we do this is
funny i think we go do we
just jump in like i guess whoever
thinks says it first got you should
sing a song
first okay yeah well guess okay yeah
alright if we buzz in with our
names okay good and whoever i yeah
really chat and you were great on
doughboys by the way when you buzzed
into me that's right oh right oh
okay i'm gonna stick yes yes i
was hoping i listen to it you're
jealous because i did talking to yeah
when when i heard that announce i
was like i would
love do you know what it was
very pleasant i have to say you
know i i've felt it all day
yeah when you said it was good
i was like i want i wonder
if i could do orange julius with
him i wonder if who ever done
that he'll never do it i don't
think it matters if they've done it
yeah just point they keep looping around
mean there's only so many they're gonna
kill them this is my formal request
to doughboys to do orange julius oh
shit throughout everyone out there how did
we get this too
them tweet everyone out there tweet
how to contact either austin you clip
this and send it to them immediately
paul wants you to pick this up
like a hamburger and bite into it
yeah can we ruins the whole canal
i'll take a video of it you
do that well maybe what you need
you're getting paper towels
okay ready okay we'll figure it out
make a video make video okay right
yeah is it gonna be it's impossible
it's impossible impossible it's
oh good try and action oh my
god he's picking the hamburger oh it's
still licious hamburger thanks scott and i'm
starving and i can't wait to eat
so hot meat
ah
wow hamburger that meat so white
that's how i like it meat so
white just like oscars okay that was
fun i was wondering how's it taste
let's go
okay you guys ready to budge and
it takes like you think it would
taste yeah yeah i mean i cake
that's all frosting and a couple ideas
yeah thank you dear you write a
buzzing yeah here we go ready some
frosting among the staff oh my those
fun though here we go ready and
a bc
d f g h i j l
yes paul
abc by the jackson five yes that's
my term
look at the dainty little bite i
took it so various yeah
you cut off a slice for me
or what yeah wherever your hands into
yeah with my mouth knife get your
teeth
okay here's my son okay
hell them
all done she says
thinking of songs you know
you really thought it would just gonna
come a b c d e f
a b c d f what no
gotta go in order what are you
doing
and you have to do more than
one note ah don't do a rap
so please c d f g h
i k ah man abc of five
jacob coker yes abc d e f
ah okay ready
abc d e f g h i
j k l m n o p
q r s t u three o
anti x y z a b c
d o scott penman yes oh i
heard what i heard abc d
f g h i j k l
m n o hey you sign know
better so much everybody can sing it
yeah all the words you know
yeah okay um
alright okay alright
abc d e f g h i
j k l m n o p
q ah s t u v w
x y z and z a b
c d e f g i don't
know abc e f g h ya
that shoot up but paul was an
arrow by abc by abc wow so
i'm going mad on abc on the
brain yeah didn't know that one okay
um so yeah sorry yeah
we have to namely do the ten
most popular songs in the world that
yeah excuse me you know my musical
tastes are far and wide i just
simply didn't know that one song like
one song from every genre i do
i mean that's pretty well-rounded i say
yeah it's like i would know a
lot ok um this song is
a b c d e d a
h i j k l umm and
ahh
i'm stuck with just peters out the
middle but it picks back up
i don't know i'm getting confused almost
singing the words a b c d
e g g
yeah um and o p q r
s t u v w x y
yeah she drives me crass ah wow
okay it's really hard actually for me
for me a b c d f
g
i guess she's gonna hire yeah yeah
like sing the song how it is
oh i'm gonna help my god
e b c d e a yeah
desperado yes that's right
ah that was that was look i'm
definitely up alright we need some of
them okay now he's gone met on
the first tuesday i know so let's
see if he goes met on this
one too yeah a b c d
e f g h i j k
l la manno p
q r s t u v double
yeah oh twice z yeah
i'll put again there o k b
c d e f g h i
j okay no pigou r s t
u v double yeah x y z
a b c yeah it's on the
edge of my brain i can't think
of it though
oh i have no idea really josh
what's your guess no one in the
usa no born in east l a
by jeez remember
okay wow
set up a no parodies rule we
have to we did not say four
star zero it's it's too late there
is there acceptable a b c d
e f d a j k l
baby
i love rocky road by right exactly
oh by the way i got the
birthday card from owl oh yeah i
got mine i don't know how he
does this i don't want to know
i'll tell you ah chao will tell
you and computer generated system but he
sends it he sends for thirty doing
with your last name no my first
name okay he didn't want with my
last name to wow and he did
one cool name
he did one for my full name
yeah i don't understand i'll ask you
what later yeah i'll ask you about
it later yeah same job twice yeah
as your birthday will you be doing
it it's my birthday i saved your
choice tell the joke twice each birthday
alright abc d e f g h
i j k virgin no sir i
was like a surface damage taken with
it
alright ready yeah sure ab ac wait
sorry i know it's hard a b
c d e f g h i
j a b paul's yes is it
ah holla back girl by winston no
no is it
callback boy by weird island yeah huh
o b c d e f g
h i j k l m n
o p q r s t
no no that's the chorus i don't
know any of the if there are
verses i mean i'm just all i
can think is the same thing so
yeah my neck my back my pussy
oh sure
a b c d you're doing exactly
what you were doing it like cheery
so yeah i'm on my back my
pussy and my crack that's housing let's
go go team my neck my back
wet pussy cat let's go
okay this song is like this ah
a b c d of j j
yea whatever ah sky man o walk
out and wow and you yeah see
me as hung and i'll tell you
that i am gonna tell you i
get by with a little help from
my friend yeah okay it was good
yeah
a b c d e start saying
joe larsen j yeah morris yeah you
got it
you know one more one more cool
time sure nbc d e f g
fucker and ghostbusters who you are and
you got it yeah lauren you got
it okay this is a little song
that goes like this
a b c d sky abc yes
yes can i steal the alphabet yes
you actually got correct
alright here we go how did he
steal a budgets saying this a b
c d e f g a sky
jacob jingle bells yes and our happy
days the beginning was patchy d e
f g that's happy no no happy
b d d yes dot rockin movie
do
dupe these days i just disagree
a great song because it's nice but
you have a male goat bells jingle
bells gina oh hell nah you know
i love it it stands yeah to
the bells jingle dramatically it's about belle
i love how the bells jingle and
jangle i like to imagine the christ
child jingling some bells in the in
the manger would have been as popular
forward jangle bells i don't
think so sounds a little chaotic yeah
alright well i think we're at the
end of the show where at the
end of the show where one show
one left in our season today yeah
ah and in the sea and in
the season next week is going to
be our climactic season finale is well
loved and the sea
where we're gonna say goodbye to you
after that yeah and perhaps for good
we don't know we don't know you
know we don't know and the future
is not guaranteed to any of us
know that's not just promised it's also
about freedom yeah yeah yeah but we
would definitely will be back next week
unless one of us parishes in between
recording episodes do you think from eating
that taking a bite of the hamburger
you think i might die how about
you both eat and i
don't we'll see what happens sure
i mean i ah said one of
those my die
you seemed like you were trying to
will it know it was an experiment
oh spearman let's see what happens is
it experiment okay it's experiment cake full
of gum have you ever had spearmint
anything other than gum toothpaste i guess
so i ain't like it's not a
flavor like eat it yeah it's so
wow
or that people like it for gum
but then it's like for like you
for gum but yeah not for like
meat or wheat there was somebody that
was on the tour and i will
not say their name that we learned
ah likes to take little ah nips
of ah mouthwash and swallow eight yes
i do know who that is
um that person shall remain nameless alright
to you all anyway three dm usa
at gmail dot com she wanna write
to us for some weird reason we've
i don't think we've ever or maybe
we have i don't know have we
ever read any of these emails no
okay good i never knew about it
mostly people use it for the three
years i don't know anybody i don't
know if anybody has july guess josh
what do you
think does anyone ever just written to
us to say something oh okay yeah
yeah he's saying yes alright i guess
we're being protected and it's all complaints
i like that um if you want
to hear ad-free episodes there on stitcher
premium and at cbp world dot com
and i think that's the income sierra
show september twenty fourth dynasty typewriter or
online that's really yeah it's you could
watch it any time anyway we love
you thank you for listening and we'll
be speed will be speedier
next week goodbye bye
ugh