not yelling it anymore you're not already
our father the yell louder
freedom or union after you get ah
i feel down during three
a yea oh it's just the nato
guy we know that tickets balcony hickory
ah well have your three tic tac
with this ticket you think andrew dice
clay's tank jack because he's gotta get
rid dick music jokes are succinct people
one seems fifteen seconds or less you
got it if you went back around
it's come back round that kind of
humor and you don't have to pretend
you're a character anymore right and just
be the way you feel right isn't
that
it beautiful and isn't that beautiful isn't
that beautiful just beautiful that is what
we're all a granted isn't that spanish
and isn't the social top and back
ole
hey well the misread oh nah i'm
paul f tompkins i'm scott aquaman i'm
lauren lucas yes and this is the
show where three people talk at the
same time and tell the same story
yeah and they're about to show up
so we gotta go oh no i
got right behind me are thinking wow
are you guys doing well doing good
doing good
um i gotta say since our talk
about our new year's resolutions oh i've
worked out three times that last episode
hey that's great that was all that
was only a week and it was
not because they were new year's resolutions
it was because they set up a
photoshoot for when the book comes out
and shows like this thing
some pictures taken for us soon oh
and you knew your photo you guys
could be in the background the background
and get some freebies you could photobomb
that would be great yeah he's all
speaking of resolutions i'm on my fourth
book well which one i just started
um less as la yeah andrew sean
greer
i read the last when it first
came out a couple of years ago
as did and it's so good yes
it's a pulitzer prize winning novel sounds
stupid no it's the opposite really it's
actually very smart basing that on yeah
just like the title and like with
the way you said is a pulitzer
prize but oh no it's great yeah
that was a green what's great about
the book is like in the in
love
yes he's talking about the pulitzer prize
yeah and why chance of winning the
pulitzer how very metas actual i know
it's really he really manifested that he
really did this sort of vision board
is so and so this is a
sql is sql like empire strikes backwards
better than the original may think there's
a chance you know paul would know
because he's red bow it is like
the empire strikes back and that it
takes place on a swamp planet oh
right and is it full of like
aliens and stuff i don't wanna spoil
it for you okay but just i've
only read one point is aliens everywhere
yeah it's teenage jodie
okay that's funny she's got pimples and
the same baby we've seen early most
we've seen baby we've seen old now
we need teen get less something we
can fold give us something we can
fold duda it's warm in here oh
do you want me to turn down
ah yeah i've been turfed i'm perfectly
fine
fine but if it was colder i
wouldn't be upset okay so you want
me to leave i'm understanding and go
over oh well hold up i'll do
it your sweatshirt from american apparel back
in the day no it's not but
i don't get why you would think
that yeah it's just a run of
the mill herpes but yeah that's all
i think
i got it from the grimace archstone
i used to have that one is
what i'm saying oh did you read
from my back girl i had purple
i gotta say i was listening to
that you were eavesdropping boring itself okay
so thanks for coming back so you
could help it out yeah sure whenever
it's goose this up politically so where
did you really get this from scott
what book are you reading if any
yeah right speaking of
dome i told her i read the
steve martin book and then i got
that was a cartoon that's past tense
my god i got three other books
for christmas i got heat to or
another sequel to yeah the book by
michael mann yeah he wrote a sequel
but is he doing ah he what
does that guy quoting he sounds like
he's making a thing and the chipmaker
these book make bank on this book
people love that movie like what does
the school bully to actually hear it's
good paul scheer did yeah posters
yeah gift option on add to cart
he was suggesting over mister taste he
has to tease what he likes to
call you know what i thought was
really great he hates you by the
way brilliant idea feel like on the
podcast where he's sad at christmas time
paul what it really sounds like to
me was that paul was very on
top of gifts in the household he's
kind of he's kind of half
handling allows the opposite of me a
lot of men you know don't do
that in their relationship because our big
dicks are in the way oh yeah
you're trying to wrap presents and just
knocking i'm trying to keep the world
going for that too but the world's
economy that he had a great idea
which is that he bought a couple
like versions he bought a couple of
virgins
me it keeps everybody happy he brought
he bought um some games that he
likes and like they're just kind of
crowd pleasers wrapped him under the tree
unlabeled someone comes over with a gift
for him he's like i have a
gift for you it's already to go
under the tree wrapped and oh the
the personal like who's were these people
dropping by his place
yeah sort of the that's santa part
about that makes it feel a little
special is that no one ever gives
yeah i'll give me back what
yeah i know i'm saying a shirt
please yeah cool up i think got
a lot of gift ideas from him
because she gave me this ah game
as well as a cinephile game or
something i can't remember what it's called
but i haven't cracked it open yet
and yeah three i think the books
were from his everything he said she
was like very much
like that's great for scott yeah i
think it was the quentin tarantino book
maybe i only remember the other hurt
it's one long sentences that true yeah
and it's all about feet wow
so at the end fascinating he says
he loves them and the end of
that set at the end of one
long sentence i love fi
and by the way i love feet
yeah oh and by the way and
there's on its own page i love
i love feet and draws the ugliest
foot you've ever seen yeah like that's
the one you love they're all beautiful
every foot well is the jesus loves
the little children and all the children
in the world do have you ever
heard the song yeah yeah never sung
so beautifully though all the children in
the world
they are yellow black or white they
are precious in his sight or that
those are the three types yeah yeah
like
like a box of crayons the worst
fucking party
yeah
yellow black and white the white crayon
is i don't have a white crayon
i guess i could draw the sun
and outline it isn't annoying cran but
that's the one i would like hollywood
care around the most because she does
draw on the walls right she draws
on the wall yeah why do you
know why why did you say incur
i find it later it's like i
find like in the room that i'm
like oh there's fuckin
crandall over the by the way i
have i have decided to reclaim spankings
and a horrible idea i give him
spankings when she's good so i'm trying
to teach her that they're good okay
you're taking back the word of making
it yeah i say you are so
good time i gotta give this boy
um is kranz very hard to get
off the wall is it's very hard
to get off the magic eraser think
that right yahoo is crayons very hard
to get off the wall i love
a magic eraser and i love magic
anything yeah big fan of magic magic
flying carpet yeah yeah yeah love it
wand yeah radek wanda
a grandma
no i mean he does magic to
the rabbit mushroom yes this is like
my game that i like x x
l i'm not able to play my
brain somewhere
you could think of words that follow
matches you ever have a magic set
wow or young um you know you
just love anything castle yeah well and
f em um i didn't have a
i never wanted to be oh you
know i don't want to be a
puppeteer a magician or any kind of
like artistic like hey look at juggler
know yeah
really wasn't a joke how i upper
are we not raising our young girls
to want to be magicians juggler i
think we're really pushing that on men
i i really we need men with
ponytail magician
why do fire wind you men with
ponytails want to juggle so bad i
don't know
it realised that was a big it's
definitely true that they love hacky sack
handling definitely true i love to do
magic with their wand and i guess
i'm thinking of um like professional ah
magicians or people like that but i
feel like such they they have the
ponytail more seldom lee
they don't have room to have a
ponytail because they're they're whipping around they
can't have their exactly in the way
yeah have a hair in their mouth
when they're doing those trick and hearing
imagine know if somebody is doing an
intricate magic trick and then there's going
i know i know
i went to where they have like
a wet hair on their cheek that's
disgusting why is it wet because it
was in his mouth oh my god
i went to drama school with a
guy who thinks busy on the phone
i had to send something for work
to someone and i did it very
therapeutic way hey whenever i know lauren
to shut up okay
a good test
wow um and it worked but he
had he had long hair that he
knew i forgot the beginnings guy i
went to drama school got long hair
that he would put into a ponytail
and he wanted to be a magician
and but he was an acting school
and we were always sort of like
you're obviously a magician um i think
yeah acting is
it's gonna be helpful to doing magic
true and what did he do he
ended up being a magician will drive
is easy yeah still true golden hersh
yeah i do yeah i like him
now he have long hair he didn't
have long use on a ponytail guy
had beautiful long early early hair that
you love to run your fingers through
you do yeah after the show he
would sit on stage and everybody could
come over run their fingers through his
hair so he was here he would
think he was into shows like this
yeah i know you want to and
he would sit on the chair and
he wouldn't even
say you aren't oh so everyone i
want ever may at the edge of
the stage with his hair daily off
the stage oh yeah kind of waterfall
through well sometimes they would raise the
stage like that a past people's heads
okay so people could just reach up
and do oh why did they jump
like what can they do to at
level or look down at him he
initially just never worry with lay across
two chairs but they
we're were just like wooden chairs or
hers back yeah and he he put
it in his rider you have to
get me a special padded bench to
lay on yeah so people can run
their nobody read that far of course
after you've said you only want the
horny imams people kind of stop reading
yes yeah what is the eminem's thing
that everyone is all up in arms
out heirs
ah possibly as an asexual eminem now
it's a sexual in what way no
dick they all have no dick so
hey i'll have no debt no doesn't
want to know like it's not like
the although the the nine one one
analogy bt q i'm an m or
something and what way i saw a
fox news clip where they were going
having a reward i don't know what
was what i saw i think you're
right
rent i saw an eminem commercial the
other day and not nothing seen changed
um how do i i'm like i'm
only like the personality of the hardshell
we get these things anyway is there
a purple limonum introduces first new character
more than a decade purple this was
october three twenty twenty two okay okay
the new purple spokes candy is a
peanut m and m designed to represent
acceptance and inclusivity the brands wow
it's by anti-bullying or something on the
characters charming quirky nature comes come from
her keen self-awareness authenticity and confidence hold
on read more she's really happy she's
high and none of this sounds bad
to me she no okay so james
january they redesigned green so green no
longer had the boots the heel glued
winstar
cool laid-back sneakers to reflect her effortless
confidence oh everyone's confidence in the go-go
boots can i here's the thing it's
not that it's bad that you know
inclusivity is bad it's just wire is
this fuckin can write there's more there's
more okay you have to hear this
the change came after mars received criticism
for green sexy care
activation and said she would now represent
confidence and empowerment as a strong female
and for much more than her boots
rye company also changed the backstory to
green and brown the two women eminem's
they now have a more friendly relationship
showcasing a force supporting weight so they
were they were rivals before i don't
recall brown hearing against green
why here's why here they get into
trouble because they've decided to have these
characters in the first place which are
stupid right and then they hey i
left them one by one voice all
of them and they're like we want
we didn't really think this through i
guess that way we can anticipate people
saying why is that one of them
orange why don't they put out an
album that's just fine
they should put it on my couch
sorry this is so perfect you should
say that in announcing purple mars put
out an ad with the character singing
an original song oh just gonna be
me the second part your real life
artists saxophonist grace kelly dancers and choreographers
devin santiago and colo cag an opera
singer anthony roth costanzo mars also
watch eminem's fund the cow game here
we go this is the song i'm
just going to be me one dollar
from every stream of this will go
to sing for hope
i'm the new stammer rough and soggy
july yeah takes i want to be
the best or even pretty good would
be great shame a little unsure that
i have to admit herbal right now
just be yourself
that man in the plant sits around
the opposite yeah and thank you mister
plant mill i think it won't die
so yeah fuck the purple eminem i'm
on fox aside ah i disagree wholeheartedly
i support i support the purple and
i support amazon paul law
loves it because he's purple today i
am purple today and i'm gonna do
the best i can i have nothing
against amber ruffin of course nothing yeah
amber ruffin one of the greatest i
do i think i'm on the record
with this i despise the eminem characters
see i think that they are my
family i feel extremely can you have
a family but i
i feel that they are your family
and extended family you owe nuclear family
feel extremely connected to these characters and
when she changed out of the boots
i thought where'd they go you know
to shave a closet is she going
to put em back yeah who's doing
the voices of the other ones now
and we die love aka romans jake
she's released ah john
and um goodman goodman did he yeah
why did that have what i did
this happen why john goodman like the
first round of ads and then he
was like i don't wanna do this
anymore he said he didn't want to
that's what i'm assuming don't you assume
to fire john goodman that's what i'm
wondering he's a good man
and he's been around so long you
know it's so who's the red time
for some new blood the red i
thought was john lovitz i don't know
if it's somebody different show me to
look this up but yes i do
can you believe we're talking about m
and m's again you know we all
comes back to stop i think we
still have a taste test in order
we have a lot of flavors we
didn't get around to there's one that's
just
ash yeah that's bold it's the retired
j k simmons yellow nearly west terrain
red oh yes that was good for
him john goodman yellow jon lovitz red
vanessa williams brown really it's a williams
eric kirchberg
auger orange okay i'll take your word
for it this is like the opening
credits yeah blue rob pruitt okay okay
so they really spent their money on
john goodman and j k simmons and
then they're just like oh john love
i assume john leveson and i actually
think billy west probably get a good
amount of green demands and agree
summer no crees me crees green cree
is one of the best creeks are
you agreeing no world chocolate bar phil
hartman chocolate bar this must have been
years and years ago before they made
eminem's round
who wasn't filled your heart and leave
the chocolate bar chocolate bar oh wait
someone we know carmel voiced by david
cross and one other way
i didn't even get the when did
carroll will get a chance the matter
is it carmel by the way was
he was square with david cross style
glasses i remember the camel newark where
carmilla square bow no candy coating i
like when away wait was this one
fill or morin and david cross came
together to excuse finally they put
neither differences over my throat is actually
my chest is burping i said to
make it clear because you know how
when you're burping you can control it
but when it's here you can't i
think i think i know anyway i
think that they smashed the carmel on
the and the bar together to make
a carmel bar and this just happened
and phil harm has been
dead for decades when did that just
happen i'm saying it was decades david
krasnow david cross just became the cara
we did this is a recent thing
that's a recent thing i believe unless
they re you believe a commercial that
unless they reissue it can you please
please google the david cross martha david
fucking get done today we are on
on of bravo please look up that
information yeah yeah
alright here we go this is we
really have to choose him to be
our next spokesperson seems like a good
fit but he sounds boring i'm yawning
just talking about him well it's our
job to change that ah guys i
think he can hear us
hey sounds like you're on the fence
why don't i just leave you my
resume guess it's laminated
no hired carmel has been squared for
far too long ah al try caramel
lemon mta so they i see he's
square it was an origin story and
then they they have candy coating that
like surrounds him yeah and in traps
him yeah and then we eat him
i love great and the other
norman doesn't have a great voice for
they want this to happen
hi right i'm like we're hiring a
new person to get a new one
of us to get to get eaten
well they want they you know they
need they don't want either i don't
make they don't make sense i hate
that they don't exist in the bags
they are a representation of a flair
there there make they're having sex with
other memes and creating these babies that
we then eat
but but but but but but but
but because we're eating their children yeah
because you don't ever see anyone of
them get bitten this toe there is
one that has been this to me
is like the movie cars in that
there's such a fundamental problem with the
with the concept that i can't get
on board now what's wrong with the
movie cars carson talk
that's a huge number one cause i
wanna do it when i saw finding
nemo i thought fish don't just couldn't
happen yeah the same toy started now
is mantle fish get lost the toy
story though kinda works thinks i'm like
maybe they talk when i'm not looking
toy story the main issue for me
was at the beginning when that lamp
bounced up and down and i was
like yeah i'm out
because that was way early in the
movie that was like the first second
yeah yeah it was just like fuck
this wow their production card doesn't make
anything what i think was gonna happen
when you sat down well i thought
a lamp would be stationary and just
sitting there and maybe someone would turn
it on you seen the brave little
toaster how brave and how little and
hotels
i've never seen that i've never seen
any you know i really loved it
when i was little and i will
tell ya doesn't hold up gouging is
that miyazaki isn't no it came no
i think it's okay that's one possible
let's you're saying a guy who can
make a moving castle can't make a
toaster brave nope
he doesn't have many old school film
directed by jerry reese based on the
nineteen novella the same name by thomas
m disch based on a novella that
we're able to sell a shocking anyway
i remember i love that movie and
found it extremely calming as a child
and yeah it just doesn't what what
what appeals to you about it that
i just thought
it was sweet on top to being
brave because you were such a no
they were just sweet little characters and
yeah i was afraid i was afraid
about you oh my god you okay
ronnie yeah yo milf island ah no
but i do need to see man
i just want everybody does today manner
yeah if you worried that i wasn't
watching it let me just heard milf
man assuage your fears let me assume
you watch that alone i watched it
with my daughter okay ah you like
your mommies one of these um i
am watching special forces oh i heard
about this okay i know somebody who
has asked to be on that show
really i can't really tell us during
the
break but that show is actually taking
me all different places emotionally i was
laughing i was crying i've cried probably
four times there's been three episodes okay
that i watched one episode three times
for episodes day they are doing they're
pushing themselves to the brink kate gosselin
i mean we got hd
doctors ru pinsky we got we got
okay now i have to know why
is it called special forces so these
are like celebrities yes and after a
fashion are taken to jordan where they
are problem when they are on the
new ceo angel gabriel forces closer training
ground that the
a real special forces train on and
they have to do all sorts of
challenges with no luxuries and their luggage
are pushed to their breaking point no
clothes there the entire time they you
lose people every episode okay for different
reasons they're either like it's usually like
yeah that's one of them
injury treason they don't take you out
you just have to keep going so
basically they say don't kill you out
just basically they lose people because people
are liking take it anymore for different
reason really so you could just go
on forever know i mean there's there's
an end date itself think it's ten
days but it's really hard and how
many days would you let us know
better
i swear to god watching the first
episodes like i'd be out ny i'll
do all time here's the first thing
you'll do yeah here's the first name
to do what they hover a helicopter
oh yeah exactly
over the ocean you you are in
it then you know you stand on
the side of control you lean off
the side of it and you stand
stick straight and do dude does your
head get chopped off by the blades
yes no and you cross your arms
over your chest and you fall backwards
as six straight as possible because you
will automatically fall headfirst
down like a pencil into the water
and your head goes in the water
yes but if you just your friend
if you bend your body a little
your slap in the fucking ocean slapping
dough slapping the bass okay you're slapping
the bass and it hurts a slob
but we had a neck injury first
episode shows
cry yeah right well i don't wanna
give it away are these fucking it
away give it away give it away
no skip ten seconds if you don't
know kate gosselin
and she broke her neck broke her
neck and she had to leave bro
and she was really upset because she
really wanted to she was so huge
that she broke her neck well yeah
but you know what she was actually
so afraid to go in the water
that she was like she couldn't you
know she actually did do it did
do it in a book or no
yeah you should be afraid of these
things you know there's a lot of
really scary stuff that happens like another
really scary one is that they they
put you underwater in
like again with the wall there's a
lot of water that's the stuff that's
placed to count because i'm most afraid
of it but you're in like a
um it's like a simulation of like
a it's like a g rome has
all the windows out but so it's
it's attached to chains so it's your
you buckle in and you get lowered
into the ocean and you have to
hold your breath for twenty seconds and
then they'll tap you and you have
to
under your seatbelt and and swim out
of the sofa and so all in
all you're holding your breath for probably
thirty twenty one now probably twenty five
by the time you're out of there
um and how long do you think
your monograph two seconds i remember reading
a batman comic when i was young
where he was like i can hold
my breath for two minutes and i
was like oh that's what everyone should
be able to do right yeah and
then it's about you i think you
can hold your breath for like what
how long can you do it eight
seconds mean they therefore you start paying
limbic gym you know that the panic
well it's all yeah it's all mind
games because it's yeah they're like physically
everyone here can do all of these
things like call it mind games yeah
it's physical but um this this um
olympian nastia what's the last thing you
call an h hirono but anyway she
was extremely she's like i can't hold
my breath at all at all
it goes through this whole thing she
ends up doing it but wow there
is a twist to it which i'll
let you watch if you want okay
well this is this is amazing it's
honestly really good mike was like i
don't care you can put it on
i'm not gonna pay attention to go
you'll be hooked and he was riven
he was what was the the kate
winslet record on oh yeah she was
like saying that she was doing for
four minutes she hell
at her best for an insane amount
of time really yeah and i just
saw it the other day and a
you can't even tell who she is
right so it was pointless cares that's
can be the movies bats oh it
was pointless well they're advertising it everywhere
i look it's on jeopardy they're putting
it into the questions they're making commercials
i'm like it's literally everywhere i saw
poster for on the way here
her and the poster looks so dumb
it made me mad i've never seen
the first one it's not like we're
sorry avatar lovers i'm not my homie
don't play that
hours long where's the homey the clown
movie yeah well that's that is what
people have been demanding look we have
to take a break alright i don't
make the rules we'll be right back
we're back we're back and you know
we were talking about carmel and i
was thinking the other day
like a how did they figure that
out and how to do it because
i've made it i made it a
couple of times and it's hard you've
made caramel yes it's very hard to
hear my call i made i made
a i don't know which one i
say anymore i'm just copying i made
a cake that caramel carmel i did
them i did the scott scott please
carmel i
i think the correct way is caramel
but i grew up saying car carmel
so yeah i want like a karma
harmony com sunday como code it's got
carmel and chocolate with carmel ca car
sounds carmel camille encore come on come
on come come come come come come
com momoko ker chameleon so
you tried to make it it's a
plot it's a process and burned to
the first time fuck i'm sure you
did it's why are you so sure
of that dear
wait as pam risk is calling me
oh she want hello scott are you
ready to raise hello
hello
thousands on home heating bills
that's the part that bothers me the
most any minority that's a middle of
the thousands on home let's start talking
the first robot backed up that that's
why they're so messed up it's like
don't need the technology hasn't evolved enough
you need to wait for the hello
yes but they are the ones that
you do say hello and then it
starts and that's actually creepy to you
i don't know yeah so you can't
win okay but how did they ever
figure out
out like oh okay we're going to
take this sugar if we do this
to it it'll do you know i
really just kept around word their word
that they were like nice you say
so boring yeah i think also a
lot of things like that come about
from accidents k where they're trying to
do something you're trying to cure polio
and they're like yeah they're trying to
always try
we have so many things from trying
to cure polio it's kinda brutal illegally
um but i but it's really like
how do we have chocolate you know
what i mean like i don't have
pasta how do we have the pemba
how do we in ma you have
table but but it it led me
to wonder
being hungry for pinball have we figured
out everything at this point yep
well i wouldn't either though like getting
crazy with it now when you go
to restaurant they're like we put
you know freeze dried sales on top
of a pile of fake dirt that
yeah just because we've figured out everything
to do with everything now just like
trying to create there was a this
may be an apocryphal story but some
patent office in new york or something
closed wanted to close in eighteen eleven
or something like that because they thought
they invented everything right
that's what yeah yeah now that's just
silly yeah they're full that's just not
seeing the power of the human mind
yeah hadn't heard of metta yeah world
peace speaking basketball yes why were you
out of askable being the first professional
basketball game last night you'd been to
a weight the way you've
i've never been no professional bat never
have never i've never followed basketball that
is absolut but you haven't just ended
up at one no i haven't yeah
just been walking by an arena gym
i think i'll go in here i
have ended up at basketball games with
no intention of being about it you
know i don't i don't like i
go like maybe somebody invited me once
i don't know but if
if so it was a long time
ago but i just i didn't have
fun it's so fun i had a
great time well here's the thing so
christine mangle um who's from philly and
joe winger who's from philly yes um
he hides it christine he tries to
yeah i can always tell the christine
writes for the simpsons and she's so
funny so she did she write
whoa yeah she was jewish as for
the apostrophe oh so it used to
be told they needed to come in
there oh god this is actually
yeah grammatically correct yeah um so this
somebody at the simpsons music department has
this da da da da da da
da da da da da yeah we
just thought the music was urban for
us um and are always doing that
so this is at the crypto dot
com marimo tales
yeah well i'm sitting here i'm really
gonna need things to just be named
just fun i know i know just
staples you know is a company but
we never minded it because that was
the original well you know yeah i
think a lot of times i let
companies slide if it was what i
always was used to yeah it's a
new company i'm not so happy i'm
like if it's just one word but
like saying a web address is so
irritating
no and i think it should be
like the sparkle dome like i don't
think it should have ended thing that
works any also it should be the
whatever forum like i don't mind that
yeah i mean like if it's it
shouldn't just be crypto and then arena
i think it should be you know
whatever the name of the building is
sponsored by whatever yeah it's still powered
by anybody
the kid and it's like oh yeah
crypto dot com is not going to
be the name for the next fifty
years they wouldn't get their money's worth
if that were the case you know
because no one everyone would just drop
it well they'll get their money's worth
because crypto is gonna be around forever
umm so she invited me and it's
like come to your house and get
down on one knee
d and bring flowers what is the
propose that i go she just invited
have you been on the simpsons i
just did the simpsons last year yeah
i was wondering if this later connection
happened you just you homer i'm sorry
i i won the contest where you
get to do homework huh this is
a really big deal that you were
on the simpsons ah it was very
exciting that
it's a really big deal for a
second grant yeah people who listen to
this show listen to our voices and
put us on things look because all
my tv shows are on for forty
fifty years eventually i'll be on it
and now it has that aired yes
well what's the what's the episode i
don't remember the world's biggest dumb shit
comes to springfield what's your character
ah first leapt episode
um they it was a succession sort
of parody um and so i played
the um the fuck son of the
john lithgow character who was like fuck
off character okay yeah that's you play
jeremy strong maybe i think so it
was not it was not that one
to one like it was more the
the plot was more succession type plot
with it with a rich family and
everything right um there was a rival
to ah grandpa simpson um that rival
companies i don't remember a lot about
and honestly i still haven't seen it
have you did you just record the
words i just
according they not in order not north
aka video they gave me just a
sheet of words dialogue and you chose
will make your name selection like you
have to be like i do every
word with every inflection i could think
of mad angry sad scared camera and
ah how would a camera say it
um but it was
yeah the trump thing it was very
what was that again man was a
mamun camera tv
this was to prove he didn't have
alzheimer's
remembering forwards yeah it's something yeah well
i think what i think what happened
was he was like they give you
forwards you're supposed to remember four or
five years five some but then he
just pointed to things in the room
and said i'm like man woman camera
tv yeah for examples so those weren't
the school words he got us why
would you need an example like yeah
yeah we all know that there are
more than forwards so
the sixers were playing the philadelphia seventy
six seventy six years now they were
this is based upon the fact that
one of the most famous things to
happen in philadelphia was in seventeen seventy
six fill in the blank what happened
scott i hate to correct you it's
because you philadelphia was the home to
the firm
first person to turn seventy six years
old oh i'm rigorous life expectancy used
to be so low actually sorry to
tell you that you are both wrong
way y de mars candy companies from
philadelphia and it's to represent the seventy
six flavors of eminem that there will
be oh there will eventually it was
yeah
it was hopeful yeah it continues to
be hershey's by the way he's from
pennsylvania
well it's true that special shrimp in
the shop and broccoli could be satan
so did you like it would they
have a little digital like you like
they had the lamppost with the hershey
kisses what i've heard they hersheypark is
funny yeah well i remember those like
chalk la i'm like oh there you
go on a little ride i'm sure
i've talked to for this i'd like
to go to there you go on
a little ride and then i thought
was going to be like willy wonka
where they just like go here's a
a whole bunch of candy yeah and
instead you get like into a gift
shop and you have to buy it
and my piano not buying that to
be that's fine
why were like you can have one
fare or something isn't the same price
it isn't right yeah yeah that sounds
like the factory yeah not the amusement
park oh no no we went to
the factory i didn't know there's maybe
the amusement candy hershey park well that's
really cute or she parked where they
have like a guy dressed up as
a package of reese's cups you know
what i mean like shit like that
yeah
what guy so did you love the
customer ship you love when the when
the when the dancing girls came out
in the middle and shook their money
makers shook their little duty makers oh
it was first being a dad has
changed
for the same um i had never
um ah been in one of those
boxes before oh that's really fun it
was insane that changes everything because you
can like really be free with your
water you can go drink and go
the bathroom very easy to show right
there in front of everyone was so
fun so was this the simpsons um
sponsored event
no it was not they just had
to have a purpose has this box
and we we're not we're not the
only ones there there was one of
the people that is that is one
of the owners of the box was
also there with his family oh and
this of a little pie i hope
i am not blowing up this man's
spot but the man who wrote to
black panther was also there with that
vancouver de ryan
coogler right the movie i know he
directed it are you carota the very
least let me look it up maybe
it's the other guy well let's get
this right but um so we get
to you know we we have great
view of the game um yeah it's
nice the sixers one i've never really
watched joe robert cole i think so
yes
they call him joe and we called
him king cole we did not meet
for some reason um i who did
not write black panther no i did
not it was only people who had
also written black panther were allowed to
say a little bit yeah i was
nervous around the strangers who were very
everybody's right yeah but sometimes you're seeing
stroh rum and say hello my name
is paul but i do feel in
situations
like that i do feel like a
hillbilly you know what i mean yeah
oh i feel like you're trying
i'm like oh my my purse now
it's like oh also used to this
also some people like cum laid and
yeah and everyone is talking already and
then it's like oh there's a new
screen with a football game on that
sometimes people are taking a break and
watching a football game right but i
really love sports i really i really
enjoyed it and i was like oh
i will
probably watch basketball on tv now oh
wow okay and the sixers won that's
great the last that last minute of
play is like that's all you got
to see it's so wild well that's
why i've always said that basketball games
should just be one minute one shot
whoever gets it first oh you only
get one shot at halftime they have
people that they have like sort
a little obstacle course so people from
the crowd can like they have to
run through these things grab a basketball
shooter to get money yeah and so
the new guy does dot com no
no doubt the one guy was dunking
left and right he missed just like
the last two but he made these
like like trick dunks where he would
um you know bouncing on the floor
and then
catch it right yeah that's great oh
wow then the second guy did bad
since the first day also just an
audience member he wasn't like so he
was doing trick dunks yeah as an
audience member yeah and the other guy
was really thinking i was trying to
do it and it was not working
while trying to do don't cry just
do your just do your thing i
imagine this is part of the
the thing like they've probably been doing
this forever and it's like no specific
guys know i think oh yeah yeah
yeah so no apple no activity yeah
you know what they're getting what they're
saying i usually like it when they
it would be like ok if you
can make this basket from halfcourt but
i do like you though i like
when like videos kids really wow young
and a kid ah this kid was
probably like nine ten something like that
okay i feel like the older i
get the less i can judge kids
ages right where it's like yeah he
was like jose pipe and he's in
high school um i don't i don't
wanna say i'm like um hell do
i think you are yeah like your
your internal age yeah of my internal
organs how will do you think people
say
i am
i've been to two basketball games what
is going on well i've never been
to basketball games how many have you
been to the two is a job
i've been to like and respectable no
thirty three from chaturanga yeah oh you
know knew your name dumaini naval yeah
i'm trying to do that yeah that's
true that's where i started that i
get bored and play
you're doing excellent
i guess this is just the woman
to do and how many people choose
have you been to oh a million
right so let me tell you oh
my gosh okay ball basketball is better
than baseball i went to i went
to the lakers once and i sat
in the very back row oh and
this has been dennis rodman's on the
lakers and i bought it a form
i bought
dennis rodman shirt transcranial do you still
have it ah no should and then
i went to one with our good
friend armin ah who has has like
regular the cannibal yeah any he bit
my butt
during the game now are we with
armin who has like i think he
and his family have season tickets or
something like that and it was like
ah relatively close it was very fun
that's really fun yeah like it's very
exciting when you go with someone who
has close seats yeah i've had that
experience a few times and that makes
it feel really special because you're seeing
sweat on their faces and like all
that yeah assertions and everything that's really
i feel that sport in particular to
be down on the um on the
floor for it i can see how
exciting it would be like the best
eats i've read at a baseball game
was ah just to the ah left
of home plate oh yeah i would
like to see a little base
people gamer if i was really close
very exciting but not all of the
play happens there but if you're like
courtside and you're right there and they're
just going back and forth in this
one area yeah you're seeing fucking everything
yeah do you want to be by
a basket or do you want to
be halfcourt
yeah of course i guess would be
yes i feel like sat behind the
basket and that was kind of breaks
and you see them running towards you
and jumping up and stuff and you
get scared you're like oh and i'm
always growing
here's the thing i didn't know about
ah best professional basketball is that when
when the teams are down at one
end there's a guy at the other
end frantically mopping up the floor oh
wow i never remember notably yeah yeah
never occurred to me but a guy
runs out like
oh no yeah yeah gotta keep it
really shine because if one of the
players gets injured they'll sue yeah this
exactly you know i don't i like
it more in-person than watching on tv
because i feel like there's stay adds
so many distractions and like the talking
really worried about the there's a lot
of shit happening in other dads and
they were worried well started televised ads
yeah
yeah because the ads there's arriving on
the thing on the thing and then
every there's sleep or nothing rally you're
not hearing them like burger king is
number one place you're just like watching
exactly yeah but it is like this
because things are changing every two seconds
but that's to keep you in getting
really interesting with yeah i think it'd
be interesting to write down every ad
you see any
de fun you should do that yeah
okay report your findings
you have to leave this room now
weren't they afraid though when they started
televising games no one would ever want
to go in person anymore they said
about everything yeah it's just not true
about anything no no going on firsthand
that makes your phone would rather be
improved with the pandemic people like i
don't know if it were livestream what
you know after the things over should
we livestream because then people won't want
to come and it's like no they
will of course know it's great to
live stream now
now it's like it's it's open up
a whole new world i did my
show on saturday and had it was
livestream and it was it was so
watch oh my guy it was so
fun jason so funny yeah some of
the code those don't have to pay
for it yeah send it to you
um no but ah they know bucks
yeah sounds like an improv show yeah
she's
yeah you're listening to this you can
still get the livestream who cares alright
let's go to a break that's actually
important for me to say no
and we're back
and you want to do a voicemail
yeah don't last long while if you'd
like to call us here's there's some
options um for them options yeah we
know you have a lot of options
when it comes to calling us and
like for one for instance you could
call haha in poo but here's some
other here's some other ones
i a gala host
hi a gao host that's what lauren
would say haha jag opt
gaga jag opt gaga yeah a jag
off hag alla host
gag allah host all great ah host
actually works i would yeah i think
gala host is maybe one of the
best about like you gag haha lajos
haha host i la lajos haha la
host though because we're from los angeles
now if you want to add a
number haha la host
hag claims eight
i like that gaga la ho seventy
eight gag alla ho sophia or gaga
jag opus wow so we have a
little ton of options yeah my son
way too long it's forty four two
five two four six seven eight jag
jag you know you could either write
that down or memorize
gaga jagged opus thank you jay olympus
gaga jack but that's way too many
letters it's one that's one extra letter
okay scratch i did say
here we go here's here's one
hi guys first of all i want
to say i love you so much
fuck all favorite people in the whole
world two-thirds boy i love pinball i
was wondering what is the worst beat
each of you has been on organic
bunny oh god we're state oh god
i'm sure i was the worst state
in any situation like that
he took me to this place
i see
i ok i got i got one
example okay my friend who i'm sure
i told this before but we worked
at knott's berry farm i was in
security in the line and he was
a monster and one of the rides
yeah and he would take off his
monster mask and show he was handsome
and say
go talk to my friend out work
in the line and um we'll see
and we'll set up a date
and he was handsome he was handsome
so he he um he was trying
to get with this girl who had
a friend and he was like let's
all go out she has a friend
will ah you know and basically like
we need someone for her friend and
and it'll be great so we come
ah i
go over to his place and wear
what i remember very definitely told the
story before remember very vividly alive rolling
stones concert was on and my friend
is a drummer was criticizing charlie watson
technique ah and ah that's a little
detail that sadly handle let's do and
see
so yeah like peterson story
two girls came ah we want them
two girls one cup um that we
sit down we chat we meet we're
watching the rolling stones thing we stand
up to lee they go okay let's
go i stand up with them and
the girl looks at me and goes
oh he's coming to
that's gotta hurt yeah that's they thought
these two ladies thought they were gonna
get get with this one guy i
think they were trying to three some
with with the hand can you blame
them i can't really because threesomes are
great i just remember dates that were
not there there was nothing interesting about
them being bad but just that at
the time noah
ing this person is not interested in
me oh yeah yeah i will i
went on a date in high school
um with someone that this is what
i was because i was thinking i'm
a bit of a serial monogamous so
i didn't i've only gone on a
handful of dates i didn't turn into
relationships but to i would say any
of those probably weren't great because nothing
happened after but oh i also did
have a date with
the woman that ah shirley throne played
in the movie monster oh anyway oh
you wanna hear another one is that
is that what i'm hearing yeah
so what i'm hearing yeah you're hearing
it ah oh did i spaghetti spaghetti
oh alright let's hear another one here
we go
hello this is chief i have a
hypothetical name as a verb go if
you so's yours were some sort of
endangered species what would you be the
fuck there's more what animal on the
endangered species list
which is rephrase oh okay i'm gonna
actually look you have to be in
dale okay hold on you have no
choice
okay thanks bye
great i'm gonna look up the animals
theirs
i could lumpy right the animals okay
so like who what are the endangered
animals because i know chicken chicken is
one definitely
for delta here i'm gonna reveal yeah
i'm gonna reach the ten most in
danger to animals okay these all made
the list okay and congrats to them
all and i said yeah is this
half tie list yes they want to
get them all um the john rhinos
okay right never even heard of it
that's why it's that endanger imo
muir leopard
the sunda island tiger
mountain gorillas tap a newly orangutan
yunxi finlets porpoise what black rhinos
african hour yeah hello family sumatran orangutan
sumatran orang yang tang hawksbill turtles so
you know i would just say rhinos
tigers monkeys elephants you know where you
fall on
i think a porpoise right because you're
at least so these are just like
strains of certain answer that was i
was like so specific that i can't
even deal yeah like i'm like give
me something that purpose sounds good or
maybe those mountain gorillas i don't know
why this is another thing people search
for endangered species in ohio and the
first the first one is indiana bat
indiana ah
we may and we don't get a
lot of those around you kind of
want to be one of those indiana
bats i don't want to be oppose
an endangered species i'd be like an
elephant
because no one would fuck with you
they're so sweet they get killed all
the time yeah they're just there i'd
be one of those turtles because they
live because you want to go turtle
turtle turtle turtle also you know ninja
i don't
yeah but i'm saying you know ninja
what is yours gonna be no ninja
ninja ninja no problem i'll be a
monkey gorilla like it or anything remember
why do we say around one of
the lake gorilla yeah rula women around
the lake gorilla yeah you have a
lot of signs around your house yeah
yeah yeah and i'm a girl why
do we say orangutan is really say
a tang because we're dumb i think
those were dumb yeah okay alright so
ten but it's it's what at this
point just call it a rank tank
because that's what everyone calls also more
fun to say yes um call the
thing if you're gonna put a rang
in there and then you're gonna go
up to put a ring on it
put a g at the exactly it's
true oh my i saw fucking video
of these guys narrating um ah like
marrying a nature i can't say nature
video but an orangutan is standing in
front of this guy wearing a cardigan
like zip up scenarios have i'm just
sitting around the animals are damning in
front of a guy
and so the monk the arrange things
like i want that sweater like he's
indicating the guy like he left he
lets the orangutan um unzip the sweater
and then he takes it off gives
a talk slower and the guys these
guys are like
oh noes you gonna put it on
it's gonna put it on and then
he the the orangutan like just throws
it over his head and these guys
are cracking up then he does this
twist with it and all of a
sudden he's wearing it whoa his arms
are inside it these guys lose their
he put it on twitter like human
does yeah you got some great
method of putting it up it was
inside out though we should use the
orangutan method to put on all of
our clothes yeah because this sounds amazing
they should have showed him wearing pants
glass shoes spats hat monocle monocle you
know what also i'd like to be
a tasmanian tiger wow there's lot to
be they were thought to be
extinct for many years but somebody cited
one recently really that's a myth that
they were long-gone isn't it wild how
we you know they say we only
know like ten percent of what's happening
in the ocean or something yeah no
we keep track on ten percent know
there's something like there's it goes so
far down yeah we we we pass
any idea i've never
heard the ten percent lie made up
the number i've heard that for brains
which is also bullshit well that's what
i'm using to tell you this fact
what do i think about p twenty
four p twenty four xy the time
p twenty twenty two show some respect
and he's dead why do we think
about him why i find it odd
that everyone is so you know everyone
was like everyone and there was like
a yeah they were like p twenty
my funeral for animals like that it
was honestly confusing and i don't mean
that in an unfeeling way i just
agree with you i'm just like i
didn't really follow it that closely i
was kind of like oh there's a
mount land and then everyone's like p
twenty two was like my hero and
like everything he did was for me
it truly feels like something i want
to farther but i will say that
i did not follow the the antics
of p twenty two too closely but
every once in a while you'd hear
there was a sighting or whatever yeah
and i was i was unexpectedly sad
when i heard that he died i
felt a little sad because i was
watching them on the news you know
kind of showing a lot of footage
and i was like oh let's let's
use famous sad to watch an ad
with someone
i'm famous yes it's like especially thinking
in the memorial he was a local
celebrity you know i guess but i
never want to see like when people
go i som yeah i'd be frightened
i'd shit my pants absolutely i don't
want to see jackpot when he attacked
he attacked multiple dogs right oh get
over your shit my bad yeah and
put down yeah yeah
because see the term baby yeah he's
been hit by a car and so
he was acting as they say he
was acting you're right yeah but but
but there was a baby and don't
you come after my baby that oh
you're kidding of course and kill that
thing attack he didn't kill the baby
though you want to i want to
sometimes sure what happened i want i'm
not
my name oh they weren't really highlighting
that piece when they were to giving
the memories of p twenty two yeah
well you know remember that time he
attacked a baby the other day let's
keep him around twenty two will miss
you all right do do we do
it did you have a three cheer
that you wanted to do oh do
we have time well yeah do one
more voice valerie
i think alright let's see one more
voice now trump will do a teacher
and then okay here we go so
this is another
voicemail another one another one he paul
scott torn it was just really from
den hi joey i'm just curious how
many cuckoo clocks do you think ago
would have to own before people talk
bad behind his back calling him that
weird cuckoo clock day thanks well
i'll tell you our neighbor was an
odd and oddball our neighbor had when
we lived in toluca lake we were
in economy in him he's that old
man that made the puppet that came
alive yes
he had many cuckoo clocks yeah no
we had we had a ah an
oddball neighbor who when i moved in
ah
ah my dope my front door was
open and she just wandered in and
was like wow um and she mentioned
that ah like she wanted to ask
she's seen me around and wanted to
ask if i wanted to go get
ice cream and then she also mentioned
that half of her brain had been
taken
yes and she was i will i
want to say you imitate her voice
the same way every time yeah no
she had a very distinctive voice so
she she um one day i came
back to my place and found that
half of my dvds have been stolen
wow and in their place half a
brain
so we theory
no so cool i went went to
her place to like warn her that
someone had stolen some stuff and she's
like they're not my place you want
to take a look um is very
guilty very guilty sounding anyway so but
collapse over there once and she was
like she had a collection of cuckoo
clocks for one thing and then
she was like
took her into the bathroom to show
her around there's a big ah cuckoo
clock above the toilet and that's how
good you really don't need that up
there yeah you don't need something well
you don't have to twist around to
look at the time was very help
you want to come over your head
and down in front of your eye
or if you're standing up after you
shit and then it's the clock strike
suddenly baja
back to your neighbor but then then
she was like she had the shower
curtain drawn and she pulled it and
there was just cat litter in the
bathtub well that's convenient and then cut
out the middleman oh maybe it was
cat food okay cool thanks you don't
like any idea um like in camps
or just loose just loops and then
that's okay that's actually so disgusting but
then but then i
then she also had like open the
closet i think and she had all
these baby clothes and she was just
up the clock she was like i
don't have children but i love their
clothes that's possibly the creepiest thing anyone's
ever said yeah anyway so she was
real weird and then she what does
she just had the
cuckoo clocks but everything else was clean
beautiful pristine she had a whole brain
i think two is too many i
think you know what you know so
okay i you know the kitcat klock
know the old you get to break
a piece off of it
that's the one that's a cat though
the eyes go back and forth oh
yeah famous celiacs isn't it or is
not exactly it's kitcat it's not official
felix ah okay i've had a few
throughout my life but i was weirdo
i liked them but i've only had
blue book but i like what i've
only had one at a time and
mike got me one recently which i
was so happy to do already have
one now
no but haven't had one in a
long time it's like i don't know
what happened but i have one why
aren't you but the second it doesn't
work anymore weren't weren't you getting another
one if you're gifted to me oh
and and because whoever rule you can
buy weight honestly feels like just if
you saw one and you were looking
for a present for me you'd be
like she'll like that it's like this
it makes sense and it
happens i mean somebody you do like
and die but when i hung it
up in the kitchen i thought i
want ten of these okay i need
ten and ended them all swinging now
and then i sat there for a
bit and realised you were so loud
that i was like if there's more
than one wow it was it's not
allowed but i could hear it as
i was sitting there eating and i
was like
just like his head and that would
be insane yeah yeah yeah but it
would look because you could never get
them all sync'd up you never could
and even if you could that be
maybe worse because be one loud tick
tock we have a cuckoo clock yeah
you do that's rightly the third host
of your podcast it's
it does it does it talk i
can't remember what does it do it
i've been over there it's yeah it
says one of the who famous words
that it's supposed to just coo coo
um and we enjoy very much the
other day um i we've talked about
this you turned it off at night
or you or you just know there's
a sensor and then when it's star
when it's yeah what's really funny is
like sometimes you can hear it stop
itself like if it's like oh really
yeah it's like i got caught like
oh sorry guys i thought it was
morning but um i i broke a
piece off of it the other day
oh just like what i wanna do
your ass you
no scott i need to report you
to h r yeah but i think
that if you have more than one
thing like that that makes noise all
day long yeah that's too much i
agree i agree i think one is
really worth my grandfather had one of
his clocks a grandfather clock my grandmother
had a grandfather
we call a grandfather clock it was
just like ah we would say hey
this is a you but yours was
just like a little so you nothing
because he was a grandfather called it
that also is yours you're saying the
grandfather clock is a clock who has
grandchildren that are clocks
and then he would say these are
you why is it called grandfather clock
i don't know because it's it's steadfast
and true my grandfather i'm i'm looking
it up though and i'll i'll tell
you exactly what but that's a good
question why do they call it a
grandfather clock uh
um wait mr wikipedia is going to
tell us in just a second origin
weight naming naming naming naming names also
look up controversies
first personal life the oxford english dictionary
states that the popular eighteen seventy six
song my grandfather's clock is responsible for
the common name grandfather clock being applied
to the long case clock the song
was composed by an american songwriter by
the name of henry clay work who
discovered a long case clock
in the george hotel and pierce bridge
in county durham in england when he
asked about the clock he was informed
that it had two owners okay two
owners where they married after the first
owner die oh it'd had two owners
since i thought kahneman had sold
cut it in half yeah after the
first owner died the clock became inaccurate
and when the second owner died the
clock stopped working altogether the story inspired
henry to create the song grandfather clocks
are of a certain height usually at
least one point nine meters six feet
three inch
his
don't get it wrong there are also
grandmother and granddaughter clubs so we talked
so lightly you sure know slightly short
at least you're a liar and a
thief why no grandson clock
you know why why god
when are you gonna give me a
grandson ca
huh
i love my curvy clock um i
let make sense that it comes from
a song that's why we call birthday
cakes birthday cakes because it comes from
the birthday song it's really disgusting to
be blowing candles out and yeah we
never knew it until the pandemic and
now if i need it in a
movie i'm sure there are people out
there who are like i actually only
saw homeless fucking of course i actually
already wash my hands
i already scrubbed down all my groceries
well when it's that time because lawrence
texting it's not quite what i'm doing
what are you doing i'm not paying
attention let's just go all right let's
just go but we do want to
say you heard all the numbers you
have a lot of options if you
want to follow us on social media
freedom usa is
is where we are that's right and
freedom usa gmail dot com if you
like says a three-tier which will play
next episode we need more we need
more we need three cheers i know
we have a lot that we have
news but we don't like them yeah
the sucks since once we live we've
seen it for a long time it's
stale to us so sorry if that
happened to you
we always want things that are new
and fresh yeah exciting new um and
if you want to hear ad-free episodes
um go to you know stitcher premium
or cbp world and then um on
tuesdays we're re-releasing the old episodes that's
what we call three visiting on the
two
it is what we call it alright
well i'm laura engine
yeah i don't need to look at
you to be listening to you what
do you want to tell her listeners
oh yeah the word was this is
lauren you have the floor it's whenever
you wanna say
i've ever endangered species is the tiger
okay there is it will see that
we're able to live by
uh