three
the people beeping
um yeah my neighbor dee dabba dabba
you know about boop and beep but
what about bip have been saying this
for years we are not getting enough
bip up in this clip
because bob yes obvious topic bob up
up up up what if we did
that as a three year warranty but
we just say it out loud how
do you play bobby ahead yeah it
was a machine you have to have
a machine the machine like a cotton
gin those weird yeah lady michelle vacuum
cleaner you know when you'd get one
of those and you'd be like i'm
now this is my
the thing i remember when baba was
known it was a whole personnel was
so mean what constitutes a machine ah
you're wanting one
your one your one of your part
i think parts yeah i think you
nailed it yeah part it turns on
turns off but does it have to
have a use or can it just
be a machine that does nothing well
i think like me oh wow also
if a machine is broken it is
still a machine that's so timing such
a philosopher if a heart is broken
it's still a heart this is so
deep although you're dead yeah is a
body which it comes to the brokenhearted
they die is the body machine because
it's a lot of muscle machines it's
a beautiful machine extraordinary machine but once
it dies and decomposes is it still
a machine no
thank you for answering all my questions
here's why a lot of the parts
went away oh so if you have
a tire that's part of a machine
but it's not a car okay so
wait if you have a tire but
hook it up to any like flat
surface it's suddenly a machine any flat
surface yes exactly a board that's like
so
that's right yeah yeah a lot of
science project i did where i would
just kinda like start gluing stuff together
i'm just like it's something
what were the ah and we've talked
i don't know i didn't want no
science projects now don't think so i
didn't glue a tire to a board
but i did do i did one
that was actually very involved i didn't
think you actually glue but my dad
was heavily also involved in making it
um but it was probably middle school
and this was like maybe it was
elementary school it's to admit it would
be clear that i had helped in
elementary school but anyways the idea was
it was a self-watering plant so you
have water or even a watering can
that's on a timer so oh okay
i had a watering can on a
sort of ah which we call it
how often we also know water plants
you know
no
give me a flat like it was
you or you're doing miami so little
air actually okay there was a wheel
wholly but i meant the things i
meant the rubber like i'm sort of
like excusing when it goes around what
she's doing i didn't she's trying to
make this look like gaslighting yes okay
are you done ladies
um yeah anger i mean you know
like you know like put your finger
in that hole but your finger in
that hole but putting them here i'm
gonna conveyor belt conveyor belts around it
and then it had a ton so
it was attached to a timer and
the timer was made the
the wheel move which i often was
time to go backwards go it i'm
sure it was sixty seconds i mean
you're watering your plant every six cycles
every midst it's a concept piece i
didn't have the tools this was what
it could be let's say if you
had a kitchen timer that went for
an owl why aren't there timers that
go for like
water play twenty four hours yeah why
aren't there times they do everything for
kitchen timers to do twenty four hours
their job you need two hands to
drink
yeah i want to invent one oh
love that put an egg in a
pot i guess it's not inventing it's
just making i'm making my famous twenty
four hour eggs
oh yummy there they're only twenty four
hour ray they're completely grey they're absolute
shock enjoy so for my science projects
when i was i think an eighth
grade um our teacher at the beginning
of the year was like ok you're
going to have to do a science
project this year and you're gonna have
to clear it through me and it's
going to be like half of your
grain it's going to be a big
thing
you have to make a huge presentation
and i get the patent yes but
so i was so lazy i wish
to shark tank with things that students
didn't they just act like it was
there they have a pull out three-sided
board and it has three sided born
in this phone boards that have three
sides that stand out but they say
like science proj
fact yeah it's like it's it's like
carbone but you just fold it like
a gatefold yeah whatever you needed to
be called okay honey you don't know
what a something has
when you say something has three sides
that's hard to picture while a triangle
isn't hard to picture something huh three
sides yeah about a person top bottom
middle
i stood corrected both sides asking
um so i never said that i
was so lazy that i just said
like my my idea for a project
was we had a poodle at the
time and it was something to the
effect of like how how long does
a poodle survive underwater
and then we didn't have a poodle
and i had to go to a
counselor it was like how long does
a poodle be outside versilia
suitable pianos
how long is it considered abuse if
it's outside hello does a poodle build
your name pepsi me
wow
i forgot about that mc the poodle
but basically just entailed me like staring
at my poodle all day for a
few days and writing down my findings
oh i love when kids do survive
that and they think that's like a
project and it got cleared and then
i'm sorry what was experiment again how
long how awesome hobbies
a poodle of psi of poodle outside
long ago i'm not what people do
what dat poodle do doe or maybe
it was like how often how often
does a poodle sleep i don't i
don't remember what it was but it
just i just remember sleep you gotta
figure stuff like that now you can
just look it up here i'm gonna
look at it yeah please no way
i've known that or does a poodle
sleep sleep approximately thirteen hours and only
at night ah um total thirteen in
their life sleep during
they're so tight their lives and over
a year they're running on fumes okay
it can be normal versatile use these
running a few some dogs can sleep
as much as twenty hours a day
well that's early hours a day duck
yeah that's like a dog just chill
ah yes it's a hanging chill dog
and cuddle but i remain
nber barely doing the gatefold fold out
and just kind of like doing it
with a marker and no pictures or
anything i think i just like stapled
my the the lines paper where i
wrote down what it'll take to it
or something i got a terrible grade
in high school my first year of
high school i had this class called
ah i p s intraday
victory physical sign your swing penis irritable
penis syndrome you just poop out of
your dick all day yeah and it
makes you irritable
i used to do this we had
to do this experiment we are not
experiment we had to do it we
had to redo a report and i
can't remember what the broad assignment was
but i did a report on computer
languages which really i'm wearing which by
the way who bip bip probably came
into play bip absolutely gaming
this ties into our connections the other
day computer links right that one i
did not understand not complete you finally
did get the computer languages i was
but that was the first one i
don't know i didn't get it i
that was a line i didn't understand
or it was just ah i left
to i don't know what happened it
was bad you gave it to god
i gave that one to god through
god
never gives you a connections that you
can't solve that's not true
you're just not trying hard enough oh
and so it was like i didn't
know what i was doing it was
my idea do you know anything about
computers no ah that go beep boop
yeah that's right that's all i put
up ip i think where i failed
but i got a failing grade on
that paper no baldacci was like
this is one of this was the
beginning of my problems with science at
school where everyone assumed that i should
be good at it why because he
had good because i had good grades
otherwise be right guys shy war go
to school
yeah your name was nikola tesla and
i was just like i didn't know
what i couldn't i couldn't do any
science that had math attached to it
i also just a lot really didn't
know yeah except biology great yeah they
moved me and they moved me into
the slightly dumber track o in biology
ology yes really yes and then i
was like this is where i belong
baby i was talking on the sun
mike's pod tracker but i was talking
about um that in my so i
skipped it into biology freshman year of
high school because you were allowed to
save it to sophomore year if you
want to but no one did that
i just didn't want to do it
yeah and so i
did it in the next year but
that i was in class with all
freshmen hot and two other sophomores because
it was like mostly freshmen
modes and i had to do a
project where we had me we had
a whole semester long project where we
had to like a season long arc
you had to be doing this the
whole time doing what whatever your project
directing a baby pig
god one year they tear it apart
the next year the next together they
put it back together we've talked about
that oh yeah disgusting um what was
your project so i didn't have anything
i didn't think about it for months
i just was like i don't care
but this is and it is weird
that they make you take sides like
what bearing does it have on your
life at all i mean i remember
a couple things from it but anyways
so like what the one we loved
about deet so i remember but what
deet is from silent spring that's where
the kids grind at each other
ah
say i the last second it was
due and i was like i gotta
figure this out so like the weekend
before it was due i i don't
know somebody's friends mom my friends mom
helped me they knew a biologist who
is going to like the creek to
like do a study on how do
they know this person it was so
lucky wait this sounds familiar to me
i probably told it well
well on this i've talked about the
bug man of the bug man of
alcatraz previously i made talked about this
then but this person took me to
like the creek or the river whatever
the fuck it was and you were
never seen again and i want to
hear emma
and we got a big waiters on
and that was like in the water
like getting getting samples and like looking
at the samples of what the semitones
on the spores and like in a
microscope water right just like yeah okay
it's like justin this shit and yeah
and then i had to write a
paper about it and they did nothing
worse than a creek they took pictures
of me on yeah disposable
camera yeah yeah it does in my
book right yeah see my decor yeah
honestly i'm like i didn't know i
did great wow yeah congrats because i
just dated everything like it was all
different times and stuff
that was the only science
report that i can remember that i
ever did well i i did biology
twice because we did it in junior
high and then also in ninth grade
and we've discussed before i dissected both
a frog and a worm i did
worm frog pig i did pig frog
i think the end pig frog the
end
pigs that's the worst that's the worst
it's horrible that it's the most like
a human that's really well you look
like one
just cheese weight and looks wise yeah
you're like two pounds and you're covered
in mud
so your best business partner would discussing
and i was able to skip chemistry
investments just
ah but then i had to take
physics which i don't remember anything oh
that seems than irresistible force and shit
you resistible force in my high school
you only have to take three years
of science senior year i did not
take one i was thrilled huh yeah
that's why schematic in here but that
was my mistake yeah i didn't have
to do math and science my
senior year yeah and we also did
not have a p program at my
school wow guys you never got to
see other dudes naked know you want
to know yeah i've never seen a
penis isn't that crazy it was crazy
i don't i don't not even running
around the school or know nothing i
mean there was a sports program but
we did not have to do p
that's
nice right right hated it every day
going eliminated one way to do swimming
that will come elevating right coed i
remember you saying that they there was
a the pulling people's pants down craig
oh well that was just during basketball
that's just running around the gym yeah
panting people in middle school i know
people would just you could happen at
any
time yeah you're just you have your
guard down and suddenly your fucking shorts
guard always uncles before we do that
during freedom episodes we're always pulling your
pants is so brutal this time around
though it's really youtube because we're sitting
down at a table and yeah my
pants are down right now i mean
i can't tell because we're easy yeah
i took scuba
guangzhou ninth grade weight it's screwy school
but we are planning to drag racing
like in the paul's yeah wait it's
cuban in the pool yeah we just
scoop it in the pool too okay
that's where you do it but it
was disgusting i mean i'm like why
we can't have a i don't imagine
that they were really cleaning those masks
and mouth pieces
you just pulled him out of a
big tub and just used it yeah
i gotta believe that they cleaned them
i hope so i think i think
it's a cursory cleaning at best because
they're wiping with paper towels you guys
have brain worms alright it was horrible
i can smell it right i can
smell the chlorine in the locker-room and
hell panicked i was and it was
like well i couldn't switch to elect
to take a
well then why do i had to
we had everyone had all we got
but i didn't say i couldn't swim
because i didn't know i was embarrassed
and there were some girls who said
they couldn't swim and they weren't sat
in the little pool the whole time
i look back and i'm like shit
done that oh my god just sitting
in a little pool that all but
they were friends and i wasn't friends
so it was like that would be
you decide to drown instead yeah
i jumped i mean i'm sure i've
told this i just on the first
day of the test i first day
of the test i jumped into the
jumped off the diving board and it
was i never done that and i
was like that's great sixteen fifteen and
how did you feel about that i
was a terrifying yeah but no but
yeah good well able to dogpatch yeah
okay but i think frog frog battle
excuse me i wasn't dog that would
have been like library log paper i
just sunk but i i mean i've
got lessons i'm sure i've helped us
to both but i'm not getting in
our heads when i was i don't
care you ever talk this when i
was in fourth grade i couldn't switch
i can swim forever obviously and when
i was in fourth grade
a book about a girl couldn't swim
and it was called wrote a book
by rata but read a chapter book
the alice books not go ask alice
but it was a separate thing it
was real alice always had trials and
tribulations and she couldn't swim and she
learned by and someone told her like
pop up like a champagne cork
i love shrooms go yeah corkscrew yeah
and i just remember that and then
i just did that you just sit
back great and i passed and then
i that i was able to do
all the activities and like i did
probably got better at swimming because of
it but it was always it's also
horrible cause you're gonna bathing suit in
your with poison it's
so gross it's bad and you don't
know your body that's yeah it just
seemed insane that it used to be
to teach someone to swim you just
take them down to the watering hole
and throw him in yeah and that
was it yeah because i lived in
our town as well
no but just you know a hundred
hours ago i mean my parents would
write i was the that was the
theory they tried many times for me
to swim i just always quit because
i would just start panicking i'll get
a little bit better every time i
kind of start from scratch over and
over and i'm not a great swimmer
i had tried i remember going to
camp when we had swimming that was
the worst that can it was
cause i remember being like i could
i could survive said yeah you know
thank god yeah yeah yeah yeah otherwise
it would be to them
oh we never would have had this
show if you died would have been
to them oh no you definitely would
have done a podcast together
for sure um
when i was little and i apologize
if i've told you this but i
did we leave my stuff safe during
your point there are no more oh
i knew it was no more but
we can't during my swimming lessons when
i was five or six i i
was so scared of them that i
email the stone yeah wait how old
are you
give it like well i was eighteen
wow so that was the line six
plus five and then people yes but
i was so scared of the swimming
lessons and so scared of drowning that
i ran away out of the pool
and the pool it was a community
pool and it was next to a
graveyard and i ran into the gravy
i ran into the graveyard and hid
behind the gravestones i this is less
narrative
what a creep
cool next to the graveyard so scary
this cemented too many scary things happening
there's just not enough room we've got
to put it right here my eight
is quite well first of all why
have graveyards well you know that is
good that is a question we need
to consider because they feel
over time there's there's not going to
be space why didn't we bury people
standing when you drive into new york
from the airport yeah and you'd go
pass those very long amounts of graves
yeah then they the skyscrapers just hanging
out right behind them just go like
this is just one step to the
next
ks we live we die it's just
very very depressing to preview of the
future when you go into the big
city one time i was i remember
one night i flew into new york
and i was on that same route
and um by the side of the
road was a car and the rear
of the car was engulfed in flames
mes and nobody slowed down yeah it
was like this is new york and
i'd never seen a thing like that
just like full like kind of a
movie yeah i'm burning my car here
what do you look at ahead
i'll do we were driving yesterday on
the freeway and ah suddenly cliff went
oh no and i looked around i
couldn't see anything i'm like what is
it honey and she's like the guitar
is you sounded so weary what is
it honey what is it now and
she said she said the guitars the
guitarist the guitarist i saw
but what i'm looking around it's called
the pianist idiot
and it's amazing
ah
oscar worthy honey
i'm an l but ah and then
suddenly i saw what she was talking
about she think she meant motorcyclist
oh no is this another one of
those rovers oh she just passionate motorcyclists
but there was a forty two motorcyclists
there was a guy in the fast
lane doing it fit in the downplay
will surely about to lose his ma
doing a complete wheelie whereas ninety degrees
why people in saying i don't like
and it turns out everyone was slowing
down because no one wants to like
be the person who murder this luna
yeah and he's wasn't there totally wheeling
and doing all these tricks and
you know if the freeway is fucking
crazy he finally moves out of the
fast lane weak like creep by him
were looking at me as like a
gopro on his helmet least like
don't lose that because he could hurt
himself and others yes yeah that's no
also just you know being the person
to murder someone like you know i'd
feel bad about what's really well and
you'd go to jail for that the
guitar makes me think about town there
was a period of time where i
kept calling umbrellas balloons and i couldn't
i'm sorry what
how long have appeared this was i
this was when i was twenty four
and i just happened once and then
i was talking and i was like
oh wait i just just kept saying
look at that balloon
and larry or vice versa and then
i was like why what's vice versa
umbrella was like a brand oh right
russia if it was umbrella or a
balloon i was talking about but i
said the wrong word and i was
like what and then i'd had it
happened many more times and then someone
have to sit you down ah it
was like i just kept catching myself
when i was going why
do i keep doing that and then
every once in awhile it'll happen now
that's so straight isn't that weird but
it is like where i'll think the
wrong one and i'm like yeah what's
well it is a rainy day today
rainy days because i have my own
gong gong gong yeah yeah what it's
an english not english the general public
it is very rainy today and it
was raining all night long yes and
that
was lovely oh night long i would
say it's television instead of ed sullivan
all the time i still like on
my john michael was and we didn't
ed sullivan episode on my tv show
and i kept saying ed solo vision
to the point where i was like
why is this happening do you even
know you were saying yeah yes yeah
sometimes when you say mean you don't
know oh yeah weird yea
cool out by the way did laugh
she said i called a guitar
yeah that's really become quiet
i would not identify it as motorcyclists
i would've said motorcycle i don't i
don't acknowledge the humanity of motorcycle wow
i don't think there's done michelle wie
said look at that fucking idiot exactly
and i would said in the rearview
mirror at myself yeah alright we have
to take a break okay great i
don't give a shit
and we're back hope so i was
just about to pop it other vendor
lenovo yeah enjoy that mandarin paul and
i will talk he was going to
tell you guys saying that you say
mush motorcycle machine know there was something
else about something that you called ed
sullivan we were talking about that before
the break
actually that reality we haven't really recap
yeah really recap yeah oh there's this
um new game show i guess that
counts as reality and it rob lowe
hostess so he's a floor we seen
this i've seen one episode of the
flaws seen the episode fly too but
i checked it out larissa wanted to
see what was going on the premise
is is very simple okay
hey here's what this war well just
sound complicated it's a room and it
has a floor in eighty one people
on squares on a floor to weigh
each one edit paul and that's it
and that's it yeah to each worker
they have to figure out what to
do
is an expert quote unquote of one
topic fruit there's no way there's eighty
one deserts anyone want does your hundred
eighty one topics in the world world
know yeah how then they go ahead
go ahead how much is dog outside
show your project go ahead they show
pictures of what they might do for
example they shoot pictures of freedom and
expert in what that mouth
the one i just checked it on
another show pictures of fruits and you
have to name it each person digs
are going that's a lemon lime cherry
and if you get it wrong you
lose time and then you and then
it's three sec and then person is
eventually eliminated from that because they don't
get and they lose they run out
of time on their side and they
don't get enough fruit away i'm sorry
all the eighty one experts are competing
again
each other yeah yeah and so when
one gets picked up again you would
be like i would probably know all
of the
what would you know yeah
way you know about shapes of types
of ties yeah right like a live
ha ha let's say happy because your
name i'm thompson pats okay and like
that i'm older i don't feel confident
going into a wide ah fedora trilby
yeah the candid dogs the other day
it was very difficult i thought i
did that i watched that one i
watched
however the first one yeah that was
the first one i've only seen the
first one one ways it's gonna take
them a million years because i checked
in on episode seven there's still like
a billion people there i'm like we
gotta get down to the one i
want to see someone win the money
well that's that just watched the last
one is not out yet that's all
but i will that's also to me
like potatoes because i love great he
just finished the the first season of
the show alan cumming bringing island so
much fucking my low energy by the
way all of his clothes she has
amped it up so much in season
two i can't wait if i guess
right so when you're thinking do you
need memorize this little his monologues
he hums him yeah i think so
yeah get performer please yeah so great
but he's quick study yeah he's awesome
i watched season one of the u
k which that was where after like
three four episodes when they were when
they voted the roundtable it's still so
many people yeah and i find no
way in the beginning get about them
to us they amped it up
to where it feels like there's five
or six more than the first sees
there were so many and and you're
it does feel like you want to
go like let's just get to yeah
but you also need to see of
course ah yeah because you don't know
you can't just pop in later like
oh so and so has gone yeah
it happened like you need to say
eliminate all the traders the show's done
so they yes i feel like they
must keep
they have to recruit the odds yeah
yeah traders boy in the world that
is part of it we're on like
season three or four episode three or
four of of the us version it's
great so we're trying to avoid spoil
we are caught up but it's tortured
a weight every week here some books
me about it yeah about the us
version is all those reality show people
but why
i hate season two no see i
know because it's all reality right or
you're watching season one right now yes
oh well cause oh well season one
supergirl season one civilians and reality people
smile the way i like the civilian
we've talked about this right do i
need to explain what the game is
anyone out there listening it's basically mafia
are like a small fee which which
we would play ah we we played
when we were
into y u together famous hawaii trip
and the the funniest was when i
turned to janie and i said you're
mafia and she burst into like laughing
tears
it was like why would you say
that like it was so obvious that
you oh my god i love it
it was so funny yeah meltdown it
sucked to play with her because she
could tell when i was like we
could tell each other ally yeah right
i think she thinks i can't tell
what she's lying it's like of course
like everyone yeah which yeah
but she was like i it's paul
yeah right right well that best was
when nora just was like yeah i'm
i'm ah i'm in the mafia
yeah i know when i was playing
mafia know one party i was playing
so hard and i was like people
were saying are you mafia i'm like
i will tell you when i'm mafia
eye opening gambit i'm an honest person
and i when i am mafia i
will say it and then sure enough
the next one i got mafia and
i said
everyone i am mafia
wow and they voted me out and
i was like that proves oh but
but then but then it's dropped into
the next round you don't tell right
i will we were playing that game
secret hitler or the board game which
i'm now certain i mean the real
one was bad enough
you know what i mean the the
public one anyways yeah we went to
watch a game night and we were
thinking about private hitler yeah i think
he's in the army
private hitler reporting for duty nine anyways
the same game essentially right yeah um
but it's a board game version of
that but this way you get to
think about it i know it's not
good but anyways what's worse mafia or
hitler make anyone think of a werewolf
but hitler if he went to a
board game or game nightmare like this
was
years ago and we we all smoked
weed this was years ago yeah okay
okay so three years ago
but i think i was definitely way
more high than anybody else and i
didn't really know the other i can
see that very little
and so it was like my close
friends who were hosting them to other
couples and eyes and like i didn't
really know the other couples like maybe
my first time hanging out with them
and were playing this game and i
like to get very into games like
this like i i want to win
it's fun and but i was also
really high so in the game like
your great grandma oh yeah
i'm very competitive and also out of
my mind you're like you pull cards
and you're determined whether you're a fascist
or liberal which is the famous traitor
faithful and then i like the the
way the cards work like the other
person like will like you basically you
pull cards and you can go like
ok since i am a fascist my
goal is to push the fan
fascist agenda so i'm going to try
to give this other person who gets
to choose for my cards only fat
you know they kind of have to
go with what i'm trying to push
anyway it involves lying involves being like
a little thoughtful i'm right meanwhile you're
high yeah and then i gave the
cards and then they were like i
had to put a fascist site
damn it i want to tell you
you're wrong by the way you're hiring
nicely tell everyone this is too confusing
anyway i literally just go like i
said exactly the wrong thing but i
was so adamant about it and i
was like i had to put ahead
a profession to give me all liberals
or whatever like it was like it
didn't make sense and i was like
why and i was like so strong
and then i was like he's hitler
he told me like
maybe because i'm pointing through the bathroom
i was like when everyone had their
eyes closed he said he was like
i was like
and everyone was like hating it and
it was not cool i can feel
the room turn against me and the
game was bad if you ever seen
any of those people ever again um
i don't remember who one of the
couples was and then the other one
yes but i always feel like the
guys kind of like hey here there's
maybe speaking of reality hi hitler speaking
every other week
yeah um when when my mother-in-law was
staying with us right before christmas or
during christmas actually she she always that
old battle axe she always comes out
for a month or so ah and
stays with us and we were searching
for something to do with her and
um and tricky a cup
of years ago our friend maddie i
had set up she's a big bravo
head she he had set up ah
a sort of tour of the vanderpump
rules restaurants that were out so i
think they went to sir yes they
went to we did tom and they
went recently and they you and i
on this show we didn't
i believe we did we did
where she saw tom yeah i believe
we do we talked about this about
two zero yes two episodes ago
no i wouldn't have stopped you if
it was last season but it's now
but they're dating now oh this is
a new developer mother-in-law yeah and tiny
tom okay you left that out of
the store sandoval know this is resource
why i'm bringing it up samuel can
show up there anymore but he might
be dating her and cheating on her
that's all good boy torching with her
i'd never eve
i thought about that now that's scanned
layers he's cheating with tom schwartz's girlfriend
that is a stand-up wow mutton is
meeting ah my mother-in-law and tom okay
it's still going that's why i'm that's
why i'm how long does bitgo how
long because science report to big gods
but did we talk about the m
day musical hihi etc
because that's the other place got i
don't think so the game of musical
is he
you'll get it all the hits you
e u et cetera you went to
see that yeah it was the other
thing we got we got cushy loves
michael jackson oh it was something to
do she hasn't heard
something to do something to do i
got free tickets for research purposes
oh yes oh and so we went
and like the towns in that time
i don't know that joke please don't
explain it yeah well
ah um but a very very strange
musical about racist maybe his whole life
has their multiple actors playing him no
known well know there are there are
child actors it but but the the
conceit of it is is mtv in
nineteen ninety three
comes to a rehearsal for his concert
in order to interview him in the
the tough but fair interviewer wants to
she wants to make a real documentary
about it and ask him real questions
and they're all it'll be amusing that
is needed to have this sort of
kunci i think he'd just go like
it's his life story what a wish
yeah so so they isn't there just
enough there like to go like child
star we all know the story yeah
yeah i guess i assumed it was
more of a jukebox kind of thing
that was not necessarily was it was
a strange combination of like him talking
about his life and you flashing back
to the sixties when he's in the
jackson five as a kid and
yeah exactly all these and they're singing
the actual songs as these are songs
and we are the people singing them
right and then suddenly hill like starts
in the present day feeling really bad
about something and then start singing it's
like i'm a stranger in moscow and
like it's not a song they'd ranger
in my scalp
happy that it's scary
i'm afraid it was that after he
his haircut burnt
he's injured myself through my own skin
but there was one time where i
what does this thing you see like
man in the mirror something like that
and he sings it to her the
interviewer and they dance around and then
she's like i love i love the
way you see the world through your
eyes it's like so this sounds terrible
i really like god but it's one
like awards and shit right it was
yeah it was winning it was doing
was winning did you play m g
one right where they were and the
guy the guy we thought he was
great i can't leave just link if
you gotta do it don't give don't
call attention to it you don't eat
meat yeah if you're gonna do this
musical i can't stop
you but does everybody else should not
call attention to you should be able
to stop one musical
in our lives i know that nothing
a year one monkey don't stop no
show right but does one you know
it was doha that was musical do
you think it yes gutenberg oh yeah
you thought we talked about it to
show who was the celebrity guest at
dina manzella until z should they make
that note she made that she met
gosh
he's just gotta change it yes so
much better just simply have to flow
change your name it's challenges team adele
design and then we go to emilio
yes which would be great he would
if he she changes her name and
then he he hears somebody referred her
as adele zoom and he's like i
was right why did i get one
so let's make that difference gaslight
z mfa tv moments and like the
last oh it was a gift whatever
years so show i think about it
so often
it's just so amazing he never has
to make another movie that's like it's
perfect capstone of the end of his
could have run for president after that
and yes he should but his name
was adult disease why don't more celebrities
run for president because we found like
this lower really started to yeah but
you know what i mean like this
lower tier gameshow guy yeah gets it
it like anyone could but that's there
was like after trump there was like
the spate of like all these fucking
people that had never been in politics
for of doing like i'm going to
run for office but well there all
your life that fame is better than
politics
why was it like incredibly famous and
rich oh you mean as a guy
just success in politics no just just
like you're you're happier being famous will
probably see me during a colts yeah
public seems like a fucking boring drag
yeah and everyone hates everyone hates you
but you do get a lot of
money being corrupt because the one thing
that i related to trump on is
oh let's hear it is like when
they bathed everyone came out in admitted
oh yeah he doesn't roll up to
the office till one i was like
yeah i get it i wouldn't want
to either so when he was did
he live at the white house at
all yeah you usually do but i
thought he kept his department and didn't
really live there no he he lived
in the white house
but they but they are smart along
with the winter white house yes so
he just wasn't there a lot but
he know he would just be on
the internet every every morning and then
he would like my space and stuff
and then come down yeah like what's
going on his phone i'm like yeah
i got it yeah that's nice but
no i mean there are days when
it's cool ups turn to lose my
job and he's like adjusting to get
the baby in the morning
ng yeah where it's like kind of
just enjoying laying in bed like being
on my phone and i'm avoiding what's
going on downstairs i understand it's great
oh i never get to do that
meaning hollywood allow me to continue sleeping
if mike gets her well that is
the one thing that like we despises
mike right now
but it's like litter like mostly down
with this guy we do take turns
cool up and i go every other
day and when i get emmy i'll
take her downstairs and i'll you know
give her milk and you know a
snack and all that kind of stuff
meanwhile cool op gets her and then
five minutes later i'm still in bed
i hear let's go say
say hi to daddy yeah is defeating
the point like we're taking turns so
i can just layer yeah yeah yeah
yeah i do it so start coming
over when she says that yeah let's
say hi to daddy say hi to
daddy and suddenly i'm in my jammies
crawling into the room crying
jumping up and down daddy
daddy wake up and go oh love
mean alright we think big
and we're back and paul is it
three your time you know what guys
it is three your time holy shit
and this time i was worth going
to play a game called wait if
you would like to send us a
three shirts nothing more than a parlor
game you can write to us at
three dm usa at gmail dot com
send us an email and if you
have a for once new life parlor
game a car game you know that
kind of thing um a game to
pass the time we have fun and
we're gonna have fun with this game
we've played before we're gonna play it
again right this very second it's called
cornell e cornell e what this is
is we go
around in a circle will say the
title of something that we should decide
whether it's maybe will do different rounds
we can do song for instance yeah
and someone says the title of a
song and then the next person has
to say a different song title are
we doing a letter the last letter
or the last word i think the
last law
letter last letter that just see the
last the last can it just be
a word in the song i think
it should be the last oh because
because that's the way it weird if
the word is like a word this
time common let's let's try the last
letter and see how it goes um
let's let's remind me too much of
hunt
let's try it let's just see in
the next okay i don't want to
do that but let's try it let's
do one this way and then the
next time we'll do yo maybe i
did we're gonna try it to see
what it feels good to see because
the ceo goes because usually we say
what the rules are in paul you
say you don't like it and then
we try it and it's fine wow
he said usuage
i'm like yeah i heard you could
pop off right now if you want
to top good but i'm not going
to let's hear it let's hear what
the game is i mean like about
started let's do it let's hear it
by doing with your last letter let's
hear what the game is by doing
the game yes ok
well put thank you do you want
me to start and we'll go clockwise
yes alright trump doesn't understand clockwise you
have to explain it dreamweaver
um
it's hard we just sang one right
before you wanna do a song that
starts with lever reunited reunited
i don't wanna said ron coma born
joe stop believe in
now this is an n right about
it being so because it's an antipasto
medallion but i don't have to start
i don't have to do it starting
with an apostrophe toy if you could
to be great
some tis a figgy boy yeah you
do yeah okay let's say what it
is but i'm gonna do an around
midnight round midnight that's good that's great
ah i'm gonna do an okay ah
no one is to blame howard jones
e
each me
um everyday i write the book
keep
keep don't stop believing keep don't so
um
this is hard keep
keep it calm in ah keep it
calm and keep it calm and oh
don't stop it and then instead don't
stop don't stop don't stop don't stop
the beat i'm out you're out yeah
so we're seeing how we like it
it's hard knife edge by the alarm
e again
um
everybody wants to rule the world whoa
drive a car fuck is wrong with
wow
a lot of words end in e
on finding the ones yeah yeah you're
finding
um
anything with eggs
thanks
anything with eggs or anything with twenty
four hour ways egyptian national anthem
oh my gosh
wow that's a deep hole
oh actually egypt egypt by whom by
oh what's the guy's fucking name i
have it i have it on my
phone okay there's also what it was
something lover is his name jonathan richmond
and the modern lovers modern lovers because
he does egyptian something the egyptian lovers
name of the artist oh the egyptian
lover has long egypt egyptian lover lover
okay so what does it eat egypt
egypt's yeah okay so t the way
we were within
paul you're enjoying this enter the dragon
ooh is that a song i don't
know
let's look it up bet it is
enter the dragon song i'm gonna look
it up
ah there's the soundtrack and to the
dragon but not a song i'm out
wow got you won congrats congratulations now
let's play the way you want to
play paw with a word sure thank
you it's not gonna work it's not
gonna lie isn't gonna work because let's
just try what's right but let's do
it the way why is it not
gonna work do i do a movie
or do you wanna do a song
or do you wanna do like dreamweaver
we now will don't say that
but we want to say it how
about we want to win about in
dreams there's a million dollars ok the
way you want oh it is rain
hell any word from the song well
yeah if you have a compound word
like that like what do you what
else you like wow john weaver come
for me that's two different words this
is getting really here's you're saying dream
weavers two word yes well then what's
the problem
lawrence well we we thought it was
the last word weaver weaver only i
did i also suggested that it didn't
have to be the last word well
that's been let's play that way i
liked this and we'll have a light
on how it's being so because i
i swear to god this how we
played it before that it didn't it
wasn't the last shirt because i just
take a word from it that was
really hard
so i think that can't be how
we play it was irritating and it
was shitty
your attitude yes i agree you know
what you'll just talk let's try it
again stray weaver weaver my heart ah
weaver my
ah okay okay okay um
in a got a dvd because jesus
christ gotta new attitude
ah
new song howard jones ah yeah because
i kinda shit out no i'm not
then why are they all howard jones
oh the butler right let's hear a
bit of new song by our gem
boasting up
a
a throw kilda
throw off your banjo and change smooth
here we have an ad before it
video play soon though it's only ten
more so say please suit those yeah
i'm skippable filed one but don't worry
a video play soon into it you
could also do like the itunes preview
that's true which would not be ads
what are we doing we're listening to
our jones alright let's start again
this isn't even it this is something
called coincidence okay just terminal how about
safety dance okay
wait i wanna dance a new i
wanna dance with somebody
okay
um
i
wanna
um
we dance howard joe
spot i'm joining a body songs about
width i sing the body electric
vain vein um ah
um
i think the sing a song isn't
that what it's calling saying oh saw
make it law was that is that
from sesame zeroing out straw it was
someone so secret i don't know if
there was a carpenter so i don't
know said the original but it seems
like there i'll tell you sesame street
good morning star shine soccer jeff key
gentlemen up
kerr stew this is so me back
to a good song for zula
it's a song song for zula yeah
yeah i know it's a song thing
at the end thing of the other
songs in the world
we bought a zoo
let's talk movie
we bought it too is moving in
parentheses
yes okay and is that a assault
we're doing movies now oh okay fair
enough alright that was interesting we bought
a zoo moving movie
that was the actual title would be
better with parentheses absolutely absolutely because it's
so strange you see it in the
paper about a zoo the muppet movie
so it just movies yeah
um
a muppet christmas carol movie the muppets
take manhattan movie
manhattan movie oh oh oh man on
fire movie the man with one red
shoe movie
ah angels wanna wear my red shoes
song
retail this is like uno and chinese
song angels in the outfield movie we
should do it like you know where
yeah where someone names a movie we
can just name another movie yeah that
doesn't have a word in common or
we can change the subject
let's try that okay okay or what
changed the star weekend or we can
change the category by saying we're already
doing that year no but i'm saying
why are you and elsa like you
say even if you have nothing for
either one you could yeah like obviously
a name in london movie absolutely let's
do it okay okay we'll die
imo she feels yeah because okay so
are you to say anything yeah yeah
yeah just now hey anything okay i'm
just a oppenheimer who ah the atomic
bomb thing
because my bomb person
ah soy milk thing
soyuz this space station thing use guys
afraid yeah okay i analyze this phrase
analyze that movie analyzed this corn
doctor who a porn parody porn
oh um okay
corn
do you do porn or you can
do could you just stop at your
tv
not to give it magnavox tv okay
life's good l g td
lcd yeah i hate that when you
turn on the tv my appearance says
life's good oh yes well isn't that
how you feel when you sit down
to watch your favorite show you know
what's good now you got me yeah
well this is fun that's great i
liked it i tell my game is
cheaper i like to be modified
oh style yeah carlino although we started
school you should also include skips and
draw force into it somehow yeah yeah
wild cards yeah so like girl then
like arm bunches arm punches so i'm
like gotcha like jing sort of like
punch buggies yes yeah if we if
while we're playing the game if we
see a car with one head
like yeah yeah wallflowers yes jalen person
band bob dylan person father
no our own father's father role my
father father my pillow pillow
there's something somebody calling your business like
my pillow
bessie could do that was like my
pillows okay i've never thought about what
heroism thing they were his pillows or
they were saying anyone can have their
own pillow i think it's like when
you have your special building clump my
pillow i've never done oh can i
have my pillow may i excuse me
madam may i have
yeah like a pillow that you like
it's your pillow that's i stay on
the airplane me and my pillow
okay to me in miami
yeah ding sorry could you could you
pull the blanket up to my tune
but not passed over
alright we gotta go listen if you
want to send us a three-tier three
of usa gmail dot com if you
want to leave us a voicemail you
go to a website wait yeah you
gotta head claims eight dot com and
on tuesday we re-release our old episodes
we call it three visiting on the
twos that's why on tuesday and old
episode comes out i mean what do
you call it that too yeah so
listen to those and then also every
other week on wednesdays we release our
three meme episodes every other week on
wednesdays i remember holding this out like
i'm like like like we're all supposed
to if anyone wants to jump in
i guess yeah which i guess you
don't because you're eating and you never
do it lauren you never do it
we learn how saying all of
that we always have to do you
want to say this last thing cbp
world plus apple podcast premium perfect great
job perfect no but that's where the
freemium episodes are that's where we answer
your voicemails yes would you go to
hag claims eight dot com leave us
a voice message and we will respond
to it aw the podcast follow us
on instagram
and this is that the only social
world that's pretty much right i respond
to every comment yes god responds to
frankie entire page yes yeah he was
let us everything he posts everything that
is posted is by scott i won't
give you the login unfortunately yeah but
it's three of them usa instagram yeah
and you know that's
just about all we have to talk
about will be back next week we'll
see you there will tell the exact
same story but in the meantime you'll
get three visiting on the twos and
you'll get a three pm if you
wanna go get that you don't have
to just wait till next thursday you
could have more of all don't don't
try yeah
this is embarrassing
remind me next week to talk about
when we went to shorts and sandy's
with my mother oh yeah goodbye