after
oh my gosh show is you
and you can't hear yourself well guess
well we can hear you and that
was welcome
wow ooh
welcome to three dm everyone the show
or paul screams like a metal god
for ice cream like a metal god
of course well laughs oh they learned
how to scream and metal singing is
they wanted ice cream yes ice cream
like metal gottfried craig hughes can like
about loud right we all go like
oh right right
oh my ice cream days
ice cream please
like say the truck any time whatever
rob halford from judas priest he comes
off stage every concert is like ice
cream please it's my reward eight
ah good ol rob halford and good
ol three-day and we are back welcome
back to the show my name is
lauren lamkin good ol raw alpha my
name is paul love tom k my
name is scope to outdoor man and
this is the show of course with
the pretzel attack to interesting people know
or the pretzel gang wearing them soon
see people we are interesting people and
we are talking you know what it's
the show where interesting people talk it's
a show where interesting people talk to
each other yes right so three interesting
people gathered for interesting or interesting what's
everyone's baseline mood right now ah
everything's ah weird i don't know if
it'll be weird when this episode comes
out we are of course taping a
bit in advance probably by the time
this comes out no family weird yeah
i'll be normal by then we'll have
forgotten everything that was weird weird weird
hey weird do you want to tell
your weird story it's a more
idolized for is it and on laboring
under delusion oh that's right i don't
know what that is what i don't
like you're telling ya it's my comedy
special oh i know now i gotta
believe me scott i know i've seen
it then you have you really i
think so i've seen all your stuff
i think are you sure including his
penis know that's a big part of
my stuff
i mean i think i have i've
seen i've seen a handful of specials
and stand up and you've seen them
all i mean i see
how many can you fit in your
hands driving driving while crying is that
correct
crying and driving okay close close ish
okay um but i've seen one from
like probably the nineties driven oh my
god where i drink the beer and
the drank yeah that's on hbo i
think yes why did you see this
do we are talking about things that
do i know i know but i
mean did you did you see it
while we have known
in each other um probably both what
if she's a super fan like i
probably saw it before i knew you
and probably right instead of it all
comes out now that she's the biggest
allies really love to watch anything my
friends are in i watched entire series
did you enjoy that one hundred and
ten episode comedy bang bang i didn't
watch all one hundred and ten yeah
hey watch it the ones viewers
i saw those
so a few others for sure as
you downgrade to do a view now
like why you saw my i saw
yours i had to chicken with my
paw we have
we never got to do it together
i know because scott hates fun yeah
i don't want to watch you two
doing it together i beg your part
because it's too fun paul was the
driving thing a motif that you are
going for driving and crying driven to
dry and then wait do you have
one you love why don't you book
ended my career for special end
a loud crash roll give one more
ah yes you should have told me
and what was that like while dry
looked like well yeah i should have
told me that you know what but
that story takes place in a car
oh interesting europe still like cars yeah
see ya fuckin weirdo i'm like haha
i'm like speed racer over here too
bidu in cars
funky lyrics you know
like just kinda add more about how
specials in cars more than two
ah i do specials in car duty
did it and so why do you
feel weird paul ah oh i'll say
this so you know i've caught caught
up on all my covert adventures that's
right yeah um not the way ventures
i heard an air ventures about that
i don't know if you've got the
same update but i heard that it
was a false pause i hear that
yes no text to do my i
assumed you knew alleged and cassiopeia told
you yeah
they're not sending you this guy's personal
medical history i'm sorry that's important though
if you don't know who it was
they gonna say like nervous because yeah
i'm sad and if you found out
no one ever had it yes you
feel service but then after the outside
did tell you about that that last
day because i think it was the
next day we were all together yeah
and so sin
since then i've been like maybe what
happened i should go oh yeah i
remember i was like i should go
get a test because i'm not getting
those free tests anymore for for just
showing up at work so i should
go get a test i haven't done
it and of course since then i've
been thinking well i'm sick of course
i think i think i have it
all the time i just got tested
a couple days ago at union station
and it's a walk-up in spanish where
i got married i actually said that
because i thought that was true to
mike oh no you said i tell
testing you started today
oh one hundred and ten episodes of
his show just a few
um but it was easy and i
got my test results within less than
twenty four hours nice okay were you
ever watch dodger stadium yeah dodger stadium
sorry well yeah but they couldn't i
couldn't get a car test as soon
as i want i want to i
went to the walk oh i see
okay one to explain myself i ah
glad you did yeah i got my
first flu shot ever the other day
i really do i really don't want
to do ah why i don't know
that's how i was honestly that's how
i like i don't know i think
i'm when i did or something i
don't know yeah i'm never going to
avoid that from him for some reason
but then my someone i worked with
was like why and i kind of
was like i don't
no i don't know why i was
away from him who's this rude person
ah oh my god remember when you
just asked me why
but everyone should this year right i
mean i know i think it's important
than ever but i'm just like here's
a couple of my things i guess
where do you go
i went to a walgreens right like
i don't want to go stand in
line at cbs no line okay is
walgreens the same as walmart yeah they're
the same okay got it um so
so as paul walker died no high
seas yes i have wondered are they
offshoots just because no no no what
cbs the santa cbs yes they are
the same and ok and the c
v h s also used to be
and is can i tell a story
about that can i finish can i
finish um is vi just say mysterious
yep think i was listening to just
randomly on the radio came random k
leave it i put
a little guitar so rental
entitled things that make you go my
wild morning i know the whole okay
well don't spoil the story but okay
so i'm listening to the story about
your life i'm listening to it hit
right where we are right now and
i hear the lyrics in the last
song and for those of you who
don't know it it's kind of a
song in the bus to move kind
of storytelling like wild thing type song
i went here and
to say hi and they said what
and i like by a lot of
is like these people are doing this
and they do this yeah so he's
telling a story about like a suspicious
woman who who thinks that her man
is cheating honor and so one of
the lyrics comes up and it's like
and you wonder it who bought him
those dvds am like
it's not dvds see what did i
say don't spoil it what did i
say
sorry
but you yeah you know something so
one time you know something you have
to tell everyone i didn't realize that
was the point you were making you
finally retained something you had yours and
you blow it for everybody what did
you think that i would say display
that is not a song i forgot
anyway so i was like just send
me into like an hour or two
like kyle don't play for me by
the misconduct anything like what kind of
dvds would be suspicious first of all
like well at first i was like
is it porn dvds but why would
she think someone bought him porn dvds
as mm
much as just he had porn dvd
yeah around and i was just like
thinking about it forever going like well
who would buy a person dvds i
looked it up and it's b v
d's sure belle viv davos
so they were cds but i don't
even know what a bbt is so
i don't even see underwear random underwear
toilet for you because i didn't even
know
now you think we need to make
up for it by saying you don't
know something that's your base huh so
bds great news
i don't know anything shrine whose timelessness
character that's not a thing about me
and also bds aren't underwear you're more
likely to show you know
they were a brand i don't know
if they're still existed but they were
a brand of underwear they were they
were popular in the nineties when the
song was popular it was like oh
the sex because like they were popular
in the nine mo guess yeah texting
cassiopeia crazy with a picture of her
and dvds in space zoo um but
they were what people were talking about
them because i think before
before then like underwear was just kind
of boring or whatever and then suddenly
like dvds came out they were like
sexy underwear i thought b v d's
was like an old-fashioned there'll be aware
mid arise they look like super fifties
and yeah i don't think it's actually
hot i think it's they're not like
sexy nineties calvin klein underwear
that you're thinking of calvin klein underwear
oh right
you're thinking of jockey shorts wait so
new i just found what certain positions
before nafta was circumcision care protective cover
so it's underwear that has a plastic
dick hole and you put your dick
in
okay but bb these are a nineteen
eighties vintage three pair white underwear so
there's a package that has bpd so
why would someone buy him these i
guess because he stained them you when
he was having sex with lacroix is
the idea that that the the lover
is provided him with soaring underwear and
let the wife like or the girlfriend
whatever she is she's suspicious because he
has new underwear and maybe maybe it's
in the nineties wives by their underwear
seem silly dress to a t to
hang out with the fellas over the
guys and i'm getting jealous coming home
late smell like perfume fume things that
make you go whom
now why wasn't the song inspired by
hit with a brick the song was
inspired by arsenio hall was it was
ah one of his ah in his
monologue it's samuel horse show he would
he would always have a little not
always but quite often have a little
section where he would talk about things
that make you go which was sort
of like i guess kind of
like stiglitz in a way as well
or no jack candies like deep thoughts
or whatever but sort of but though
it was tied to current events yeah
well i don't even know if it
was or as much as it was
just like have you ever done this
this this and this things make you
go we should just look up and
then the audience would go along with
him you and ye
yes you would give after after it
caught on he would give like a
little space so when he would lay
his finger aside of his head as
if in deep thought by jack handey
the audience would also have a chance
to go huh
as loudly as they could you know
whenever i'm i'm thinking man's cheating i
go yeah
i wonder he smells like perfume room
all right here's someone who's found him
dull underwear a little arsenio hall some
sort of a three-pack to see exactly
how he would do it because i'm
interested in the construction of this bill
and to see whether it was told
to our plastics
i'm interested in the construction of this
way that was it oh okay this
video is jason i'm saying that i
talked through know what i mean this
was just like him saying things that
make you go hmmmm ah ok here's
i mean that's all you need yeah
okay yeah you're right alright different minds
proof we proved it we proved he
said remember this will come
later remember when like a month or
two ago wendy williams was like we
are afraid of cordova
no goodness she said it shows confidence
video she she reads trump she doesn't
read trump's tweet i guess about don't
be afraid of coven and then she
goes we are afraid of cordova or
very afraid of those things and the
audience but she say more than one
i said twice now he's going at
their maths zellner
truly was a thing made yeah maybe
i'm awesome
um it was i mean it was
ah it was just a few months
ago but we knew so little about
it it was ah but i remember
going but like core what cordova you
mean in march yeah yeah fred cordova
cordoba actually remember listening to a podcast
ology is all about shaw
photos by ellie ward nineteen i'm like
march twelfth and i was like how
curious that a bat could start such
a thing and then like
just terrifies criminal safe for my children
leaching my apples you know
i never went that far i did
i didn't spray down my packaged groceries
i never did it um times and
i would wipe them down yeah i
don't regret it but my i will
say my parents should regret it my
parents whom i just spent a little
time with they they get out the
handy wipes and they wiped
down the newspaper bajo dying well i've
gotten over the whole thing of like
my packages are gonna kill me but
i do wash my hands after open
the mail but yeah like spraying them
down yes shit i just i wash
my hands after i touch anything from
the outside yes same i wash my
hands after my dirty body janie
every attempts
sure it's cut two videos about poking
jamie
ooh
just look back i still don't like
it
um should we ah make our reservations
for the tamu shattered oh man oh
my god nothing funds ever gonna happen
you know so much fun but we're
here together right now i know i'm
making this happen we'll make as we're
making we are for those of you
who have not heard where we we're
in my backyard and we're
just doing it together because we didn't
want to do it over the internet
where i'm lee scott documents away from
scott scott away from sky i'm probably
four scots away from you lauren yeah
and you have to cross water so
i kind of see whatever airballs can
walk on water but don't ask me
that please i've always wondered i've always
liked you i thought this was over
too
questions for you yeah one do you
feel your name's religious and two do
you feel like your name is the
beatles' i feel like my name is
religious and i feel my name is
the beatles and that's why walking wonder
if i take my shoes off have
you guys and and lauren i've probably
done the answer to this ah ah
but when you grew up did you
ever feel like your name did
it fit you we've had this conversation
we have had this conversation exact conversation
yes one hundred percent get out the
spanking pen baby that's called chevy and
have him drive over with a mask
on and thank us from with speedway
twenty foot long pole does anyone remember
what my true name is
john moscow no it's a name deals
for traditional oh god
less traditional um thomas
no although people do call me tom
by accident that happens to me a
lot of phil
i don't know we don't have like
a fill to you i know you
don't look like a ball to me
i want exactly you like a gift
i want everyone to tweet scott and
lauren what my true name is because
we know why should i remember anything
we've talked about on this show series
hey i'm not saying you should remember
it i'm just saying now that you
don't this is what's going to happen
hey remember my true name i'll see
y'all know it was not healthy yeah
isn't it something like that dorothea allegra
right a a lauren allegro that's right
allergy medicine ah yeah and also lagers
window the nickelodeon show both these things
were invented after i was ligger the
allergy medicine was offended after your
i mean it became a commercial about
the dance the allegro yeah what about
the bada oh the forbidden dance yes
do you know about a little mata
lauren but dad at dead and still
you do okay good
does that is that's familiar to little
bada yeah but i don't know you
know what i mean right i've never
seen a nice god says i don't
know anything baby
i've never seen it actually in front
of me do it o'meara yeah ever
seen anyone do it then no you're
doing it the lord saville rabbit
oh god it was called the forbidden
dance why because it was so sexual
it was so sexual i don't know
that anyone movie you know what they
call the forbidden dance for my era
no grinding your butt on someone's day
what was your first do you remember
your first dance yeah like oh well
you know what i don't know that
i've talked about how i talked about
fortnightly the ball
room dancing classes i know fortnightly yes
so this was a thing and was
actually pretty popular probably for this is
the video game know i know fortnite
i've never played i didn't know about
i don't know if i've ever talked
about this and sorry if i have
but i've i don't remember grade um
in my hometown there like over eager
with me
my home called fortnightly and this was
a ballroom dancing class that you would
take my boys and girls ryedale hot
for every friday night for like you
know starting during the winter i don't
remember why but and it was november
through halfway specifically for a certain kind
of um mainly why
white person but not not fully there
was a black guy it was i'm
sure it costs a good amount of
money and was a waste of everyone's
time
humiliating humiliating because i had to wear
you to wear a long dress if
you're a girl how long um past
your knees and so everyone hates that
because it looks ugly when you're in
middle school math and then why does
that look ugly when you're in bills
because your body it looks matronly yes
like i want to wear eighty no
i was told but i want to
wear short dress
it's like it's like cool you know
it wasn't cool to wear a long
dress now maxi dresses are more in
but it wash and turn to the
left it was um yeah you you
don't wear white gloves eyewear like like
arm length glass right they were showing
were short oh really like you guys
are just trying to learn how to
dancer when we learn how to do
like the faa
fox trot all the different dances wow
and the boys had to wear suits
and ties yeah maybe for the last
class or something but every now every
time you had to say all my
dresses were from limited to it was
like they were that fancy but they're
fancy to me and i would have
to dance with boys but if you
didn't get asked by a boy to
dance you had danced with a girl
and so we had learned how to
like lead and follow because oh oh
yeah and i just remember really distinctly
and maybe i have told you this
but i remember distinctly that the there
was a man and woman teacher and
the man would save the guys grab
the grabber back like a football like
yeah like the shoulder blade like a
football
lol when you put your hand into
the what yeah it is let me
think about this so you're back like
a football so
huh you know like places like you're
supposed to oh like like with two
hands like with one hand like one
of the shoulder blades okay that makes
them back so like when i'm passing
for i'm passing for like you know
two hundred and fifty yards per game
or so oh my god you don't
know what you're talking about
scott who are you trying to but
anyway i'm a nerd your high school
dances where you do to football comic
book one time where you would juke
or grind on people and then there
was what alien and i was never
invited to cotillion this was a sort
of fancy thing that only cool kids
around you and it wasn't
i don't think it costs money but
you had to be cool and i
was never invited to that and that
was like a special sort of fancy
so do you remember like another person
you did a did a dance with
um yeah i remember i don't remember
the first i remember the like the
times that i got to dance with
my crush um in middle school and
ah he
he married a girl from that clay
from from the dance from fortnightly she
was there yeah oh but i mean
he dance with her that night i
don't know but they they were friends
through high school and then eventually they
got married but it was kind of
i i actually googled their wedding website
as a stocker wood and found out
the information say because
i was like i learned they got
married and i was like fascinating and
then i went to their website and
i read all about how it happened
and they were they were just friends
and they never wear anything and then
suddenly they confess they both had liked
each other in middle school
i know but know what is so
much better that it wasn't for many
reasons earlier together yes i don't know
oh it's good it's good
and so i really like the sound
of this guy do you ever ever
i mean i don't think i wonder
if men would even and i don't
think you what was in particular both
of you would care about this but
do you ever google like the wedding
registry of people are like that you
know that you like from like high
scores like i'll never occurred to me
to do it so yeah i well
are they still up huh sometimes they
are or if you know they're getting
marry
you could go check out their wedding
website but sometimes wedding websites are up
forever because people don't delete them i
hope we don't have one
no somebody comes out you can make
sure we got married i think i've
said this on the show before we
got married before wedding hashtags were thing
like yeah right like putting your name
together yes you are somebody who are
sovereign we got married and twenty ten
the year we made contact
and what year did you get married
twenty two thousand and nine oh yeah
thirteen years ah thirteen years no eleven
years sorry two thousand and eight to
twelve sorry two thousand and eight two
thousand and eight you know what i
do which is a great tip for
you guys
november okay huh huh i look at
my exit yeah talk about anything i
want okay but i'm gonna go yeah
i look up anything i really want
yeah why i have it on my
google calendar my counter i write anniversaries
with the years okay i just don't
think i'm doing a show right now
so i didn't want to sky look
it and i'm doing
and i do it for kids my
friends kids birthdays i put the year
there because you always lose track because
he won yeah yeah yeah was he
three yeah what does he for and
you don't want to ask that because
it really seems you're not paying attention
so paul do you remember your first
dance slow dance especially i would say
it was probably at my eighth
grade graduation graduation and everyone's all pumped
up what's the super paw which the
song that you think of when you
think of oh i know dance from
middle school ah ebony and ivory wow
what about you are you dancing with
someone no i wavered right yes i
was not in ebony and ivory wow
we all see jay playing it because
of that to like tell everyone to
calm down
it was philadelphia how does the tune
though oh ne yeah oh re live
to gather and burfict harmony side by
side on my piano key bod oh
lawd wow
god we to it
a banger so good i mean i've
heard every day i loved that rand
can't remember how the verses go at
all we both know that people are
the same way wherever we go there
are good
ooh when everyone now imagine being thirteen
natural learn super weird there was also
also a willie nelson on the willingness
and version of you were always on
my mind oh that's beautiful that would
be wonderful yeah can't remember i remember
dancing that was the same dance yes
oh man i pray for someone man
you
use at all for one and casey
and joda oh right ah thing yeah
better that finally found you and we
also got you also got baby when
we're grinding i get so excited and
rubella like a trap but i can't
hide it and that's all
but the penis touching the girl was
was what did you say earlier joking
is that what you call branding yeah
yeah yeah i mean yeah while grinding
joking to me and where i'm from
and what we called it was when
you basically put your hands on your
knees stick your butt out and the
guy comes up behind it goes
for the record lauren simulated sex with
the bird
they are so weird of them now
but it's doing what there be would
there be little
older twelve thirteen know and were there
there must have been like you would
probably get in trouble for this right
if you got caught by a t
boss everyone was doing it and then
you could then you go like shallows
were just like wow what are you
putting in there on like grind and
someone where you're like basically humping their
thigh yeah yeah sure i mean penis
get hard at thirteen so he never
get high
hard at thirteen
my first dance what well okay i
think i probably told you about square
dancing lessons when i was in sixth
grade we had to do that in
gym and and that was a thing
where it was ah it was you
know leading up to us all going
to camp and having to ask girls
to dance and that was a big
part of like ok when you ask
a girl to dance do this and
this and of course
source the the the day where we
what were the things that you had
to deal it was just like the
dances going to come up it's traditional
for the man to ask the woman
to for the dan's yeah don't be
scared guys you know i know you're
going to be nervous but it all
it's very easy you just go right
go right up to the girl and
you ask her to dance and if
she's polite she'll say
say yes you know do they feel
like go ahead do they give you
like a little script to to use
yeah it was sort of like you
know if you get the glengarry leads
it's like yeah did you ever um
do you think that if you if
you had cordova happen when you were
doing great as you'd be like yes
probably because you have to because i
went i went to camp
i remember watching ah surfing videos at
this camp and then suddenly the square
dance started and i remember being there
were like five of us who just
were you know as they say wallflowers
and never asked anyone and so it
just never happened but then just have
like
did you have like anxiety the whole
time well everyone said i was a
nerd and everyone laughed at me and
everyone like i remember there was one
i always forget that that's a huge
part of your childhood is that there
was there was a time when people
were like the popular girl they were
like daring me to oh the last
stuff go basketball rounds i'll give you
a dollar if you somebody trying to
do that to me all around i
was out
in high rounds like hey she likes
you she says she likes you yeah
like i know she didn't fucking say
yeah damn that suck so when i
was all just like hey that's me
online so you know and then the
other part of it is like the
the gossip train got to her before
then of like scott's gonna ask you
to go around as a joke or
everybody including him we've been putting out
that that's what these guys said
then but then it slipped out any
grade we ah there was the eighth
grade dance and i had a girlfriend
and i oh i turned around pretty
quick free but i was i was
also like you know very diseased weird
about dancing like i never danced in
public right but it was weird so
it was like a fast song came
on
and i went out there and and
she finally was like come on come
on and come dance so i was
sort of like trying to do it
or whatever and then the slope song
came out i always remember the song
he was cyndi lauper time after time
sure just the best song das verse
lately slow dance to eat and it's
great here's my question for both of
you yeah did you go for that
ass of course yeah
early chapter derp derp derp derp air
filters after time
a nice slow juke would you ever
go on dancing with the stars let's
say you're getting a really fair amount
of money every time that you know
and you could use it back in
the day probably ten years ago i
would've said no and now that no
one will ever want me on it
i'm sort of like um maybe it
wouldn't be that bad i remain
nber advising a friend of mine who
was asked to go on celebrity apprentice
i was saying no you you don't
want to do that because that person
was also i don't want to give
anything away but that person is also
not at the apex of their career
right and i was too soon yeah
i was sort of like you're just
going to look like oh you're washed
up if you do
i'm like yeah they should have done
it is penn jillette right you know
because nobody cares ultimately and i think
no like i watched james van der
beek on dancing with the stars and
he was fantastic and i didn't judge
that he like why would you you
know it's like who cares it's not
so much yeah to me it's not
so much it's not so much appearing
on the show it's that what what
does the show and tail
oh and it's like i'm starring okay
saying we're sorry we're all i'm a
i'm a bad student and say we
were all could do it big enough
celebrities to go on lawrence's a short
amount of time though i
it's a short amount of time what
do you have to do all the
stuff oh well but then you know
what i'm gonna weed but it's not
like you'll take him danielson know you
over the course of a year like
ah six weeks oh a lot about
my friend used to work um doing
thomas geraci was a story
so what if tyra banks so great
as the host okay i wanna know
she is launching the hosting that show
i didn't realize she took over for
the bird i need weekly shows you
doing now he quit or got fired
i don't know because sean spicer he
was right because they they they put
sean spicer oh and he went on
to put out a statement a statement
when they cast sean spicer saying i
had hoped i had talked to producers
and hoped we would stay away from
divisive politics but apparently they didn't want
to do that this year and classic
cars and and i agree like i
thought it was wack as hell it's
wacky so yeah i try
horrible i got into the mass singer
and i was like hey i kinda
like the show and then suddenly one
of the singers took off their mask
and it was sarah palin i was
like okay bye yeah i see i
didn't i had stopped watching before that
happened but that was so fucked up
it's like what are we doing with
that i find that weird just because
i mean and i was the recipient
of it but politics are very
the like especially in an election year
they're very the whole world the eyes
are upon them so what i'm saying
when i say i was recipient of
it i mean the the hillary clinton
between two ferns like so many people
watching thirty million the first day but
hey it's not any sense you may
also get new letters yeah and we
get and we're gonna read them today
right
dear bitch
that was to you yes yeah can
you tell that woman i love
um we need to take a break
we'll be right back
and we're back and we're back and
we okay where are we just talking
about we're talking about dancing sony stars
sean spicer oh here's what i wanted
to say yeah this the thing that's
so upsetting about like sean spicer sarah
palin doing a stunt show like that
is that
these people are clowns and we recognize
them as clowns and yet they make
this big stink about being treated like
legitimate people while they're doing the thing
that they're allegedly legitimate for doing then
as soon as they fail at that
they just show they prove that they
are clowns and it's like yeah
yes so
why did you get so indignant right
when everyone knew you were a clown
and called you a clown and you
pretended like you weren't a clown but
now you're admitting you're a client but
then sean spicer puts on like the
fucking child from the mass yeah does
a dance yeah yeah yeah i feel
like it's a clown car like pulled
up to washington oh no here he
goes and
opened it store we gotta cut this
bargain edit point not we got i
don't want i don't want to hear
it from japan suddenly not i can't
do that out of the cloud oh
okay okay everyone who works was really
excited because last season we had a
sort of casual ranking of all of
the it was pretty casual it was
pretty i was only wearing a two
piece suit
maybe i was wearing one piece yeah
tankini and we decided to talk through
what we thought were the best memes
now no this is without eating them
we just joined them just from memory
yeah and then we kinda threw some
thoughts at the other ones we hadn't
tried yet but now paul has gathered
all
he's got fourteen flavours yeah different single
everybody know most there's too many flavors
of them and there's like thirty there's
definitely a a a good i'm gonna
say twenty that they should not have
bothered making yeah there are some here
that i've never even heard of nor
do we want to read all of
them well well ah and then we'll
talk about which seven wondering now we're
gonna do seven later let's talk about
the seven we're doing now
oh yes okay okay so the seven
what we're gonna do is we're gonna
eat seven m and m's and we're
gonna go all at once and we're
gonna decide to figure out which was
which no we're gonna eat seven types
of eminem's and we're gonna like so
pick arredo yeah it's so stupid i'm
very happy pick our top three
three and that those were gonna next
week we'll eat seven more types and
pick the top three of those and
then those six will go up against
each other yes head-to-head okay deaf and
i think we should go in order
together hell yeah we should okay so
let's start with claim the first one
is playing the classic eminem's glass invented
for our boys and world war two
where are they what's the story ah
it's because they ah the idea was
that they were not melt that was
yeah that was the idea you can
have a small portable suite that would
not melt oh interesting i'm like i
just like
it's like i mean they're classic for
a reason fuckin delish imams do you
have problems hearing people eating on podcasts
hey this okay i hate for those
are so good for i won't eat
the whole bag but i will save
it for after yeah alright now we're
going to peanuts peanut this is probably
if i had to guess invented for
vietnam
the other side they were a little
bit hungrier they needed that nut and
the charlie hates peanut but this was
probably the second version right because it
was just a plain npm my memory
yes in my memory yes alright here
we go doing a pub the wiki
can i say oh my god i
love these are always better than i
remember them i if i went to
buy
between brown and yellow bags i'm getting
yellow from drunk in a hotel room
i'll always go for the peanut but
when the peanuts are stale they're bad
i've always started letting myself do that
like recently i eat hotel food oh
really like the minibar do we have
an absurd go to the covers i
would go to cbs and buy a
doll
more
um alright so now we're moving onto
an orange bag these are peanut butter
now i love these i love these
one of the best newer additions for
me are the ones to beat honestly
i think i have to agree
oh so any of these things are
fucking amazing
okay i just saw online today or
yeah i don't know though oreos with
graham cracker cookie flavor and then the
middle is peanut butter chocolate pie flavor
why don't watch so it's like a
graham crust with you know but it's
so graham cracker oreo and the filling
is peanut butter chocolate
we just got these calls come on
co-op order these cookies online they're south
they look like a cake we have
to split them in it's still too
much and you have to warm them
up because the inside was a car
sounds like a fake
did you get a little killer's ice
cream inside and put candles
alright we're moving on to carmel and
then we have to give paul a
lot of credit for putting these little
bags together because little coke bags and
then he put co printed labels of
the flavored title i did ok karma
i say carmel too i grew up
saying carmel yeah embarrassed by it like
it's low class
if i see it spelled out i
feel like i have to say carmel
but in my heart it's always carmo
i don't know about this i don't
know apples i don't know if i
feel like i always say pop but
i have to i've stopped saying pop
because people always call our pap i
mean yeah i could only one of
those they're they're like a meal they're
so chewy and big it's so
a big
alright let's get that out and use
it as a drone no
drop like what are we doughboys alright
moving on to toffee peanuts okay so
this is interesting this coffee peanut like
the peanut m and m's that we
had earlier yet with the addition of
toffee these might be too good for
kids oh
do you like toffee though no especially
after all these sweet things to have
like a little bit of zwinky sour
is a sick it is junkie i
don't like ah i need a water
i'm gonna have one more have have
to know i had to don't do
it
yeah bad oh okay
which one do i want to end
on i wanna add some fudge brownie
okay so new white white chocolate peanut
white chocolate peanut do either of you
like white chocolate to begin my love
why chocolate i think it's fine i'll
eat my name given no other option
but it's not in some it's not
something i would buy
that's also my nickname
why does a whole long so yeah
i after that coffee one i can't
even taste it just taste the the
peanut i'm chuckling yeah no i got
it maybe you need two or three
i got it hey to remember when
they made those um use as a
sort of cookies and cream like cohen
dalmatian aid to ah they did cookies
and cream one hundred and one
formation hershey bars oh oh yeah gross
yeah it was wow oh yeah hundred
one dalmatians hershey bars so they like
cookies and cream and that was when
the it was in the nineties when
the hundred donations movie movie came out
i came up against any of the
white chocolate on that i did not
like that okay maybe onto our final
selection yellow pellicle and this one's new
right fudge brownie
this is new i saw a television
commercial for it and this is what
prompted i went and bought this is
what prompted yes but i've been really
like um what's the word like rationing
them out to myself like i'm giving
myself like a couple whenever i feel
like it because i don't know why
um they they're so big they look
like they have peanuts in them for
the o
i mean they don't write they don't
peanuts no just a brownie oh shit
dude fuck can you sell this at
a bake sale
but you know up there right i'm
not mad about him that's part of
the thing and i mean i'm not
crazy about oh my god it's like
i feel like part of why only
a few times like they're really rich
i think i really like chocolates not
as um not as chocolaty they want
very it's more like fudgy
yes ah the lodge and fudge brownie
yeah well guys i hope you've enjoyed
budge in the basket puts the gym
about ah you lotion in the basket
breeze alright hey we need to feed
it pick our god three image we
need to pick
our top three oh man we do
it we can do it it's hard
it's hard but i got it i
got it i'm on tim i'm locked-in
okay but you gonna put them in
order to get better or i just
just three just three now and we'll
wait we'll put em yeah yeah it's
okay i got it alright lauren my
top three are peanut pay
plain peanut butter
my top three are
peanut plain peanut butter
i'm gonna throw it
so no my top three are
play the whole peanut butter oh he
go on fudge brownie fudge oh so
no peanut no peanuts good but damn
make the top three sorry peanut peanuts
good peanuts good i went back to
back to the to the peanut butter
i'm going to plain take a picture
of your top three yeah ok okay
can you just take a picture of
your top three and it will be
my picture of my top three move
them around move one around
wow these are good so it's interesting
i went back to the peanut butter
you might think that would be my
favorite but i don't know toffee has
corrupted my taste buds yeah no to
the toffee no to the toffee toffee
honestly can go in the trash why
chocolate peanut i mean
i know it's the point i don't
know what they look like like take
the peanut out of it if you're
gonna have we talked and i also
think here's this might be an unpopular
opinion i'd like to know what you
think about this okay the oh no
white person should like these
hitler had good ideas they all look
the same like besides toffee peanut which
has been colored to be shades of
coffee they all look the same and
i think white chocolate peanut be white
while like you should do something make
it interesting yeah yeah like yeah it's
like we are like an iron cross
on it will you know what like
you know like you're getting fruit snacks
and
you like the special one that's like
the white mat one that's like special
do you know look ma no or
do you mean like at easter where
they color everybody taste chalky it's hard
to bite into yeah it's like it's
like you can draw with blackburn um
no but there were these shark of
fruit snacks that were fucking amazing when
sharks and
and they come out they were all
gummy transitioned gummies but then there was
the special ones that were like not
translucent and they were really good and
i feel like that made you feel
special when you got one so i
think that here's what i would do
with the white chocolate peanut i would
and there's also there's other white chocolate
varieties but i couldn't get my hands
i think we should
a white chug up you know halfway
and see if it looks is the
white chocolate on the outside or is
it in the inside i think it's
oh look the candy shell remains honestly
it looks like a skittle ooh i
gotta look from here it looks disgusting
look it up i know i don't
want to um i want chocolate i
wouldn't make the white chocolate ones a
white shell with a red m on
it so it look like a pill
oh fun tom holland show
i just ate half of the white
chocolate it's gross you know it sucks
my
it sucks my dick
sucks
oh well
i hope you've enjoyed this art by
the way are we supposed to keep
these for our next like not eat
the rest of the bag on for
the next time we sampled these are
you bringing more back i'll bring them
back i'll take them home no no
i mean to say no we could
finish are you bringing more bags of
know of our top three
no no no i will i'm going
to take all of them home
because well why are you asking me
sounds like i'm wondering if i can
finish the bags got good yeah fucking
go ahead are you bringing more peter
lungs
because we're not taping over another by
any chance would you be bringing him
is it reasonable to cite questions do
i have to keep half an opened
bag of eminem's in my house for
the ants to gideon yeah i say
water another a couple of ways you
guys what did keep me in your
race sam gonna die anyway
wait what of the other flavors that
you can do have more milk we'll
talk about it next have a ton
more i can bring in a fresh
bag we'll talk about next episode but
we do need to take a break
i hope you enjoyed that next episode
we're gonna try i'll never know if
you did seven new flavors
randy
movie will do it three year after
the show huh okay we'll be right
back
and we're back with more of whatever
this is
ah lauren it's time for a three
yeah i was gonna say you a
funny look on your face like you
have a three-tier in your brain no
it was more that i looked at
something someone posted and i thought that's
dumb bujo but anyways what i want
to do is the game we played
last season or the season before where
we um do one word impressions and
we have to guess who
who the impression is oh yes oh
hey everyone thinks of a person they
wanna do an impression of they can
only use one word we all use
the same word i think er yeah
er we give the word oh okay
so we all think of a word
we all agree on a word and
then we have to do no i
think i think what it is i'll
be like okay in my head i
have my celebrity and then you tell
me the word i have to say
oh okay
sure i think that's fun
sure okay so i'm trying to think
that eating people
oh cut out the dead space that
will ensue for the next five minutes
during like if any human being on
the face of the earth and i'm
coming up short
gonna be people we know or know
sure but they should be celebrities well
i everyone i know i'm saying yeah
of course all the famous friends you
have are pie from the famous phrase
um okay ah alright i have my
um i have mine okay i was
like i apologised law about a
word first and then we'll do ours
grasshopper okay so i'll show i do
this yes okay
grasshopper
um barney the dinosaur
doctor your best friend ivor got him
out of your friend going to hear
it again
grasshopper um um mike pence
no
i think about it though
say it again how how insensitive would
that be because he's dead by now
oh my god can you believe what
if that happens okay just be crazy
we'd be like psychics
go grasshopper
well gristle
ooh this trade energy is good ah
grasshopper who feel like today and i
don't have can i ask you a
question yeah is it from like a
show in the fifties
someone saying grasshopper nets from kung-fu hey
excuse me is the person that person
celebrity and black and i may try
ah no let me try a different
different intimation okay grasshopper
al gore
you're very close oh dipper granton know
the bill clinton oh barack obama yes
obama yes okay i guess he's your
point hey grasshopper yeah i hear that
yeah yeah it was a white boy
like me can do all right well
get ready for my impression
you know my word paul oh no
i i say you're okay i say
you say you ok intonation
intonation
drew barrymore yes andrews sting i didn't
give you a lisp word so that
must have been more different came through
with the tongue it
nah hey is this an impression you're
working on i just thought it out
of mid air because actually i was
about to someone else and then the
last second i want no i don't
know if they'll do him and then
i just switched all right paul do
you have someone locked-in
i did and now it's gone hold
on a second it's coming back i
have ten the word is
city council
oh compound
the word is city council
city council
a city council so i'm trying to
do you doing it like if you
went to another country yeah okay so
it's not brady to council city council
city council and putting pause city council
winnie the pooh no no good guy
poop the closer we need to share
read on
diarrhea oh boy um city council city
council so the pause in between city
and council is not baked in and
you just did it with so that's
it it's not a celebrity they just
think this person might often do okay
is it a man it is
is he very gentle yeah yeah he's
pretty gentle city council is it dudley
no
is it
quint know is it with that guy
fit again city council city council
mickey rourke no ah what a weird
ah dude you throw out there
i don't know i don't know we
can't get it you give up well
is is the person in black and
white now the person is in color
okay i am getting butt bitten by
a bug ah hubris i know i
thought i wouldn't so bug is joking
you toss me yeah derp derp derp
um is it a politician
it is no janie does that to
me at home all the time that's
the only way i could get to
over throw things underhand i've worked well
toss a remote to each other and
she's like if i tossed it to
her i know exactly what i'm doing
i let a gentle underhanded lob i
was told to grab like a football
she actually i'm throwing an axe at
her and
then if she thought something to me
she's going like this
i'm like i don't know that i
could complete an underhand toss although you
do raise i believe if it hits
the ground is that yeah so open
and you don't get your bug spray
it was opened and then we all
got bugs could you toss it underhand
to me i doubt it a fuck
you city council
i have a guy that
well
alright love to him do it do
it do it learn do it to
do it do it do it yeah
see it can be done you have
a shed to get up to two
oh shit oh i don't have a
space well lazy boys years why do
we get these bone stan what's your
care why did we get these booms
dance around and all these boobs sands
anyway
huh
eo do you give up yeah you
give i have a guy in my
mind but i can't oh i'm okay
but you do bother mm okay oh
wait never mind to say fictional people
well the guy who plays him is
not fictional or is it no he
was a made up guy oh my
god yes he was a puppet he
was one of the spitting image puppet
yeah he's been on a rag what
ah okay ready yeah john hodgman oh
interest is genuine again city council okay
i see oh okay no no critique
these wang q ago
city council wow great one
yeah city council you're doing reagan okay
okay now this round new round new
rounds new rules new rao okay paul
give me a word
apathetic
ham pathetic move oh boy oh boy
ah get keep going
yeah apathetic yeah yeah jack nicholson no
i would have done this with my
hair if it was you i would
give away yeah apathetic are you a
standup comedian ah sometimes
apathetic
and
as a yeah aziz ansari no
on cancelled
i brought him out of it
because that retirement for this no it's
not as easy
apathetic
it's not david spade oh or no
no someone we know
okay who sometimes a canap besser there
yeah sometimes a stand-up sometimes yeah yeah
yeah um okay alright let me give
you a word lorin
conditioner
william shatner oh no conditioner um commissioner
conditioner ah condition charlton heston know damn
you dirty apes
conditioner
conditioner conditioner now singing condition oh deserter
jack palettes no i'm guessing all the
ones that should be a shouldn't be
conditioner ah god damn i've no idea
ne boy learns waving her hand around
like a conductor like like a sort
of sword like a sward swordsman conditioner
conditioner oh mandy patinkin in princess bride
no
i younger younger than mandy patinkin and
princess bride well i don't know what
a baby bat but i'm saying younger
and that now this person is now
this person yoda
that's a oh this person oh shit
yeah is it hayden christiansen yeah darth
vader james earl jones mark campbell who
is it ah adam adam adam driver
is no yeah natalie where he's saying
at the end
oh being alive yes i saw it
oh it's great not being alive but
starting i did i never saw that
either didn't love it i loved it
wow
but i also want to work at
hollywood and i'm sending this to ah
rudy child
lombok delete adam brody or whatever his
name is sheet chief brody she told
me everything i've ever said about this
okay that was good ish um paul
okay you're giving poleward word now i
need i need your word and you
get a person i need to get
a personne oh okay i'm not a
person
can be anyone i mean i know
but the problem can be a one
prayer meeting alive or stop because we
gotta eat more don't pick someone who's
dead that we've never heard a recording
of like jesus
you guys sent heard the recording say
half what i found him in a
dinosaur ditch why that is all ditch
i found a recording of jesus the
dinosaur ditch this is a good impression
you should pick this who isn't i
don't know okay i have some book
the middle of that okay yeah of
our limited styles but
okay your word should find out about
new shutter your cameron oh what do
you feel this is a guy
your phrase your word is a pace
um
ah ah is this harder it could
be any worse inductor
conductor
oh wow owen wilson yeah it was
it really yeah how did i get
it i don't know and i don't
know it's i don't know wow i
guess the broken clock there congratulate novi
for somebody somehow around one more one
or more arouse all right let me
exhausted all the people i've ever heard
of fame
what does that what's all that oh
it's you're okay okay okay i got
i got hurt first yeah okay let
me give you a word um
come up it's
oh okay come up it's
it's probably some instagram thought no no
i'm trying to do some of my
face i'm trying to sit on my
face okay do it better come up
in this come up it's
come up ince
it's you already did drew barrymore yeah
it's not her paris hilton
come up in shirley temple surely tempt
well lawrence fingers your cheese clara bow
new shirley temple thing that she did
when she would dance huh as and
she looked at us like this okay
this will reveal who it is
oh shit straining on your chair holy
shit she's standing up she's really making
a few muffins fuck huh you were
just saying that like you're interviewing someone
that's interesting
huh i'm not you're not you're being
sarah jessica parker no okay so okay
ah i could've said yes i could
align and knock him carney forgot about
that i think lie isn't this cool
to have lied felonious monster really look
at my mouth look like little tub
i've never
looks your mouth before that's what happens
nicole richie know it i mean it
looks come up it's
ah lol man i wish you could
see her more face yeah slimer
yeah you wanna to know yeah just
tell jennifer garner ah tell your channel
i get you you kind of has
her chin's to go hey yeah million
generous gee i wish the word had
been credit card i wish it had
been
ben affleck alright i got mine paul
you wanna give me your jaeger to
do
ah
the helicopter flies above us philanthropy
philanthropy
you're not looking lower sorry
in the helicopter oh should we have
a little song from the helicopter happens
he's looking for someone he's looking for
he's like a bizarre word hell i
do
oh yeah it's great for no one
let's can we practice it wants to
make sure we're ready for the next
time we go looking for somebody like
osama he's like a bizarre mom helicopter
love it
philanthropy judge dredd
from your boy rob schneider's movie and
i don't even know it
put is that you don't know a
judge dredd is oh my god but
stopping me from like val kilmer is
isn't well you know sylvester stallone played
him in one movie and then um
i think the dude from the boys
played him in in the recent one
i can't remember any okay keep going
for anthropy
e
um jeff bridges
no brad garrett for i am therapy
sam elliott krista leia
louis c judge dredd to crystal yeah
i'm just naming comedians full y m
therapy
mr snaffle up against full anthropy oh
well well well well well wilford brimley
oh so close i'm almost at the
wilfred brimley line by the way congrats
for philanthropy the wilford brimley line is
how old she was out when he
filmed
cocoon you yes they were what they
were fifty something he was yeah when
they supposed to be like to everyone
else senior citizen was practically dead and
he was fifty i've never seen that
movie actually voicing the weather like in
a pool or something that's all you
need to see baby yeah don mattrick
oh la la full lion but i
feel like back in
the day like people thought of ages
differently like i always changed so also
a yeah i mean it's just funny
that wilford brimley like i think i'm
older than all of the traveling wilbur's
i'm not sure though there were that
picture was going around yeah we're like
it was like look at all these
old dudes well one's forty one six
it still seemed impossible yeah full
lam therapy um you were closer shy
those close with sam elliott yeah because
it's someone doing an impression of sam
elliott
what bill hader doing an impression of
sam o
philanthropy someone doing an impression of samuel
i don't know
lady gaga philanthropy lauren michael leslie bradley
cooper
ah come on i've never seen i've
never seen that movie paul and i
saw together we almost thought together paul
came came to the theater late and
what what happened you walked in and
would not let me in because the
the movie had already started yeah and
like and i told him you told
him not to let me go blind
i got to know and argue
but with this usher outside he's like
it's not fair to the other people
i'm like it is their polynesian it
is the i know it's their policy
but that's just bullshit you want to
make windu something for one minute as
also people are going in and out
you go back in time but it
is score it was when they first
started the arclight theater like a policy
to curb a certain
type of behavior right but i was
meeting other people i was i was
unexpectedly delayed from wherever i was coming
from and i had bought a ticket
yeah did he get refund the ticket
though no he said i could use
it for another showing of another movie
of he would make you go to
a different movie
he forced me to go see a
minions movie oh my god and he
stood next to me he's just actually
the whole time i was like this
isn't disruptive anyway shit minions are odd
alright paul do you have one
ah yeah sure i do your third
one and laura needs to give you
a word a word is firetruck okay
i think the person real fast too
okay
firetruck
hodgman ross perot ross pirot this seems
a little more like the southern lac
fire truck fire truck fire but then
you're doing the opposite again oh if
only i could henry higgins this puts
you in one square block high your
truck fire trick
fire trick fire truck you pick a
lot of gentle people vow yeah i
mean it's just who's in my mind
today gentlemen mind you i'm saying the
fire marshall bill no
with this person ever say firetruck apps
one hundred percent they would yes because
one's coming towards them i was saying
i'm like can't tell you that i
would say that there is apps i'm
sure there's absolutely footage of this person
saying the words firetruck tell where would
survey fire truck on camera i'm willing
to bet my life rudy giuliani
fire trout steve martin because he was
in roxanne and he played a volunteer
fireman maybe so let's get on the
firetruck sure
i can't think of anyone else firetruck
firetruck fire trick is it a politician
no five mantra no it's not an
actor five musician no um what else
yeah wow what else is there
stand-up comedian those are the things you
can build who would be on camera
politician musician is caster high nook
a pertinent i guess ah ah firetruck
tick tock superstar
no instagram thought
i guarantee this twitter image instagram thought
has said fire are going to have
the video tumblr dog mormon with huge
tits like yeah stormy daniels i worry
that instagram stories and tick talks are
teaching our young actors bad habits like
what just
you know like anytime i watched one
of their comedy videos they're always so
big and oh yeah yeah they're always
like all their reactions just like woo
your slate so horrible when they just
cast like youtubers and movies because they
have millions of followers and they're like
oh they can acted in the movie
do you remember before instagram was pushing
reels like if you
went to search for something they would
have little departments and one of them
was comedians or comedy and would just
be these people that you didn't know
that were making like little skits yeah
on instagram and they were always terrible
yeah and it was brutal i go
oh my god are you fire truck
fire truck mister rogers guys
oh well fire trucks not saying that
well gets me in that's that's your
touch so for every offensive character you
should just give me well and i'll
do with lady gaga philanthropy and that
was really fun that was fun guys
sound like it from the way you
said
hey sugar crash well that was really
sugar crumble good news because next episode
we're gonna go right back at bay
alright that's gonna be it for this
episode we hope you had fun thank
you for listening we're at three m
usa on twitter that's it we don't
have any thing creatures so does the
teachers hashtag if you'd like this one
don't tell us just send us
one that you do like yeah and
just focus on the positive instead just
candy or envelopes with powder in them
oh boy
ah yes we want dvds of powder
and dvds and dvds thousand bpd is
to josh's home
alright z-index i'm bi
a