hillary
three
ah freedom beanie
hi everyone i'm scott what happened at
the end he was to call back
up my bottles popping bottles open bottle
and mouth with hot models i'm lauren
no no oh i'm sorry i'm paul
that's right welcome to the show we're
back no further information where back from
st paul we are back in los
angeles no we decided not to live
there we weren't considering that our choice
we were considering moving across the street
from that wicked child anytime come lee
we
a chai from the hotel that's a
water boys deep couch wow um anytime
you travel to a place you have
the the option to stay there and
live there we like to do on
tours we take house tours we go
to all open houses around the area
and we say should we leave show
business and some closed ones like a
regular james ellroy a little bee
any action so creepy bp it's crappy
were creepy and then we go around
the house at night going
yeah certainly creepy wait till the light
turns on in another room then we
run out of there can i ask
about speaking of beeps going on at
night shouldn't be your robot sensors sorry
yeah should everyone be sleeping at this
particular time shouldn't they create a smoke
detector that does not that it that
high
has a clock on it like all
iphones that every year house has been
burning for three hours now no but
you know how when your battery is
low it just stops beeping it it's
always at three am yeah right just
have it time out to where like
it'll beep you you know at eight
am or whatever whenever you get up
your pastry worse
times like you go out with your
pager and then the smoke alarm beeps
you and you go just being one
one with no but you know what
i mean like why why leave it
to chance and because i think they
all run out at three am because
you're replacing the battery at three am
every time what if we left it
to dry rapper yes what's around rodgers
chunks around smoke alarms she
he's so funny he was just on
david spade's late night show and was
so great i was like so charmed
by him really i mean we met
him on ferns i'm sure anyone for
that but i liked him but i
really was like he's funny i like
his opinions yeah i knew him before
i did a guest spot on his
album ah just when you like and
that's how you up sir
i'm not a fan because i liked
the number for wow yeah so it
comes down to sesame street rules for
you always need everything you needed to
learn you learn about sesame stree it's
true wheat cookies by smashing them into
the front of your face cookie monster
eats seaweed known stuff i was watching
sesame with my nephew day and he
was eating
sushi he learned how to ball this
pc political ira did it was so
cool i hope they don't wanna grow
fur and jim jefferies on to discuss
this the pacifica nation of cookie monster
ah i loved it it was so
cute he's eating everything now and he's
like trying to see if he's not
doing that not on kelsey
e not on time when you were
just married i want him to be
happy
i want to eat pussy under the
auspices of marriage you know what i
refused to participate in the wow shot
ah i want to be his friend
who cookie moshe have you ever been
to sesame mr doe i want to
tell me over there aha some of
my friends who work on the show
and oh amazing
really do they how big is the
street or is it just like a
sound stage well i think it's a
stage but it's because they're like a
city block i don't know about that
i don't know if it's all connected
as one piece right right
stuffing or something yeah a real corner
in um mr hooper yeah right r
i p rip rip it up hooper
rip it up hoops rest in power
hooper i went to the county fair
that night i want to tell you
about it to which county the la
county fair well anything even a local
i've never been to anywhere is there
any eh
any
let's counties you found your side county
bakersfield cam how did you found yourself
a county fair just like just over
your life's just accidentally i swear they
ended up down like you took a
wrong turn and just know i've i've
been to a lot of ah bogs
and which ceremony biaxin oh okay but
not county fairs way
well i had a great where is
it located can i ask it's import
mona oh okay it was an hour
yeah they're good i mean that's really
stretching the definition of l a county
sure um yeah but it was massa
yeah it was a massive place it
was like so many and my friends
and i had to find each other
we came in from different entrances and
like took a long time
and i defined each other to just
to let you find your person yeah
i found my what ah it's fun
because my friends ate really crazy foods
and that was their intention that's the
new thing that's been around for like
ten years where they're like will just
deny a new thing that's been around
for ten years true but i'm saying
in the course of the history of
county fairs
yes of course the history of life
which has that's like hey or new
thousand years immortal looking back right hand
mankind crowd this is a new thing
it's only been a blip of a
millisecond or has it been ten years
i wanted to walk you through some
of the things that they ate okay
they were for was pussy involved because
he was not eating that night if
everywhere
um okay they got well we got
to mike chose zucchini fries because we
were like let's try to start your
skinny fries that's right i mean fried
zucchini oh but that that same time
my friends got this fucking burger which
was crispy cream donuts three patties meat
patties and so doughnuts on doughnuts
bon three patties and donors bon now
i saw on i saw these pictures
online and my question is when you
order something like that you buy something
like that you don't eat the whole
thing right so they were putting you
like a tasting menu where they have
but everything was fifteen dollars like it
was like ah and they would give
you way too much
yeah like so it was a crazy
night but they it was i was
crazy well i was crying laughing dollars
well for every item if you're trying
to have a lot of things did
you grow your definitive a crazy night
as you paid fifteen dollars for many
things you know what i stand by
that that's a waste but it was
fun you are nuts lower know you
know what
ten dollars for for well you're doing
like i'm gonna take a bunch oh
yeah and each of them cost fifteen
dollars what does this time you know
you're gonna throw it away yeah opposites
greatest scam about the strong history so
it's a crazy wasteful eve but when
they bit into it i was crying
laughing because not only did they say
this is the most disgusting thing i've
ever eaten but that burger yes it
dissolved
instantly because the buns were doughnuts crispy
creams into the air it's like the
bite didn't make any sense like you
know when you eat a burger like
you'd be chewing but it was just
like gone so it was just like
coughlin handy just kind of disappears yeah
sugary thing and the crispy creams has
sugar on it yeah it's so crispy
cream and just straight up like have
you ever had one that i thought
they made several types of doughnuts oh
like the classic glaze
classic voice okay plus glue got shit
hot gto hot chow ejido gtos hi
your name is hot cheetos please write
in if you're we want to hear
from you you know my serious town
we want to hear from you home
someone made a song that by the
way which we have to either listen
to it yeah i have not either
now anyway if everything was goes deep
fried peanut butter and jelly with
like fruity perhaps sounds good oh yeah
you're gonna like that one but it
wasn't much anyway goes on what like
i've never had i feel like the
last time i was out of county
fair was the orange county one when
weird al debuted his movie the als
brain thing he invited a bunch of
people down there to to watch him
perform and all that and to see
the movie but um i feel like
i had a
deep fried oreo does that good i
thought it was not great i think
i think the thing is fried foods
make me sick instantly so i couldn't
really eat anything there but i did
have i had a really fun thing
that was this gigantic hotdog on a
stick with a tour tornado of fries
oh i mean tornado of chips i
look i wanna look you
oh yeah it was like a swirl
of connected chips so i kind of
slow so no hot dog no bun
but a bunch of like circular chips
with holes and toys wrapped around the
hotdog that looks fucking great it looks
up that was good you didn't need
me making a right yeah you do
make doesn't what about posing
pushes me pitch
the new white beans is that what
that said always my white man that's
what you gotta figure out right
in the last thirty years yes or
has it been ah merely a millisecond
vi sanitation was born a carnival ride
that you've been on i tell you
i'd like that okay so it was
at that orange county fair i'm with
cool up and we take a look
at the she got the discount
and i got the job this scope
so like they're having fun with it
now well as long as i know
it's not true of course it's a
true um dear god but ah this
is lauren so
are you there god it's me are
you still talking to margaret get off
the list yeah i got up here
you too
that's what that's all about i don't
think is that about right important i
read it i read all those judy
blume books when i was a kid
she's that the inciting incident she was
cool cool she's still around yes she's
still running she's still doing cool shit
um you got on a ride it
was so the ride we took a
look at this ride and it was
the
a thing that ah you know it's
it's it's really just like a people
mover across oh i want to get
on that okay so the ski lift
yes a ski lift yeah basically so
we looked at that and said oh
that sounds fun so let's get on
it it lifts off of the ground
and within fifteen seconds we are both
terrified yeah because it would be too
there's nothing
preventing you from just like slipping slipping
off oh by the way what is
your in a seat you're gonna see
just like a ski lift and the
reason strapped in there's a bar okay
maybe area you could maybe hold onto
yeah falling right and then you just
start realizing how high you are and
how procure and you know just like
the precious life
versus life is and how little you've
done to deserve this chance um but
me and your nephew he invited you
to christmas you're just being held on
by who knows like a wire or
something like that yeah so we're just
weird terrified and cool up says she's
terrified then i realised oh shit i
have to act not terrified or oceanic
yeah so i'm like
it's okay honey you know i'm just
like giving her the real calm vibes
and meanwhile screaming inside like getting off
this thing and then it just goes
across the entire fair and never ends
and it's like stuff is like fifteen
minute long rod yeah liza see almost
to get back to our car with
our plan but on the way there
we almost got in a car
accident and mike whoa did that technique
of being extremely calm yeah always very
scary um did it calm you down
or was it for other people it
was it was just no just me
and him and it was um it
did work but it was kind of
funny because first of all on the
way to the airport to get back
to la recently we got in a
car accident in our uber unc we
got rear-ended right just the other day
and your drive down the street yeah
no there there and got rid of
it right and you didn't know what
to say it was actually pretty ladies
i want well someone did and it
was really jarring and it really hurt
my back um but anyway about your
neck and my pussy my crack
so when this happened we watched someone
on the freeway rear end into somebody
else like oof really hard and then
that person quickly got into the lane
that we were in trying to get
a winning ram and someone else right
yeah and then we almost hit them
move and then mike like just kept
going and then ah and got us
away and then he was like okay
what were you just saying and i
was like okay so um
is gonna not like elegy
ah but it was like very chill
was he like a stunt driver did
yeah you guessed like because we want
we could if he had been like
a second delay yeah we could have
really gotten no bad accident as well
in a strange little spate of comedy
people getting in car accidents like yeah
yeah it's really weird will anyone but
the pathway we had that accident in
brooklyn that i told you right yeah
tawny newsome got rear-ended in an uber
again see this is the thing that's
you you always feel fine when you
get into an uber you don't know
this person like worse than someone you
know i would rather be driving and
get into an accident then get into
an accident with someone i don't know
do you know what i've i've taken
so many cabs and other type
ps of you know ride cars like
that small jet engine planes small jet
engine plane what is the ah i've
never been in an accident until this
past year i wonder ever happen to
me there are nice people who are
doing ubers or trait i mean cabs
there was another uber that we were
ended our uber oh my if you're
gonna shoot uber you better be good
i do think that the self-driving cars
i look forward to that because i
think i think a lot of this
will you know my theory occurring you
know my theory i don't know you're
it's gotta be everything at the same
time yeah meaning every car selter every
you can have you know like with
bathrooms it's
like what batch row zoo automatic water
and soap and paper towel yeah otherwise
i sit there with my hand underneath
the spray think that automatic soap and
water is helpful is it actually saving
i increase it if they did it
for the water definitely for this i
wonder should i tell
you because i people behave it on
and walk out of the tech i
i would take those things i hate
them and i i was talking with
a friend of mine once and and
saying like i wish i could just
have regular faucets that i could turn
yeah obviously but you know somebody's just
gonna leave that running and i was
like i can't imagine that people why
would people do i guess to a
month later i went into
like an airport bathroom or something and
a guy had just left and walked
away yeah it's ridiculous my dog in
the world like you turn it off
so weird but people are stupid thing
like a thing of hard drives me
crazy as people spitting gum into urinals
oh people do it all the fuck
not
anywhere it's not good it's just gonna
sit there yes for someone to have
your scrape off right here a gumtree
will grow out of the euro that
makes them like san luis obispo and
there's nothing grosser than the idea of
of gum alley gum being pissed on
gum in general is weird
i love gum you love gum i
someone gave me some gum i think
it might have been you the other
day and yes i put it in
my mouth and i was like what
is the purpose of this dude it's
taste good i like to chew and
it smells i like to
that i guess yeah maybe i don't
like to chew and that's why i
don't like yeah it just feels like
the flavor is very fleeting yeah i
like your loved one and you're going
wrong some people think it looks really
stupid to chew gum but it feels
like a con that the wrigley family
has inflicted upon us like hey this
is a thing we all like to
do and suddenly gum is everyway
there you go into the airports and
they're all like hey do you want
some gum without him like he's giving
up selling you at the oh yeah
it's no they do that all the
time oh the airport they're always like
oh by the way or gum that's
the new mice look oh wow it
was like started fifty years ago it's
a new thing fifty years from now
they're always like do you want a
bottle water or gum with that every
single time
no one has ever asked me if
i want something more at hudson news
really ivor what do you buy it
how to news water and gum ah
yea i buy water and i buy
snow or like damn i get upsell
this was you know if they said
would you like to buy reese's pieces
with that
i would have liked honestly yeah i
would probably go i'd be like oh
why did you say that would you
like to buy this stupid stuffed animal
with that i'd be like yeah
can i interest you in a rolling
stone
um i guess what's the magazine named
after the band no i think it
was named after the dylan song i
lacked a role in stowe either way
dumb either way yeah call it rock
magazine oh is that why because it's
raw rolling rock beer you remember when
they debating me
maybe your magazine years ago when that
magazine she bangs comes out what because
ricky martin was so popular oh no
shit banking magazine is still very journalistically
oh i think one could argue that
the impact of the bob dylan had
on the culture is perhaps a little
more significant than ricky martin pe yeah
wow culture why didn't they
name it blowing in the wind magazine
that's a good point see there you
have a point how about raised twenty
les mec there i totally agree with
you i would prefer lay lady lay
i saw this funny onion magazine was
like the onion but just twenty i
said hey i think i'll be fair
it was a weird cheap um and
it said it was bob dylan on
the cover and it was like
bob dylan on how he likes his
corn and why he lies so it
was like that's somebody and that somebody
commented it's even funnier because it's like
implies that he was more he would
sit down with you to talk about
corn but he wouldn't go accept his
nobel prize or whatever he won and
i love that i thought that was
so funny love and i was like
i want to
know why he likes his going
really i yeah i can't imagine anyone
being that important to people anymore do
you know what i mean like everyone
knows everyone can on the same page
with everyone's just like bob dylan is
it speaks for all of us at
who are this age between you know
like ah you know what at the
time sixteen and twenty five or whatever
bob dylan you don't think is the
same
case with billie eilish
you know there but see this is
the thing it's like generationally probably there
are those people who are younger than
we just don't care oh yeah like
candy pie
well like bob dylan was that but
everyone was like younger and like well
yeah well also there was less there
were less newspapers and stuff so everyone
could just agree on something yeah they
read and be told what they should
there were only ten newspapers they were
only ten musical artists and was one
radio station and one tv yeah you
know i mean no it was weird
because they and a lot of younger
people don't know this because a lot
of
stuff comes out all the time and
it seems like you're on twitter all
the time and like oh here's a
new song today here's a new song
today yeah there would be one album
that would come out every month and
write everyone would listen to it and
everyone would decide whether it was good
or whether it was bad you had
a full thirty thirty one days to
live with it and then a new
one would come out on the first
of every month are you sure about
this one album per me
month release schedule yeah one album of
any of all music
and on the first you would get
you and your end of the month
you would get your new record
debated
one was iron maiden
new naked please so then if you
were if you were an artist and
you had a record deal and these
and they said you know your album
we're looking at travel for looking in
march but of next year because unfortunately
we're a little backed up there's like
ah john philip sousa album that's coming
out to billy idol
oh yeah
do you think billie eilish is like
this is a little too close to
billy idol my favorite thing is you
i e i was like watching her
on something she was like or maybe
it was the top of a song
that she has she goes let me
take my invisalign for this yeah like
related related oh bo little bo
um lauren who has like has there
ever been a musical artist that has
spoken to you in that way where
you like listen to their lyrics and
you say this is about my life
this is ah yeah great so ask
me ask me paul nope okay wow
yeah right
alright this is good i me i've
only heard like this is good topic
i only heard like three songs yeah
okay and they are the wheels on
the bus wilson bus national anthem green
having green sleeves
i've thought about this the other day
i had ah you and i lauren
were texting about stupid fights yeah we're
the fight is not really what the
site is about but we're on a
texting together and know you guys did
a private one about fights which makes
me think that saudi
did i say something wrong we had
guys like what it was about a
fight i wish you guys would have
just say i would strike
well use did a good job ass
all because i'm now i'm not on
this game you're you don't always respond
and sometimes we have to have a
private chain because it's like we're going
to actually respond i know but i'm
always weird talking about i think that
did not have anything to do with
you i know i know what i'm
saying we could i could tell everyone
everything but i didn't
i can lose your i can go
off the chain and get a response
i must sleep by nine is what
i'm saying okay funny if we felt
like no matter what we wanted to
talk about it had to be the
three of us exactly so but look
at me and lauren have a text
chain going and it's not it's purely
information it's like hey are you
going to this thing because scotchgard are
here tell me real lights ah we
texted about the bachelorette are you okay
nah it's just mainly a three-team chain
yeah yeah like off chain because we
text more okay just don't be upset
we say sweet things to each other
i like you better than sky for
these fights about so i had a
file identify with my first comedy partner
about the song yeah oh yeah so
yes we were talking we was about
gr
greensleeves yes because what and how does
crises go for those oh la sm
i love you do me wrong cost
me off debts good just for i
have long oh so more money lie
in your na ma ne
wow i didn't know you know yeah
yeah and we also had a fight
about another song it was like supposed
thousand different things so the fight was
about he thought the song
he was singing it but he wasn't
when he got to the second half
of the lyric he just sang it
the same way as the first okay
so it never really resolved oh so
he never did yeah yeah and he
was like no and i said what
are you doing it just will keep
going yeah like pre and i said
well i
oh yeah exactly well but it's also
this was just us this is like
an ancient song well yeah the song
is that if you know it at
all how do you not know this
part of it happens a lot though
i mean it can get stuck in
your head that way where you never
do the resolving thing you just all
you know is the first yes but
he i said i believe that it
goes like
this and i'm saying it the way
it's dining zone and he was like
he scoffed at me it was so
it was great because his god a
man such as you to be so
ignorant but also so like you know
condescending is scott talk about story yeah
yeah it feels good thank you for
your memoir yeah
ah no we are all right remember
oh we were texting about because i
had a fight with a friend that
was about something very trivial on the
surface but and i could relate but
it was real yeah and i and
i said it was real like my
friends know all about you i would
tell you
you if it was about you because
i mean funny right now but it
wasn't and i don't wanna tell you
who was about because that's rude of
course that's rude that's rude i'll say
after we set all right all right
oh but ah alright alright alright yeah
he he thought it was crazy to
suggest that the song were like oh
and the energy goes dead da da
da da
ah like just goes in one line
and i'm like that's how it goes
it was really worth user's body cell
phones and he couldn't like download it
on itunes know can you download greensleeves
i got absolutely absolutely absolutely free it
should be paid yeah yeah song should
just be free up because the other
fight was this was a million years
ago in also in philly i was
daydreaming at a bar with some friends
nz i remember one of the friends
was film director adam mckay oh check
out stand up at the same time
and philly sure and we also were
dropping out of college at the same
time
is it free ah well you've apple
me ninety nine cents anyway continue i
wanna i wanna use this to underscore
your saying so we were really tinny
and we were at this bar dirty
frank's in philadelphia
and i think in a frank sinatra
song came on the jukebox when adam
was saying that frank sinatra could not
be considered a musician because he doesn't
play an instrument and i said well
i think he can because of the
way he the way he sings uses
his integer styling he doesn't just like
you know it's not just like he's
got a you can carry it she's
doing the same thing that horn players
are doing he's just not doing it
into a horn yeah the voices in
instrument and we went back and forth
on this for ah a long for
awhile and it got heated and then
somebody at a table next to us
laughed at us that it was humiliate
yeah because i inch
instantly saw how stupid it was is
that why you're not an anchorman
i am an anchorman oh yeah yes
what are your anchorman are you the
anchorman the titular ah i had a
between two fern sized role as cat
fashion show mc
but he is in it sorry and
i had a bigger role ah we
were just a weaker me earlier this
year the movie is very funny you
it was very fun i was thrilled
to be there at the premiere and
i'm very proud of you congratulations thank
you very much i'm proud of lauren
thanks i'm proud of me too oh
sky you're proud of me too me
too move i'm proud of that
movement got got in a very funny
joke about zack um at when he
was introducing the show did they did
allow that was funny and he said
you know he's thinking everyone individually lauren
and ryan and because you'll be on
here all the way up does yes
yes and then he said zach who
you know gave it everything he had
from sun up to two hours before
ray
rap
i know you just turn off the
lights go off and you go well
that's all we're getting out his act
today that was really really funny that
was funny um well guys we need
to take a break if that's okay
with you okay yeah yeah is it
okay can we you guys want text
about what we talked for so what
do you think i don't really
i want to but i feel like
he does and i like he needs
that once last two you guys are
mad over there right yeah well let's
take a break it's crazy all right
let's take a break we'll be right
back
welcome back well come back come back
do you think that's where welcome back
came from welcome back i know it's
where welcome back kotter came from there
were like well come back kotter
and they said hold on he came
from brooklyn the fifth largest city in
america that was the that was the
problem is he went back to brooklyn
they're like well come back kotter come
back hotter well i lauren are you
done with your hoops now yes my
mesophotic friends will not be mad at
me
my microphone and friends will not be
mad at no five clinic friends will
not be mad at me alright i
do my we were eating hoops because
someone sent us some hoops so thank
you so there you go i look
no more explanation hoops babe what more
can i tell you baby you remember
i do a little bit of the
gift corner yeah so we got a
few things percent on
this episode of hit percent okay just
talk about what they gave us and
a name we foolishly sits and does
presence yeah i did okay well ah
very nice person named rory sent us
ah this threesome hoop
and also basically it's a basketball hoop
with our photos on it like a
mini basketball hoop that goes above the
trash it's unconnected to the hoops the
bank of hoops yeah the back of
hoops trying to show me longtime listeners
know that hoops are a fritos pra
prop products assume i was gonna say
project she's letting us know that she's
warrior girl
when a girl rory yes not you
you don't think it's from to go
more girls rory what's the dream she
come to life she did she send
us a personalized board oh and we
asked asked do you think your favorite
fictional characters would listen to oh i
whom i know that rory would be
ah pod save america girl that's true
okay i guess on the show
yo we promised to say people's names
if they mailed us their name now
i don't recall another crucial error there
a law or what or or was
it names that we should all be
dear scott walker knew but i don't
i don't know i'll tell you what
this means that we should all be
yeah our dear scott awkward duty and
remaining three boys please say our names
on air as you promised one brian
to kevin that will be offered today
you take care now scott o j
boys best brown and kevin right in
the trash right in the house want
to say the name doug rice
right like say want the just his
name on a piece paper oh okay
and i want to say the oil
weight did people just save send their
names yeah that's okay i want it's
all right but dunno or keys who
sent us her name and a dollar
which i'm gonna why because i just
went to the trouble of opening the
dam and then someone sent us their
name really big
i'll find that later yeah ok guys
looking at camping that big we also
got a ton of pens from someone
who works at pentel and i won't
reveal their name but i'm thrilled about
these paths thank you for the pens
these are good high quality pens thank
you chantelle person um i hope you
don't get fired for this yeah i
hope you do get fired for this
wow enough for now yeah
yeah um i wanna get into more
later i want to call h r
on this person i'm not gonna say
guy because it could also be a
woman that's right or nonbinary person yeah
anyone could be a thief
i don't think so i don't think
non-binding no thanks any thieves oh someone
sent me a spooner she'll girl's spirits
someone sent me a spoon to eat
yogurt while recording thanks will martin thanks
will martin ah do you not have
any spoons at your place i just
slurped the yogurt with my tongue like
a doggy
do you think dogs if they love
yogurt so much why are they so
fat if then if dugard is good
you've told her then why huh if
dogs could use spoons reducing dogbert dog
yogurt it's so good if dogs could
use tools essentially figured you'd know i
don't care about other tools i wanna
say they want to know darby tim
darby if dogs could use spoons would
they or would they just go look
i'm done here already my tides why
why let's eliminate the middleman let me
just get in there like they already
have no dignity
yeah i like the way they work
it no diggity spoons were invented because
of days spoons were invented because those
were invented because of dates so that's
it because of dates because you don't
want to look like a slob just
doing what when you're on a date
okay so the advantage wow and his
butt cheeks when you act
yeah because at home i like to
spoon the buttle i like the michael
jackson in the baja
hey we gotta because if you're at
home you do just lap it out
of the bowl i'm saying that there
are people using medieval times when you
go to medieval times restaurant they make
you do that yeah that's true so
it at a certain date checks at
a restaurant
what do you what is it the
theme park to go on a game
plays the game plays spare playing games
you're not playing game and i'm a
lava low but you're technically you are
playing a game you're acting the role
of finish a theater you know many
many things
everyone's got a crown on your visiting
you know monarch from another country is
it visiting monarchs or is it like
everyone is a king and we're doing
a co kingship well i think they
not they nominate someone to actually be
the king okay so but everyone's wearing
crowns yeah can you wear a crown
if you're not a king yeah she's
been the burger king
have you scam you got me because
yeah you can yeah i assume you're
a burger king
one of the main areas when's the
next time you'll be a burger king
unforeseeable i think the last time was
a burger king okay magic april
better i'll tell you thousand ten and
i know this but i didn't know
this remember where was eating it i
was eating my apartment that i lived
in at that time and i got
stomach pains that felt like i was
being chopped with a knife yeah and
so i decided that was it that
was it for burger king really it's
strange how and it made
it probably doesn't have anything to do
with the burger king that's the other
thing i'd probably probably do with it
oh you usually was directly pro know
probably voodoo attack you can be you
can get ah those kind of illnesses
from seventy two hours before it's like
that's true that's why when you call
up your point laura when you call
up ah a more burger king
no i'm saying this happen to me
i ate a mic rib i was
in joshua for shitting i know this
story i was in joshua tree with
cool op and before a bunch of
people were to arrive for shooter and
field trip with thank you i was
just looking for how to explain it
and i was there for three days
trying to finish the script before the
people got there so i finished the
script and there was no internet where
we were and so we went to
mcdonald's where there's free internet and i
said oh the mcrib is back i'd
never had one i'll have one it's
always back it's always banging like what's
going on did it ever even late
anyway like just look back to school
it's always back
to school it's like hey i've been
in school the whole time waiting for
you
i was here all summer
school so i eat the mcrib go
back to the joshua tree place and
within half an hour i'm projectile vomit
and i say it was the magritte
no i'm telling you we we thought
it was really funny to blame it
on the mcg grib by everyone had
a great time it's hilarious but then
i read an article about how everyone
blames the very previous thing that they
ate and it's usually not it's usually
something from you know and i can't
wait anywhere from up to three days
before and then i started thinking about
the the next day i started thinking
about that my cousin for christmas had
just given me these jams and jellies
that she had made in her basement
and i was like
well that's the other thing i ate
that day i better throw that out
in case that's what it was and
then i read another article about how
those jam and jelly jars are just
like they have so much bacteria in
them and so many people get like
sick from them why i was like
tyrian i don't know but that's but
i've i've heard article i immediately threw
it yeah just said hey
you know this heads up and he's
telling why i was like why are
you talking to me any leads color
line i mean remember hi threw up
in minnesota and i wondering maybe that
was from when eight the night before
so it very well could be in
because he was so weird because lauren
after a show we had like two
drinks and you were throwing up no
drinking
half yeah and it didn't seem like
you were drunk at all or anything
like it just seemed like you were
sick and i think it's just from
something you ate earlier in the day
you were drinking everclear yeah well i
go hard we went to we went
to a college party
what did you let's go back yeah
what did you eat okay wait ready
to go back so the first night
in minnesota we went out to dinner
and i and i that big fucking
the big cookie will know that a
big cookie was that the big cookie
we say nobody else got sick from
the oh that's right we ate that
pasta with the chicken what i eat
the toaster with the juco star which
was really good and then i the
next day had that shithole avocado toast
which i talked about whoa this is
it and i thought it was so
gross that i threw sausage oh shit
oh god oh oh susan and then
i eat that really good pass
nta at the place we had the
drinks which we have unfortunately was what
i saw when i threw up and
that's so this is the avocado toast
this is what it is you thought
it was gross by the way che
do you have eggs on it yeah
they under cook the eggs i read
a different article about how ah there
was a local restaurant here in la
that fuck that thing i didn't like
it
trade me there's a local restaurant no
law that everyone assumed they got sick
from whatever they ate right before it
but then when you call i forget
what it's called but you call a
line but when you get sick from
food from a restaurant they take you
back for over three days and they
say where did you eat where did
you eat and then the one thing
everyone had in common was this one
restaurant that did eggs benedict wow
oh had the eggs benedict and they
investigated it was like everyone was under
cooking the eggs wow let me tell
you i just learned how to make
a perfect medium boiled egg and i'm
gonna give everyone the information right now
because everyone every time i make them
ever knows this is the perfect day
librarian music who's over your house my
family was just terrible i made them
for my dad when i was home
i've been making the show section b
the whole time i get made
for some friends i mean people are
loving the eggs okay alright how do
you do it but rudy boy wedding
what wedding greet what i'm gonna give
you you need eggs a big pot
water dude and that's it and a
slotted spoon or you know you know
for pasta something that can granting okay
well a big pot of water
i need to have some room for
the eggs to get into it then
you put the egg into the slotted
spoon thing that whatever we're gonna use
and you lower it gently into the
pod
okay and you lower it gently into
the top because i've cracked a few
and then they start exploding in the
boiling water and then it's really gross
right so you gently lowered and le
tippett into the end of the base
gently lowered once you put them all
in you set a timer for exactly
six and a half minutes six and
a half the second it's done oh
you didn't you didn't
more things actually you're gonna take a
put all the eggs with your slotted
spoon into an ice bowl of ice
water ice water so no different types
of waters i'm not doing this water
there i swerve bag ton ni how
long are they in the ice water
until they're cool enough to eat when
you swim and then you put them
in the fridge and having two days
later they're still perk
still good huh when you say medium
boiled egg what are we talking can
see a yoke is a bright like
a dark yellow and it has a
nice creamy texture to it and i
liked and the yolk is completely i
mean the white is completely hard and
how do you eat these eggs do
you'd put salt on it and just
chomp i do i do that i
also put them on avocado too
post that i make at home okay
bomb dig yeah no dignity no doubt
what's your favorite thing to make at
home for yourself oh do you know
i like to make and we've talked
about it before i like to make
a breakfast english muffin yes i make
remember that i pretty much i mean
who makes the retesting me see the
same thing you liar i have to
make i have to come up with
a recipe that's my thing that i
make
yeah and you should be doing without
without basing it on any other recipe
you should just do it by trial
and error with wow i don't mean
inventor thing so we invented a thing
i mean your hold on a second
let me finish my guys i want
you to finish plenty of time to
talk about bill cosby i um i
because janie loves to cook
cook and she cooks all the time
and i always feel bad i often
feel bad that i don't like ever
but you're also a man it's your
right no chop of wood all fucking
nylon buckle up and broccoli chop and
raw chicken malaysia house beg your cancelled
chicken record um so i
want to figure out i want to
decide what is my thing going to
be it was when you decided because
you would have it one day and
go this is delicious i want to
make this i think i think i've
got to think about things that i
like to eat yeah alright keep thinking
it would be like some sort of
believe me i got that recipe blah
luck i keep thinking it would be
like a pasta dish yeah like a
hardy yeah sort of thing i think
i think you should eat ah one
pasta dish every single day at various
places and then a great play fine
stop exercising three room for three hundred
pounds later find the one like and
then your mario batali what did i
do to save without some chronic i
e pasta at restaurants morning noon and
night okay great i wish i had
done a way she could do that
i love pause yeah pasta what's your
secret you invited mike and i make
a thing maybe i mentioned
two we called junk and so it's
every vegetable that you have in your
house or like ah kiwa whatever like
any grain and any grain and vegetable
and some usually some fake meat that
we have okay and you just put
it in a pan and fry it
up and i'll get better at different
rates based on what
oak fast vegetables cook and then you
just toss it with some like butter
and spices and salts and stuff like
that and it's just delicious yeah and
it feels healthy because it's all vegetable
when you're having us over for this
junk night junk is not for others
junk stuff or others that's kind of
the thing because junk is so trial
and error and because we don't know
what it's gonna go richie
he has like scary to think about
serving into somebody yeah was he at
a movie called tracy letts you know
um i thought your theory freedom trying
out some risking cheery and error on
the battleground side of racist um sometimes
just the junk not work out it's
head moments where it's like not amazing
like i don't yeah but still is
like
comfort and you're together and it's like
at least we have our love yeah
and i mean we didn't order from
language what what kind of fair leveling
what kind of fake media like use
z um gardein brand chicken tenders are
really good and you can have the
gardein brand milani balls with gardein if
you're out there we are shouting you
out so hard
yeah man shit four guards are maypole
patty morningstar patties eight morning star stuff
and this iron morning star i use
the the regular and i i u
e um spicy those are good i
call them sausages and you should call
them in our heads yeah we should
have a threesome pot look wow on
the show
so we should do an episode where
we have a potluck i think it
should be baked goods where we talk
for a while and thankfully get cold
during the break we eat it it's
unsatisfying then we get to go back
and say well that wasn't a good
idea i'll make you all medium boiled
eggs okay please will be your thing
travel great right paul you have a
container that's i got in japan that's
just for once right oh
wow i'm really excited about it you
bring the eggs paul he's gonna make
a pasta good plan king remember that
from sesame street
there is a bit that that as
i guess it's like carl tart it
taught you
ah well it's very rare that
oh that there is there was a
a bit on sesame street that taught
you i guess basically how to organize
things oh because the kin says whatever
sparks joy the king wanted to have
a big ah party like a picnic
for the kingdom sure and benevolent king
people didn't use as most kings this
guy was
the benevolent and he um was telling
everybody yeah everybody brings something and these
dumb dumps were like what do we
bring he's like you know stuff like
potato salad so then everybody brought potato
salad oh okay like no no no
you can't just all bring potato salad
bring stuff like watermelon to then everyone
brings whites right oh then
somebody has to tell a king look
you gotta fuckin break it down for
these people yeah so then does he
list every single thing yes he says
he points to people and says you
bring a watermelon good plan king they'll
say oh i like that and the
idea was ah this is you have
to make a plan and then things
will go smoother so the moral of
this is not don't just
khao tao to whoever's in charge obsequious
know very much them there it is
very much you have to try to
please oh you have to trend and
to degree so just listen to plans
that your masters make for you and
do whatever they tell you tell you
something if here's dumb as these peasants
that is what you should do does
a good point wouldn't it be fun
to be on tests
v street can you cut to the
end gun we saw were on sesame
street together and i know you're angling
to be alone on this but i
think the only way that we get
on is if we hitch our wagons
and we counted three together yeah freedom
and we go one two three dom
and people are like i ok already
know how to counter to go i
don't know what you're talking about
what is an item is i tried
to play my wife she didn't get
it no one has the stitcher premium
account alright listen to this this is
great the great talking about plans oh
course that's what i'll do i'll plan
my picnic why is he a hillbilly
oh you bring the hotdog you a
king you bring the watermelon your thinking
and you bring
the pickle relish you get ie you
bring the nut is like blanking you
bring the leaking you bring the most
dirt game you bring the wrong landing
rings with the king's plan emory
brought some cats like halle berry she's
everybody had a wonderful i didn't mean
it like that you've got idea
i got the ice cream well that's
it yeah yeah yeah that was delightful
like like the world's first rap there's
a yummy sesame street songs that stay
with you forever like i ah there's
one that is a paint that was
like a bowling one and then there's
an elevator one to find the elevator
i like my favorite or hunting
p is for pussy it's good you're
trying to ruin my chances
to get on your chances now well
yeah you on yours a long time
goes like the dirtiest person they've had
i don't know and despite their career
they were allowed any brewery
look we have to keep let's watch
you want to watch them play and
you have to take a break but
let's watch us on our way out
now here's the count to play us
out i don't know if this is
what does that mean the plants out
yellow waves like and go the numbers
only thing i don't think this is
this is not it will come back
and we'll hold on to the road
up to seventy nine
a
one tuesday
a piano and i'm standing on the
ship cheeks onto n and then there
were nine one so
they've got a long time i hate
this song play together mr hall and
bent the word ten lyrics are not
crazy
the numbers don't even extent and atlanta
was like one two three four five
what are you even talking about most
of us am most of those animals
are huge yeah they're not little animals
little whan they're not much else she
says it right there wow so your
hate phil i look this one's after
my plays in anna
html on tv of course he knows
what he's talking about more so i
know what i'm talking about and plays
one of the members
what do we have on dec three
here why do we care we got
one called robber yoon comes through again
robert you're the man dude here's the
game good cop bad cop ah two
hosts act as good cop and bad
cop
op interacting with a person in an
insignificant scenario for example a couple adopting
a pet a band member interviewing a
newsroom doctoring a pet well i was
gonna let it go meaning not police
related like zack other than for the
life hey pat jackley were you're not
in you're not in crime trouble sure
you're just a regular
yeah so who wants to be the
good cop and he wants to be
the bad cop and he wants to
be the interview e um you point
it at yourself when you said review
e yeah so i pointed at you
for good copy for me so would
you like us to do that
yeah ok okay i'm like the scenario
you come up with it okay um
okay let me just think for a
second let's just think for saqa and
alright and will ah will have you
and ten and wearing by the way
we're not cops or we know we're
not cops okay we're just friends okay
but it's good cop bad
new york's the same garlic garlic and
we work at the same place yeah
lauren do you mind coming in here
oh come on in wait do we
have the scenario yet jam sure what
does it tell it you have to
tell us in advance oh i was
i was just gonna ask like i
was trying to think of one oh
this is yes i do but i
was going to have it come out
organically where i said i'm sure you
know why you're here and then she
would have told us but apparently um
it's not good enough well i just
tried to think of a situation thank
you it's like she's walking into our
place of business yeah we didn't summon
her in here while we could that's
what i was trying to do okay
alright okay
um i wanna thank you for coming
hey hey yeah i'm sure you know
why you're here yeah i was coming
to get a haircut from you guys
ah of course that's why we called
you wanted to talk about what i
want and see what you want
yeah like what you want we're not
artists here we're not the people who
can decide what we think you should
have hey let me talk to her
for a second i don't know it
just pisses me off all right you
you try to talk some sense into
orange i want you to have their
cut that you want okay this guy
he's nuts okay yeah i'm your friend
like with the way i want to
do it is i want you to
say you know ah do x y
z i want a little this little
that whatever and that's what i wanna
do for you but
he's got ideas so well let's just
shave her head oh no wait hey
dad right now soldier down just hold
her down just a second off of
me and let me talk to him
for a second i think she's really
close okay alright so what do we
want to do to her i think
he just needs to get her bangs
trimmed and may i think i actually
like ever some some
of course bangs because i think it
was virtually yeah it's like blunt bangs
yeah just like barely just like you
know a millimeter of bangs just like
just covering the hairline yeah exactly exactly
that always looks good so we're close
right yeah yeah okay let me let
me i'll butter up a little good
thing i come in for that right
now look what yeah so what what
was it that you wanted to have
done i wanted to i'm starting to
grow up my bangs and i wanted
them to kind of be pushed to
the sigh oh that's a great idea
that i wanted to have my hair
go um sort of like kate gosselin
from jon and kate plus eight kind
of the old kickoffs and where it's
really short last i slipped back yeah
what are you even talking about
about that is the ugliest haircut you
ever described here i mean like forget
it forget it we are not even
gonna give you anything i just wait
just give me one second i talk
turn away service ah what do you
have some reason why i can't so
go get us a cup of coffee
alright go get a couple of candor
your race
go get a couple coffees i can't
alright how do you want it
i want two sugars one two joggers
sweet don't go back i mean yeah
yeah are you hearing this guy yeah
he wants to shoot normal
we're already getting good
alright okay but what were you gonna
say look he um
i
i know he's not going to let
me completely do what you want to
do okay so what i think to
to to just make this all go
away um how about we trim your
bangs and we give you some highlights
okay why do i have to do
that when
i could go anywhere else hey guys
i got your coffee so i had
other i got the clippers too you're
gonna shoot here we go let's shave
your head oh damn what anyone thought
how about this just like really harsh
bangs like wine bladders just a millimeter
just it's just far enough just covering
the sky just covering their heads
not far gone i want to shave
her head come on man wow right
whatever you say can you work with
that yes okay as long as they
get to keep the rest of it
and make it really short in the
back but long in the front i
can't make any promises but i'll see
what i can do re and seen
a fan it was perfect it was
perfect it was perfect i think my
notes would be just that it was
so perfect it was unreliable
okay um alright we go hey you're
the customer lamar and your i'm good
cop i'm the bad guy i'm a
costumer you wanna come up with somalia
yes give me one moment certainly what
should we do while he thinks of
this scenario i'm going to look at
instagram
well you're kind of leaving me holding
the bag here wow am all alright
i'm ordering ah um it's flower shop
and i'm getting ah some flowers for
my wedding anniversary okay hi sir hi
have you out ah yeah i was
looking to get
some flowers it's my wedding anniversary we're
looking to get some flowers for your
wedding anniversary tomorrow ah yeah i think
we could are you okay sir yeah
you need to maybe go slow or
nervous i hiccup no no i'm just
confused because just want you you know
your anniversary is coming although a year
in advance i don't know i mean
i'm sure we can work now look
it's inco
svn for sure but i'm sure we
can work something out you you want
the flowers tomorrow or do you want
them tonight for two my guess i
wanted to get them well ideally tomorrow's
they'd be fresher your i could pick
them up like i thought i could
place the order now and then get
the flowers to howard but ah how
would the day afterward for you well
not great because that's the day
after the interval and i can't do
this i get what i don't what
did i just say the day we
suggested isn't going to work for you
because it's the day after the anniversary
yeah that's your take hold on although
i think i think we're okay i
think we can figure out a solution
here i think what we could do
is give you flowers the day after
your anniversary but maybe call your wife
and
say hey he placed an order he
just came in a little too late
yeah i'd really rather get the flowers
for the weed has a really nice
conversation with you understand you're not the
boss bud
it's not up to you and to
hear what you'd like you what you
think and what you thought and what
you want it and what you plan
well i mean what about the customer's
always right also ah who made up
that quote a customer and customers fucking
song look at i'm sorry but you
have to look at the sign we
put up it's the bosses are always
right size
toe boxes are never yeah look they're
ever wrong
you say customers never run know what
i said and i don't need to
talk to you for a second sure
look she's crazy yeah obviously she's like
clinically insane she doesn't even work here
i'm just i lit she she's literally
my grandma and she's chasing off so
she's younger than you i see yeah
isn't that weird yeah that's crazy so
is it that
you don't have you can't fulfill the
order in time is that is that
what it is is here's the problem
is this we're lazy and we have
a lot of stuff that we were
thinking of doing until tomorrow i could
probably push some stuff around but the
thing is she's not gonna want me
to you know i need to take
her to
you know thanksgiving dinner early because she's
she's thinks she's going to be dead
by thanksgiving hello you're gonna have thanksgiving
in march yes okay yes she wants
one last thanksgiving with the kids look
and we had that plan for tomorrow
you hear i mean this ostensibly this
is probably more important than your anniversary
one last thanksgiving this guy told me
i beg your pardon ostensible ne did
you see us then i heard you
i heard that he wants you to
censor him and actually you're supposed to
stencil me if you want your flowers
in time ostensible meet all that hold
on hold on can i ask you
something sure we could do thanksgiving on
a friday couldn't we instead of thursday
march twentieth instead of march nineteenth
i wanted to be on the third
thursday if if if this fine young
man he's a great young man isn't
he with how long have you along
if you've been married a year one
year we could get him some flowers
if he were willing to pay several
thousand dollars for them oh wouldn't you
how many several guys i look i'll
give you three flowers you know what
i'm a further three thousand are like
a dozen roses kind of thing i'm
gonna do oh we can't do that
into a somersault to say thank you
so much for your thousands because we
are going under we're going out of
business we customers we'll pay for our
months will pay for one month's rent
which is very high it's three thousand
dollars a month right and you see
the location and the flowers are so
cheap to flowers are so cheap and
we're willing to give any to you
so much and realising my life is
nearing it's end and i'm starting to
regret being a bad cop type person
shit
look i'm grandma grandma no ho go
by by the fall and come away
go away come let's celebrate baby boom
chick a buck
and see
good stuff good and that one i
would say was so perfect it was
even more perfect if that's possible alright
i'm the customer i'm the good cop
on the bad cop and the scenario
is i want ah you guys work
at a college and i want to
switch my classes oh
oh okay
hey hey wait who are we going
i was reading we work at a
college and he wants to switch his
class work what a weird conversation for
you guys to have deborah shepard hey
you're here we've been actually hoping you
would show up you know why i've
been dying for you to walk in
here we wanted ate a handsome sir
student to come talk to us about
his problem yeah want to help you
sort out your problem why are you
smacking your fist into your open palm
just be glad that that's what i'm
doing right now because it could be
a mitt and he was a great
baseball player for so many years who'd
you play for fuck you i asked
the questions around here what you're doing
for a team you don't know his
name i don't know
baseball players have all kinds of weird
names these days this is orange strawberry
who played who played on who's on
buying a yard strawberry what position did
you play first base third base what
did you say third base to me
because you are you old third baseman
on my team's name was first base
lou avery you're working me man you're
working in you're gonna regret it sweetie
pie what do you want because you're
actually getting really look honey no men
are talking wow door slam two and
bad cups go to hell and some
rock make you swallow down your gullet
dough down there and eat a bullet
runs through the store
buy a roll bringing it to your
mom oh on a roll she likes
roles you like roles everyone had so
many roles go to the store and
get some hoops oops i did it
again and then and then i went
to the friend who then bought me
some chips with swaps whips
and jane jane jane oh no no
one needs to blame webs webs whips
chains chains chains that scott describing his
room games fuck you
alright good reacher good thriller on you
guys alright we gotta go by we
got we got one more episode so
we'll see next episode lot of thank
you for listening we love you thank
you bye
uh