malaria
a
shh shh apu show she's a bush
abolition of whoosh i put my booth
in her bush alive
ah life
the long time yeah sooo well that's
good okay marriages do with marriage marriages
just be twenty years and then we
like reassess without having all the financial
considerations of a divorce it's just like
i want to marry you for twenty
years this was a plot in something
i residence the simpsons or seinfeld
where the people there were a married
couple who every year on their anniversary
would decide if they were gonna stay
together or not but i think i
think legally legally the problem is then
suddenly like a divorce proceeding happens you
have to split everything equally it's like
could we just like
you just want it to be like
what's mine is mine i'm i'm not
sorry i'm not countering what you're saying
this is familiar how many years have
you been married huh ah it will
be fourteen years this year this april
oh wow what about you sixteen wow
what about you let me it was
twenty it'll be six yeah single digits
arguably it has
in six that's crazy yeah i'm gonna
to be october yeah
yeah mine september yeah definitely september yay
yeah yeah toby i don't think that's
much better hundred percent october op real
pre-ap real yeah um by the way
welcome to three am i'm scott by
the way i'm paul by the way
i'm laura and i wasn't gonna say
anything but i figured i should yeah
we should probably tell everyone who we
are
we should probably tell everyone we i
could be me
have we ever not identified ourselves on
the podcast yes almost every oh i
don't think i feel like we are
so i'm trying to to remind myself
to to ideally trying to eat my
lunch
that's an all time high the whole
time it was richard dreyfuss and i
don't know if he ever said that
i'm trying to eat my lunch i
mr holland mr howlin oh yes you
turkey
we've talked about how and then i
think sean had the same thing i
had wishes when we both saw that
movie we thought that the child went
deaf from from the the open how
loud is open some the positivity was
so bad yeah
yeah we've talked about yeah we've talked
we've talked a lot about mr holland's
opus well you know it's an opus
it's like there's so much to get
into it's not like it's a magnet
it took him by the way thirty
years to write that five minute shitty
song now not to go back over
mr holland's opus again because that's always
looking to be about movie and maybe
i want to watch that again
enjoy yourself five times okay yeah
um i had i was thinking about
this this morning because um you know
i've i don't know if you guys
know this but i recently had a
daughter um what why don't you tell
us anything i'm sorry i don't help
my mind she is ah as if
this as as a p
people are listening i don't want to
say okay great but she's she's over
one sua you spend a whole year
not telling us you had a child
yeah for yeah she's over one and
number two yeah um but she she
wants to take everything apart um so
when she found out that some of
her toys naturally
the unscrew and come apart now everything
is like open open open absolutely am
and she's constantly looking at everything trying
to figure out how everything works yeah
yeah and i feel like i was
not like that as a kid i
feel like i was because i remember
my brother would console
gently do stuff like he would take
off the plates on the electric plugs
and show me how everything inside and
eizo i was always like the goods
i was always like those come off
and i remember i was thirteen once
and he was chose i yeah yeah
yeah he's different
years probably for like a year i
did it i did it for like
a year or two i was actually
pretty actually exactly one i think it
was three hundred and sixty five days
for me but as it is considered
three sixty four because it's like there's
one last daily or twelve and then
thirteen that's a good point yeah and
just on sundays yeah right i didn't
i was thirty
on vacation days yeah but he was
chasing me around as he was wont
to do when he was supposed to
be babysitting me and trying to work
with the switch place with a knife
several times and i had a child
i babysat he's chased me with the
knife once wait you're the child chase
you with an ice was he a
little boy with red hair wearing overalls
could have been he loved to fart
i mean oh that's chuckie i gotta
check back that sounds like gotta remember
only chunky classic joke charles yeah yeah
his name was just name was
chuck e e g what is chuck
he went through like a sort of
finishing school game as charles so bring
it to me oh charles now hello
i'm charles and when he farts he's
like excuse me
doing stuff you you dumbed it
he said this right i don't well
freddie did i don't know i know
friends he did chucky i don't think
i've ever seen chucky scott zine i'm
not
to watch show i think i've seen
the first one i see the first
yeah yeah it's mere child's play but
i remember my brother trying to like
me when we trying to like you
yeah we're all dreaming yeah oh i
relate come on we're just kidding um
when we were able to get locks
on our doors i wrote
member oh we've got a lock him
chasing chasing me and me going into
my room and then me locking the
door and then him
taking a screwdriver and undoing the doorknob
oh that's and i was like those
come off i had like i had
really lost everything you had no interest
interest in how anything worked for take
off shoes those come off yeah i
just ordered the same one since i
was two or my dad when he
would like fix things in the drywall
i'd be like oh there's like stuff
in
the walls and wires and shit but
what's up with your brain when you
think it is i think i do
not care about how things work you
are from a very brief wonder where
somebody who's learned to think about it
and then you didn't care yeah i
truly i think that was ah my
my father who was always a person
who if there was something
wrong announce he would fix it he
would like look up to fix fixing
yeah because he didn't want to pay
for yeah right your wish i really
like about him on her podcast said
a lot of really cool things about
him that he built their whole house
with like yeah he did hit the
house
rearranging the whole rocket lawyer plan himself
like things that are like challenging yeah
yeah yeah yeah so he would he
would do all that stuff and he
he you know learned how to do
like electric stuff ah acoustic stuff yeah
guitars that was all he worked on
but ah so he was always frustrated
that i had no interest today this
and i was always just like well
it works or it doesn't and a
repair person comes in either k that
comes part or it doesn't i don't
care yeah well like i'm actually really
surprised your parents let you guys put
locks on your doors yeah i failed
it in a dream it feels like
i'd ever want
have a lock my doors sometimes wouldn't
even close because it would like swell
oh sure like i'm just like sure
shove it and yeah that's as good
as we're getting here yeah um but
you were allowed to add a my
brother's door had a lock just because
that door happened to work and had
a lot it was like right like
a lock in the knob like one
of those know it was like an
old-timey regular old with a key
e adult in theory where there was
no key i mean oh fuck are
you talking about it was like a
fucking yeah like not a dead bull
but i was like you know what
goes under there's a doorknob and there's
a little like click and killing do
a look okay okay so there's probably
a keyhole but i don't know that
does sound like a deadbolt though sounds
like a deadbolt is that considered a
deadbolt you
yes not no i've bolt dear
excuse me let me google types of
locks fun don't spell it l o
c h oh you'll find out about
three out of the type seven locks
nessie on love him nah block yeah
maybe now daughters were almost through season
two oh boy i know you which
is a much better season to season
one oh good yeah
roblox deadbolt locks cam locks padlocks mortise
lock smart locks and key padlock kind
of measuring having you know the difference
between all i guess i would call
it a deadbolt lock and i guess
you're right greg guess so congrats
i'm happy for you there are some
families who they just never like cool
up comes from a family that never
shut stores which would drive me crazy
like she oh like when are her
mother will stay with us for months
at a time sometimes and she'll like
i'll be taking a shower i'll get
out of the shower the bedroom doors
just wide open and i'll have to
naked go over there and i'll try
to shiny imagine this dripping wet glistening
yeah blinding your dogs imagine me with
a really good body please beads the
water sliding down to my nether region
and my nipples are reading to la
ooh la club collegiate was raised in
a family we've never should i should
just walk out of the door and
just leave it open just earlier in
the shower or if like i'm sleeping
when we would go to to you
know visit her parents in minnesota
ah i'd be sleeping she would she
would wake up go go outside of
the room and just leave the door
open huh which would of course wake
me absolutely not you can't know you
choose that never really shuts doors or
it's just not really top of mind
for her yeah private like privacy issues
she just grew up in a house
where everyone i think was you know
always
in each other's business i think that's
just like a different kind of thing
yeah yeah it is because ah that's
not good what about you but you
had so many siblings we have so
many people we were always in each
other's business but not in a great
way um but we all we valued
privacy you'd go into your room which
be your sanctum and you each of
you had your own eventually but we
shared rooms for a long time because
it was so goddamn many of us
yeah um and yeah i remember i
remember getting my own room and it
was a huge deal after you know
my sisters had moved out and everything
and then eventually my brother move
wd out my older brother moved out
it was just me and my little
brother and we had lots of room
to roam and it was great did
you feel like it was really different
than
i do feel it was really different
like they all moved out and you're
like nah just us
yeah i mean charged that was how
i was in charge like girls yeah
like what does charles chucky chucky yeah
chucky and charge check she chose a
good funny or die video that oh
yeah yes let's call them perfect let
me call up gary sanchez productions
but but lauren your doors never even
close well my door was closed it
was more of a like it wasn't
always able to be fully closed in
the winter a wood fully closed in
the summer it would not in the
summer would expand yeah and sometimes door
just wouldn't and wouldn't close but i
could still close it and you honor
that
at love you have to honor it
yeah when you see the club closed
door but yeah i mean i feel
like um it's it's interestingly thinking of
kids having a lock all the doors
in my house have locks so it's
like i guess one's holly figures out
what that is she could lock the
door yeah like that's weird
rd i don't know but he was
like a teenager thing like once we
doing after afternoon to lock the door
yeah because your parents don't wanna walk
in on you yeah well also you
listening to me it's worse it's worse
for them right it's bad for everyone
is bad for everyone involved yeah you
gotta knock yeah you gotta knock yeah
but i think it was also related
you got an act i think it
was
so my brother not wanting me to
go in his room and vice versa
it was more against each other oh
yeah well yeah i'm sure my brother
was trying to keep me out but
i would go in his room when
he wasn't home and clean his room
aka keep every dollar and coin i
found
anything else
your little scavenger yeah and i was
my payment quarter portion yeah i consider
my payment for cleaning the room um
and how well would you clean as
well i liked clean i like i
still like clean i liked like to
wanna clean up around here you know
i'm off duty unless you have coins
hidden somewhere
i do work for going man coins
you couldn't even get me to pick
one up these days wow that's really
nice for you know like pennies so
remember how thrilling i pick a penny
and don't think i would stop for
a penny a timeline i would stop
diamonds are a symbol of your loved
one from the other side in my
family was
so when i went to a funeral
for one of my relatives many years
ago and this old woman who i
don't know what her relationship was to
me or shorter nose stroke your face
and say thinner yeah that was like
dying she was like look for dimes
here she takes like look for times
if you see a dime that's him
saying hello like look for names and
then you would
then you would stems and it's actually
very interesting because it's like i understand
there's somebody out there is like it's
because this is whatever the yeah because
like there's actually whenever and whenever them
well but i'm for you no more
i've seen other people would say well
the logic behind it is actually i'm
saying you see all of types of
coins
do i really real right the times
do i like what i'm doing i'm
just being them okay but i feel
like there will be many times where
it was just a dime where it's
like why isn't it a nickel or
quarter penny and then it felt like
it was like it is a dime
it is a sign okay it does
make me think of the person yes
that's what that's nice yeah
so what i'm saying is there i
don't think other people there is a
logical yeah reason behind it but for
you it was just a nice like
hey this doesn't actually make sense but
it is making me think of the
person it's a nice thing yeah and
do you think if it's a message
from beyond you think the the person
the departed person is saying give me
ten cents yeah i do think guys
i needed to get it to ever
put this on my gray
i do think that yeah yeah i'll
pick up anything from a nickel above
yeah i think pick up news by
nick nicole fifty cent piece you're telling
me i'm not gonna bend over for
that oh well that's that would be
beautiful odd and unusual a kennedy half
dollar sure absolutely
i'll pick up a stack of a
wheel i'll pick up a susan b
anthony yeah i'll pick up like a
penny if it's a rare pairing i
think i'll pick about
think about a buffalo nickel i'll pick
up a boy love alone they go
i found it on the street corner
i paid for a big girl now
reimers three-quarter and now i never did
dorner
i don't think she can do but
you did it you did it was
solid and say that it makes sense
but you don't see money lying around
these days anymore remember like i found
twenty dollars in the middle of the
street once it was when i was
like that's stunning it was thrilling it's
very yeah it was so much money
at the time but you don't see
money down twenty dollars right now i'd
be like fuck yeah
well yeah but you don't because everything
switched atm cards credit cards you just
don't see paying online here yeah yeah
an apple pay dear man if you
found some apple pay in the street
i got like a double-click on that
okay are you okay with stuff like
here and have clown time are you
familiar with the new apple headset things
yeah i don't really know about this
but i just was learning about this
here's all i know about it most
people think it's dumb that's what i'm
getting high your sponsors we love them
i love them who actually only i
haven't really heard about this place was
at the molly essay
and i saw the ad where so
it's like a v r headset oh
i guess mike said it's aer something
i don't know and then it has
a it's
something else and i had a cord
on the back like you're plugged in
you know like avatar and the strip
your pony tones see your eyes yeah
and then so the idea is that
you're like with your family but you're
like also like zara dot com yeah
yeah it's like it's like dot com
zara what's ow tos yeah yeah it's
like the google glass google glass is
like
google glass google glass google you know
how you're supposed to have conversations with
people and all that while you can
still see but that's like sofa icon
why is that better it's not if
there actually will never be popular i
only ever saw google glasses in person
one time and it was i was
driving down beverly boulevard and ah i
got in front of a guy who
i thought was driving able to solely
and then of course an open to
stop light and i'm more i'm the
classic ligurian heard that allows online yeah
but it's like really i just didn't
want to be behind that dude anymore
right and then he pulled up next
to me
and was like motioning for me to
roll down my window but i rolled
down my window and it's something to
say you had to get here and
such a harrow and i said i
said are you wearing google glass and
such and then i rolled my window
up in the light turned
nah are you wearing google glasses so
fucking nerd fuck you ah how did
you ever say something like that to
a person new to him it's actually
yeah yeah charlie i go but it
could work with like anything though like
if you're just like are you wearing
flags yeah
and then just drive away and i'm
like are you wearing a t-shirt the
oh thanks for wearing your best t-shirt
on our trip
that's savage even i wouldn't do that
alright we're savoring
and we're back and listen i want
to thank all of you wearing your
best t-shirt for your car trips yeah
thank you it is nice the all
dressed up to listen to this podcast
seriously next episode i know you can
wear whatever you want right now but
next episode put on a tuxedo why
don't we make a formal episode episode
over djokovic formal
we will wear our fancy english wear
gown our choosing breakfast t o evening
clothes we won't wear when it doesn't
have your your tail gown gown you'll
wear a gown gloves succeed i'm going
to wear gloves i'm gonna wear a
hat and avail i'm going to wear
um a big purse yeah and i'm
gonna
put my dog in it great great
i'm gonna wear spats nothing else yeah
imagine me with goodbye and leave the
door open
new am i going to wear i
guess i'm gonna wear like a sort
of tuxedo one z
yeah what i mean like like like
like sito one of those what are
they wearing a t-shirt that's kinda looks
like a tux it's like yeah funny
yeah but this is like a whole
thing was that the eighties i feel
i remember is the eighties yeah feels
like yeah they might be earlier than
that but i remember it from the
eighties like late seventies yeah but yeah
it felt like the height of humour
your tomato probably wore one without a
duped ignoring a dude with who to
doute ignore ignoring all like history and
like the bad parts of consider it's
own life
let's erase all of what's like the
best what's the decade with the best
vibes just were judging it just on
vibes yeah it's like don't think about
how there were really bad things happening
and like people were treated horribly and
i guess when does the civil war
happened
eight because he got disco i'm like
seventy s yeah i lived through it
i the tea parties i just love
how it looks parties i think the
sixties because well the early sixties probably
sucked we are you including bad bad
things that happened in history you're right
i'm sorry yeah should just count those
how about sixteen twenty s you're fuckin
getting drunk on bootleg yeah everybody on
a party everybody's having parties all the
time as long as you're rich yeah
yeah but i guess that would be
ignoring we're ignoring or hell that thing
yeah so everybody's rich everyone drink good
vibes yeah yeah guess there's great vibes
for everyone who's rich always how about
the colonial era
did you ever go to like see
one of those colonial towns like you
like well yeah you know variances i
didn't and i don't know why because
i feel like growing up in philly
we would have i mean we did
have a ben franklin guy yeah what
does that mean there was a guy
who helped ben franklin guy some nut
who walked in your street and be
like i'm in franklin wait so i
have told you about this
very pretty
it didn't look like it
well he dragged some ready old kites
um yeah there was a guy i
remember he was sort of officially hired
by the the tourism board like the
city had because i feel like i've
been to philadelphia there's like those tours
that go around to show you all
the like historical landmarks where i did
see someone who's dressed up like old
could be
like you know the person playing superman
over mann's chinese where it's like they're
not actually hired by the city they're
just doing it on their own i
guess guy was he would walk around
in full ben franklin regalia he looked
like ben franklin it was good it
was like ben franklin yeah it was
not like cheap looking bifocals he had
to buy focus of course did they
work as bifocals day i don't
no but he see out of them
i wanted to slap them off fucking
things like did you it you're so
nice so nice
lot of people think i'm nice cause
i won't slip glasses off their fucking
faces i'm trying to think if i
was in philly where was i that
i went and it was d c
they have stuff like that i went
to like suffer old of course i
said i want to sound like old
like house that i can't remember it
was probably like the best ross house
there was the betsy ross house in
philadelphia okay but i think it was
in d c
and i don't see of course there's
monta cello whatever i'm jeff harris hearing
was which
historical character but i walked through an
old house and but there wasn't anyone
acting like it was that time and
i think right what i'm gonna need
is someone acting like that i think
i do think it'd be very funny
to go on like a family trip
with my children to a place like
that and make them do that shit
like i think that's absolutely really fun
yeah yeah yeah we went in london
jamie and i went and i may
have
mentioned this in the podcast when it
happened but we were there for the
london podcast festival on twenty eighteen maybe
and where everything went to shit just
before well things started right yeah twenty
and never bad things everything was good
vibes were not good vibes were not
but just counting everything bad happening in
the world great yeah yeah
it's true if you don't think about
anything bad happening everything was good yeah
and it was also you know one
of those things where it was bad
but doesn't get worse so it's technically
like honestly twenty twenty if you discount
all the bad things happening it was
good it was so good yeah what's
the i mean we were in our
houses it was just all covered except
for wanting here we were gonna stay
but i also want to ask this
one
question yeah when you think of the
like first year of the pandemic what's
like the first thing you think of
and like it just in your life
like weekly zooms with people yeah i
think of roasting um random vegetables that
i would get in the mail what
did you say to him fuckin bitch
roasted roasting random vegetables you'd get in
the mail
yeah it was like doing a subscription
like it was like a delivery service
of like here's some widely used or
like some whatever you say yeah but
it was like that was all like
ugly randoms budge to yes exactly and
i was roasting them constant while vegetables
are coming up for getting with news
called nel mio because it was something
like that i think ugly was in
the i know
i don't know if that's even the
one i got anymore i remember being
disappointed because we get we got that
too and it was like these could
look weirder honestly yeah yeah i never
roasted vegetables before but i got very
into that as like my main meal
and i thought it was like exciting
thomas about this london paul you know
drinking a bottle of wine every day
there you go um cocktail hour would
started to be yeah ah
um this house was this one at
home it was not
luther vandross was there and we we
were gonna ask zach about it we
opened our mouth to ask and he
just shook his head and i was
like okay message received
um it was ah this this really
old um building it's like a three
story home and the people that owned
it ah had made each room like
a different time period that this house
had existed it's like a mew
azim yeah and it was ah shitty
yeah people disco there was no balls
little signs of wear occasionally it would
have like a sound effect or something
like you maser you just heard someone
walking into the other room and this
is the kind of shoes they would
wear whatever oh but they had people
that were there to store cuban heels
wedge heel
they had people know wow there were
there to direct you to the various
rooms everything and they were very solomon
series but they weren't wearing like period
clothing oh no which is like do
that you have oh yeah you have
to and then change it for each
room you go into so they're constantly
doing cause they had a bunch of
extra personnel and one room you could
all ye
yes exactly yeah and then i think
you know of course somebody always asked
to the people do people live here
still and we were and they said
yes the the the people do live
here um but they you know they
make it come to us at night
it was like they clearly live in
some other
part of the house that's the we
can see but the house is not
that big but it's like coughing and
maybe you don't say they do yeah
you think they were lying i just
didn't see how i didn't find a
live that themed room there there's no
way there's absolutely no way there's probably
like a nice sweet what year was
this a nice
yeah what year was this by the
way twenty eighteen you said any teen
i said wait it was this recent
yeah and if you think that's recent
let me throw another year at you
twenty nineteen wow that's even more sooner
seems
no but i was picturing this big
thing now when you were a kid
oh let's see more photo twenty twenty
oh that was like yesterday oh
we went on um talks about this
vacation on this show but we went
the the first like big vacation we
went to national lampoon one national lampoon
one christmas vacation oh you have european
village where my boss wouldn't give me
the bonus i wanted um but i
went to women to ah back east
for the first
time and i went on my first
plane and i saw my favorite year
on the plane over there i've talked
about this and we went to new
york first and stayed in the howard
johnson hotel and saw hello jos saw
merlin instead of cats um merlin the
musical basically so doug henning canning and
christian slater that one had such long-term
effects you
no it was like cats ran for
twenty five thirty fifty years this one
also we talk about constantly right but
so that was the first three days
was new york right and we we
did a bunch of new york stuff
was it all like crazy there because
it was like it was it wasn't
it's still really great well we talked
about this about how like we had
he was in this critique already yeah
yeah because timescale was
first thing yes sorry she was ready
it was like everything was like bernie
we have talked about how my there
was no super gritty there was a
section of that we had to go
on a subway to get somewhere then
my parents were freaked out about it
oh sure yeah um but um but
then the other part of the vacation
was it was like we were doing
this for ten days but i learned
this recently was that um you know
we were gonna be going to disney
world and at a certain point my
parents were like look it takes so
long to get to florida and to
get back and we live next to
disneyland's can you not do that and
we all agreed okay where i was
so bummed but that sounds the same
as going to disney world but yeah
but but inside
stead yup call center company but my
father was a big golf ball instead
my father scheduled all these like trips
to civil war like oh that's wow
oh that's not gonna work for me
and was days of this and then
this is what i learned is in
his ah he he recently passed away
and in the ah like sort of
bio i read that because that that
we went to the hershey ah factory
he ah he cut it even shorter
it was going to be longer but
he cut it shorter because we were
complaining you only worked one shift
you guys were so mad about how
many charities shove in your mouth
nobody got no he got the vienna
civil war like battlefields stuff shorter wow
like he called an audible because we
were and it felt like an eternity
of days and days of this it's
me oh soo glad to go to
hershey has like a treat because you
were like okay shut the fuck up
we go here now because you're being
so annoying yeah and then you were
like this is fun you liked hershey
i was disappointed that they didn't give
you candy like they don't give you
candy know you they deposit you in
the gift shop and then you buy
at regular prices candy that's fucked ok
i don't think that i think we've
talked but i do not fuck exactly
exactly and i agree well i'm glad
i'm consistent i think you should be
walking through pocketing chocolates the whole way
yes chalk it should be free
yes everything should be free well you've
always said that since last episode and
you should get to choose you pay
through in a vat of chocolate of
milk chocolate house eat your way out
yes drink eat or drink do both
and do this in memory of me
what if you only ate chocolate and
drank chocolate every meal
of your life but you never got
fat
grady okay with this
wait here's my question what what if
is your did was tired of it
that story yeah you'd have to get
tired of it so you didn't really
hear that story a lot you just
read it no i just always remember
that that was part of the trip
is we went and i had thought
it had been planned that we were
going to the chocolate factory this whole
time but and i remember there being
way too many
any ah civil war battlefields but i
never knew that they were cut even
short that we were supposed to be
doing them even longer than what we
did do you feel like your dad
like complained about that a lot to
your mom and like that was why
that was a story the fact that
it has come up forty years later
daddy's funeral yes he might ever let
it go he must have been so
caddy will
so annoying but this is also true
but you gotta understand too like we
grew up ah ooh we were just
common people i'm sure you had shouted
sharks instead of jets yes and this
was the only vacation that shirt that
they were ever gonna get to take
you know and the only time there
he was ever gonna get to see
any of this stuff wow i should've
made it his honeymoon honest
oddly she tells you all to shut
up
i would've yeah i would've said yes
sir
sure yeah yeah but yeah it's ed
sucks it's i mean to be successful
everyone to be thirteen and having to
go see all that stuff under know
i would be the most complaining person
on our i mean i definitely complained
on trips so much like it sounds
so brady cause like we went to
italy when i was in high school
and like i remember
more like pouting like who even knows
but there's like a picture my brother's
sitting on like a stoop and we
both look so pissed to be italy
like i don't i don't know i
think i love the trip but i
was like i'm sure it was tired
and like i was like we're walking
so much i want to eat gummy
worm yeah like who knows this train
and your brain's not formed yeah trips
are just lost on kids i didn't
like
unless you go to a kid play
it wasn't totally lost i mean like
i respected it and like thought it
was wrong
they and i look back and i'm
grateful for it but i also at
the time definitely complained about for sure
about about things where you're like you
shouldn't shut up you're part of the
trip is being in boston or i
remember like there's a big walking tour
of like going to all the famous
you know boston places and the only
thing that was interesting to me was
there was like a unicyclist in the
town square doing like a big
you know for for money passing the
hag your his target audience yeah and
that was the only interesting part of
that day i remember everything else was
super boring sort of think boston's oh
he's learning boston's where i went to
that special house that makes oh
if you're lucky
birthday i'm gonna joke
welcome players oh good joke
ah it's a three meme callback
was it ah
ah still makes us laugh
oh that's all you heard all these
minutes later we're still enjoying it
oh my god um we didn't take
many trips when i was a kid
yeah i mean the school trips but
there were not a lot of family
trips that i can recall they're expensive
especially with how many fucking i can't
imagine how many um kids you have
what do you call those things well
i know in the middle of it
i was trying to remember if we
were all in one hotel room and
i think we were oh that's weird
oh for sure we never had our
own hotel room yeah no no my
brother had to share a bed and
on these trips and i'm like yeah
we'd be like pushing each other like
the fuck away from me
i feel like we would go in
europe like we would take my my
dad valued going on like a big
trip like that more than like games
like portlanders like we'd never did that
so like we would be like every
few years we do like a big
trip when i was in high school
and stuff and my brother and i
had to share hotel in this share
bed in this room is everywhere and
we're like having pillows and we're like
punching easy
because i remember this trip we were
in one room and it was the
five of us and it was like
i think my mom and dad and
one bed my brother and i in
one bedroom and they would get caught
for my young sister who's who was
let's see when i was thirteen was
probably five yeah it's just like is
that fun i don't know that's literally
i mean i think
like that's but what are you gonna
do you're gonna put your kids in
another room i'm sure people do that
if you have the money to do
that but like that but i do
think about that trip a lot of
like and i saw so much stuff
that i'm appreciative for you but like
battlefields oh god
so chocolate so glad i saw that
field i saw one chocolate i saw
one hershey chocolate was a dollar fifty
i don't think i stayed in a
hotel until i started doing comedy really
yeah i don't i don't remember ever
being an hotel as a kid yeah
yeah you started comedy young though too
yes four years old yeah
yeah but if like most about how
dirty your underwear was yeah yeah hell
i can't wait to not go to
school tomorrow i think most of my
like state sightseeing was like as an
adult and like a lot of like
on tour i got a lot of
the cities went to it was my
first time going to a lot of
i think the first time i went
to australia was with you guys i
think it was my first time too
and my last time yeah i had
been there several times before oh bravo
paul not an easy place you several
times it's not but you know what
i'm glad i did it yeah i'll
always remember on that flight i was
like in the last row and i
curled up into a ball and try
to sleep for the entire time you're
in you're able to do that yeah
not anymore but
i was yeah oh yeah i don't
think i could do that now i
didn't show there was it the melbourne
festival can't remember i hope so but
i y u i just hope it
wasn't yes but i was fine but
they flew me and they flew me
in use either i must be in
business class but it was like like
stretch out comps
wheatley flat beds you know and so
i was sitting in the like second
the last row or something like that
and right by the party i was
sitting tinkle tinkle poopy poopy butt
what i've told students
i was sitting next to repr the
game wow remember him and then he
had a girlfriend or a lady that
he was seeing who was also on
the flight and she was sitting up
in the front and he asked me
to switch places with her so they
could sit together she's had a better
sir yes sir
and he said um i'll give you
that come on come on be a
gentleman oh don't do that the gentleman
actually would be you in this situation
right you switch with somebody calls yeah
yeah so i was like yeah okay
yeah why didn't ask the person next
to her it actually was worse the
seat was oh
oh like it was like it was
like the equivalent of a sofa bed
with like a bar in it or
whatever it was weirdly uncomfortable i was
like this guy fucking got me he
the game this is why they call
him that yeah he gamely games me
man and now he's not popular and
neither am i
alright we have to dig break
and we're back and it's time for
three trees reach your time everybody and
you know what this is this is
where we play a fun game like
a parlor game a car game the
three of us played together we're friends
and we have a good time if
you would like to send someone on
a great time paul i want just
to know i don't know what to
wear to be we have a great
time you're absolutely right thank you
have a great time and if you
would like to send us something that
would enable us to have this great
time why don't you write to us
at three mm usa a g mail
dot com and let us know what
three tree you'd like us to play
it's right and this one came from
someone a while back that we have
not documented who they were but we've
played it before and whoever there was
it sent us
they enjoyed hearing their name the first
time we played it and don't need
it the second time now we take
the names off if we play the
game once we take the name off
and now belongs to everyone and this
is called one three five and we're
going to improvise a scene scene and
one of us is allowed to say
one word each time one of us
can use three words in one of
us can use five words which one
do you want i'll use three i
don't want i'll do five alright
hi there guys hi
well well well look now
look at what
huh
look at what look at you two
here
oh that's right
payment
oh um right now today ideally pay
for what work oh you did work
for you me that's right i um
i don't want to
pay you that
can we work something out
done whoa tone it down point that
here pay
okay be cool no
is that even loaded honey
condescending
ah okay you showed me
well it's in there
yes bullets in their use
making choices
ah okay honey apology
oh okay to differ no no but
yet she interrupted
she interrupted me
hey be nice okay die
i'm not dead
that that gun shoots water don't it
sta you missed honey
quitting
look i'll pay you okay good
how much did we say
million
pennies or would you say pennies counts
too much oh the oh was a
freestyle because i just realised we shot
shut up that's two words would you
accept nickels in
in lieu of pennies okay
check
you now you want a cheque atm
card okay no oh i can't just
no up why not
how
apple pay fun on phone sure
so
have a faithful road apples you're out
there what are your slogan sure ok
double click to pay put gun down
don't pee on
me and tell me it's raining judge
judy
okay there got it have you received
received glad we could do business by
judge judy by
wait your robe is caught naked judge
judy whoa sir judge judy you are
hot
would bang judy
hey judge judy you up
die
oh no shot at art
ah i enjoyed it i enjoyed it
i thought one would be easier somehow
we're quitting quitting
winning represent
no waning hashtag winning tigers blood and
for that tour he did oh yeah
yeah and people were like screaming and
yeah joining it can you imagine ah
damn as like tom sandoval went on
tour with his band after skanda vol
at least he had a band
what if he just went on tour
going scandal remember what he was like
hitting the wall with a hammer and
going scanned of all i don't like
this guy i don't think he's good
but if he did that on tour
he brought out a sledgehammer and probably
like gallagher or peter gabriel like gallagher
wow can someone take over gallagher's sledgehammer
duties
i thought his brother did that i
know but i mean now that he's
gone can can we just do it
like public domain yeah i think it's
up for anybody if anybody wants to
make that their comedy i think you
could do you think smashing a watermelon
with the big maladies in the public
domain and i think it's just kind
of an oman at this point you
think like the first person who ever
picked up a guitar and sang like
they own that well i know a
friend he got his first real six
string
he bought her the five and dime
i know yeah i've heard of him
this was i mean this is it
feels like it was about fifty four
fifty five or something like that yeah
yeah but it's like a big story
just story that's told a lot yeah
yeah i mean he considers it the
best days of his life really obviously
i mean honestly it's only
he was really free god damn i
don't think i can look back at
the past and say those are the
best years of my life maybe when
i'm very old i can do that
but i right now i feel like
i'm having you couldn't name the halcyon
days of your life right now i
like to think i'm in them i
know i'm miserable all the time yeah
no i think i said
each each era has a positive thing
to it but each era has a
positive thing for sure i was thinking
about the decades and like what what
just all of them yeah like twenties
thirties like from zero to now now
i'm just talking about my decades like
oh sure you know and i was
trying i was trying to go
like oh what's what are the best
ones but i think they've all had
their own flavor yeah i mean like
in my twenties starting out in standup
and forging relationships that i still have
to this day and it was a
lot of fun we had a lot
of yeah um thirties moved you know
when i was living here
ah and working in showbiz for the
first time a lot of fun lot
of anxiety
forty s getting to know my getting
to feel more myself having some triumphs
having some tragedies
fifty s remains to be see yeah
how old are you knew met janie
i would have been in my
it was two thousand and five
two thousand and five we met does
not nope two thousand and i just
re-wrote down we managed two thousand and
fourteen for me and my math so
i would claim my good math brain
um i would say it was in
my mid to late thirties wow yeah
because we got married we dated for
five years and then i was forty
when we got married
wow wow it makes sense
wilson wow we did the same that
wow wow we went through all the
famous wells yeah yeah owen wilson onassis
for walk-in and then whoa i'm i'm
trying to do another one but that
doesn't have i said wow the nanny
yeah drescher did she say well no
surprise to me
staff guys let's let's play one round
of the picnic game oh oh no
we don't think we do it right
oh nuts okay we one person thinks
of a criteria ah theme or category
of things that their guests can relate
to the ethnic different yeah i'm gonna
do criteria yep this is different than
than we
ask if we can bring specific things
to the pic note that gay yes
yes and then ah you let us
know whether we can come to the
picnic or not okay lauren think of
the criteria of what we can bring
or category or i've got it ooh
alright
can i bring my
lunch pail to the picnic yes
can i bring my ah pack of
individually sliced american cheese yes
can i bring my round spherical ball
to the picnic know too well how
big is it
this v big lets yes superman oh
okay can i what are the things
so far lunch pail and individually sliced
cheese and a ball that's this big
okay
for the listener it's probably a circumference
of baseball baseball yeah
can i bring a handful of raw
almonds yes can i bring an elephant
no can i solve it yeah how
this works yes things you can hold
in your hand yes whoa i gave
it away you did your mounting is
bad last time thanks
well we gotta just demand somewhere real
quick okay yeah this is for the
three days just three three amazing this
is a story that i've told before
that i'd like to tell again same
his picks hello piss this is for
all cats tour outside soon
alright i'll think of a thing okay
okay
i thought of it
can i bring a basket of cherries
um it depends oh no it's a
bad start can i bring my little
red riding hood cloak no
can i bring um my purse
depends oh my god can i bring
my depends no
come on can i bring a camper
named black leather jacket yes
what is it cherries okay right right
right right
um can i bring my elephant no
can i bring my you really wanna
bring an elephant yeah oh like so
weird and my depends can i bring
my water by plastic water bottle depends
these depends are not helping
depends shouldn't be an available answer can
i bring my blue plastic water bottle
no okay oh can i bring oh
oh can i guess things that are
black yes i owe you have guessed
correctly thank you master
her
or your turn to one alright i'll
do on your turn to one okay
i got it okay
can i bring my comic book collection
no
can i bring a watermelon know can
i bring a turkey sandwich no can
i bring ah a trenchcoat no can
i bring my elephant no living only
elephants ah
it depends can i bring a lunch
box yes
can i bring
a picnic blanket now
can i bring an umbrella
part of it can i bring a
window no
can i bring the car door yeah
can i bring a book no
can i bring a picnic basket no
can i bring um one chip
be more specific what type of chip
tortilla no
i bring a nineteen fifties robot yeah
please can i bring a funnyman know
that like yourself okay things that are
metal that's right i would have accepted
iron maiden album as well or like
a chip from my computer yes wow
that's heavy when you think about it
as wild it's actually really deep how
he did that was actually super deal
progestin damage
title you're saying is that by dbi
dbi dbi dbi guy may do the
guy dubai hello
member that kai scooby-doo beat up billy
dupe is as dvd yeah david lee
roth whatever happened
i became a paramedic and then he
stopped being that did he really i
don't know was he any good ago
what if david lee roth came to
your house and you're having a heart
attack and you're using goodly newly bap
ba zippers the map ripple ripple here
ah i don't really know him from
chris contains impression of him so i
mean pretty accurate but i think you're
good you've never heard of m helen
tyler i've heard of van halen i
just don't really know got it bad
got it bad got it bad ah
for deja i know that would mean
down between my legs shut the polis
seatback
through this rude song i now it's
nasty it's nasty because i think what
he was really doing
so this year so i was always
wishing for change kids that listen to
this so let's just pretend need to
do pretending he's just pretending what are
you saying that he was the double
entendre was yeah ah he's talking about
crank and is yang i got that
part right i'm saying what's so he's
in he's in a car whatever oh
okay and he's like put pushing like
ah you know releasing the lever to
it's pretty releasing believers pretty spot arm
yeah not that much nice filth layering
to filth man he's a filthy guy
well man i think van halen songs
and david lee roth song should be
outlawed okay wow that's heavy
if they make an outlaw outlawed yeah
like they almost are i haven't heard
one a long time
i was thinking about that ah like
certain songs some people just will never
hear them ever again do you know
what song i've heard a lot recently
i wanna say in the last couple
of years more than i ever expected
ever hear again is the follow-up to
rupert holmes the pina colada song oh
right the song him yeah
yeah that's right well you're going to
do about him it seems will reach
me and then there's a little bridge
goes
ooh that is a weird weird song
well i was i heard a song
the other day um which was like
an which was an answer song to
billie jean and it's called chat is
my son it's called ah
who does it i heard it for
the first time melba moore neuner but
it was like if someone in that
it was it was a woman singer
in the guise of billie jean like
my name is bailey g
um and it was kind of a
hit but ah it got me on
the wikipedia page of answer so sure
and most of the ones on the
wikipedia page or not true answer songs
they're just kind of like related songs
yeah um but i do love a
good answer song they're so fun do
people do it anymore well ah
ah in the twenty twenty s we
have jessie's girl to coheed and cambria
is but rick's wu coheed cambria i
don't know who that is they're like
they're like emo but happy yeah but
rick springfield is on it as well
so it's now more than an average
song um
um yeah yellow of course answer sanga
papa don't preach yes which was papa
just wants the best for you papa
just wants to see you through is
an abortion
oh my god i thought the papa
doesn't want her to have the abortion
to you and see papa don't preach
she was she was anything or be
able de papa don't preach so i
made him a man and keeping my
baby i always felt like that wasn't
truly about i'm gonna keep a baby
she was singing like about her baby
like her boyfriend that's that's what i
think
are you an eighty i've always felt
like the song was more about like
i'm keep like papa don't preach to
me about this guy that you don't
like i'm gonna keep my bag that
is a wild georgia literal song and
then they made it literal later to
to like never mind they did that's
a weird theory usually are ashamed or
tea though
okay just letting me in front of
us don't peep um in trouble pop
i know you're gonna be upset because
i was always your little girl but
you should know by now i'm not
a baby grows you always taught me
right from wrong i need your help
daddy please be strong i may be
young at heart but i know what
i'm saying the one you warned me
all about the one you said i
could do without were in an awful
mess
oh okay maybe you're right i don't
mean making these
she doesn't mean maybe yeah i'm gonna
keep my baby he says he's gonna
marry me we can raise a little
family i still don't think this is
but so danielle a low sigh yeah
a lot
by the way they say miley cyrus
is twenty twenty three songs flowers paraphrases
when i was your man by bruno
mars yeah yeah but isn't an answer
song i don't think so
it's supposed to be matched jiang to
some song in bruno mars song i
think he says i will buy you
flowers okay so maybe ciphers it is
an answer song like i don't need
no man myself whoa hey guys
yeah so there's a good example of
a modern one used to be waymo
from reality is yeah yeah yeah can
you hold my own hand superstar by
the way was lydia murdoch song the
answer song to billie jean by michael
jackson superstar superstar and it has the
same kind of like doom doom doom
doom and it was like
michael jackson stop lying you know you
had sex with that woman
right week to go ah if you
want to call this call had claims
eight dot com that's right don't call
it go to the website of the
website um and then our old episodes
come out on tuesdays that's what we
call three positioning all the twos and
our three meme episodes ah those come
out every other week that's at cb
world and apple podcast
premium or something like that um and
you can hear all of our archived
episodes and ad-free episodes over cb world
there you go what more can we
say but goodbye to you bye bye