three
ah anybody know anyone with a movie
but everybody
yeah but i mean do you have
anybody would even believe me
ah nobody been there but yeah
do you ever do but never did
that do whatever they whatever do
dbi dbi dbi dbi frick mob oh
our good friend babu frick no room
that little frick voiced by julian henderson
yeah from trainspotting and doctor who yes
rick do amongst others and also topsy
turvy when my person yes topsy turvy
she's great in that does run singing
yes we name is
babu frick i have to confess i
did her see i don't know what
to do i did her singing for
that role hey you never told me
this yeah she called me i knew
her personally she's my best friend ah
did i ever tell you this no
i'm the one who'd said you gotta
do the star wars movie and call
yourself bobby frick she came up with
the name
no i came up with the name
oh shit you're right yeah anyway i
did all over saying y la la
la because like she's
she's got a beautiful voice she's got
babu frick eyes dude guten do do
do do
what a weird kind of beautiful
hey welcome to three-day his you know
us oh go that she's surprised she's
got buddy dave shy ready to ever
show ya yeah she's got bette davis
eyes dog she's got bette davis eyes
now dog and i can't see
was he talking to snoopy when he
said that yeah of course he was
mississippi became a person for a day
yep yeah that was weird always very
unsettling peanuts because i didn't like how
he didn't he he didn't look like
a normal p know he looked well
he he looked like a human but
he saw those long years right but
they were like his skin
in tone yeah and people were like
did you have gauges at some point
and he's like no this is just
how they are are we talking about
snoopy and the red baron no yeah
ever i mean i'll probably want the
red baron stuff is the most boring
stuff of course it is he's like
in a war you're like let's make
it modern people i would have fucking
little dog be fantasizing about flood
eileen a world war why don't i
do it oh i'm not even talking
about the why would he do that
or whatever i'm talking about how boring
it like i watched the feel like
it was the thanksgiving special or something
and there's a whole long riff where
he's pretending to be it always bored
me to tears part of everything turning
you're in a war do you think
it was for the parents of
of the children at the time maybe
but it just shuts the plot down
like there's no plot moving forward it
sounds just like it's like dream sequences
charlie brown is the plot yeah let's
remove for intricate story i'm like is
the great pumpkin coming or not and
and that's why i told you i
think it was real it was the
great pumpkin okay do you know what
i when i was
killer really bummed him what happened lauren
you drop something stop the process i
dropped my lotion cap can we get
the late addition it puts the cap
on the lotion that i don't want
to get the hose so i do
put the cap on the issue when
i was a kid a bow again
so yeah i guess it was again
it hurt last time yeah it's much
stronger than they think um just was
a whipping those outer he was turning
the hose i mean she was in
a hole so it's like how the
wall just pressure use that movie is
scary visit still i haven't watched it
along i only saw for the first
time a few years ago i thought
oh
oh man what did he say feel
it's creepy mail tony foster what did
he say oh so creepy i saw
an interview with her where she was
saying he did something unexpected and remember
what it was jacob
anthony hopkins pinellas county he like you
basically did something scary that wasn't planned
in the thing that she really had
a real reaction was the tongue thing
yeah wow i think it was i
can't i can't duplicate it was the
tongue thing you don't ever do a
tongue thing with a wolf thank you
pardon
yeah you've been you've been told okay
like the soprano guy jay college because
i was told to stop this told
them never don't ever do any visitor
michael douglas don't ever do that you'll
get cancer from doing this call it
when he was like i'll never eat
a pussy and then the internet was
like your soup ah sounds so you're
stupid
really picked the wrong hill to die
on here today why did paul stanley
come out with a statement on god
it just i don't know why i
don't know who that is from kiss
hey i'm my jaw dropped but what
is even on what do you say
he's on january times challenger i was
like who is asking paul stanley for
them buddy shut everyone just talk huh
got up damn it huh you don't
no one needs to know europe just
don't care and your opinion is garbage
by the way yeah that's garden let
alone that it's garbage but it's like
no he put out a statement it's
like really you simply have no reason
to that can't talk about it it's
like oh my official letterhead yeah yes
paul stanley what gives letting you know
i used to be kicked from the
desk of the star child will see
the circo you star child when they
put the makeup on away with time
is ace freely surveys freely as freely
as the spaceman ah paul stanley's star
dot star child do you feel like
the makeup ever got old for them
like where they're like an were no
faces again
again i used to hate doing theater
and having to put because i did
just make up for jesus christ superstar
one almost forgot about that it's just
such a pain in the ass yeah
i did just make up for something
once and it took so long you
were in kiss for one night yeah
you're like wait wait what were you
gonna say before we talked about everything
else that interrupted you ah oh
the great pumpkin charlie brown yeah yeah
bummed me out when the great pumpkin
did not show up i know i
know it's a thing but like come
on go go by ones i didn't
want to learn a lesson i want
to seem like a great book yeah
sometimes those can be really like heartbreaking
film absolutely yeah a lot of nostalgia
is so crushing that it's just oh
i mean
there's so much on we in the
peanuts universe oh we yeah there is
the the movie snoopy come home i
remember that in the book rib z
we're both about dogs who were lost
from yawns oh no you know who
has a funny story about ribs he
is tig shi z i'm gonna tell
the story wrong so whatever but the
gist of it is that i like
your coffee
she did show the story wrong she
wrote a book report about rosie for
like many years at school anytime should
do a book report was about it
was always been really yeah there's a
point to the story of course well
that is kind of genius because it
gets you out of your elementary school
teachers yeah i'm sure like certain at
a certain age it's like yeah you're
in high school
calculate telling that story so robin why
not why not just use it for
like third grade fourth grade fifth grade
thanks for yet another one another one
no i don't mean eaten pussies
i of course famously as junior year
of high school did a book report
we had to do a book report
on black like me yeah and the
teacher ah gave me a failing rate
on that said i did not prove
to him that i wrote the book
you wrote it you know
wow i like me somewhere in our
class wrote the book and we all
had to write well i guess we
all over the we wrote yeah it
was like mafia and i was like
i wrote it he said you didn't
approach me that you read the book
did you prove it to him like
after that and say well look i
don't know how to prove it to
him i was like i did the
report what how i
wasn't vague i didn't know i had
this teacher once who's my journalism teacher
which makes you wonder why we're even
doing this project where we had to
um we all had to like i
guess what we had to report on
the grapes of wrath who you're just
but he assigned us like as groups
like a section of the book like
i just had to read channel par
as someone entering the end then we
each present are
a little motivated but it was like
i don't know what happened it was
like a horrible it made no sense
a bad assignment i'm trying yeah i'm
trying to figure it out from a
journalism angle i don't even know if
there was any connection freeing me back
to peanuts from for my newspaper class
um there was an editorial about spanking
in school because it was still happening
at the time
and for some reason and i drew
a cartoon for it which was ah
charlie brown like bending over the table
being spanked and going good grief and
my and my ah journalism teacher like
held it up in front of the
class and said all right everyone what
is wrong with this and someone like
raise their hand said it's copy
righted and he went exactly there's no
way we can publish this in my
mind i'm going he's wrong and it
is wrong yeah like you clarity is
not yes the that's the whole the
whole point of it is you can
use copy it's fair you know just
made me so much true because thomas
nast the famous political cartoonist tool the
reason he driven one so fucked up
well he's so he wouldn't get sued
because they were originally who they're well
the bondi characters dagwood and blondie no
no no he would draw like boss
tweed but he would be it would
be a gross caricature so the boss
we couldn't sue oh wow he's like
because if you sue you to admit
it looks like you right right
yeah yeah yeah i'm that yes looking
yeah that's me obviously in the corner
i am a big obviously a big
round man who is boss tweet again
cipa dome scandal my dear boy i
don't know that much about that much
i know i was famously character characterized
in mad magazine as part of orange
is the new black that's cool and
hideous but ah that's great
and to tell you the slightest bit
of echo someone had me sign their
books zara jacket nice ne snag good
stage name no like zanskar jackie hi
richard i'm zack energetic he's sure jacket
is it oh man yeah early that
was a real moment in time everyone
skins remember i remember the
the introduction to the six million dollar
man
steve austin was and i was an
early ally i was imagining a man
in a tuxedo introducing the six billion
yeah every week everyone it's like cheaters
yeah i'm so glad you're here tonight
we present a yet another episode of
the six million dollar man this time
he may be encountering him
mythical creature who shoe size is rather
large
did you did you see that episode
of cheaters that i'm talking about where
the producer came in a tuxedo you've
told me about this so many times
i can't remember if i saw it
or i just envision i had on
t i'd also like saying have you
seen that episode of cheers like there's
five million and it was same it
was ain't no i just want is
less than watching chandra because he was
like
a very special episode yeah it was
like the the one hundredth episode or
something and so like the producer came
out in a tuxedo to introduce it
and then said and it's a brand
new era for cheaters because the old
host i forget who was old and
who is joey but joey greco was
one of them yeah who i met
once in a garage and ah ah
the guy
i was greco joey greco joe yeah
so one of them was one of
them got fired in the other one
was replacing zoe it was one could
only tell the truth so it was
guy in tuxedo introducing very special episode
and then they they filmed the new
guy introducing the footage but they only
have the old guy doing the footage
because of the
most confusing like three hosts show of
cheaters i've ever squeezing
that's a good episode and you have
to watch that over and over yeah
yeah just love you gotta say i
want to switch on youtube does it
always end the same no it's always
in the same one time
no one cheated and ah we just
kissed there were says oh insult to
name them like how dare you insinuate
this
oh my god have you ever been
on cheater yeah and we'll go around
the table
that's widget yeah you know taking it
to we're moving it from our personal
lives don't you kind of love when
there's some hot goss going around why
do you know some no i'm saying
like but those moments when it's like
some crazy happening and you're like oh
this is insane i like it when
i'm there's a certain remove from the
gas yeah that i enjoy no yeah
it's
some people better when you don't when
you're not in mesh of course yeah
yeah say when you don't give a
shit about yea when you care yeah
yeah i think when you care about
the people but not enough where you
would be part of it
does that make sense like you're like
you're not their best friend but you're
like you know them yeah yeah you've
hung out with them enough to be
like oh that's juicy yeah yeah but
not so much with sauces yeah well
that's true what if it's real nora
what if they're in love who the
people you know what i don't
the works of gossip someone did love
oh my god that's wrong huh that's
fucked up um by the way i
saw elvis yesterday and the funniest part
i meant to tell you all this
like tom hanks is like and then
we were in movies we had fun
i just thought i could watch the
movie i'm hearing your impression of him
these are pretty accurate right pretty good
but you just like one because i
got him i got the this still
be in movies were fun football weird
that framing devices so strange he did
you see
i will see as an interesting word
because yeah thank your looking here i
had about eight screens open ah this
was the eight screen experience yeah you
saw that running time during like i
think he's like oh i'll be shopping
for ten thousand things on ten thousand
different tabs and on my phone open
and yeah i watched denver ah
losing to doing your dead yep
that's amazing
well yeah anyway what the fuck were
we das oh gosh i laughed some
gas no but i were just talking
about how do you have a blind
item i have a blind item um
no but i've probably mentioned this show
normal gossip it's icast yeah i like
it they it's the host has not
about seven minutes like nor like gossip
from their lives like and then they
just changed
the names yeah and then they talk
it through with a guess like some
this happened at this person's i feel
like every place or whatever i feel
like every newspaper now is doing something
like the ethicist or ask carolyn hax
or whatever because they're always coming up
on my twitter feed but i read
one yesterday about um a guy who
went into his wife's phone
and looked at her messages don't do
that don't do it but every message
that she was sending to her friends
were about how much she hates him
ah so he's like well that's good
well i was chibi oh yeah that's
it's all like what to get to
the bottom of that what a loser
he is oh that's so sad yes
he was fired and now
i've had to to pick like i
it's been a financial drain on me
and he's like no we're i was
fired yes but the money we got
from selling our house she hasn't kid
at her so he's like what do
i do because obviously i shouldn't have
gone into her phone but now i
know she hates me so i'm supposed
to sit here and take it
that's really rough i think you just
have to say you went in her
phone yeah that's what everyone's suspicious of
something i think they were saying they
were saying it's not equal yes i
did a bad thing but it's not
equal like her hating you shouldn't be
in a relationship so lead story yeah
you need to like settle that yeah
yeah yeah but i but it always
gives the other person excuse to go
like well what are you going through
my
oh that's true that's so that's it
that's a tactic yeah yeah you're definitely
attacked
too good anywhere i use it all
the time and it's it's great because
you were right you know i use
it whether or not the phones involved
no because you can always say well
why were you going through my phone
and chances are they probably were yeah
ah it was to see if you
thought i was a loser
i felt like you hated me so
wanted to make sure um that's obvious
and i feel like obviously he's going
through her phone because he knows something
is wrong yeah yeah yeah you don't
you don't just do that yeah like
oh i think i might want to
go through someone's phone yeah that is
so chilling to me like if i
were to discover yeah
come upon messages like an affair or
something like that would be i know
i mean i know someone that's happened
to me you guys don't know yeah
yeah we don't know anyone no but
i mean i wouldn't be saying if
you did yeah oh it's the worst
jane seymour yes okay i had a
feeling
no but so scary from wedding crashers
was she dr quinn minister will she
was yeah what a funny descriptor medicine
woman like was it didn't have a
term for it back then
can't call her doctor oh you're not
allowed to everyone go to like neuro
where is the actual doctor medicine woman
ms matterson they still did that to
this day scott what's my gynecologist is
a medicine woman really i just talked
i say that about her your guy
no my my my day no my
guy
now a male gynecologist that's just a
creep right well let's that mel gibson
sketch that's rough the s and l
sketch remember he was like whatever his
name is male gynecologist and everyone wanted
to go to him to oh awesome
rare right takes on a different meaning
now yeah
just thought of something i can't say
ah thought of a joke i can't
make um but the fact that you
thought of it means you're a bad
person oh no doubt
don't worry i've gotten myself low they
get taken care of so are you
on twitter still under your checkmark oh
yeah yeah my checkmark went away i
i i think i still i was
gonna give it up after the book
came out um but i also i
don't know it's the only way to
get news but it is so bad
had the worst people now are just
i don't know i don't feel like
it's the only way to get news
i should be i should be more
just on the news app do yeah
i mean how do you get your
news i've i mainly i get my
news from hudson news that's my trusted
news oh i go to hudson news
everyday like groceries in the morning i
hate that i have to spend a
ticket but
it's worth it's retina thousand dollars on
four bags of snacks every day yeah
i never take a flight and someone
several watch lists but i but i
must say i didn't used to get
all my news from twitter taken the
flight lessons i loved it but i'm
so scared to play
i didn't do the flight simulator
let's do look fun they do look
we should the three of us should
take a flight class no fucking chance
why we'd never get up in the
plane oh you just want to see
me just go on the simulator and
go yeah that sounds good does sound
like fun i don't think they just
let you hop into that part i
like to call wheat all the way
home
oh you know all the way i'm
alright speaking home
take a break okay yeah let's go
let's go mr ever returned by amazing
and we're back for people who don't
know during the breaks we each go
to our separate homes yep and then
we reconvene three four hours later four
hours later yeah we just yeah we
like to just we need to come
down from the tie break it up
i you know what i did do
that last
last night come down from the high
of the showing we had a fun
show yeah and ah and then i
yeah even though i knew i had
to do this in the morning i
stayed up a little later though i
stayed up late last did you really
coming down yeah how late i stayed
a little past midnight i mean that's
right that's what we're gonna let it
all hang out yeah oh but i
was you know what i was doing
is
yup on one of my favorite shows
a million a million little things oh
yeah totally i somehow because you know
sometimes hulu doesn't tell you doesn't show
you what you've been watching yes and
if you forget yeah i was i
was like wait i'm like five episodes
i'm like what i just thought there
wasn't an episode and so i i
have been i caught up last night
oh my god the
series finale i'm going tomorrow tomorrow tonight's
live event a million little things because
i was on the show and so
i gotten back to this thing but
it's the finale the series finale wow
shows a series for them this sob
the the episode the most recent episode
before the finale is so
emotional and soul crushing i'm like nah
i don't know what the show is
oh it's a great show it's on
abc it's um say no more i
love it james rowe day rodriguez allison
miller um we got a lot great
people have you ever seen that show
a hundred big things yeah yeah i
love that one this is like that
only it's tweak slightly
well if there's more things i'm interested
but if they're not big than i
don't think i'm interested i thought the
same thing
okay it's interesting okay alright i'll check
it out anyway they're taking my ride
has they knew that they're gonna end
the show which you know it's always
hard when a show doesn't know they're
going to end and just ends from
like they're they're taking out everybody has
ever been oh my tna so emotional
journey towards the end and it's really
it's breaking my heart yeah a good
way yeah
yeah it's really good somehow heartbreak feels
good good you know please like that
yeah um now i understand at the
event they are they've hidden a million
little things all around yeah and we're
not allowed to leave until we find
all million yes yeah there's gotta be
a group effort yeah well there's no
way i could find million by myself
well exactly yeah you can find how
many things in a day tell you
say you know in twenty twenty four
hour to find yeah like today no
sleep yeah how many things could you
find if you didn't go to sleep
ten ten yeah so if you did
go to sleep how many with some
rest maybe twelve
wait so you would find more things
if you slept for eight i'm resting
that twenty four hour period i'm arrested
if i'm not rested at all i'm
not looking at all you know it's
like i just stopped looking you start
to zone out how many things can
be here in this room right now
ten which so it's ten every time
guitar tv frame guy guy yeah window
door how's window how's window mace windu
mace which you know makes me anyways
i've seen every star wars film today
my boy weighing guys doing
really wow driving watch and doorway five
i was cure i don't think i
watched andor oh i think you'd like
andor really i'm not going back for
more do you know what i didn't
i asked out of did not think
that grow goo could get cuter and
then on this latest season we start
doing little gurgles i know because if
he's in the gurgling stage fucking love
him
love him he gets me every time
i love i don't die season he's
not gonna get me he gets me
he's such a cutie pie you know
my feeling about the star wars shows
the only one i have not really
the the one that kind of was
like the least enjoyable for me was
obi-wan right but the rest of them
i you find saying oh yeah i
would rather than make them
the not making yeah a great you
know sure because maybe i'll get to
be on one at some point i
was like yeah i see there's definitely
comedians on there yeah kathleen kennedy if
you're listening we don't think you're gonna
get fired ethylene kennedy if you're listening
i love you oops put me in
whatever put us in star wars i'll
play whatever and coach i said okay
i'll play a laser beam
i put in the work to be
put in star wars at this point
i've yeah oh really you were for
to watch things that we watch for
pleasure and i talked about it please
put me in this thing i don't
care about it yeah like no but
i would like it if i was
onset assure that was loosely that's different
you go like i kind of have
an appreciation for this note yeah yeah
see how i see how the mother
how the soup is made i especially
through the eyes of my character blurs
flavor i got your doggo yeah um
when's the last time you stayed up
for twenty four hours oh and i
think i think when we were doing
the the all night shows
and you cv the the twenty four
hours i don't even know i know
that when i was younger i'd have
to peel that's true i guess when
i was like in college but it
seems unfathomable to me now yeah and
it's so unnecessary i remember one night
like ah in my i was probably
in my forties or something and i
had an ur
early flight but a late night the
night before and i was like i'll
just stay up stay up and go
to that always seems like a good
idea do it oh my god i
stayed up for two more hours and
then it was like i can do
it hey ho sleep i know i
got like forty five minutes of sleep
and it's stuck but one cycle in
college or
whatever was like fun to stay out
all night yeah and the sun's coming
up and you're like doing hanging around
all fun yeah that's not fun now
i have a fond memory of one
night working at the local comedy club
in philadelphia how local are we talking
ah local to philadelphia walk to it
from my house okay at the top
it's not
local to us right now no it
is not because it's in philadelphia it's
in philadelphia still right i think it's
still open under a different name maybe
by now joe um yeah it's just
a own it's called thomas oh um
this was the funny bone in philadelphia
and i was hanging out i don't
like by the way when
those clubs are called funny bone because
how many times can they be gold
i know it hurts when you get
it's not like haha it's so funny
yeah it hurts it just reminds me
of getting hit there i don't like
when it's a name that sort of
it's supposed to be comedy adjacent yeah
yeah helium yeah i'll say oh that's
ten junior visitors
as you talk helium to be fun
yes sa alien to be funny
or like what's laughing gas what's the
next dockside i chose like that would
be crazy nitric oxide doing nitrous know
to know what it is i think
it's o two oh i hope so
um now's um but so i had
a little i had a little fling
with one of the waitresses at the
clay oh yeah oh no
no nitrous dioxide is eno two
it does the die mean i think
that means the two parts so i
think i know would be what does
that just dioxide do anything fun ah
try it's crying guy it's one of
a group of highly reactive gases known
as oxides of nitrogen or nitrogen oxides
no x
what are you okay bye
no i'm just reading that it felt
like you guys just froze and i
were on zoom am i dying
i felt like that in my brain
too so here's what happens so me
and this ah in a few other
people in the waitstaff we this club
went through many changes of management right
and so there's one period where this
person did not give a fuck and
we would stay there and drink all
night right and so
i remember leaving yeah in the morning
when it was coming from all night
i remember leaving in the morning and
then walking down the street with this
young lady and the fancy gourmet grocery
store those two doors down had just
gotten their bread delivery it's fresh bread
and we fuckin took a baguette out
of this bag this nice warm fluffy
yes did you pay for it no
we were like
street urchins wow now that's romantic yeah
it was like paris but you're in
philadelphia way way wow that's so raw
it's that's the kind of thing marriages
are built upon like oh remember like
i don't wanna i don't wanna break
up with you because remember that magical
morning where we did get married yeah
four
forty five minutes
it's like seven years and i kept
bringing up the bread story she's like
i don't eat carbs that she wanted
to break up with me and i
was like remember right bread bread we
found the free bread what time of
day wasn't dawn dawn yeah let's it's
always darkest before then yeah
that's where
that's really weird i'd say that's a
pattern there's something good times yeah yeah
yeah it's definitely pattern yeah it's definitely
something yeah yeah it's still a sudden
it's gonna notice
yeah he's awesome hey jay did you
notice the you've been noticing things do
i look it wow
also the sunlight when it comes up
did you notice the thing came up
again thank you yeah yes i know
it's i came up with it went
down last night i was like that's
never come back up again it's looking
up at the eastern went down in
the westlands then come back up in
the morning who it was coming back
over martin who used to do that
the two two boys chris elliott it
was chris l yeah yeah yeah yeah
so what am i real huh
yeah maybe like any other boy down
here yeah
hey man
huh i love that one of like
in homer simpson how's that words like
two voices was like oh wow you
know
peewee peewee herman that's the other wars
give me herman blah blah bows like
jiminy glick does it as well oh
my god he's like i have to
die
jiminy glick is that voice is one
of the the hardest things for me
to not accidentally oh yeah when i'm
doing a character that i haven't done
before so funny it's so it's like
your character funny james glick
yeah that's one where you kinda tend
to go in and that you really
go into it there he interviews celebrity
and you're wearing your diritto shirt
you said you've never read that in
public and i guess you're not in
public are you this is absolutely not
i know you said the last this
is a private record so he's wearing
his rio's shirt to dirty up his
good shirts when he sees people in
public do you ever when you read
a shirt to be by us other
or shirts to be buy them when
you're dressing do you ever take into
consideration or what happens if i get
arrested in these clothes i don't think
about that but you know i think
about a lot is ah if there
was like an earthquake or something right
in the middle of the night i
sometimes think like i'll go do i
put on shoe
shoes or do i just drive in
sandals and then i go well what
if i get arrested than i'm wearing
sandals in jail you look real mcnulty
do you shit um keeps ah running
shoes under your bed for earthquakes that's
what you're supposed to do um so
there's under my bed yeah like an
old pair under your bed older gym
shoes why old well because you don't
know if you're if
or one you want to wear every
day that you just put them back
under your bed everyday it's like you
just kind of toss an old pair
under there and then if there's an
earthquake you go oh shit i have
my shoes right here and about some
through like like air jordans or something
fine put new ones to have a
really nice moment when the earthquake happened
what about the ones they make the
movie about yeah can i put those
yeah you can yeah actually a lot
of shoes in my bed
yes yes and also you have some
like nice dress shoes you're throwing out
with your pajamas yes you're absolutely about
a super high and it's on top
of a big gesture and these are
all boots yeah yeah they're all thigh
highs
what am i everywhere i've never yeah
you hardly ever see guys were wild
unless you why captain jack sparrow or
something paul stanley him again look good
and what else are you supposed to
do and seven earthquake i don't know
but i thought there was going to
be one the other night because my
dog was like hiding in a weird
spot like an a blanket being like
yeah like all scared
and nothing happened yeah just means your
house is on it yeah i mean
it's either that or there was a
firework which can happen at any point
yeah where are the fireworks happening all
the time around here um i think
people just like to have fun but
you know what i hate is when
they shoot one show of his citibank
don't you hate when they when people
do a firework in the daylight you're
like what you're just making a huge
boom yeah for no reason i
was walking too dynasty there was some
show it was still daylight out when
i when i was getting to the
theatre and as i was like turning
the corner i heard what absolutely was
gunfire like a block away oh my
god it was fucking crazy and i
was like what and i'm looking around
like no one else seems to be
boss
authored by this oh my god it
was really scary scary yeah but then
i just walked by regular speed because
they were like he doesn't care guess
it's fine i don't want to go
i inspired them yeah i don't want
to get shot i really don't want
to get shot that's something i really
don't i really i guess if i
had to rank em i really don't
want to get stabbed with like a
butcher knife
then underneath that a shot well no
shot in the head is above butcher
knife okay that's like john hadden live
no ah you're talking fatal certain fatal
i'm not just talking fatal things i'm
just talking things
well where are you both yawning at
the exact i was oh i was
ripping yarn
oh i always want you to yawn
and unabomber i was farting oh okay
um i upped my rank when you
shot this my ranking is if i'm
going to get shot and die yeah
show me that but what about o
casket we're all going to weep over
you put ahead over my face like
i'm taking a swig affiliate
yeah just like taking a snooze in
the hammock
bury me in a hammock that would
be so cool if you will don't
do aboveground barrow it's you wonder why
if you went to a funeral and
the corpse was in a hammock and
just like pose like i'm doing weekend
reading like laid down down down you
love it you you'd talk about it
for baseball game and a transistor radio
oh my god
odd you'd love it so much i
mean that is kind of cute why
not write cheaper than a cashier yeah
it is how like have you priced
hammocks these days though yeah i mean
i think you definitely get a hammock
for like one hundred fifty bucks meanwhile
caskets so expensive thousands so expensive thousand
and what are we doing by spending
money
in that way i know we i
don't think we have a choice were
crazed with grief yeah yeah i understand
the like the way it looks people
just sell caskets i don't know yeah
oh by the way new booze speaking
of slimy people yeah my mom got
scammed twice the day why
a yeah it's like an english happened
on the rockman and i do an
okay job of telling her of like
hey these things you've done i think
i told you about the something came
up on her computer which said your
computer is frozen she believed it yeah
a number and all kinds of anyways
so might well with my mom whenever
she asks me if something's real like
an email but like re
read it out loud because you will
yeah see guys is not real i
know like yeah so this this one
was your verizon someone's tried to put
a thousand tried to charge a thousand
dollars to your verizon account call this
number oh my god so shit that
was that was kind of a good
scam honestly i know washy message yes
yes and she has a verizon account
so she called it and all this
kinda stuff and then i said yeah
you should just call variety so that's
why i said i said mom don't
call that number anymore call the number
on your bill yeah and she did
and they said oh no this is
a scam yeah they took care of
it but then on the same day
she gets a call saying wells fargo
your wells fargo account is whatever whatever
she doesn't have
have a wells fargo account and said
i don't think this is mine this
will give me your social security number
oh she does yeah it's like what
are you and they go nope you're
right you don't have a wells fargo
account it's like come on man huh
now just change your social security number
yeah it takes forever really does he
get mad at you that's sucks i
really like people who scam old people
it's cheap and it's an every rotten
business here's here's part of the problem
businesses in general like verizon or wells
fargo they're so confusing now and yeah
you know yeah exactly helping they want
you to overpay yeah honestly confusing to
pay your bill yeah yes everything eve
something they want to make it yeah
everything is so conf
fusing know that scammers prey upon people
knowing that old people are just like
i don't know i have autopay on
this not i don't know and tell
the boys from the girls
i don't know it's so depressing it's
fucking sucks man and some are and
yet i think we're going to fall
victim to it as well i think
about that all the time because at
what age do suddenly we yeah yeah
well i had one recently where i
thought i was being scammed i don't
think i was but i just couldn't
continue because i was like if i
am
stupid it was about serious exam because
my my try at my membership whatever
it was ending and i was like
i don't want any more and like
they were calling me nonstop and then
i was like i don't i'm just
i don't need it i have this
other thing bubble about then they call
me back and they're like do you
want and i was like actually kind
of do because i wanna hear my
friend show and now i realised my
app won't work if i don't have
this anymore
more so i do kind of want
it and i'm like okay great i
was like i'm sort of like i'm
glad you called me back and then
they were walking through this thing and
they want my credit card they went
wait a second is this really like
i just started to panic and think
it wasn't real and then i was
like this seems like a scam i'm
just gonna go online they're like no
you can do it over the phone
they'll be through a different thing where
like i want to see your number
goes through if
it wasn't a scam it's them trying
to like get the credit for right
right right so i was just like
no no no no let me just
i was like and then i was
like i have to go
no one should ever answer to that's
why i told my mom i said
mom never answered the phone yeah there
there's a because i think the verizon
one was them calling i was like
the simple solution she's like well i
need to know for like doctor's appointments
because there they don't know the doctors
are trying to scam you know because
it says the name of it said
serious excellent yeah and so on oh
check them again
the first time i was like stop
calling me because you call me so
many times and this time i actually
i do want your services so it
was like i kind of was always
answering for some reason i got scammed
last year for someone a lot of
time i was looking for i was
looking online for specific um phillies hat
that was sold out by the time
i learned
if it's existence on the official like
new arab site or whatever and so
i've been looking for this often on
like for a while and then found
this site and it had like that
one that i was looking for and
some other ones that were sort of
out of print you know items and
so ordered a couple and then got
an email back
that said you know your orders confirmed
and everything and then so much time
went by
and i was trying to reach summer
i tried to go
this was a county coaches are blowing
up um i went i went to
go back to the website and just
like the pages kept loading and loading
and then eventually timed out and i
was like oh no did i get
fucking scam and i looked up the
shop and it was like yeah this
is probably a scam huh
dan like three months after that that
website sent me another email saying your
order is still being your awesome so
yeah my body just leave me alone
i haven't tried i haven't even i've
just i haven't replied to you yeah
yeah yeah i had one that i
got scammed with during the pandemic that
was like i saw this the whole
panther maybe it's cold truth true but
there was like this instagram ad i
think and it was like this really
squishy big seal pillow
garcia anyway the one that i was
okay i still see that arrived and
it was a carnival toy yeah i
couldn't stop laughing the one i've started
to notice and we'd notice it because
paul and i just did some shows
in new york which sold out thankfully
but people on twitter are now saying
like hey does anyone have want to
sell their ticket to the show
and then like several oh god scam
because these other people search for that
and then they say i have tickets
dm me and then they pay them
eighty bucks or when i noticed this
on facebook because i was providing none
of them follow me and i always
and so i've taken to try to
write back to everyone going these people
are scammers
because so many people have fallen for
it and contacted me saying yeah scammed
out of eighty dollars trying to come
to your show it's definitely if you're
doing something like that make sure you're
in like a group or something you're
not just throwing it out to the
world nobody was like this my facebook
might like public facebook page i posted
about my show and then i noticed
somebody was like hey i have three
tickets but i can't go it isn't
me
want them and i was like okay
that's normal that happens and then it
was like happening like spam like spam
amount of people saying like i bought
these tickets and unfortunately when i go
i bought these tickets and unfortunately i
was like oh this is fate and
the checks needed all of them but
it was such a believable way because
that is how people do sell tickets
and another one that i can't figure
out is the i'm paying five thousand
doll
dollars to anyone who did this it's
like how is this and it's happened
so much on instagram no what did
they think they're what what does happen
people are going like give me i
think this is what it is because
this is what happened on my my
mother-in-law it's like you won fifty thousand
dollars you just have to pay us
two thousand gift an apple gift cards
and as a deposit
that and we'll send it to you
for the shipping or whatever it's like
doesn't make any sense machine sounds right
speaking not making sense we got to
talking it through here we gotta get
out
maybe you're banging on the door
okay we're back and we haven't done
this in a minute but you want
a wild friend had been awhile over
and you want to play some voicemails
yeah what's what's the voicemail jingle again
it goes a little something like this
if you ever leave a message but
nobody calls you back you after voicemail
yeah they do if if you ever
say a thing and all you hear
is a beep you left a voice
oh you did if you rambled on
and on and no one interrupted you
your
not on three umm ye left a
voice mail wow it's getting shady yeah
alright this is from oh why the
hell i don't know but they'll say
who they're okay great
oh my gang longtime pig first ten
picks my name is anna and i'm
calling uitm advice i'm horrible dating especially
at noticing red flags can you name
any red flags i should be on
the lookout for any that may be
used ignored and some examples of green
flags i am
i'm in need of help oh my
god love you bye that's a great
question it is i would say the
first and it comes to mind is
it's not cute to have to teach
someone everything well yeah like i think
there can be a thing where you're
like oh i'm like oh this guy
doesn't know how to do this let
me show my dad let me um
like how
to drive know like um like sort
of social cues or cleaning things or
like just um how to join a
gym buddy or like like you're fixing
someone is not if that's a red
flag absolutely yeah you want and if
enough people say i'm not i'm not
going to deal with it maybe they'll
fix themselves yeah for the
yeah if you're a grown-up you want
to date another grown-up yeah you don't
want to date somebody who studies so
common to be like sort of charmed
by someone's are like think like oh
i'll fix him yeah what happens is
you do that and then the next
person gets a better version so yeah
just ask my wife
waiting to be her next husband i
feel like there's so many hey
there's so many people who stack like
ap dates now and do six and
a night or whatever is in there
some way to look oh yeah that
she's not something that that around when
i relate people have told you this
yeah looks nutty like they do they
just roll like they'll do half hour
drinks with one and then schedule and
sometimes they go
actually totally i totally get why that's
a good idea because it's from what
i hear from my friends like online
dating so horrible and then you're like
you waste your night good yeah make
getting made up so yeah yeah and
you're like out with one person and
go home like that sucked so i
understand going out with a bunch but
that's not cool because then you're kind
of just you're not focusing
and you you don't really care about
ain't right i mean it's like you're
not yes that doesn't feel i don't
know why anyone would ask me about
dating advice so i'm not even going
i also say um if somebody is
talking a lot and not listening a
ton yeah people you know it here's
what it is somebody who doesn't ask
quest's yeah
it's just hard because you're trying to
seem cool so some sometimes you the
the impulses to talk too much about
yourself because you want to go like
see i'm i'm a good person to
date because but but yeah really i
asking people wanna just ask about the
people i want to be asked about
themselves so i wouldn't even talk about
myself at all i would just like
go but then you seem evasive yeah
well yeah but i'm drug dealer i
do i do about ah don't worry
about that yeah yeah really
let's not talk about me let's talk
about use as a shield over the
question ideally it's it's a given taken
if you're not feeling a given take
then it's probably not a good idea
and i think it's a red flag
if you can't tell if they like
you if you're going out with somebody
yeah i don't know yeah yeah i'll
do that a lot also someone doesn't
visit what i did once if someone
doesn't show up for the
the first date that they set and
then they apologize and say oh no
i'm so sorry i didn't show up
but let me make like just didn't
show
what happened to you
no i i'm the one who did
it what ah sky rocking red fly
my
oh god alright well that's enough for
you alright green flag somebody who's nice
yeah green flag they like you they're
fun they're cool they're nice burn also
have a real hot bod and oh
yeah if they're jack to shit and
absolutely that's a green flag yeah it's
actually a red flying do you do
yeah you know what
alright
i got paula morin my name is
amanda longtime this time etc etc
i'm calling to ask what is your
sliding doors moment aka what is the
moment where if you made a different
choice everything in your life will be
completely different um okay thanks i owe
my last question bums me i now
have so many i mean because it's
like don't shoot kyle
end of associate that with something negative
that happened like if i hadn't done
if i just done that oh i
think about the opposite about all the
good things in my life like how
precarious oh that's the way to do
it yeah guys seem better i get
an easily crashed and burned yeah cool
up was such a crazy ville you
know version of like
this had to happen this had to
happen this had to happen this habit
yeah yeah it's like if i tried
to replicate it if i had to
go back in time and live my
life over i don't think i would
ever know how true my favorite movie
about time yeah okay which about dotcom
about time you watch that you should
do it in your podcast i'm not
going to do it but you should
do it what do you mean you're
not good you have to do it
with my celebrity crush donald gleason of
course that's right joanna gleason don't ugly
so um you know joanna gleason from
into the woods i don't um know
roger rabbit that okay that or even
like getting into comedy i think it
was such yeah random thing yeah i
had a teacher who was like you
should take improv class
the system and i was like if
he didn't do that i guess i
wouldn't yeah i don't know what would
happen like what if you had not
said whatever funny hilarious joke made him
go like oh she's pretty funny yeah
well that was just a combination everything
i did but yeah if i had
not done the ah the musical in
my freshman year at high school oliver
i would not have met the guy
who became my comedy partner got me
into stand up the little kid who
played oliver yep oh well i like
twenty years old but actually when i
when i did the show clipped i
was up for another pilot and i
chose clipped because it was picked up
and the other one right and you
met mike and i would
like if i hadn't taken that miserable
job on real time with bill maher
i would not be married to jamie
wow how did that connect because ah
one of the friends that i made
at that job knew these other people
that ah i was invited to like
hang out with them when their regular
sunday night thing
janie
she was having a sort of fling
with one of these guys but she
came in one night and that's how
i met her wow and so i
would not have if i had not
been sitting on the stool
off to off camera watching and real
crazy real time with bill maher i
would not have met my wow wisely
i realising there was even more risk
with my story that i i basically
got two pilots we didn't know what
would happen with either one of them
but only one of them i'd only
been like seven episodes out of ten
and one i'd been all tense okay
i'll pick that one we didn't know
what would get picked um then it
did then it was a full year
of waiting for it to be shot
the next episode to be shot and
then i got to know mike during
the time as a friend which is
also so that was all just so
random but normally that would be very
disappointing situation and i've been you know
think anything of it at the time
but i never do do we have
i think if i hadn't got into
comedy i'd be a movie star okay
famous one ah oh yeah suppose those
movie starts that are you just stuck
to drum what have you are an
infamous movie star yeah
alright here's another one
like it's my name's rachel i'm from
canada um i just wanted to know
by the way i love you guys
um thank you i just don't want
to know placing and you guys want
to listen to on a podcast because
you're my favorite comedians and yeah i
just wanna know who you think is
funny
oh thanks i also made sense thank
you that's nice that's a nice question
i was always my mind goes blanks
um well i listened to a lot
of comedians on podcasts i know i
can merely i feel like i do
too i love naomi paragon's podcast couples
therapy i like bryan safi and jessica
chaffin asked ronna i like smart lis
i like those guys
um are not comedians well i would
say will arnett is almost a comedian
almost but not yeah he said he's
not i guess on a recent please
right all right todd glass i would
say todd glass i just like i
like hearing his voice
yeah yeah he's um harden marine and
bryan safi have a great new podcast
that paul was just on that was
the right word was well yeah the
menisci to discuss every comedian has a
podcast that's the thing but who do
we like every comedian as a preacher
character remember that it's alright every comedian
now but who would you who would
you
want to have one who doesn't
i would like martin short to have
a podcast yeah my god yeah martin
george and steve martin had a podcast
together every week yeah i was just
talking i would just say yeah i
don't know what i mean i don't
want ever to have a guest on
and i know somebody had to do
writing or work no make it just
changes show up and do what we're
doing yes well oh threesome with the
two of them and selena gomez yeah
yeah that's exactly right
that's what it should be it actually
is a lot like the show to
older guys yeah well i think only
more building space sauce
it wasn't that he was a thing
yeah do you know the older i
get the more i find jokes about
being old to be so funny good
i've been rewatching um doctor who like
i started feeling the beginning yeah from
the sixties and i there's some other
some episodes and blu ray there's some
extent seasons on blu ray where they've
like restored
rd or or like updated some of
the effects but only a little bit
which is really funny right but they
do this thing called behind the sofa
where they have the original cast members
watch the episodes and just comment comments
like tapping um not gogglebox what's called
here um franco phi the the p
apple's couch where they watch tv but
the old cast members you sounded like
an alien which human he said that
but it's not gogglebox would you call
it here yeah what do you want
people go
oh yeah of course watch gogglebox where
i'm from well god television that's cool
boxes of british show that they they
remade here as the people's couch where
it does like different groups of people
watched the same tv show that yeah
i really enjoyed that show like they
have ninety day fiance um do they
do that now when they watch
watch the show and comment on it
yes yes yes yeah um and the
old people making jokes about themselves being
old and close to death is so
funny yeah it's so funny to me
by the way i wanted to say
when i was in chicago meeting fans
ah i think like maybe a fourteen
year old ivy he's probably listening to
i'm sorry if i gave your age
wrong but a fourteen year old fan
came up and dabbed for me it's
very funny i was like hi big
fan yeah so that's bad data lift
that's very funny
look if you see us dab and
you see his dad be me i
hear you've you see me please throw
me a day is another
hi lauren column stop this is becca
from milwaukee when i was about six
or seven my teenage cousin told me
that people with flat feet cannot serve
in the military because they're very ticklish
and if they were tops of the
enemy soldiers to just tickle them until
they revealed us military secrets i believe
this was a very long time i
think it was a middle school
cool before i finally realised it was
alive it's not that low my question
for you is what is something silly
that you believe when you were a
kid or something that you need briefly
fell for as an adult that you
really should have known better and love
the show by oh my god i
feel like i have so many but
yet can't think of one you know
i remember for me a humiliating moment
was getting in an argument with a
classmate when i was in eighth grade
that ah england and great britain were
two separate places great and then had
to go in front of the class
like we were arguing and and um
the teacher called us up and said
what are you guys talking about and
i was like she thinks great britain
england are the same country
and ah then i had to i
like i was made a spectacle of
in front of the frame perfect yeah
i can't think of one enough taught
my head but i've definitely made many
many mistakes in my life yeah that's
right would you like to apologize i'm
really sorry for everything wrong i ever
did i forget what her talking about
this kind of
i love this kind of thing where
it was somebody was talking about podcast
about a thing that they were told
when they were growing up that there
was this
there was like a pool that had
sharks in it and you had to
go like retrieve something something for the
pool i don't know it was like
some something that's so fantastical and it
wasn't until he was relating this that
he realised like whoa yeah what about
the pool with without the search like
this is really it was a really
dangerous thing in my hometown right
a yeah like those kind of lies
and yes yeah i don't have anything
like that other than you've always understood
everything and you always know what's real
i feel like other than like sex
when you're first learning about sex stuff
in like slang terms i remember someone
talking about someone's bush for a while
and i was like what are they
talk about and someone said oh it's
when you drag someone in
to a bush and you kissed them
yeah that's what i was like oh
okay she gives money gives great bush
alright here's another one
hi pretzel gang this is keeley um
i wanted to know if you guys
could swap hair styles with any famous
person real or fictional ooh fictional it
be and why
i oh my god there's so many
women have amazing hair yeah the rachel
i would love the rachel i'm saying
yeah i think we'd probably all get
the rachel probably rachel
um i've i always hate having wavy
hair so i was always so jealous
of people with like straight hair like
your tom cruises or alg bio nose
to who could who could like do
all these you know the fact that
that tom cruise got to have different
haircuts and all the mission impossible is
like oh
he can have long hair and it
doesn't look ridiculous or he can do
you can shave his head you know
it was always very i was always
been yeah i my hair has lost
a lot of it's um it's way
if i used to have my i
was like kinda almost like curly and
now it's much straighter you're like tom
cruise now you're you're this generation's tom
cruise
yeah yeah i mean if people are
saying it that yes fine yeah um
who's got here that i really owe
you know who i noticed had really
good hair in an interview you riley
keough oh yeah is she's just like
nice thick long hair who she's related
to elvis is yes she's ah great
um or
no granddaughter granddaughter she is lisa marie's
marie's daughter yeah um she has great
hair she i just noticed it in
an interview i like i had never
really seen her anything and i was
watching her on like seth meyers or
something around and show fallon um and
it just was so pretty
stuff i would swap her with lauren
yeah that would look good on you
it would have to be a swap
though you'd have oh no no no
no no no don't you want my
hair oh no no no no no
no no no no don't you want
hair
i would suck just for one day
i was so i would look really
grow one day where you didn't have
to leave the house or anything okay
but eventually the house and yeah i
would just film a bunch of cameos
as you
what's the service your hair has ever
been um in high school i cut
my hair like chin length and then
when i was little outside the same
but like when i get high school
is when i did that again and
i had like that for like kind
of like mid neck for a while
and just never brushed it and it
was just wavy and like did whatever
it did yeah i liked it yeah
it was very low maint
since as a person um well yeah
then i let it grow and then
i was like yeah yeah do you
have outfits where you're like oh i
only have five minutes for before i
have to leave do you have like
some classes of outfits where it's like
oh i have a half hour i
can wear anything or oh shit this
is this is what i wear when
i only have five minutes
um are you asking because of what
i'm wearing now
uh oh he's yawning but it's almost
laugh oh okay it was nice and
for this um yeah yeah going up
fast but it's you know i just
throw i just kind of probably where
we were yesterday if they've been in
that situation yeah you know but you
do yeah there's like shortcuts you can
take yeah
there are short guy where ye will
begin any what is that the same
thing
yeah alright well sure it's look i
wear a little bit at a time
for this okay
um well i gotta go lauren i
know you have to personally i do
have to go listen if you wanna
leave us a voicemail call us at
hag claims eight if you would like
to send us a fun three to
play write to us at three m
usa gmail dot com and if you'd
like to hear ad-free versions of the
show go to stitcher premium dot com
or cbp world dotcom we love you
look we lie
love you you are physically love you
will never stop loving you also grab
tickets to my show on june eleventh
it's my next installment of a very
steal i'm cast tbd steal the ticket
don't steal it and you get a
bad watch on the livestream go here's
what you do if there's two of
you have one person go and then
they open the back door that's fang
fill it
brian tropea is coming to underground arts
in your city so please come out
and see that it's going to be
a lot of fun friday and saturday
the sixteenth and seventeenth of june tickets
are available pool of tongues dot com
slash live
i have nothing oh the book by
the company gaming book you have a
lot i give a lot man i'm
tired of talking about it but it's
too early to say i would love
if people bought the book because i
think everyone who's bought it is really
like it so that's nice it turned
out great turnout yeah i'm alright goodbye
bay
uh