sir
three o three
no one this three-day oh no
nah frito three
what happened there oh you've read rhythm
i lost my sense of rhythm here
let's let's hear you count afford you
more yeah you're missing the two and
the three really yeah do you know
what i did again oh my god
slowdown how many fingers am i holding
us for
no this is too shit about this
five yeah but it was one flaw
yeah this yeah
ten four good buddy yes exactly yeah
like i can only my tiny expertise
to structure like ah yes i love
on the dirty side i'm when i
was a kid and smoking in amanda
came out and cb lingo was a
big deal man i fuck i loved
it is that why cb lingo was
a big deal yes i think yeah
i mean there's no
no other reason
i mean we know cowboy stuff in
jet like trucker stuff in cowboy country
in general bb is a civil whoa
morse code being cool
yeah i guess dot dot dash dash
dot dot but it makes me think
of a christmas story was like he's
using his his decoder oh yeah he
was first coast no it's not morse
code actually at all and i know
it's not no but i am thinking
about things daring to know thinking about
morse code because i'm trying to think
about semaphores because
i'm trying to and seventy four so
far is the flash so me for
like some file but i think my
body some of four's my favorite girls
i try to do oh absolutely but
what so flag flag language like a
few you're holding my flags like language
and they do ah it's leaps depending
on how you boo
it's for naval stuff yeah you can
communicate to another ship to ship yeah
it's a lot of good twenty as
honestly you're really good aliens i feel
like being over here ah you're forcing
me to only look at you oh
okay well that's not true at all
what are you talking about oh yes
forcing me to lay lord you huh
road morse code is like i think
probably the hardest language to learn of
all the languages ok it's like two
dot dot dash it's like there's no
vary because i i'm a person and
i do words and those are ads
what i'm thinking right i saw other
languages italian that's words i only already
many workers dot dot dash and other
language you want you only know snow
so you know it and a million
versions of your hold on hold on
here no oh isn't that a myth
that that in ulysses spell the word
design we don't say that anymore sorry
what is it in you it thank
you um but that's isn't it a
myth wasn't an urban legend that the
yeah eighty five words
for snow yeah yeah fuck it's not
real no it's not real okay i'm
catching up to speed
this is the podcast where lauren learns
things by the way welcome to three-time
the podcast where lauren learns yeah i'm
lauren i'm paul and i'm lauren to
love just like in ah little shop
of horrors oh yeah resume to learn
two there were two laurens in my
worker class this morning oh no i
was eventually called tall lauren oh
well it was the other lawyer though
my small lauren but she was she
should she have been short and like
was she so short she should have
been short lord i never really clocked
i don't really pay attention to height
honestly i think it's a tad person
thing yeah either i'm always looking down
at the top of the head yeah
exactly so what am i thinking with
a lot of women i don't really
clock their height yeah unless they're extremely
the short are some of my coworker
works really tall had to tell me
i think two years in that she
was five one wow really yeah if
you met brianne of tart yeah you
would be like she's tall yeah who's
out she i didn't meet her toys
he's the big woman from game of
thrones oh i did we went where
we did
this where was i it was like
ah it wasn't it was a dream
come up with any lonely roads oh
my heart my voice for hearing his
name tar heels north carolina doris carolina
the word for where are you from
north carolina and met her we did
like this like series it was like
a night of one act plays that
i was saying i cannot recall how
i got there who my thing was
what was the sweet know it was
a new inflatable neck play well it's
three one act plays i guess do
you feel a lot of memories of
things
if you don't wear like i don't
remember anything about that like i i
yeah i want hundred asia and i
did a play that required me to
be talking to a man on the
opposite side of a hospital curtain and
i was all we had and we
were reading the play i believe i
don't think we had memorized it okay
and less i don't remember anything else
yeah i do kind of love that
that when you when something pops into
your brain and you're like yeah what
was that why was i the yeah
what else happened yeah how did i
get there why did i say yes
this is my beautiful wife thanks yeah
dressing him saying that i did a
one act with rachel acquaintance for agents
that i do not remember what it
was
shield yeah it was for agents of
shield this race may need some entertainment
they worked hard too and they're always
together they need up there right i
know where we did it i remember
the rehearsal process vividly i remember everything
about it other than the content of
the play which i guess tells you
a little bit about my acting process
you remember about the rehearsal process if
not the content
just like hanging out with low initial
going to going to the theater during
your legwarmers yeah doing my stretches looking
in the mirror saying it's time
you know your pills eating them oh
well we had a topic that we
are going to bring up on the
show this is lawrence topics no whoa
a topic later they'll be lawrence topics
yeah it's really good um wow so
that's actually it's actually more of a
question for my topic so it's not
really a topic it's more of a
it's not
topics so it's not it's not long
topic although i guess you could this
is the odd raise a topic this
is the opposite of i usually goes
usually people have more of a comment
than a question yeah it's more of
a question than a comment and i
just ask you you lent that dvd
to cool up and it's unopened yeah
it was a movie that i've seen
many many times but boy but did
she not alternate not open it no
she
did open it but i'm taking the
the stickers were just sort of you
know oh my god a return locks
cover those of you who wonder what
lauren what the fuck lore know i
sound insane i returned to dvd from
kula to paw
and ah lauren sees a sticker on
it and thinks that cool up didn't
even watch it because i think that'd
be a great reveal but i did
you ever have for christmas i one
time got ah cd opener slicer in
my yakking yeah yeah because i had
so many cds i wasn't sure yeah
oh yeah yeah sure but wait warren
tearing the the question was because you're
tearing that i was trying to do
gc ah intro from the life and
times of sean carter volume three anyway
oh hell no we won't very well
um i just wanted to ask because
you walked in two minutes late maybe
three five is totally fine yeah but
paul is here before you and i
was actually really thrown because usually you
are variously thrilled
sure that was great too but usually
i'm here and we have to do
small talk but your here ah we're
forced to do that's how you think
of it as that's how you think
of it but i'm saying you think
that's how you put them so i
think that's how you'll think of it
but i'm trying to say is it's
it was very unusual not to you
first as
and i asked paul and then he
said well now scott has a baby
so there's gonna be more chance you'll
be late well was it the baby
or did i just leave late i
don't know and then that's my question
that's paul said i don't have a
baby but i'm always late and i
said that's just part of your nature
and he said it's not good and
i said it's fine you know what's
not and then i was curious
what makes you late and i wanna
hear what made julie and i wanna
hear what tends to make you late
alright what i will get wrapped up
in little fucking projects in my home
such as fixing something or like fixing
something that will make an extortionist thing
something putting essential house yeah ah making
a hell
the copter yeah um yeah right into
it's little it's little projects that i
get fixated on and then it's too
late yeah right and i wonder sometimes
not to be one of those people
but i wonder sometimes if i do
have some sort of h d i'm
thinking i have that i've never
i've never ah like tried to get
diagnosed or anything and i don't i'm
not going to say oh i have
it was that let me diagnosing sure
god you're a total piece of shit
medical it pills
i am paying bills um so ah
yeah i i i noticed that
i will be doing in the middle
of doing something and then i think
of another thing like i passed by
something that i need to do and
i'm like i also need to do
that and then i'll be like no
do this you can't do both of
these at the same time see mike
and i just had this conversation because
i asked him because i had heard
on another podcast okay so i'm elizabeth
lee
sam's podcast her husband andy was diagnosed
with the i believe abt yes so
i can do that's right it was
a whole thing were he was talking
about some things and i think some
listeners were suggesting some things and he
took an actual test and knew nothing
and then he's now feeling much better
because he's dealing with it yeah and
then one of the things
i think it might have been said
on that podcast was leaving cabinets open
and then there were having it open
for the you're supposed to do that
yeah that's something all your cabinets
poltergeist therapy
there is a cabinet like cabinets are
being launched over a couple times within
a couple days and i said to
my dvd i heard that this is
a thing because he was leaving kevin
yeah open but now i like to
be female been fucking concentration never knew
this and she's like me every time
i have what openings like dvd and
i'm like you just stop asking me
that because i didn't mean
but now i kind of do because
i get really fluttery one thing too
that i wanna like because i'm not
a computer you do come to basically
you're doing something in a cabinet you
get distracted you leave it open yeah
go to something else yeah theory okay
and then i'm like oh my computer
and i have a tie of a
thousand tabs open and then i'm doing
something then i switched something else and
then like four hours later
i go back to the tablet oh
yeah i was gonna sign up for
that thing i have no memory of
it i mind thing is a combination
of your only fans yeah i gonna
only fi fan
here's my thing i think it is
a combo of the getting fixated on
things which may or may not be
eighty h tunnels also part of that
is procrastination on things i should be
doing yeah for no reason whatever reason
where it's like you know you have
to do this thing you have to
send these emails you have to contact
these people whatever it's organizers saying and
i'm like yes i know but i'm
going through this other thing that is
of not pressing orders at all yeah
all right but here's one other question
do you feel like the eighty first
of all eighty eight is probably becoming
one of those terms like oh cd
where you were saying where weirdly and
we may be saying
incorrectly yeah and it may be minimizing
yeah because there are people who act
or like just using it like it's
a word and not like an actual
diagnosis yeah right
but do you think that maybe and
i'm like what am i talking about
just good do you think that anyway
see you later shooting and maybe you
could finish my sentence and computers internet
social media probably lowering our tolerance for
task maybe but it might be also
that that just is a is it
an it's just another
other thing to get lost in as
opposed to it being of something or
be whatever yes yes yes yeah or
hoeing your garden right which i love
she do i love i miss it
since i got a laptop i don't
have my garden i know your garden
so unheard it's like so unholy when
people i can tell people are thinking
when they walk past yeah lauren to
answer your question i was thinking
about this this very morning why you're
late well i have something before we
did this today okay and i ended
up being eight minutes late to that
and i was like i knew that
i was going to be late okay
i hate being late yeah it really
bothers me and i stress out as
i'm going to
the transfer feels terrible i stress while
i do it and today this morning
i was like but here's the other
thing i also don't like being early
so i always tried to time it
to where i arrive right on time
i tried to do thank you so
what usually happens is i very rarely
ever
or show up early to something but
i'm often like two to three minutes
late to things right yeah so today
i was eight minutes late ten was
it an appointment it was ah yeah
physical therapy for my tender tender fee
minutes later that is stressful i would
say well eating into your time here's
what's great though anything involving any medical
professional you can get there
there yes a half hour early you
can get there an hour late you
will still wait for a minimum of
thirty minutes right interest well the physical
therapy there here it's a tight ship
well it's well on a boat it
is this is why i mentioned some
of yours because they're telling me how
to flex my foot with it anyways
are the best cookies um
but but here's here's the thing i
don't like being early so i will
fill up my time with just like
reading something on the internet or whatever
until it is time for me to
go and then suddenly something else will
happen and it'll make me two minutes
later something so today so today i
was like generally
be taking my time knowing how long
it takes me to get ready for
physical therapy and then something happened and
i was like man i wish i'd
heard before but then i had to
remind myself it doesn't matter if you're
late because you're paying for this and
they just waited for me you're the
boss and they did and so i
was trying not to stress yes there
was no no one even cared when
i was yeah and that's times where
i'm lee in fact
engage in therapy
or like told i can't do the
thing like my ghost i arrived late
to physical therapy when i had to
do physical therapy or something and it
was like they i was i had
just done it totally wrong on my
calendar and i showed up thirty minutes
late so yours can't see you and
i was like i cried but those
homer
but
you're gonna cry anyway yeah probably it's
right there you were in love with
really needed to hear um but i
feel like i think i'm often like
right on time if not two minutes
late but i would i'm usually late
for like literally i always have like
wet hair like it's always like yeah
the last second yeah i'll take my
shower known for i am known for
it is your thing i will just
putter about until the last possible
a minute yeah take the shower arrive
with wet hair yeah because i've instead
of because i feel like it's a
waste of time to be cleaner early
i just feel like i don't prioritize
it until it's like okay now i
have only this amount of time i'll
do that but i'm trying to do
the training a little better and i
think also my acknowledgement of my distress
easily distracted vnus not necessarily a d
d is just that i'm trying to
be more on top of it so
i last night was journaling and i
was like
let me just try to center myself
a little more my day and then
part of it i read your journal
you so good it's hilarious um yes
so i try to be fully mature
impress myself um but i realized like
so like part of my morning is
like i will be up with holly
for hours until mike wakes up he
has insomnia he tends to sleep so
he sleeps in a little bit like
i have insomnia and i have to
wake up early yeah we've made this
our routine you know you could have
the that deal no because cool ups
is like your take
eating the early because i like to
wake up late and there you go
yeah but that's how you are that's
how your situation is but i also
have zombies so i'm up in the
middle that's how your situation is working
complaining about yeah i fucking hear you
and i'm like you can do something
to change that i don't know what
ah well i got physical therapy at
eight am that's so yeah i'll enforce
it go up to get out so
you also have to yeah and so
cheap one of your therapist to you
you can do something about that but
i don't know what yeah you can
i know it's possible i know you
could do something but so i get
up first and then i'll be with
holly and i get her dressed immediately
and do all of her things for
her and i'm like it's like later
in the morning and i'm like in
my row being like i'm sloppy dapi
do like i just feel like it's
been off yeah scooby-doo so i'm like
i've started to go i'm just
going to take i'm gonna do everything
for myself and make her just deal
with that which now she's old enough
to do that now so it's like
i'm just a you play in the
bathroom while i do all my things
and actually get dressed you play with
a hairdryer in the bathtub she does
little splash around the toilet oh my
god she fell off the toilet this
morning she just turned it sit on
it to tradition they just go everywhere
i'm trying to sit on
the tunnel to the lakes which is
right next oh now into like turning
on and off she doesn't say taking
shit that turns off the light she
has no connection to the toilet being
which doesn't
no yeah she's just she thinks us
i don't think she goes in her
diaper oh you free bikers out about
yeah yeah yeah fifteen months i'm not
trying to get her to squat on
a party she's know what's going on
but she was today can you potty
train earlier like say at a month
um
people i saw saw tick tock type
thing of someone with a three month
old and you just basically have to
like hold them over the toilet like
constantly throughout the day sounds good
hey i gotta quit my job
hold my toilet training my infants
same as you can imagine but anyway
just i pretty much just camped out
here the bathroom all day long to
make it clear she fell off the
toilet into the garbage can which is
actually ah it was totally fine she
was she just like making poster at
first until the garbage janet was like
putting some yeah my distressing mondays yeah
totally
nice to be an avid a hard
day but i just haven't done that
for a few days and it's made
my life feel better so if anyone
out there you know like priorities are
you know pride oh okay you're doing
everything for her and then i go
now it's time for me and do
my thing yes yes and i want
to do that even if it's annoying
to you for five minutes and then
whenever maybe someday you get address first
and she's sloppy up you do yeah
yeah i did that
because just as charlie brown's all over
how did you sing
chocolate i met face but i said
how's chocolate cake all over your house
you're insane
wouldn't you like that though you have
a brain tumor i might have but
sounds good doesn't it chocolate cake all
your house anywhere
he's just grabbing it everywhere yum yum
yum
that reminds me i know i've told
you this when i worked on kelsey
grammar presents the sketch show um that
they would put crushers would put um
little dishes of things all around holistic
right yeah i just allowed just fine
we can't do that anymore with calvin
know thanks to convert you have to
wear gloves to eat a peanut to
walk up
we're dino de one this is true
though you have to walk up to
crafty and tell them what you want
and they serve you which makes you
look stop being like i'll have ten
reese's peanut butter cup yeah exactly yeah
you should do it the way you'd
normally yeah go and just go up
and ask for one snack yesterday a
better cup edit yeah cause five bags
of fritos to take home i know
it's so funny
i miss that can i get a
palette of t'challa ice tea when i
worked at marie calendar's rest around it
yeah there was a there was a
waitress who would just go around like
grabbing little parts off the cookies on
the bakery tray excuse me just nibbling
on them all day that's so nice
we called her the
yeah just she was just always like
reaching into the cookies and taking off
like a little bit and like no
usual disruptive shifts that's like
just always now call her the nibbler
called the police on her exactly the
cops med thirty years later we got
like somebody's been breaking off pieces of
cookie break me off a piece that
could just call nine one one say
oh
now three calendars
my god is ladies and dibley oh
can i do reality recap yeah yeah
there's been fun new show on netflix
called natural the name um all of
it don't work applying beverly hills starring
marie ceo from real housewives the husband
of cow richards he is a either
real estate mogul who i'm up
obsessed with why the husband of cow
richards tile richer okay who was in
halloween as a child
she was a child and halloween the
movie if you remove yelling i'm i
remember the holiday i remember someone film
like a child just trying to remember
was a little girl with black hair
and braids and she's like sitting alone
in the house watching tv at one
point and then she's just one of
the main kids that um what's i
am yeah that's so funny i don't
remember kids at all jamie jamie lee
curtis
um yeah like he had a really
white face yeah that was mask william
shatner yeah william shatner said that star
halloween yeah so the show's really good
it's about um a real it's about
a real estate agency called the agency
in la and they sell really expensive
beautiful homes so if you like watching
home
homes that's fun to look at and
then what's fun about it's a family
business because maurice who has hired two
of his many daughters to work there
and then there's some conflict with that
there's a lot of ah non relatives
who worked there of course i was
going to relatives oh you mentioned his
dad working there too and we never
saw him so i'm like i need
more about that
aus him like we're going a big
bushy mustache i would like that dude
think about me maurizio azimi the thing
about like million dollar listing which is
another version of yeah which i love
which is i enjoy but then one
day we were watching it and this
guy we knew and they were trying
to sell like a thirty million dollar
house create the houses are in
insane it's just but they're they're trying
to sell this thirty million dollar house
and then suddenly they're like ok well
we have one person who's really interested
in the stakes are very high and
the guy walks in is our friend
and he doesn't have thirty million dollars
like this is an act of this
he's just a friend who did a
favor to them right and then and
then we kept seeing stuff like that
we're so we're
we're like no we know we know
that like suddenly a tough agent comes
in to look at you know with
to look at the house and we're
like yeah but sorry but yeah
shield of shield yes thank you for
clarifying
she comes into like look at the
house for supposedly on behalf of their
client and coco's know i know her
she works for the other one stop
you know it's like every part of
it is fake because o j truman
show falling hair stay j every interaction
because how many times we have to
be told that i don't care i
know
no because i like looking at the
houses but they are stays for well
it's like no househunters as as househunters
they've already they don't where the houses
are already
they're putting out the house food call
it coyote hunters
i read a blog about that which
i'm sure we've talked about already know
lots of how house looks some just
empty someone's house just to show it
yeah well what whatever whatever the house
is that's empty is the one that
they always pick because that's the one
they bought recently yeah it's really annoying
everything is fake on realities yeah i
like this shit the romances oh and
then and then
some of it going as this part
faces the story but i don't really
care i like the characters than on
ah america what does the one where
it's like you know some more plastic
surgery and then they turned it into
houses like chanel makeup yeah
let's see me over it was a
movie and it's like your mom looks
like a totally is this tweet what
oh are you fucking yes yes sarda
is extreme makeovers those people who thought
they were really ugly would guide have
like no one has like ten plastic
surgeries at once and be recovering in
a hotel for like six weeks or
more and then go maybe months and
they
would change like every like their body
their fate everything about they'd have full
like they get implants in their face
they get structural tn it was not
a feel good show necessarily just really
so it sounds like there's impossible to
feel good but i remember actually this
because i i've i watched as a
kid which is also fucked up and
i remembered this thing about tea
teeth but now i know that it
must be veneers but it always confused
me until more recently i had this
memory of them sort of you putting
on baloo laid on the teeth and
like moving them into place they just
put veneers out and they just whittled
them down to shard yeah and put
gauss and that part of it is
so scary yeah but anyway it's not
attend a little peg it wasn't really
a field
i know about that process it wasn't
it wasn't like a feel good show
but then it's such a weird spinoff
because they they turned them the home
edition into a big feel good family
show oh yeah we have but it
was the same show like no it's
spin over extreme homemaker oh she may
go now extremely media should know because
think they realised it's so toxic like
the
the kids and the the dad and
you know whatever like the husband and
the kids or the wife and kids
cousin they'd show up the child see
there eventually the reveal and go yeah
oh you're beautiful looks so different there
was no there was no gradual acceptance
of the change so it's like you're
just seeing your mom go away their
bandages for six weeks and they come
back
but yeah but so the the homeland
i read some article about like oh
they do a really shitty job and
then they raise the value on the
people's homes so much that people can't
pay the taxes on the home and
family can be hey yes so they
but so i was like huh that's
interesting and then people i knew started
being the like my ah
the the in my old apartment building
the what do you call it the
person that you pay the rent to
landlord yes you know they know they
they they they're they don't own the
building yeah the america thank you forgot
their um she was not a designer
and then she like was suddenly hired
as a designer on that i'm like
are you good does
diner she's like no i'm an actress
but i'm just like okay well that's
say they made the rooms like oh
this kid loves cats generally base side
yeah and everything's furry it's it's cat
intestines a cat hard to it's it's
really what gastric acids for fun actually
hear your bed to slide it's like
he has to grow with brass it's
all like anyway we have cigarette cool
arabic
and we're back before we get into
lawrence topics yeah yeah ah as you
know the older is this paul topic
let's say sort of it's a part
two of reality recap yeah oh okay
the only reality show that we watch
southern charm okay
know that's what we drink or water
yeah um it's all just it's a
terrible show right and the people are
extremely boring um and we keep watching
it and the thing the way someone
lift that and use it as a
commercial for the show
three numb it's
the people are extremely boring
oh it's what happened shoe board came
out oh my god emergency call nine
one one b
is who here
listen to me dibler
metro's nibbler
cookie dough
so um it's all it's all the
i sort of get reality shows now
because we have
three friends who also watched the show
good your sandwich like fun to talk
yeah so we text each other and
stuff like that you feel but here's
the thing is that i because it's
all just horse shit when i find
myself when i'm watching it even when
we're texting each other and i find
myself thinking
like making a judgment on someone's actions
or whatever right like they fucking got
me thinking yeah they tricked you that's
what's fun and by the way you
do doesn't reach you do it about
scripted shows to like oh my god
why would he do that i can't
believe you do that baba like it's
like but yeah but i mean but
you're only watching the reality shows
because it's real like the idea was
like hey idea being a voyeur on
these idiots yeah but then you would
never watch a scripted show featuring these
people on love is blind for instance
so but i think there's some way
you know doing doing the exact same
storylines yeah i mean i don't have
to defend it i just like it
this is an interesting idea
a reenactment you take lifted you take
a season of a reality show then
you have those people reenacted a scripted
version yeah we're like yeah that seems
to help and see which is better
see much as i would like and
you do like you know like you
shoot it exactly like a scripted show
rather than a reality show yeah
although it's like things like avid elementary
same thing i mean i thought that
was a documentary i really do because
i spoke to the camera explaining our
feelings were in what's your lowrance topics
it's not really a topic it's a
question i think i need a new
category and you like segment for queries
yeah okay lot of questions i like
that love questions okay here's my love
question for you yes jay and i
will you shoot me wonder have we
talked about this okay that's the first
one by the way probably yes if
you're listening please send us the spreadsheet
of things we've talked to guys needed
was the nibbler knew we need yeah
that precious we hates it her name
maria why do i still remember your
calendars and i only worked with her
two months and i remember her name
maria has she rubbed you the wrong
way eating all the public's cookies also
there's a song about that name that
really makes it sound like it's great
yeah it was the most beautiful sound
i'd ever heard how did you come
up homeland tana song maria maria maria
does you ever seen a memory yeah
white glove saying that so
yeah good for him he swallowed back
on top all i know is slew
thirty featuring of by santana featuring rob
thomas i i really don't like that
song no offense to anyone would no
offense to me like so much when
about his wife that fucking mood that
just that episode filter once that episode
of bazillion with the smooth running throughout
it it was so funny
a so where anytime the word has
mentioned the guitar sing happy man and
other stories it's really funny um my
question is what do you think is
the food you've consumed the most in
your life
we have not talked about this because
i was eating i like i had
bought one and it's it's making me
sick to fail so yeah i'm like
i've eaten truck loads of fries yeah
yeah i love fries and ate them
all the time growing up nonstop so
it's like now you can finally theme
as much now even if you
go to a fast food place in
your order not a burger you're having
fries oh fuck yeah i'm having a
mushroom right i mean like maybe lunch
meat wow gina what's lunch meat bologna
um i can't i don't know if
i can narrow it down loanee passkey
i don't like it oh my god
because of the region it's from
you don't like the bologna region don't
know i only made bologna and spell
like that it's actually really annoying i
think because americans are stupid probably but
i also wonder are bologna and bologna
is there a difference between them well
well there's yeah there's no packaged there's
no package thing that says baloney right
toe one wells
well we went when we were in
my bologna has a first name when
we were in italy we were talking
about this because florence ah by the
way i'm speaking out of my ass
now oh good it smells like shit
but florence is not the is not
the the the fiancee it's fury n
z right but we but if you
look at on a map it's just
florence and that's because like we are
when we're trying to save frenzy we
say fla foot flower or abhorrence oh
because we are trying to say you're
trying to say it
really yeah so it's like napoli what
is this theory you are talking about
your so what happened because we're not
trying to save the lagna i would
say blog enough now looking back while
people say lasagna and it's not lasagna
lasagna
that's beautiful thank you
so you think you'd be
i think you mean you they were
trying to wrap our mouths around a
foreign what i'm saying the reason that
we translated that way like we're not
saying napoli
nobody is leaving nobody believed to be
overly bitter
peter crooks oh bobby meets with the
wonder your tombstone
it's just is is commercials for the
english people trying to say this word
that they that they don't have the
ah the tongue sounds for i think
they also in those days i think
they just decided what the name was
as opposed to like they hurting to
say they heard italian people saying and
they go like oh florence yeah that's
probably what they're saying and then they
put
on a map mr charles atlas puts
it on a match
then you look at the whole world
yep kick sand in someone's face
so read some book do you think
you've eaten a truckloads of bologna not
no i haven't you love bologna specifically
bologna probably the one lunch not eaten
truckloads of like this that's my real
question i don't know like delhi like
chip silly hammer dough chips for sure
yeah yeah chateau jibs
oh no poker chips oh got it
i break your stomach yeah i i
completed it but i didn't like them
at first yeah but then after a
while i learned to differentiate the the
differentiated denominations wow the way you said
that well they must like another which
one would hey what's the nomination is
the tastiest oh fifty yeah definitely
oh it's so good it's thick is
thick toothless yeah um you know the
burger chips depending on how much they
are worth yeah it's a fuss it's
taken this increase like me so that's
why you want that giant just like
pager delicious yeah um i would you
know it used to be burgers so
until maybe i was thirty because i
think i had one or two like
three trucks of burgers and then
but i think when you say fries
i think you're probably right what all
the burgers i've eaten fit in one
truck what size truck wow i'm talking
like move like an eighteen wheeler like
ah yeah he's bound da mean we
we want to do with ha candy
we got a long way to go
in a short time to get their
eez boundary was oh man it ran
beat me me me here seen that
movie smoking in the bandit know i
just watched it maybe four years ago
for the first time and i'm interested
lauren in in hearing what you would
make of it yeah
would you even understand what was happening
because it's like an white because i
can't see that it's not black oh
you can't see what do you mean
you hear the opposite of don't i
get bored ah no it's in color
but i wonder if like because it
had such a cultural impact yes because
you're old enough to kind of remember
oh yeah everybody's google this i don't
really feel like i have any sort
of joking in the
burt reynolds who he is yeah only
for just you ever seen him nude
in i've seen him laying on the
floor yeah yeah playing in my house
dan okay oh yeah okay okay i'm
familiar with this imagery okay here's the
plot sally field who has just been
a plane with the other day oh
worst thing happened to me but oh
my god it's really embarrassing oh what
do you tell me this first and
i'll tell your story are you sure
yeah okay so first of all is
behind sally field i realized that the
end of the ice was being very
kind to everyone and had a she
was very nice
between two dog she's a really sweet
very sweet anyway so anyway i actually
prefer i got some unfortunate news about
a friend's family it was like ah
just but i was kind of processing
this information just to give a little
backstory as to why what happened happened
because i was a little distracted
and i was and you had to
fly the plane because the pilot i
passed out on says that yeah captain
got know yeah i did do that
and i just have it every time
on the plane just to see what
happened but i was on the slender
okay ever let you all down to
baggage claim i had my suitcase i
will also note that i was using
my worst suitcase
case um it has released ability to
stand okay can i ask you hey
i actually hated i couldn't reach my
other ones a lot of backstory i'm
just giving you still have it this
is i'm actually thinking it's time for
it to go i i'm telling you
it is no no it is i
have better ones but i mean most
suitable other ones were behind something heavy
and i was like fuck it i'll
just take that one
kind of a whatever who cares i
wasn't thinking about it and it was
only two days it was kinda like
who cares okay i know i know
you care but it was like else
we need to know as setup know
that's it what what airport las so
i was on the escalator going down
to baggage claim which i had my
suitcase on the escalate which you just
announced your carry to term presidents see
i was on it
guess it would be i was on
air canada i guess it would be
dealt international tom bradley yeah dang no
but i don't think it was it
was tuesday's journal by terminal five oh
wow did you park there where you
being paid being picked got okay which
is part of i know what you're
doing i i'm interesting audi i'm interested
in her whole tr
travel thing i couldn't wait to get
home i'm standing on the escalator i'm
i decide to pull out my phone
while on the escalator to where you
dying like a trump thing when he
came down the escalator and he was
like mexicans are raping no no no
i was standing and i was doing
my i was being proper and i
are being properly i'm like hold out
my phone again
the emerging for a second to look
at the fucking text regarding this actually
serious thing that i was dealing with
and my bag decided to fly down
the fucking joe jacoby jacoby it was
flying i mean just sliding down was
there anybody ahead of you yes oh
no there's this woman ah off to
the side where anyone streams down a
bit further
seems i start yelling what jones i'm
screaming okay i'm screaming i'm straight on
headphones on everything i'm very present have
streams thank god in my head in
the moment but i would like to
have headphones on at this point and
i did not i was just there
and then i was just screaming oh
my god watch out
it so here's what happened in wet
horizontal and the handle was up and
go so the handle hit her hit
this woman in her income streams
and the bag was stuck horizontally in
the escalate in the escalator so i
was no i was down there i
was i ran down after it yeah
and i'm trying to pick it up
but it's like i can't get it
out from the rubberized things on the
escalate wedged and her leg which she's
not helping me at all and wishes
saying oh no but i think she
was processing how she's gonna make me
feel like shit what she did
did very well so she i'm sitting
down and i'm so sorry oh my
god are you okay i'm like apologizing
profusely i'm so i'm like i'm humiliated
i was literally i'm humiliated i'm so
sorry i'm trying to put my bag
i get it i'm offically with her
i'm like oh my god i'm so
sorry i'm like are you and she
starts limping now i do think that
was oil what she was
whacked by a plastic piece i don't
think it was a wishy see you
and save the wrong ms adam mascot
again thank god because there was a
lot of people watching this happen yeah
tmc posted up oh my god it
was i honestly my heart races i
was so embarrassing i felt like such
an asshole and she took when i
was like are you okay actually there's
nothing you could do there's nothing you
could do and then she was she
worked at l a x
i was like you people do this
all the time you people to hold
onto your bag and i was like
i've never noticed my life i trust
me i'll never have to go to
get like it was just like i
don't do this all the time this
is so unlike me my bag actually
is an asshole too this is my
worst duties doing this day around it's
tukey's that kind of toppled and i
did let go of
yeah like round just got one wheel
i'll never let go vacation me because
it was like so mean to me
and i understand why i deserve it
because i felt horrible i was like
yeah you don't just i don't know
what to how to fix it but
i wish it was mortifying yeah and
she just was not letting me you
know i think if i got hit
and so i don't know this is
a good or bad quality but i
think i would've been like it's ok
don't worry
a yeah to the person like i
know it's on the plane when someone
takes their bag out it's fallen out
onto my head and i've been like
it's okay it happens with obvious accident
of course yeah throw my bag on
the fucking thing but to never she
didn't let me she let me get
away with it oh yeah and i
felt she didn't make you exchange information
no she just went to a
some working you know person place adore
that nor their ceo in place so
i go into their little clan i
couldn't wait to get the fuck out
of there so so embarrassed and i
was just gonna go go go go
and then sally field looked and i
said yeah let me sally field have
to do because she was writing so
what part of what happened before this
is that this one woman kept trying
to race ahead of me
and it was really annoying and so
i eventually took you're trying to box
her out with your suitcase so sadly
it's um this as a smaller escalator
before this you know and this other
woman like has to get onto like
let her go and then i just
go i'm just going downstairs and then
instead of doing the stairs i get
onto the escalator and then drop my
bag on that woman so i think
sally went to a secret hidy hole
where they let celebrity
e-z-go she was being taken by a
person who was escorting her somewhere i
think she was being taken special thing
yeah but i ah yeah it was
just honestly that horrible it is really
horrible and i'm sorry that that happened
to you i truly like to get
rid of like i say i'm gonna
say i wanna fucking get rid of
it yeah cache doesn't smack to do
it was so embarrassing i can't even
tell you
scott i have an update about the
florence thing okay our producer met a
producer
it was called florentine florentina in latin
then fiorenzo in old italian then fiorenzo
the names foreigners call it by like
florence in english and french and florins
in german are closer to the original
probably because they were mostly used in
writing a similar case is the city
of ca
cologne in germany locally called cone yeah
but he just made that up like
he didn't make wrote that yeah he
yeah he wrote that he wrote he
wrote on a piece paper and then
he he says screenshot thing like like
like papers he doesn't know this is
just his opinion now you got me
there
you taught me something embarrassing that's happened
to you once once
situation i was so embarrassed ah it's
like an embarrassing thing
god to narrow it down yeah one
yeah just one i mean me comes
to mind me waking up screaming on
the airplane oh what was that i
think i've talked about esterified that's where
i had a bad dream that the
people that someone was like looking at
old men were looking at me and
i woke up and i saw
two men next to me because i
was a middle seat and i screamed
that they were in line with them
and you said that the entire plane
know i was like yeah that's them
and the entire plane looked at me
and i said whoops sorry bad dreams
and age and the guys just like
tried to make me feel like shit
and shook their head like man that's
not how a civilized person would act
huh
you're not oh yes culpable for anything
when you're in your dreams totally and
i mean like i totally give it
to that woman that i injured her
and he was unexpected she was just
stand this happens here all the time
and because she probably has happened if
i worked somewhere something would happen to
me all the time too if you
worked man that really puts things in
perspective like people who weren't look if
you work somewhere something
is going to happen to you yeah
a lot wherever you happen to be
you don't work somewhere oh nothing happens
two things happen to me at home
yeah do i get mad at my
house you worked there
um i remember in my early twenties
i used to drink and drink and
drink and drive and drive no thanks
that's right i do not drive yeah
that really was lucky for you but
i wasn't real it was real stroke
of luck
um i was in wildwood new jersey
performing at a place called the comedy
casbah which was legendary for having the
worst audiences and you would do a
week there and it was just have
to go rock the casbah interest believe
me they played that at the i
think before
four and after every oh good um
but ah it was so his weeklong
gig two shows a night for people
that were not going to enjoy what
you did um and you stayed in
these sort of apartments that they had
above the club and then you can
be it was actually it was a
fun gig except for that weird hour
or two
hours of the day that was the
reason we're there yeah i feel really
stand up and go stay somewhere so
hard and that was actually it was
nice to stay at the like the
rooms that were nice that's the thing
if you didn't have to do comedy
images it was someone who's just like
hey come study some say lee she'll
roar why is it the worst when
you have to do the thing
you know this is the eternal question
i know okay so go on so
i was at a bar afterwards and
i was so drunk i think me
and whoever i was with we were
doing dr pepper shots
drop what is zin whiskey you're seeing
drops into a dr pepper some know
probably the way to what is dr
pepper up to do it it tastes
like dr pepper whatever whatever i forget
what the shot is that you drop
into the beer but it makes it
taste like dr pepper sounds good no
little too good
and so i was of course of
course wearing um you know ah a
blazer and a tie and a ah
of fedora and a heady underneath just
for you not what happens on tour
stays on
and i was ten staggering do people
still say teddy staggering back your rotated
eighties staggering back to the to my
where i was staying like i could
not walk in a straight line and
i heard and i'm like me i'm
in my early twenties and i
here these kids across the street say
oh no hey look at that old
drunk ah and i knew they were
talking about me
that old drunk i was like really
to be so drunk that you can't
walk shape it to have the wherewithal
to know you're being made fun of
your teeth yeah yeah that cuts through
yeah cut-through we have to say break
will be helpful for your embarrassing i
wanna hear realize you said you told
me i don't have anything new he
was a fresh embarrassment or gta foe
kind of saying ray fi high
and we're back and guys i'm gonna
need your attention no i'm listening no
you're not sure you struck your shoulders
sarcastically like right like of course i'm
not listening i know i'm listening you
just waved your hand to me like
you
to dismiss your very words i'm listening
to you say oh my gosh okay
so i'm playing three cheshire everybody loves
at where gone to do it if
you don't like it go five yourself
yeah this is the part where some
people turn off the podcast of this
that's not trying to save told people
just
trump told you this but other well
who was telling you so a tweeter
a tweeter was almost yeah
oh my god i'm showing you say
this is their favorite part okay it
was so funny when everybody started changing
their name to elon musk's letter was
fine and then he was like a
dagger used by some i'm gonna suspend
any account permanently explicitly say they're parody
that's why he said yes what a
she's a big dumb baby i
i think i i really want to
delete it my my one issue because
i'm not gonna pay the eight dollars
i'm i'm simply oh my god no
not just doesn't i want to delete
the whole thing but i wanna just
my name just to have it be
reserved as mine yeah yes yeah here's
though i mean i guess cares it
honestly doesn't match
no i don't i don't care about
what you're talking you know you think
that's worthwhile no i just don't care
oh okay whatever like you might feel
all the time when i got rid
of the checkmark i was like you
got rid of it yeah when a
while ago you chose to not have
it you wrote yeah right to say
i don't i wrote to twitter and
they nobody wrote me back and i
was like and then i heard somebody
say
oh you just change your screen name
and change it back and i did
that and then the the check mark
was gone interstate and you because you
got a lot of annoying replies i'm
sure because you've a lot of followers
it's not why that that has not
changed but um you still a lot
you just viewed it as a status
so i haven't looked lately because there
might be a bunch of bots that
were following me they're gone i have
no idea ah but i
it's that i the checkmark became this
this weird status thing to people because
they want to really take you down
they wanna take you down this way
like oh look you blue checkmark yeah
they just miss a thing that you
say sometimes you have a blue check
turn it on its head in an
interesting way for every asshole to have
yeah exactly it's so dumb still have
mine as a
preston sure who cares when um keep
it don't keep it all i think
i'll just let it do it's thing
i'm never gonna put credit card and
it's to know if anybody pays for
it critic ridiculous if i tell you
it's one to eight points
i've got to tell you we usually
tell each other but we are credit
card eastern time space that's our little
ritual before we record as we recite
our credit card numbers to each other
and our mother's maiden name history we
grew up on um alright let's play
three your guys okay okay i do
it i do it there's a little
fellow named
tim ward oh my god the three-tier
submitter yeah you got all saucy and
he said he won one night he
was like drunk as hell he was
in his cups and he was like
as i know something good that i
always in his cups that's a good
one yeah yeah um he submitted this
it's word alley oop
w i know regular alleyoop can i
also just ah and yeah i know
when you say i like weekend water
that you guys saying yes and i
like your merch thank you very beautiful
thank you very much when i'm when
water compliment we can walk on your
merch
you're wearing from marvel we get water
comes from jamie's mom oh she made
it up yes her grandson and that
was like a southern phrase or something
her grandson was reaching for her drink
her cocktail she said no no no
that's that's nikki's weekend water wow i
really thought that was something i just
didn't know now
you know that's really good i love
that it's a really personal yeah yeah
yeah extremely purse oh okay i need
we can order cups now okay here
we go this is called word alleyoop
now we're going to text each other
a word fun the person on the
left i'm gonna very strict plans so
how long is this game gonna go
do you mean with constrictors
well i messages this is going to
run into money for me do they
punish you or they punished me owe
somebody money no so many comes to
my home and shames me you can
sense a text yeah ten cents yeah
i'm sure it was like that and
my dad would get mad at my
bill madison
high school just your build not at
you know just scream it a bill
he just told me to go away
yeah okay we're gonna text a word
to each other yeah i'm gonna take
the lore and play individually not on
our group anymore know anywhere word any
word alright wait so you're texting lauren
yeah i'm injecting you all you're texting
me yeah exactly um
alright we're texting each other a word
i've texted lauren i've texted scott same
paul okay
we each have our word now we're
going to do a scene an improv
scene fuck i knew there was a
catch i thought this was the whole
game i just had a text award
and get yes i think there's so
much fun it was time we usually
only takes one word at a time
anyway and you're right what are we
supposed to try to do okay we're
gonna do a scene
we have to say that word okay
in the scene at some point easy
okay now afterwards
if you use your word know everyone's
gonna use their work and if you
can get and get it out you
can't figure it out if i say
it in a sentence we we have
to guess what the word was ah
oh so you're trying to horn in
there really obviously because yes because that's
what it was right yeah so
um we all have our words um
alright let's do it here we go
yeah okay
well intuitively i beg your vote and
deliberately people think that libraries are free
are they not they are it's just
that they take a little bit of
your soul when hi guys hey i
were just talking about libraries oh intuitively
unrealistically speaking all things considered
by this things considered so listen to
that you content npr you the her
contention is that libraries are not free
i think that they are free monetarily
but they're not free in the sense
that they steal a little something from
you and keep it like it was
like what like what but if your
essence because i don't know so people
really go to libraries he says i
just i don't think a lot of
old older older people but they they
fall in session
and like you're saying grumpy grumpy old
men yeah good old grumpy old men
oh i rented them from the library
can rent that at the library on
e gray senior citizens oh yeah but
wait so but but if you go
to ah another place of business and
you buy something you're not leaving well
i guess you are leaving something of
your essence if you go to the
supermarket
and and you by ah ah a
group you one ape a bunch of
grapes could you buy one grape from
what would you like to try if
yeah what was it because it's whatever
whatever a pound but yes i please
do the math for me i will
have one great you have to hope
that the the person checking you out
is
is in a good mood and you
know intuitively happy intuitively and deliberately delightful
and not feeling you have to hope
their delight feeling left feeling annoying or
noida sort of sort of horn horn
feathered and cantankerous you know horn feathered
yeah
horn feathered um
horn feather tour horn feather i'm not
familiar with that term yeah are you
the owner ryan by the way lady
like you know just your your laming
like lady what are you library i
am the librarian that you need something
yes really just after his talk oh
you have to use the recipe it's
always taught you're gonna go to the
down the hall you see the exit
time
go out there and take a piss
in the ad
god yeah wow i want to rent
grumpy old men too oh okay well
that's some grumpier old men i think
we have that we only as you
know we only have sequels um and
they yes this is library to isn't
yes you need to go to libraries
like chile
a little t o origi oh yeah
yeah the jerk too yeah and you
have your own song that you're saying
for people's birthdays jazzy birthday it is
my birthday can i see your id
ah yes
um ok it says she's born on
this date and this is a fake
agents of shield employee card but it's
my real birthday oh i'm willing to
see it
wow i'll start over apartment i sneezed
and i may do so again
butcher start over
you start over every time we sneeze
yeah if you could just chain it
it's allergy season if you must sneeze
simply as a receptacle
okay have we all said our word
i have i have okay okay now
we obviously i know your word so
paul you have to guess lawrence i
have to guess yours and learn your
guessing i guess yours thank you hi
yes right okay but i'm right
really fucked your o because i really
i've tried what i have my guests
paul i'm guessing essence wrong whoa i
have no guests for you you have
no guests you are not paying any
attention well i was getting really caught
up in a lot of things
so you have no guide i guess
my word i mean i want to
say and debatably
she was saying red herring if that's
the right word um i want to
say it was either horn or feather
no no okay okay you really pointed
to it cantankerous
i tried to say varied and a
lot of other guys there i think
i buried my pricing you did you
don't mind was fashion i never went
up yeah yeah i said it when
i said of libraries fallen out of
fashion
very well done none of us got
any points it's a hard game you
don't know what wanna know my word
was oh yeah what was it grape
grape yeah when he said i would've
been my second choice by well because
now it would have been because it
would've been right yeah after his fashion
would have been my second choice had
one alright do you want to go
the other way
yeah yeah i'll try it again okay
so wow we didn't need to other
way i'll talk to weed to make
the rule not make the word
a little bit yeah we don't no
no no okay okay but it can't
be like though we don't have to
do anything but i think scott yeah
you're texting me i'm texting paul and
i'm texting you lauren yeah i mean
obviously like you're the one texting the
word so if you make it really
simple right then no one's gonna
you wanna make it as hard as
possible for the person to say i
think okay
okay i've texted mine and i've received
mine away and i've checked mine and
i've received mine wait wait i'm anyone
text me yeah i got it i
got it
hello hello come on in come on
okay look i get it thank you
for coming no i guarantee your name
to you for having us it's alright
so you guys who who are who
are you the we are the mother
and father of i'm sorry am i
assuming you're a couple a wife and
husband and mother and father okay
i love jarden jarden german he's named
after the jimmy john's sandwich oh ram
great speaking to gym but we didn't
want to get sued so i don't
shoot on my name's jimmy that's so
really what's the word james well you're
gonna get sued superintendent jimmy john yes
okay we do the superintendent of i
know
the teacher no no no no higher
and teacher straight to the top wow
no i i called you in because
we've had a nervous we've had some
terrible terrible things happen to jimmy oh
okay yeah don't you feel the dread
in your heart it's like oh it's
time is rape so plank have to
jump into the ocean and hear the
bad words and
the alligators mouth i hate hearing the
edwards in the alligators mouth yeah like
any just eat you and be done
with it why does you have to
sail those he wants you to hear
the tick boom of his club yeah
well here's the thing it was so
crazy that this happened on parents so
sure that conference arnon what is it
he's dead
was i'm sorry we lost we lost
him to be clear this is our
monkey jardin yeah and we send to
the human school yes and i love
the outfits you pick from every day
i just say funny monkey and cool
you know i dress him first and
then address myself that's seeing your so
and i'm allowed to sleep and now
he has
isn't sonya i sleep like a baby
i go to bed at three pm
and i wake up at ten am
and this is why i look so
sloppy
yeah i'm a well put together i'm
standing tall handsome writing sexy lie my
friend s pam risk is calling me
as spammers spam um it's really the
risk here
here's here's the issue he got into
the laboratory oh no he was working
in the lab you late today this
afternoon okay and we did experiments on
him wait so what happened was you
killed our son the monkey yes let's
stop calling my son i feel like
what this bad news it's kind of
just taking it to a different place
trying to make him feel worse but
analisa because the workers are pet okay
i'm your pet know i can hear
everything you're saying well then i wasn't
talking to you i was saying my
way anytime you you're right now you're
talking to me so you assume that
he should not be listening to you
talking to me
wait by d i don't see anyone
else here besides somebody or you undercover
it's me bobby d i'm under cover
what are you researching what roles you
should roll oh what what role yeah
um i'm researching the role of a
parent of a monkey oh my god
school is there anything in this movie
for me i mean i'm sort of
an amateur
i teach the drama club why have
nipples does that make me a casting
agent ah no let me tweak those
right yeah here come the fuck is
going on
right yeah we said our worry and
i don't believe you have we said
our word why we want to see
jargon and then we'll end the game
started so is jordan have we said
the word was jarden
i say i have said it okay
i've said it all right so i'm
guessing lawrence yeah i've forgotten everything by
the way i do not know i
know i'm really hard to do guessing
plank that was right yeah i'm guessing
sandwich
no do not say sandwich i don't
remember sammy hundred families i did say
jimmy john's sandwich out but it's not
sandwich okay what was it we do
guess scott have to have to go
scott's nasa you don't have a guess
because it's like really hard i don't
have a guess because i don't remember
anything that i know same it's nothing
it's almost like really nothing that can't
hear you
ah i wouldn't hear him i was
acting too much after i got my
word i was like i'm already when
you're in character ah was it my
word was live when did you say
i don't even remember you saying it
i was describing myself oh easy i
was saying yes that i'm usually i'm
sorry i'm sloppy do because usually i'm
oh standing guy
i actually know ma was what i
didn't hear that word and i actually
thought that moment was when it was
happening was the last word i signed
that little zero hyper aware oh how
he was doing it that just made
me think something was going on so
you have no guests for me
um per you you said let laboratory
oh how would i get tried to
really give you a hint to i
give you a head that was not
it he initiated so that he could
get his word out
superintendent yes so i've ever done in
your initiated by parent teacher god without
trying to stop him i was trying
to say no you're right you're saying
you're sorry i got it in there
yeah i got it in there like
oh jesus you're right i turned up
my volume mode
out with my knee accidentally newer guys
were shouting okay we have to go
that was fun this was fun i
enjoyed that game fun it's a fun
game it's a good game yeah thank
you jim ward ratliff yeah yes tom
um who can no one ever knows
alright so here's the deal what
is it if you want to follow
us on social media where three usa
on both twitter and instagram okay yeah
okay change it to elon musk on
instagram yeah
okay and then if you want to
listen to old episodes three of them
were re-releasing all the old episodes we
were calling it three visiting on the
two because it's happening on tuesday so
this tuesday will re-release another episode three
visiting do you think we if we
had a producer who could tell us
for sure what it is that we
don't have
one of those we just have he
wouldn't say we're mad is making up
shit about italy
anyway
anyway italy we love you
uh