three
oh
a bone
age bonk bonk bonk bonk bonk ow
my head how come you catch ca
didn't make it into more songs i
know you would think that other other
songs would be like you know that
one song so popular let's just put
a chick to ca they can't sue
us yeah they could they could you
imagine that core
art landmark ruling goes all the way
up to the supreme baby wow and
it's a two guy braff ruling on
this i can i love to imagine
him ruling on things i like his
opinions j k do you think this
particular day today
ticket ticket ticket okay gotcha kay just
getting j k harris j harris j
k harris note oh yeah they're saying
j k rowling but you have no
idea what i was doing
c j k simmons we have to
introduce notorious turf chicken yeah j k
simmons j k simmons
j k simmons your three or more
of everyone j k simmons jack hey
yeah really same-day k harry j k
rowling jack majesty jackson der magically gets
jackson what's called black yeah don't you're
not supposed to bring them
it's going okay with playing get what's
going on with playing get well it's
going
i did not obey the rule of
three i wish i had yeah shut
it down into a beautiful heartbeat
waters but
crosses narrow
or they cross road but if really
cross crossroad doing ga
yeah this ross perot doing it now
as i did not search yeah oh
yeah i'm not a cross
bro doing george h w bush herbert
walker syndicate it would ah
get it you're gonna get away with
it
yeah
hi everyone welcome to freedom ah light
batteries what's up players we're back and
better than ever i feel like we
true yeah i feel like we haven't
seen each other a million years no
no and throwing racism has been a
while yeah really a lot happened a
lot yeah yeah tell us why i've
been all over the place i mean
wait what was i saying
we saw each other it was before
the fourth yeah it was wow i
went to chicago i went to new
buffalo michigan chicago i said i was
going to michigan anybody was actually new
buffalo michigan why did you lie yeah
why are we talking when i punched
the air bnb i was searching michigan
city and found this one and then
after i booked today
guys it was new buffalo which is
right next to it and then you
felt embarrassed so you lied um i
didn't know i lied until i was
done speaking to you speaking of being
embarrassed i thought it's pronounced urban oh
kevin never heard loud before and i
feel yeah oh i think we should
back up i think we should talk
about the fourth of july did you
guys do your movie night did you
need yes
did but but what we didn't realize
was ah my my next door neighbors
who constantly parties on holidays we have
already say forty yeah we'd have one
that lasted late into evening and so
we couldn't do the outdoor movie we
instead watched it inside tough to not
be invited to the big party so
you're saying yeah
i wanted to part the bushes and
yeah room for smoke
we were just gonna watch some movie
but it sounds like girl have fun
if i'd gone i wish i'd like
had pajamas and gone over the land
you have your candle and you're like
my candle stub yeah but it's a
little firework because it's like thematic carry
lindo ah comedian ah that i know
from philadelphia um she
posted an instagram story somebody had brought
to a neil young concert that she
was at a fucking like ebenezer scrooge
wow the little stub of candle that's
how we get along bruce springsteen has
been popular like back button scrooge was
a thing do you think bruce frazier
still young honey because nobody mentioned restraints
ah i knew it was better idea
young little weird slam on britain really
don't even know why i said that
it was like i don't even know
why
i just don't know why it just
came out not what i meant wow
what a man i like what am
i coulda woulda shoulda i also entered
neil young was chopping broccoli was not
that's why you were so confused it's
like i was like why am i
still talking like it's like he doesn't
give what i'm saying and he's like
yeah cause that's make any sense okay
go ahead
was not was not approached by anyone
at neil young i feel like his
audience is older than our three mm
audience but i will say so i
was at a couple young himself said
i would pass on the original piss
pay i got a lot of it
at they might be giant sparks that
makes sense ah and then i was
at ah
the ahmanson watching into the woods which
i know you're about to see into
the woods the tour the woods the
touring production and a gentleman came up
to me and i was like oh
here we go and he goes hey
i yeah i used to come to
the death ray shows great to see
you when i was like i left
that interaction a little disappointed that i
was like huh i guess there are
no piss pigs here
literally three seconds later i'm a pippi
yeah that different who spoke to you
should get in to being a piss
pig because it sounds like he misses
you i think that you get into
a trash can and go to hell
wow straight down a hill
so yeah down a hill to hell
yeah yeah um what if you felt
ah yeah what a child joe went
to hell
oh my god this is a great
premise for movie re re okay so
how do we get andrew dice clay
in this
there has to pay him five dollars
there has to be cameo from the
jack and jill went down to how
oh but it but it remind ready
reminded me of this story that i
read the the median disappointed that the
person wasn't pittsburgh not the new testament
oh god
okay so there's a little carpenter
oh not again um but it was
it was this profile of tom waits
written by the woman who wrote eat
pray love um and her name and
name has been gilbert yes yes so
she she wrote this profile of of
tom waits and there was this funny
part where he was talking about like
everyone was talking about like oh yeah
ta
tom because he doesn't have a regular
job with regular hours he's always the
guy that we call on for ah
for his kids in elementary school to
drive them around to all the field
trips and they asked tom waits about
it as he goes yeah i have
really old like one of those big
you know sixties cars it's really long
and big because i have one of
those and i'm always looking for new
nine passenger opportunity
but then so then he's talking about
so anyway i took the kids down
to guitar center for a field trip
and i'm just sitting there and i'm
waiting and i'm like alright when are
people going i'm gonna be mobbed obviously
i'm sitting there no one recognizes me
none of them now that people who
work there i'm getting upset and i'm
getting angry the longer it goes
i'm i'm posing next to guitars i'm
like come on guys come on guys
then three weeks later i took the
kids to a field trip at the
dump i pull up people go hey
it's tom wow everybody knows me the
dough wow duh that's how i felt
everybody knows me the dough yes he
is funny tom waits yeah he's very
funny yeah i heard a story about
him this is this was a story
from a a dear departed fruit of
hope perp is my emotions
have you ever breath yeah i burp
whenever i'm sad
yeah you never burped your emotions yeah
um so tom waits this is like
not long after the early era that
you and i we sang that song
together do you remember on freedom yeah
please call me baby i love this
probably around that area that's that's like
one of the best songs of all
time
go ahead and say put on list
of overdone list of three hundred greatest
songs that's on their day three hundred
yeah song please call me baby remember
we played it on three months i
don't let's play again because i'm sure
listeners don't remember okay well no actually
anyway remember anything to them yeah
i can't believe they played the song
again i'm so pissed scenario first we
have to hear it we have to
see a better help class but the
desk over here my god paying for
the fucking premium know it's funnier
three hundred top three hundred songs just
give it a second let this alone
let it play
i don't know about three hundred maybe
five hundred and twenty five
let it move you
that is log song
why do we play shh you're talking
about songs like we were talking about
songs we liked your horrible
this is crazy
i like cats and dogs
i just know just let it let
it go play the entire song no
let it get to the heart i'm
talking what part
wait there's only a part of the
song that belongs in the top three
hundred
his role in the streets
here we go
we do crazy things when we're wounded
hilarious
they have little musical notes jump into
your co
outlaw in the re
it's a lovely lovely so beautiful
australia the show here wait what was
the part you like that part that
part
so here's the story that my friend
my friend my late friend big daddy
graham told me that's the name that
was his stage name it wasn't his
name dodge
he was little daddy graham and the
little days named after the dad little
daddy no one's ever dad junior why
don't we do that what do we
do that
how little daddy how little damn junior
kids aren't like my dad junior yeah
if your daddy and my daddy daddy
junior or my mommy or my little
daddy did you ever know anyone who's
a true junior or i knew a
third true near yeah
we call my brother meaning is someone
who a man who's pregnant my father
was a junior we started my father
was a junior his father before him
there was a strong ball in our
family because they my fat my father
was the firstborn so he was the
the junior and then it was expected
that when my parents had a son
that the firstborn would be a junior
yes
they are not do that do it
and so i know my father's brother
my uncle named his next kid the
third like makeup yay don't worry it's
still in there do you feel i
think it died with him i thank
your parents now want to use that
name for some reason or wonder why
i find it like weird
in a different name so you know
who you're talking to i think i
liked the tradition but a lot of
people will do like they'll name the
person the next the same full name
within they call them the middle name
or they call them on and ah
yeah nickname of the first name so
everyone has a different version junior yeah
which i'm like oh i think i
do i like i see both like
i do like deadbeat i
think that tradition i see both dead
welcome
i see both and paulie rowdy roddy
piper
the two dead people i see a
ripley gonna rally roddy piper and i
never taken in the same place which
makes me wonder okay i got questions
um ah oh that's definitely what we
were talking about juniors and thirds and
before that we are talking about big
datagram that's right but oh yeah and
so he gave me this
stories around that era of tom waits
career he's playing some place that has
ah a kitchen in it you know
it's like some venue that also serves
food and so he hear that yeah
i'm hungry my assembly i guess i
could have some fries right now yeah
i can have some fried you bring
fries forever i did bring fry
yeah but we'll have them after the
show okay and there will be ice
cold honestly so dad and the consistency
will be disgusting this guy's the real
real hard potato ian's yeah just doing
you like ooh yeah um and so
i just got an airfryer and i'm
really loving it anybody really yeah we
have to talk more about it later
tomas does
covers that an old friend of his
is working in the kitchen sky name
art and so he says i wanna
go back so weird art he makes
art and then art makes food and
and and and and the artist should
make art sing the food is a
painting okay people would eat it and
then it
was bad because they're eating paint i
see but did it taste like fries
no but they would certainly wouldn't spray
a fry smell on it like i
do fries go with that shake not
anymore i just drove bio run over
skunk on the way here wow thanks
did you make a wish i did
and the skunks will hit me like
thirty seconds later i was like ooh
they really
loved a release yeah or they just
holding onto it the entire yeah is
it is it like a fart it's
just like our part where they're like
i really would want to let this
go but i needed to protect me
they have a stinky sphincter that's like
release things to our standards what is
amazing about evolutionarily skunks they're like
look i'm not going to stop eating
the things that meeting yeah i love
them and i love my method of
getting them yeah
the best i could do is like
a spray stink out of my ass
yeah i know they do feel like
i should have gone away by now
yeah i'm not going to involve big
teeth because if it was so useful
humans would have it right that's not
what a perfect lodge were not the
best their thai world right yeah well
that's why i wonder like oh i
don't mean to be better
i don't want noses like dogs like
i get jealous when i hear oh
the dog can fucking smell this well
i mean want to evolutionarily shouldn't we
know why why would i want to
smell we're we're in charge we don't
want to know because of our thumbs
what else bad in that way you
know i'm feeling so aware they love
it when you see dogs like going
over to poop and quince like they
love it like don't you want that
relationship without hearing information yesterday true it
is like usa weekly for dogs i
saw the usa weekly united states of
america us
like those patriotic celebrities doing crazy things
you can't stop us remembering our paper
that really
um so really oh ah united united
states today
um i saw this dodo video you
know the animal account ah sorry no
the doh oh yeah oh dodo like
the like dodo just what's it called
like dodo happiness or something it's called
something dodo told the dodo okay the
fucker you don't happiness oh that's their
lifestyle magazine
yeah oh yeah i'm a subscriber i
love it it's actually daily why did
they name their cute animal content account
after a dead extinct thing you know
you gotta ask these questions because here's
what here's my guess every animal that
there were no i'm not worried every
ana i've talked with listener dear every
okay d
for every animal that there is definitely
already has an account named after it
yeah right there's demand to go to
one's dog there's a deadly cat dog
da the start simple at cat dog
at draft anteater yeah go look this
aardvark go look up instagram slash aardvark
um so this dodo video with this
woman saying there's this filter where you
can see the world the way your
dog sees don't know because dogs are
colorblind or whatever the sorry this page
isn't available no one has aardvark know
i'm gonna get that and so everything
looks tope except for this one toy
that is blue and she's like that's
why he likes this toy so much
because it's the most color
powerful one and it's like wow this
doesn't make dogs do not exclusively like
blue stance yeah that was the only
difference she's looking at all the shit
everything is tan except for some things
are blue it's crazy yeah and and
my question dojo i call upon you
to take that down even listen to
it yeah i heard everything
yeah because you said it's crazy like
no okay i'm glad you're yeah no
no no no no no it's crazy
because my question is how do we
know what they see how are we
getting this esa thing exact has has
one dog talked and we just interviewed
him about his life i guess it's
that time we think that about all
dogs should come up like oh dogs
are colorblind why because this one gained
the power
of speech and told us he was
colorblind come on they might not all
be colorblind yeah he never thought about
nah i'm a little booboo and little
no no i'm still a little little
bit of a tunnel the sausage king
of chicago so tom waits says i
want to go in the kitchen and
visit whoa my old buddy someone's in
the kitchen with dinah art
art and so he walks in how
does he hear about this i wonder
like hey your old buddy art spector
that's someone with a similar voice to
tom waits tie bent art probably saw
the tom waits was coming to the
venue and said hey i worked there
right um so ah he goes back
and ah art is at the dishwashing
machine
and tom wait says a already so
you got yourself a hobart and then
he washes dishes with him ah for
the rest of the night oh well
what a nice guy yeah yeah yes
yes that's wow cool that's great that's
really that's really cool man i was
expecting more from this
oh i liked it i added use
me a good feeling it went in
a direction i wasn't expecting at all
i just wasn't expecting anything but that
also wasn't what i was expecting we
should we should do a shift of
washington issues once a week yeah we
sure the three of us yeah we
should do yeah yeah yeah i'll see
you there and we're definitely going to
do it for sure
or you could just wash the dishes
at my place oh i see how
this works okay i'm trying to tom
sawyer us
i already painted your fence last week
what was the psychology behind it it
was like he would say like boy
there's fence painting sure is fun you
probably like it and then these idiots
were like oh shit like you but
i would love it yeah and then
they all paint the fence and then
he like just kicks back and chill
what did she a genius genius man
and he's
brilliant what else do you do oh
he fakes his own death he didn't
fake his own death he just like
missed it they thought he was dead
and they anyone she was own funeral
yeah oh my god like that guy
on instagram wait i haven't heard about
this guy was a man is ten
grand dot com slash river yeah and
by the way shocked there's no at
aardvark what are we doing what are
we doing guys as a p
people yeah yeah as an aardvark but
um this guy he faked his own
death with the you know his family
was in on impotent tricked all of
his friends and people hadn't seen in
many years and they all came to
his funeral and he popped out and
was like now you got to appreciate
me because i'm still here so
they're like we hate your voice
so recently he faked his death it
was something like to teach a lesson
about like appreciate people you still have
more fluid news copter did they film
it it was for filming it was
for instagram just for dough did he
get sued somehow because that's there must
be way to sue for that i
want to see fucked up yeah i
want some too it's so fucked up
i mean his his family was in
on it so at least they weren't
traumatized
xd that would be really horrible i've
been boozing you your friends could be
traumatized oh definitely i'm saying it's worse
if you do it to your family
oh traumatize your friends like why do
you think anyone we know who's dead
is actually alive god i hope not
um could be cool third somewhere in
a bunker nobody i like his dad
hitler wow he was in a book
okay you guys can you milk him
milk it like
it's like a breath
quebec quebec um if you are a
the third yeah a nickname for that
is trip people will call you trip
oh really i don't actually like that
my best friends from f fifth grade
to seventh grade that he moved away
was a trip if you are named
after someone if you're named
my redneck if if you are named
after show but if you're named after
your grandfather your father did not have
the sunday skipped one they call you
skip they call you skip oh they
also call you tray if you are
the third okay he didn't have any
of that he was okay you don't
have any of that his name was
edward and
his wait a minute a middle initial
was p and his last vampire yeah
sorry he was sleep glittery i'm always
champs sup was he a scissors hands
he was a vampire and the sisters
hands so he would like cut someone's
neck with his hands and then suck
the blood out now was etched no
teeth was scissor hands of sweets you
just had all his teeth removed oh
okay was edward scissorhands an original screenplay
not based on any short story or
anything you are
correct source i know that's a great
movie yeah like where are we just
gonna get some edward scissorhands style weird
shit happening i just want some edward
scissorhands like the you know i p
i want them to expand it you
know i want or cans and a
i want um did surprises what isn't
it
i want the prize isn't what it
is what is what is well i
am i mean to do is buy
myself a brand new law or somebody
you better alive i don't know that's
oh i'm gonna look this up wait
i'm so surprised you don't know the
song surprise
what a great day ready yeah okay
alright okay fc yeah
yes
bad thing you're like isn't it gonna
strap okay grand juries lab with here
this commercial chip skip ads oh i
finally i can skip it we saw
a trailer for gran turismo and janie
lucky leaned over to me and said
didn't clint eastwood already if this and
i said that was gran torino not
about racing itself racist racism yes
hell hell
down the hill to hell
jack and joe in hell
darling was too hard to swallow i've
got the solution i'm leaving tomorrow now
i stand and stairs where are you
going saying see there want surprises really
need to do is find myself a
brand new lovers
with eyes for me to snow zombie
others need to do
i have to say oh
first time i saw ever i love
that means dead or alive for me
on a show yeah i love that
for you know because actually you know
what it means
you let some stuff go still things
out there
yes like that what was your story
what happened the first time i saw
dead or alive on a show is
like what a beautiful one and it
was the first time i believe well
i think i'd seen boyzone yeah i
don't know what they look like i
don't know what you're talking about oh
it's ah i mean it's a man
yeah yeah but it's a mad baby
you are like i'm
when tell us about the last time
you said that it was just about
two seconds ago okay and you're like
huh so coming now have been coming
the entire time fucking problem you need
to go to the doctor what just
because i constantly come all day and
all night
would be a blessing recurse i'd go
with curse yeah but if you couldn't
come
like you never had it would be
cool to do it
would be cool to do it i
can't argue with that okay okay alright
okay alright paul why are you looking
at your watch i'm looking for the
date dear why why why are you
promoting the outlaws on your on your
paper here ah because the last ah
cbc episode i did ah was with
adam devine nice it was
for the strike and we talked about
the outlaws amazing and you were invited
and you said fuck no oh right
yep because you were gone i was
yeah all of your trout do you
wanna tell me more about your travel
leases i went don't just name the
city i went for no i i
really enjoyed new buffalo it's really q
it's like a little beach town
down in michigan on the lake and
we actually got air bnb that accessed
a private beach um book which was
so great because i was willing to
strip your clothes off and it wasn't
that private oh um ever all the
houses connected to the speech but this
one was across the street but we
got access to it oh and um
well like a key car
or what you had to bring a
little flag down just to show that
you lasting approval to be there and
it was a don't tread on me
yep
confederate flag like dad's diyala and we
had to wave it proudly um what
with my brother and his wife and
kids and then mike and holly and
we had it was just like there
i think
it was a great time and we
holly loves the water so much yeah
it's nice she loves to go a
little why do you have it at
your house water yeah we have some
yeah she has a little kitty pool
she really enjoys yeah um but it
was lost and then you know yeah
we came back we celebrated holidays second
that's right i was there on
chilly miss i know it was so
sad to miss it we had a
petting zoo with bunnies and guinea pig
we met the kids loved it was
so sweet yeah it was really very
cute however when all the little kids
were like quiet and gentle with the
animals i don't think emmy would appreciate
i don't know she she might have
been like wanting to touch them or
some change i think she'd be
curious yeah i don't know i think
she would just look at it is
like oh another dog totally yeah i
have gotten to the point and this
i'm not sad about you can tell
the rabbits are yeah for a while
i was like that's not what is
it and then somebody would say it
is and then sometimes i'd say there's
one and people like no
um i've gotten my instagram search page
to the point where it is all
dogs and babies wow gray i mean
specifically dogs and babies interacting wow it's
the wow my click on one easter
bean looking motherfucker
and we talked about this and let
it all go downhill you know the
mr bean looking guy i talked about
it like literally two episodes i know
wheatley familiar there's the italian yesterday yeah
yeah i clicked on one of his
videos to say what's mr bean up
to and now that's all i get
my sky now my page is a
lot of like yeah people with
tons of injections and fish face plastic
surgery looking you get a lot of
looking like influencers a lot of people
spoiling magic tricks like showing you how
do i don't even look at my
ex point because the mr bean guy
i don't go to that page they
decline is india it's your hand it
wasn't in the year wow everything is
basically just like
oh yeah it's it's in some it's
in a hand she's just hiding it
yeah yeah yeah yeah every magic trick
in the world is just ok other
hiding pretty much yeah i want to
learn a magic trick because then you
can become a member of the magic
castle joining with one dragon i knew
one trick and money okay wow
oh i know one great one what
was yours
i mean i could still do a
stripped down version of it but i
knew a really scary blue and and
you do don't do that please don't
i mean that is that's hard magic
to pull off you're completely nude yeah
you can still do a trick pretty
much like i guess it's up his
ass yes the one that's amazing yeah
yeah yeah but love
gosh azar shay how can we talk
so good for all the saga oh
no we've completely fooled
so you learn one trick that you
pay a fee how my buddies who
do you show the trick to
tv you to top magician yeah yeah
top top top hat magician i'm sure
it's like three bored people
b or d or b o a
r both and i'm sure they're not
magicians they're just people that are you
know approving his books or whatever yeah
that's always a fun place to go
though it is um what about those
magic tricks where you know this is
when i've always kinda wondered about where
like somebody's getting information okay
so he's okay i saw where it
was where it was i don't know
maybe it was penn and teller maybe
it was like that
there's color was one word teller couldn't
pin can talk that was the past
i'll never forget it was so amazing
the one person who couldn't speak couldn't
get words i was like this is
so high i loved high stakes wonderful
entertainer saw their show until yeah they
actually have a masterclass on doing magic
my friend was watching ripley's house sitting
turn on the tv and saw that
it would been left on by my
friend i got a master just like
so you're staying busy while you were
here
wow my friend who was house-sitting was
watching so you're staying busy while you're
learning to paul learning magic tricks on
my couch ah making my couch disappear
you know i'm a devout your ass
and that is black satanism man
so you're always a trick no i
don't know if it's from penn and
teller ios from another magician but basically
they they seal an envelope like a
big envelope with like paper and they
write something on it and they seal
it and then they talk to the
person and the person says all these
things bubble butt and then they open
the envelope and what's written on the
paper i'm like how does that happen
yeah
that kind of that kind of stuff
really throws me for a loop yeah
yeah yeah i saw a really good
broadway show right before kovind ah what's
his name daren brown oh darrin brown
it was great is he let me
see are you looking yeah he's bald
oh shit
not interested
if he's magic wanting to make himself
heavier wow it's not magic is mentalism
oh well that's why he's bald yeah
because of the following so yeah what
yes see because i gotta get outta
here off he burned all the hair
out with his mental powers yeah ah
yeah it was a really impressive show
that's no shiva mentalist yeah
um he would solve crimes every show
essentially yeah every broadway performance someone would
murder someone at the top if you're
gonna murder someone please bring it to
broadway so i think i solved the
crime for show
um i do love stuff like that
in penn and teller i like going
to the magic how much do you
have to pay because i know one
trick i don't know how much you
have to pay i don't know how
much we also don't know if that's
correct this i feel is what i've
heard a long time ago i thought
you had to be like a certified
magician know okay because like gary carey
gary k
gary gary mary's in there and he
doesn't know anything he's fucking dumb shit
he's not certified by ruined information gary
carey grant was a member of the
match oh but he was also incredibly
famous yes they want him to be
there yeah they will learn one trick
so it's the cary grant sliding scale
if your cary grant
one trick if you or anyone else
fuckin have a shoot i know someone
who's a member yeah either who is
not none no no no you've a
pi also easy but ah somebody who's
not a magician who's a musician maybe
they got confused oh that's probably a
yup but he did a magic trick
and he paid the fee much as
this fee
i don't know it's gotta be oh
man i've ever heard about that how
much money that club thirty three is
in disneyland oh yeah so much so
isn't it like is it fifty thousand
a year it's something fucking already twenty
five thousand or something like somewhere around
there and it's yearly it can't be
worth oh no no no no i
have a friend who was there and
it's like oh yeah that's
just kinda just because there you can
have drinks there yeah and it's secret
initiation fee of thirty three thousand twenty
five thousand up front member and ten
thousand each year after discussing it says
it's now open to the public but
i'm like well but i definitely know
why isn't the way it's everyone's hand
i mean not everyone who would do
that what does that mean it's open
to the public i don't know they
chain mouse
a trap news says club thirty minutes
yeah knows now is open to the
public i think he will now line
up especially now they just run off
goofy from mousetrap
i mean especially now that you can
basically walk out of disneyland go to
downtown so i just got a draft
right that's right we took holly for
two nights and it was so fun
days we didn't go at all we
just didn't one day we wake her
up we didn't one day at the
park you know she's only two so
one day in the park with holly
yeah but the fun was thirty sunday
in iraq majority i liked it the
fun was we got the hotel so
we could sleep over and then be
the first people in the park where
she gets up early yes and then
we know going to tell you we're
in take a nap and secret info
yeah i know but i do feel
there
i had had some complaints i imagine
yeah the other ones better now i
know um but so we went to
the we went to disneyland first thing
and she was so excited and it
was so great because when you get
in really early there was nobody i
mean it was like it was sad
i felt busy but then once everyone
just goes down oh no you're the
hunted man wow we were at toontown
which they revamped oh good i have
to see it run around it's really
good for little kids so you'll take
me there eventually and she'll really love
it because like they made play spaces
i'll show her pictures okay well i'll
take her i'll show how about then
i'll show a o tutto
um and it was really great and
then we went back to the hotel
and we chilled for five hours ny
during the ninety five degree heat we
like no one took a nap then
we went back out to california adventure
for the censorship did she feel like
because this is how i would have
felt as a kid like we're missing
prime disneyland time no she was totally
happy to be watching a movie she
loves monsters
there's more like yeah so but what
does she call it again because she
said oh mater mater said to me
saying it to him at the time
it was released the room
my favorite movie that's advanced well so
we went on this ride though there's
this new ride at toontown and it
was crazy so it's called mickey and
minnie's railroad runaway or something and runaway
railroad yeah thanks percent and we didn't
know anything about it i had read
on links i did some like toddler
research
which to be like so that was
a ride that was approved and then
i asked as we are going in
i was like is this okay for
her and they're like it's good for
everyone okay okay so we walk in
and there's this you i mean spot
spoilers about the ride if you care
about the kind of thing but we
walk into a room and there's no
i've i've i've i've ever met
there's a movie screen and so it's
kind of like oh is it not
arriving i was a little confused they
used to show the movie about it
they showed it a movie right up
black wasting beau willie and then there's
a crash on the screen and then
the screen pops it hasn't been jagged
crash hole through it and there's smoke
coming out so hello hollywood like smoke
coming out of it's crash hole yeah
hollywood looking at me like oh no
like what you've gotta get me out
of here so we pick up we
will oh no we're going inside this
you walk through the screen you're like
oh we're going in the movie interesting
and so i'm like already going is
this a bad idea then there's a
train that pulls up and she's like
train train and we had just been
on the train yeah there no party
and so she's like ix
cited and then so we get in
the train and it's just a bench
with like a bar that goes down
some already getting a little bit like
it's better be slow and like slow
and she's tiny
the cars immediately separate and start going
in different directions so mike and i
are looking into like oh my god
everything is blaring loud bright screens loudest
sounds in the world we squish together
to like hold her tightly in place
the car is going all over the
place it's crazy we were like panicking
we're looking into like oh my god
she's good
and then like there's a glaring sounds
it was kind of scary feeling to
me i couldn't even pay attention to
what the ride was because i was
looking at her covered her eyes lot
then like you go in the other
room and it's calming down and you're
in front of like clara the cow
dentist comes out but basically you're in
front of clara the cow who's like
that old timey thing right and you're
looking at a mirror at all patrician
appreciate
it being described that way and all
the cars turn and face the mirror
and they're going really slowly like she's
like one two three one two thick
coating ballet that's good that's okay it's
looking a little creepy but it's okay
and then she goes let's conca and
the the fuckin benches start like the
drawers are going crazy around the room
come on how he's like yeah and
we were freaking out
we often were like oh my god
it's overthink god and then it's the
only thing she can talk about she's
been talking about the social luck and
a half she's like train movie smoke
hole like she does is like every
word so this is my theory she's
obsessed same thing happened with when we
took our nephew when he was younger
and we took took him on the
goofy ride yeah
yeah and i'd read that was fine
for his age and it's it's basically
a roller coaster where your legs are
dangling that's pretty goofy and ah seemed
scary when right on right as it
started going he goes i want to
get off this is scary and yeah
and i was like we can't now
and i was yeah can you share
yeah twenty eight years
old in it and it was scaring
me and so we we get off
and he was like oh that was
bad and then about thirty seconds later
he was like i think we could
do it again yes like they like
being scared i think she really liked
it it was just so funny and
then another friend of ours their kid
at the same reaction she's about the
same because she was freaking out and
then like loved it wow
like she talks about it every day
wow yeah so i guess you gotta
go back every day yeah i mean
i was thinking i wonder what happens
when we take her back there will
probably be like a year but like
would she like it or not curious
or ashore member yeah or care yeah
maybe don't give a shit will she
stay lucky it was really fun and
we just spoiled her rot
and i had a great time that's
great well you raise your birthday yeah
of special should you do any star
wars shipped we walked through there for
a second but then you killed the
rookie
that wasn't gonna tell anyone i texted
you that cause i need your help
bearing
people don't know if you but it's
like an off menu kind of thing
you can have if you like well
i'm where i wanna kill one of
the cookies yeah oh like okay okay
i have i'm lucky burger after
know what it's a sentient being so
is a cow doesn't walk on two
legs though a big day big difference
what about horses about kangaroo meat horses
don't walk on two legs they get
up there say dan because they're fucking
freaked out by something did you ever
see that movie wild hearts can't be
broken and always kid oh we should
do that
god hasn't seen
yeah have fun
this woman is blind and does horse
diving yeah huh that's crazy that's what
it's about if i'm caught but that
was a thing and i'm like the
steel pier whatever atlantic city ah where
a horse would dive into a pool
it's awful not really die from lehigh
yeah yeah i watched that
and i was freaking out reading that
you know matt and trey from south
park that restaurant they bought yeah middle
of the country just like a mexican
place or something yeah yeah but they
it was this place that they would
all go to as kids um that
way because it has like crazy like
grottos are like weird yeah yeah fine
but but they were talking about this
this room where basically like when they
were growing up as kids
they bought the place and the people
came to inspect it and it was
these divers would dive into a very
shallow pool and the only way to
get out of it was swimming through
like a hole oh god and the
people and then there were elect electrical
equipment everywhere out of it yeah like
you could but for the show right
essentially you had you couldn't just pop
your
head up oh i would you had
to switch do that i do but
the way it was they were expecting
it and they and the inspectors were
like this is the most dangerous room
i've ever seen wow
um so they retro you know they
they retrofitted it to make it safe
like more libertarian yeah but ah no
it sounds really cool i would love
to go to it yeah whereas i
think it's the middle of the country
i'm gonna look this real america
matt stone trey parker restaurant casa bonita
in here we go like good yeah
sure colorado colorado of course colorado where
they grow right yeah yeah south park
takes place of course
of course it all makes sense where
kenny died yeah somebody killed kenny
somebody who did those bastards yeah
i guess i guess hopefully it was
on broadway oh my god um so
the mentalist could solve it we have
to take a break okay i know
you want to say something it's like
you're sure i'm going to save it
yep okay we'll be right back
and we're back and learn what would
you want to say um what did
i want to say it's not worth
it i'll save it for the next
episode okay it's not worth it i
will bring it to the next episode
yeah dude i don't know if people
know that we record these back to
back routinely yeah do not always do
back well
i don't i listen back because sometimes
i just make sure we didn't say
anything horrid meaning you ah actually i've
helped your ass quite a few oh
hello
that's not true um you tip you've
typically don't say horrible things yeah thank
you
last night we watched on television asteroid
city the west yes and oh yeah
i enjoyed it i feel like
ah he is he has settled into
a certain style of thing like a
almost a wes anderson style well but
i mean it used to be it's
it's cemented now it's not as people
like the performances are all kind of
uniform now um in a way that
they didn't use to be like yeah
like if you watched rushmore like bill
murray is doing a very interesting thing
yeah and really like schwarzman is doing
the most wes anderson he type stuff
everyone else is kind of lying and
now everyone's quiet nobody speaks above a
normal conversational tone you know i mean
no there's hardly any inflection but it's
you know there's a lot the
only one i really have not enjoyed
all the way through is the french
dispatch but other than that i never
saw that there like enjoyable you know
i mean it's like it looks it
always looks great it's fun to watch
something the auto beautiful yeah yeah and
there's an honest course there's always a
lot of funny moments and yeah the
you know people that you like to
see whenever anyway
in this movie these kids are playing
a game that i think is similar
to a thing we've done before but
you had to do was that hopscotch
yes i do that that's how you
make game people hated that when we
played it on the show i know
that's why i'm shipping closer to the
mix yeah i guess and your pebbles
should have been miked my pebble
as my fruity pebble yeah
if we do pebbles bit
it's nothing
looks like something right it sounds like
forty fifty dollars bid sunlight isn't like
saying your possessive free pebbles or you
are oh i like saying i like
your saying money i would yeah that's
better for the people but oh your
fruity pebbles it's like saying five by
five so what's that but i thought
for buffy the vampire flaw your square
okay oh you're pretty pillows baby that's
what faith like you're like it's all
good you free it's all good no
seven minutes all that and a bag
of chips square where it's five by
five years what does five by five
men from buffy if i just remember
it was raining like i'm good fine
yeah yeah yeah but with eighth the
vampire slayer which i didn't really get
into
that show
you know because you're a vampire you
are afraid like oh i couldn't watch
it because it would keep me up
yeah i didn't make any tv show
keeping you up if you watch ou
i was hanging in my casket um
you know i've realised when i if
i think i'm going to be cremated
okay oh cool sometimes funding by me
probably that's what i took that's a
battle which was like okay um we're
gonna pulverize you but if i were
to be buried i definitely want one
of those old-fashioned
like hyphens oh ah what well where
it's got the top that looks like
crip crip site yeah you want grips
to i want grips the grip to
somebody representing the six things i've worked
on over the course like
but you know those like the like
ah wild west yeah where that's going
nowhere it's like a hexagon yeah yeah
that's what i want yeah that april
in there i of course there's people
i think here's what i think i
think you're allowed to do that i
think what's going to have to happen
with with caskets and burials at discernment
wouldn't be bear
worried straight down i think you should
be standing and i think yeah they
should be horner's should be vertical because
because so many space running out of
space but no idea here's what i
mean and it makes the most sense
here's what sucks is that if we
are buried that way then when somebody
digs up your coffin all your bones
are gonna be in a pile down
to bottom as your clothes are just
going to be kind of pilot gravity
cool
a remedy still exists yes when you
open a coffin you want to see
skeleton skeleton laying there like bone tattered
clothes because the school would be on
top the feet bones beyond the bottom
that's how it's going to be on
top the people to be on the
bottom when people are exude for like
research or something or like for evidence
one yeah are the are we
looking at bones is always like we
look how long it takes her like
like a body to become three days
that's it in the in the shutout
well on yellowstone when rip had his
mother zoomed she was still kind of
had some skin cleaning tour when he
went to get her ah engagement ring
i think it takes a couple of
years
yeah but i'll look it up let's
see what's in the casket i assume
that takes on email so i also
want to throw up talking about this
to decompose kind of hit me in
a different way to see if insects
can be excluded a body will decompose
quite slowly because maggots are the most
voracious crash feeders yes that's why we
must exclude insects although unexposed
human body in optimum conditions can be
reduced to bone in ten days a
body that's our optimum conditions for an
exposed human body like sort of castaways
seen like sun tea a body they
there i go yeah a body this
buried one point two meters under the
ground retains most of it's tissue for
a year
so that's so crazy out in your
casket and smoke that's so three weeks
to several years for to completely nose
into a skill i guess i'll say
i would like to be cremated but
i would like you to be you
know would like to be a plaque
or headstone tombstone of some sort even
if i'm not having my data there
as my dad did he got cremated
and the
we put that fucking bowl in the
ground yeah what about an nfc
if if my like what's it called
gravestone nice fun trip said like how
like a tv screen and there was
like a moving image oh yea yeah
yeah that'd be great yeah but be
cool let me great who would change
the batteries the grave shift people you
know here's the thing that i've become
like the people i work the graveyard
i've had a career
i've become obsessed with this idea with
various things i would like to be
put in an urn or something because
i like the idea that eventually that's
going to pass into somebody else's hands
will have no fucking idea who i
am yeah but no it will make
them look you up and listen to
all your podcasts or not they'll just
be like i
i got this this this thing this
thing yeah they hope he interested at
all wait so but it makes me
laugh they play an asteroid city okay
you you have i think when you're
buried by the way you should do
whatever you want and it should be
when you want it should be legal
whatever you want done with your body
is legal because what are they gonna
do like prosecute you know you're dead
what if you want to dump in
a public pool great that that's ruined
the day for the people well so
you know fight me
you think it would be something and
i think you should leave i think
it might be a crime for who
though you're dead well i mean you
can't be prosecuted but whoever you instructed
way like that bernie style paul into
the pool and just like you will
be the louche yeah oh not peppery
ah have anyone make that yeah this
will be one percent of the pool
if it's just shaking like bernie's being
held up by joe biden and trump
and it's burning in the middle but
in the like moderation are you getting
the hat i don't know if you're
funny best friends yeah they spend so
much time on the campaign trail
together um okay so in this in
the movie they play this game these
kids play this game where you name
somebody starts to name a famous person
um and then you go around the
circle and everyone has to keep adding
a name that everyone has to repeat
the names that have been saying yeah
and add a name now i think
we played a game like it's like
a memory thing yes exactly exactly
and trip and i'm taking my this
am i this i might dismiss your
name every yeah yeah everyone's been saying
okay yeah yeah okay so it's a
simple game we can play okay i
would like we can decide maybe we
can have categories like if you want
to do characters than you you just
stick to that can we do it
where each name has to be start
with a letter that easier like alphabetical
alphabetical order you're not talking about the
sounds dangerously close to celebrity hunt oh
maybe
i love supplies
yeah let's play asteroids note i think
it's harder when it's random like zoo
random let's just see how we get
yeah before we get so should we
do a category um yeah let's do
let's do actors sure yeah living or
dead doesn't matter just a known person
yeah yeah okay would you like to
kick it off lauren yes
natalie portman and then i say natalie
portman and then add mine okay natalie
portman cary grant because great
natalie portman cary grant zach braff natalie
portman cary grant zach braff um ah
joan rivers some action sir well mean
i don't know why natalie portman cary
grant zach braff joan rivers melissa rivers
they she acted in that thing about
her mom okay natalie portman cary grant
zach braff joan rivers melissa rivers
and ah let's put on peter o'toole
natalie portman cary grant zach braff joan
rivers melissa rivers peter o'toole
laurence fishburne
okay
natalie portman cary grant zach braff joan
rivers melissa rivers peter o'toole laurence fishburne
john wilkes booth i don't know if
you guys do he was yeah
alright i know that no one else
knows that alright
natalie portman cary grant
joan rivers no
lmao your wow mount on my own
thing and your own a guitar
hoisted by his own picard
make it so
i don't know you just fucking said
natalie i don't know what you just
said as your name i'm gonna gotta
remember you gotta lean for key to
the gay natalie portman cary grant zach
braff joan rivers melissa rivers peter o'toole
laurence fishburne john wilkes booth
um gabrielle union
natalie portman cary grant zach braff joan
rivers melissa rivers peter o'toole laurence fishburne
john wilkes booth gabrielle union
jerry springer
natalie portman cary grant zach braff joan
rivers melissa rivers
peter o'toole lawrence fishburne john wilkes booth
gabrielle union jerry springer
oprah winfrey
okay here we go natalie portman cary
grant zach braff joan rivers melissa rivers
peter o'toole lawrence fishburne john wilkes booth
gabrielle union jerry springer
fuck who did you just say you
said yeah
i'm out i can't remember who you
just say when i do lauren windsor's
dash i do one more time lauren
was this round of asteroids see if
i can do it yeah okay yeah
natalie portman cary grant zach braff so
joan rivers melissa rivers john wilkes booth
pete nope tom rivers joan rivers managed
rivers peter o'toole laurence fishburne john wilkes
booth's
gabrielle union jerry springer oprah winfrey oh
brah why oprah there's a host who
also acted yeah and a little movie
called the color purple color people the
color of purple yes she great class
eddie elson
yep and she invented prince i always
recall she got the call she was
getting the part when she was on
the treadmill
yeah sorry look for the listener lawrence
said that and then looks down thoughtfully
she was remembering oh camera crew i
think it's true i mean i've heard
oprah's memories a lot um and steven
spielberg called her and yeah she was
how did she because this is before
cell phones how did she was there
i think the phone or landline low
so she stops treadmill we should we
i'm sure somebody else picked up the
phone and said oprah steven spielberg
yeah i held the phone up to
here yeah but at this point she
has a roommate right yeah she was
in college i think still doing the
show did she do the color purple
before the show or no she wasn't
she was a known quantity she was
already yes yes good for her good
for good she was huge at the
time like already very famous
yes yeah i know what you're talking
about i wasn't gonna make a joke
about that and i got scared and
you know knowing you what you know
me
you know me you know you don't
know me still the same old gee
but i've been lucky oh no oh
no oh should we play again with
a different category okay ah yeah we
should okay snorkel figures cheryl boy okay
you wanna start and let's go the
other way yes okay now alexandra hamilton
yeah oh the other way napoleon okay
alexander hamilton napoleon bonaparte alexander hamilton napoleon
bonaparte um ah harriet tubman
alexander hamilton napoleon bonaparte harriet tubman ah
john wilkes booth
alexander hamilton napoleon barnum bonaparte oh my
god i forty points a boner part
owner
thirteen is just a chef ah harriet
tubman john wilkes booth martin luther king
junior
alexander hamilton
bonaparte harriet tubman john wilkes booth martin
luther king junior john f kennedy junior
troops this article figure the j f
k g he said his violet isn't
a president a historical figures
the president is but not junior oh
junior i didn't mean that julia i
didn't mean that yeah i waited and
that doi made the dole saturday thinking
junior i said j f k junior
hey it was the same no i
didn't mean him i mean j f
k fair enough fair enough i think
they're both historical figures meaning that both
dead ones know that was a daisy
horvath vincent fusco
i write about that on this show
okay okay okay area
if you watch ah often hymer you'll
hear a little bit about his background
alright i'll probably have to watch that
at some point i watched a movie
called barbie which i loved
did you barb hymer hi barbara i'm
right right to play this and trying
to let you do it really about
trying there's been so many interruptions now
how can i remember i'm begging for
you to play the cool up barb
what did she barbel mentally what's mental
she saw elemental and barba same day
type elemental i know so things are
moving
oh it's sold for what events what
if the elements were ally oh my
god everything's gotta make me feel sad
including this game it's tough we're really
losing steam yeah we are i want
you to go alexander hamilton okay
napoleon bonaparte heard of him harriet tubman
yes been there done that john wilkes
booth that's what she said
martin luther king junior must be nice
john fitzgerald kennedy
god fitzgerald kennedy
ah lyndon baines johnson junior
um okay
alexander hamilton napoleon bonaparte harriet tubman
um and i don't care i don't
know i don't alexander hamilton napoleon bonaparte
harriet tubman john wilkes booth john wilkes
booth martin luther king junior john f
kennedy
let what did you just say lyndon
baines jaw i don't know no b
j o o o other president don't
look at me like i'm a horrible
person i don't think your horrible person
lyndon baines johnson yeah okay l b
j if i said lyndon johnson yes
yes okay bain threw me off because
i couldn't
the biggest though his whole thing but
i lost track of what was happening
when when baynes came out of your
mouth and i went i'll hear it
when scott says it and thinking of
the control of your game
you're the beam yeah bain to hell
do you think it was a big
argument when he did that voice of
christopher nolan was like what if it's
not quite that extreme and you like
having wow up in hymer i think
he hates his dialogue and wants no
one to hear it that's what i've
heard but i've heard these icons very
hard to hear it's very hard to
hear an oppenheimer he's embarrassed by it
so he like turns to music up
he's like script socks is this what
i wrote oh no it's crazy well
we had fun oh yeah that's how
you play that game and i won
that race he won both my lower
fifth i said it eventually but then
not by forfeit bad name and then
it got just help yeah yeah i
couldn't well i tried guys that was
fun
i dunno i couldn't really i just
we can't have anything nice why couldn't
i remember john wilkes booth i mean
i'm the one who knows he's an
actor he's on the five dollar bill
yeah on the back he seemed creeping
around
i've got killed it's a little ricky
around to the front
alright um thanks for listening if you
want to follow us on social media
it's at three am usa and if
you want to call us yeah if
you'd like to write to us suggest
three tr of your own um it's
like a game like that that we
can play oh three m usa gmail
dot com if you'd like to call
us leave us a voicemail it is
high ghg claims
eight and if you want to hear
ad-free episodes you can hear him at
cb world and if you wanna come
see my show it's august fourth dynasty
typewriter in los angeles or you can
live stream it from anywhere in the
world august the fourth mice yes for
this show are amazing i have arden
marine suzi barrett cornwell chelsea davon tez
and lauren ashley smith august fourth seventh
thirty pm tickets are fifteen bucks if
you wanna watch online and twenty bucks
live please get tickets and come you
can believe it i have a show
on late august nineteenth we also way
live scott hasn't seen where we're watching
the aba ah mamma mia here oh
yeah rowdy three nine podcast taping that's
a dynasty typewriter so if you're no
law comes here and look you know
me
yeah i have shows yeah august moji
august twenty six at a bad ah
the aladdin theater in portland sold out
um sorry to say but i'm looking
forward to that and then some jazz
show in september with nicole scott i
was just about to talk about really
i'm so excited sunday september tenth in
los angeles at la droom me
me and nicole parker we are doing
our first two person show it's going
to be variety show just the two
of us doing ah music and comedy
and characters and all kinds of shit
like that i'm really looking forward to
this exciting it's gonna be a lot
of fun because we'll do a countdown
at midnight to september eleventh
we're probably going to have ah nine
eleven cake at the end of the
show okay because i know a lot
of people are sacrificing their tradition yeah
i'd love any plans to come out
um and then of course the hours
will be okay i wish i hadn't
said it well hey sunk good you
can cut it out ah could will
won't
whoa yeah so there you go go
to politicians dot com slash lie from
my dates and chat and um until
we meet again just keep remembering everything
you've ever done i couldn't say it
better myself out right but i buck
uh