oh wow
boo
oh really
build on that welcome to three nah
i'm i'm di di um dough yeah
let's introduce ourselves why don't you start
o knives knives to grow
it's me paul f tompkins it's me
lauren lips and it's me sometimes scott
aquaman what does that mean sometimes sometimes
i mean sometimes on you sometimes do
you feel like
and sometimes i don't my my ic
stand is fucking i already in my
mind the almond joy commercial and the
chicken tonight commercial are very nice do
you like chicken tonight like chicken to
na eight
so daddy be like sometimes note um
and those guys mounds don't this is
the podcast where we sing a jingle
jingle why not not closer with big
so gears a little longer in your
last so that alone that's basically telling
you gum makes your breath smell yeah
good shit his while you're chewing gum
i'll make your breath smell good so
you never understood people chuka it's like
the only reason anyone would so choose
god you to guide shoe
gum ah for that reason i chew
gum because it tastes good or to
gum because i like to to something
let me smell those breaths ah your
buddy says you know what i'm not
a fan of gum anymore
breadth yeah need a bit of going
more like it did the masks have
really taken down the gum in her
paw i wonder if the gum ah
think it would make it better my
gum drawer is so stocked right now
because up here i beg your pardon
ma'am you're looking your what like gum
drawer
what is your gum driving gum drawer
are we talking like a dresser we
targeted like a desk it is it
is a dress it's a treasure chest
um no it's a small office as
the justices it's a small kitchen drawer
just a small small kitchen drawer you
hear some onsens just curious sure i've
got some drew twenty packs of gum
and
there
that's wow because typically i'm sure you
given him know i buy it in
bulk and i often chew gum when
i'm traveling to keep it in bulk
in the garage and then bring it
out like you know a package holidays
big bring it out back into their
tiny attention everyone i'm bringing it back
no but i'm just
i'll draw what else could you put
in that drawer this wasn't a stack
of ten twenty dollar bills do you
not have what you know you know
just don't tell my twenty dollar bill
whenever you ever had ten twenty dollar
bills i believe in carry cash
don't you think hey i was just
hearing somebody talk about this on something
um great start to my story but
that tree
your sources roaring cash is a is
something that men are encouraged to to
do now i feel that i kind
of ah i agree that mentioned carry
cash but i think everyone should carry
cash why men i mean there's i
guess they're saying it in the sense
of from what i was listening to
is like sort of an outdated thing
of like
when you're on a date you gotta
have cash because what if there's a
valet or there's a thing they don't
take a card or there's a list
about you've gotta be prepared yeah and
oh i know what it was was
on i said no gifts and um
the guy was talking about the guests
was talking about how his mom always
made him carry cash and so when
he lived on the show he gave
bridger the premise this shows you're not
supposed to bring your spring if you
give him cash
which i think is funny yeah but
the whole thing is were you ever
encouraged growing up like you better have
some cat you should always have twenty
you know i tried it i'm not
talking about lots of money no i
yeah stuff like that does come up
so i try to have at least
two thousand dollars on me oh yeah
let's never see me on the street
i wanna buy some art i'm a
big fan of having one hundred dollars
in your wallet if you yeah but
that also comes from
many years of having no money and
then being like i would be very
aware of every dollar yeah and then
so i once i was able to
have one hundred dollars i felt like
that's makes me feel like i'm like
prepared and we talked about the gym
and in santa maria that that gave
out ten dollars instead of you told
me about that oh it was the
greatest we found
one atm because sometimes you would just
have twelve dollars in your account and
you'd be like fuck i can't access
it because i can't put another eight
dollars in my account because i don't
have a dollars but i've ten dollars
just sitting there and i can't i
can't eat so like we found one
atm that that would give you ten
dollars i think it was still like
a two dollar charge on the eighty
sucks that would piss me yeah but
still it was good because you could
get that last ten dollars before you
got paid again um and it was
it was the greatest yeah
it's thrill it's a thrill anyway i
encourage everyone to carry at least five
dollars five five for one though like
what would five dollars get you out
just comforting i mean if you're going
to carry cash you need twenty twenty
yeah but if you don't have twenty
shift
i don't argue with that i had
a friend who loves you so know
what's gonna come up i had a
friend who loved five dollar bills yeah
sure he i love them right here
no moustache he wore this really cool
hat
he felt like that was the most
um adaptable form of conversion a lot
of stuff you know it's a great
tip so he hated when he would
get change with twenties he would always
ask for fives instead and if he
ever got that jesus if he ever
got fives instead of a twenty of
like someone were to go
give him fives he would always brag
about it he would come and go
guess what happened to me at the
bank today and he would brag about
and then he would open up his
wife thought i was gonna be like
then he would give the person five
dollars no no he just loved having
other problems did he have and then
he ah was what was what was
this eventual diagnosis
then he would open up his wallet
and show it to me sometimes and
there would be like ten fives in
there and he'd go i'm packing
wow
davao don't know the person is you
you've met him okay we told me
off yeah well okay yeah i'm i'm
adam no i know i've met i
just know but ah question but ah
just know you know but he also
he he laid into the humorous aspect
of it it wasn't no no that's
funny well as a cover sure yes
i know but
thank you it's like fives rolling around
a bed of five five five
like a batman villain was just like
his his home it's covered with fives
and indecent proposal
and also during coven i will say
i feel and by the way someone
pointed out that we say i will
say and i thought i don't say
that i've said so many times i
think i'd probably like imo no i
say it all the time i had
no clue until i never noticed i've
never listened to any of these backs
so i don't know back but i
just feel like i do from time
to time i had to recently for
a different reason oh
grumble grumble but anyway um i was
going to say that coven i find
there a lot of places are not
taking cash because they don't want to
touch the oh yeah yes but that
that is bad for society when everything
becomes cashless because everyone said well there
was a whole coin shortage during the
covert right that's right i forgot like
we need the coin
rns and it was like this is
weird needless your nickel alias jojo roy
needs to put coins back in
did did you guys can i tell
you just got there i thought i
started first i think you did i
know but that's how you like you
just shush me do you know what
show your ah i take we say
fucking love that coin star i start
to buy love a coin show
satisfying i love points to a percentage
yeah they do take a small you
gotta dip to be out
a beak i say you know what
i'll find out okay oh and by
the way this brings me to another
thing i want to tell you guys
oh never got to take seventy oh
yeah you never
um i recently tweeted a joke about
venmo about how because what i don't
understand is that people will have their
venmo things public and you can see
what you're doing yeah so i just
i hate that aspect it's like oh
yeah why would anyone want that remember
when i tuned you are doing remember
when itunes was
like twenty point nine percent coin store
wasn't pointing nice that's you gonna have
a lot of coins to make that
make remember when itunes was trying to
get into social media and they were
like trying to turn like people would
post stuff on itunes about music they're
like it's going to be music-based social
media but then i found out anything
you buy suddenly gets posted to your
profile that's
dislike my god and so i bought
this like shitty pop song once and
it was the first thing that came
up on my profile and everyone's like
yeah that's rude well i just wanna
say that venmo reached out to me
and they wanted to use my tweet
in there was you know both that
and i said yeah is there compensation
i idea i'm there and i said
is there compensation
and because i thought nothing could be
easier than them venmo owing twenty dollars
yeah he's my tweet then they go
back we'll send you a fun surprise
if we use your tweet i was
like oh so it's not money but
what the fuck are you going to
send me i know i could venmo
huh hats i kind of wanna know
like i'm like if it's venmo t-shirt
i don't want that it's oh fingerless
gloves
if it's like just something cool like
i might want like a speaker i
want it i doubt the angle sending
speakers to people for tweets speakers retweets
i just want to know what it
is but i don't want to do
the i don't want to give them
my tweet yeah you're a person you
don't need to be advertising preventive i
don't want to do that i want
them to pay venmo more like fuck
no
ah well it's been mo not venmo
fuck you pay me venmo more like
van less that's my samantha it doesn't
mean anything sexually what about bevo bevo
um what about more like what bev
mo ma like bev me
yeah i said my boss
what was your critique of venmo more
like fuck no
it not you are gonna critique it
well i said it's been mo not
venmo yeah i never said it was
then no you guys rhyme it's still
was a fun thing all loud fun
reason it made me sad reasons
reciting this podcast is because one day
i want you guys to brawl and
phone's like on dynasty
i don't think we were talking about
data zoe works lawrence said she got
checks her dynasty and scott for a
second thought that she was on the
nighttime soap like lorne on dynasty and
i never shies j ah jail
like jay less
no it's not jay moore jane
buying a shame horror
good run guys did okay so this
is what i want to ask when
when the pandemic was first announced are
we supposed to stay home i remember
i was against it when they said
there's gonna be a pandemic i was
like let's let's go should i voted
no to um but there there was
a there was a saturday
i remember it where the rumor got
around that banks were going to stop
giving out cash that banks were gonna
run out of money ah and so
and they were like go to several
different banks and just take out you
know as much as the atm can
then give you until your ah like
so
pandemic mean that computers are going to
go down and you'll realize i think
they were saying there was a run
there is like an it's a wonderful
life where there's a run on the
battery where people everyone's gonna want to
withdraw all of them i was so
stress and so they're not of it's
a wonderful yeah
does the summer where he committed suicide
was a little more stressful didn't die
he tried yeah well i'm spoiler alert
of course ah but ah first twenty
minutes so cool x-ray an hour in
the movies it's a long movie go
up and i went around to like
every atm we could find it meanwhile
we aren't wearing gloves and we're
trying not to to to touch our
hands to our faces just like drawing
money out and of course nothing ever
happened with it well it yeah yeah
funny here's what i what i don't
get about it is okay so the
the the the panic part is the
banks are gonna stop issuing cash they're
not going to give you cash anymore
so get all the cash that you
can
can but then if if they're not
issuing if they're not giving cash because
i only have so much the only
have so much in the bank right
so why do you know where you're
going to be using cash because they
were saying that things were going to
get so bad with the pandemic that
no one would accept credit cards or
checks or whatever like cash was going
to be the only currency so the
banks are saying
we're not going to issue we're not
going to issue cash because it's a
it's a it's a a touch thing
because it's a thing that you touch
no no no the banks they don't
have the rumor was because they don't
have everyone was you won't be able
to use a credit card anymore you'll
have to use cash everywhere at the
bank goes we don't really have that
much cash and i was like did
i get online before everyone else can
get scared much dancing
okay so it starts with the story
starts with we think down the line
you're gonna need to have cash because
the economic the economics of america are
going to collect right right so at
a certain point the pandemic is gonna
get that bad but you better get
cash now because the banks aren't getting
when i get out of this i
gotta know it sounded i guess i
was confused because it sounded like it
started with the banks are gonna stop
giving cash right right right um but
also like we were
we're practically cashless now like why would
it i don't understand how that the
pandemic would affect what it was i
mean when it first started we went
to the the the the mayfair or
whatever it's called gal yeltsin's and nothing
was called mayfair it was called mayfair
for a long time the one i
used tb but i just shouldn't have
where you've only known it as girls
but i want to get hyper specific
i want to where your brain just
went to in the past that you
just called it mayfair it was called
that one that that specific one i
called mayfair for the longest it it
was mayfair for so long that it's
just hard for me to call okay
yes there's a dominick's
dominic's is the chicago version of gelson
right and it sounds like it's also
the christmas donkey chancel what did break
hey they treat from the main issue
in the mariano's and from the major
ma what did he do ah he
was just there that's it he gets
a name joseph passer bys in italian
he's an italian italian christmas donkey yes
when he came over ah yeah he's
italian okay he speaks it i think
he guided he guided santa's sleigh over
the alps or something like that i
will get so good so and i
just gently say he did do a
thing san is like i can't get
over these mountains and then
in dominick's like this is my thing
he was sure this is my little
drummer boys an emotional christmas song yeah
i can see that alright do you
know what else do you hear what
i hear that one makes me cry
well month is i have no clue
well we get to do anything
disneyland opens april thirtieth now are you
going to vote no no no no
no but i like them but i
would love to go is no law
i would love to go when i
feel fucked is yes land
i like to go with my whole
family yeah but you're not going to
do that no fucking way
well yeah there's ah i would not
feel like i was having a good
time i need to be anybody very
i have to say they've they've had
a year off if i ever go
to disneyland in the next five years
and they've shut down a ride for
construction do that when the pandemics happened
fucking anyway man their shit better be
tight
it's like when we went to the
christmas light thing at ah i will
just open it up again and it
was so like pathetic glittering how long
everything had been closed lauren you weren't
there you can't call a couple of
videos we call it ah i could
not believe how
just sad it was yeah there were
a couple like kind of ones they
put real effort into but most of
it was just like this is jenny
go hey hey man you had since
march to figure out what you're going
to do for christmas i don't know
if you really thought you'd be open
by then you should have seemed like
an act of desperation on their part
they're like we need five dollars i'm
gonna say election
like july they should have been thinking
this is what we're gonna do what
because it is a big park but
they had you on a very specific
path i know going all over the
world how i felt about it there
they figured on your head i want
i want your feelings about carrying a
car just because you're gonna car i
felt like they figured out a route
that would work for cars first
and it was the only route that
would work they couldn't shorten it and
then they were like fuck this is
too big we can't can't dilate we
can't fill it well we'll do what
we can and so certain it was
patchy certain parts of it were kind
of impressive but as a whole it's
like if you're going if you're traveling
that whole route you want shit the
whole time let me tell you that
let me tell you if that's if
that's what happened they should put we
did what we could on the ticket
yeah as a mountain we did what
we could i saw a handful of
those things on people's instagram like there
was one of people driving through umm
i'd sort of jurassic park like dinosaur
thing at one of those places and
so they had these like animatronic dinosaurs
but it just looked like really not
exciting especially because it was open during
the day as well as the
night and the person i saw was
going through it during the day but
you have to understand this is just
wrong this is twenty twenty we had
nothing to do back then and we
were happy for it i don't think
that's like chris harrison being like it
was twenty eighteen and to think things
change what happened to him oh no
vaccines go he's all right what
it went raw i could tell you
so he what happened was our reality
recap yeah actually yeah which we never
sorry it took so long to get
to it okay we usually do it
impulse really bored josh insert the jingle
reality recap yeah alright take that and
remix it
anyone
um so what happened was there was
ah bachelor recently matt james who is
a black man he was dating many
women as they do on the bachelor
narrowed it down guys doing the bachelor
narrowed it down to two women um
now as we know from understanding the
time links
this came out before we knew who
was gonna make it to the final
two there was a woman rachel who
was pictures of her came out that
she attended an antebellum party and develop
themed party dressed as sort of a
in the period then bad southern belle
but like slave owner yeah the fashion
yes and i never heard of this
party
i don't know what this is i
never heard of this party but it's
kind of important to me to pose
but i've never even heard of this
because so then what happens is we
don't know who's gonna get to the
bottom two but we started you know
i think the fans start to assume
rachel's going towards the end because it's
becoming a huge deal that this happened
and rachel lindsay who is an ex
batch
claret or contestant who what she was
she was the bachelor right yeah she
was the bachelor right yeah she has
a rate she has a show a
podcast about the bachelor which is like
bachelor branded and so she was interviewing
chris harrison about it and chris harrison
got very defensive as she's a black
woman by the way so yeah kind
of weird for him to be even
arguing against enemies like this i'm not
i don't
ah woke cancel culture he woke police
like forty times in his interview yeah
and then he also said oh rachel
the show twenty eight to twenty things
are different than me
wow fifty million people attended the antebellum
party that year what are you talking
about fifty million people do that i've
never even heard of millions of dollars
in thai but there are where are
you getting this number it is i
there's no way that numbers saying but
it is like still a popular thing
in the south and it bums me
out yeah
you know because i like stopped i
feel like this brought a lot of
light to it i didn't really know
but it's interesting because i think growing
up like it's insane to me that
the dukes of hazzard had the confederate
flag yeah car and and i think
as a kid like okay so i
basically didn't even really i'd heard of
slaves
until i was and so i knew
that slavery was a thing and it
was bad but i didn't really know
until i was what until i was
twelve and oh okay and my history
teacher showed us roots and then it
was like oh fuck did that really
happen though okay so like sud for
a little kid but suddenly i'm i'm
seeing that but it's like the confederate
flag growing up
if it just meant the south to
me you know do yeah absolutely i
didn't have it didn't have any connotation
to me other than that because i
didn't understand the civil war yeah you
know so and i think i think
things like the antebellum party and the
and and the confederate flag have just
like been programmed in us to be
fine ever since we were kids and
not understand
ending it so it's like a blind
spot for people yeah people let it
go for so long and it was
just like a cool design yeah just
for the record rachel did release a
statement which was like a pretty good
apology i thought but then on the
after the final rose she had to
sit with matt and they'd broken up
shits she won she was chosen at
the end wow she was the chosen
one um he and propose because he
got cold feet about proposed by the
way was this store still in reality
reality recap
don't pick someone to be the bachelor
who says they've never been in love
before serious relationship do like past people
who are twenty four to get married
yes yes give me people like us
give me thirty give me thirty and
above for the show peer yes i
need there to be some you have
some experience and you know what you're
looking for a new hour
ready to send me i'm a hot
milf please we've had that no babies
once yeah maybe once we've had a
delf i think but yeah couple knows
but it's just so much she says
she said this on their roads and
and talk to him and it was
very painful for everyone involved what does
alf alien i'd like to fuck um
yeah
raw from the muppets
ah rude guy rude ah what was
right he was a dog he's a
dog oh he's a delph yeah he's
a good dog yeah yeah you gotta
be careful
he's not ralph itself behavioral jewish for
the monkey paw the figure girls they
set up ah really wants to talk
about it thanks to but we haven't
gotten talk about it this has an
ex two bachelorettes oh yeah the cast
them they don't usually do that the
cast to and advance from this season
by the way i feel like they
cast the white girl and then they
were like
oh shit all this went dancing exactly
what i thought it seemed like but
but i've by the way i like
the other one michelle's fantastic she's so
she he should have picked her oh
she's great i think i sort of
like i feel like yes the system
is fucked up that it's six weeks
or you know however long and then
they have to get engaged but you
know that's what it is going in
so everyone should be everyone should
be primed as a fucking pump to
get engaged yeah like everyone should be
at the end of their she was
ready and that's what kind of killed
me proceed he was a perfect ah
she's ready person for the show she
was like totally mannish suis teacher nice
normal seemed ready for marriage yeah she
let rachel
was the younger immature dumb shit who's
like obviously going to date around and
have twenty more boyfriends we share and
share the real one the wing racist
i'd like to yeah i just couldn't
but anyway so they cast these two
girls to be the next two bachelorettes
but then there's gonna be a bachelor
between them so it was like that's
why it seemed like yes this is
redemption
why that's my fantasy to bachelor that's
an ambassador between that's why it seemed
like it was a sort of like
trying to fix something because they don't
usually announce them multiple seasons in advance
right how about this this is my
this is my re still in reality
so to recap and this is me
it should ah that the bachelors should
not be about getting married but it
should be about having sex yeah and
so try a sexist that's what happens
because then you're not putting pressure on
somebody to getting gauged but it's like
now we're going to have said yes
finally i pick one person to have
sex yes
x that's going went on i got
it i want to know more about
the fantasy suites um also i love
the show meredith but you've got to
know because when like you would like
to know but also the i watch
married at first sight which is a
fantastic program so firmly within reality rica
have i talked to you about this
now you can if i say yes
about ninety days yeah i would like
to just say one thing about it
okay it's a great show one sense
oh wow it's it's a couples that
have now they get they meet at
the altar they've never met they are
paired up by matchmakers and psychologists and
they walked on the island our wedding
day to meet the person that they
are married to and they have eight
weeks
where they're married and then at the
end they decide if they want to
get divorced or stay together can be
an enrollment um it's probably technically an
enrollment because it's only eight weeks so
i'd rather be in no i want
it for them to be in an
element too because sometimes it goes so
fucking awry that it's like socks if
that's like considered your first light i'm
not a huge well i think it
depends on where you are in your
life
but i think some people can be
like i knew within the first couple
of weeks and we got married three
months and i think that's okay sometimes
especially if like both of the people
yeah or in the at at the
time of their life where they're just
like i really am day with dating
ah the time of their law is
whether
a daily and they knew that is
ah
they were tired of carrying twenties all
around i ty buys that song by
the way i've come around i hated
it when it came out i've come
around on liking it now i don't
like the sound of it
oh no i don't like their voices
together and i don't like the random
man and the dazzle sounds like right
this other hey i like a righteous
brothers like finally coming out of the
shadow of his own brother and being
with someone else the property really should
do that yeah the property brothers and
the righteous brothers should team up one
rather a piece righteous yeah brother the
righteous property brothers and they and one
of them gets to do a reality
show and the other half to do
pop music the property brothers have four
thousand programs i'm now learning that we've
taken a hard left turn back into
reality every we're almost out of music
criticism discovery plus
i gotta talk about it again they
are not paying me or send me
a surprise yes say oh yeah everyone
every other show ever and there's like
a thousand i mean it's great good
for them fuck you who would you
like to send you a fun surprise
and then we'll we'll go around the
room okay oh wow i mean pretty
much any thing that's worth something i
guess
yes like gucci gucci gucci care about
round i mean let me rephrase it
whom would you not expect to send
you a fun surprise that you would
like to get a fun surprise from
a guy not venmo but a company
that's not known for sending funds to
crocs crocs crocs why are you not
sponsoring us crack rocks trucks i swear
to your notice crocs i sort of
crocs we've done every
i swear to crock she amount of
people who said they bought crocs because
of what because of what we've said
yeah on this incredible submission queuing queuing
drop our our news i don't know
if we can drop pi common judgment
kind of if we yes yeah okay
so if you hear a big long
beep right now josh cup this and
blame him didn't cut it he just
believed it and you
it's him saying glee for as long
as we owe it as we have
coming soon crack three threesome jib
a you can put on your own
cry
kids really get hard dumb faces you
have the pretzel that says the pretzel
gang you have a helicopter that says
he's just looking for someone we have
aig na j famous catch russians swedes
i could've used to say yeah i
didn't choose to use it and that's
the thing about ignored you can choose
choose to use or use to lose
it
and what else that's really okay take
a breath josh if you understand was
another without crocodile crew you know every
once in a while yeah i'll work
for a like a an award show
are you saying that
but they they they always want to
give you a gift back on this
time yes there they always want to
give you a gift after and they
always call up your manager and say
like what is what do they want
whoa and it's ah i didn't know
they did that i got a purse
one from somebody i actually never knew
who thinks i feel like it would
be easier for for me if if
like meh
when nerd or i were a person
that had purses or yeah like numbers
like i think i've got company i
worked for sent me a purse right
yeah but it's always nice can we
send you in an i-pad and it's
always like well i have i already
have an ipad or i'd never know
god so they're like just does he
like exp
pensive champagne i don't want i don't
want expensive ciency reliable chat i'm sorry
but it's people he doesn't want the
ipad how about expensive champagne
that's why i'm bringing it up because
it's got to a point where i'm
like i don't know what you can
send me who would you like a
cartoon bag of money with a dollar
sign no money would be great sure
money just pay me what that's that's
my point just paying new belts fuck
you pay me
i feel like but i should start
keeping track of like if i had
to because every once in while i'll
be like fuck i don't have any
shoes
yeah don't have any shoes here you
know i don't have any shots anymore
yeah you know what i mean it's
like i should be keeping track of
stuff like that i don't really like
champagne but the times that i've had
expensive champagne which is not that often
but everyone's so all you know you
get somebody giving you a fancy bottle
or something it's so much better i
want yeah i feel like same way
headaches but yeah this is relatable yeah
well no i want i don't buy
it i'm like i'm not out there
buying a bottle gone everywhere and yeah
i've never bought it a bottle of
champagne but we have like twenty five
hours sent to us yes and cool
up did that thing where she scans
them there's an app that can scan
and tell you if it's expensive or
not and like
ten of them are extremely expensive and
when you like deal with that you
just never drink it because they're too
expensive we just save it you know
we had we had a bottle after
we had a bottle of fancy champagne
that sat in her fridge for ages
for that reason we're like we have
to wait for a special occasion and
it's like we moved house with it
like had i've done
carrying around ya and i think we
finally opened it like after the election
yeah yeah this is this is a
good experience yeah we did one of
our expensive ones on the the day
that it was finally called yeah the
ah the landscaping yeah
if cool i finally was like we're
busting out the goods yeah fitna we
just like you oh i never like
champagne and and i went to a
fancy dinner party one time where the
the hostess was a champagne person and
served dom perignon and i was like
oh i get this literally i get
why this is magic i didn't get
ahead
yeah it was fun i had a
fun drunk oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
but that's not so champagne companies weren't
you sponsoring a champagne companies look how
great we talk about you always want
free thing it'll champagne mow edge by
the way i appreciate when people send
me free things i'm not saying that
i there's nothing that i would accept
it's just like
ike hard when they the onus becomes
on you like if people were to
send me an ipad engraved with the
show or whatever on the back like
i've seen some people have um i
would be like fucking awesome thank you
but i just like when it's only
one on me to me like something
you already have if you're giving me
a gift give me a true gift
i don't want to choose my gift
right it's gonna blow up on this
i want a rim and put a
ring on it would give me a
ring
i've been waiting honestly if someone if
someone were to give me like a
gold bracelet
great i never learned gold harness it
in my life that would be so
weird if i which i like a
gold bracelet well i have to say
i want jewelry not i will say
but i have to love jewelry companies
hey companies pay venmo give me a
ring klopp's friends sister started
ed selling gold chains and all of
her friends have started wearing gold things
like necklaces like and so it's became
like a trend for her or for
her friends it reminds me when i
was nineteen and i were suits and
ties every day and with simpkins then
everyone everyone in my social
circle like it expanded to where like
everyone was because it was that's never
happened to me yeah no it it
suddenly became rocked everyone in our dropbox
and san romero drama program like every
guy started wearing suits and ties and
la and long trench coats that was
it was long trench coats and let's
like dress you know dress like oh
yes i will lose the winter as
well
but it reminds me of that we're
like suddenly every single one of co-op's
friends is wearing like this kind of
like it to me it looks like
new jersey gold chain you guys girl
she asked me if i wanted one
picture of i don't know i don't
or the unisex yeah their units yeah
oh no she does not wear one
thank you
yes nice i check in that i
got in trouble sorry you've been out
voting for you but i feel like
it's all because the sister is selling
them and people want to support yeah
yeah yeah that's exactly what it is
yeah it's more than a few gold
chains are in like i mean like
in terms of layering jewelry like let's
sell freedom gold chains okay
how much does a gold chain i've
no idea what have we like those
name necklaces like a carrie bradshaw oh
yeah do this threesome and courtesy freedom
let's sell those how much are they
will sell them for fifty it would
be fifty dollars let's make them super
expensive okay that's because there'll be one
person who wants one get a thousand
miles simone we're looking at martin shkreli
he'll buy one i want um
how is sending someone else we know
on twitter who listens to the show
while gayle is the only person i
know who ah seems to not know
what the show scale the slow can
you remind me what her because she
say she listened to it on the
tweet yes she's a big fat gale
hello gail simone whoa kano reiner extraordinary
air a wonderful person
or illustrator yes that's nice they have
nothing to do but while they sit
there grinding it out but um being
stained wretches
i'll remind you off air anyway we
need to take a break okay
and we're back yeah we are ah
lauren can i ask you a i
guess it's a show biz related question
okay and you can say i don't
want to talk about it and then
joshua will have to do a long
long beach okay what are the oscars
things helped me get there you were
we're nominated for something oh yeah this
last week and i didn't when i
saw it oh boy here we go
he's like for some law he's like
marsala he's like ever someone else out
there
you were nominated for two razzies yeah
and i i when i saw i
think i saw two one is with
david david spade from the wrongness because
they get invented a category surprisingly worst
kind of all or something yeah so
i i when i saw it i
think i saw at first because i
it just popped
up on twitter when i was on
it and like right when they announced
it and i was like oh should
i text the group about this and
then i was like ah how does
maybe she doesn't feel good about this
i didn't feel good about it i
thought i was really mean yeah here's
my gun was like you'd just the
problem is i'm in a category with
like a list people i mean it's
me and i'm like you're just being
a dick like i like randy got
to do a movie he razzies were
about taking down the joker my babysitting
job i mean like basically like it's
just like blob up go out over
here co-op who are you wearing cool
up she did dress up
this is her dressed up by the
way a big bottle water h two
o everyone's in the big bottle up
i love you it's a big bottle
by the way that's like you fill
this up at the beginning of the
day and you're supposed to drink at
all but i have one of those
but i but i like her as
more than the one i have is
why i will give it to you
as a gift okay it's a fun
surprise venmo
but but the recipes used to be
about okay there are these huge movie
stars and they would make a mistake
like halle berry in catwoman and that's
even better yeah and they would have
a sense of humor about it oh
yeah because very showed up to accept
it the day before she got an
oscar or whatever and glenn in my
in my category or my year whatever
glenn closest nominee for an oscar for
the same role she's nominated for a
razzie and right anna hathaway or some
or somebody else right but but it's
just when it's just a when it's
someone who's on who's like trying to
make a name for themselves and is
arguably the best part of the thing
that they are i said arguably yeah
and i'm the one who's gonna argue
it seems weird to to call that
out and it seems like the razzies
have taken a turn over the last
few years into just being like mean
asshole things like that they're meaningless now
it's like this doesn't have an identity
it's just it's just a negative thing
what i thought was could have been
funds you know yeah it's reported on
by like
the actual like deadline oh yes ny
not even you even regardless of myself
being included i was like i don't
understand why you would post this this
has nothing to do with like actual
anything it's really just mean and it's
mean even if you are anne hathaway
i'm like i think that's mean i
don't yeah i don't so for me
i was like it made me feel
about but then i was like who
cares whatever and then part of me
was like well i'm gonna list all
these fucking famous people yeah i mean
in a way it's like they they
deem your work serious yeah i mean
if there's that but like i also
thought they nominated a child from the
movie music and i was like yeah
like it's just that's not her fault
that that movie is not appropriate like
i
just thought the whole thing and i
looked up look where it started and
it was like some publicist started in
his living room and i was like
okay so some publicist wanted to be
a dick making fun of celebrities and
his living room and now we have
the internet where like you have to
read about that yeah and like share
it like it's me or the people
what humor in it well i also
think like what is the
all of these places that give out
awards are so are basically just these
like the golden globes and all this
they're they're the award show is an
advertisement for their place where they all
get salaries yeah right and they get
big big salaries in order to do
this and even though the golden globes
is like a thing of like oh
oh well we work with charity when
i was watching the other day it's
like they're talking about like we gave
one million dollars to feeding america and
they and that you're constantly bragging about
it it's like you guys are making
millions and millions and millions off this
yeah either the best as they and
and the golden globes i feel like
it's news to people this year because
of the i will just
crustacean yeah that the golden globes have
always been just a scam and they've
always been extremely buyable i mean back
in the eighties that we all knew
that yeah that it was a scam
that he is a dora stuff and
it was just like yeah everyone knew
johnstone would buy a nomination every year
yeah movie you've never heard of why
she would just like leave for the
golden globes yeah
golden cherry stone wood would perennially get
a nomination for best actress at the
golden globes from a movie that nobody
saw you know because she would wine
and dine them she that's how you
used to get nominated but it was
only in paris a flew out of
the people i love that and they
didn't win right no no but they
were they all no money and voters
to para
yes but people would want the nomination
because it's just another advertisement it makes
it makes entertainment tonight keep saying emily
and paris and oh right yeah again
because the golden gloves but that's like
when it worked for that movie survey
company
what i where i worked when one
of my day jobs when i moved
here was i worked for a company
that you're making sure jokes that i
couldn't quite understand but no israel this
is real it was a place called
energy the national research group high energy
get it and we go and he
had to um why do these movies
surveys and
the surveys we had to do word
for word and the involved saying the
same cohen brothers ease over and over
and over again oh okay and it
was to advertise these movies it was
like slick covert advertising like just planting
a seed yeah yeah trying to get
people to like awareness raise awareness for
yeah yeah yeah hobby interests
eating well um on another malema was
it oh yeah well i do want
you to say something i just want
to say i got good reviews for
that shit so fuck off yeah okay
and i'm gonna hold onto that so
i'm trying to just not let myself
be brought down by flores is terrific
in this movie and it's like whatever
whatever problems you may have with that
type of film put out by
bye bye those guys yeah because you
can't stay down there a la yeah
you can't say the lord is not
funny this movie but also the thing
about the razzies to me is that
i can't believe it's still a thing
it feels like a very specific kind
of like old-timey snark that's bad that
people aren't doing any of that people
now but also has become so terrible
on the internet
that it's not fun anymore you know
like back yes back when it first
was around there was stuff like the
golden globes that people were paying to
get nominations for and it was like
hey let's bring hollywood down a little
bit yeah and i'd say something funny
to that when there's no law but
nowadays it's like look we're just faced
with it all day long the people
saying you suck you suck yeah
so i think they've outgrown their usefulness
and i did see a lot of
um people tweeting like what this like
okay it's a pandemic and you still
did the razzies you just feels like
really like
not going to make it just leave
everyone alone they should have nominated novel
coronavirus for every category they should have
like well i also i also when
you were nominated i was like i
wouldn't have even expected this like in
the same way know that when between
two ferns came out when the razzie
nominations were coming out i i did
not have awh
awareness of it because i did not
expect it would be nominated on reddit
no it didn't i didn't but i
but that's what i mean is i
was like look you know say what
you will about it people enjoyed it
for the most part you know in
a lot of people watched it and
it was like okay great
so i never even thought like it
was a possibility i wasn't sitting there
like you know for the razzie announcements
going like oh i hope we don't
get one so that's why i was
mad as a cast member of the
film yeah i remember being very invested
and saying god of the razzies leave
us alone but i you know i
feel like to to not let myself
go
go to a bad place about it
it's like whoa okay i got to
be in a movie that was tech
one of the most watched movies of
the year modesto sixty million views yes
in the first month or exactly when
they try to tear you down that's
what you know your other right time
and with some guys popular it's good
well
yeah i feel like a yeah it's
it's just like i think people don't
associate anything with like real people when
they do something like that where it's
like i have to talk myself out
of a hole because that like with
like facts and figure i'd like to
talk myself into a hole like the
bachelor is a bachelor matt anyway he's
christian
ian i don't even know if he
back to reality recap i don't know
if even bedded any of these women
bedded well bones guided he's christian right
yeah i mean i assume some of
them seem pretty happy the next day
someone if anyone smile i think you
must assume that they are having sex
and that we are meant to infer
that you know the bachelor did a
did a left turn from we're not
even going to intimate this is in
the early seasons we're not even going
to intimate that anything intimate happened ah
on that show too now
now like pretty much if there was
one who who in the after the
final rose said well if you didn't
feel that way about me why did
you make love to me that nick
land's that was that opened the floodgates
for the bachelor franchise to then like
just admit that the bachelor were having
sex with every single contestant who gets
that far yeah
um anyway ah man i'd love to
be less left turn he just wanted
to get away from it if you
could be the bachelor would you huh
if you could see the bachelor would
you paul yeah
like i'm saying in a different circumstance
in your life where you you're single
you're single you would never met naini
i guess he doesn't exist how about
that ooh
her parents didn't have sex on that
fateful night sliding doors
um no i would not i couldn't
i couldn't take it if it was
didn't take it the elder bachelor like
this the elder statesmen bachelor that we're
talking about like hey everyone's you know
are the guys fifty and the women
are thirty would you
ah that's sick
the sick man i know what you
mean no it's like i i find
all those people like i there's not
anybody on the shows that i would
want to have a conversation with well
what if they were like hey we're
gonna get people you actually liked
then i guess i don't know with
the filming it doesn't have to be
a show well that's that's that's this
just be like a nice party this
is the question i'm getting too will
you kiss someone on camera yeah well
today
one of us
god
it's what i've been very few on-camera
kisses yeah i've had way too many
away too okay you've had
david spade i can there's fifty fifty
kisses no i mean but there's probably
twenty and i and i surprised by
it but yeah okay i've had two
i feel okay i've had christine with
three
my friend christine woods and that was
awkward
tap dance teacher my friend natasha lucero
and that was awkward that's weird and
you wrote all of these right yeah
but then you begged them to but
but no when you're a writer on
why these things you refuse to cast
anyone else when you're riding on one
of these things you're thinking conceptually about
it and then it comes to the
day where you're supposed to do and
you're like fuck fuck i guess i
better be
the actor in this
we should fire that guy i don't
want my friend because a stranger is
my own show
oh i'm gonna suddenly guess what else
um and then what's her name abigail
spencer from umm we did the hotdog
kiss which was disgusting where we each
ate one end of a hot dog
and then met in the middle and
kissing it was so fucking gross
but yeah it is i was actually
proud when we did the ferns movie
that we didn't put a romantic so
i was thrown and the movie was
because i was like why does this
have to be first of all even
giovanni and ryan have domingo i was
going i'm so glad i want to
fuck oh my and we cut that
subplot i know they make for no
reason yeah but you know even worse
some of the food
no i was correct ok i hate
having to do i mean everyone does
it's like well i also think like
it's weird you and zach had a
mentor relationship and why no it would
have been weird to make it so
i thought it was much sweeter ho
was yeah exactly like he just was
your friend you know and yeah yeah
normal yes that's normal can i say
that not only does that not
have to be a subplot in most
things yeah like an action movies and
whatever you don't you don't need it
you don't need sexual tension doesn't add
anything and it's also it's it's usually
done so poorly that it just comes
out of nowhere like at the end
these people hook up and it's like
why wow yeah there shouldn't be romance
in anything in
any stadium well because my ears or
other my friend know but here's how
i feel the stakes and movies like
i watched the snyder cut of justice
league last night oh that's on you
the staring about this the stakes are
so high of the entire world is
going to like next snyder cut is
because i didn't know and everyone's talking
about on twitter everyone knows and i
mean i'm like this i don't
need to explain i bet you there's
five people listening who don't know ok
there's one there's a movie that was
always going to be dumb it was
made even dumber by the guy who
directed know it was better it's better
it's better yeah that's way better it's
like night and day better or at
least a special cut of that he
made he made his basically what happened
was ah at the end of the
movie he made his cut at
and the what's the movie justice league
is movie and he sent it to
the studio and they didn't like it
and so they hired just weeden to
come in and rewrite and reshoot the
entire thing so it's like a very
different and okay i didn't even understand
that just sweden but and and the
sad part of it is is he
his daughter committed suicide so real life
in real life
so he said you know what what
am i even doing that's horrible i'm
gonna just walk away you guys do
whatever you want to it because my
family needs me so he so he
put together the snyder cut in a
lot of the profits from goto suicide
prevention anyone i got so ah horrible
but but the stakes in that are
so high of like the entire world
is going to die and then
a romantic comedy is like when two
people kiss like it's not the same
thing yeah i mean i romantic someday
though is what i'm saying taking romance
out of movie he thinks it should
just be confirmed he is or dramas
or actions and there should be no
roman no romance because the stakes are
not high people kiss all the time
who cares
rs the stakes can be high and
i like romcom it's you kiss janie
right we're killing his shit you're killing
the planet that's happening every day
that slowly i'm saying there's a fast
killing of the planet so put it
in motion festival
so people when the kitchen gets really
super fast yeah if you give me
a for all the way the snyder
cut should all be in fast motion
by the way instead of skills like
four hours long right yeah um here's
the other thing that needs to be
taken out taken out of um specifically
police dramas is the sirens
as a wife now the wife is
worried about her husband no not worried
about worried about will be great but
of man city spending so much time
in family that doesn't understand the concept
of police it's fucking we just watched
this um this ah it's either swedish
or danish um the ah the investigation
on hbo max and it's
great it's like a real slow procedural
thing that's based on a true story
true story okay they're trying chez that's
from present exhibits no it's not a
gibby that's john from real-world guys
why talk to reality we can't be
done with the real world you know
i'm you know how in this where's
the drama dings now an episode of
real world they they always start by
this is the the story and then
someone says true story but he sings
it in one episode in season he
goes true story and if you see
the
country singer oh sure sure my friend
mariah smith's podcast called spectacle h episode
is all about the genesis of reality
tv it's vegan
so back to back to cops so
the entire the investigation this guy is
investigating the death of this young journalist
female journalist who has been decapitated and
dismembered at sea her body parts are
dropped into the ocean they have to
recover in all
order to have a base did they
decapitate and dismember at sea or they
did it on the land and then
they'd all happen to see it everything
happened at sea yeah wow okay so
in order to have a murder case
against the suspect they have to recover
every single body part so that they
can rule out all these other like
it's own this is a factor
rules like to murder which scripted show
based on a real story they dance
murders like the their ruling murderers who
keep toes or something so if they
find the toes there like they have
there's only one guy it happened on
a submarine there oh there's one guy
burying the lead who is the suspect
not a submarine
we'll murder da stone taylor submarine
so they have to rule out all
these because this guy says oh ah
yeah she hit her head and she
died that's how she died so i
hit her head i water please that
could kill you so they have to
rule out everything in order you gotta
jump at the pool
i can't wait to talk with manna
i'll throw you and you throw me
in the blind throw you if you're
the someone needs to roll
hi
one layer one you better be underwater
by yeah the season this episode is
underwater you know there's no law so
show he she hit her head and
so they i'm just not about that
no he's saying she hit her head
and yeah he keeps he keeps changing
his story every time they get a
new detail because i guess in in
danish law
law you're allowed to do this and
you have to just believe this guy's
story until you can prove beyond a
shadow of a doubt oh like it's
it's like i guess it favors the
accused so much that they're saying we
can't even bring the case because he's
saying this we have to just pray
have to find the bio dorky yes
yes yes yes
right you have to just prove that
she killed herself we have to disprove
blah blah blah blah blah like yeah
to the point where he's saying like
no i i cut her up and
throw thrower in the ocean because i
was thinking of the family she killed
herself in the family would have been
upset you know like that's how wild
it is like huh
so they have to do they it's
like an impossible task where they have
to find every single part of this
woman's body in order to say isn't
it all like kind of by i
know that stuff moves around in the
ocean but wouldn't it all be in
the general area of your life ahead
is or did he yeah did he
as the submarine was moving was like
throwing out one
every ten minutes i don't i'm not
gonna i'm not gonna don't spoil spoil
the thing or recite it
can you recite it from start to
finish yes and here goes yeah yeah
yeah um that's the summer so while
this is going on this investigation which
is just beyond horrific the the lead
detective has a daughter who is pregnant
she's she announces that she's gonna have
a baby and because this guy
this guy takes a phone call at
the dinner and walks outside to discuss
it they have an argument she she
leaves the daughter the daughter and her
and her fiance lee awe and then
he she's like he's trying to make
contact with her she won't talk to
him come on guys because busy with
work yes
he's getting calls about this submarine the
decabde say i don't understand sometimes jobs
are important i don't know if this
if that was part of it in
real life but it's such a trope
to throw of detective shit that it's
like i yeah it doesn't need to
be in there it doesn't want it
what purpose does it serve i don't
get what purpose it just makes me
annoyed i mean probably
he is a thing with cops spouses
i remember that day i remember in
a very no doubt about that back
to reality recap every the very first
episode of cops when they didn't know
what the show was that it was
just going to be the arrests right
they they followed the the cop back
to his house and showed that their
spouse
house was really upset about it so
i think it's a thing about about
the police about like the person constantly
being gone and yeah ours but you
don't see it in doctor dramas all
that much because it's like the automatic
assumption is well doctors are rich and
so their spouses don't have any reason
to complain right you know what i
mean like her do you
see it in doctor stuff i don't
feel like i do that docu series
about the late night stalker person or
the nights years yeah it's a scary
series but once you got to you
nailed it
the detective they they interviewed his wife
and she was like it was very
hard to be together during the whole
time she went somewhere else because they're
also afraid you know it actually the
trip was good and mind hunter i
think because that he had specific challenges
with
ah with his kid the older cut
yeah yeah and and the the just
how depressing that case was not like
it was well done in that absolutely
but for the most part it just
seems like a lazy thing that doesn't
especially in a movie where it's just
one scene in order to elicit a
response from you of like wow this
our main characters pray
columns i yell for him but it's
like you're already yoga lowered you're already
yeah with the character like he's it's
hard to solve a murder you know
i mean yeah it's not fair to
be taking that out on him
would you like to solve murders paul
i have which my wife and i
get along great
i think it sounds kind of fun
to be a detective i think it
would be fun
because like do you ever read the
book homicide life on the streets yeah
but so i will i think that
it's very trendy right now to solve
murders well to do it's very timeless
hi gerry o'carroll it's like everyone's like
wanting to watch things about murder and
listen to things about murder yes murder
and murder is having a moment that
it is and i don't know about
that anything
about that i we've always been ah
we've always been fascinated by that and
you can look at your old old
um ah sensationalized crime like it's always
been a thing that people are drawn
to we've never remember when teen made
a podcast about able huh
you mean my character from lucifer that's
your eight
i don't think we've ever had as
much um access and ways to distribute
stories about it as we do now
and once people also once people it
became like it came out of a
guilty pleasure kind of thing and into
just being like mainstream entertained
but you know well also the cbs
shows yeah you know sure i bring
up homicidal mines or whatever i guess
i bring up homicide life on the
street again because young sheldon it's fast
kill young sheldon know he was killing
he was on a killing spree yeah
and that's why he's so weird that
he just became a nerd
but um homicide they they talk ah
there there it's a really fascinating book
and they talk about how long it
takes to solve murders right and there
because it basically it's david simon starts
on january first of one year and
then he ends on december thirty first
of another year yeah and there is
a murder that plagues them the entire
our year that they never solved right
well and it tracks that and but
but that it it then you watch
these cop shows and it's a different
murder or multiple murder every single week
and one town it's like if life
were really like that i would move
away from wherever there you know it's
like there there's not that much murder
i know there are murders in the
world
that much do you know that um
like i billy johnson who he was
in the patent aswell documentary i didn't
see or even watch them i'm sorry
no i'm just i've scarred find that
interesting i'm sorry i can't trek the
next generation good and bad episodes of
and not i can report it's called
right now i will fall
do you yeah alpha all fall be
gone in the other guns i will
not
death cab for cutie song of berlin
are you into the dark
you know what i always think about
him just decided about death cab that
when he got divorced from zoe deschanel
i don't know if he had him
yet but they released all of her
bank statements all of her spain personally
habits on her bank statements but her
her spending because it's part of the
divorce things where he wanted money or
whatever else maybe that that seems like
a tmc thing where they get their
well it was something not cool yeah
who know all look it up but
but this guy billy johnson
and who i met doing his podcast
which was all about murder when i
think they were doing like um a
sort of month of talking to people
who have nothing to do with this
and so i was like this why
i'm here like it was some of
the bachelor with him it was like
random as fuck and i'm sure the
listeners were like why is this happening
but i really liked him and he'd
follow my instagram and he is always
seeming to be solving some raw
really hard murder that has been like
mysterious forever like he goes on like
in-depth things to try to get unsolved
cases solved from what i can tell
and he was involved a lot with
um he he knew michelle ah they
were friends ok um but so ah
very interesting
and i thought that series was terrifying
in fact i'll be gone in the
dark um yes like what what she
was studying just pure horror yeah yeah
right a true monster yeah that guy
oh
oh my god i'm not i love
when people get caught it's fun and
that could lose drama dings drama dings
alright we need to take a break
we'll be right back with the three-tier
welcome back welcome back from da ma
three dominance three your tile man this
is the moment this is what people
really want yeah because they want these
three church now three-tier is a portmanteau
of freedom and feature and three m
is a portmanteau of three of us
free and freedom
and portmanteau is a portmanteau of portman
natalie portman and toe wiki feet
you know there's not going to harass
these my wiki that's right and out
of ten you have a honor yar
crushing ah this feature is entitled to
delete due to crazy pet return oh
this is submitted by robert tucson
pst one person is trying to return
their pet at the pet store because
something is wrong with it but they
don't know what they're paid is or
what's wrong with it the other two
they don't know what it is they
don't even know they don't know what
that date is and they don't know
what's wrong with it and the other
two people work at the pet store
and do know these things the first
person has to figure out their pet
and their issue it's crazy pet return
because the pets can be whatever you
want like mythical creatures or whatever you
figure it out you figured it out
dude do you figured it out peep
peep with a pencil and a pad
i figured it out alright who shall
be the pet person and who shall
be the employees i want to be
the pet
person first alright so paul and i
will text each other what the pet
is and you checks me what the
pairs and i'll text you at the
problem hell yeah what makes the dreamwork
where already having fun
um i'm supposed to do the pet
okay guy supposed to
ah right i got it and i've
sent it and i got it and
now i'm coming up with a problem
and sending it to you okay
okay so now you're not even you're
cutting yeah it's got pitched scott pitched
a problem the problem just because it
came to me it turns out that's
what i was going to say hell
yeah we're on the same page let's
do it
alright really
so we wait we own a pet
store together yes are we partnered like
nobody said we were owners romantic and
work at the pet store i'm in
need a little back why don't you
see what happens okay every little backstory
near little mac thank you me too
thin as a needle look at me
i'm as thin as a needle
it's kind of just like her i
don't know what it did britney spears
oh it was chilling thank you because
i didn't even know it was gonna
come out so whoa um okay incredible
one of the most distinctive voices i'm
skinny as a needle i'm a skinny
machine bragging about that at some point
she's saying that the pavarotti show pictures
of her where she looks like she's
overweight but right now i'm skinny as
a needle and it's just taken one
day apart
because i just got a text from
paul f tompkins fuck you
it's nice right now just joshing around
i don't need it i'm just kidding
um ok hello
ding dong doodling hiding don welcome back
hope everything is working out with your
pet it's unfortunately na nie i'm really
yeah i spent some time in australia
forgive me it comes out so well
for one thing i should have listened
to me are you in australia three
years ago oh rye age i should
send you are going down
under it you know what you make
it fuck it i'll just leave oh
okay yeah oh ding dong ding dong
come back
i have sort of a complaint and
i'm just i feel awful because you
know all my friends told me adopt
don't shop and yet here i am
i bought a pet from you two
lovers and i love your lovers were
lover thank you it's called lower spec
store that's right i i'm really devastated
because there's something i thought was going
to be called rub your my head
store
and he thought it was lovers pet
store yeah and i want you not
understanding what his dick was in your
mouth
or vice versa
it's tough to understand in that situation
we don't have a lot of times
so we have to have these conversations
whenever we can
and i'm a power bottom thank you
just like ebenezer scrooge that notorious power
well i don't like cry every time
i feel bad are you i mean
i think i need to return her
well did did you bring the ah
did you bring her i don't see
i don't see a ah you know
a trailer hitch on the back of
your car well it's not every day
you can get a unicorn to come
with you a unicorn i'm just saying
random stuff
oh okay dang are you okay
are you a unicorn themed movie recently
you know i don't even know why
i said that i but i do
have solved my penny gigantic there is
a trailer hitch tobacco my car out
there oh i i'm sorry yeah there
is she out there now yeah okay
she's really not doing well and when
did you notice because i thought you
yeah what what do you
i thought you would have noticed the
one issue i'm thinking of right when
you were shopping here i mean you
know it would be hard to miss
well her coloring was off yeah yeah
yeah her hair was falling out no
not when we saw oh yeah definitely
that's a new thing to us it
her she looked slips limp and lifeless
this i don't know why you're continuing
to say problems when you've already said
with the problem oh so her coloring
was awesome
yeah you could get more specifically trying
to buy a green dragon but she
was wow why would we want to
get your head on the same day
that you bought our pet i look
i took an edible before i came
here and ah damn more we sell
dragons i can't believe you'd go somewhere
else no no no no i don't
have a dragon you
highs hell you know that my creature
has four legs yeah yeah of course
we do course we did it has
a tale yes of course has two
eyes yeah it's real yeah of course
it's real we only sell real not
mythic we only sell real animals here
a santa train dragons yes and it's
a horse no
i mean that's a common misconception honey
no donkey no yeah okay oh strikes
back donkey party dregs back better than
ever
um no i mean a lot of
yeah yeah yeah no stripes yeah okay
we'll return him but we should not
have sold that too
it's actually just a white horse yea
we lie to you okay i get
it now now i will be the
person oh good okay lauren what do
you want to okay at sam i'm
gonna name the atom or you did
the animals i'm the animal yeah i'll
do the problem i look i'll i'll
do the anti animal
and i'll i'll text you back the
problem and meanwhile paul what are you
going to do i'm the person i
don't do anything i know but what
are you going to do with your
time i'm looking for looking for a
game for the next episode oh honey
like the hold up hey
um
okay
ah and we haven't k
okay so i need you to put
all of those fish sticks back on
the on the show was selling fish
sticks it's weird because we sell fish
it's not that they eat fish quirky
brand
oh excuse me i'm sorry i was
yelling at my employee in front of
you well already again really in husband
get ready because i'm gonna yell out
for long i'm gonna yell at the
both of you i'm very upset with
the pet i bought from your store
oh no i knew this was going
to happen i may we open a
store i knew we'd have one attorneys
it's gonna happen the minute we sold
that joe
yeah it tells me this is right
wow well no of course i mean
i can't from looking you're right
you can for looking know i can
i wouldn't be able to tell if
it's right or wrong happening can't see
how the it is affected the mood
of the creature i'll maybe a slight
downturn in the smile but i mean
the smile example when she always has
my oh it's an animal i think
ken smile
while i'd like to see smiles where
there are none like on my face
so so this you're telling me this
animal can't smile it's just an optical
illusion well i wouldn't say smiles i
mean yeah it's yeah it's kind of
a neutral but
but you choose to interpret it as
a child that's what i'm into well
that's very positive that's how i'm an
optum together as long as we have
but yeah i would argue no way
out let me ask you so to
you this looks normal who gets to
keep the business
have you read the outside i know
yeah it looks like the name of
my store
what is it again well i'm not
so lassen did you like
i didn't really pay much call did
you like it oh no i didn't
pay attention to that i just saw
that it's so easy old pets and
i came here about this bet every
time a satisfied customer leaves the store
we say to them did you like
it and they never answer because they're
already gone and they also just got
the patch so why would that site
i know rick wage doesn't make any
sense she wanted to name it that
it's
well it's my hope is that they'll
be return customers and they'd come back
and i'd say did you like giving
you want some more i am a
return customer and then i'd like to
return this pet which is defective what
do you think is wrong with it
i really can't want to i think
is wrong with it are you telling
me this is the way it's supposed
to look that's the way i suppose
yeah so then it is an internal
problem yes sort of
because you know what the problem is
i know it's not external but we
wouldn't be able to tell by looking
at it i can't i'm not really
need some other clue
how am i some other one of
our others to gift one of our
other sensors use one of our other
senses in order now shut up is
this the way that the the peace
practicing for american idol i think telling
her she's too old i literally don't
care law is aware that she's too
old or that she's
sure about eighty of it i would
care about your life isn't boyle wasn't
too old for a g t and
look what happened god i would love
for you to get famous i wanna
be sous ma she was britain's got
tell of eight years to shed customer
what's wrong with that thing and what
is that we will have to use
one of our other senses of the
venere eyes okay right yeah i mean
it's it's
supposed to smell this way yes yes
of course it is it's supposed to
sound like the sound it's making you
know i admit it's not okay so
then the sound that it makes usually
is familiar inaudible it's familiar to anyone
yeah so it's inaudible that is familiar
the absence of saudis
yeah inaudible use familiar to anyone hear
it okay so normally it doesn't make
a lot of noise true oh it's
silent it's silent pants asylum pet yes
okay then something is wrong because this
thing is making a noise as you
can hear yes of course okay yes
and i i find this noise is
indescribable how would you describe it yeah
yes i mean i hear the experts
obviously bit as something that could happen
to anyone from ah from human to
animal yeah it's definitely it's it doesn't
sound good i'll tell you that much
no it doesn't sound good yeah and
so normally this would not be making
noises that
correct correct okay because it was not
making noise when i bought it and
shit noise ever yeah alright and should
it should it be this big this
short appropriate so that's an appropriate size
this is within all small accurate parameters
so it's it's typically it's small like
it is yeah okay alright
a small house looking for somebody like
him
gotta like he has that coloring all
the time so this is not an
unwinding depending
okay so ah there are times when
he would it would change colors sure
okay and this is to blend in
with it's surroundings zoo oh yeah as
a defense mechanism probably okay so it's
ah would you how do you pronounce
a d say jamelia shamil yes chameleon
okay
and the noise yeah
um it sounds like burping to me
is that correct that's not what you
describe it is that it shouldn't let's
your brand know what you're i don't
know yeah can you burp for this
please in case i can't do it
on command but if you have any
soda pop up every now and then
within minutes i can burp for you
okay um so if you ever see
charlie and the chocolate factory that burping
scene what is that ah
when my wrapping were the burping seen
it either i'm not familiar those words
you said to me make no sense
you don't know what charlie means a
you via vietnam no no of course
not i look i want to talk
about my my pet chameleon sure now
i know it shouldn't be making that
noise noise it's very high pitched ah
it's
not really i don't know music okay
it's more of um it turned it
upside down it's pitiless it's it's pitiless
i don't know how to interpret that
at all it's low pitched ah yeah
probably but i mean the quality of
it i can hear the what's wrong
with it in the quality of what
i'm hearing it's it can't sing very
well
well no i mean it shouldn't be
swinging at all to yeah i know
it shouldn't be so that's not i'm
talking no i'm talking about my wife
you wouldn't quantify the noise a chameleon
is making a singing no of course
not no okay this is more of
a medical issue i don't know why
you're bringing it into us also is
gastrointestinal
no not really but are you sure
with you to more common
how do you know about us i
read some yelp review oh okay god
but it's when it's more common yeah
it's more of a common thing i
don't know what not you know could
mean something really bad or i mean
nothing at all yeah like it's it's
happening in regular intervals yeah so it's
got hiccups would you say no not
a hick i mean the shy hiccups
would be something that would just go
away on it's own i mean this
seems like it's something that would need
persistent yeah it's persisted it was making
a persistent noise that will not go
away yes it's i mean it certainly
hasn't ever since it's been in here
and it could happen to you what
she's talking about her favorite movie it
can happen yeah maybe he wins a
lot of bridget fonda nicholas cage
remember the themes under that movie
it could happen to you
that i mean there wasn't a theme
song she just was singing that's the
boot happened to you the audience members
were pleading with her to be quiet
so there wasn't a theme food you're
after she remembered when she sang that
got kicked out of the movie i
said yes i like to be carried
out of places
um so it's pretty she has to
walk out of a place she will
do anything in her power to make
sure that she's carried again i don't
care so the persistence nowhere the petition
noise is something that i could i
could also be making i hope that
you don't catch it yeah yeah what
are some noises you might make
that are medical conditions sure things that
the body does
okay so
ah i thought i ruled something out
you probably did gastrointestinal yeah sure but
there's other places sounds can come out
say why not that anyway well i'll
go pick one he doesn't have covert
but you know it's alarming but it
but it could it it the it's
it i hope he didn't vocal noise
is not related to gastrointestinal issues and
it could happen to me it could
be coven but i don't want to
rule it out i hope the coven
i give oh okay so it's not
covered but it is a symptom of
covert yeah coughing yes but a certain
type of cough a dry cough yeah
it's alright we'll take it back
here's your two dollars you thought the
worst of us paul and it was
just a dry cough
you guys you've tricked me
the one time you didn't do what
you absolutely would do
wait what did you chanting he was
like he kept the games diarrhea or
i can't believe we didn't do that
ah alright i'll be the person alright
never looked i'm never good at this
part the symptom and all texts the
animal but not the symptom
what
rocky horror previously mentioned on threesome
they're laughing at the i'm loving it
twitter oh you're on twitter right now
i'm just shitting jenna lie ah trying
to lie you see i'm trying to
lie
but one of you tells the truth
god and one of us trying to
lie and one of us is trying
to tell the truth okay we're writing
but you're not successful at either
oh hi guys i'm sick ebbing can
join to you i love it hi
hi yeah what hey i bought ah
you know
what about ah you know a lottery
ticket like it could happen to you
you see that movie it could have
a new you nagging them a knee
yeah big we were enjoying it and
then somebody got thrown out of the
movie oh and you've been saying that
ever since i think i was stuck
in my head shower he sings weird
um about a about a pet from
from you guys are you one person
or youtube people or to vp oh
dairy i hate i never know he
likes it that's two different people i
bought a pad from you guys and
i think it's i don't know there's
something weird with it well we pride
ourselves in selling top quality pets not
once okay well it's in the palm
of my hand right
yeah i mean that's very precarious you
really should oh okay well he wants
to be put down alright let me
put it down is it safe to
put down here yeah well yeah i
mean without ah should be okay should
it be restrained at all i mean
i mentioned put something over it put
something over yeah yeah yeah okay so
as it doesn't escape right right
right over it so is it in
like should i put it in this
cage is that way your that i
mean cage could work yeah would have
to be a decent sized cage though
oh okay okay well anyway it's um
you guys ready you were fine no
i'm not leaving you you're the one
who stopped in the south yeah yeah
you like went away i keep hoping
you guys will fill the space a
little bit like yes why would we
just on the actual items i have
something wrong with your social anxiety and
i say sorry said john sorry
noticing something wrong with this process i
am it's this it's ended it just
doesn't look right and what do you
think is it should look like i
mean i guess it just want to
know you know what what's an issue
that you're saying well the invisibility is
just a huge aspect to this but
i don't think that's it's oh
i'm thinking my other pet that's right
outside here i'd like to hear about
that at some point this creature is
very real and cannot do anything like
that oh yeah yeah it looks okay
to me but maybe a little i
don't know out with it you're not
really supposed to admit know i know
but what come on he's like i'm
a i'm a
loyal customer i buy a pet a
day from you guys i mean i
worry about that outwardly his appearance seems
fine yeah you shouldn't be he looks
at you that i mean i buy
so many pets from you if if
one isn't right i would expect you
to be honest about it so i
think you should kill uncomfortable yeah yeah
well is it is it ah
a problem i mean you know the
what i call legs do you call
them legs yeah and there's something wrong
with those there's nothing wrong with lexi
and fantasy the legs and there's four
of them obvious no no that that
would be a problem ah that would
be over so but but the hands
i call them hand you shouldn't you
should know okay i was just shy
call them paul
this is my pet store i called
them pause there's that hands are not
really an animal that only has two
legs and a burwell it's ah what
about the wings yeah so wings seem
following their clips and yeah wasn't too
worried about flying right right right right
so it is a bird yeah yes
of course it is is a specific
type of bird no it's a general
bird it's just
i never asked him is this specific
waves absolutely every bird is a specific
type of oopsy it's pretty big we
put my big great well yeah but
i mean you know i think it's
a two can i've been looking i
know your way no i hope you
didn't we didn't mislead you somehow and
we sold oh no no the word
is right yeah
well i mean there's only two syllables
wait two to two syllables two is
those uses that is that right know
what's wrong with can can can or
just one of the letters that that
that that that that that that that
that you know just why am i
dancing right now it's just i'm i
make people wanna dance with my music
oh make me whoa
my texas
um can canada the canadian birds right
oh no come on um can er
ca ca ca oh gee ya don't
focus on that so much so okay
anyway so this bird this bird which
we'll all figure out the specific i
mean you never told me what it
was but i'll figure it out it's
assumed you knew
i mean you know i don't know
i can't very it's a very recognizable
is i mean no you know look
i know your zoo isn't by the
water i think this bird would appreciate
it if it was yeah right yes
the well it's it's a siegel no
no it's not i'm saying i'm talking
about my friend jason oh yeah is
a
siegel
he told me in between shooting movies
he's a big movie star i do
i don't like to brag about my
friends but i mean i'm a huge
star yeah and tv started out you
know he did yeah how i met
your mother yeah anyway buddy um he
ah it's ah it's obviously a bird
that likes to be by the sea
e obviously um exactly what i said
and ah it's a pelican yes and
um
it's but it's not it's not right
right now it's certainly not i mean
like yeah like i think it's pretty
clear but but but i can't tell
look at that i can't tell just
oh yeah i mean i should look
at that obviously i can tell when
i see it no boy it won't
stop shitting either yeah because it has
it has directed yeah
hey sorry we will we will take
this okay fine i keep the diarrhea
yeah as our gift to you a
fun surprise
oh my god oh dear another read
on in the books that was a
long one guys i was really yeah
i have fun i had fun um
thanks be on the lookout for those
things we mentioned earlier in the episode
unless they've been bleeped out yeah and
ah anything else we should say
no i will see you next i'm
ah hey
uh