three
yellow hello hello welcome we're hearing who
was just on the line oh now
hold on a second turn your radio
down
welcome to us once more us once
more that's good that's better step and
what we've obviously settled us once more
everyone we still don't know what the
show is called oh hello my name
is paul f tompkins hi i'm scott
ackerman and i'm lauren lab guess and
we are
our three friends just want to sit
around just have a good time sitting
around having a good time trying to
hurt anybody no we're not three seven
to three friends not trying to hurt
anybody so but we might hurt people
we might we met in person lying
to it's not our intention if anyone
was hurt by our actions yes we
apologize whether you
you're a man a woman there's only
two genders we're not trying to hurt
anyone ooh boy click
you called one person to do our
podcasts so you think audiences reach you
you call you call because you called
um you say on a random topic
higher where okay friends doing a podcast
that's anyway i need to know yeah
i have been listening to a podcast
that i'm really enjoying uhf and it
was recommend dung bitch sash i just
heard ah casey wilson recommended and so
i checked it out and it's called
where should we begin
and it's couples therapy sessions recorded each
episode is ah the first couple therapy
session for a couple with this doctor
are they anonymous yeah oh thank god
yeah and it's so fascinating you just
like here what you hear the couple's
main problems and then you kind of
hear like the truth comes out at
a certain point and like or they
have a breakthrough or breakdown it's
like it's really fascinating are you ah
do you do a lot of therapy
i'm in so much therapy do you
do i do zero yeah i do
ah journaling and supper
now are their voices altered in anyway
no um but they've said they cut
out names and any like identifiable sort
of things but like if i heard
i have thought about that if i
heard someone i knew i would know
like yes i would be afraid to
do it because i'd be constantly mentioning
my ten inch penis and be like
oh okay that's got
how does everyone know so much about
your penis well you know it's famous
i'm sorry i've just been enjoying when
i say that sounds
i don't mean this as a as
a judgment so much as a feeling
or a sexual harassment
that sounds hot
i love to hear you do listen
to it with you in the news
ah it feels feels
the new nude is the sexiest sexual
tattoo
game the unsexy a sexual harasser and
that's rough but you just turned me
down so i tried to turn me
down i love to lube your boo
oh
huh
nasty mother fuck knows the unsexy sexual
harass it's still nasty still no i
want to lick your arms yeah um
it's it feels creepy to me like
i feel like i would feel not
i don't mean ended like an invasion
layer of voyeuristic it's not some yeah
it's i don't know it's it's it
feels unset
failing to me like i'd be hearing
this personal stuff so i wouldn't feel
like i was it's not so much
like oh i'm morally wrong for listening
to this but i would feel like
uncomfortable i think at first i under
like i felt that a little bit
but then it's like you hear in
case you said this too is like
you hear yourself in these conversations and
i'm off for no thank you
why do the people do it though
i don't know because i be famous
but that's it's weird because on the
podcast at the end they're like if
you're interested in being on the show
and having a session with the doctor
then editor but it's like my way
to work with this specific doc she's
really good okay maybe that's it um
like the way why do people go
on doctor phil to like get
breakthrough from the national yeah what do
you mean the cash me outside girl
what do you think dr phil success
rate is on his show i don't
see the point of the show at
all
you don't think that he's earnestly trying
to help these people either law or
not anymore i do i just heard
is dr agarwal dr yeah i believe
he's a medical medical doctor okay never
did somebody say he's not that he
has no license to yeah like mike
said that
my bike shop tired shucked a fucking
by that i mean my boyfriend said
he's not
read he's not even real
he's like a computer simulation know there's
those things dr oz like i really
believe we're the matrix
yeah well that's great yeah my recommendation
little podcast recommendation yeah oh yeah paul
do you have any recommendations for any
sort of media sure um josh bell
i have another one oh good
the confession tape so whatever ever seen
this the kenosha tapes or whatever i
have i have
i'm not sorry oh lord if you
don't know the title i'm still trying
to wreck a blog didn't have anything
on netflix yeah it's in my queue
remember when we say q my list
because america is getting dumber and dumber
do you remember that when i remember
this very vividly when um you would
make a withdrawal
all at the bank and wells fargo
and then they change the button to
say get cash were also dumb yeah
i have one of those um those
ah spikes that come out at a
parking lot yeah and um you know
the sign says don't backup severe tire
damage it used to say trebles cause
cause tire damage because those things are
called trebles and then i guess people
were like i don't know what that
is you know no top now it's
just like where medieval peasants and it's
like don't back up severe tire yeah
it's like witchcraft people don't back up
so strange is going to happen i've
always hated those things they stressed me
out so much
what a back up i like well
don't i also think what if just
going over them for ya huh have
you ever actually ripped a tyre up
on one of those high ones but
i do have i don't recall the
circumstance what happened just like different late
entirely i think so yeah but it
was very early on in my driving
career did your cargo fly
and all over the place ah like
a helium balloon yes like not really
moved a regular toy balloon yes ah
no i don't recall why i did
it but it did but every toy
is the balloon
ah here i bought you some toys
kids what is it it's blue i
think you make me feel so yeah
that song yeah you you made me
want to bounce the moon just like
a toy balloon oh yeah that's true
a balloon yeah taught why is it
now like in the forties or something
was there a thing where i was
like a balloon on like a stick
where you'd like kick it or something
a balloon that you can't kick why
would you kick it isn't there was
a circle like know what i mean
it's like a hoop a hoop on
it yeah whatever i were i used
some who was not on the stick
but no use the stick to propel
this propelled oop yeah got boring so
that's my favorite vocal warm-up you
use this stick to two oh um
what what time period would you never
want to be would you never wow
so oh wait i also question like
this that i thought of for this
specific show okay um but anyway i
just wanted to run myself that when
would i not want to live
i think like in the nineteen hundred
so when would you not want one
of us don't oh no why would
my answers now for yeah
okay you'll be sorry
we'll send you over the edge um
ah i don't wanna go first oh
i mean i think anytime anytime pre
air conditioning would wow really yeah i
think win-win was invented in the twenties
or something about air conditioning really yeah
really depending on where you live i
guess but yeah but my when i
welp we didn't have it and it
was was hot as hell we just
lay there man just so you got
used to it yeah we it was
years before we got air conditioning in
my house and it was really just
like we had those we had those
foldable screens that you put in the
windows you know that they would like
not accordion with a slide with a
protect you from the l
moments or were they what was their
purpose to to let air into the
house where they're okay so so there
would be around of the house there'd
be no screen i was a window
with no screen and then you you
put the you could buy these at
the hardware store they would be um
you know like a square of screen
you pull it out and will wreck
time yeah and put it in the
window and then box fans and that's
it and it was an r
it got really hot we lived in
a house where you know an old
house and in fillion and you could
feel the heat as you walk to
the heat pushing you do decide is
that what the lyric maybe like you
i don't know you say it really
confit
thank you well i yeah i in
the middle of it i was like
should i i don't know i don't
know you made the right to say
okay good so you could feel so
bored right it was like she literally
was like going ooh
i was thinking it was
it was like walking into an upside
down pool where you could you can
that's the dream
it's like thick well i remember that
too at my house thank you love
stairs we get thicker in the air
because heat rises yeah right nasty our
air conditioning was broke this summer for
two days or something and it was
the word no i mean once you're
used to it it does really suck
yes i will say this
showing disagreement with my mother even though
she's now dead about the direction of
the fan because she would say you
turn the fan outward so it sucks
the hot air out interest i wonder
what the real funds you want on
you so you feel the breeze you'll
be like some free breeze
is pushing you to decide sam could
you turn my headphones off okay
by the way do you think she's
still disagreeing with you in hell yeah
in the hell absolutely well she was
obvious she was right
no stopping no do not pass go
rule number one yeah i don't think
are we talking about the nineteen hundreds
are we talking about anything to anytime
in history yeah i wouldn't want to
live anytime before nineteen ten probably what
happened in nineteen ten yeah what happened
to you
huh is it just culture now or
you know what i think about first
of all it's like you have to
be rich in any era before the
like forties probably to feel like i
was having a good time right because
like my american girl doll when i
was growing up samantha parking ten was
from ninety no four and she was
really rich children victorian home
and her life seemed good but then
some of my other dolls from different
periods than iraq because they had to
make their own butter yeah make their
own butter i would love it if
they made like a poor doll from
samantha's time that smelled
i thought ditch his head permanent der
yeah the perimeter club and i went
to the ten-minute boat the burberry and
my raving cool up and i went
to the tenement museum in new york
city and one lower left neat one
factoid that i thought was very interesting
it was one of the reasons and
this is in the ah nineteen twenty
these are thirty or what have you
one of the reasons that everyone wore
hats is because people were pouring out
their bedpans out of there one second
and third and on top of the
yep that's right just they've had their
big hats on they wouldn't be covered
in diarrhea
it's his new album title um it
was definitely diarrhea but that's also everywhere
that is also the reason why women
ah it was polite to have women
walk on the outside like more by
the co either street so they would
walk on the inside you would the
gentlemen would walk on the outside but
but that but that was ah for
splashes from from like carriages and it's
like all sorts of thing but i
think the pouring of it they i
bring up the duty the pouring of
the donkey i believe when that was
very common they would switch because the
man would be more likely to get
it i think then they would just
like
whole lot of things so the man
we are not the same time period
you're saying that like first manners change
first it was splashes and then it's
like alright will do i'll walk on
the outside i think so that it
was pissed and shit raining down like
okay let's switch place i think reverse
it maybe but yeah why dump it
out your window how route where else
are downstairs
like it's ten stories yeah yeah yeah
if you have your whole impoverished immigrant
family and you're all sharing one bedpan
you gotta empty really god can you
imagine way okay paul you didn't answer
the question yet when would you not
want to live ah caveman times yeah
commando
having to battle animals i think the
i think like the eighteen hundreds like
late eighteen hundred before the turn of
the century because it's an age of
some enlightenment but everything is miserable and
so and you have to get the
civil war as well if you're living
in the united states and yes so
there's still like all the social horror
that's going on
on but then on top of that
you have to wear like eight layers
of clothing everybody stinks there's no they're
yeah maybe there's everybody's stairs probably not
indoor no ma'am there's no like showers
you know what i mean so it's
it's the to me that's the worst
of everything yeah i remember the the
these books did you ever read the
great
brain series yeah when i was a
kid i was like get out yeah
okay so it was it was about
a ah a kid who was like
the smartest kid around it was set
in the early oof i guess the
early nineteen hundreds i believe
but the smartest kid around he was
he was very very skidoo around it
was the only bucket that's what he
saw
the sun by danny
oh man came over whenever you finish
a little man paulo talking sound anytime
you look to the cover
so he was he was a kid
who met her you would invent things
i believe or he would
he would hear about things like i
remember he went to school in ah
in a ah boarding school with jesuit
priests maybe or something they were mormon
was maybe they were mormon yeah oh
it was in utah yeah yeah so
they were like mormon priests and so
he brought basketball to the school and
they they had a basketball team at
one point like you he didn't invent
it but he read about it and
he
he started it anyway there was ah
the indoor toilet book was the one
that i really think about because everyone
everyone to a person in the family
was like the week we can't have
this in the house the odor will
be terrible yeah because oh everyone just
assumed like if you shit in a
in a thing and keep it in
the house
house in the odor is going to
be awful but then they then they
flushed it which is true of cats
right yeah exactly there you have cats
right i have one does it's just
shit wherever it went a box red
one shits in a box and my
dog eats it was oh if i
don't clean it in time what is
in time like
like yes three minutes no like i
should clean it every day but if
i miss a day my dog's gonna
go in there and try to eat
poop what is it about dogs taste
buds that they have more developed taste
buds so maybe poop tastes great i
don't know it's really weird that my
dog ah jumped into bed at two
am last night
like really excitedly she was sleeping in
bed so i don't know what happened
and then she just burped my face
oh so nobody went to all the
cat food i discovered in the oh
good i think she does it every
night i've been trying action was going
to set up a camera because do
you think she burps in your tits
and she burps after every meal i've
never had a dog my dog burps
like after every meal
it's so funny you didn't know that
was possible either you're gonna set up
a camera so you could show the
dog like look this is your doing
this lady yeah
i was gonna see if it was
my cat eating all of her food
at night so like maybe she gets
really hungry at night yeah maybe your
cat is starving and then but she
is yeah because the dog's been eating
it every night but i don't really
know how to stop that because if
i don't put it down on the
floor then she can't have it either
so they ah there don't cats climb
better than dogs yeah but i don't
really want to go
on the kitchen counter e because yeah
that's gross it's like having a toilet
in your house having a cat
no putting the cattle in the kitchen
count wait can i ask you guys
my question decades yeah okay what deck
if you could only listen to music
from one decade what decade would you
pick would it have to be ah
a full decade of like the like
nineteen seventy to nineteen seventy nine or
could it be a decade of your
choosing like seventy six to know
i was thinking seventy to seventy nine
nothing um and you can't listen anything
before that you can't let so so
can i ask you a question would
you have been able up to this
point to have listened to anything before
that or would you have to knowing
what you know now you would go
back to the start of your life
and then choose the decade knowing what
you know now you would and then
and then that's all you get that's
all you get okay so this point
yeah so so you would so i
guess my question i am working to
stop my head why would you
well no because a lot of music
is based on like oh wow this
is what the beatles did but like
inspired by old rhino enemy so so
if you if you could not listen
to the sixties music anymore right then
some of the stuff you would listen
to would be like insane because you
you wouldn't have that basis of no
you know
what you like i'm just saying what
era would like if we don't say
you have been able to listen to
the sexual like is you yeah and
you know everything you know okay and
then now i see you mentally okay
that's that is my question yeah but
but he got it okay but so
if you if in this
scenario where you go back to the
beginning of your life and the only
music you know is from these ten
years right
what didn't seem weird nothing would seem
weird i don't know because i think
that would be all of music that
would just be what music was no
no well it had it would have
to be with whatever is released in
in those that day yeah right so
but you would get that no matter
when your born or whatever you in
your mind that's all music
you get to listen to is from
whatever and but you also it doesn't
matter when you are born all of
our friends get to listen to whatever
they want yeah and you don't contact
you about new thing you never hear
about any other music got it alright
i'm locked in i'm locked into
london i've had to think about that
yeah i guess admired by those thinking
this is all the music that there
is but now going from this point
forward my friends are listening to whatever
they want yeah no one tells you
from history no one talks about you
and you don't read about it can
i also ask you to read books
about the muse
that you're interested in can i can
i ask you when you're watching television
do any songs from other decades do
they drop out like like shit to
where you're like say there's a needle
drop in the americans tv has whatever
it would have tv so i mean
you're watching tv or hear it again
you can't watch mtv right now
i mean they don't stop videos yeah
it's true you know what i mean
it's not the same as these i'm
watching i know my answer ok whoa
whoa are you okay me too it
was so simple in my mind no
fuck no and ultimately it really is
yeah it's like
on a cd or record or an
m p three it has to be
recorded between gordon and released or just
record yeah yeah no okay i'm gonna
say i'm gonna save the nineteen hundred
and seventy s okay go on and
explain yourself i believe that girl smells
spleen yourself my favorite period of music
is seventy six
six to maybe eighty three but you
basically said in your exe write what
you wish you could but but ah
i think if you if you had
to pick a decade the seventy s
have such a good breadth of styles
of music you have like americana you
a full rock you have ah funk
you have disco you have the beginning
of punk
ah before you know you have new
wave before it gets really bad so
i think you have like all of
stevie wonder practically yeah you know so
much great stuff in in the seventies
even though some of my favorite songs
ever from the eighties um i would
pick the i picked the seventies i
like that answer i would pick the
seventy s
i was thinking for the same reason
because there's such a there's such a
wide variety of styles you also have
people for older artists that are still
alive at that time and still recording
sinatra and dean martin and those people
they're not making great records then but
they save his junior i think was
still sammy davis jr is doing okay
like some of them were making like
elevator music style
yeah absolutely absolutely you know like anything
post sixty eight for sinatra's kind of
kind of bad but but yeah alright
well sorry no no no no no
no my interest bad no no no
my answer is the sixties oh that's
because most of my favorite music is
from then so i'd be satisfied by
only listening to that so your favorite
music is like summer of love like
like um joni mitchell but see then
it goes into the seventy seventy two
or so hold on hey birdie you
think i'm told
yeah hey stevens knows that seventy is
that joni mitchell kesteven yeah john o'keefe
steven ellman i was thinking of cat
steven stevens is kinda early seventies although
he might be late seventies or late
sixties is a lot of these people
interesting maybe i'm wrong then i want
seventy s yep and then you get
but i don't like discounting shit you'd
get all of your disco i find
it annoying
you get all of the beatles you'd
get all of the beach boys not
all the beach boys you wouldn't get
cope kokomo excuse me i shall join
good cocoa like well i just shut
up
more like joke of course i had
like choke imo i thought of this
question and it was wrong with my
all my facts
look we we should take a break
about okay let's take a break da
bank data to the brakes hamilton what
to oh we'll take a break
hamilton's working too hard and his wife
is like take a break oh i
we'll go to the house by the
lake is that right before intermission yeah
i'd be perfect dick they're asking the
audience to take a break that's true
yeah um give me one break gave
me one break let's take a break
we'll be right back with this show
and we're back hey gang hey why
don't you have here kevin i love
it it says comedy bang on the
right looking at us i'm back oh
my gosh there we are the all
star i've never seen it
why don't i have hurt can we
all have one we all need yes
i wow i wind it cheng daddy
give me die one must live picture
lie do you have times when you
were a kid where you're like just
embarrassed by how you acted like rain
retrospect only one hundred percent of the
time but like i guess to your
pet
parents or whatever we were like man
i was being such a oh yes
the worst yes absolutely absolutely twenty years
well we were not well off when
i was a kid but my parents
hid it very well and you know
they were they were working class people
and we never we never wanted for
any necessities but kept a clean house
i kept a clean house um but
i fans pointed directly at the outdoors
you pointed directly at the outdoors i
had all the suits i ever needed
but i did in school pickles it's
like covered top i'm wearing the same
suit for several years for picture day
oh yeah um but who like how
often would you even wear a suit
when you're a kid you know what
i mean it's like well real once
a year i want to wear suit
all the oh did you really like
if you love my nephew like we
got him an outfit for my cousin's
wedding that was like a botha and
he
loves it so much and he got
to wear it for school pictures and
you want to work the day before
so he just wore his bow tie
to school the day before and loved
it and then he dressed up for
the picture i love you yeah yeah
so it's like toys and things like
that i remember giving my mom a
hard time because she wouldn't buy me
this thing that i wanted and so
she bought me like a less exp
expensive thing and gave that to me
and i was so it was like
thanks a lot so it's so sad
so hungry oh no and i but
i it's weird that i replay that
moment in my head so many times
it pops out of nowhere yeah and
i and i still feel bad there
are still things that i think of
every time a certain thing happens
ah that i feel bad about how
i acted for for decades like ah
i remember once at carl's junior i
was there late at night with a
friend and it was it was right
before they were closing and some guy
came up and said hey yeah do
you want some more fries and um
and i thought he was
like saying that our fries were bad
and i was like yeah these actually
are kind of cold that you gave
them to his kinda cold and he
was just saying he had a whole
bunch of fries like left that they
were gonna toss or whatever and i
turned it into like yeah i think
ah fry you know please because you
failed you know and now i cannot
go to carl's junior without and eat
those
fries without thinking of that day oh
i feel bad yeah i go up
to the counter you say these fries
were delicious
don't do this when i give my
compliments forfeiture is the may i say
a little shit like now you're an
asshole for whatever reason
ah my mom one time pulled me
out of school for a surprise thing
and it was like they were going
on a surprise adventure and whatever and
i was like really really excited i
was in second grade it was maybe
i guess the the american girl store
is only out here was no yeah
we didn't have that yeah but we
had um i guess i might have
thought
i don't know if i thought we're
going to like amusement park or i
don't know i didn't i have no
idea what i thought but then she
took my spade it was did we
do a cat show which is really
funny that you said yeah yeah wow
but i love cats
gary the cat show and shows something
cool yeah but i was pissed and
i was so mean i was like
why i don't want to go here
oh this is awful you know and
then we went and i was like
fun or whatever but like she never
let me live it down that i
was so rude because he was so
happy about the surprise right um but
but it's gonna be taken out of
school yeah the best thing yeah but
it's also something that you guys talked
about after that and you probably were
like i'm sorry mom yes great yeah
like oh in my family we would
do i would just be a jerk
and we would never discuss yeah yeah
on your story paul yeah about the
getting sort of like second rate things
i remember when i was a kid
um we went to buster brown and
every forgot about us
yeah buster brown shoe store i don't
know if you remember but they had
the thing that would that you would
stand on a wood x-ray your feet
and you would see the bones in
your knee oh neat but also i
read a banker yeah they like discontinue
to like anyone just hops out as
many times a day as you want
it's insane the radiation levels coming off
of it you get foot cancer yeah
um but um
they have these they have these shoes
called sharpies um and earn yeah they
were they were jaws jaws and sharpies
and um all the all the guys
at school had jaws and this is
nineteen seventy seven when jaws came out
right and what these shoes look like
they were brown ah and like yeah
they had they had a kart
attune shark on them like cool and
every every kid at school had them
sure and so i went and my
my mom was like these are more
expensive than other shoes i don't know
if we can afford them i was
like i have to have them everyone
at school has them please we went
to buster brown i got a fitted
for the
shoes and they um when i was
a kid i had very narrow feet
and they were like i think that
you're not going to be able to
fill out the jaws but you know
what we can just put you in
the sharpies which were the women's sizes
and they're the exact same shoe and
no one will know and i was
like yeah oh okay that sounds good
to me
um yeah like rationalizing like yeah no
one will know okay cool so i
bought him i was very proud i
get to school the next day within
two minutes some goes you're wearing ladies
shoes how do they know because they're
slightly different or something like the salesman
blowingly shit and so i guess i
came home and i i put them
in the box and
i hid them under my bed yeah
and i was like i lost my
shoe who's ah and my mom's like
they're right there and
and xim and she made me wear
them until they wore out oh um
under duress i guess he's mushy know
why you didn't want to wear them
probably i probably said what it was
like everyone made fun of me or
whatever and she's like i don't care
these were way more sense of the
normal shoes and you have to keep
wearing them on and then of course
i don't remember anyone ever
bringing it up ever again after first
you know three minutes it was all
a joke yeah that'll ruin anything you're
branded forever
you still have those shoes i do
i'm bronze them
huh i want to see a picture
of them yeah can you look them
up you know i was trying to
look up something the other day this
john denver record that my parents have
that we listen to over and over
and over again and it doesn't exist
not to sound like adam scott terrified
doesn't exist that's weird um ok but
speaking of narrow feet
i couldn't wear the shoes that i
really wanted to wear which were moccasins
with little jewels on them remember those
shoes yeah little gem oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah it was so cool i
want them so bad but i couldn't
wear them and that's why i wear
them all the time now wait so
you had your your feet did you
have to wear like sort of special
issues oh no i just couldn't wear
like slip on shoes because okay
they would just look off oh
they were called chas shaw oh they
were called shaw's so i can't find
a picture of the shoe here's a
poster for them
let me see the pose that's funny
though because that's how you heard jaws
and then you'd like you probably never
saw it no they you know what
i probably did know they were chas
but in my mind i probably did
know in your heart they were jaws
you know what actually now that i'm
thinking about it i didn't know it
i just wanted to say it wrong
like yeah one who i can't see
a picture of these when i went
on no i don't know but the
poster says that they were real when
you were in high school or just
growing up was your sincere from here
where your lockers outside ours were outside
yeah always thought that was when i
moved here it was like this is
like tv like i'd never heard of
that in my life
oh right because every time i see
lockers in tv they're inside now but
i guess that's because of a sound
studio oh yeah is maybe in the
movies they were always outside yeah and
like ninety s um like single cam
thing yeah um but yeah that was
like so crazy to me i couldn't
imagine i never saw it
even on television until i moved here
and and on a set and we
were i think it was mister show
and we were filming at a high
school in simi valley and that's the
first time i saw lockers outside and
i was like whoa yeah it's always
warm oak yeah yeah yeah we um
i would have this thing where i
with my desk growing up
and ah and lockers i would just
basically like throw shit in there like
whatever papers or whatever to the point
where i never would even use them
anymore because they would just be piled
high with papers and that i would
never look at for until the end
of the year when finally i cleaned
it out oh i loved organizing my
locker yeah i yeah i don't know
oh i'm trying to think of what
i had in my locker i guess
like i like the books that i
did the books that you weren't didn't
even tell ya and that's just like
you were assigned to locker outside away
from your class yeah in some random
place and so you would have to
plan out your day to like ok
i don't want to have to run
i'm back to my locker yeah so
i would just take every book that
i needed that day and carry them
to every single class and never go
to my well we did that and
i it was like really cool to
wear your backpack really low and full
like below your booty hole like well
your buddy who'll um like you'd wear
like on the lowest strap like the
lucis way the shop
this could go and it would be
like dangling down your back and like
hitting your butt basically and that was
really cool and we would carry all
our books around but it was so
heavy and this it feels like you
would yeah balance would be like oh
yeah and then they made a rule
that we weren't allowed to do that
we had to go to our lockers
and we only wanted to make this
rule like because every
rns backs were getting hurt corner lodge
debt and we had to carry our
books like you and you couldn't use
a backpack at all for you couldn't
use a backpack at all i mean
yeah what's bags are getting hurt and
you and the children are like oh
my bad bad and then they were
like you can use a rolling backpack
or nothing and then we're like we're
not using a rolly backpack and you
just all look like airlines
some people gotta make this flight i'm
a pharmaceutical pharmaceutical rep artist beautiful i
know i can do you jump all
over that scott i'm sorry i'm not
perfect you are sharp keys
oh right we need to take another
break take a break take a break
um when we come back with we're
going to have a segment does someone
have a segment
okay we're gonna we're gonna come up
with a segment ah we'll be right
back
hi we're back and um of course
on this show the show you're listening
to what you already know the name
of so why do we have to
so why would we ever say such
a name it's written on the screen
yes by the way my voices feels
kind of low and like radio d
j today just
because i'm i'm feeling a little under
the weather today so and it's very
early ironing so it sounds the same
to me as my voice sounds the
same too
i feel like i'm on some like
sexy level though like that i never
that i never get ah
you're lucky you never get to
i'm on a sexy level i ever
got ah so at this part in
the show we're one of us is
supposed to come up with a segment
and it can be anything it can
be a game it can be ah
task it can be anything we want
to do but one of us is
supposed to come up with ah that
that and ah for this episode it
was me who has come up with
something in his hi thank you um
and this is something that i'm going
to call switch it and pitch it
okay switch it and pitches all right
so ah the the person to your
right will
or will ah
paul
will name a television show okay okay
this sounds easy and then what you
have i can think of five right
now okay but it doesn't in the
hook oh man now you're nervous so
we'll we'll start with lauren naming a
television show to you paul and ah
you will then have to say
say ah the opposite every word is
the opposite title so if if she
were to say home improvement you would
say workplace destruction okay you know and
then you would have to pitch that
show to us ah the characters these
the setting what happens every week and
then you'll see if we buy
or know what a winner for the
show and the
and they have to enter actually gets
a show on so ah okay um
anything
um
so well turkeys were they so here's
my question is yeah because not every
show says like words so is it
like can you make it like the
opposite of what the show is sort
of ratios well you should i mean
you can in the pitch you like
if you were to say workplace destruction
you could say okay tim tool time
taylors so ah yeah he he finally
blows up his
garage and you know like you can
do but but when i'm saying you
say the opposite title you just like
again guy do the best you can
family matters family matters ah hey so
it's great to see you paul so
very excited of the show that you
have thanks decided to pitch
this so thank you for the water
by the way oh yeah let's a
dollar if you want give us that
oh i thought it was i assumed
it was complimentary why would you assume
it's you don't go to a restaurant
and people give you rewatch honor or
ships
what's your idea what's your idea to
say you don't have time for well
it's a ah it's a sitcom okay
okay and it's called
a title friend anti matters friend anti-matter
yes sustained it is about a group
of friends okay who are scientists oh
they are like studying almost like the
big bang theory people grown up or
something well it's it's a little different
than that because first of all though
people are grown up
but i liked that show and was
almost ready to buy it oh okay
so it's different well it's right i've
you know it's it's but it's similar
in a lot of ways because you
know the dynamics are are are a
lot of fun you have where the
characters who we there's there's four characters
there's ah rancho
rancho rancho is the chief scientist who
is an indian names that way you're
saying is the chiefs well it's open
to diverse casting oh yeah so ram
joe oh he's in charge of the
laboratory are you trying to play the
part
doing my robin williams impression from joe
if you do the whole radio laws
meter
you aren't getting much i got yours
truly it was perilously close to the
elbow but yes because why would people
applaud just at the name row rancho
oh wow isn't this one law why
isn't it so rancho is he's like
the sort of center of the show
and he's like ah every man you
know
regular guy but he's scientist who's trying
to ah use um anti-matter to explore
an alternate universe whoa so and his
friends help him with this well not
as much as you with like oh
i bet okay because his um best
friend and ah right hand lady
ah mris she is ah you know
this ah beautiful but doesn't know it
oh got to oh that's perfect she's
super hot has no idea she's no
idea ugly yeah yeah yeah but channeling
to be around yes she's constantly saying
i'm a hideous hag
and then that's always a huge laugh
because the other characters like you know
cuckoo she's crazy um
related hot huge tits and they're so
when you haven't cast it yet that's
just having casting gas to be part
of the yes and they have to
wear a tight white tank top to
the machine okay yeah white jeans oh
this is andy asked to be honored
right
that's the only so are you going
to be at the auditions i could
be we weren't expecting that but yeah
we haven't even bought it yeah sounds
like you're close to buying it well
i'm just asking some questions yeah oh
yeah i'll be at every audition and
then um then ah the oh so
rancho and and marissa have like a
will they or won't
and i love dynamic you knew they
are don't think well we'll see
so then um the other two character
midway through the first episode or yeah
it'll all be you can't tell for
the first ten minutes the first ten
minutes will there will be okay and
then just ended a lot they do
yeah great and there's like twenty minutes
important that's right oh i love yeah
yeah oh which brings in our other
characters oh uh
um careers career who is he's like
this stuffy office jerk you know you
like always buy the book and then
which book which book the good book
to oh okay yeah it's very really
idol he's extremely devout which i think
now that the country is kind of
heading more into a conservative direction with
donald trump yeah
um that this will be a popular
character because they look great although there's
much report on there at least there
is a bible loving god fearing man
who's watching these people have sex right
and enjoying it yeah dan polar opposite
of career is different pole
no there i meant um like they're
all in this way they're all polish
no they're all they hang from poles
i didn't i didn't expect to have
to explain this phrase but i've never
heard just forty just me he said
someone's very they're the complete opposite in
personality from somewhere oh okay i understand
i'm gonna start saying that
so the yeah hey lauren you're the
polar opposite of me fuck off ah
very good i'm so close to buying
this tie it up so careers stuffy
by the book
the opposite of careers is our final
character mar are served marv marv is
a real fucking slob ah he's dumb
he's fat right there she'll hate that
careers hates him but they're really good
friends and there is an episode where
they get trapped in an elevator together
anyway finding the alternate universe like beyonce
i don't wanna spoil it for you
oh okay but it happens when in
like mid two of the first episode
yes when they get to the alternate
universe yeah great um i you know
i don't think it's abide in the
room situation no but it's a bible
mark outside
okay let's talk outside
so you're gonna buy this tomorrow yeah
isn't it weird that scott walks on
two goat hooves yeah i didn't want
to say anything i thought those were
weird she's a descendant of pan oh
i thought it was maybe that you
wanted some cool shoes and your mom
got you like an off-broadway yeah alright
let's buy it yeah
a chance very great as my term
will then paul think oh it's all
okay all gives me a yeah alright
let's see let's see show title that
then someone has to come up with
the opposite of i think i've got
it great sixty minutes ah ooh
okay hi guys thank you so much
for saying hi sorry jolie nowadays the
parking oh no in fact you have
to give us some money from yeah
pay us and then we'll pay the
valet guys then you also pay the
valet guys and then you get to
write it off oh sorry that we're
late we just see worthy killing time
just not killing time you know it's
interesting
how about that is i'm here to
pitch you a show about killing time
in a way real so this will
really tie into what you've been doing
all day this is off to a
great start yeah i'm excited this is
a ah show that it's a reality
based show ah we're listening okay oh
good good yeah that ties in with
i'm gonna be speaking so that's great
ah this is a show called
ld six hundred years six hundred years
okay and provocative title you know ah
you may be wondering okay what is
this show gonna be about is it
sort of a documentary about the last
six hundred years no it's a show
that literally takes six hundred years to
watch wow um so you can now
ever finish it can binge forever or
you can finish when at the end
of six hundred years definite so does
this depend on the audience living to
be over six hundred yes i believe
with the singularity and with life expectancies
growing longer and longer eventually we're going
to transfer our consciousnesses into computers and
we're going to be
be really really bored unless there's something
to watch for that amount of time
so um what i'm proposing is obviously
we don't have the ability to ah
make the episodes six hundred years right
now um and we can't do it
as it's airing ah so i think
what i'm proposing is we
we need teams of c we need
six hundred teams making each hour at
simultaneously and when they put it together
we'll put it together and it'll last
for six hundred years smart i love
okay so it's a reality show yes
about what well oh good point it's
a reality show ah about why
what happens ah to people ah every
day he takes place in an actual
day so it's set in real time
it's kinda every day takes place in
an actual in an actual day so
not a fake day no no definitely
not it's it's like jack bauer on
steroids oh yeah so it's
like you know how jack bauer he
he twenty four big hit yeah he
gave our he twenty four he twenty
four big cars twenty four okay twenty
four big hit you know you like
you like you like jack bauer he's
twenty four big hit you look like
so
so but why not twenty five hey
why not why not check bar twenty
five wow what are twenty five whoa
this snigger hit six hundred years jack
bauer six hundred years yes it stars
jack bauer if you're asking okay
but it's a reality show
a real jack bauer will be weird
we're gonna we're gonna go through the
phonebook and we're gonna find every person
named jack bauer okay the phone book
alright scott lee stop you there um
because this does sound a joking um
so no no you're i'm not gonna
let me let me stop you here
yes okay what were you gonna say
thank you so the first
season is six hundred years one episode
the second the first episode the first
episode is six hundred years yeah each
each season is how many episodes total
would you like we're gonna do like
netflix kinda like ten or thirteen you
know real shortened season
sort of like british television you know
where people can really wrap their minds
around so it could be like six
thousand years yeah it's probably going to
be about six thousand years yeah alright
and jack bauer jack bauer he'll put
his brain into ah into a computer
he twenty four big hit
honestly that's all i need he's twenty
four bigot yeah is your right you
know when you're right you're right i'm
buying it oh let me ask this
yeah can we call it jack bauer
twenty four bigot alright fine well alright
i did wow the other room let's
go downstairs room oh gosh
alright now it's my turn come on
now my turn my turn to come
up with something for lauren um alright
here we go i'm preparing ships
okay okay hey you guys i um
i'm so delighted to be thanks for
coming early yeah i'm always early i
know five forty five am is a
weird time to pitch something but yeah
well it is a little weird i
was wondering um if you typically do
that yeah um you know we like
to work sort of we don't we
don't like to hit traffic when we
come into the
i'll be home by noon it did
make it really easy to get yeah
yeah pitch today yeah wow okay because
the last thing we're doing today we're
on our way out wow sorry we're
a little antsy and looking at the
clock know i i'll try to get
through this quickly um so my idea
is a show and it's called potato
good start oh potatoes why
it's called potatoes camo whole potatoes camas
coma whole potatoes couple pertains that's interesting
is it sort of like a chips
situation is but it's so this is
an acronym it's the pair yeah what's
stand for it stands for people over
the
age that
originally
um run exists people over the age
that originally exists sometimes sometimes kombucha ma
women
however women however only so another colony
live eternally and then the first part
then the first part again interesting so
so people over the age originally originally
exist winning
women women however however only live turn
only live really interesting so this is
about existence itself yeah so it's really
um just like a nerd situation no
one ever really dies like a barrel
type thing um yeah if that's something
you're interested in it can definitely be
our nerds in it yes like big
bang theory there's
one yeah there's one nerd but adults
um so it takes to basically what
it is is it's um a bunch
of cops and they're the original cops
so it's ah is cops an acronym
as well yes it is ah can't
only perpetrate
strangers go oh that's guys true a
good tip for copy it is yeah
yeah yeah sometimes you have to arrest
someone you know you can't that's gonna
be an uncomfortable situation and that's part
of what we're getting into so it's
really for dramas old old original cops
the original comics for people who were
ever police and they're still doing okay
adding they
and are they there or what time
is it said in its time of
day it's set at noon every episode
i loot i love that yeah i
love that you were home watching tv
when they're always on their luxury bed
and the capture was on lunch so
they're off duty but something will happen
and they'll realize they'll have to step
in so um so they're primarily off
duty unless they witnessed a crime and
then they have to go no one
alright job
wow what a great job that sounds
yeah that sounds great job of such
great jack is jack bauer involved in
this ah tahini for twenty four tb
in it yes
um you know and so it's about
a group and there's ten of them
and they all link arms and walk
around town together and they go and
have lunch wow of course they have
doughnut they link arms walking around down
unless they witness a crime or do
they then arrest the perpetrators so then
they start and create a circle around
the bad guy oh until they intimidate
him into putting on his own hand
cuff so walking around town straight-line yeah
think dorms then they complete the circle
yes okay god now do people refer
to them on the show as potatoes
whole potatoes
we never hear that word ever which
one potatoes p they will say hold
because it just is a word to
use more often right like like hey
fill my holes yeah or sticking it
in the hole
yeah yeah that's actually comfortable in this
media yeah um you know yeah fill
my holes w h o l yes
yeah that's
that's right so whatever it takes to
sell it here is fine um so
yeah fill your holes i hope that
happens to both um ah new bless
you bless you um and produced by
it here but is there a season
long arc ah yeah there's a season
long arc of the arc is basically
that one carrick
actor you'll find his name is mcgough
he um is he a human ever
see some sort of crime dog cheese
or crime potato well um he's half
human half dog which have to see
a dog ah the year the ear
half how big are these years so
no
oh so basically the two outsides of
his body are dog the two outside
stuff is like the apollo nice oh
i see okay so chocolate ten vanilla
rod section human section dogs actually oh
okay so hume yeah got it okay
interesting i like him but but side
by side as opposed to front middle
so it's weight
so the nose is human you cut
him down the center um it will
be exactly the same as what you
see on the outside i see so
nose human belly button human genitals human
he's got a human penis um but
he's been neutered really okay because that
the dog sex
fans of him would not be able
to control his human penis he basically
had one child with a dog who
was three parts dog and he made
out of three grof the call waiting
o show that mcgough is mcgraw's father
yeah okay god oh right oh okay
oh right okay okay so i yeah
i don't have to get your holes
filled are you guys gonna find this
or no okay no i'm not interested
not sure i think it's something i
said or just the whole pitch well
i when we said that sexy thing
about getting your holes filled we kind
of expected this to devolve into i
mean it's the last pitch of the
day and we kind of thought that
something would happen i'm also worried we're
never gonna get the right demographic
yeah that's a big part of it
yeah okay and it's so inherent to
the pitch yeah no i don't think
kind of throw it in there at
the last second i i know it's
got to be part of it in
marina such a big part of it
and how do you know you haven't
discussed i we have the same brain
yeah we share our brain they should
make a show about us we should
make a show about us oh
do it are you thinking that you
think a show about
of course i am we have the
same raid
and that's how you got away switch
it and pitch it oh it's fun
oh hi segment scott egg oh alright
well that's we're just about wrapping it
up here that's about that's the one
that was fine univers show everyone i
think should go
get one wish to go okay okay
what's your word ah like a wish
for can be but i'm not going
to tell you what your wishes here's
my wish okay
i wish
that everyone listening to this
will know love
just once will only once
and if they break up with you
if you already have no memory that
you you're done i wish that everyone
listening to this will know the feeling
of someone putting their hands on your
cheeks just one
do they do they smash him they
slap them
wait so you actually ever get slapped
in the face i mean that is
someone putting your hands on your cheeks
i wish i were a little bit
taller were baller
wish you had a girl no okay
okay
are you enjoying it it's a double
wish but do i get it both
can i have both do well to
forget about jack bauer he twenty four
or e bay you like you like
okay we'll see exact bike
a this has been an era with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com