three
ah
ah oh yeah whoo oh yeah who
was the first person to do a
vocal run like that until people lose
their mind okay the song's over you
shouldn't be doing that
because singing used to be like this
ah i've got a flaw before oh
well to take my name and going
even further back do you think caveman
sang yeah yeah you think for sure
they did three hours yeah wow the
why don't even think why do we
think they rented why did we make
why why why do
we put that gravelly grown on there
we know as they sounded like
three was another video of the what
king tut sounded like
was there a jesus one to that
video so funny as i love to
every airways thing though
hi i'm kim
it was so funny but if you
need a video where they they have
the caveman skull and they tried to
determine what the voice was sound like
and so they have this like vocal
expertise dude or whatever they're saying okay
now it pitched higher than like i
feel i'm pronunciation british too
it's
are you playing your game
oh
so yeah he asks them to to
pitch their their the person the anthropologist
is looking to the skull and saying
it's like somebody who's like a linguist
and knows some souls and how yes
like here's how would you know reverberate
throughout the scholar whatever and so this
guy that's good at um you know
duplicating sounds ah i guess
she's just like an actor you know
is able but he's like very provisioned
with his voice is is following the
the instructions and he's just saying one
two three and then adding in the
adjustments as they're giving it to and
eventually john like come
and that's what jason that's all caveman
sounded yeah
hey everyone i drew on the one
two three so there should be some
bandit samples that as the intro to
their song there should be any bans
the sample yes this should be eight
hundred the sample that there's to be
nine minutes and i think all banjo
sampler if nobody samples by tomorrow they
just topping a band
music has ended
good tasks ravi in an edict issued
by lauren lamkin no bands have taken
up the challenge um hey everyone welcome
to freedom my name is scott my
name is lauren my name is paul
that's right that's what your names are
yeah i was wondering it's been so
long what is the longest you've gone
not knowing somebody's name
you would see rose so many decades
yeah very long i there's one person
in particular that i think of that
i started seeing when i first got
into comedy and i know he must
to come up to me and introduced
himself at one point and then it's
just like it would be very rude
to ask anyone what is asked for
decades now yeah it's so
weird when it goes that long and
you don't even overhear it from somebody
oh yes never said yeah yeah i've
definitely got a few of those yeah
too afraid to ask yeah i'm not
one of them write your name
is we don't listen for thinking okay
is his name is his name dale
dalen
one two three i like pretty sure
it's something like that okay you don't
know either no i've never known one
my toe three says something at the
start of the show every time yeah
but i don't i tune out if
they know i think it's dale
taylor okay hey guys what do you
guys ah are you nothing jalen
wait
what did you go easy that see
i the last time where was i
i was on a set and i
was saying paulo occasionally acts in shows
this was enacting those appearing as myself
zone after midnight oh okay and i
was i called adam and i knew
yes i'll after my i did not
catch that it's technically called at sturman
that's right oh
okay term midnight yeah and i look
i used to be great with names
i never forgot a name or a
face and then just as time goes
on you just know idp i used
to never forget either yeah to know
everyone's name and their whole deal yeah
meet all the people you're ever gonna
meet by the age twenty five that's
interesting
in don't you think and then you
just cycle through them should be like
a tuesdays with morrie kind of book
yes in one way you should meet
everyone you're ever going to meet by
the age of twenty five and that's
a book about how to live your
life so fast and people would be
clamouring will go into the paper back
then it will go into many post
transform it to p ooh
wait are you an actual ghost yeah
oh no how did you die all
in between the last episode ah boredom
yeah we didn't even pick you up
off the ground because i missed my
friends ah nice baby so oh so
the thing about there are there are
certain situations where maybe you see the
same group of people every month or
something sure situations like that it's like
tj
just long enough where it's like i've
forgotten everybody's name that i met right
and spend a day with them had
a great time miss maybe i never
expected to see them again and my
my brain just deleted those files here
you don't need that kind of thing
i took a pottery class recently right
tell us everything congratulations thanks i'm really
cultured you make anything i did but
here's what i did
is i was saying everybody's name all
day long on the set oh okay
tom cruise every exactly my old scene
but it does work when you say
actually what they tell you is when
you meet someone you should say their
name back to them because that actually
was a lie yeah mention your brain
yes if he don't say it out
loud you're really not giving yourself much
but i think everyone you
talked to you have to assume you're
never going to talk to them ever
again see i think only i think
on a set everyone should have name
tags and i don't mean that in
it i think so choose helpful we
should've done a bazillion and it was
great yeah it was great because you
really just know everyone's yeah and after
all you didn't need the name talking
yeah yeah pottery class so my calorie
platters clatter
lower and took a pottery class get
on the head and fell around fodder
di di di di mau made another
bowl now i got two bowls um
it's a good song i first took
the so i'm in a little group
called class club with two other friends
of mine you're in class club i
don't know that one and we do
a different class every so often we've
done
on a cookie decorating class we did
a sewing and mending class just one
decorating class seems like you're just going
to eat the cookies so why bother
it's fun oh it's fun and they're
all one off screen mendonca hours yeah
i did a sean mendez class where
you put sean and mendez together yeah
and then what came out
and here i was like whoa
wow if you put shawn mendez came
out what came out charlie puth who's
that again charleston yes a shameless don't
you roll your eyes at me yes
i can't explain a did just respectful
child
he's your elder we and we also
did a pottery class and just a
one off and then we liked it
enough that we decided to sign up
so as me so you re upped
well so yes so the class one
of our class club members wasn't there
for the for the pottery class but
it was me and mary holland and
lauren ashley smith
ith by the way for new listeners
mary holland will never be on freedom
yeah she'll never she's mentioned a lot
she'll never be on on show because
three times the three of us if
she came whenever it was throw off
everything we may stop talking yeah maybe
paige davis eventually paige davis did we
cut her loose she wanted to come
on i think we think that really
is all right
always been massa ooh yeah sounds like
she doesn't want and it was ready
no smith she doesn't know that she
does write randy smith of the indiana
pacers he will hear from him we're
waiting to hear from him yeah yeah
so you see you re up your
pottery class and what happened so so
okay so the class might class club
is mary holland carrie barrett and me
and kerry couldn't come into powder but
we had lauren ashley smith come with
us but then we did decided you
know what let's sign up for six
weeks and lauren couldn't do it so
then we had marry and then carrying
her boy
friend and then me and my husband
mike and we we took this class
and it was really fun it was
downtown and there were different but the
kind of the thing of you know
you're seeing these people every week i
did learn everyone's name within that time
period i only know two out of
three now you know it's like that
kind of stuff
meeting the people you didn't know in
the class yeah you learned their names
because is there a lot of interaction
not really but it's a lot of
people autonomy i each other and being
like hi we know some small talk
of i learned a bit about their
history some people talk more that you
need in a class environment like that
there are some people who are going
to just talk talk to every
gone are the person next to them
yeah
i was really focused on trying to
learn this skill which how are you
as a potter now i made some
things that turned out okay but i
think my feeling was i don't care
you don't care enough to to make
them and i never want my free
time because you're allowed to go to
the studio and like practice and it
just was a lot for me to
go do that
i just didn't really have much time
and then i also just didn't really
want to everyone thinks pottery oh it's
gonna be so great you know like
lamb seen ghost oh wow like someone's
gonna come up behind me it is
really fun but i'll see a man
suck to hell they were suitable parts
i didn't like it was stuck to
hell once oh my god it's so
good it's so nasty
there's like so many steps into each
week your learning time a new step
by the way now that you're a
second mother are you like now approved
and i'll never ever talk about dick
sucking
ah in a negative light no only
positive maybe um there's so many steps
to pottery and what are the steps
take us through oh god one guy
get some play clay on the wheel
leak you get the clay you you
weigh it you weigh it you need
it out which is how the word
i can't think of right now
now and then to get all the
air bubbles out seems like too much
noise and you make you make these
like balls that are like about the
size that you want and had the
right weight and then learn by the
way is is mining cupping cupping like
hagrid balls
what about working in the shop i
don't want to wait so you are
a potter like harry potter yes oh
and the the time
and then you wedging that's when you
get all the air out of it
due to it kinda like that and
then you like oil i'd need do
all this there's so many stats oh
my shoe is like can't you just
walk into a store buy this you
could but wait so the first lesson
you enjoyed enough to take a second
lesson oh yeah well the first the
first
lesson is just you make a bowl
but they kind of like lead you
through it pretty quick like you don't
do all the steps right and they
kind of because they want to hook
you yeah and that feeling of like
late to the bowl i have they
do touch your hand in a way
that makes the thing come to life
better like it's like oh here just
touch like put a little pressure here
oh notable since and your job amaze
yeah it's really horny and then i
made this cool shit need two bowls
in the class to bowl unless i'm
a bowl master two bowls lucas over
here then i have to make the
myself you know it's kind of different
story but i did have fun there's
how many bowls you make framing and
things that i don't like yeah many
bowls did you make after the two
bowls that you made with assistance in
class i think i n
ended up i threw a couple in
the trash that were honestly no less
wasteful i was like i'm the kind
of person who will keep this for
the rest of my life right so
i better throw it in the trash
now i do not want this and
there are enough that i made that
are like usable to put some nuts
in or some balls and just super
some gonads so specialty even just drop
by your place and put their testicles
particularly easy i didn't think straight yes
so the first night met an astra
that was really good for his friend
and airstream the first week you make
a bowl and they they sort of
cut corners so you can get the
feel for it that's that's a separate
class that's like your one off class
thing
so it's a one off and then
you can sign up for them though
i would say very many here starting
from scratches if you never took that
class because they don't care if you
took that right they even save it
they don't hear you i'm so if
i understand you said that the the
first class that you do end up
making a bowl and with their assistant
and they glaze it for you but
skip they skip a bunch of yeah
steps
and then like glazing and then sure
sure we all like glazing yeah who
doesn't and then the next lesson they're
like oh you think you made a
fucking bowl guess what it's a piece
of shit you didn't know how to
wedge you don't know what you're doing
you don't know what anything is they
break away break you down you suffer
and you can just take the one-offs
classes because you leave there
when you actually know how to make
anything who cares but what i will
say is that by taking the class
one thing i learned is i like
so i like doing the activity but
i don't like listening yeah oh case
you guys haven't picked up the freedom
story
i really felt like i was at
school sometimes i was like that's the
worst part of school is feeling like
you're at school you know you're going
like i could be doing anything else
i chose this yeah and i'm wondering
why and i've looked to i've looked
into college classes just for like certain
subjects that i that i i do
and they always something to leave you
i open physically right now
they're like get out here's the ladies
locker room yeah i just do lago
we talk what does this gym class
nor i've looked into community college i
get to see like killing plug it
up plug it up could i could
i learn more about history or whatever
but then that's the fear is that
i'll just feel like i'm back at
school again where it's like i'm not
interested in this there's i think there's
two things at play here one is
it's i think it's it's very rare
to be a captivating teacher of adults
right number two i think it's very
hard for adults who don't have to
be in school anymore to to like
sit still for this shit where it's
like i don't yeah this is more
steps than i thought i liked when
they were
would set me free to do my
thing and then give notes and help
yeah what like that was all really
good so then i've said like okay
well i like reading books maybe i
could buy a book on the subject
and i'll learn more about it and
then i can't find the right book
okay you're also never going to read
the book i know um but but
they don't just die without knowing the
stuff there are some people who love
being students yeah
i love make isms autodidact no realize
love to less abraham lincoln impersonator yes
and he's really good at with the
big big head and you excuse me
for just one moment
where did that come from i don't
know
it has no connection first thought best
thought i was really racking my brain
just sounds like he loves to learn
and he's always learning something and it's
very cool and huge but even his
admirable it's great he was a little
bit like ones pottery and but he
was getting good at the autodidact himself
because somebody else was dating yeah yeah
yeah he did have a lot of
fun when he got to go by
himself and just do it but it
was you think that he's
good enough at things where like he
could just go into like a pottery
class without any teacher and by the
end of it he would have a
bowl and be like i don't know
how this happened but i made a
bowl um no it's potteries i want
tuesday
or is release specific it's amazing when
you watch the teacher because they'll just
like create something out of nothing it's
like amazing to watch people who are
really good at that but when you're
trying to make something you can fuck
it up so easily it's like you
really need someone to explain the basics
before you can i mean i think
before you can start i also took
puttering in high school we had it
at my school i did it at
a uh
um it was sort of like program
at our local playground yeah that had
like an arts program too yeah and
all i remember is making ashtrays i
made like a bunch of bathroom making
i made see no one smokes at
our house or anything like that so
it's miles oh okay oh but isn't
it weird to be like a seven
year old child and then everyone going
like here make an ass
trey yeah yeah those were the days
but those are easy because they're flat
wow get a seven year old child
to make you an alibi when you're
cheating on your wife whoa
don't go too far no i'm far
enough or i gotta hear more
but yeah i don't know i asked
trays i had one in my my
mom my mom doesn't throw away anything
either i just remember it was there
for years and years just like old
tissues and stuff yeah yeah that's weird
yeah all the garbage she should she's
gotta throw that stuff away i have
no car pottery made in high school
which
whore you gotta bring it in for
us and really get please we want
to see it i have every like
card and letter up to a certain
point i want to read all of
them and take out to a certain
age i went you don't need to
keep them all yeah i know i
it feels early cards it feels yeah
especially when like someone even if someone
writes something really nice i sit there
i look
at it i ingested i take it
in and then i'm like i have
to throw this away now otherwise it
will just sit on a desk i
don't keep a card for i still
keep many cards but i try to
show let's whittle this down have you
ever had like a box of old
stuff and you look through it and
there are things in there and you're
like i don't know what this is
or why i've kept
yeah the like a ticket that just
has ticket on like audible
like i don't fucking know no i
have like i found a lot of
today i probably talk to those college
papers that i found anything until jesus
but that's if i was like why
am i saving it but then i
didn't just get to go to allergy
because it's kind of funny to look
at it's yeah that stuff for sure
what i did the last place when
we moved out of i found a
lot of that stuff and i just
took took picks
years of it all i think i
even sent you a picture of something
that you sent to me and like
nineteen ninety five and i sent it
to you that sounds familiar yeah you
should take pictures of them print the
pictures out like the size of the
young and then like put anybody
this alright we have to take a
break
and we're back yeah i say very
quickly before we move on super fast
how quickly can you say i have
stuff i want to get into so
just i have something i want to
get to know actually don't but we
do a thing where we tried to
try to say something cost yeah to
see who could save the faculty started
oh hitler um it was like the
butcher baker candlestick maker butcher baker candlestick
maker i was slow it was so
so yeah but very
updated for sure because you'll see another
taste test is the one that genie
gives me an a card or a
nice note or something i cannot throw
to i save em yeah right i
can't do it i it to patch
some hodl it depends on how detailed
is yeah yeah if there's a whole
page written to label full size car
tldr
a friend writes me a thoughtful card
i keep it if it just says
merry christmas signed by so and so
it's in the trash oh yeah i
have a frankish myself even a friend's
card i can eventually part with but
yeah if janie i can't throw away
anything you have a couple of things
that were written to me from people
i barely know that i have kept
that i keep
should i respond to these that's the
that's right back to a christmas card
no no it's just like a nice
note that someone sent me that i'm
kind of like oh like you suppose
it could be the end of it
you know or should i respond and
that's why it's the both of these
things are just sitting on my desk
should i respond to i have over
fifteen hundred emails in my inbox yeah
see i think
you should buy
lot went back some of the earliest
ones ah twenty seventeen so how did
your inbox i can't wonder what the
earliest in my inboxes oh my god
it's whenever i go to minus twenty
twenty three there's no real your you
just don't know i mean my inbox
o inbox in bios but as unread
on my old boss what i would
i outbox
carla apparently inbox heir apparent was a
joke my friends had towhere oh absolutely
your friends out yeah for sure if
it was really specific yeah um to
my experience but then everyone knew it
apparently in this room so yes it's
a joke um it's a joke yeah
so it made the rounds they've hey
the rounds my gmail is
is very full but i delete years
at a time you delete years at
a time right yeah i'm i'm always
afraid someone's gonna get a hold of
me six years later and be like
hey remember me that i'm not going
to know who they are so i
always need to but i think refill
like refresh my memories to them like
coming out of a shadowy alley yeah
i use it's usually batman remember me
used to like to have every evil
knight search batman said remember me you'll
do up in my hand and admin
dot com i would absolutely pretend not
to know who was you know what
jenny for when you had audition in
personally it used to be then you'd
search and go oh i didn't meet
this yes and already you know that's
a lot of what i would like
yeah meat
ing people and just reminding yourself that
you've met yes yes exactly i um
yeah i now just kind of go
let's just let the dice chips fall
where they may the dice are falling
exploring the bodies hit the floor i
thought about so i went i really
wanna sit out somebody's hitting the floor
once yeah it was a beautiful can
i say one more thing
am i bleeding years of yeah celsius
to see like like you can hold
it can i also say you made
it sound like you were keeping up
to date with your email i am
but by but you're letting years accumulating
no no i've read and responded to
every email and then when they're in
my you know all male sex oh
delete years in time ago okay maybe
you're right let's just get rid of
two thousand and five and two thousand
seven yeah let's just get rid of
guys since i can't do it you
gotcha can't do it there are old
like romantic email things that i know
that i've sent you i had revisited
you know in the few years after
that whatever like look back and make
oh what did we was like a
hydra are seeing want to see that
you you are a chair you feel
like them being in your inbox is
like poisoning some i just don't care
i just don't care it's not that
i it doesn't say i'd rather save
a physical card but i also throw
those out from people like that alright
however you say i feel like
mediating ah what was i going to
say to a couples therapist i want
to set up my i've been threatening
to do this for years but set
up my twitch channel
because i do like the all the
things that you can do on twitch
and one thing i thought would be
fun and motivate me is to do
like ah maybe a weekly thing where
i just dreamed myself answering all the
emails in my inbox for deleting them
and you're gonna read out loud what
they are i will give information that
is safe
to share so say this one's coming
from someone john from montana yeah i'll
give the dates for sure you'll like
this from twenty seventeen i always got
fifty bucks i'm not going to reply
do you guys owe anyone money
like meaning a meaning like are there
people in your life there's somebody like
a friend from la even from like
two decades ago or something like that
oh probably and i ever be that
person back probably um i'm sure that's
happened i have guilt about people buying
me dinner and then me never buying
them dinner really sometimes they really don't
like that imbalance
nsw and i feel really uncomfortable depending
on the person i other times it's
fine but there's there's sometimes i don't
i don't like that
i remember feels sort of like i
owe them or something or that it
was weird that i didn't pay or
something but they offered to pay yeah
yeah my old roommate i just weird
interactions my roommate i i i definitely
paid everything you know what it boils
down to just weird like you know
roommate roundup i definitely
paid my last roommate that i ever
had was roommate roundup yeah did we
do reward network complaining that there was
restaurant roundup oh okay roommate what was
the weekday new roommate recap or you
may recount we're going to do we
started food yeah we started we got
like three inners we got we got
pretty far but then i felt but
my last one my last one i
ended up paying everything
so i'd like wipe the slate clean
but um there are things like when
i was up doing theater at a
certain theatre company and and they would
they would let you stay with like
a nice couple for like a few
weeks ah like the phone bill that
i like ran up and you know
calling my girlfriend or whatever like that
and they'd never paid you know like
skip town before paying and stuff like
that they're a little little like find
them have you ever have you ever
lent money to someone knowing i'm never
gonna see this money and oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah a meeting a mama
a black mamba woo it's poison oh
okay i guys i want to tell
you oh something else had happened oh
i know that i ally
alluded to this on our text chain
but for the listener they haven't heard
this exciting story um you've heard my
stories about finding lost dogs yes i
had a great interaction recently where i
we found a lost dog with someone
who was in hawaii and the and
the dog was being taken oh yeah
okay
yeah i acting surprised and we coaxed
the dog out and and i'm just
half listening and he was very frightened
and it was it was so good
because i'd had previously i'd had two
three rather three experiences previously on dogfighting
i had experienced i three experiences with
finding lost dogs that were the people
were new
not very generous gracious yeah two of
which were down the street and i've
talked about these on previous shows where
i've found this scared little dog outside
of this person who lives down the
street from e's house and i've knocked
on the door and i've said is
this your dog and they go ah
yeah fine and then they they grabbed
the dog and i've always been like
they need their dog privileges were sued
yes and i've always been like ok
twice to find the same dog twice
it feels like this is now your
fault because like how many times the
did you not find it that it's
exactly that's how i felt okay so
during the break in between seasons of
freedom i'm walking down the same street
i'm walking my own dogs and hollywood
boulevard i see the street of dreams
i see up non stars left yeah
right but don't step on foolery
hey mamie van doren you know like
these are the stars i'm stuffing so
anyway so i see the woman that
i've returned the dog to twice and
she is packing up her giant truck
um she's got ball and what
why did you say that and like
that
are you laughing i'm laughing because i
shouldn't have said yeah
oh she's got a big truck just
so one with a big truck she's
to the truck nuts is that what
you're talking about truck nuts sure she's
chuck cross she's truck cracks cross you
need truck crux
so she's loading up her truck and
i see behind dogs i see behind
her the dog that i've found twice
and i see this dog looking up
at her not unleash and looking up
at her quizzically and i'm thinking does
she know that dogs there is this
a situation where she's
let the dog out and he's not
he's wondered who did it yeah but
mohamed it turned out were the culprits
but it's the day let the dogs
out them then then by aha men
do you think the dog was playing
a prank on her that could have
been it yeah so i'm i'm just
i'm across the street i'm trying to
ascertain what the situation is um this
dog is looking up at her she's
not giving the dog
gg the time of day can you
describe the dog because i have a
picture of my mind what the dog
looks like he's very tiny he's brown
he's got like now and i thought
oh this is this is what i
was what you're thinking oh yeah why
do you think this you've seen it
no okay i just would you've been
visiting me in my dreams i never
you know that yeah zalmi yeah
yeah i've seen you in the corner
skulking sammy in your dreams yeah oh
when you describe the dog looking at
her all of a sudden i had
a picture of the yeah yeah so
it's just kind of looking up shoot
a black and white dog with like
ears that were like huh
huh
figures were saying that yeah they really
go well so she gets into the
truck the dog is sort of trying
to get it's her attention goes behind
the truck oh the woman starts her
truck up jesus the dog guy directly
behind the drunk off-leash i run across
the street i'm way
waving my arms with my dogs on
on my leash so the dogs are
flying all around and yes it's chaos
so i'm waving my arms to try
to get her to stop before she
runs over her dog um she is
not even looking in a rearview mirror
just say starts to go backwards then
a screech like sees me waving my
arms she gets out she
just like what and i say your
dog is directly behind your car but
what's your obsession with my funny yeah
you're about to run over your dog
she gets out and goes oh oh
my god and comes over and and
as she's going over to go pick
up her dog this dog then
like dogs white and starts to bite
my dogs this is pure cooler under
leash i'm trying i'm like trying to
get my dogs away from this dog
who is now chasing them inviting them
and she's like the the woman is
not going over and picking up her
dog because it's like she doesn't want
to get in the middle of it
or something so i gently as i
can i'm using my foot which is
my only appendage yeah too like sort
of like tap the dog back to
back it away from my dogs she
eventually goes and grabs it and is
like oh man sorry about this but
ever since we got another dog this
one's acting out
out is the dog in the yard
so no there's a squirrel that had
a huge saw something from a tree
line really okay cone pine cone maybe
we're overlooking a tree here and in
the studio sorry see a tree i
love a squirrel it's raining hard so
she she's basically saying she got another
dog and now this dog is acting
out so she has two dogs that
she's treating
really bad i did maybe i was
thing about this experience i had which
i'm sure i've told you but this
was like ten years ago i was
just driving in like how on the
west side somewhere in some random streets
but you know where like things start
to intersections crazy and busy and like
big big intersection coming up off of
some like city essential streets yeah cool
i'm just driving along in this wonder
about your country bumpkin paul oh so
there's like trucks and cars and they
go on these things and high buildings
but tall buildings taller than one story
high what work did you say cibola
city life house stimuli so you should
really see live course stimuli
and i also a perpetual state of
hygiene yes we're talking see this little
tiny baby head walking down the street
i could only see the hobby of
what of a human of a purse
a bailiff said it was like a
toddler i could see just the top
of their head from my car sounds
pretty cute just walking down the street
towards huge intersection alone
phone so i pulled this is not
an episode of old enough know this
child has not been sanctioned to do
this task and i um got out
of my car and and went and
helped this baby and walked back in
the mom was on the phone unloading
groceries in her driveway and had not
noticed that she wants to show no
reaction it was
so we're like i was like your
baby was just down the street by
the corner here and then she was
like okay and she's like grabbing groceries
i was like that's drop the grocery
easy i stuck with me forever so
you get it now if well yeah
so there's this one off yeah if
i hadn't gotten out of the car
i'm like what would have happened like
yeah so if you
one of you said not my problem
right wow can you spiderman physics baby's
day out like he's just just babies
just narrowly missing construction beams and yeah
it could have been funny crazy right
i fucking baby's day out crazy it's
a rip-off mr magoo and they won't
they won't admit it they acknowledge they
want oh my god they don't oh
my god
if they don't admit it yeah i
have to say i want this we
will have talked about this already on
another podcast but ah on my other
podcasts neighborhood listen people send in we
we read ah posts from next door
and we use them as improv you
guys both been on the show um
and sometimes we you know we encourage
people send them in if they have
an interesting one and somebody sent one
in that unfortunately turned out to be
ah
a good chunk of a sketch from
i think you should leave someone's sake
sent in a fake name not realize
it was fake oh and they didn't
realize it was oh it was the
premise of a sketch yeah exactly exactly
so you guys did improv based on
the print what ended up being the
premise of a sketch from yeah you
should yes yeah it was it it
was five hamburgers know who's
it was not but that figures into
this tale oh it was ah they're
planning a baby shower and yeah what
should we bring for the baby shower
and tim robinson is like i have
what about like ah you know a
bunch of fedoras what about um you
know i got a thousand little plastic
meatballs so what's the next door of
it all like
like my neighbor was talking about this
somebody posted in like because there's a
for sale for sale free lecture the
sale for sale if you got something
for sale so somebody said i'm selling
a thousand plastic meatballs look like a
piece of shit or whatever and you're
like reading this post like this is
too good to be true and it
turns out a way
a was too good to be true
but i like this
but then people were were saying like
how could they not know like they
quote i think you should leave all
the time it's like we we quote
one sandwich i don't remember oh my
god he admitted and fifty five years
says everything maybe i remember a sloppy
stakes so i forgot about that you
just said yeah and i don't remember
that one with me pose i remember
the high
i watched it again and i didn't
remember it and here's what brand new
to me go really fast the episodes
are fifteen minutes you're like you're not
going to or you just kind of
have like one part that sticks out
here's what i find interesting though is
is like i think it would be
interesting to watch a sketch show where
a premise is given to two different
teams yeah and you see like that
you see
how's a both write the sketch yeah
and it would be wildly different and
it would be they'd be two totally
different sketches yeah with the same premise
i think it would be really interest
which is kind of what happened here
because the guest was dhruv uday singh
and then he had to he didn't
catch it either and then he had
to come up with a reason why
this guy had these things it was
trying to sell them in the wording
of it and everything
yeah and it'll be a fun live
show yeah well it would be a
fun live show nobody steal this way
where you get the premise alive and
you have to write the sketch in
front of everyone like yeah like i
feel like no no no no including
lunch order like there's other things that
happen during the show but like people
get sent off to do that task
and when they come back and perform
it yeah yeah
or they come back from the previous
week and then you have the previous
week professor why is alive
yeah everyone lives in this classroom so
they know it all roommates yeah or
it's like okay it's improv and we're
like
nobody in profit is kind of similar
where you could like well like they
want to leave the room when you
give the team the same opening line
and then ever and then and then
and then and then and and and
and and and everybody and they do
it every have fun doing it yeah
you pay when people get hay to
get in and we'd all be rich
and worry me oh oh much little
money toys
what's a little money so it's a
little money is always flowing on my
coins that sounds like an she'll sleep
so i made so much little money
guys i gotta go back to the
dog thing and just ask yeah two
questions yeah one meeting you does yeah
why who were questioning you when you're
questioning this one who to where what
what does
does anyone i don't want to be
a narc but does anyone need to
get involved in this in this woman's
dog i don't really know what the
deal is but i know okay kind
of thing that seems like sound good
it sounds like she lives like really
carelessly careless life okay here's my other
question
i was sort of after all this
where even the dog is is is
biting my dogs i'm kind of like
if i ever see this dog again
what do i do if i do
i save this to if it's the
guy so you gotta iso know but
if the exact same thing happens and
i see this dog is about to
be run over i'm probably going to
have to go save the dog again
but it just feels like
it can't happen four times i don't
like i respect sounds like it could
i really respect the saving of dogs
on the street and i have many
friends who are passionate about this although
i'm not special there was this dog
in my neighborhood it was like just
a puppy and it was in this
just in this yard front yard with
a fence
nsw and like i could tell these
people didn't care about the style makes
me sad all i had to eat
was a ball and i was like
i'm gonna save it yeah it was
a rice krispie ball but wait that's
stealing
ah because he stole a dog i
mean i took it out of the
yard and would you know it's money
went by the snake was eating now
well food okay what shape is mashed
potatoes yeah it's a miracle yeah those
mashed potatoes you can only use ice
cream
potatoes why do they call them ice
cream slash mash potatoes again that i
didn't i i'm being dumb yes i
do i always get her sweet got
it
but i was hoping to now the
worst was it rice krispie ball which
was not the premise yeah
wait what harvest was the dog was
playing with a ball i guess and
i was dumb enough to think that
was it's food yes i liked it
i enjoy you thought it was very
clear no build there was no confusion
he gave me a little confession i
know i'm trying to protect him and
don't protect him protect me protect me
lauren you're both being protected by what
i'm saying
he got it he did a good
job god and did a good job
he did a good job we all
did a good job and i'm proud
of us yes and we can do
it and we had to do it
alright we have to take a break
and we're back oh boy are we
and man is it time for reacher
it means surely is there has hardly
ever been a time that's been more
time as sure as the earth spins
round and round it is time for
three chairs the earth spinning around around
i think it's stopped actually to stop
all day i think there's wind
i think like in the sixties oh
when we went to the moon oh
fuck that's right oh we pointed the
space laser at it and it stopped
who i didn't hear that part yeah
what we what we put in the
space laser at the moon and then
they made the earth know from the
moon that's where we kept the space
laser oh and then this guys can
we pay a three cheer sure well
i loved assures the austrians around all
link wing consider but yes this is
lawrence request but today this was originally
submitted by yoni gordon yoni gordon do
it dude
yanni gourde
alright so the way so you're all
familiar with the song by wham u
k called jitterbug no tackle jitterbug it's
called wake me up before you go
go yes a wake me up by
go go buddy man and no ego
no lickable you have people snapping their
fingers and saying jitterbug yeah man i
tell you the first time
i heard it i was confused and
then i was like i don't know
it just makes sense at first time
ever today so this is inexplicable the
second number had thought this is explicable
yep can you expect it i did
and you know what it makes the
sun shine brighter than doris day that's
right yeah so our world is better
for the fact that this song exists
the sweet sweet you know
we like to play the game capture
the bed we chose the tyrant napoleon
could have heard the song half you
would have a two words that fill
the syllable count of the word jitterbug
in the time allotted we're going around
in a circle we're going around i
would say clockwise although paul as discussed
on the show you don't quite
know what that he doesn't understand know
when we're sitting in this configuration i
do not know what clockwise meaning to
your little travel to your left
that's i don't see how you don't
know like imagined scots oh you don't
imagine scotsman night and you're three am
after midnight
oh okay watch me on cnn nine
thirty s okay
evening for you know what are you
dear three i said ah yeah i'm
supposed to be three twelve three nine
okay
i get it now you don't liar
oh okay ooh
hello hello paul gets it here and
you get that he gets it yep
okay i understand i i decided i
liked that we're doing this now this
is good we need we need the
third person and we need deescalate waiter
bug
we have to fill up twenty more
minutes slower and so you rushing us
to believe tinderbox not going to make
it go any faster possible it's possible
it's probably it's possible for a plain
country bumpkin and the prince to join
in marriage oh that's from cinderella starring
brandy
oh brandi she's a fine girls that
the rodgers and hammerstein version i don't
know well my own why should go
oh wow man up now and come
back i want a second home the
second lauren doesn't know and you understand
that she doesn't know it's not her
fault okay yeah you write code because
this good this is good this is
this a way we can keep the
show going
otherwise this might be the last episode
we come back for two episodes everyone
cheese i've never seen any of those
those televised um things that where they
not disney thing my ex girlfriend was
cinderella in this version i believe my
girlfriend yeah well prensa de roi andy
that's who i'm talking about brandy
she's a fine girl so it's not
the rodgers and hammerstein version however i
do want to google that i do
believe rodgers and hammerstein verse but she
was not to know raul law who
wished she was cinderella
what what are you talking i'm saying
i pretending that your ex girlfriend was
brandy because scott come i'm saying my
ex girlfriend was cinderella in a stage
version of the rogers and hammerstein fucking
cinderella oh now who's gonna mediate me
cinderella brandy nineteen ninety seven why was
that long ago shit
doesn't say a word about rodgers and
hammerstein okay let me let me do
a beto he does che it on
on the o doesn't right above the
name or right above the name of
what who's della cinderella's yeah rodgers and
hammerstein's cinderella yep yeah so it is
that and whitney was in that which
the fairy godmother when it's very god
but i got whoopi goldberg we got
printed at peters got bernie we got
jason alexander was the original one because
i think it was written for tv
was your girlfriend ah shut up i
just don't know okay i don't have
all the answer i mean look it
up okay rogers and hammerstein sinn der
rohe law the first version of it
i was written for television then adapted
to the stage it was originally broadcast
on
march thirty first nineteen fifty seven as
a vehicle for julie andrews whose jointly
title was julie andrews why wouldn't you
have her in it you know how
many people watched it when it was
broadcast twenty seven billion million trillion billion
billary close one hundred million people that's
so many imagining that any day watching
anything now she's us it was
subsequently remade ah in sixty five and
ninety seven the sixty five version was
lesley ann warren poe nice and then
the nineteen ninety seven version of course
brandy norwood
lesbian warren was in clue clue she
ran for senate as scarlet did she
really know i don't know this this
name sounds like sen elizabeth warren yeah
and then there was also lesley anne
down that's right she ran for i
don't remember what she did or what
she was oh it was an actress
right i hope so
that's a good life it is a
good life you make a go of
it it's a fine five even just
doing like random little facts under five
oh yeah oh yeah even wrecked and
random oh you mean micro
you got a good a good life
i had a good run all you
know so our so self-deprecating but you
have such a great career and you
have so much more fun to be
had i that's beautiful
i have had a great career i've
had a lot of fun yeah and
i guess it's like there's always the
worry of like that's over now in
fact i am gonna make a prediction
i think you're gonna get on a
show and it'll be the first
actor ever to win an oscar for
a tv show wow oh that started
out fun and then i realized oh
this guy's crazy oh you crazy fuck
you you're crazy no i think you'll
be on a show at some point
it will be a popular show guy
happens all the time i think i'll
be an old man and being on
a show that's good i think so
i'm fine with that yeah
grandpa hunting and it will be like
a june squibb situation or something like
that i'd love to be a mailchimp
squib john square and you'll yeah jon
squibb and he has squibb's were you
shot every episode should change my name
yeah to john squid
it's a good stage i think it's
been so long since i've had an
audition that the turnover has got to
be there's all new people yes i
got a new guy yeah you're just
talking change cojones squibb and johnson's axe
yes i i've spent a lot of
time shitting the boards that's why we
probably haven't met before i'm always treading
the boards this back-and-forth
there by the way speaking of ajahn
fill in the blank i was reading
a nice children's day okay that is
a segway you could really apply to
any why not reading a nice children's
book ah called ah goodnight gorilla i
don't know if you have holly loves
it great book yeah beautiful illustrations
um i looked up the author who's
peggy rachman i believe yes she's married
to john wick
oh that's crazy it is crazy i
look up a lot of authors when
i'm reading these books because i'm like
okay let me guess if they're british
or not yeah that's one of the
ones that i can usually tell from
the photo yeah but a lot of
times they aren't but they'll have mum
or something and i'm like why is
it mom canada thinking alum and kim
yeah and and massachusetts is why in
massachusetts i
i don't know interesting how mitch says
it yeah is is that when you're
saying mom or you know how they
say mum ah for ma'am
as well they said mom this mom
yes mom mom mommy now is that
just are they they say mom are
they saying ma'am but pronouncing they're saying
ma'am pronouncing mom and when that guy
says mother about his wife he means
to say mom that guy you mean
mike pence yeah oh my god
yeah honestly couldn't remember his name and
i was happy
honestly we could memory wipe ourselves the
last eight years it would be so
much fun till then we can do
the show over again i knew i
would all the stories would be new
wait oh ah no i think we're
talking about we were well we were
talking about chug mommy jitterbug massachusetts
model stitched ucits um okay well we're
talking about jitterbug we're about to play
it um originally submitted by yoni gordon
and then we we've talked about the
song how goes jitterbug we're gonna go
in a circle clockwise and we're gonna
go with me we're gonna start with
jitterbug and then we're gonna go clockwise
and we're gonna have to say things
phrases that fill up the jitter book
the meter the meter and it has
to the meter it has to work
it has to eat it has to
work and we can work and we
can do this we can work we
can do this but it has to
work and it can and it can
can i swear again newly swear but
it's not a guarantee come on we
can do it that's a guarantee yes
do it it has to work that's
up in the it has to work
okay here we go
what do we say jitterbug first we
snap for step first okay
do the book
jitterbug
jitterbug who goes first yeah jitterbug here
we go
pretty pic
rosa grants
gilman stern captain got to the hamlet
boys
parking lot
meter maid
traffic up
orange juice
no keys
diner food
go veg up
coffee mug
hot debug
hershey bar
show her she squirt
so much thanks
yeah
hershey scored to me
ah diets work
ah
butterball oh the fancy hat
dirty leg
maybe both
candied yams
date or mash
french fry
large fries yeah yeah well i'm out
ah
diet squirt after urging
real diversity is like a diet squirt
yeah so we're that's sort of the
exhibit is diet squirt squirt squirt justin
jamesport yeah that's true have a diet
squirt for the sport lovers out there
honestly anything that exists it's kind of
weird that it does scare me you
know i'm high don't do that okay
i'm sorry paul is always high during
i'm always high and i don't wanna
have a bad trip
i've never had a trip and i
tend to keep it that your high
twenty four hours a day twenty four
hours a day day so you're always
on a good trip i always ah
love being high
guys that's gonna wrap it up for
us if you want to submit a
three cheer to us and we pray
that you do oh my gosh lee
if you were ever to submit a
three-tier we would be so happy i
lay me down to sleep
okay this game mode my soul to
keep ooh nice little burp is that
a pregnant mary brady burp baba deep
doo doo mommy mama does a good
go
i should've said that what does the
baba duke when you saw him you're
like ah and he was like jitterbug
i'd love him that would still be
really scary by the way not to
be that guy but it is pronounced
baba duke baba dough is supposed to
rhyme with book yeah that was very
confusing the first time i saw it
absolutely yeah it's like what this is
a book because you want to see
oh oh oh baba baba dough go
away colby ooh baba it's supposed to
rhyme with book yeah because in the
book in the actual book it rhymes
with book yes sabah baba book probably
about three bought a book but being
bad about a bladder being made a
book but the of the bad guys
get publishing
by now but i don't like this
because it was me mister paducah here
a yeah i'm sorry to come here
the with the bob book came over
me today said ginny but
oh but if you want us to
meet three teacher here's how you do
it right to freedom usa at gmail
dot com oh two won three four
o two one three four what's up
that's from zoom will come oh what
was that boston mass right to zoom
oh the jazz yeah
you gonna zoom zoom zoom out oh
my god zoom zoom is not to
be that guy vs pronounced zoom ah
oh no not again um and also
if you want to call us occasionally
we'll take phone calls on the show
yeah not live you leave us a
voicemail yeah leaves a void to verify
that the message is lever social structure
leave your first pet's name the street
you grew up on your need to
tell me yours slut name
does your slut name is your mother's
maiden name and your last four digits
of your shows ah my slate name
is my first name and my last
name wow you slept slut i praise
you if you want to leave us
a voicemail what is that number paul
hag claims eight with some late so
easy to remember
because there are a lot of hags
in this world so many and they
all want what they want do they
want to claim things and how many
of these things do they want to
claim as many as possible eight is
a good number eight is used like
we've never tried to just say the
numbers no because whatever they were literally
like four four four five five five
five that'd be great but unfortunately tag
claims
of those people four five five five
shout out to all the hags out
there i love you and all the
things you're trying to claim you'll get
all your warty noses and yeah whatever
potions you're making so call hag claims
eight extension of assimilate and leave us
a message and maybe walls
hear him on the show who knows
maybe when i know you'll waste your
time it could happen yeah i i
would imagine there are hundreds of messages
yeah i remember reading logged in was
because we hardly ever do it i
was gonna say stranger things have happened
in real stranger things did happen that's
right we all want nice i loved
it i've never logged in someone has
and has been listening to them
if you can imagine it it's been
done yeah that's right there are there's
a parallel universe out there where everything
exists multiple parallel universe square where literally
anything that could ever possibly happen then
that anyone has ever thought of that
sounds crowded that's like what it is
here by the way we haven't we
haven't um
in the new season we haven't said
hello to our piss pigs i just
wanna say hello to the things that
have found us here we're so happy
we're so happy that you are if
you are a new listener
again we've said this before we have
to say it every time we did
not pick this now this was the
listeners of the show voted to call
themselves this yes the the the the
name for our fandom is piss pigs
and i don't know why they did
it they had a we weren't even
aware
of the election necessarily it was it
was it was a poll that we
weren't consulted on no um we've came
to it very very late and and
just at the last minute we're sort
of like oh should we really be
called this and by then it was
too late they were getting so many
emails why aren't you calling us piss
pigs please do it people were say
and i saw people were upset because
they couldn't find the voting it was
closed it was closed by then and
we had no opportunity to start ferrying
us we didn't make the poll oh
yeah somebody out there made the poll
but we are bound by it's results
i mean if that's what they because
we love our listeners better than we
love or so tell what exactly so
this pigs it is they all feel
like fans or it's people trying to
die
identify that there are more than that
yeah yeah yeah your participants yeah so
we love all of you and um
we will see you on the next
episode of threesome which is approximately one
week away yeah it's been it will
be
jitterbug goodbye my jitterbug