three
oh
oh um
name of the show that were on
anyone
do you need any news
picks three of the name of two
of those low but limited but whatever
they would do one of your raps
gone okay i'm wrapping and wrapping
mean the show was the same with
the dough but if anybody whenever they'll
say well wait a minute
okay i won't go into the box
office excuse me yeah yes sir now
i'd like to ticket price refunded please
the whole ticket price yes oh wait
the price that we were you on
stage
oh i get it again okay years
old yeah let me here's all my
money
now let me on that stage okay
come on up here sir freedom is
no rappers hey everybody's temperature rep is
about avenue but if he did ruby
but excuse me i want my money
back you know what you're right here
okay and here's some range
she's on her phone
ah already and done
hey everyone welcome to three dollar shower
laurence on her phone i vowed to
never pick it up again i vow
didn't have a pick up the phone
again i am not a phone user
no pickup upvote learn was doing the
j f k voice and the um
yeah and they should not a crook
these combined every president in one and
be a super president that'll be easier
to they don't wind up to vote
we know we would just go last
guy is every president combined all four
from every president so im would it
be
all forty five of them that's right
i don't consider the forty sixth
biden biden she's not a real president
brandon um duck brandon wood every president
combined be a very tall thing or
like a big blow would have to
be tall like lincoln i picture babb
like yeah head don't mean it's all
of them it's mainly ahead with like
a meaning like like a giant like
all this godzilla size thing yes like
a body
comprised of all of their guys so
different where their body is you know
if you're really making it like a
character they're all basically the same arms
torso legs yeah to be president regular
so honestly i'm not regular restore legs
well my torso looks different because it
has tits on it
haven't yet seen a female president and
yeah we are going to talk about
that today
well i hope when there's a female
president we just talk about her tits
well you know it's gotta be a
point of conversation because we've never discussed
it with them on her tits
butter tip nails but it's hey butter
tales your present day butter chips she's
stunning she's perfect from head to toe
her tits are disgusting they aren't this
she is the most attractive one ever
saw shit
so restful she's picked it i think
it would have to be a regular
sized human with the qualities of every
present always quality stovepipe hats quality
that's something
i think i see like tag gritty
not able to tell a lie yeah
yeah yeah cherry triac wouldn't teeth one
in t no no let's talk about
that with you let's say you had
to get all your base weight in
the amish community sure they will preemptively
remove all of your teeth and give
you a lauren this has been a
long
rome springer are you gonna go back
or nah yeah i'm thinking no because
i love five seasons of this show
i love math i'm not going back
neff too much we don't have it
they're just take some meth mouth you
do let me just say what i'm
playing let me just say we don't
have mountain we don't remember the cows
don't make that out of their pussies
yeah that's true can't argue they don't
tell argue now i'm thinking but that
kid listened to this with his mom
anyway huh
okay but i was gonna say in
the amish community as they will and
i watched a video regular know breaking
amish the yeah yeah yeah reality show
junkie well yeah where ah it was
really great it's a bunch of these
teens that they're following going on their
rum springs and so forth but they
would were preemptively remove there
teeth sometimes because they don't deal with
dental care and yeah them dentures i
chop off my arm so i don't
have to like break one yeah it
is smart but this poor teen girl
enters know t o let me get
an introduction okay you disgusting fuck wad
who does this one of the homage
apple does an amish thing an amish
dentist so they're not listening to this
to correct me so i can say
it but they they why can't they
have dental care because of drugs it's
ah nova spencer to be navy but
they like they like barn raising so
much they're like let's make everything would
like that so i really don't know
they take up those extent she ever
said this you wouldn't
the teeth well it came off coming
from there but the but the the
interest don't always fit perfectly and they
have issues with their gums and they
of course that's going to be the
good where do they get the inchers
look if your ex amish you want
to write in call us ah i
concur guide claims eight dot com yeah
please i would love your on your
rums former amish this yeah take one
day off so it must be exhausting
most people gotta be so the but
even just putting on a jacket with
all the books and i figured here
sometimes i think
you have to spend all my money
on spirit gum
when fully my system when
in our culture typically senior citizens who
have dentures sure
when does that become the thing where
like do you transfer into some ditch
do you crossover like you do then
pull all your teeth and just do
i'm like when does that because like
my grandma had interest but i wasn't
really aware of that right and then
they would just slip sometimes i never
saw them no no no it was
only when she would always be when
like i think near the end of
her life that i was aware that
she had dentures but it was like
i last thing she was
through
yeah there's for me by far really
think about it but i'm like i'm
sure many people who are ninety have
dentures but like my dad dentures when
did so what my question is when
do you go from regular t to
be like let's just call it and
just go to denver let's get em
all let's get em all out um
i don't know and i imagine it's
it's the amount of teeth that can
be preserved because he did not like
have a full set of dentures it
was like they fit in between other
yeah that already exists yeah well he
i think he had i think he
had back teeth but he didn't have
any more front teeth because they got
too weak or something yeah yeah that's
so sad because i think the teeth
can
the infection can whatever can the rums
i don't believe in god is because
like if there was a god he
would make teeth last forever so why
are there why do we get rid
of baby teeth and then suddenly we
have adult it's like too confusing i'm
a little mad at you because i
asked you to let me guess why
you don't believe in god i'm so
sorry spoilers and we've been saying for
a year i felt like i was
really close to he was getting really
it was kind of twenty questions times
yeah well what did you narrow it
down to i narrowed it down to
why do we have nightmares but it
seems unfair it's we just sleep can
we have just like pleasant dreams yeah
we always say sweet dreams yes right
before bedtime to each other and the
platypus oh yeah the plot was like
what's the point it's a weird combo
skills extinct it but it's not it
should be
b what's the deal with ants like
we don't need a question we don't
i think we do know we do
yeah here's humans don't i know but
here's what everyone says ants bees all
this shit they're always like well we
need because they kill the other thing
let's exterminate them all and though it
looks not so neat for something to
kill the other
thing well yes i've long said we
should be developing synthetic bugs yes don't
leave us alone yes but ai controlled
take care of everything they're supposed to
do he is yeah scream that on
street corners yeah it's like sign a
little tiny mechanical bugs they're like rooibos
the cleanup effort yeah yeah we will
have oh no we're saying different things
oh wait
i'm saying i'm saying replace the bugs
that bother us with robot bugs that's
what i'm saying but not to clean
our homes know not to click i'm
saying they're like rooibos but something raw
they're like room boss that that cleanup
your other mechanical bugs that are bugged
you know the ones that they're like
if ants kill whatever yeah there was
all happening in my house sure you
do know i don't want rising ecosystem
here i want to sell you some
bugs exactly i want i don't want
to see the ecosystem what's it gonna
take to get some bugs in your
house while ankle bugs i sell you
i already have all the bugs that
live in my eyebrows and whatever this
is crazy that you have bugs all
over your face oh i don't respect
that you know
yeah and i respect that belief they're
they're they're they're better sucking my way
your face right there micro mites and
anytime you like kiss another person you're
eating their bugs that's
so don't guess anyway okay now you
took science class from a seven year
old sekera sure
i thought one started on every episode
you're eating their bugs when aids a
bug so that somebody's face so you
get the of all the bugs that
they have if a girl puts her
hand on your p than you she
gets pregnant we should introduce ourselves it's
ten minutes into yes please allow me
to introduce ourselves my name is paul
f tompkins my name is lauren
guess and my name is scott ackerman
this is threesome you know what it
is you love it ma come on
guys you go with this john q
public that's like a ticket for god
so loved the world he gave his
only begotten son yeah that's sort of
the bible that shot through sixty i'm
sorry
yeah
is that just like a john doe
thing no john doe is someone that
is anonymous let's john q public that
was like the average term for yeah
the people at large joel lunch pail
it's it's actually i i don't think
it's the average person i think it's
like a collection of john q public
is everyone oh the public yeah the
tickets john
q public junkie public joke you public
grandma
oh my god dude
joe public group huh
open a group huh
then i pull your heart out of
your shit
kind of wish you was oh i
don't want it anymore it's me you're
too much too much love no i
have a heart attack no yeah
going the doctor i have a heart
attack okay tell you about this doctor
i went to charities oh god i'll
tell you about somebody how many mean
oh shit i don't have one okay
you know how a year and a
half ago over a year and a
year and a half a urine a
year and a half junkie public mba
it's really his own language you know
esperanto law
oh duca said says gonna do do
do command on seinfeld of course so
a year and a half ago i
broke my foot playing pickleball that was
tough previously on three of them those
tough previous antietam wow huh i'm looking
foolish trying to play this little dumb
game we're gonna continue pick a blogger
you know i gotta keep
trying let me dig the dog foot
um we even we went to the
hollywood bowl when i had the broken
foot and diorio oh wow right you're
walking around on it squirrel hill what
did you see steve martin yeah yeah
sure yeah um so anyway i broke
my foot i was in the walking
boot during the entire scary
no i was in the walking boot
and then i got it off right
before the tour and i was in
a a brace for the entire tour
then that's turn of the walking boot
yeah return of the argument and then
um and i was in physical therapy
and stuff okay so let's get physical
physical so i've had this issue with
it the entire time where anytime i
i point my toe as if not
like i'm doing ballet doing ballet exactly
and during the physical therapy oh i
knew you'd like to show up oh
it's over there yeah my feet are
like basically pointing with your head is
rude walking downstairs or climbing lower stairs
will trigger it but i would feel
the nerve on top of my foot
twinge huh and so for a year
and a half i've been going to
this ah podiatrist or foot doctor and
i've been saying you know thanks for
translating because i had no clue what
a podiatrist was this thing he doesn't
call himself a tigris so
it doesn't rabbah
because yourself a junkie oh like roomba
these devil words
so
so i've been describing these symptoms and
you'll see like well it'll go away
that's good it'll it'll go away after
time and then he would prescribe me
like this early eighteen when you're dead
yeah yeah yeah see hc cream and
social yes come on i would get
let's get high
ok so it just has never gone
away so he said ok you know
let's go to this other doctor and
get a nerve test i was like
okay and i scheduled it didn't think
about it at all i was just
like i'm going to this doctor what
does it oh it's a nerve test
i get to the doctor he's like
so do you know
what's happening today no i know he
goes you didn't look up what you're
going to be doing oh come on
these motherfuckers i'm sorry tell us not
to look anything up i know they
do yes doctors are always like don't
google yeah because you connect your phone
yeah unplug your motor hutch crass yeah
he's
like you didn't you didn't look it
up you don't know what you're what's
happening i'm like no i'm starting to
get really nervous i'm like no what
are we doing he's like well we're
doing a nerve test um he's like
ok well you know reactions to this
can be either very mild or you
can be writhing around the floor in
pain so god
ah you know ah we'll see what
happens with you um but basically i'm
going to be attaching these electrodes to
your legs and foot and then i'm
going to be sticking needles into your
feet and did he say writhing around
on the floor in pain something to
that effect okay so you pictured at
least yeah yeah i'm going to be
sticking these these needles
into your foot and activating the nerves
um like their electric shocks and i
was like oh okay um k and
ah so i got this i see
your credentials please
you didn't look up what i'm doing
so crazy poke yeah but when he's
new to zoom battery i suppose i'm
gonna jump your punk ass noodle so
so he put a bunch of noodles
in my veins
put the noodles in my veins i
went to the pasta
so he he started doing it and
thankfully i think because in physical therapy
one of the things they were doing
to try to cure this was wrapping
my leg up in this thing that
would ah give me electric shocks and
you would turn it up as far
as you could take so you can
lose weight in your foot yeah i'm
sort of remembering
one hundred fresh shade is fresh high
this noodles in the vein
charlie yeah man i do fasciitis whatever
they would they did some electrode thing
on my feet right that would be
like something sound so you would turn
it they would say yeah this is
going to be fifteen minutes turned up
as high as you can in order
where you can still take it for
fifteen minutes right so i would turn
up as high as good yes i
think because of that he's basically like
sticking the
the needle on my thing and making
my nerve go boop yeah and then
making a needle in your thing yeah
and that sound my needle that is
that too so you tell the difference
is that to see which nerve is
being activated the pain you're feeling also
he's he's he's sticking a needle in
it and and hearing like
like the the echoes in it and
stuff like maybe like ah like literally
he was like a dolphin it's like
connected to a computer with like these
sine waves and stuff and it's it's
like going oh huh and so that's
your foot noise yeah you so he's
trying to figure out which nerve
is the problem right and so he
does all this and he goes alright
well go back to your i'll send
the real ride around i didn't i
was fine i liked literally just did
he seem disappointed it would make spasm
yeah i think he was yeah he
wanted to be like oh dog
cheers guy go back to your little
house yeah i presume you allows for
a little tough guy
so i was fine i was just
like didn't make any noise and just
was like oh this is i mean
it's uncomfortably it's uncomfortable in the way
like noise of like weird that it's
happening to you because you're you're having
spasms bring um but i was fine
so then i went back to my
foot doctor and he's like these results
are inconclusive go back and get it
redone hey what the fuck
didn't that guy know that i don't
know so i went back the other
day and said you know i guess
we gotta redo it because he doesn't
know so so so he had me
redo it again but then he's like
ok i think i were gonna test
out what nerve it is um he
goes you didn't drive here did you
like it santa monica sorry
well yes i did he is you're
not driving back though right i'm like
no arguing me in my drummer to
fuck yes i drove i drove here
so he's like well we're what we're
gonna do is we're gonna block your
nerve so you're you're driving foot is
going to be numb so i'm like
what is this nonsense so i call
my coworkers you know which foodies you're
driving foot
so you made a good point lan
driver exactly like me to make cars
for left left-footed
you make cars i go wow can
i buy one do you want to
let fuck off just for the days
where i get my nerve wow
um it's yeah this issue with before
with this fight where you couldn't drive
why i drove the whole tour yeah
you weren't supposed to yeah they said
no so so your nerve says otherwise
oh you find god okay let it
rise right you're the object of your
own misery structure that's true
so i call my coworker the baker
and she she takes an uber to
santa monica at four in the afternoon
during during rush hour drive because she
has just drive my car i understand
now yes so and and he he
injects lidocaine into my nerve nice and
trying to see if that's the one
and he's
like well just write to me tomorrow
and tell me you're you know if
it right helps send me a postcard
there's a letter it was like enclosed
one dollar
and so and by the way i'm
living my return and also into a
sticker by the way by the time
my coworker arrived i was like my
foot feels fine you didn't need to
drive here and i could have driven
home but um great so she loved
to hear that the good news is
you should really play it like oh
my little oh my fucking the good
news is that
it was the nerve because it felt
great for a felt great for about
fifteen hours and then the symptoms returned
and he's like yeah that's perfect that's
when it wore off so we found
the nerve so no this guy sounds
like he's fucking making it up as
he goes along but but what happens
next will next is there going to
put steroids in
do it and then it may go
away and if not then they block
the nerve which is like an operation
oh god and and so he goes
i go he goes can you just
take it can you just survive with
it or do you want to do
this operation i'm like well how involved
is the operation he goes you didn't
look it up because it's simple
bit but this is the i don't
like being told what is this oh
this is the this is the other
doctor remember the last operation i had
trying to remember on your balls yes
the drain your balls yeah see your
bees guys was like it's a simple
operation it's outpatient because we'll just numb
you and snip and do and it
wasn't
and it was it it was horrible
and i passed out and they got
the smelling salts and then i was
out about all the details and i
was out of it for a week
so that's it this is what i'm
afraid of is like they they they
can do an operation that blocks get
simple which is like a reset your
foot open it's a reset of the
symbol for me i was like do
they put put you out he goes
no it's just a simple
original then yeah sign me up that's
how i feel but what if it's
like this radically what they go through
your balls to get your foot oh
man i hope so why
oh my god while eating her my
story yeah so we don't have time
oh sucks let's take a break but
lauren has a very important story right
there's a finger okay
and we're back okay so i was
helping mike because he had a number
of doctor's appointments that were getting confusing
we're to go and they were texting
using different texts anyways like they're like
your apartment to the same airport in
that time we didn't know which one
was for which person so it was
like i was
i called this play he just like
wrote the word doctor
knew he was dr tom i'm not
throwing him under the bus he was
being it was it was his jesus
smart guy who just great is dumb
about this one now
he was just kidding annoying and i
was let me just call okay so
it was that type of situation so
i get on the phone with and
i call this doctor and i was
like it was the worst you know
the guy working at the front desk
and i was like
hey i'm cleaning just connect you right
to the
i was like hi i'm in surgery
what do you mean i was like
hi i'm calling to see ah i
had left a message already where i
had said i'm just calling to see
what time this appointment is for today
please call me back as he calls
me back and he's like hi ah
this is so and so from the
doctor i was like yeah agree i
was calling to see what time the
home is say he's like i've been
trying to get here hubby
and fill out some paperwork and i
go oh no i know i just
he'll he'll do that i just want
to know if this equipment's okay he
to leave right now or if it's
later and he goes oh okay we
want to talk about your thing and
i was like white and he was
like you interrupted me oh come on
now it was wow showing new wow
it was like oh
okay ali shift and then he went
on to say all the appointments today
have been canceled his appointments moved to
next week and i was like well
one was someone going to tell that
but okay and then i was like
oh he'll fill out all the forms
and then i was like i'm sorry
for interrupting you by the way and
he was like it's okay but i
was like you apologizing passive aggressive but
i could not leave and then
then we found out later his equipment
even worked his appointment was never that
was the confusion his equipment was never
at that place i mean it was
always going to be the next week
yeah but then he said all the
equipment cancelled it's next week i'm like
you're just saying that this facing luggage
it was so crazy i know but
i couldn't believe that oh yeah now
we'll just talk about your thing it
was like
oh the thing that i called you
about that you're calling me back about
you don't want to talk about for
some reason not even like ma'am you
were up to me ma'am but but
it was like it wasn't even being
rude i know but to be like
that sarcastic was so instantaneous news all
of your power in the hollywood ecosphere
to get this i'm gonna get that
guy but it was so it was
so
instantaneous that i was like this is
just how you are because like obviously
my message was what time is my
appointment you called back and tried to
not tell me that when i asked
that and then i said i just
need to know what time the appointment
is yeah you're so you're mad at
me here's the other thing doctors now
anytime you go see any doctor they
want you to fill out a million
forms before you get here and i
online and i'm like that's a new
pr
problem two new thing i look don't
give me homework before i go i
liked that claims lord yes i think
there was johnny let me play with
the clipboard i have filled things out
online and then i'm still filling things
out and yeah they want you to
fill one thousand they don't actually have
it or they didn't there's some fucking
bullshit i don't like the fill it
out and there should be no doctors
well
the system is horrible there should be
order sorted without doctors yes supporters we
have so many borders bookstores but anyway
with border it's a really horrible system
in our country that's why we need
socialized medicine yeah i'm coming around on
this yeah i think you might be
right i know after the ninetieth go
fund me that i've donated to i'm
like what is
this shit is fucking bleak man it's
just horrible so bleak don't get sick
if you're a listener don't ever get
sick yeah
hi guys anyways that's my story i
couldn't believe it i couldn't believe how
i can't believe that is a shocking
story i would my head my head
was spinning i wish i'd had the
balls to be that rude when i
worked retail yeah people would call and
be assholes but i went over but
see i wasn't even being an asshole
i was being very polite i don't
think i ever had an asshole on
the phone
oh yeah if you're calling you don't
worry like your bowling bowlers cat it
really pullers kappa yeah that's like a
swimmer's cap if i have a disease
we have swimmer's cap sobotka what does
the word i'm not so swimmers cow
you should be kept oh yeah oh
yeah yeah um yeah
mostly it was just people saying do
you have this kind of hat and
i'm trying to remember like what what's
the most specific question did you have
to know every type of hat
when they ask about certain sizes like
you do naturally know every type of
oh my god wanted to turn the
all over here over here yeah did
you actually know but every tip i
had already known it wasn't nature you
will call people call about the house
and every time i would say between
biden yeah
no but like is it was there
ever it's like a super specific call
would have been like oh you know
like an abe lincoln have like shit
like that but as for stuff like
that and you have like a jester
hat and did yeah we did wow
but they were before were they more
like it's for someone who likes to
dress like a gesture
it's ah it's a leather gesture it's
not for someone who doesn't want to
trace
all sites offer customers this is a
lifestyle yeah this is mostly nude i
have a question
this is gonna be like a daily
hat for him it's not gonna be
like yeah we needs to be durable
we just saw a lot of yeah
we had like regular hats on the
shelves and then we had costume ads
on the walls right hanging up on
the walls we got down by means
of a long stick um and we
also sold the classic ah play
plastic helmet with the beer can holders
wow beer oh that's so cool all
your hats so it was like it
was like a funny store it had
a whimsical side but you could also
get just a regular old hat there
i almost think they were doing too
much could you order i beg to
differ failure was just right if it
was just
just right if someone came in and
said like do you have this specific
hat and you didn't have it would
could you say like we're gonna get
it though to you in four weeks
or like like if you're like an
independent bookstore you're like we'll get more
ordered that specifically for you because we
love to i think it was just
based on what they had always carry
hat so that if it was just
when we had you couldn't like just
name something
and then we'd find it right it
was like if it wasn't the internet
to know it wasn't luna sweetie this
was before the computers were yeah i
so i would tell people you want
to get information superhighway
what would would you would they give
you free hats we've never talked about
this paw then this is a question
that all of our listeners have had
we talked about this store yes so
much and never have i learned what
types of hat was never drilled down
number i've been dying for a deep
dive on the store so to do
i knew someday you guys would get
overcomers
coming up the courage to yeah we're
coming we're in are coming around junkie
public new room na ah
nudism ave
a
noodles in my veiw we i we
were going to discount how much on-hand
for every ten nancy bought
i really want stores where by those
monkeys you know what what store do
you think or what place do you
think is the best forgetting like a
a really good discount on the thing
like a free service if you work
there anything involving food i mean when
i worked at free food marie calendar's
you know obviously around
round up yeah um i would go
home with like three pies that's great
but and and i thought that was
every restaurant oh that was special and
so then when i were going to
another restaurant i'd say give me three
pies
yeah wearing ski mask and free
no but when i worked at like
baker square then they would throw away
all the ah unused food in a
dumb startup that was law yes so
that unhappy people could not eat it
so grown and i was always like
well could i just take it home
they're like no because if you get
sick from this you can sue the
restaurant i was like but but but
marie calendar's three pie
yeah
your square french silk pie so good
yeah sounds good i like french so
i don't think so
from a dumpster they need it from
a locked dumpster that i break into
i love a poisonous pie a lockdown
love the legal system um that there
but this store that had in the
belfry location where i worked they had
more than one yeah oh where there
was there was one was called hats
in the belfry to know do you
think they number all the like the
j crews so you know how there's
really number two to five was one
a pair
thirty three like bats in the belfry
yeah that's the healthy there are places
that say to yeah okay man like
the there there's a bar right isn't
there but i wouldn't equate hats in
the belfry to j crew with thousand
million never been there okay thousand locations
in philadelphia alone wow was this puree
affair with the no no they i
think that were also in baltimore they
weren't they were on the east coast
what what
what do you do ah i don't
know sandra has a water like we
do and what about what they do
eater i was wondering althea okay w
o dan yan anyone would ultimately be
more water i don't know i don't
like this place disgusting to me
um so the location where i worked
this is before the other location happened
in center city which i think was
the last one in filling i think
recently closed down oh no um people
can accumulate data recently that was a
lesson long time yeah they really so
there's no no hats in the belfry
is any longer i fit in philly
i believe there are not but here's
what happened at this
location it went out of business no
not have hats and the manager yeah
not enough had ordered out of hats
the demand was to a manager at
the time said ah the stores closing
here are your paychecks take whatever you
want wow took a bunch of money
easy as hats you would really benefit
from this i and i did but
not i did everyone who worked there
love hats no cam i definitely love
that's more than anyone so how many
hats did you take i took like
half a dozen acts like a gesture
like i would tell you not take
just half a dozen sounds like more
than six it just yeah twenty
he hats half a dozen like just
a phrase i know it's like when
you say like a quarter of a
million is like that's so what it's
well it's a quarter of a lot
of things my my god a million
why are you saying half a dozen
just say just say a handful because
that size just say six no just
say five because you probably why does
why doesn't just say the number that
actually took yeah why are you lying
to us
you're passing my test which is wonderful
but then that store reopened and they
didn't have an imam shaker hats back
and you had to give him back
paul paul paul you need to be
here to see the bearcat hat we'd
be joker just took six year old
dances because you bought a twelve x
yeah you stay and i was mad
that they didn't come with beer yeah
i was like oh shut the beer
would half a dozen hats needs
a dozen beers this is not math
this mapping massive is a mathy um
i thought it was a couple of
years later the jungle boo bomb news
updates and they did what they reopened
and then eventually closed down again well
as that's unfair but why don't we
open it lasted a really long if
a place where he opens itch you
should not it should not be legal
to close its twenty twenty four and
people don't want hungary's yeah that's the
thing no one wears hats anymore because
our heads are warm from global warm
i don't you guess what year it
is without knowing
at all wait let me cover my
name here
when you're okay astra ask me what
years you know like a little bit
a little bit in your head it's
like a different year june i mean
no okay what do you mean i
guess like if it's like seventeen seven
like it's loosely twenty fourteen seventeen but
like it's actually playing twenty four seventeen
but i'm sort of like you know
like how people are always like if
you wanna feel old
tour two thousand was twenty four years
ago or whatever it's like right there's
a little bit of that where i'm
like i kind of feel like it's
not that far ago but it's it
i feel like well thomas edison is
closer to urkel the urkel bot yeah
then he was to the light bulb
that's right it makes no sense so
thomas edison was does
albert einstein was alive when pearl jam
was a band and pearled pearl jam
has been a band longer than albert
einstein was even alive pearl jam had
a secretary named einstein einstein his secretary
and pearl jam is a woman yes
and the pearl jam was a woman
the entire time was
you know what i always think it's
gonna be better was a woman i
think i think picasso's life is crazy
make so i mean i don't think
so i thought he had a very
normal border whatever the dates like he
was alive mush he made other peoples
lives interesting because we die in the
nineties now that that's what always is
interesting to me when you we died
at the premiere i'm sorry guys
he didn't the seventy s looks like
he was born and eighty one who
died in nineteen seventy three and i
just feel like that's pretty recent never
go to studio fifty four nikolai tesla
he was in kabaddi radio he was
one of the first people to see
the movie j f k yes and
he hated it it's too long too
long goodbye
you are i you i love this
movie i honestly i i would love
to do than you're killing the flower
moon i'm dying to say goodbye
guy movie goodbye
cooper cooper did you do we all
see that collision the farmer no i
did i did yeah i liked that
leonardo dicaprio was playing a guy who
is just fucking dumb like a dumb
fe and yet savvy new bad t
and t yeah the tiwi he was
amish oh if you had nice teeth
you would be like i was taking
me out on a movie
yeah okay well there's constantly imagining the
teeth back that happens all the time
yeah also he would have been too
handsome where they'd be like just go
to fiona hollywood be a movie star
yeah you know i mean i don't
think he's that handsome anymore
i feel like he isn't that weird
i mean it's like check my phone
maybe we're so good i are so
used to him like as as a
how old is he now is he's
like a middle aged fifty thousand ease
yeah he just looked for fifty let
me look for fifty looks great would
bang he's a very short change but
he always looked the same to me
anymore but he also
i was always have a uniquely handsome
i would say but i also feel
like he's one of those guys that
looks how i here's this is gonna
come back to haunt you in your
hotel and he's more yes
six feet mommy six feet um anyways
here's a doll i feel like this
is a weird theory i guess okay
but i feel like people have this
segment paul's weird theories yeah okay good
poles weird theory
e
um when i saw once upon a
time i thought you know
and i am brad pitt in that
movie i felt like oh this is
the this is ham this is the
age that he's supposed to be like
this is when it all comes together
like he look he's never not been
extremely attractive he's been attractive but he
didn't he has a depth of this
is the most attractive he's ever
yeah check em out in fight club
when shirtless fighting yes scots huh i've
seen ah thank you i stand by
my theory okay and i feel like
for leo i think you pass that
he's passed now hey i like hearing
men talk about other men's looks i
like damn man i'm talking about other
men's bodies like that we don't get
this
like us talking about okay now no
way talk to each other
hey paul i like your body
i like your body i like me
casing around your soul i like the
contours of your frame wow
wow i'm enjoying this
ah it's fine because because it's it's
preferable to us talking about women's bodies
on the show it is probably can
we today i know are allowed
this brings me to a question i
was gonna rahm is bad is ah
um
yeah said i didn't get to hoi
yeah but i don't know if it
actually works both ways but so ah
you know a lot of times men
will date younger women sure and do
end so it's hard to i guess
i will say it's hard to date
someone who's the exact same age as
you why because it's just hard to
figure out that math
well i mean they have to be
born on the birthday that you have
yeah that is very odd yards and
daytona is your exact same birthday it's
always hard it's very note i just
read this thing that jay leno like
is attracted to people who are born
on september fifth you something my birthday
september six but
fuck me i had to find this
little reason jay leno knew i read
something where jay leno was attracted to
people who were born attention listen this
is this is what it says it's
an interview it's an interview i don't
excuse me i don't know what it's
from
jalen horse made up dot com source
x twitter x whatever jay leno i
lived with five ex i've lived with
five women and every one of them
was born on the same day i
can look at a woman and go
september fifth i don't know why that
is i don't look for a woman
born september fifth i just wind up
attracted them mavis says when we met
he asked when my
birthday was and i said september fifth
he started laughing i remembered it so
clearly i said what and he said
on nothing and then jay says i
remember i had her in yeah what
the fuck that would that would concern
why do you keep this close i
wanna say everyone i date is september
fifth it just sounds yeah but you
say something yeah you'd just be like
god nothing why are you laughing my
birthday yeah
no reason i worked together for five
blocks
stay
i remember i had cathy guys wait
on the tonight show of course credit
county grandma kathy or shiny sack i
he said and i said i'm happily
married don't take this wrong i'm attracted
to you but in an odd way
we said this to her on the
show are you born are h r
are you born on or around september
outside or around
danny yeah timber fifth all right this
i don't like any now i was
every day so for me it just
makes me wonder would he be attracted
to me and an odd way jay
leno right please go to hack claims
eight dot com leave us a voicemail
would you bang laura know it's not
that he's happily married many would he
be a tract right yeah wow
on banging lori yes i want available
for such actions
b that's a great way to turn
such actually accidents my question is so
like there'll be times where a celebrity
who is somebody i grew up liking
like here's here's what i bet huh
any woman that he's attracted to comes
on the show because i'm attracted to
you when you wear your born mean
it's always like april twelfth or whatever
he's like nobody he set up didn't
we were on september fifth so he
probably says that to everyone and ninety
nine percent go no and he goes
well i'm still attracted to you
my question is so coming okay so
oh my god i know it's been
really so am i okay just jesse
okay disgusting
there are there are celebrities that i
grew up like watching and things and
admiring whatever and then they'll marry someone
who's my age where i'm like so
i could have married them you know
it's that really like and also like
when you're fourteen know like like they
marry someone my age now yeah they
made them now if you even come
before that person if you would like
kind of meh
married now yes i think you i
think we've talked about this about a
specific person you've thought that about oh
well don't bring maybe not on this
show but yeah okay i'll have to
ask you about that late al gore
but then the question is sad enough
it works the other way because it's
kind of gross either way but like
you know like you mentioned mary kate
and ashley they married people who were
older or one of
them did and then i'm like oh
well that happens the other way too
where it's like oh some like somebody
but then i guess it's gross i'm
asking it that way it's a good
idea i don't answer if you're donate
answer tony are you asking us to
marry you don't answer do you know
what here's the thing that i that
i am realising somebody asked me like
about celebrity crushes
and i have ah there's a weird
thing now where you know mentally you
have not aged in a certain way
or emotionally whatever yeah i still feel
ten i see you act like it
fuck you if i see an attractive
current attractive actress in a movie yeah
and i'm
like oh she's very attractive and i'm
like she'd find me disgusting yeah yeah
i'm old and growing too old but
kind of having a crush on this
act then if you saw that person
marry someone who's your age you go
maybe i'm not that's the thing i've
i think i think i feel bad
for them i think shoot your shot
paul
yeah we have to take a break
okay
and we're back and it's it's three
your time it truly is and this
is a special time of year it's
special time during the episodes during sounds
of episode yeah and if you would
like to send us a three-tier to
play three fears like a parlor game
and you can send it to us
at three am usa gmail dot com
tom or i mean should we open
it up to head claims eight dot
com oh no okay don't have the
same james' special leave a voicemail at
all any guys we don't want to
hear your rules you have to type
it out so this is when we
played before and it was originally submitted
by kristin kelly and never submitted by
anyone else was nice while he's
you think someone would like listen to
this show here a three-tier that we
played and submitted i thought would be
like looking into typewriters yeah and shakespeare
who shakespeare originally was a monkey with
a typewriter that was that's what we've
been trying to get he was the
one guy the one monkey in the
room who ended up making being a
chick hey guys you don't see that
one monkey in the room
you're it shakespeare was the one monkey
in the room who ended up taping
out shakespeare plays yeah but that's why
they called them shakespeare so because the
plays shakespeare
who because the plays were by shakespeare's
yeah we're gonna call you shakespeare yeah
you seem to be telling us your
name shakespeare
know what shakespeare's name we don't hear
off shakespeare's a guy think koko the
gorilla enjoyed shakespeare oh i'd like to
know more about that whole anyone enjoy
shakespeare or do we just say we
enjoy shakespeare it's a good question i
think there are some people who genuinely
rarely do
but is it it's sort of like
when you remember paul you probably have
this experience gentleman spot when you go
to the sunset five and watch an
independent comedy and everyone would be laughing
at the screen going ha ha during
any dough to prove how smart they
were yes like the brothers mcmullan
ah
um alright this was submitted by kristin
kelly and it's called rated scenes what
we're gonna do is we're going to
improvise a two minute g rated movie
scene right
might be pg who know it's g
g or pg then we're gonna different
to contain decide right now now it's
g so it's gotta be it's very
very clean squeaky clean then we're gonna
do the same scene again pg thirteen
okay then we're gonna do the same
scene again as our yeah and then
we're gonna do the same scene again
as triple x
okay triple yeah you'll see ange okay
what if we don't want to
forced to i'm available
helpful for such actions alright so ready
here we go table hi scott how
are you ding dong was the place
waiting oh what's going on i just
was wondering i feel um were interested
in playing fetch with my dog oh
that's such a cute dog i love
playing fetch with dog yeah she's a
dalmatian i just got her from the
fire station they said she was too
good
good to be a fire dog had
has she saved what does that mean
god doesn't mean she's just so sweet
and loving and she doesn't want to
work that hard i was so sleepy
when put that way what i mean
to good whose words are these two
good yours are the fire station i
guess i put the label too good
fire one of the firemen say
that she didn't help out at the
last fire and was lazy they didn't
say lazy
it's hard it's hard to blame a
dog for not helping out during a
fire do you want to play fetch
with my dog
sure you guys are my neighbors i
love your marriage i'm so happy about
how nice you are to me all
the time this is a g rated
movie i can we be married
and i would love for you to
play with my dog in the yard
what are we fetching can i ask
that um you're away there's the dog
through yesterday and were fetching you're gonna
throw a stick and my dogs don't
bring it back does the dog know
it's a game yeah she's really really
smart okay alright so where where do
we get this stick it's just
office tree have you ever i'm sorry
have you never wait whenever every time
you play fetch you break off a
branch off a tree can't you just
find it again yeah you're the weirdo
you weirdo oh um look my mom
my mom's calling me i gotta go
but but i just threw the stick
i didn't hear already come on fido
wait but that sticks over there no
wow we really missed our chance or
did we i guess we have to
get the stick ourselves should we do
it as a team sure okay and
one two three four five six
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
paces there we go hey one last
thing my mom scared me take dog
what did you get here's my next
one you ring the bell my mom
offered to share this pie with us
too good to share with my whole
family too good or too lazy
and that's it
alright a real g review raises yeah
from a great movie yeah right such
a good pg thirteen version oh so
called a perfect scene everything made sense
and move forward and it was logical
alright and pg thirteen ngo shit fuck
ding dong oh hey da but the
fucking play yeah so we already had
our one huh
i mean
players ding dong what's happening what's going
on i was wondering if you want
to play fetch with my dog oh
sure i love playing fetch with dogs
shit i don't know if i have
time shit you might be right what
do you mean you don't have time
i'm going to do some drugs soon
oh i used to play with my
dog if you're on drugs i'm gonna
do imply drugs yeah and implied sex
i like and sexes implied in this
marriage between you two and i'm so
we see your but why does just
but just
i know it's your body and available
projections poly is unavailable for such action
alright where'd you get this dog well
the firehouse just let her go because
she was too good shit shit
oh
so saying shit oh no some problems
are here oh and she violence she
hoped the l the firemen all day
long every day and they just couldn't
take it anymore oh yes
anyway you wanna play fetch with her
i guess yeah i would really like
to but hold second did the firemen
say this or you said this shit
well this shit was kind of sad
by the chairman but not in so
many words they said she left a
few are squeezing our shoes bodies behind
and a fire and she
didn't help so they had to let
her go umm alright well ah where
do so we're gonna fetch this or
where does the dog throw yeah we
don't one have your guns through the
yard and she'll go get it or
i'll throw my gun yeah alright here
we go
hey gang shit shit
she she's getting it don't worry she's
not dead from that no if that's
what you might have been think carrying
what she was dead carrying the gun
in her mouth but there's no no
no blood her effect wonderful
and that's it oh okay great alright
and now we do it rated r
rated r this c raise it on
our anger ding dong in the dalmatian
read it all
hey scott what the fuck
fuck what's wrong what's up players
hey do you know do you wanna
fuck i hope i interrupt you guys
having sexy time because you're married no
no we're just fucking around we could
do without being married yeah we have
anal sex right at the edge
we do both kinds of sodomy we
great we don't show it this is
not rated triple x no i don't
think it has to be these days
we have dicks but you can't see
them speaking of dicks maybe once you
want to throw your dick for my
dog sure here we go wow let's
all shorts
ah
oh where to get the dog oh
the fire station throughout the window those
cock suckers yeah they said she's a
bad bitch who can't help it all
so i said i'll take her i'm
i'm realising the problem is this just
hurts more yeah what else research no
difference
oh hey my mom's here she high
boys oh baked you ma this is
ding-dong it was so please can i
make it look like i'm fucking pie
that's what i want you to do
without seeing your penis though around you
will see my erect penis but yeah
it you will see like a pie
attached to my groin as if i'm
having sex with it yeah okay let's
do that okay you got me straight
to boot
i'm going home okay no we're gonna
kick by ms ding dong oh i'm
saying that's right being tongues leaving now
fuck that pie
see
alright triple x
oh we're not doing triple ah yes
we are here we go and go
you're stupid
hey fuck you yeah you are jai
paul hi we're we're fucking right i
deliver the graphic hey ding dog what's
up players i've got a pi delivery
once you get in on this i
don't have any money how am i
gonna pay for this
here so you pay suck my dogs
pp
dogs okay no zero eagles
tags from triple x does not cover
bestiality also triple x is meaningless it's
just
aaa like up ansi i mean cnn
when you don't want to do the
thing ah well thank you kristin kelly
suck my dogs
i just kind of ajar oh okay
it wasn't anything the dogs oh i'm
sorry female stood oh okay just sucking
piss with a straw the straw outside
the chili dough
alright well that's gonna do it for
the snow day buddy but remember yeah
um you can hear our premium episodes
which we call three new episodes fun
those are every other week on wednesdays
and those are exclusively at cb world
and also apple podcasts premium yeah that's
where we answer your voicemails if you
want to leave us a voicemail head
on over to hag claims eight dot
com
it's a great place to be it's
it's where oh people hang out follow
us on the socials at threesome usa
and instagram if you want to write
to us three team usa gmail and
of course on tuesdays we do our
three visiting on the twos which is
worse older episodes we take him out
from behind that paywall yeah you can
hear them
so there's a lot of freedom for
you guys and can be really great
for you guys and i hope you
guys love it so much it makes
your whole day you guys we love
you we love you take care be
very special we're not in love with
you because we're in love with each
other that's right okay take care now
tae lie okay no no no i
want the last word goodbye ever you
are
are you are the longest movie goober