um
um um um no three everybody tried
to steal my fingerprint free nobody trying
to break up my sti aid brigham
my side brake died
just stride i don't know i think
your stride i hate to man's plain
wilder too what is it
it's break my stride right motherfucker
that's what i say said motherfucker when
scott saying sti to stop stop saying
sky god did i say scott doe
i said who knows stop it scalars
shazam you please let me ask you
this first of all i'm paul f
tompkins do you think that the name
scott counts as a name
is more of a noise ah it's
a noise and i am scott aquaman
did you learn lab guess scott hates
his name he always wanted to change
it to dick butkus
but kiss the two things you want
to kiss dixon butts what if he
was kissed dick butt kiss taking but
but kristic
but first coffee
but
but first my cause dick
kiss this but hey how about i
want to ask you about this yeah
or we were all right-handed is that
correct ye yeah betcha
wow we all had a weird thing
where we held our pen like left-handers
yeah left-handed coffee mugs now this yeah
what i know of janet i don't
private i've told in your left hand
or what because you can't see the
fun exist because you can't see the
fun it makes me love because to
me it's like you
i want to be showing people so
scotch suga lauer are on notice use
out in just like
well we're both from the same place
and you're both honorary the hell so
i feel like i i don't need
to stare at the sign on the
mug that i want people to see
it look at my grandma before but
it's like at the end of the
day you left handers gotta get over
some of the shit you know although
i always think about the left-handed store
on the simpsons okay
why don't always think about it i
mean i think about how we're like
i'm only thinking about it i was
here i want to marry i have
a problem
variability
i think ah like being left-handed can
they train you to be right-handed they
try right they tried to like they
often try yeah yeah yeah but you
know why do they try isn't that
annoying it's going to stay natural tendency
was i supposed to be left-handed where
are you did you did they try
to get you to switch
hit well i they tried to get
me to hold the pen in my
right hand and i did a bad
job of it and do so to
this day i mean you're saying but
like how do i know i'd be
good with my left hand let's try
it do you want to switch here
switch to your left and see if
you see two labels now they've ruined
us you're almost dead well i can't
do it i can't do my weird
way of holding it when i use
my left hand it isn't
like if we found out we were
like mutants right yeah like we had
secret powers i think we used to
yeah haven't have super powers which ones
yeah did you yeah me too i
had so many
so many mean i had to well
like if i could be invisible i
can they i can walk through walls
steed d dude
florida marijuana oh sorry good scotch you
ever want to be invisible either of
yeah totally any point
no i mean honestly attention darling yeah
i mean i've wanted to disappear yeah
man right i wanted to disappear i
mean i think i've wanted to be
invisible and i want to spy on
who because you're a little snoop any
bar snoop and like to hear a
conversation and edited
wood
i think you'd need sound muffling powers
as well so yeah i mean showing
going around and you're seeing the invisible
man i would be naked what have
you were you were invisible but your
home's the oef and you're making so
much noise people like oh i know
you're in here does anyone think i
was a ghost and then they'd be
scared
it goes i think make very deliberate
noises this just be clumsy oaf noises
fuck na shit
i wish the recent curses at the
recent invisible man movie is the first
in the entire envisage verse to take
care of the being naked while you're
invisible problem yeah they really need to
make sense yeah that was the last
movie i saw in theaters before cupid
nineteen mine was onward i think that
was the first movie we saw at
home under lockdown wow well you know
it was it was it was totally
it was practically empty and the only
other people there were like two people
i didn't want to see well that's
kind of the joke i made on
instagram but at the time was a
year ago of course um still but
no great britain dino or the heads
up dana
wickens and brett oh that's right yeah
i remember this were at the theater
and it was very funny to have
them walk in and now they have
a corgi hensarling and i totally making
out during the movie because yeah if
if i knew someone in the theater
i'd be too embarrassed to totally were
sitting right in front of me and
they were like oh wow
kept looking back and they were like
did you see that
it's such a funny thing to make
out during like i've done it a
few times now you had and not
with cool up a bag of chaffey
cornea ellis
ah the funniest one was the ice
storm just like yeah taking out constantly
during the ice storm yeah keep watching
yeah he'll remember the movies that i
went to when that happened i guess
because i was too focused on the
web that didn't happen oh wow oh
well i've made out i
guarantee it oh right now limited to
take two i feel like is there
am i on a delay my slightly
behind everybody i don't know like in
life there yeah try this when did
you hear this hello now
ah
i don't know this is fun to
play
here let's try it let's try paul
when did you hear this right now
okay good okay i'm gonna make a
sound and then you make it back
to me and we'll see how delayed
you are okay beep beep that's great
let me try one boob boop
yeah this is working great i think
you're finding all right then i don't
need that medicine josh said you sound
in sync on my end and that's
the only end that matters thanks josh
i had i had something for topics
scots scots topics everybody week because he
wants to tell ya
okay so i was the other day
i was trying to go to the
other just the other day down three
yes pretty lady you know what to
say i was dumbfounded i had no
idea what to say but i i
was trying to remember the exact blueprints
of the house that i lived in
until i was eight
and i was trying to sketch it
out because i just trying to remember
just exactly where everything was right okay
because i i can you know kind
of remember it so i sketched it
out and then i was like nah
kind of remember this house i used
to fucking move
but i sketched it out and then
i was like wait a minute there's
no bathroom i couldn't figure out where
the bathroom was shit
we're doing it i was literally drawing
it but you find that used to
shit in a chamber puppy kept under
your bed well that was the thing
i was like i don't ever remember
shitting in this house but i what
i finally ended up having to do
was i ended up um i remember
taking a shower in my parents' bathroom
but i don't remember errors i always
i don't remember
shitting and
hi
elsewhere in the same house the whole
time right we never moved
i know that i shouldn't that house
i told have a memory of it
though i've memorized i've taken shits yeah
yeah yeah man
i've had a lot of memorable ones
i mean for bad reasons but
what would be some good reasons to
have member i mean i guess if
i read something interesting i mean i
used to read magazines on the toilet
yeah so i remember doing that i
literally didn't remember the room at all
so i had to google map the
place and do a street view and
then i saw like i saw a
window saw lady showering and
so yeah i always high a window
i was like that must be a
bathroom window there but it must have
been in that place now but i
don't remember it anyway but what i
was here's the topic i want to
get to know is i started just
thinking about the rooms it made me
start thinking about the rooms in the
house the rooms where it happened and
you're funny funny
and yes it made me start to
remember like memories started to flood back
to me like things that happened in
each room and i want to two
are you all alone in the moonlight
i believe so memories of the shit
i used to do in these rooms
but i want to see if you
guys would imagine a certain room in
the house that you grew up in
and then just start saying whatever kind
of came to mind we can go
one at a time so you're not
talking over each other but okay paul
and just kind of come up with
any memory in pick one room and
then just think of anything that ever
happened to you in that room i
remember a bedroom that i shared with
my brother know at this point it
was ok
and because my older brother had gone
out of the house my sisters were
obviously moved away by that point so
just me and my little brother with
the obviously i mean it's obvious anyone
hearing the story um ah and so
it's just me my little brother we
had our own rooms and a bat
got in the house whoa and it
got we were trying to get it
out with a broom and
a medicine that ah yeah
loser you're trying to hit the baseball
baseball bat through the window
there was a note attached to it
and said get out of our neighborhood
um so we were trying to get
the bad out of the house and
then we did and it was so
exciting to me that i read an
entire book overnight wow so you were
just like jazz i was wound up
what book was i
don't remember the name of it but
i remember hopefully bible he was like
up it was like a young kid
was all night
that much longer than you remember
yeah used to hop on many things
before
um the book was it was like
ah ah judy blume adjacent kind of
young adult fiction yeah um and i
remember because it had we must increase
our bust that's right how about it
had about milan called for everywhere there
was a penis in it that wasn't
for kids i know but i read
it when i was kid i'll bet
you did you little you dirty mom
easter ah ah yeah dirty um it
had the words that had two words
that i'd never heard before farc f
a r k which i think they
were using in place of fuck cool
but i but i but i knew
that word when i was a kid
so i thought like this is this
has some different meaning i'm not sure
what it maybe it
does yeah and the other word was
prig prego she brig i feel like
i've read this book because i remember
mine i'm gonna drum that prig right
out of the club i remember this
what book is this i don't i
feel like i read it too and
i'd never heard of the war and
john lawrence on it to look up
pagan farc isn't it interesting that in
sci-fi in the future
fuck is the one word they change
to like frac and that's already in
one thing c'mon no i think i
think they do it in scene like
star wars stuff and stuff like that
wow hey get the fargo away who
godzilla did shui yeah han solo and
godzilla ever schedules show
rules when you get a third of
the way
i don't know that's star wars the
problem star wars is they they don't
do it consistently so when they do
throw in a fake slang word it's
always like blaster couldn't have been a
jane austen book scruffy looking nerf herder
know yeah boot out it's the closest
i've come with my google did you
look up i'm gonna drum that pro
right out of the
they didn't and it just was like
drum lessons want to learn how to
drum did you put quotes around it
no i did not want do what's
right
i wonder if anybody out there listening
knows this book because i remember it's
auto filling but i don't know if
it's because i already searched it yeah
well why don't you just what if
a million people are searching i want
i'm gonna drum the progress of the
club and drama right like why does
i'm gonna drum that program of the
club give me drum sets like stop
i don't know i don't know someone
who looks like they're necessary and wants
to be part of three hundred apparently
but no no no just the three
of us who you go away go
away is that come up yeah hi
i love you she can't hear you
why don't you tell her then i
will not tell her that
whatever be modern scott tau want me
to say that i love you
no i love you saw through your
room huh
um we oh so that's so that's
one this is how i written the
memory that's one bedroom story lauren do
you do we want to switch to
lower energy i want to hear another
one so i can okay so i
can see the range let's keep going
till we run out of rooms oh
but you don't want to do another
one in that room yeah one more
in the in that bedroom i remember
my when i did share that
bedroom with my little brother does anything
and he looks up to the side
like
i'm looking at
the old cool ball and jay what
does this weird tack you're thinking for
you suddenly acre and so rana zero
it's my life
um my little my little brother was
very little indeed and he was waking
up and talking in his sleep before
he's fully awake yeah here the secret
said he keeps i did because he
said aloud what are you doing here
little ducky you're supposed to be in
the water that's funny do you make
fun of them all we've course did
it became a story
we told many many times didn't you
ask him about it and did he
remember what he was dreaming about obviously
i didn't wanna be in the water
yeah it was a duck one who
should have been in the water i
don't know if he was in the
gobi desert i have no idea where
he was i'll give you one final
memory from that room and this is
this is i think all oh nope
i just remembered another one oh boy
great um that room when i was
in high school i ah
had a ah a girlfriend over
and we were in that room and
we were sitting on the edge of
the bed and guess while we were
kissing oh hell yeah and my time
machine was this thing for space my
dad was sliding into first you feel
in that burst area diarrhea
right so my my tad walked in
and was very put on that's horrible
oh so he walked out he didn't
walk in intentionally to catch you to
stop you from doing no no no
i think it was dinnertime he was
gonna learn oh teams make out with
someone at dinnertime you sly dog i
got to work out everything alright
yeah burn a few calories so
coca-cola though let's make out i don't
know i don't wanna bulk up so
he closed the door and said your
mother wouldn't like it if she knew
you had a young lady in there
oh so this was against the rules
no that had never been discussed ever
there had never been rules
german rules they stopped doing i was
the fifth of six like they stopped
with rules said rain it was like
you found out you fucked up after
the fact yeah yeah so i forgot
to tell you i hate that there
was an zero i'm no it does
not it was okay in the same
memory and was that janie
yeah that's right the high school we've
known each other since high school
um and i really run that ran
the gamut from i forget your first
two stories and kissing oh you fat
she ran the gamut from i forgot
the first two
wow what a range that story had
everything from i don't remember pursue what
did you say
ah wow i have one more memory
from gay me yeah give it yeah
i want as many as you can
remember my cousin what are you doing
i don't know i think this is
fun i think it's fun this sounds
like a cold activity now to me
what he's saying is you can remember
because here's
you think is happening scots like busy
with something else so he just keeps
making us do things
oh damn cool up walk in here
even though i'd locked the door because
i'm podcasting share wow let me see
ya thanks using key um and the
final memory i can recall from that
room was my ah cousin doreen and
i um what there are houses had
joined there were connected by a wall
duplex essentially and ah she had the
room opposite mine and so we we'd
thought it would be fun to devise
a code so we could like tap
on the wall you talk to each
other in the code i devised had
some flaws because it was one i
will say you have told us about
this but
i don't remember ah it was one
a two tabs for b and so
on to oh my god here we
go if you want to know what
z and you've to wait for twenty
six taps we'd never got that far
but i do remember trying to tap
a message to her i remember also
writing it out like if there's a
sheet of paper that had like
oh and you and you like you
think that's morse codes exactly oh my
god my friends and walkie talkies and
tracy want to come out on a
room story sunroom spacious i'm almost chased
my memory go for it
go from memory um i attempted to
send her a message and i was
hitting the wall with a hammer and
then i just eventually wore a hole
in the wall oh god and could
she not really within the closet so
no one ever saw it i got
away with it in the closet she
could hear it but it's like doody
dude i realised
he's doing got taken over by jacko
wacko wacko jacko and his dancing in
his chair
wow um did someone say awake to
hear this or was she totally sleep
and like shout to fuck ah no
she was she wouldn't speak to me
that way we will shot gap i
don't want to hear about how you
want to go to the zoo in
little taps oh
oh i can give you imagining getting
the word z where z means you'd
be sad and you'd probably start over
and say animal place more morse code
was devised because it's quicker as that
would like the awareness so that i
think also to be a code when
you know true but you know instead
of just doing a replacement well because
any
nothing good rely on me that you
get like sica de longs and shorts
longs and longs and shorts and isn't
that what life is longs and shorts
series of which came up on who
wants to be a millionaire recently and
i knew the million dollar answer and
some are there new episodes no no
not right when i say recently i
mean many months ago well because i've
been like wait
yeah um walkie talkies you were gonna
say i had walkie-talkies with a friend
of mine and they had morse code
to them um you know paper that
came with yes yes we had the
beeps yeah i can never figure out
what the fuck was going on with
that but we tried
um that's why it was supposed to
be an aside within the middle of
your story and not it's own story
yeah really we only did so well
probably as far as we got with
the morse code and walkie-talkies yeah that's
all you really need i'm sleazy save
our ship
i still sort of love walkie talkies
even though yeah we try that we
tried to find some for our right
that's right and someone someone by the
name of coop said she would buy
us all walkie talkies and then the
day came and there were no walkie-talkies
think that's probably for the best i
feel like there was further discussion well
yeah so there's an app there's a
walkie talkie that
that's what a doll came down to
is like oh let's just do the
app instead and then no one gothia
the upsets it's just like once just
face time yeah that's what it ended
that's always good and the biggest biggest
scream was ah john's with his initials
taking up almost entirely the entire thing
because he didn't answer he would not
put he started the call will not
put his v
on ah
psychotic oh alright lowering you think of
a room and i've got the rim
what room two boom boom boom let's
go back to it okay the room
is my dad's office in our house
and this is a spare bedroom he's
turned into the office or it was
a garage that was turned into an
office attached to the house
oh and um
ah one memory first memory that comes
to mind is when i was in
middle school and i looked up on
youtube the first music video i ever
saw online wo was it wacko jacko
no it was macy gray i try
wow
because i really liked that sign so
i was like maybe we could find
it online and then we went online
and we found it and it was
very exciting i really remember that very
distinctly wow and why were your dad
found it for you know i was
with my friend and we just were
like with a computer was in that
room as well yeah it was so
i was in that room a lot
um chatting dying days yes
wow chatting online um you know getting
bullied by people at school online um
with secret accounts um yeah ok other
people i don't know that i did
that why you did no no i
barley real life um
i did get bullied online but it's
okay um i'm okay we figured out
who it was at one point and
it was pretty exciting the prison where
their consequences no
okay yeah we just were like who
knows fuck you and then it was
like whatever still got made fun of
um and then okay another memory from
that room is that the an opossum
came up to the back door i
have i told you the story no
bats opossums and this is this is
a
by the way naturally i wish i
might have brought this up because i
always wonder about this how do you
say a possum or possum i say
possum but i see that's how i
was raised i say possum too but
i think the correct thing is actually
a possum i had like a full
debate during wild horses one time like
on stage about this and i was
the owner
only wild horses show yeah
like you guys it doesn't um because
i was only one who said a
possum and everyone thought i don't also
awesome that's and then the half the
audience was like no it's a thing
and then i googled it later and
i was like any other thing and
then whatever so they're commonly referred to
as possums yes but they sometimes rendered
as apostrophe possums that's too much but
where i'm from i never heard it
possum sounded like a hick would say
it power awesome yeah yeah like the
beverly hillbillies yeah whoa turns were simple
country folks so that's it makes sense
that they would have taught everyone it
sounds like everyone was doing it that
way except me but um there
or was this possum that came up
to the back door and it was
i thought rabbit but then i recently
read online that they can't get rabies
but somebody random wrote that i don't
know that's true some random wrote a
possums can get rabies can you google
that no i don't think that's true
at all i've never
you had me here there why would
they not get it anyway i think
it had rabies so what happened so
we came up to the door and
in the middle of the day and
it was like yeah me it was
being really nasty to my cat and
and that we are all kind of
gassy
and my dad hit it with a
bat
baseball oh i thought it was the
bat that got chased out of paul's
i know it could have been but
you hit with the bed you have
told me that story and i blocked
it out of my mind yeah i
know i've told this story a bunch
of times so so didn't break it's
back and like blood spatter on the
head but then it then walked away
it locked away it laughing
okay wow and then from by the
time i went to school the next
day it was um lying on our
front porch possibly dead or playing dead
oh you never know when those crafty
little monga and i went to school
and told everyone the story and i
was really um delighted by what had
happened i thought it was
it's just you're right it was also
your dad because it was just so
crazy it was such a crazy thing
but it's kind of my dad's like
it's my dad's old world tendencies you
know too like we recently this happened
um like about well now everything's a
year ago now i feel like but
my dad was staying with me in
la and i was um he told
me
we went out to eat
me him and mike and he was
like you guys aren't gonna like this
um i saw a huge huge cockroach
in your house and you like he
held held up his hands like this
like it's like wow a few inches
something nasty okay big and we were
like oh why did you tell us
it's horrible because he he was like
he's like well the worst part is
i don't know where
it went okay and then so we
were like oh great now there's this
loose roach in the house i want
to die i mean i know we're
called the witch she will make
yeah it was just it was just
like a horrible story because i was
like now i'm aware that there's this
like huge bug somewhere in the house
and i'm here hours later maybe a
day later i'm sitting on the couch
and the corner of my eye a
gigantic roach walks up the side of
the couch to my ex to my
face okay then i scream i was
like
you like try to like my dad
just stood up grabbed it with his
his ho i would never do that
and threw it out the front door
wo said don't come back you saddam
and he grabbed it so hard that
it like a leg of it's like
a leg was left behind on the
o
so yeah that's my dad's like energy
surrounding you know you're wondering why dealing
with wildlife it's like no big deal
that let's just get to the point
shit yeah i mean sometimes you have
to have that in a house because
there's people like you who just scream
and i would just sit in the
people
a little low and it was so
scary yeah but i'd loved it i
love that i went to the the
awesome story you know kind of in
context is not a big deal really
it just kind of like this is
just yeah something you gotta deal with
is to tell you about costa rica
how like
you can tell yourself that but i
mean it was what's kabul first i
don't believe in animal abuse and second
of all it was out in the
middle of the day being um aggressive
so it had a problem this awesome
was acting cool yeah
and it's been at least twenty years
since he's done that wow
um i was gonna say did i
tell you about in costa rica how
in the hotel we were staying at
like lizards would just come into your
hotel room and like sleep up on
the ceiling and i don't yeah i
don't like that i don't like doing
either but i don't know a fellow
bother me but i i guess like
it depends on how big they are
will do they ever come on the
bed now that's the thing they don't
they they as far as i know
they never dropped onto the bed or
anything and like when i first got
there they're like oh by the way
you know like lizards are gonna come
in here they're gonna be sleeping everywhere
it's like i don't want that but
then you just kind of like as
long as they don't bother you you
get used to it what about like
a net around the bed
yeah right i didn't bring a net
with me why didn't you i bring
it everywhere i go
the bangle do want a third story
from that room since y'all swapping course
i want a third story i don't
want to be doing
really wanna go crazy okay well the
next store that comes to mind is
that for a while in my twenties
i had a party every christmas with
my friends from home and what do
you mean friendly from home like from
evanston like oh i see
my high school friends and whenever we
would all i'd invite everyone over for
a christmas party and it was nice
and while it lasted then suddenly you
know in years past and nobody's coming
home anymore and everyone's moved in everyone's
it became like there's only two people
to invite um that's why you know
and not two of the good ones
yeah it's just
kinda like let's just move it along
the real second string material but my
we would put all of our coats
in the office and my friend was
standing in there and she told me
from afar that she was having a
baby and she was twenty four twenty
five they had recently gotten married they
are pretty young so she told you
from afar
maybe she's like twenty eight shy guys
wow well no i mean i was
not
i was not
remember i wasn't standing in the room
but i was looking at her in
there and that's what the memory is
of her telling me that and then
i was like
um and then let me think of
another memory
no matter how lucky they are good
memories okay i got another one well
just to give you a little pastiche
you know yeah yeah um pistachio these
and other stories i just i just
want like glimpses of memories so when
i was little my dad had a
rubber stamp memories
when i was little my oh yeah
bring it back so it's t-shirts so
ah when i was little my dad
had ace rubber stamp of his signature
because i guess other people would use
it for his work to sign checks
or whatever i guess it sounds like
this drug plus he would use it
i don't i guess i was little
so i never really noticed
yeah why what's happening to the authorize
yeah yeah yeah so he was probably
stamping him and i had used that
i remember sneaking under his drafting table
to get it out and to like
say a report card to sign that
ah permission slip or something oh the
thing the thing was at my parents'
classes going to a strip
club
i never needed it i never like
i was always in charge of like
just doing all that stuff like getting
all my forms together and like keeping
track of all that and i it
was just a simpler you know way
to do it just be like he's
got it we're good and it worked
and they never found out no one
ever thought anything of
it
like does he know that it was
happening or they they just would my
parents yeah would have signed it if
you would just he would have signed
it but i don't know there maybe
i had to go to school and
he wasn't there and there was some
like i had to do it at
the last minute or something but yeah
well i usually would like just walk
up to my dad while he was
reading and then be like yes sign
this guy do this guy tell me
give me five bucks for this
fingerprint here
yeah you're done i gotta go kick
some raccoons
ah
wow these are good said let's say
you're in the hot seat we need
a roof time memories and i want
a weird room yeah what's the winners
i mean yeah there weren't a lot
of weird rooms but i are the
most you know familiar my room is
probably the the living room where the
tv was
the har i remember faking being sick
once and like just because i just
didn't want to go to school that
day i must have heard of it
five or six i don't know how
i faked it this time i do
i remember in the other house i
lived in after i saw e t
holding the thermometer up to
the light bulb yeah i got to
try that and then your temperatures four
hundred degrees i was thinking about that
the other day like i never got
it completely dry and cold but this
thermometer gonna lie so i think all
i did was say that i felt
sick and i just sore throat and
instead of going to the doctor whatever
it's like okay well we'll get you
fluids and all that kind of stuff
but
i wasn't sick i just for some
reason and and staying home was the
best i know but i don't even
know why i didn't want to go
to school because then it sort of
surprised me it surprised me years later
when on the last day of school
they were like oh by the way
you got perfect attendance is here and
i was like really don't i hate
school like i don't know i was
all over the place on school
was this the same d not not
the someday you stayed home okay no
no no of course not no so
i i remember to drift for a
different reason if that were true i
remember being sick and lying on that
couch and then we were watching cbs
and they were doing the telethon at
that point and
um a dog was barking and um
and i remember them saying like please
please you have to obey i was
faking learn genus i was like oh
okay da so yeah i remember the
pbx people saying please please you have
to call in we're in dire need
of money and i was like mom
ya gotta call is your entire native
money and she's like i thought your
throat hurt
wow she got you trainees krista yeah
screaming bee has a bit though huh
hey ya gotta call in they needed
they made it mom oh that's so
funny outside you felt for them it's
like they'll be saying this for years
right
um i remember there being a batman
punching bag that my mom bought me
which is really nice and that was
in the room for a little while
until it had sand on the bottom
until it finally deflated um i remember
reading are you my mother in that
room i remember
there's a rocking chair well okay so
the rocking chair ah i had a
weird like bladder infection when i was
six or something like that am i
and i i remember i had to
go the hospital chief source of stuff
but i remember my mom like comforting
me because i was crying and i
couldn't i could
didn't like sleep because it hurts so
bad oh yeah all the piss was
just upside this was going back through
my eyes were yellow
i just remember her like rocking me
to sleep until i could finally like
sleep but that was that was that
was like i had an operation when
i was young where it was like
first i remember them taking x-rays and
then basically saying you took half your
brain and then say
it'll probably be fine no they took
x-rays of me like they took off
my pan or maybe i took off
my i probably took them off and
it was this an alien abduction i
know i'm da shove this thing know
so i'm sitting there and they're like
ok we gotta take x-rays but we
need we needed like we need it
in process we need like you p
king while we take the x-rays so
i was like this does nasty just
anywhere they're like yeah just where you
just like let let it go and
we'll take the x-rays so i'm just
sharing a room and a room yeah
so i'm just like p when they
didn't have like a diaper on you
or something no no they they had
i had to be like naked for
the x-ray part of it and they
had no
no but like you like don't they
do x-rays that don't to being naked
maybe not back then i've no i
don't know and i was wrong not
for the diaper area all i remember
is like peeing everywhere and going on
the walls and the ceiling and still
go fuck i don't think you remember
not to do that
i think you made that up and
then i also remember a beautiful dream
you have i also remember that was
the first time i ever had anesthesia
and them saying like okay now count
backwards from ten and me going
tens not enough numbers for this guy
ten nine com yeah and yeah and
then waking up later they do you
think anaesthesiologists love that like they know
that that's what people think and they're
like oh okay okay oh my god
give you a bigger dose if you
need it have we talked with this
when i got my wisdom teeth out
like five years ago or something now
more than that now
um i was under anesthesia and then
i came out of it and i
was saying that my doctors like george
clooney not true quebec and then also
a saying i just tell him about
my improv showing that they should come
to it
it's so embarrassing
do you think the doctor made up
the part about you saying he looked
like george clooney because that's what i
would do it because i started out
funny you know i think i kind
of remember one of my patients when
they come out of anesthesia since the
senior was very handsome like a movie
star no i think i remember it
but be like told back to me
like i kind of remembered saying it
but it was like
oh and then i was crying because
it told me i couldn't play basketball
anymore
why after the operation yeah whatever while
i was on the basketball team at
the time and my wisdom teeth this
was i mean in my thirties this
or you know my late twenties when
the older girls were playing basketball in
that like comedy league oh yeah yeah
i'm very confused i was a little
bit too yeah it didn't make any
sense and
i got my wisdom teeth out and
they were very impacted like they'd been
like going sideways for like very many
years and then when they took them
out the bone here where the wisdom
teeth are was very very thin and
they were like if you got hit
with the ball it can break your
job she's she's raised and
i already had already been hit in
the face with the ball because i'm
not good at basketball and so i
was like i have to quit but
i was crying about it at the
time which is kinda so is it
is it fine now or could if
i threw about all you're good
with therapy i think it wasn't enough
um
i think part of it was that
good so with time it would have
to like heal and grow more rye
as we all have to do wow
friday friday sit fridays said very restless
right now yeah i get it well
speaking of wrestles we have to take
a break i mean we got to
stretch our legs walk around yeah i
believe it was john muir who said
we
i have to take a break
topless we will be right back
where back um i also remember by
the way in that room a continued
the year that my parents brought home
yeah like a star for the top
of the christmas tree that was electric
and like how to learn of yes
thank you
had a pattern of of lights flashing
it was so gauche and ah like
loud and vibrant but i was just
fascinated with it when i was a
kid and i would just look at
it it was the best thing that
we'd ever got it sounds great um
yeah just saw me do we have
taste we did not
um but that's that's another memory from
that room those are my memories from
that room i love it and watching
a lot of tv i loved having
a christmas tree when we were kids
it was so magical to me so
imagine i still feel that way their
christmas trees are
fantastic invention i think it's just like
a great time of year like it
always just feels so cozy and yeah
when you put up an industry i
guess for me it's like that that
particular kind of
forms of the of the holiday season
when you were a kid is so
yes like i it's still i still
love it i love the christmas season
and i love people's decorations i love
decorating our house and you know i
overstate the glow that's where we used
to eat from but that ah ah
when that when the room is just
lit by the tree that's the only
light that's on is such a wonderful
feeling but man when you're a kid
is like it's like nothing else i
agree i hate it ah hate it
i hate christmas sky dome rather work
i'd rather go to work and simply
rage
who's that he's this guy
oh hey i never want him you
he's a mouse right no hearts or
he's a duck and he has this
mouse it's working for him oh it's
donald duck the scrooge in that i
don't i really mean does the scrooge
o of core get together
i've never seen that by the way
i feel i must yeah i think
i remember seeing it in the theater
in orange county i'm like sounds about
right what which cineplex six no it
was the one ah okay i saw
oliver and company there oh my god
i never got to see that movie
when i was a kid but i
wanted to so bad and i love
the commercial
and they had um the toys at
mcdonald's or burger king and i tried
to get those and i did get
some of them what was it what
was it but i don't remember anything
about oliver and company was like charlie
joseph jaggers remains all these dogs and
all the dogs had great personalities and
they were always dancing in a car
and singing and i was like i
got it
i gotta get my hands on this
and i just never got to see
it where are your parents keeping it
from you too they don't want it
i don't know if they even knew
how much i cared about it but
i just loved the idea of this
movie and i was like i need
all toys okay so my choice to
take me where you're where my parents
are very cheap or your parents cheap
or was it like if you want
to see a movie was fine yeah
it was usually fine to see a
movie and i'm i mean when i
was a kid my mom would take
i remember going to the movies my
mom and my brother a lot and
again a hot summer day and sneaking
in with some we'd always sneak in
with you know snacks and coke oh
yeah my dad did that too even
though they were religious that's the one
one thing that they were like
popcorn and everything is too expensive at
a certain point in the movie i'm
gonna unwrap a candy bar in hand
oh yeah it was always ah i
mean i don't know if we've talked
about it like that moment when you
just have to click your pop open
like right when like there's a big
noise like ash and then you say
wherein okay hey is it was it
a thing that you were ever really
not allowed to do
do or was yeah like did people
get busted for it oh yeah well
it's felt like that when i was
growing up it felt like someone is
going to kick me out if they
see this and so even till now
i feel very self-conscious with br i
was recently at universal's not recently obviously
because nothing's been recently but i was
yeah for stacia i was a universe
liars and i bought i bought
a gift from popcorn oh you did
tell us this yeah that's right away
if i tried to get in they
wouldn't let me in so i had
to throw away an expensive popcorn right
in front of them before they were
less crazy and i'm wondering could you
have gone to annapolis and and gotten
a refund or had them hold it
for you until yeah like when they
hold it for you in the box
office they wouldn't do it these stupid
eighth
eighteen year old kid that says they
didn't help themselves but that's shit if
there's if you're in like an area
that has stores around it like that
like yeah that's what i said anyway
but then again who cares but i
feel like if i'm getting the food
in your home free like it does
they don't care the guy circum with
me yeah if i were alone i
had bought a gift at popcorn propolis
which
what how much that costs you over
thirty dollars a day ah i don't
even know i don't even know what's
in there but i'm just saying i
chose three dollars like it's price overpriced
that's disgusting and i would be pissed
forever about that if i was like
i paid thirty percents i'm still picking
gift michelle kuo fellow was our anniversary
she didn't get her pepper is present
i will say i used to sneak
into the theater with my friend where
we we had a scam where whew
one of us would buy a ticket
and then open the back door yeah
the person in and then our plan
was if anyone ever asked us we
would we would pull out the one
ticket and go oh i lost my
stub but they can't kick us
out for having one ticket and know
it always works except one time some
guy came in and was like hey
you guys snuck in and we pulled
out the one ticket we're like oh
we can't find the other one he
was like i know what you did
but i can't kick you out and
he walked away ah you must have
felt really proud it's just a kick
you out if you don't have
a ticket
yeah i guess i could but i
don't know ah what have you walked
right in the front like i guess
i'd like to get sob i feel
like making a big deal out of
someone sneaking into the movies is very
petty yeah and being like you need
to leave it's like you're not really
making money off of this like me
sitting here doesn't affect how much money
is
coming in or money is just a
concept anyway
to make people think they're poor
yeah it's really deep man power your
parents cheap they were thrifty because we
were not ah particularly well off but
they were very good at um hiding
that from us so when i was
a kid i thought of them as
cheap and now i realised they were
not yeah my dad had a thing
how about he he just didn't want
to pay anyone to do anything that
he felt like he could do himself
so all sorts of things and he
still does it but it all sorts
of things happening where like i remember
a cement mixer pulling up to the
back to our backyard of that old
house in him like taking out the
bricks in the wall
call so that the cement mixer could
like poor cement because he wanted to
pave the the backyard himself and he
did it all himself like he would
he he did all the tile in
our new house himself show us do
it dump all your cement and i'll
take it from there yeah it was
it was but it was a big
day it was a big day for
sure hood where people were
like coming by going like oh look
at the cement truck you know same
thing is when he like hauled out
a huge tree himself with the help
of like five of this church buddies
it was like the whole neighborhood came
around like checking out the the tree
being the power are in your job
zoning out nil i'm just i'm actually
thinking about a question for you oh
okay hit me
once a gambling scrambling it's
no i was gonna say like you
don't mind outsourcing you prefer it i
prefer it because i there's yeah like
find i don't find it a waste
of money to for me to pay
someone to do something that i i
can't do like i've fixed are like
hearing stuff like that especially during quorum
teen when i was like oh no
one can come by the house so
yeah i would watch a youtube video
and i figured out how to do
it and like you there there is
a pride to it but it's like
then you look at it and go
oh three hours of my life are
gone when i could've been doing something
else yeah i mean i think if
there's a situation where someone could do
it much faster and more effectively and
efficiently i'd much rather outsource it
um but i but only with things
that i'm like not sure i'm going
to do right or that might be
hard like i don't mind cleaning but
i don't want to fix like an
appliance really i'd rather just call someone
and make sure they've done proper but
if you knew how to do it
and it's still like you weren't you
weren't doing it all the time like
a professional so it would take you
five times
as long but you knew how to
do it would you do it that's
my dad i'm saying i don't so
i don't think so dependent depends on
what it is but i feel like
the idea of me spending hours trying
to fix something and not being i
mean i don't know i just it
feels um
feudal yeah i let him you're saying
in this hypothetical i do know how
to do the thing so unless you
like you have done it before you're
like oh i know how to do
that it's like longtime for example i'll
plunge a toilet i'll figure that out
oh yeah i hope so but i
mean like that we had we had
a toilet overflow
and then i was like i think
i could talk to my dad and
figure out how to do everything and
i did it all and i think
but it's been a plumber got there
which i did call anyway just to
make sure it was things like you
check my work because i make shit
everywhere like this why do you like
it filled the toilet
but i don't mind like trying to
learn me like that where and especially
when i know it's gonna come in
handy a lot like i know how
to like change the ball thing in
the toilet and all machine to mow
thing in the toilet and now you're
looking for it i know my my
my dad used to have a job
where he flew helicopters for a guy
oh
so um forgot who what who ran
a company he was the ceo we
know what to say
was his name oliver
he had this great company with great
personalities everyone had a really good personnel
know but he's so in and his
thing was he would fly a guy
to ah he would he would fly
from the from the building the corporate
office and he would fly him to
like another sip
eighty that was only like a la
ballet and it was just a half
hour away but it was but it
was like ten minutes instead of half
an hour for him to drive and
yeah that doesn't seem worth it to
me and he was like button but
for that guy it's worth it because
those twenty minutes that he could be
working and making money
he would rather pay the yeah that
was really kind of real because yeah
it just seems like a weird flex
like real housewives will fly from o
c to l a for like an
episode gonna helicopter like we'll make jokes
sometimes about like flying from burbank to
l a exercise yes just like it's
and they're like in a helicopter it's
like coma
yeah just drive just drive your housewives
just dragging yourself housewife say a few
hours please yeah please please and by
the way we're begging you please housewives
want you to drive please but he
housewives
real housewives times of ot
there's new warehouse i was coming sooner
you guys okay reality recap would you
be one lauren we already cover no
i want but i want to fill
my own version i'm so cool up
on one of those shows oh my
god i'd love to see the i
think the most interesting one i would
like otherwise so defensive
i would love it if you were
on a reality show all i want
is to watch somebody i know on
a reality show i love really love
this i love someone i know might
get on the bachelor and i'm like
really a bachelor i'd actually and i'm
very excitable currently um it would be
a future season but he has interviewed
for a job he's just been born
yeah yeah to be shakyamuni mate maybe
on a really hot he might get
on it shows me it's any season
eby potentially could get on one of
the bachelor shows that's so exciting about
a new baby it's like the world
lay before them you know just options
that is exactly so you just want
to see your friends
what in personal moments that yeah filmed
okay yeah i wanna see i wanna
see how they are in that context
like i would love it if there
was a camera crew following you and
janie and you and kula up in
your houses me and janie and paul
and cool
and i would just i would think
there would be so entertaining i just
can't even express i can't think of
anything more hellish why don't you hate
it i never thought about it until
you said that and the idea of
pot to my mind of what it
would be like to be just like
in your own home with some camera
crew there yeah it sounds so
weird when you really think about doing
it actually in your house like yeah
how mahal coming a probably rules like
you can only come over on these
days and on you know no issues
or whatever it's like hey come over
on monday we're gonna do this bit
where we do well traditions islam more
scripted than other shows but i feel
like if for like you know real
housewives it's like
they know they're going to be filming
that day than you know they get
into a mood and they get my
highschool and oh yeah exact but it's
not every single day of your life
right did i tell you that when
rockwell the singer of ah somebody's watching
me
had his big hits hong who is
being interviewed by rick dees on kiss
fm in the morning and um he
had brought a camera crew with him
and because he was going to be
making a documentary about his life um
so there he had hired them to
follow him around twenty four seven until
the end of his life and i
wonder how long that actually happened what
way were we with this
like when su stevens was like i'm
making an album for every single state
and then he made two
for the rest of his life was
like yeah i'm just slam yeah i've
just hired a camera crew they're gonna
follow me around because you know like
i'm a superstar now in my life
so interesting and so and i just
wonder like how long how long before
we accept everyone knows like okay the
money's run out i would love to
see the end of that footage like
what it was like the last
we like let's just call it him
just making real cheese sandwich
ah man we gotta take a break
we got to take a break we'll
be right back
and we're back well now it's time
for the part that everybody loves the
most it's the three true section this
is the part of the show where
we all play a game this is
a game that was sent to us
by i don't know who and it
was called
celebrity impressions couples therapy each person writes
down the name of a celebrity and
passes it to their left then the
three people begin a scene in a
therapist's office where one person chosen at
random is the therapist the other two
are a couple with a dispute and
issue resolved they play the scene as
the celebrity they've been passed now we
think the best way to do this
is for one person to be the
therapist and the other to a sinus
celebrity to each other and then the
therapist to guess who yeah they are
so tall and i paul and i
will be the couple and we're going
to text each other
who we are right so right now
and then lauren you're going to have
to guess who we are we have
each other's phone numbers we did we
don't like to brag about this but
and by the way paul you have
a little something in what i call
the stash
and pumbaa you have a little crumb
yeah it's gone oh it's gone too
you don't have to keep touching your
face it's like oh it's gone yeah
you love so space
um he's about to pause about to
send me i've already sent him his
celebrity i ever i'm seeing a person
in my mind and i keep blanking
on the name which is weird like
another name gets in the way yeah
and it's ah it's frustrating i understand
you can go to wikipedia look up
there just chit chat show
josh me shut up you shut up
okay i got it okay i don't
get it though because i'm sending it
to you and then you will get
it
wonderful
i got it alright are we i
don't want to do an impression that
is what you're doing does it have
to be an impression i would much
rather just save user choice from clues
okay fine yeah you'll see why i
understand already i'm guessing okay so go
ahead
and um ok well thanks for coming
in today guys i'm really happy that
you're here thank you for accommodating our
particular needs because um yeah you know
it's it's toby don't mind doing this
outdoors yeah i don't i don't yeah
do you have do you have any
water yeah would you like a bottle
of
cold or room temp i'd like a
bottle but he wants you know could
you just yeah um i knew i
needed a simple yeah in mind yeah
do you mind yeah do you mind
okay no i don't mind um yeah
in any case thank you so much
i mean i know it's crazy
that we're together um you know mansion
yeah i have no jealousy after i
got divorced you know so recently to
that hot hot hunk of a man
okay okay j lo i'm not shallow
okay j lo that's what i say
nursing this edition starts talking like yeah
well you know that's i don't use
your but you can't tell us apart
ooh and oh no no of course
i can't i was just it was
a joke because she recently got divorced
as well okay but i think it's
i wasn't working she wasn't married okay
my joke is going i don't like
you calling another latin person j lo
ok not i'm sorry that's i don't
either
thank you honey here let me scratch
behind your ears thank you hey so
i guess what's weird alien thing to
ask us what are we doing here
how should should we just start talking
to you i want to just ask
is have you been in a relationship
with a dog before
i mean my ex husband is kind
of a dog but this one's a
literal one who seems to want my
little sir literal literal oh okay well
he's had a little and yeah well
yes thank you thank you yes and
so you know you're dating clifford the
big red dog yeah kind of obviously
he's big he's red and he's a
dog
dog now here's the thing i think
she's moping around the house so much
because she got divorced from her hahaha
k husband and also her show just
ended and she's got nothing going on
also because you make no money other
than just like i'm a dog yeah
and i have so much money from
syndication
so deal deeds on that show that
ran forever
so it's just you know i've so
i'm one of the richest most well-paid
celebrities in the world and and sofia
vergara yeah thank you so much divorce
from joe about popular in this reality
because we'll see that's the problem with
this reality is that you needed to
be factual because i'm going off of
what
should i say we're cheat i'm cheating
on him yes there's an odd tourist
i know there's no other there's all
guess right you are j lo i
beg your pardon than what i thought
you were saying that they got divorced
see you have to use contact was
doing that because hell why would i
leave with you it's called it's not
about that it's about how you measure
me it's about how you
figured i'd lecture you say you need
to figure out who the celebrity is
shutting you know your place their real
lives hello everyone it's paul oh
so okay fine let's do it again
but don't get angry so do it
again save these lies thank you yeah
who's who's doing okay so i'll take
paul i thought we did rather well
and you've got it very i thought
so too i knew i forgot it
was severe sofia vergara is former husband
who's in the weird fight with her
about about
embryos yeah embryo gives me one and
i was talking about when i was
saying i was divorced without hong kong
hunk of a man so your law
doesn't apply you just think oh got
in on that so you you're okay
wait who's playing
all of us need your the therapist
i'm the therapist okay so i'm gonna
text paul a person or place or
thing to be
oh a thing well since you were
clifford or place sure
your montana i am cathedral voter tom
this is exciting this is the part
that everyone yeah the anticipation is building
because it's like it's your thinking and
they're texting to each other at all
in we don't get any of it
we never got anything out we're just
so many checks yes here it comes
so just thought it was just doing
bits and put his phone down
okay yeah he wouldn't emails are like
so dramatic like i got one from
gavin newsome that was like lauren please
let me explain like that was that
was so funny can i see my
apologies like doing describe that i don't
like plain every tweet that they do
now is starts with a let
me be clear or let's get this
out of the way or i've said
it before and i'll say it again
yeah it's like just tweet the thing
i don't like tell me i too
will just pass it on it's like
no you're the person jeff you're usually
telling everyone yeah yeah deal with it
passed something about government okay ready yeah
yeah hi guys
oh make so much come on in
here you can take a seat anywhere
even on the couch
yeah that's mainly we're okay great the
sat on the couch too okay do
you why what you don't want to
sit on the counter you worried annoyed
all i wanna do is sit on
the couch yeah i don't usually let
them sit on the couch your couch
guy obviously you don't i don't think
my i think of myself as one
yes if you don't let him sit
on the couch i usually just to
preserve the fabric there's a bunch of
shit i'm not allowed to do by
the way oh like what oh what
are the rules at your house now
you guys are you guys are here
because you're having issues i would love
to hear you're really gonna do this
you're gonna the first thing you're gonna
say is you're gonna list all the
all the things you're not allowed to
do and i'm like okay let you
start doing that let me confess something
i
i'm a bit of a loose cannon
i guess you could say and you
know like i um i tend to
not be aware of my own presence
you know like i don't know i'm
just like a bull in a china
shop sometimes vary see at least you
have some understanding so i awareness that's
good so so so you have no
self-awareness
and in your bullet edge and so
and so you think the rules that
she sets down for you are valid
i guess but i don't i can't
keep them in my head i just
want to do what i wanna do
you know what i mean yeah when
you say you're a bull in a
china shop you're you're talking metaphorically right
yeah yeah i'm notable
doesn't reach you know michael mayer let's
just say my book was recently made
my my picnic was recently destroyed by
how out of touch i did yes
i destroyed a picnic i'm sorry again
i didn't know i was destroying it
and just joined this thing are you
sure my daddy named school and what
what is
right spaghetti night at school yes it
is trista kennedy school look what was
even doing there
yeah why why were
anyway i don't understand the the picnic
the spaghetti night what does it what
are your food issues she likes to
make a mess i i know i
like to make a message that i
don't mind when a mess is made
is that fair to say you don't
like to clean up or you you
don't like to clean up okay i
clean i clean i'd take care of
my own side of the street you
know what i mean if i
can help if i could teach him
how to clean up i'd be a
happy woman yeah okay so would you
say it's a bit of a pig
pen around your place
yeah it's messy okay anyways um well
well let me ask you this why
your were so worried about cleaning you
have all the time in the world
now yeah what are you what are
you up to do you have a
job do you work i don't know
that much value could you just give
me all of your bio biographical facts
who me yeah
ah you you don't know who i
am well you said sorry i'm kidding
you you gotta be you don't know
who i am i'm seriously i'm on
one of the most watch most watched
tv shows of the recent decade yeah
um i'm of course you are i'm
i don't want i don't own a
tv i'm sorry sir
so i i got my start a
long time ago but this show really
made me pop off let's just say
that okay and um i'll take your
word for it i i don't i'm
not obsessed with celebrity culture okay have
you seen any movies seen happy gilmore
ah julie i of course have seen
happy gilmore so you do know who
i am yeah well you told me
your name walking in here julie julie
well then why were you saying i
don't know who you are you're no
i don't know who you are in
the in the context of the world
you're trying to brag about who you
are so you don't know my last
name ah you
no ah good old julie yeah no
googling no
was going why is your face lighting
up with whites
julie you know
do you know how about how about
getting a little mad libs blank and
arrow ah bo bowman no bo g
my guy or above finger using your
iso goldfinger earlier bow finger anyway as
for you yeah as for me yeah
now you know
we're done talking to me i see
look i'm more of a guys guy
you know i mean like i have
more with guys yeah can you get
him a bowl of water to put
on the floor
i was gonna say alright fine here
you go so you're a dog as
well yeah are obviously new to earth
so you're you're i mean look there
has been some messy animals who have
come through this office there's been garfield
there's been heath cliff always throw in
the fist phones around at cartoons yeah
and you're a real dog you're yesi
real dog well a messy but he
doesn't want i'm saying i'm a messy
real dopamax but i'm scared
because he's getting really old i'm actually
shocked he's still alive he was likely
going to he was popping about thirty
years ago so we're you know where
i'm concerned thirty years ago you were
popular in the nineties that's amazing do
you know one of my favorite movies
and it's ironic clifford for with charles
grodin i love him but i actually
charles grodin is a good friend of
his they were very other his movie
us yeah well ah dan dan dan
dan dan dan hey that's the alarm
saying we're out of time beethoven whoa
can you never knew who i was
your julie bowe what's her name bowman
bowen bowen yes oh my god bo
finger
alright now me and lauren
ah okay ah by the way lauren
i'm not thinking oh i know that's
what the joke was that's a joke
and i think someone from hotter family
we had a good time yeah did
you get that that's a joke
zepp your joke it
gallagher these two goons alright here we
go
okay
welcome thank you for being here how
are we feeling today rough um i'm
feeling
depressed
ah
oh
we're going through it okay i'm going
to try to say i can't even
i can't even write a song to
cover what i feel okay yeah i
just want to go home what do
you wanna do there i just want
to come home
can i ask you to get off
the couch cooks baby bath full of
water i would take it
just about to offer you thank you
i just want to come home hear
you i i don't want to be
here
now now you say you can't write
songs i'm just stuck i mean that
being with this guy it's too much
it's like it's just taking out my
creative energy i'm totally zapped i should
be i'm usually you know writing new
albums every few years you know i
mean i yeah i've got a lot
of hit and you could write a
few more
more you know get some a little
more money coming in here and say
thank you so much time in between
you're okay well you have no residuals
so it's not grand plenty of residuals
from the fifties i think those more
a thing yet until the brady bunch
yeah you're right
so maybe elegans stop and stop lying
about having money coming in to space
my point we know you're getting residuals
from ah these are tv specials that
you did i he doing specials yeah
i i had i had a very
popular television show but he doesn't i
mean
you get some zip residuals i've been
on tv a bunch i mean look
i like to make concerts that really
um yeah it's the thing but you
know anytime they repeat the grammys and
i chose nice a lot of my
songs are in movies i caught up
on all the grammys during the quarantine
so um it was easy to see
you there so many times and lassie
to see you there as well thank
you was really wonderful um you seen
i mean i'm in black and white
i'm dead
how do you like the color sometimes
yeah yeah that's true um don't let
me ask you as far as your
your albums go what's the last one
that you were really you felt really
proud of and connected to well like
i gotta say that i'm not trying
to say you don't have albums judy
kessler here's the here's the problem i
already did guess lastly here's the problem
with with him is
everyone loves his early work especially his
first big hit song and then he's
just being like obtuse with his career
and going off and doing like weird
solo stuff and and you know and
and totally changed his style can ever
been scuba diving yeah what's what's ah
have you not
you lassie have you ever been scuba
diving therapists ah no i haven't please
call me therapy doctor i ah i've
never been scuba diving i have a
terrible fear of the water um not
just when you train of any water
with those things in it that can
get me but aren't you afraid that
maybe there's like something that would happen
to your body when you're going under
them yeah that creature would get me
um but with like
yeah
maybe if you fell into a moon
shaped pool or anything you know a
moon like round yeah
so what i'd be worried about my
air supply if it started to run
out what would happen to your body
you know what happens to the body
when that starts for reno well i
would drown yeah no but but i
wo
that's what he's really a fanboy but
also you do here's the other here's
the other problem i mean here's the
here's the other big problem yeah everyone
loves the song right everyone loves the
song but then everyone thinks it's a
song by like some other band like
stone temple pilots or tfc or something
you know and it's like you yeah
because they have songs that are titled
the exact same thing and everyone gets
confused they all came out of the
sea
same time weirdly and nineteen ninety four
and everyone gets confused and it's hurting
his career it's hurting his career and
i just want him to go or
i'm just i'm just remembering the title
of every song from nineteen eighty four
i'm british and i'm out here just
so i
yeah i have an interesting look about
me i'm thin as you can see
a lot of people a lot of
people make the joke that ah he
should wind up with peppermint patty
you know which is fun even studies
with me right because his name is
thom yorke yeah exactly yeah you nailed
it so now we get there for
free
yes i would we oh i'm not
a therapist but who are you huh
daddy
ah and i won and all of
this how you play celebrity couples therapist
that was job sent by anonymous that
was fun good job thank you anonymous
is that the same anonymous who wrote
that the trump book and didn't tell
me were shakespeare radiohead
and and and then well just teacher
he's he keeps going back and forth
he does what should put out more
radiohead records button studies seems more interested
in his that's what i was trying
to show dakota yeah i'm your aid
and they haven't put out one since
we were in australia huh yea that's
where i first heard it radiohead this
uno's and plein oh no yeah i
want to go back to australia oh
i want to go back to the
back i'd go back i go i
took so long to get there but
it was fun we were so tired
that first day yeah it'd be more
fun to go for longer and to
fly like yeah not good just not
going to perth yeah
yeah and also i was doing press
and i was flying back and forth
from city yeah well you know baby
we know baby i had less from
the new guys if we could get
a new zealand that would be great
too oh i would love to go
to new zealand so i was asked
to go by ah musician i love
and gandalf
yeah so and they have no strums
his beard
he fucks it like violin strings that
would be cool if gandalf would take
five beard hairs just
including lupu
um alright guys we kept the six
everybody thanks for listening nothing funded them
sewed we'd love if you can say
this thanks for watching listen ah rate
and review all that stuff tell people
about the show we are ah freedom
usa on twitter and instagram
i'm um and if you want to
write if you wanna send a three-tier
i think it's three am usa gmail
dot com we could use them we
could use run
out put your name there new went
on the air um but alright everyone
shut up now and go to sleep
go to sleep tonight gonna turn nine
wow you worked
it worked
uh