three
if you'd like to make a call
please hang up and try again
oh yeah do they know it was
a good impression of that lady it
was certainly better than that impression you
did on the last episode of the
computer house dare you how i dealt
with hearing that well so how dare
har no longer dan which was if
you're sucking dick is good
yeah sucks oh haha
oh my god
welcome to three-time i'm scotch yeah we
have any introduced ourselves cove
both going home i'm lauren i'm paul
and this is freedom what's rubbing your
eyes i want to remind you ever
rub your eyes and it feels so
good have you ever been so hard
that like you can't see like wow
you doing now hey here's a recent
thing oh tell my fucking my left
side of my jaw started popping when
i chew now no never happened that
i was never an issue what are
you supposed to do about just one
day it started happening i don't know
i have dentist appointment this friday so
i'll see you in the face maybe
it would fix it that's where i'm
nisha right yeah that does work though
it works like a charm yeah yep
also a coconut falling on your head
oh yeah well that just has to
happen naturally though she'd say yeah yeah
you give you can't drop one up
i live in a coconut area you
have to get fluffed yeah that's just
the way it is some things will
never change i was slapped in the
food know who's that guy bruce hornsby
yeah this is wayne is ah i
know him by just that's just the
way it is but yeah he usually
goes by that but yeah
some things never change that is a
jam what was his other song i
don't know looks good mandolin wind oh
the man listen to me
there was a voice type that was
so popular today michael mcdonald so interesting
that everyone was like yeah wow you
categorize him is in the michael mcdonald
category the i do him
oh sure
it's basically the same thing um and
then there was like the these bans
damn yeah yeah the way here i
was listening to the president of the
united states of america she's wow she's
like he changes up she's in my
like didn't ever really surprise again peaches
come from a can
can they were put there by a
man covering every factory down town well
okay but here's my question would you
think it was coming when they wrote
lump that they thought it was gonna
be a huge hit oh gonna love
it no because they're like just a
little indie band and that was crazy
to everyone who's long slump yeah we
love yes i love scored i listened
to that
all the time did you feel i
loved that no idea what's about it's
about a guy named lump right yeah
no it's a woman named lump she's
lump she's lump she's lump i shall
remind me we mean he's gump gump
i'm probably thinking yeah i like the
name the presidents of the united states
of america it's great
band name yeah grace where are they
now want to know i bet they're
still around they replaced the animatronic presidents
in the city yeah so now it's
them yeah that's great so they just
seeing lump and peaches all know they
say all the stuff that the president
oh good it's hilarious to me that
they have but they do live they
had to put down trump in
it's so funny it's so sad that
when you go to disneyland have a
good time and then like walk in
your room and you got to see
him miss too long tie
a million years so it's updated with
the current people it was like the
current president and there it's like like
the year that this happened it must
have been like oh fuck guys we're
gonna die coated dogs seems boring when
i go much i want to go
now i like going to the to
the weird things that no one goes
to disneyland that's always nice
it's when it's like a cold inside
place that nobody's end because it's boring
like i love the trip i love
the train around the perimeter did you
see the movie a cold inside play
with a train around the premium isn't
right oh no the trail the trick
isn't boring no no i went one
time i've never been on it and
i was like boring thing that was
really cute i think i would have
laid and i was little like they
when they show you the little like
sierra yeah of the dinosaurs and stuff
yeah that's i like the old school
rubbings from the fifties that are that
people consider boring now that
no one lines up for example yeah
ah oh like the train or the
presidents for example like shit steamboat willie
no absolutely oh willie yeah i'll watch
that yeah exactly like all the seven
man straight assault it's essentially they played
the cartoon you go you walk yeah
it's a theater dedicated to one cartoon
or the magic shop that steve martin
used to work right around like oh
yeah i go in there i'm making
big plans to return to disneyland this
summer and whoa and better not stop
me i remember taking my nephew my
nephew yeah yeah they're going to base
around the wrong missy
yeah they're fun messy code sticker
it's a disney film you know that
um i know i'm really excited and
i i'm planning a trip and i'm
like it has to happen you're planning
a trip forty five minutes so well
because i want to get a hotel
room and i want whole thing well
so i was looking it up and
first of all the prices seem lower
right now and i don't know if
that's i know but i don't know
if that's like
right now and i should buy it
now just gonna stay in arrive man
yeah but i want to get a
room and have my parents come and
have my brother and wife his wife
and kids and just set up a
tent in here my father and my
wife brother and wife is what i
want said she is though that set
up a tent in your room um
oh why
i don't know yeah um one little
one little tip this that's kind of
like a grand californian as a place
to stay you stay they did not
like it did suck it i love
the lobby sucks a lot of your
scroll i am and you're right they're
adjacent to california fungi walking around you're
in yeah but it's not it's so
expensive
and it's not worth oh the well
the grant is fun california also doesn't
have like a pool which i don't
care about but little kids like well
kids love it yeah and that was
the thing about our nephew is like
we went to disneyland for i think
it was a one day maybe even
two and he had the most fun
at the pool
yeah people will just keep jumping totally
it's like over and oh we just
go to a hotel and you probably
have a great time but go to
a pool right but i usually take
them to disneyland whenever they visit and
now it's been two years since yesterday
then so i'm like i gotta make
it big and do a hotel and
you're going to more thing how do
you know if you know um they're
nine and six about oh i forgot
you had to have to
yeah they're getting older there we go
but still prime disneyland oh even better
because now they can really enjoy it
yeah yeah yeah like two years ago
or they loved it but it's like
they always hit that wall where then
they get exhausted and like started crying
and stuff and it's like i think
nine and six you're kind of like
ready to yeah partei partei yeah we
the old style you went with alyssa
over here um no sister-in-law and ah
she was young enough that she really
wanted goofy's autograph oh i chase him
down for the autograph and goo for
my nephews who he was on like
crack or something because he kept like
he kept doing this dance like you
can't catch me you can't get me
in he would like right away so
that's pretty fun typical
behavior of people who are on crack
you can't catch me yeah i was
just a shit man about it down
multiple characters when i was there with
them like these because i wanted to
fill the autograph book because when i
was little that was a highlight of
the one time i went to disney
world as a kid right i didn't
even know this was a thing oh
i would look at it over and
over a guy like all their stamp
a special signatures each one so it
was like i like gotta
get em all but i'm gonna do
it again we gotta just do it
again and i wonder it must be
you have if you are that character
you have to learn that signature yes
maybe have some looking right at you
motherfucker
well i also know this you're you're
telling me what it is instead of
just asking me ah well obviously i'm
i'm directing it at you so you
can confirm or deny famously scott played
bradbury v oh shit are you a
digital or goofy and there i was
rare bear a lot i was goofy
ally goofy when he got the big
bad wolf yeah i was goofy
oh no you know i was like
yes rbis everywhere um little john horribly
um no you don't have to learn
little john's a bear as well as
any you don't have to learn a
special signature just sign it the way
you know but there there there's this
the i thought there was a consistency
for lauren ah let's say i was
never taught any spell
she'll signature perhaps they have changed things
from what i understand they have air
conditioning in the suits now so a
lot has changed since heidi wrong and
i struck him wander off yeah well
i feel like ah shit lorne yeah
shashank you still have that autographed book
i do yes whores you they probably
lost there is by now so i'm
like i don't know if they maybe
they didn't maybe they cared but i
i cared i have everything over yeah
these kids today i know guys saved
it all people um but i do
love that stuff and i wanna bring
holly and then you know part of
i wanna get the hotel to such
a nap and seem to be so
crazy by yourself well yeah no i
mean like if i'm doing splash
they'll let you stay um in the
millennium falcon why if you pay him
enough really but under like in the
out of the way they hide people
yeah yeah i've never been to california
adventure um oh you gotta go because
cars land is really where it's at
no i don't care about cars at
all but the last
land is orlando's good the land is
greatly man is so very poetic it's
very i think and i think we've
gotten shit for talking about disneyland before
but you know what yeah people like
it because people think it's corporate bullshit
everything things they also think like aren't
shot adults white-out tissue and so much
well sometimes on yeah funded
like you're fuckin cleaners oh i love
to look long before i ever had
a baby i was disneyland all the
time when i moved here i was
so confused because everyone in at usb
had a fucking season passages land and
they'd be going all the time on
their days you know when they have
work anything just a whole erp confused
but it was all the time
all the time then i was like
oh i guess someone goes a distant
well it's right there so i guess
everyone just go no it's it's like
an hour yeah but it's closer than
you've ever been if you're from chicago
you know it's like wow this is
amazing so i got my season pass
and i would go quite often i
went a few times a year off
quite often oh but it's so fun
to have it near right so close
by i bet a half
full of times over the years ah
the the thing about disneyland that i
always have this moment anytime i've been
where it's like you see the the
magic and innovation of it especially if
you go to like an older thing
yeah
but you also see like the the
like the money behind it like the
the the the thirst for money all
the money like the cynicism of it
as an adult yeah yeah it's wild
it's because they both exist at the
same time yeah they they like that
thing with the birds from around the
world whatever that the tea room the
tiki room it's like you see the
nineteen fifties magic
of it of like or sixty s
whenever we made like that that they
had an idea of like we're gonna
make these things um that nobody's ever
seen before it's going to be charming
and blah blah blah blah blah it's
gonna make a shit ton of money
exactly yeah yeah yeah but like there's
a there's a the method to it
of it has to be
be that you it has to be
that you don't see the cynicism of
it yeah it has to be like
people have to be charmed by it
kids have to have like wonder in
their eyes when they gaze upon these
things but also we're gonna be fucking
rich yeah it's really it's a lot
of art and yeah exactly it's weird
like movies it's weird how they exist
side
by side yeah you know it all
wrapped up in the same thing but
i mean it doesn't it doesn't mean
that it's not special i do like
the fact that disney keeps things like
the tiki room and the old stuff
that they could easily yeah pave over
and shoot something yo in i mean
yes they do that all the time
adventures of and in inner space where
i teach
touched my first boob that's a good
example
right after you say excuse me ma'am
are you crushed by oma
ah but after that it's gone now
it's ah i think it's a sartorial
like permanently gone yeah it start tours
but they could swap things in and
out like they put them like because
i think when i saw the tiki
room it was like reopened or some
well they definitely update
things sometimes are like give it a
facelift or whatever but they but the
tiki room is a good example of
something that's like charming from nineteen fifty
five but to modern audiences like if
if you don't just buy into the
charm oh it's a transgenic it's very
easy to go like let's just put
something new in there like i'm dutch
german bird and i like to sing
about pratt
otto right and small it's a small
world is a great example it's huge
yeah it takes up so much real
estate and it's so boring yeah and
it's just there and it's so long
and stupid but i like my life
that's great yeah like
yeah i liked anything where you go
in something like a boat like that
was always exciting orca trains yeah i
feel like that it's a great ride
for that i know is it's great
but that's what i mean is it's
great but and they could very easily
go like let's just make this star
wars whatever yeah instead they keep it
around because it's charming which i which
i love the ah you know the
the ce
cement footprints and handprints in front of
the theater they swap those out too
yea do yes not not really the
newer ones but they but they've they've
made like ooh ahh
do you mean the newer ones are
the ones like oh what are these
like people from the thirties the snow
or you know they already fifty xl
yeah sometimes like add because there's so
such limited real estate there now and
they were just given me away for
wow yeah that now they just like
kind of move in and out like
it's interesting huh that's also kind of
sad like clara bow or whoever the
fuck yeah well see three people is
more famous than you
but even the star trek people it's
like you know because they have the
whole big ah federation in sydney and
all they put in there like at
some point people are not gonna give
a shit and they'll just swap those
yeah i mean i guess that's it
at some point wherever the podcasts cement
you know things are yeah we put
rector so many cements
mouths
raiders are yours in our rears yep
i just watched this movie kimi oh
i was ah it's so natalie joined
on my app of some sort and
guess what surprise surprise andy daly's in
this movie oh yeah he uses a
lot of comedians well not not not
as many
a been on this show i was
in the informant you are away because
it has an exclamation mark yes that's
right he used yes means yes paul
i haven't taught paul and i haven't
seen a lot of your your bank
works i would say pepperoni guys don't
want a big word no but i
mean even that's a big movie or
whatever like i want i would like
to see that and i wonder
are your what are your big works
you've got the informant there will be
blood if there's any boy i saw
before i knew you but i haven't
rewatched the sione in the picked-up this
far away my biggest film role i
think i have two scenes right
people really remember that yes they do
and of course it was not a
big hit at the time but then
ah dvd it became ah much more
pacquiao what's
i don't want to say ah hey
so it's a private show
yea yeah huh
um meanwhile over here we got the
wrong missy and babysitters your favorite thing
i mentioned the wrong missy ally asian
fuckin drag world how about that bitch
alright isn't is there any kind of
universal studios i guess with it what
kind of jurassic park representation do they
have their they have the right there
is a ride
yeah i know okay agree they read
to the right and i don't know
what i haven't been on it though
what happens on the ride okay i
haven't been there
so i'm not looking at first of
all you are though and then i
stopped when i asked my question oh
first of all before you to this
nerd had been willing yeah before you
get there you you watch tv s
where your guy is there this is
at home now this is this is
before you know like when you're in
line yeah there's no d before you
get to universal studios
you watch tv
yeah so your guy is there ah
welcome welcoming you and saying things your
number yes he's not my guy but
saying his brother is my guy but
saying things like welcome to jurassic park
and also goodbye
dion dido
yes it's
so he's sitting there like introducing guys
and peddling my mom would say i
saw your friend on t tonight oh
my oh would you say the comedian
who does the political songs with the
piano now she's three mark russell i
told you my mom said because there's
ah
there's this punk ah musician milo aquaman
that i'm not related to and everyone
always asked me are you related to
future man he's in the descendants i
believe and everyone's like are you related
or your we're not but my mom
you related you're related you related everyone's
like our hero aladdin are you related
are you related are you related
mom was like stay away of task
my mom was like like an auction
hey he's he's claiming that you're related
on his website what and i was
like what his website and i go
his websites wikipedia yeah huh i was
like he's not claiming that mom anyone
can edit
comedian comedy bang my van is claiming
yeah that is so funny i'm so
okay so you
like someone's updating on wikipedia so you
get into a like it's it's a
flume ride so you can do a
lower sun yes you're in the dress
maybe it's not a log is it's
for the whole log do remember that
yeah
benson bit oh yeah good i you
know what i gotta take my nephew
c universal that's ah easy yes yeah
that's an easy day it's way cheaper
there are a lot of ah it's
it's a little more hardcore than than
disneyland in terms of like you know
the rides or more riser a little
more yeah backroom but i
love that the movie to arrive where
you see jaws and all those oh
that's fun yeah and that's a good
twenty eight thirty minutes and you go
through fast and furious and there's this
just i tell you about the extra
and the the background artists the fast
furious ride where he's like and they
left it in but he likes slaps
this model on the butt as they're
leaving and they left
it into the final cup anyway how
ru seems to me to me yeah
yeah that was bad in any case
so you go into it not displaying
the class of the franchise
you go into the the car you
you're having a nice you know ah
doctoral oh so i wish you have
a nice docile ride as you look
at sega sources and stuff and then
you go down the wrong ah you
got the wrong guy
and some bodies so the magic school
bus and you go down the wrong
pipe and they start choking and then
you're like sorry i guess there's this
part that's like out of order out
of order don't go don't enter but
you accidentally go that way and they're
like no don't go that way it's
lot like splash mountain and that way
and then you're in the dangerous part
of the ride and does anyone yell
from the log we have
oh i hope so stop screaming at
me um and then there's like dinosaurs
that spit water at you which is
fun okay um and dinosaurs that come
out at you and then you go
up like a big ah incline and
then ah right is and then you're
in the dark and rice zo and
then
right as your like stars feel like
they're on the ride right as you're
moving through it suddenly of a huge
t rex comes down and is about
to eat you and you're going right
in it's mouth i was hoping a
little one would come out and then
you think you're gonna be eaten but
that's where the drop is and you
drop down thank god for that trump
dad um they put that there and
and our nephew
hate tid is so scared or he
just said we have the funniest picture
of him crying as as he's going
down it he hates it so much
it's so funny because even maybe now
he would be fine with it but
had he seen jurassic park
i don't know okay so this is
on that's part of it too know
but just the whole right of like
going down the incline things like that
and all that but once i was
trapped on that ride i got trapped
in indiana jones really what parts i
got trapped in the closet
i got trapped in the line right
before you get on but i was
in a stairwell up to the long
i couldn't they couldn't let us out
as tweet that just being in line
no but they couldn't we were there
for hours our couldn't let us out
we were too far i think to
go back or something it was like
anyone out but but we we they
wouldn't but they couldn't there was some
reason
i remember what it was that the
power went out or something crazy oh
and so we were down there for
hours my friend and i oh and
i mean it was really boring but
um we were trapped on the jurassic
park ride on the incline going up
oh wow and it was like kept
trying to to get us up so
it kept jerking us up
oh and this was the first thing
we did in the morning because it
was the most popular ride it just
opened and so this was at seven
fifteen in the morning oh my counter
too early trump for forty five minutes
without a ride at seven fifteen a
layer yes
oh a scare right
why are they even open yet they
really shouldn't be so we're trapped in
this for forty five minutes and there
was this like old man with his
grandson behind us who were when they
got on the right was like yeah
we're on it and it was like
gonna be a great day for them
and buy in by like minute twenty
five they were arguing he was like
i don't know what to do just
cutting me i will
horrible to ruin their doing not getting
my honus wagner baseball card now oh
my god and then and then all
they did at the end of it
ripped by yeley like we finally after
forty five minutes we went through no
one's in the mood to be scared
of that pointing to go down the
incline or anything comes up everyone's like
oh yeah yeah
at the end we get off the
ride and there's just a guy passing
out like line front of line passes
to it to to go on again
he's like here we go they should
again i was like twenty bucks to
allow the restaurants that was the only
time that i've written like a complaint
letter to universal studios and i wrote
like a letter describing the experience
science and they had just had because
they had been testing the ride out
it had sprayed hot oil on a
bunch of you know before i did
ever opened officially oh yeah hot oil
it scarred people why and so in
the letter i wrote like after forty
five minutes we were just wishing someone
would spray hot oil
sassy yelp review and this is the
only time it's ever happened they called
me personally and apologized and gave me
free tickets to return to the park
wow did they say at any point
like you didn't need to be sarcastic
i like to think that she thought
it was funny but the one thing
she said you still have your receipts
to get in
and i said no i'm sorry we
threw it away she goes i'll still
give you the tickets yeah goddamn right
you oh wow but what a nice
person a nice person anyway they've revamped
it now i don't know if it's
an ex so that might not describe
the ride at all yes but it
was great for the time oh it
was amazing alright
any ride you guys want to describe
should we take a break backdraft greatest
ride in history what happened is i
went on it once i don't remember
you get just hot like you go
from place to place and then it's
like here's a here's another fire here's
a different i guess shit is like
falling down because it's a burning building
or something it's like what a weird
idea it's so weird i remember being
that yeah it was bad alright let's
take a break but i wanted to
tell you
alright amor back i know i am
came back in the middle of lawrence
xian i was here no no you're
here but i felt bad because like
i said ann were back glanced over
nah hippopotamus time over there oh my
goodness i'm great m d wish they're
revamping the jump of jungle cruise and
a german cruise jumble cruise are you
going to do a word jumble as
you take a cruise have you guys
ever wanted to take a cruise i've
been upgraded allison
i hate cruises um i just think
there's gonna take you a while to
get your sea legs or yes it
did alone well a few days i
was really sick during it um that
was the time where my boyfriend at
the time was growing the second city
and on the cruise and so i
went to visit and anyone like improv
on a cruise
i think they really did but um
the the is really cool bug has
had to stay in rooms that had
no window if i recall correctly songs
yeah so it was like kind of
throws you off to a little bit
i think yeah because you are staring
down in the bilge yeah because you
you you get seasick or or carso
like when your eyes are not able
to see to wear movies yes so
i felt really horrible for a lot
of that and then i remember watching
the show and then getting up afterwards
and like everyone was like falling over
walking up the stairs because there started
to be like a very rocky thing
during the show and the cast was
like sliding around and then we all
stood up at the end and everyone
was like look
like falling over because it had no
sounds sounds whore why does anyone go
on these things i don't know who
the alaska ones are nice i mean
i think it's cool to see multiple
things but i just think i don't
really want to be on oh you
think here
these guys let's go on it just
seems really like not ah also this
was in hawaii and like you just
get out at different islands for like
a day and get to walk around
lake i'd rather just stay on one
island and enjoy myself than like go
around they're all similar when you're only
seeing them for a moment and you
you basically get off and yeah you
could like get a sense of yeah
yeah i do
don't think i would like like the
puerto rico cruises or whatever like yeah
i stayed on the boat yeah where
was in the boat it was to
the caribbean both times and you didn't
get to do three times and i
didn't get off well because i figured
because for that reason i was like
i would rather just go there once
to go see like in some times
someone selling you t-shirts and stuff on
a dock essentially that's it
it yeah i mean that's what i
wanna see should i have gotten off
oh shit
at that point i did want to
see that because i didn't like being
on the boat but yeah um because
it doesn't ruin your sea legs when
you get back on probably it probably
made it worse i don't know i
don't remember but yeah i i don't
i really am not a huge fan
of boats in general i can't remember
a time where i loved on our
honeymoon we went out on a dolphin
you know what
they wrote adolphe mary's exciting you guys
got on a dolphin first of all
you guys got married whoa second all
you wrote a dolphin oh no we
got it we went on a cruise
that were dolphin watching i mean that's
neat to get to see animals like
whale watching cruises that seems really cool
and it was all fun and we
saw so many dolphins and video them
took pictures it was great and then
they were
like oh by the way on the
way back this is going to be
pretty rough and so total sick like
barfi rama i think we talked about
this because i went on that whale
watching jane and i went on that
one and iceland oh that's not see
a single whale on the the sea
was so rough i forgot people were
like vomiting all over the place for
it but i'd rather go
iceland i want to go to iceland
and like see what's iceland is great
and now ice age man to get
their land and not ice water by
drink that at home i named it
i loved how rough it was i
it was i loved it it was
like a ride or you're an officer
i don't get seasick i don't i
don't get just like i don't get
moshe sandwell your opposite guy i love
those cookies
they're sandwich crackers with dirt in them
no calories and dirt
that's what a lot of people don't
realize yeah that's what you need all
the dirt you why you will ever
get oh i love it i love
it yeah i'm permanent pica yeah
pike always make you think of um
the my strange addiction yeah like i
say we need drywall well there's one
way you couch cow shows a woman
who would eat cow sh sheesh that
was she's addicted couch and it was
like the stuffing here the the fomo
stuff is she is anything so much
as the solution to that usually
just admitting it well there was like
no they keep doing it like there
was another fill ins deutsche couple where
they were obsessed to watch this one
like a couple of years ago they
were obsessed with getting giving themselves coffee
enemas all fucking day they would the
head start working from homes they could
do it all day they did it
all day
i mean i feel like little stations
in their house where they would like
do it oh my god i like
the bathroom i know how to lay
on the floor something so i don't
know well let's first assembles there's no
such thing as a normal mind the
mind is like okay so i guess
you i like doing coffee
ah no but you know what i
mean if anyone out there you always
sit in the same place this is
curious if anyone out there has a
strange addiction i'd love to hear about
it well also just you know a
lot of empathy towards people like who
knows where where the mind is wow
you course i'm happy i'm just having
fun talking about these coffee
your strange addiction i feel bad for
the guy who was eating drywall because
like he knew it was making him
sick yeah there was a woman who
ate um cat oh god cat cat
fur and balls she would like roll
it up and then put it in
her mouth into it and people in
her family are begging her to stop
and then you enter the doctor and
they were like well you have a
blockage it's the key
cat fur um you know you really
have to stop doing that yeah and
she was like i'm not gonna talks
about this i don't know if we
have but i know it from san
manteo yeah so why but i feel
like i've i've tried to say it
on this podcast before i'm sure i
brought up eating couch but i don't
think i mentioned i feel we've talked
about that stranger my strange addiction i'm
sure
well we've talked about it for sure
but i don't know if we talked
about the more recent episodes okay so
what's going on know that there's some
saying that coffee enemas and the cat
hair so what is what does a
coffee enema ah they put coffee up
their anus and then um it makes
them awake all day or assumption doesn't
coffee come out the anus or come
out yeah i think it comes out
like soon
now coffee fountain say they have to
be close to the bathroom all day
which is another reason why they want
to work from home so they could
have these animals and then do this
in the name that's the couple had
created this ritual together
that's fun that there they do it
together yeah i think that makes it
really romantic and cute and it's like
not a problem it also makes it
more of a sustainable addiction if somebody
else is doing right there with you
that's true about addiction in general i
is to show intervention stolen i don't
know if that is that show is
so dark it was i got into
watching it for i would say like
a month or two and then i
just couldn't
i'll take it anymore that's how i've
been with hoarders like sometimes i just
kill the one i remember the most
though was there was a guy young
man who was addicted to video segments
you do you're addicted video games yeah
right
it's become a real shame um are
we playing less he was later he
was he so he's playing video games
all the time and it was impacting
his life and impacting he had a
relationship he had a girlfriend and so
when they get to the intervention part
well of course but when it got
to the intervention part the intervention was
so short
because the girlfriend was like if you
don't stop doing this i'm gonna have
to leave you is like stop any
well like that stuff the same as
other types of dough but it was
like well so of course most of
the show is the addiction and you
see the person doing it and you
talk to the people that it's affecting
you know and all that shit mean
i always remember as the one woman
who sucked canned air
oh you know what yeah let's spray
air yes so spray dust is is
an intervention part of my strange addiction
or no no this was an intervention
okay and she would suck that it's
basically get really high and talk really
slow and then oh wait wait she's
sucking the nitrous whatever it comes in
those dust spray cans she's just so
easy
president nitrates well there must be something
in it because you know like whip
its winces or major slows the brain
or something i don't know write whatever
it was she'd be like if there
was a whole compilation on youtube of
her going like um walk god said
shy and yes she's do it yeah
she's not just not doing literally air
she's doing yeah so
nothing in the stuff that's in there
that makes it come out yeah yeah
okay that makes sense anyway it was
pretty intense wow stuck with me stuck
with me yeah whenever i see one
of those cans i think of that
the thing that really bummed me out
was that at the end they would
do it like an update on the
people yeah you know and then there
was i would say half
of them went back to using it's
really sad yeah it was really sad
yeah okay you're out there struggling with
something there are a lot of resources
that yes absolutely please absolutely we don't
know any we're not making light of
that it's that you're saying you watching
the show i'm not me i'm trying
not to make light of it at
all it was just a bug i'm
not even making light of it with
the walkmans
hi i'm a good person
i'm saying it just stuck with me
forever yeah yeah that was like the
video thing i stopped me like he
was like you've never played a video
game since then no when i kept
a girlfriend
my country my god yes i've and
it's gotta be as fun like dead
he was ah he was waiting on
quandary in texas anymore gotta be game
buddies oh yum ps five yes i
do i got one i was i
had the weird thing where i ordered
online and i just got it it
was like i had there i got
whatever i get oh yeah and i
it's like a whole pan the whole
pandemic my friends been trying yeah and
people were like man these are impossible
and i was like let me just
get on a wait list or something
or whatever and it was like i
i can't remember might even best buy
i was like do you want to
pick it up at stores like yes
next day when nah oh yeah awesome
yeah yeah just waiting for bestbuy show
godwin sure what are you're playing games
well ah cool up gave me a
tabletop pacman galaga for christmas wow like
a fudge right in there really yes
that means like an arcade game yeah
it's arcade but it's instead of the
standup it's a tate it's a tabletop
like pac man seriously that's one of
those
screen was ah like a tape on
the table oh but yeah it's dig
dug galaga galaga has been the one
we've been playing the most because there's
like a ton of different pac man
stuff um but i like gallagher lot
of fun so everyone's also just come
into my office while i'm working and
be like it's gallagher time
yes up and we play some gallagher
together it's fun also she's just play
yourself she's okay you're awesome wow i
enjoy nah he's like a marsan helicopter
almost missed it i now yeah
really getting there for man can't yeah
can you what i don't know if
i can finish
there's there's just okay okay this is
hard hard for you this is my
friend but if it's patrick comedian out
of out of new york there's a
new jersey will say that um one
of my oldest friends
he when he was growing up there
was this funeral home in his where
he lived
called the house of gayer
g a y e yes and so
i think it was a lot of
people mistake it for something else or
like they go in and go oh
i'm surprised as a funeral well with
the last name of the people yeah
i think so and so when he
was a kid his a friend of
his i think started this i think
it was in the friends
neighborhood houses gayer because buddy and i
grew up not that far from each
other um and so they there was
a thing where they would like say
like when they were kids this is
when they were children of course
gay gay house of gayer going gay
come out gay here
i don't know how this evolved
but it got to be that
if you started saying it the other
person's challenge was to say say gayer
before you got to the end of
the front ah it's a pretty fun
one so like gay gay hell so
good yeah yeah exactly like that so
then we started doing it as adults
like he told us this right and
then we saw
noted doing it
and so i randomly pops into my
brain like i can't remember what made
me think of it just now where
were we talking about i don't even
know what we're talking about you being
gay
oh yeah you're gonna come out being
a herb
you're gonna tug glass ah goddamn like
this show how do we what i
can't come out on a podcast on
dvd f o nine even his own
podcast that's how selfless he is he's
great guy
and gave it to mark marathi his
old fucker
what do you do in brazil plug
that book oh no he didn't write
the book for two years he planned
that bo yeah yeah crappy it's gonna
take todd glass thirty minutes to write
a book of course it took him
two years you can read a book
but if you've not read todd glass's
book it's really missed out i haven't
seen well i'm sam i'm so long
either got him as i haven't seen
because like yeah i mean like i
feel like the last time he's armored
those stained glass episodes one of the
fun everyone's passion guys ever want everyone's
only takes me too says hey advertised
my show for me well what's it
called
it's called the todd glass show their
ego yeah we did it no text
necessary very funny do you want me
to give todd you you his number
you want me to give todd you
his number why was it still it
could well you couldn't get it out
second about why would i need his
number no i want to give todd
your numbers so he can text you
random huh
oh so laura and i would really
appreciate it but i have a show
that's showing you know honestly be once
every two years i think i've i
don't know if i've ever met him
maybe once one of the funniest guys
just so weird and funny he's so
great you truly and so nice too
to me like when i first started
yeah mainly because he wanted me to
rye
get him songs for his act he
could have been nicer to me when
i first started oh why what happened
he was fine he just could have
been more now he was so so
nice but he could have been nicer
he could have been a guy that
took me a sense that you're so
great and just keep at it yeah
why didn't he do that he'd never
did it never did it huh never
did i never did never did it
davidow
emanated i did want to say paul
you should keep out at comment thank
you i'll take it into your site
so good at there's no time limit
on it you can tell me anytime
yeah i just want to say i
won't tell you now that i think
you should you're really good and i
think you should keep pursuing this thank
you very much thank you for coming
from both of you that means to
don't tell you my mom at one
point she stopped doing this like maybe
ten years ago but stopped encouraging me
no stopped encouraging me to go back
to school
yeah i'd like it even up to
maybe ten years ago she's like do
you ever think you're going to go
back and get your degree i'm like
why she's like well you can't know
everything can you it's like she was
couching couching it like there's still so
much to learn and you know and
that that is the only reason i
like everyone's all look up a look
hookup like community college classes and kind
of go like would it be fun
to take a class we we have
talked about this a little bit and
i i do think that could be
cool and the you don't know the
homework you know you can do you
can watch lectures online like yeah sometime
exactly yeah yeah mike does that something
had to be a good husband why
am i not surprised
yeah you have to go to that
one yet
mike we love him we love ray
you he's doing good he's right because
he's taking to fatherhood he loves it
he loves that baby she loves the
making the baby or the happy lady
every scarf joe ordeal forward from meal
from soup to nuts literally when you
were a baby i love the whole
ordeal of you yeah i can't really
say that on her
are wedding day loves it so much
does he ever like holder yep he
does wow i love how much he
loves it i think you also sir
he yeah you know he cleans he
helps how's the old diaper sitch well
he just texted me that she pooped
and went all the way up to
her neck so he just sleeps
i mean babies are like a fine
now how is this happening and now
it's so far
it worked because like was she upside
down squished up or something oh lying
yeah okay yeah not like standing up
now
wow he was holding her upside down
and then it just dripped down to
toe that's not what happened no no
no she was just sitting there i
think it just happened to happen to
me almost every other day i mean
yeah you put on your neck isn't
just this happened how does shit on
their neck before come get over yourselves
yeah i really do
don't care about ah the poop anymore
you know i mean you just get
me into novels yeah oh no that's
the thing when you love something yeah
we said yes you love your dog
shit yes yeah it's like you don't
i don't care about my dog shit
i see it but there was a
coyote shit over there the other day
and i was just like google god
again when you say the other day
this is months ago right now
it was story just another lady again
just candy shop and i'm like yeah
cool cool i've started chasing coyotes again
last night what does she does she
have an implement when she does it
and she she's gotten a slingshot and
this she started practicing why joe slingshot
for christmas
and i'm like don't hit the coyotes
with a slingshot but she started practising
practice slingshot for christmas i feel like
it was kevin seizure or something but
that trip makes sense one hundred percent
but um so last so last night
um her sister parked over there and
and called her and said hey cool
i see a coyote by your pool
and so cool i've came rushing out
like yeah
a guy at a hair and that's
just to keep them away well we
want to make it unpleasant for them
to be here because you know we
don't want them eating her time sorry
to say that sounds fun i know
to be left by cool if cool
on commentor yelled at me like yeah
i would have a ball
maybe she came over so we do
a show here like are you talking
to me and she's like yes paul
get out like trying to make yourself
look big and everything like yeah guy
do they do they run away they
run away but then i think i
told you this they give you one
last look like are you serious and
you gotta give him one last thing
of like yeah i'm serious and then
they finally see you tomorrow night while
we got the flashing lights lights which
will animal evil wearing they don't work
they
last night they're so scared they scare
me yeah okay the michigan i'm never
coming back here oh no oh my
god you're teen wolf medusa your team
will routine whoa
ha i've never seen the film classic
i've seen teenagers you know scott ah
yes i've seen teen wolf and have
you seen tee-off two with jason bateman
classic that was in my monster book
though ah teen wolf was not but
i was excited when teen wolf came
out because i would i would borrow
these books from the library which were
the universal monster books and they they
these these are a bunch of books
that apply to everyone the chapters on
every iteration of the monster right so
it was
like if you could check out the
werewolf and it had like okay here's
lawn cheney's here's this one here's the
sequels here's hoping castello and then and
i was a teenage werewolf which is
the michael landon movie and so when
teen wolf came out i was like
oh a new new thing that would
be put in a book if they
ever updated it so i was very
wow i wonder if they've updated it
i'm able to watch the guy
was the only person checking these new
screen movie i'll watch the news screaming
out on um streaming somewhere this month
i can't wait do you know i
listen to a podcast makes told you
about it please
for you wish a podcast called too
scary didn't watch yeah hosted by these
strong women and they two of them
are scared to watch scary movies and
one of them is not and so
she tells the the she she gives
like a breakdown of the movie cool
up i'll do this where she'll just
read summaries of it yes exactly this
which i didn't realize that was a
thing
but a lot of people to someone
who doesn't want to see it will
just they want to know what's happening
in it like like take ah malignant
for instance my later malubay yeah every
time every time i see i like
that every time but malignant like such
a good concept but cool up doesn't
want to watch it so i actually
don't
anything about it but yeah i also
haven't seen hereditary i just know that's
fucking scary hereditary scary yeah i don't
know if i want to i don't
i like to scream i always loved
scream yeah and i like the scream
franchise and so the screen feels good
i've seen like it and some other
things that i thought i would never
see but i don't love i don't
go to my
good things about yeah it's not it's
not scary in the way that other
malignant oh yeah i don't know i
don't know the plot i've no idea
but i'd like to see it so
i will skip over i'm now i'm
now going through their back catalogue and
so i'll skip over the movies that
i want to see so okay so
they'll just like this person just explains
the whole plot people
and the other hey yeah ask questions
of style yeah well one of their
host ask questions no they just listen
and comment and everything you know they're
just silent
yeah but curious what the conversation goes
okay it goes it goes all over
the place yeah they talk about whatever
so they don't have to like yeah
they don't have to like ask they
don't have to ask what happened today
on shit better than this show oh
for absolutely people why wouldn't be listening
to that and so this well you'd
only get a lot in one podcast
listen to everyone
i listen to as many as they
want or why it's true yeah if
you guys only listen to three of
them i listen to one podcast at
a time wow you can listen to
more but i like this podcast very
much but they ah so scream i
didn't think i was gonna watch the
new scream and then i started listening
that episode and i was like actually
you know what i wanna see this
movie you know what i would like
some recommendations
of podcasts if someone wants to tweet
oh btf of you know what i
i just listened to people i know
mostly and i'm not trying to sound
whatever with them though we know about
people who make podcasts and i love
puig and i love the deep dive
i would like some podcasts of people
i probably don't know because i just
started going a little wormhole and i
saw this podcast
gee thanks just bought it and i
was like oh i might like this
stuff like add to cart it's about
shopping right yeah i would like more
recommendations if anyone knows maybe i should
okay what do you have a certain
type of podcast that you like conversational
style yeah i like conversations and i
and i do like listening to women
having conversations okay
i listen to a lot of men
talking about shit to jason to women
having conversations well you know i'm talking
about marla so let's do a lot
of men it's very easy to find
podcasts i would like to know like
what are the best give me some
good recommendations out there you know i
mean you might have one i will
look at my subscriptions and and see
what i think you might like great
i'm happy to do it because i
will not do that for you i
don't
i want you to i don't think
your recommendation diet do you listen to
podcast at all i don't even know
if you do oh of course i
do
but i'm not going to tell lower
in what they are fair yeah these
are my podcast was like oh my
god loves last podcast and the left
which i've listened to a lot with
him and i really like it too
but i want i'm like i want
my fandom i want like you know
i wanna like find like my people
that i don't know who i'm excited
to listen to totally yeah that's why
your own special thing that's why i'm
not going to tell you yeah
that's how i felt about this show
and i think you might like it
too starting wow check it out well
we have to take a break even
though that felt like a commercial for
whatever you were talking about but we're
gonna
sorry god i didn't know we had
rules all of a sudden we do
we should establish the rules house like
they're going to come up there i
did a tie gear damage oh alright
we'll be right back
where back and bad nature time which
means a game and speaking of games
i have to say this yeah and
it it breaks my heart to say
this oh no
as we all know wordle was purchased
by the new york times the paper
of record yes the old gray lady
the the creator of wardle josh wardle
got millions of dollars good for him
and we know we know it's at
least one million
so a million and one dollars we
know it's seven figures so so good
for him it could be nine million
we don't even know i think it's
nine point nine million dollars and good
for him and they just didn't want
to say they're giving figures good for
him and his labour and created for
but
we have learned
that we are no longer all having
the same shared experience just shoot the
word is i feel like a mike's
word is different today okay we're gonna
need to investigate ah yes yeah but
there was a story about it because
shane my sandro the word yeah he's
in the world because the original world
is a day ahead or something
something like that something like that by
the way there we haven't even talked
about wordle on this show but no
we have at some point i know
world people are sick of hearing about
wordle but at some point lauren learned
about wordle i've been playing for two
days i think at that point we
had tried to keep it from her
lauren learned about words that she was
too young and she she got very
excited and she texted a sol and
said we all have to start playing
word author every day i'd send each
other each other yeah let's compete with
each other and i was like i
thought it was so wholesome and i
was like lauren good for you too
for finding some way to keep us
connected during the pandemics and
and and i was like you know
what and it is
like a month ago but i was
like
decree two here we don't see each
other as much as me two years
to figure out how to keep us
connected though yeah so you're right i
thought it is i is a nice
way to check in with each other
in the mornings ah sometimes in the
evenings i see when sometimes a short
time like like you played at five
thirty today yeah i played a fine
job somebody's for thermal i was like
what the hell
well um yeah but ah anyway so
it's been fun but then the new
york times took it over of course
all of my my streaks and stats
erased all of jane's streaks and stats
erase and are still there but i
have a new york times subscription is
that why mine are still there i
don't have new york times subscription but
mine erased after the first time i
played after
new york times took it over but
then i immediately played again and now
i knew the word yeah and then
my stats were back oh interesting so
i don't know while i'm ah yeah
anyway so it's been but that sucks
that sucks but the the fact that
we're not not everybody isn't doing is
having the same
experience takes ninety nine percent of the
fun out of whoa what on earth
are they doing changing the war i
don't understand it and the whole point
of the fucking game is i don't
know how to even post your score
on twitter yeah because people know what
yeah that yeah i don't know how
there are two versions of it that
doesn't make any sense to me let's
talk about today because severe pain dorsal
i hate that
i'd say that but it's the world
will know i saw lords the same
time no it's a brain fart somebody
pushing somebody plays quarrel that i know
and i'm like i'm not doing for
this come on i know let's talk
about today's word because i've worried that
mike is playing the different one okay
let's see what that word here is
cock okay that's what i had oh
hey now now
now he played he got the c
right he got the k right and
then he got then he gets something
on the middle one i may ask
him to send me his what's his
first yes send the screenshot because i
was trying to figure out what because
sometimes i'll look at you guys as
words and i'll try to figure out
what yeah words you guess i
i think that will be a fun
way to keep us connected to is
like what if we guessed everyone's previous
previously unworkable but i was trying to
guess his first word and i find
out i didn't think it was possible
because it had it can't be the
u so it had to be an
l or something so i was like
what did he guess first first word
and then i started worrying that he
and his second word i started worrying
that he had a different rudeness yeah
that's gonna freak me out because we'll
see if he writes me sick with
worry it's gonna free i was so
i've just been sitting here the entire
time we've been recording saying i hope
this comes up well the other day
nicole parker ah my co-host of the
neighborhood listen um she said her husband
played at
and when the word was aroma he
got a gora
right so yes so two different words
in the same household when they made
them similar to a yea word yeah
i don't like it one bit don't
like it or maybe yeah maybe he
just gets to gore and thought he
guessed wrong here's the
advisers he got but that's why me
and vice versa who like he just
he put in aroma and was like
in his mind he thought he put
in a gora alright can we play
a game yes this game is called
so just like yells into the other
room it's a gora for me dolly
really goes huh
the french toast is submitted by gina
my den one claire is the clue
giver and thinks of something that the
other players will guess at for example
mount rushmore or ghostbusters or a chocolate
bar the rest of the jersey on
the ghostbusters mount rushmore made of chocolate
probably bill murray i think um
terrell brandon probably up their game again
and kristin wigg melissa manchester know what's
her name melissa
don't cry yeah the rest of the
players and nope slimer dude aka i
need head of course the rest of
the players and no particular order yeah
but shut up
ah what do you mean somebody thinks
of the four ghostbusters okay so one
player is the clue giver and thinks
of something that the other players will
guess at for example mount rushmore ghostbusters
chocolate bar could be anything okay the
rest of the players in no particular
order asked the clue giver comparative questions
in the form of is it more
like x or more like y
to the best of their ability chooses
the x or y that's more like
the answer got it and in the
first question the game axes french toast
in all subsequent questions access whatever the
lawgiver said was more like the answer
for example if question one is is
it more like french toast or bass
fishing and the clue giver says it's
more like bass fishing the next question
must begin with is more like bash
fishing bass fishing or
or friendly game ends when someone offers
a gas and guesses correctly with dancers
french toast why would the person say
it's more like bass fishing of the
choices no no friends just when you've
used in the first question got it
okay so this is extremely subjective it's
really yeah that's that's what's it's fun
i think that's like apples apples and
i say it wasn't fun you fucking
apples apples isn't phenomena say it right
now
now it's not funny i said it
was fine now but i'm saying people
always like let's go crazy or like
cards against humanity or whatever carson you're
thinking of cars oh apple sells isn't
supposed to be funny no no
who thinks it's allies plenty and i
was like fifteen okay let's get out
of apples to apples the other day
was so well okay we gotta we
gotta say sorry i'm okay so i'm
example apple's game i played one
okay you're thinking of the thing i'm
thinking of a thing hold on let
me think of what is okay
okay got it okay is it more
like french toast or murder murder is
it then i go right is it
more like murder or a bush a
bush it's it's
is it more like a bush or
a vacation a vacation is it more
like a vacation
or a beach a beach is it
more like a beach or a boat
a boat
is it more like a boat or
an improv show on a cruise a
boat is more like a boat or
a ship a boat is more like
a boat or a or a cruise
ship about
is it more like a boat or
a shark
a shark hey guess huh is it
more like a shark or
a jetski
a shark
is it more like a shark or
a gorilla a shark is more like
a shark or a whale
ah a sharp notes
is it more like a shark or
a sneaker
a sneaker what i don't know what
this is
oh is it
is it more like a sneaker or
jaws a sneaker because remember my story
about jaws sneakers i thought it was
the answer my jaw charles and now
is it more like a sneaker or
a picnic a sneaker
think back to other things yeah yeah
is it more like a sneaker or
a swim fin swim fin did i
get it right now but you're really
getting is more like a swim fins
snorkel sarko is more like a snorkel
or a soaker hose norco or a
self-contained underwater breathing snorkel
lol
don't give up paul is more like
a snorkel or a straw snorkel is
more like a snorkel or ah ah
underwater met what do you call the
masks the they were underwater that yeah
it's more like an underwater mask
is it more like an underwater mask
or a halloween mask underwater mask is
more like an underwater mask or
ah
overwater maths goggles goggles is the answer
oh okay gago is you paul we
did it he has such an understanding
do my shit like that i don't
have a yandere reading of goggles in
general or whatever swim goggles swim goggles
goggles wow
swim goggles sixty nine okay okay next
neck zaire screaming i got one okay
okay yeah i got it
okay is it is it more like
french toast or um a palm tree
more like a palm tree
is more like a palm tree or
a sidewalk it's more like a sidewalk
is more like a sidewalk or a
shoe it's more like a sidewalk
is it more like a sidewalk or
a house it's more like a house
oh oh my way
zara house or an apartment ah more
like a house
is it more like a house or
a castle like a house is it
more like a huh i'll go with
counsel is it more like a castle
or a king more like a castle
is it more like a castle or
a car more like a car
it's more like a car or like
a scooter or like a car
is it more like a car or
superman or like a car is american
car or a truck or like a
car
is it more like a car or
a car seat more like a car
is it more like a a car
a jeep more like a jeep
no more like a car but
is it more like a car or
a roller coaster while a car is
there like a car or a hummer
or like a car it's more like
a car or a blue car more
like a car is like a car
or a prius more like a prius
is it more like a prius or
a tesla more like a tesla is
it more like a tesla or um
like a monorail more like a tesla
is it more like a tesla or
a wall outlet like it's that's more
like it does or a private plane
more like a tesla is more like
a tesla or a public plane like
a test like a tesla or a
b m w you got it
ah i started doubting that a specific
type of fireworks yeah okay paul think
of a thing alright the onus is
off to you should you should enjoy
this yeah this is fun for you
now yeah this is where you just
get to release time
nine yeah this plenty keep going with
this you're doing great shine here dude
i have an item okay
is it more like french toast or
a raincoat
more like french toast oh is it
more like french toast or
iraq more like french toast is more
like french toast or pancakes
more like french toast is it more
like
french toast or whipped cream
more like whip cream is it more
like whipped cream or butter more like
whipped cream is it more like whip
cream or chocolate more like chocolate is
it more like chocolate or jelly
more like chocolate is it more like
chocolate or caramel
more like chocolate isn't running chocolate or
ice cream more like chocolate is it
more like chocolate or
hot fudge more like chocolate is it
more like chocolate or croissant more like
chocolate is it more like chocolate or
a hershey's kiss
more like chocolate isn't really chocolate or
white chocolate
more like chocolate is more like chocolate
or carob more like chocolate is it
more like chocolate or a lollipop more
like chocolate is more like chocolate or
macho more like jolla marla chocolate or
donut
roy chocolate is more like chocolate or
sugar more like chocolate is it more
like chocolate or coffee more like chocolate
is more like chocolate or a hershey's
chocolate bar more like hershey's chocolate bar
is monica hershey's chocolate bar kitcat more
like a hershey chocolate bar is it
more like a hershey's chocolate
more like a kitcat oh is it
more like a kitkat or more like
a twix more like a kitcat is
like a kit kat are snickers more
like snickers is it more like a
snickers or three musketeers from musketeer yeah
yes was that far chocolate was a
long had a long streak was more
fun than the other part okay yeah
how was it for you listeners oh
let us know tell us in you're
running to how did this get me
well that's gonna wrap it up for
us and mike hasn't seen my tech
so he doesn't know that he needs
this expenses i know i know you
know um you can follow us on
instagram at threesome usa and on twitter
and write to us at three am
usa gmail dot com or hopefully three
email at gmail dot co we hope
oh and if you wanna hear ad
free versions of this show you're doing
it right whatever you're doing right now
yeah how did you make it happen
you manifest it yeah but it doesn't
dangerous if there already is a three
mail and so on i wait for
us to confirm yeah we got three
e-mail um and but if you want
to hear ad free versions subscribe to
stitcher premium or and or so
cvb world dot com okay by ah
uh