hi everybody leaving why
yeah okay so we're gonna stay we
have to wait i have to go
right now no stay is called
i got a check for this show
and it said threesome know from cvv
world for me oh yeah was an
ethan yeah wow dal cool or threesome
oh that's right i was guy you've
heard oh i haven't paid for that
yet
okay it's like i'll throw the money
on the bed for you
the ultimate indignity oh i lost some
money if you're on the dresser clean
yourself
i'll clean myself up i don't need
to be told about ugly good clean
yourself hard or bow or bow to
ny i worked at cafe ordeal this
is restaurant roundup oh my god hey
another story
there was somebody thought they were exhausted
we've heard about okay okay fair i
can tell you no because i just
thought of it and i'm thought of
it in years but while we were
doing the podcast for years i stretch
i was twenty i must have been
twenty five twenty six yeah it was
very good you i worked at cafe
cora yeah this is ross
drought ro dah restaurants store you ever
there was a waitress there maybe sometimes
bartender that was a waitress sometimes bartender
and i considered her to be older
bud like wiser well like i consider
her to be a little like too
old to be ah she was old
a little too old to fuck
i mean okay she was probably thirty
five yeah right up old reason she
was like ten years older than me
and side note there was this article
that was like hillary duff still looks
amazing yeah yeah and i was like
yeah there was so much everyone else
online talking about but at the time
i was twenty five and i was
like oh she's she's she's like she
she
i felt like an eighties like a
like a hot girl from high school
in the eighty and your nineties bitch
yeah because of it
um but you have a poster on
your wall
never say well wait do you mind
posing for photographs for me just like
an eighties like you know hot lady
she had like bleach blonde hair oh
she she seemed a little out of
date yeah does that make sense but
yes but did she have dockers dockers
did she wear dockers and honor dockers
dockers dockers if doctors girls
listenings you are leaving money on the
dockers why are you not making broad
offer speaker i want jackie
pleats ditch
ah oh my god that's so dockers
get in touch with us because we
got a million
for you know nothing
one million dollars by the way you
have to pay us nine hundred thousand
yeah please please fans still it's a
tank brand okay so this oh so
she was nice and everything but but
um i've told you about how on
the weekends they would have bands play
they would have the the beatles cover
bands yeah um which every time they
willed that i
can't run mugs these needles because it
was a restaurant to four lads or
something like that i think it was
something like that but it was it
was like
should simply call the cockroaches every single
time they started every cardio
for a company bang bag when we
ah we did are a parody of
a very obscure sixties beach ah film
with frankie avalon um that's honestly who
i pictured in it because i know
this from full house right and that
finance because he was in it right
yeah i think an iphone chelsea blanket
bingo was
oh it was even worse yeah but
even even worse today you just like
dominoes be true to the issue don't
think they shut out on a real
beach but they ah they they had
a beatles parody character that frankie frankie
avalon play called the sorry i just
got a loud environment warning from oh
no loud environments how loud good b
the you need more
want you to go lay down
your environment is too loud ma please
say hey grandpa you can't handle this
but he was called the screaming it's
called the dirt bug what it was
it was like a parody of the
beat of they were making fun of
the beatles and they called it the
dirt bugs in the movie in the
movie yeah so we did a parody
of it and we called me the
beetle
write a parody meaning you've got on
stage or you mean a video now
this is in the television show the
comedy oh i thought you meant at
cafe cartel no so a catholic ordeal
we would have bands who played there
every weekend and she would she wanted
to do this
but but it was also like chicken
group people are going come on do
this doers was her idea wanted to
do that there were all these like
older gentlemen who like hung out of
the bar and i think forty yeah
probably
ah so these senior citizens would come
in that's how i felt when i
started improv because i was like sure
never one was like twenty eight and
you're like jesus what are they doing
with their lives records that old kill
me yeah but so so they would
always go like come on do it
do it and so she would give
a cd
two i guess the band or no
it knows you put it on the
the house speakers and it was a
karaoke track oh no it was just
the joe cocker song you can leave
your hat on and she she would
do the nine and a half weeks
kind of strip dance with with a
fedora would she
remove clothing or no i think she
sort of would go dead she would
like unbutton the shirt and go down
it was just like it was very
weird in a work environment that we
have to loop so this is where
his paul's teacher kissing a student in
i've never heard that sir yeah i
may have told you this before when
i worked ah on kelsey grammer resents
the sketch show rump the p it
was ah we there was ah one
of the one of the people from
the production i forget what for jobs
she had she was she was like
she was not like a p she
was more she was she had a
higher status job than that right but
she was like essentially like a clerical
person on the show yeah and she
was like a sweet like extremely sweet
um quiet but very funny like one
of those types of people um very
reserved but when you really listen to
her it's like
she's fucking hilarious she should be in
this sketch but she was very she
was very late
i did suggest that a couple of
times keep just let me stay here
in london and have a good time
why wouldn't be in london right it's
a long night so that's why did
it happen at all so much more
annoying yeah that you have to be
like away from everything but it was
her birthday there's towards the hundred production
was her birthday and ah we were
you know this
studio that we shot at had a
canteen and you would go eat lunch
there and everything was well there's a
lot of different productions and stuff whose
it was a small studio so maybe
a couple of the things but mostly
i think at the time we were
the only thing that was shooting their
way but they still kept the canteen
open yeah well there's a lot of
people you know and so it was
also like the the the people like
the um the people ran the studio
and stuff like that were would eat
there and it was i really liked
that aspect of it so like it
was really cool and star wars yeah
the aliens the devil was there honestly
i even shrink scum and it was
a hive of definitely high school mobility
yeah um and so they hire so
at lunchtime
for her birthday they hired a male
stripper oh and this guy it started
out it was kind of funny just
to sit there on a chair two
things and was a stripper and then
it just got so fucking raunchy and
it was uncomfortable for everyone it was
like please stop
it was like the equivalent of watching
somebody beat the shit out of somebody
like long after they've stopped moving yeah
yeah it was just like my sons
have you ever seen that
a few times and yeah you know
my brother was in jail for awhile
he was a white supremacist and i
assume curb stop people and then but
then he renounced those ways oh he
did yeah yeah wondering yeah i was
happy i remember being happy yeah you
remember that being happy that he wasn't
white supremacist oh my god yeah i
was surprised with a stripper the other
night really unsurprised
hey john okay okay um what it
was so it was like a bit
but it was um i did my
friend show sloppy seconds which is like
a podcast hosted by big dipper and
meatballs very fun um and they have
on a lot of drag queens and
other types of performers and um i
was the guest but supposed to be
me nicole byer
and we were supposed to play like
a newlywed game where it was like
where because we host a podcast together
and big dipper and mipa host the
podcast next is gonna be like whoa
who knows their host dad a fund
but then nicole that covin and so
she wasn't there so i teamed up
with big dipper who i went to
high school middle school with and was
my prom i don't think i knew
that yeah wait i knew that you
we're friends but yeah like i knew
that you went back that far yeah
wow prom date i was i went
to his prom my junior year in
his senior year and there's a hilarious
picture that i can find that was
just so funny because we both look
so sweet ah so young and naive
yeah the white trustee is the fifties
it looks hilarious
um and he just like ditched me
the whole time i was like dancing
with and partying with everyone and i
the best picture from the night is
me at the like dinner table at
the prom with my arm around his
suit jacket on his chair nobody's sitting
ah um but um so we played
but then at the end of the
show they had this plan to surprise
or with the stripper ah which makes
sense and i think she would know
exactly how to react of course yes
so they booked the study yeah and
it was a friend and he was
really nice and he was great but
instead it was there like it will
surprise foreign and i was i really
i didn't see understand that it was
happening to me
if like a long time
yeah like squid and he made me
get up and dance to them and
stuff and it was where it was
fun but it was just like i'm
like nicole would have been the perfect
person yet been to because she would
be like i've heard no saying oh
were you guys deakin deakin yeah what
does that mean isn't that what was
it called what are your in your
school dances when they outlawed it jus
fucking juki oh yeah juki like that
i like taking them there should be
a field sounds like a penis is
coming out
lucky
the thing is dk
yeah we would grind yeah we would
cry yes absolutely i've heard too many
stories about women hiring strippers for parties
to for fun and then it being
just bad after five minutes yeah like
it's fun for five and then i'm
just being like holy shit we have
another half i see it's better to
go
go to the location where the strippers
perform rights because then you can take
a shower yeah yeah how much you're
involved you know but have chippendales i've
also heard about they all as they're
getting paid like once someone's numbers so
they can come back and party yes
come around all weekend ah you know
like maybe i can get your number
i could come back and party
we won't say the guy who did
this dance on the show that i
was on he was like oh my
god i'm sorry i hope that was
okay he was like so nice huh
i'm sorry ma'am he hasn't really like
do that because i kind of just
a bit oh really yeah yeah he
does like burlesque i guess but oh
okay um he was great he was
very funny because i was like no
you're leaving mike and yeah well i'm
in love with him and
fair that's a sweet story yeah it
actually started so q yeah
i did a gem last night yeah
that mike worked at this super fancy
hotel
huh and you know i hope it
does anyway it was me i sort
of like i guess like the the
sort of apprentice concierge there was like
an older man who was that mike
loved but was also like scared to
disappoint or whatever and me and him
in gabe ross were hanging out and
like gardening i remember one time
if we were going to we're going
to use the pool like they have
this gigantic hotel pool right and getting
in the pool one time so this
is like like you were there for
weeks it was a long dream we
went to a lot of different places
but i remember that's great pool thing
was just before i woke up like
i wanted to swim in the pool
and there were all these fucking people
like in the way
a and i was like i have
to swim under these peoples i can
get across to the other side of
the pool yeah that's right in the
esl lessons intense this is a white
lotus kind of thing and you just
know but i was doing
i just finished doing that
oh i love bam law like lamb
lamb
look i had a dream i woke
up so horny yeah nobody was like
so just seeing this trip was so
real it was one of those dreams
it was like it felt like i
had been exuding for hours yeah yeah
yeah intermodal lot of celebrities really like
who will arnett amy poehler wow elsa
the handler whoa i interacted with and
jason bateman whoa whoa i don't know
why i guess i was looking at
smart loose poop i do know why
because i was looking at a smart
list post right before i went to
bed so that's why they were there
chelsea handler probably my instagram as well
instagram influenced but it was a very
real feeling they are influencers but just
in dream yeah yeah talking
wow it's working it's scary spooky spooky
kooky and dreams that feel real or
so amazing aren't they aren't they so
amazing really in my eyes oh i'm
typing words yeah live there only there
yeah you want to be dead throughout
the day in dreams i walk with
you that's true i last night
i put ah the lotion in the
basket
because you don't wanna get the hood
so he does get those sometimes when
it doesn't
nah resolution skin yeah then it puts
the lotion in the basket yeah i
put the dog wait a minute just
do the lotion down there yeah let
me keep the low schist and when
i run out i'll tell you but
if you yes if you want me
to ah buffalo bill i have some
note movie is really scary that's great
yeah it's great but i put
the i put the dogs in their
crate where they sleep i think we
show where the fish yes the dogs
in his shoe who put the dogs
in and everyone's like the song yeah
i didn't think of that i was
just talking wait yeah yeah david dogs
such as the crazy adult had dogs
before me or yes they've all they
always have yes because a rocky or
previous dog used to sleep with us
for a little while and it was
a constant me waking up all throughout
the night because he would get too
hot so you'd come out from under
the covers then you go back in
and in now i'm ready to take
your
i'm like you do understand what i'm
dealing with here yeah need to sleep
so eventually we moved rocky to his
own bed okay um but now we
haven't stay in a bed and i'm
stay in the bed yeah so bedroom
with posters and stuff yeah most of
the farrah fawcett farah dogs it sorry
oh my guy walks if it's there's
somebody sort of
notorious note o rajendran who had a
room or i'll think about this for
the job that had a bad full
room and it was like a miniature
room well that's not bad you just
gave about to take a long step
back to listen i'm almost positive it
is a manager oh
oh yeah well i i put the
dogs into their crate and they they
have a lot of blankets and by
the way molly will get very scared
in the middle of the night if
she's not in the same greatest georgia
she gets all scared wines because she
wakes okay she wakes up and doesn't
know what's going on is like whereas
but
if you put if you put her
in the same craters ga they sleep
pretty much through the night originally they
one of them will wine or georgia
will grow like you're in my space
and we have to go like in
the middle of the night if it
continues it wakes us up and we
have to go shh and they usually
say no i know but so like
i i put them in up
turned out the light i put on
the sound machine and i just heard
this growling from georgia and it happened
for awhile i was just like shh
and then i turned towards cool up
and realised it was her snoring so
loud it sounded like she was out
within ten seconds wow during super dang
yeah yes she usually is like uphill
twelve or twelve thirty or something yeah
she just it was ten pm and
she was snoring immediately so much that
i thought it was a dog growling
yeah i fall asleep pretty sure i
don't know if it's a second show
but i fell asleep i fall asleep
really fast like i will be thinking
like i hear mike doing something like
okay i'm falling asleep he's probably going
to come in here
soon and like i just don't ever
remember anything that happens after that like
i fall asleep instantly janie falls asleep
pretty quickly i i love to read
myself to sleep it is like like
you i'd actually fall asleep holding the
book not always yeah that's happened occasionally
but usually i'll be like i realize
like hey your eyes have been closed
for like fifteen seconds so you should
put this book
but jgr will fall asleep reading um
and we both read on kindles so
sometimes i'll think that she's still reading
because it's the lightest oh yeah oh
yeah and she's just out cold that's
um but i it's kind of thing
it's one of those those sort of
pleasures you have that you kind of
forget about it until you're doing it
yeah like get into bed i'm like
i'm gonna read my new
whoa oh my so much better than
being on the phone no matters absolutely
reading a great book are you reading
something you enjoy right now yes i
am what are you reading i'm reading
i finished i finished lessons loss which
i love i have to read that
um and then i ah there are
a couple more of those i fear
i told you i read those slouch
house books
slouch sour houses and so no apple
tv series it's based on this series
of spy novels and i started watching
the show yeah sure something no no
no it's english it's oh my dacha
sweetest tones yeah right i do sometimes
i've got show me danish ah you
know i like i go over all
of the world yeah but this is
this is a ah ah
a series of spy novels about um
a place in m i five there's
like a ah a branch that you
go to if you fuck up as
a spy and they'd like shovel shuffle
you off to this place and they
just give you meaningless tests until you
retire wow and so what looked like
a great book but okay should i
put it to paper
clipping the cup but guess what wow
interesting things and ah now i think
but i started but i started watching
the show and then like ten minutes
in and gary oldman plays the main
character of it's great casting and ten
minutes in i was like i think
i read this book
is an old man yeah and so
then i i never do this but
i tore through all of them i
read them all in a row i
just really enjoy them they're like they're
very they're very like fun to read
they're very absorbing great stories and so
um ah i started what i so
there there's also
a series of i got all cut
up i read all of them but
there's some novellas that he wrote also
in that world and so i'm currently
reading the last two of those that
are yeah yeah that's cool yeah i
was at my parents' house trapped at
my parents' house for like a week
you were trapped in your parents house
this is ten years or so ago
can't even sing that and they limit
you trees
yeah
but out there that's right they have
library wow books they judge the worst
thing he's ever done the books they
check out from the library all the
time so like i was trapped there
so i just started reading one of
their books and it was a mystery
novel and it was like obviously not
written very well but it was like
oh let me check out and it
was a popular series i read go
these are popular
i read it and i was just
like i had nothing else to do
and there was one black character and
i could not believe this is like
a modern book because everything that the
black character said they took out like
the i n g s they just
had i an apostrophe and that was
bad enough and the n
and she was always saying things like
show enough instead of sure enough and
stuff like oh and i was just
like i can't believe this is a
popular book current book and this is
a book series and then at one
point towards the end the murderer came
out and the black character said feats
don't fail me now no it was
crazy says insane
was insanity i wish i could remember
what it was but and it was
poppy wow it gave me such an
insight into like middle america of just
like what is still acceptable it was
just like a twenty first century book
yes and what it was like richard
north patterson or somebody like that it
wasn't someone that big it was like
a a semi popular was like ok
a woman wrote these like charming mystery
novels and it was a series and
it was just like dang it was
crazy i was listening to your podcast
um this guy isn't seen ah you're
welcome and ah that line in the
bodyguard i don't i saw that movie
oh yeah yeah a million years ago
i've never seen it where he talks
about kevin costner
says he got always gets killed a
mouthy black chauffeur or whatever it's very
weird weirdness very very strange anyways making
him uncomfortable i'm ready to go but
we're gonna continue doing the show yeah
but we have to break and i
tell you what i'm gonna know it's
like you're cliffhanger finger we have to
take a break when we return we'll
find out what book lauren is reading
that she likes on the freedom episode
that continues next nice
previously on threesome i really about that
i really like i'm gonna tell you
yeah lauren what but how is your
jamba juice by the way it's good
i haven't had one in such a
light went on tour you know there
was any airport i've been kind of
letting myself get a little jumbo from
time to time if i'm um yeah
taste pretty good so the book that
i'm reading is called such a fun
way to get a job
jason yeah it's right here to get
a job such a fun age by
kylie read it was going early tour
the it was long list first point
yeah surprise um it's really good i'm
really enjoying it i everyone was posting
about it like a couple you even
brought it here enjoy your time had
a chance to read when i was
a little early during the show
yeah i don't blame you but um
i'm really liking it i highly recommend
yeah more right it's about this um
woman who there's like a rich woman
who has ah two kids and she
has a babysitter and so you kind
of are twinkle you're witnessing the babysitter's
experience in
her life and that woman's experience in
her life and then there's this connecting
thread that fucks up their home
existence and i only i'm not far
enough to even go know i'm getting
right to the really juicy part and
chic and so i gotta just wait
so it is about java it is
yeah it's about strawberry world
a boosts novos you don't know booth
you get one free booze i haven't
done boosts since old days i actually
feel like boosts are a placebo yeah
yeah i think that's super say yeah
i'm reading war and peace booth i
read that during the story yeah
ah spi of my he did his
second season okay the web series yes
and paul was in it and so
was i i wow your part was
so funny and i cannot wait to
see it it was really fun can
i say what it was or no
don't say yeah yeah alright but but
i
did hear a he walked me through
what your whole thing was and i
was dying
so funny i can't wait yeah yeah
and i saw a picture of view
also in it and i'm wearing a
beautiful way where my beautiful widow way
yeah which is stunning and i would
just stunning i really like how i
feel in it yeah in that in
that works but again that wig yeah
why don't you wear that way because
it's not a chair
so but it's funny it's funny yeah
and if it's just feels great and
my character wasn't like an idiot so
it just felt great down that way
it is fun when you get to
do a character thing where you have
a wig or or you know some
kind of weird makeup of rachel eyre
and it just totally makes you look
different oh my god well that's like
why i feel like
super fun who win oscars for like
roles where and like a ton of
prosthetics like yeah because fraser oil uses
maybe about two well that's nice i
haven't seen as it come out i
have a genie i don't know if
it came out so i've just got
a screener i'd like to to watch
that here
ear coming on wondering um mixed um
perspectives on that right but um some
say he's too fat i'm hearing mixed
nuts what is this box you have
here conversation those places game once before
oh okay that's for later let's take
a little around the snack oh i
thought that was your ah heck heavier
socks
no dear it's music these headphones would
fit in that box he's an idiot
don't you know hey yeah i have
to be honest i've not looked above
your chin oh my i'm really sorry
actually it's that same funky if you're
staring at his chin this is great
because you could pick out a lineup
this is a great tip if you
were being attacked okay just
and stare at their chin you will
not the face throughout the whole attack
as much as you can really process
what really relaxing enjoy yourself because that's
supposedly an easier way to pick some
out of a lineup because when people
all look similar that they've a chance
is the distinguishing yeah feature also if
you have to do like really fast
pirouette
bets you won't get dizzy yeah focus
on the chance yeah yeah
because it would take ballet scott i
did wow what what are you doing
i didn't expect him to say yeah
why did you do that i went
to theatre school oh first position third
position fifth because i didn't know everybody
would have to it was required yeah
and i didn't like it all that
much but was a ch
child and i will stand on my
tiptoes quickly yeah my whole weight on
my dumb tos know a lot of
my fears to be for disaster a
lot of my physical therapy for my
foot recently it has been like very
ballet very kind of almost ballet stuff
of like you know okay now get
into like sort of first position homers
least do this kind of walk
rock and all like how's your foot
coming along by the way ah it's
alright so i've nerve damage yeah saying
do you think it'll ever be the
same no that's the thing when you
when you fuck up your body at
our age it's done it's done you're
you're it's over yeah that was that
was all an ankle you had yep
i'm done i'm over no
oh it's that my my doctor says
like yeah everything should go away in
time so but ah that's very bleak
nerve damage everything should go away i
mean yeah i've been rubbing on it
is little cbt yeah three or twenty
four down rose mo guidi no sleeping
no
judah jews lay back i'm i'm i'm
i'm i'm i i'm ah stephanie allen's
mom has oh debbie you score in
um in palm springs and she's selling
all sorts of amazing little wears and
one of the things that she is
telling what she created is this amazing
box and stephanie gave me one and
i'm so excited about it it's basically
a shark cooter reward but with cbd
gummies so you get it today take
a plate with a knife and then
these beautiful cbd gummies and a new
kind of mouthwash usually it's cbt so
it doesn't get you stoned just as
you figure the blacks but i'm saying
you put out at a party right
yeah and it's like just really
cute and clever and interesting and i
love you wow have story number huh
can't control what's put on it after
you own it okay but the idea
is cbd gummies and i love i
think it's such a fun idea isn't
that cute it is she's an artist
and she designed the box it's all
painted and i want to get more
into that you know yeah like because
well it doesn't
stuff i love but well you know
like when i see a cat in
a box i'm like ooh oh man
good easy and there is enough call
mr schroeder huh college boy he knows
a thing or two about stuff um
but like every every time i do
like we we have gummies in the
house that we indulge in ak
occasionally janie more than me and then
every once in awhile oh it was
wrong i'll have one and not ah
gummy
their narratives believe them like waiting for
and you know what i enjoy it
sometimes it doesn't work at all oh
is mesh me ah but when i
when i when one works it's like
this is fun i like i enjoy
this yeah it's great and it's like
but i don't think of it as
a relaxation that it's just come to
mind like you're probably glad to wine
style yeah it's usually on the weekend
ends i'll have three bottles we know
yeah the weeds all the bottle one
night yeah and then nothing throughout the
week yeah i love that but i
do i do forget that oh yeah
i could it's legal i could just
do that then it would be you
know the next day i'm not going
to be hung over you know watch
a weird movie have fun i had
a doctor's appointment
awesome yeah it was great um i
got a physical you know okay um
which actually i haven't done in a
very long time i feel like like
i assume to fisa as a woman
i feel like you go to the
doctor a lot but it's not a
physical it's like you're obi yes psychologist
yes yes and that kind of feels
like you should do one was the
basis but i
i don't yeah so i'm like no
i'm i'm like planning to do that
and um they asked me if i
um were using them to fill out
the form with what you you drink
and if you do drugs smoke cigarettes
and then it's like i put down
marijuana which is funny caring male yeah
and then they're like okay and then
she was she
it's like this young though it was
like a nurse talking to me but
she's like asking me about my weed
usage and it's like it's just very
funny because it's the same as drinking
this is not like revelatory it's just
like feels like you're man this feels
like you're writing something elite like i'm
like yeah say yeah luckily we yeah
sorry judgment and just try yanis drugs
yeah well the weird thing they they
will really judge you for smoking yeah
yeah like it i found that doctors
don't really care about the drinking they
don't as long as you just go
for the drinking like you know like
twice a week yeah just lie and
just say please
but they they really judge you for
the dread a wedding maybe i'll have
a drink and a cigarette but yes
cigarettes they'll be like yeah yeah stop
stop right away doctor once when i
said how much coffee i drank i
said i drink three cups of coffee
in the morning and went oh whoa
hey yeah you maybe want to cut
back on that so that's
i mean although i guess if he's
temperamental like the doctor well it seems
like a little bit more he seemed
she seemed like alarmed and i was
like is that but i didn't think
that coffee was yeah bad well what
is it i drink now i drink
two cups i guess it's the caffeine
yeah i don't know yeah probably
do you think shapes five one cup
of coffee of the morning that's it
and and i used to when we
lived by coffee bean we would always
walk rockies me yeah and teeling i'm
so sorry daily yod we would walk
the it was an excuse every day
to walk the dog his dog tricks
of course walk the dog yeah
my you walk the dog in front
of soppy
i make you sleep i would do
it for all the customers
no tips needed i don't know what
ah but it was always an excuse
to get like a big demon like
coffee drink and yeah and that seems
kind of fun if you ever buy
a nice coffee shop yeah it was
a five minute walk or whatever joy
because sometimes that's why people buy places
is they're like oh it's just a
five minute walk to a coffee place
whatever but
first of all my financial person was
like you know i see you spending
a lot of money a coffee bean
and tea leaf basically change avocado toast
millennial sort of it's kind of a
weird one to pick on because you
just feel like yeah well i'm sure
you were spending more money in other
areas sure but any your accountant can
i please have one goddamn pleasure in
my life and i get a fucking
coffee in the morning however much we
know so when you really think about
it it's like between cool urbanites like
twelve dollars a day or whatever right
yeah so she's like maybe you could
drink coffee at home and then the
other part of it is like you're
putting six hundred calories or whatever well
that's more like one of those hey
yeah and i talked to another friend
who was like yeah always gaining a
lot of weight and
and then my friend said well you
get one of these every single day
yeah it's so so we then just
got a coffee maker and now have
like i put splendid and a little
a little bit of fat-free cream it's
like i drink my coffee black which
is which makes it that i don't
really enjoy having coffee out yeah oh
no what i mean i don't like
why we feel
found our nice coffees that we like
that we make at home and for
starbucks black is terrible right um the
blonde black maybe is better maybe but
sometimes sorry paul i'm sorry for saying
that gotta go to a nice independent
store yeah let me get it's two
i want
i'm just too much you know what
i mean but i also don't like
coffee after a certain i like coffee
in the morning and that's it yeah
so like if i'm going to stand
or something like that and say we're
gonna do a coffee run it's like
i'd rather drink like a coke or
something for katie nice sometimes feel jealous
because i think it seems so fun
to have your coffee routine and have
like like when you
yeah we'll just seeing him was like
oh yeah my just sitting at a
starbucks and stuff like i mean when
we're on tour i would like every
morning i would kind of get up
early and just go find the nearest
coffee place and get something or whatever
yeah but i would go it's always
fun you go wit to match oh
every door yeah every day on tour
i went to mass i would find
the nearest catholic traitor no idea
that's about what you said the night
before on yeah yeah yeah because it's
like to entertain people i say these
sinful things and then i would have
to confess it and know that i
was going to do it again and
and you know the priest would but
you need money so it's like that's
what the priests yeah the priest would
invariably say what else are you going
to do hey speaking to the doctors
i
told you i got were speaking to
preach i told you i got a
colonoscopy recently okay i still haven't done
it i gotta do a ddot now
the warriors three five and over gay
hang yeah wow every gun i've never
done it yeah yeah i know i
gotta do it you can use the
color i just clean stuff i did
color guard first which
yeah they make you drink and die
and it goes out your books parnell
box yeah basically you're gonna love this
i am you're gonna love this lord
you of all people you're gonna love
okay can't wait you take a shit
and put it in a box and
mail it
i've done that before in about ten
may and and the results were whole
or but you could not pay me
to be receiving that mail here i
would get up if i were them
i would i would always send an
angry reaction first like why did you
do this and then leave me like
just kidding of course we know this
is what we asked you to so
but did that so i did that
first
yeah literally saying your shit in a
box yeah so but what kind of
baia notebooks yeah so then then it
kind of boxes it it's ah it's
a cube about this period it's cardboard
you don't just send it you have
to fill it g
so it's with you for like a
month
ah with the keep going almost yeah
but but the results came back that
there was like foreign matter in there
which shot which means pennies you know
cancer essentially oh no my so yeah
you ate a thought
on paper killen yeah i say
screw so i was like i gotta
know the people eat an average of
four screws a year just when they
crawl in your mouth no way really
when you become a foreign matter well
think that's the thing they don't know
what it is but they they say
we've we found foreign foreign matter in
there so like i looked it up
yeah i was like holy shit do
i have cancer i looked it up
and i was like they say just
basically these the it's very easy to
get a false
it's positive essentially so needs to call
an oscar so so my doctor called
in and i was and he goes
hey so your results came back he
goes i would not worry at all
because there's so many false positives you
need to get a colonoscopy obviously but
because when this positive comes back you
have to get one but just don't
even like stress about it
all like don't put it out of
your because that could lead to cancer
yeah so i went and got the
colonoscopy and you know they give you
all the drinks and all and you're
supposed to fast and i question yeah
you could've skipped the shit in the
box step because you technically your age
have to get anyway right no no
no if you if you get that
if you do the color guard thing
and you pass and your happy face
oh so it is just
shit in the yeah yeah so there's
no such thing as a false negative
color thing is i don't think something
in your actual intestinal tract that is
not seen on poop i don't know
like if there's a little guy in
there like i live in
i like trump in the way like
whatever you write i'm not a doctor
by the way so i i will
say people should not lie sometimes i
have to remind you guys that i
always assumed i mean yeah i heard
on threesome that i didn't have to
get a goal austin
a class action suit
don't listen to anything speaking of a
little guy which i was going oh
i'm sorry so i did the i
did i did everything by the rules
like i'm a rules guy because you
are not at sixteen hundred pennsylvania oh
of course yes so your rules remain
the same drank the juice granby drank
the juice i did i fasted everything
that i'm supposed to do ah there's
tiger movie but i get upset i
really want ever seen it cleanse everything
out did everything by the book i
was like ok good this was because
you could
keep your badge and your gun and
and then yes and then also i
have the i had the the surgery
like so the the colonoscopy semi late
in the day it was like at
nine thirty there were like you sure
you don't want to do this at
like five in the morning so you
can eat all the way up to
i was like so i hadn't eaten
for like you know eighteen hours or
something at the point where i got
it and um you know they put
you to see
lee one during that period what are
you allowed water and that's it i
are you allowed water i do not
know how to let you drink water
not in the morning definitely i think
maybe no water twelve hours before it
or something like that jesus um i
can't remember but but so i went
there i did everything right you could
eat like
cheese yeah i'm like a little bit
yeah yeah i know thing that looks
like yeah yeah okay
yeah so i go there and i
get it and they put me under
and i go get the the thing
and um i wake up and um
i'm kind of loopy and i send
adam scott or weird text and a
camera in my ass and i thought
you
adult it is yeah that this weird
like about five hours later you responded
i was like oh noes never mind
sorry um but why did you say
i meant to on the last show
we did i'm gonna tell him on
the next one oh and with the
reveal but um but ah and so
the doctor comes in he goes hey
everything looks good
because did you do all the stuff
we want to do to do i'm
like what do you mean because you
fast did you do all the thing
because he goes this kind of a
mess down there
wow yeah to vomit
okay yeah and but you know this
is your job you clean it up
it's like you know rude i take
my car to the mechanic and like
i'm not cleaning up the oil spills
like i'm not apologizing
yeah the story is sick
envisioning is
what he had to experience and this
can be the first time this has
ever happened to call it nobody wants
to catch you in a lie like
he wants to share yours do it
did yeah he didn't really drink over
stuff i did everything alright we have
to take a break are you fine
oh lord oh yeah you know he
mentioned you said everything looks good we'll
be right back
and we're back wow and everybody yea
guess what three church times so you
know what the many voicemails
oh i'd love to hear one just
mad you know everybody know we have
x over number da la in pu
if it more of a mocking number
huh oh haha alright we do have
a three-tier here while matt is looking
ah ah producers looking we have a
game that was sent to us a
physical game that was sent to us
by zan toward the magician oh late
at once before we did and it's
a game call
old conversation the game about the game
just follow the one rule on your
card and have the most ridiculous conversation
you've ever experienced that's fun with cards
like only ask questions initiate another player
imitating another player speaking inappropriate volume it's
easy to see why everyone's been talking
about this game so basically one each
get one card right
and yes and we do so yes
an idea everybody gets a prompt and
then you have to figure out what
the other person i think that's fun
for christmas
i sand old enforcement so creative when
you're around the whole fam yeah who
gives a fuck up out cleese mers
who gives a fuck cop out creed
xmas alright alright so we're passing out
the cards right now let's see it
tho way that doesn't make any sense
okay
take it back i mean it doesn't
make any sorry just had friends what
does that mean i don't know that
is weird yeah yeah that doesn't make
any sense okay
i've got mine
i'm trying to figure out how i'm
going to do it right hey part
of the fun yep
and then we have to guess what
the thing was yeah yes you have
to guess what the other peoples okay
things are alright yeah um ah well
hey man hey
what's going on what's what's it going
how's how's it hanging what's it going
on it's hanging pretty great i have
great news really so you know i
want to start my own tower records
yes it's opening up next week wow
that sounds groovy yeah yeah remember when
you had that concert that you played
ah where you were like
i like you said you could play
guitar with you actually could and yeah
it sucked because the fuzz can break
it up but darn it i missed
that yeah well how was as you
are in jail it was it was
pretty groovy you are not bringing up
the dang jail but you were in
jail it was and i mean did
you ever tell him why you are
in jail yeah why why did they
throw it wide wide those pigs throw
you in jail well shoot um i
was being naughty with the law and
doing things that the law considered naughty
ah and so they were like guess
what you jerk
man you're going to jail and i
went there wow you didn't even smoke
any refer anything like that i did
not do anything like messed up to
lie what do you mean that's a
lie you
climbed into the draft area at the
zoo the draft areas that giraffe area
you said that you could ride one
you pulled one's tail till it got
on it's knees you climbed on it's
bag you hold onto the neck and
you swung around it over and over
and over again what the fudge that
is absolutely
not true it's absolutely true scott i'm
sorry i he missed your concert because
he was doing something so absolutely this
is blowing my mind man this is
this is tripping me out she's a
dang liar this is trippy that i'm
not a liar i just i just
i'm saying something you know
want to hear whoa the snl friends
behave can't we all just like you
know join hands and you know kind
of like the last time you did
that wasn't the really fun time um
you got everyone to join hands across
america
yeah it kinda turned into a big
thing yeah it was like you know
i was like hey man this is
just like really putting us into a
peaceful mindset you know to me yeah
so it was it was really cool
to join hands with everybody it was
just really it was really groovy crumbs
i'm sorry miss that yeah do you
guys feel ready to guess yeah already
yeah
you're like you can't swear
yes work fake swears fakers yesterday you
are hippie yeah i'm using a sling
slang yeah and you are telling everyone
secret you're accusing people of things bring
up stories about players can be fictional
okay
can be factually vincent canby alright alright
got it right pretty good yeah so
yeah let's give it another shot give
it another shot
are we supposed to disguise what we're
doing um me but no one can
guess okay some of these are different
i mean some of it yeah the
ones that are different colors maybe you're
oh so this one category when it
says rallies yeah there must be some
sort of doesn't mention that on the
fucking thing well thanks so old
tar santa sanitary doesn't grant wishes zone
huh
then i'm alright we're passing out of
the cards we're all looking at them
one guy
got it did saltire ever give out
any other wish or was just because
little tom hanks was such he was
plugged in it was you know it
was a dream of duty give wishes
to everyone who like came over or
was it just like hey no everybody
else saw the plug and they're like
i guess it doesn't work yeah well
you know it's so i tried to
show big to my nephews
cuz the summer and they didn't really
care at all and isn't it weird
when something such a classic and i
know a modern generation is like for
whatever reason they're just turning out just
going like this does i know it's
like just the wrong time of day
they just don't wanna sit down but
i'm like oh i wish i could
just force them to watch every movie
that i watch
at them to watch yeah well you
can you should be mandatory and so
they need to do the big sql
with elizabeth ah narcos perkins yeah and
collin hanks as the grown-up version of
thumb yeah yes and just see like
how weird they reconnected like connect and
they add
and they run in each other somewhere
yeah oh my god i went along
it's actually a brilliant yeah it's right
and it's like oh yeah we didn't
fuck because it's not like and then
maybe she makes a wish of some
kind you don't need to get younger
in his age yes and then he
gets conveniently statutory rape like no show
nazi shortage
watch me his age like forty right
then and then he's like i liked
you for who you were and he's
like i like twenty year olds yeah
like because you make another wish just
one more
alright ready all right yeah oh sorry
oh you didn't look at your yard
i forgot it jaws are here we
go
ah clark company meeting time i'm like
this is the time for the company
meeting oh ooh the time for company
meaning hmm oh no we are going
to let's just like sit around and
everybody say um things that you know
your experiencing here working at jomba
and um you know things that you
feel could be improved things that you're
loving of course we would like to
you know we love to like hear
things you're loving as much as things
that you are you know um wanting
to change well i would like to
say um you know it's it's such
a pleasure to be here among all
of you and to be ce
selling these juices to people that really
need them
i don't think the boosts are doing
anything is that fair to say that's
one perspective so um hey darin
derren yes did you hear what bamba
said bomba ah mama jama
he was i mean he was he
was talking about jomba juice of course
yeah i think anyone could've could've guessed
that um was i correct you are
so i did a good job sure
alright um look i guess i'll just
call it the elephant in the room
um darin you don't pay attention to
shit that's going on your your thinking
your life is more important than ours
it's absolute bullshit um just among us
i agree with you
about their what
deron what you do can you hear
us yeah i'm paying attention are you
sure yeah it sounds like you're lying
why um because like you literally say
um like what after everything that um
yeah being said maybe she gets your
hearing check because when you're among people
you're using
yeah because right now you're seeing a
bunch of bullshit
bomba
okay don't use his name against him
and this has given me
thank you among my people it's a
fantastic name like jody
so it's a little bit uncommon yet
known and and liked precisely okay and
you categorized it um perfectly so um
i want to just draw everyone's attention
to the board deron yeah what
okay um like i'm i'm actually gonna
quit what i don't like i don't
want to i like you won't be
among us anymore i don't care about
working here so any moon zombie idea
say i'm talking about when samba samba
java and i don't want to work
here anymore well
i'm bomba john but i need you
guys and your daring jones i'm the
only what is not a legacy hire
you change your name from derren bowie
yeah
that should have stayed among us there
in bowie
yeah
we feel ready yeah i mean i
don't know either you guys it's the
word among not just us but this
pronounce i'd say a moon you use
the word moon once per turn really
yes like easiest one yeah yeah only
just noticed it was
and you aren't listening i'm distracted okay
i didn't hear him yeah and just
regular then you wanna do pure aggression
when you're always a winner you come
at me ah i have no idea
what yours is yeah you're calling a
meeting yeah you're a woman like you
used filler words like ah um etc
you just sounded like yourself i did
not i added them all the time
oh yeah i added them all the
time one more okay let's do another
one another one another one
huh interesting okay
well it's come an interesting one that's
good
i think oh i think i didn't
know i need to look down where
the guards are bad huh huh hey
everybody i want to say thank you
so much i really appreciate you all
being here um i'm so sorry i
wasn't earlier know i'm just grateful for
your presence this really means a lot
to me because it does mean a
lot to me too
i'm so glad i appreciate that because
you only turn forty once do you
and i guess you do yeah and
then i'm and thank god ah so
i'm actually i'm sorry i thought you
were already forty i i know i
said that last week and you don't
look a day over
i'm thirty nine yeah yeah i appreciate
that because it makes me feel like
i'm my mature you know that i
give you feel different and i also
appreciate you saying that i look a
little bit younger than i yeah do
you feel different at all yeah you
know i'm really um
i'm really just ah reflecting on life
and really i'm so appreciative of of
all the people in my life have
all the the wonderful places i get
to go of all the the the
the beautiful smiles that i see what
about your friends do they share these
feelings kinda hope so i think
if they do i'm so sorry that
makes me so stressed out for a
second i write so rude of me
i'm really really i apologize don't you
wish you were paying attention i actually
do because i really don't know what
you're talking about that's okay i you
know i just am glad that you're
here ah i'm sorry i didn't say
that first i'm glad you're here
thank you should have said it and
i'm like god saying it crossed my
mind i don't have anything to apologize
for yeah well no you don't and
i appreciate that so i started bringing
it up but you did do that
one bad thing what did i do
i'm so glad you mentioned that i'm
so sorry you pooped in the sink
i didn't okay don't say that no
i'm really sorry i said i just
feel like it's true
don't ever spread that rumor about me
because i did not do that where
do you think it came from just
wondering don't you think there are other
people that you could implicate with this
ah say i was foreign matter and
it seemed like it was yours i
feel so privileged to be with people
who can be this open and i
can
believe how lucky i am i don't
feel that way after nilgiri which my
god i'm so sorry i didn't mean
to make you feel uncomfortable i didn't
know i really didn't i'm so and
i'm really sorry if i did don't
come to me with these fake know
and i'm relieved the world to me
they are standing up for yourself i
really really wish that i had not
said what i said i wish you
do
didn't say that either i'll i'll take
it back i'm really really so don't
don't even bother don't even bother please
forgive me sometimes you okay oh see
sometimes conflict is a gift and aren't
we so lucky aren't i so lucky
to have
the opportunity to bear witness to something
like this thank you both i'm so
sorry to even make you make that
speech because i feel like i am
i'm not worthy of it i appreciate
you saying that so much i do
too
okay okay okay i don't think that
you
are overly appreciative be overly thankful nice
you copy what he's saying no no
okay you you you ah take what
do you think it is i don't
know i think you're apologetic yeah i'm
overly right right mine i did it
and i just did it and i'm
doing it now making intense eye contact
show i always do that when i'm
still doing it what i have to
use a conjugation of do every single
time i talk
is crazy that you one's antiwar fuck
you zan tour not today not today
seattle cantor not today well that was
fun teacher matt any now let's maybe
next time oh okay well you know
what great cafe okay big cliffhanger time
uh
m z h look if you're not
listening to us three visit on the
twos what do you do with your
life every tuesday we're re-releasing our old
original episodes like old original from behind
a pay wall behind the pay wall
for free and you can hear them
and you can like them yep you
can love them and hey if you
wanna follow
follow us on instagram it's at three
m usa that's right we're also that
on twitter because that's still around we're
tape as far as just recording twitter
is still we're so far in advance
we're about five days in advance and
i don't think it'll still be asking
when is this coming out a wonder
people hearing this ah last last thursday
of december i believe okay my love
gave
to me um so if you wanna
write to us if you wanna suggest
a three-tier three m usa gmail dot
com or give us a phone call
at haha mine poo haha imho and
if you want to hear ad-free versions
of this go to stitcher premium or
comedy bang bang world dot com or
cvb world dotcom great anyway um ah
do you have anything
when lauren out the why was she
paying attention when i just said it
as i was on my phone oh
okay that's cool um last last thursday
of december i believe oh please okay
my my live show is january fourteenth
dynasty typewriter it's sold out but you
can get livestream tickets which are available
please watch some great lineup i posted
on my instagram you can see everyone's
playing it's john gilbert
sean distant jason masuk is mary holland
nicole byer be good i i am
currently in new york city i'm looking
for barbecue sauce and i will i'm
doing shows with amy mann and ted
leo they're doing their wow christmas show
i love that um at city winery
so we're there tonight and then
tomorrow and then january first oh interesting
we have new years many years eve
there yeah what do you guys do
on new years probably sitting hotel room
i love that cool yeah
i'll probably get blind drunk is janie
gonna be with you know she was
threatening to come up she'll be in
south carolina that's oh with her mommy
i'll come up and see you oh
my god sometimes new york new years
switch
i'm looking forward to i remember one
that i spent after the fish shows
where i was just really hung over
and then on new year's day i
had tickets for a matinee of follies
and i was so just hung over
and sick and watching that show was
just torture yeah right
alright so that's something you can do
to goodbye bye bye
uh