sorry
the the the the the the trade
you're doing the buffer so well so
long and i want to i want
to do longer next time i'm starting
from the beginning of the front of
the air here let's try it again
okay let's do it for that i'll
save it for the day my friend
next we need to lie you snoop
dogg i am soup talk y'all ready
for this note
so snoop dogg snoop did you do
hey that i'm su he says next
episode he doesn't say it who says
the next episode dr dray really yes
but even snoop dogg song snoop dogg
allowed him to errors who allow me
to give him permission to think they
drew straws to see who got to
say i want to sit here for
like
see i want to see it shut
up welcome to the show there's three
show this is freedom and that's paul
f tompkins over there i'm paul tomkins
i'm over here that's got aquaman over
there and right over here next to
me yeah right next to yes across
from me and paul uri
you're wearing a is this fully nautical
outfit i cannot tell like because the
hat is a captain it's illogical cap
it's a nautical cap but yeah okay
with my rank is
well are there any stripes or stars
there's no in the signia anything captain
of captain antonio fame have some sort
of rank he was well okay yes
but to me it wasn't indicated upon
his hat know he had i believe
he he had many captains hats as
we call them sure um and they
usually
had like the the traditional lifesaver with
some rope around is that no i
think that was purposely to say this
is not stolen valor i'm not i'm
not trying to pretend i'm in some
sort of navy i'm just a rich
guy as a boat oh wow so
so but it seems to me as
if all captain's hats from
then on in have had that lifesaver
with the rope around yeah did he
start that no no okay so this
is you think he said i'm gonna
call myself captain i better invent a
hat but i don't know what about
the anchor with a rope around it
isn't that a common theme that's a
common symbol though the united states navy
there are certain ranks where that would
be the insignia on your cow
yeah i think it's the anchor with
petty officer it's it's an anchor with
a rope and it says u s
n on it and so too i
think i honestly think this is just
me assuming i think it is to
avoid the confusion you're not saying i
am in the military rhymes just a
rich guy owns a boat or i
want you to think i am and
that's where you are you're
a rich guy who i don't even
have the ivs nothing on my head
you're just saying i like this which
would you and i'm not saying that
you'd have to spend money on it
to the exclusion of something else that
you'd rather have but if you had
a boat yeah would you would like
that yeah i would i wouldn't want
anything less than a boat
there's nothing there less than a bicycle
you listen to the wrong inflection there's
nothing in the world i would want
less listen to it or you gave
you permission
what does accusation
i would hate to have a boat
is what i'm saying why do you
not like boats at all i don't
really i don't like being able to
see sick very easily that's a big
problem and i don't think it's fun
do you think the one has to
do with the yeah definitely i'm just
not charmed by a boat and you
know what i don't want to deal
with the main oh no
oh that's what if someone would have
someone you could just pay someone to
do that though well if i had
a boat i probably could but what's
the problem for me is is like
the actual the the getting off of
the the marina or whatever you know
like if someone were to sue guy
too rich person's hobby because there's there's
so much upkeep and hassle involved in
it to do nothing yeah
well like to do nothing well i
mean the people une with nature do
boy i used to date a girl
who had didn't yes i did know
i dated two girls who had both
know two girls lauren
after lord said no you did she
looked at me with her eyes widely
can you believe i said that my
last year of high school i went
to the performing arts high school in
the richer part of town yeah i
was in kindergarten and
she wasn't even yet she was she
was she's my rule say she was
she was in bible school there's she
she was negative ten for refreshing yeah
umm woof but ah so ah so
i that year i dated two girls
who had boats and they took
me out on their boats two girls
one bow two
eight cups cups oh that means for
carry the one
but um i remember it's just like
yeah like this is the kind of
pleasant way to have a bonus yeah
i could go around them but the
marina or i get we are a
newport beach or wherever or huntington harbour
and you just kind of like go
around and everyone's like lit up their
rich houses with all their rich person
yeah it's you know like christmas lights
and all that kind of stuff and
you just like travel around really
the slowly but it's like can't you
just pay someone to do that once
and not have to buy a boat
well but here's the thing you and
this is very timely because my wife
and i are going to south carolina
as we always do in the summer
oh that's right how long do you
go for a week i wish i
wish i was only fun i would
live a friend who
who yeah i have a friend who
goes up to an island for in
vancouver for three months and for like
the sombra summer that's it just sounds
beautiful it sounds fantastic ah yeah yeah
but we so janie was saying i
want to rent us a boat like
take a boat out for a day
and i was like i'm pretty sure
you need a license for them you
can't just
rent a boat i don't know it
it turns out you can just rent
a boat yeah thank you yeah that
does isn't that right oh dang yes
i'm moving well that's the same thing
as these scooters that you see everywhere
around road one i think it's a
little different yeah well more thrown and
get lost at sea you're thinking about
yourself think about the danger to other
people yeah well
yeah but you can also a brownstone
hurt other people they hurt yourself the
bird scooters oh yeah and you're killing
birds it's scooters no but they are
low over bird scooters are mostly dangerous
to the person writing it seamus sure
yeah but they they could cause axes
agents yeah have you tried it no
i just went from like coffee foot
like i literally wrote it for like
for twelve inches i went for twelve
inches
my friend was using it then i
was like let me get on for
a second and then so i just
did but it's very fun but it
was very powerful crazy to see people
in hollywood here going thirty five miles
an hour through busy traffic just like
and swerving around having fun it's bad
i do it by the beach so
that seems fun somebody who's doing it
against traffic the other day right like
what we're having to be a law
was wearing a helmet and oh yeah
you just you know the whole thing
is they have a whole i watched
this like buzzfeed show on netflix about
that about the bird scooter and you
said i'm boring yeah i know
goodbye but they said one of the
like in that it was like one
of the rules with them legally as
you have to wear a helmet but
then no no one helped me with
never seen a single part while the
idea here is a helmet with a
horn yeah hopefully yeah hoping to get
well i hope i get one the
idea i think the idea what that
is
they are supposed to ah they can
be a help to people who um
either don't have a car or yeah
or don't want to use a car
or don't or there's no or public
transportation is not an aid to them
where they want to go nowhere they
can get the bird scooter they could
bring a helmet with them get the
shooter and then i've never
seen a single person wear a helmet
on one of the things is how
do you get back like you can
you take it inside wherever you're gonna
go so no one grabs it you
know and otherwise you're like shit out
of luck wherever you are i think
so i mean i don't know how
the i don't know how the um
the the the payment works on that
like if you have it for an
unranked i think it i
i assumed it was i think he
was a certain amount of yeah once
you turn it off you're you're you
stop paying but i think then people
have an app where they can go
find these scooters anywhere and what yeah
what if they find the one that
you need to get back home right
and then you also have to charge
them so you couldn't link keep it
in your house yeah forever but then
also in this documentary series
is on netflix
yeah he's just starting
um they talked about those people who's
like job is from bird scooter company
to like go around collecting them to
chinese more of those people one they
fight each other on the beach why
like they're basically like like anchorman i
i've never seen that
the crazy reveal
yeah is that weird no i mean
wrong i think but anyways they will
like battle each other because you get
money based on how many you bring
back to charge oh so working for
the same company battle each other yeah
and they're like several entirely non santa
monica boyer when it does it's not
it's not like a a van that
says bird
on the side it's people just in
their own car yeah i want i've
seen them i've seen them like driving
around yeah with like the pickup truck
or one guy had a convertible wow
that he just out of the bag
well that's easier than trying to fit
into the back of us then they'll
like go on the beach and like
collect i don't like stack them together
and then like moot push back on
pack em and stack i'm sad
really wow but anyways i wanna go
back to the boat yeah let's get
back to this boat because yeah are
you going to do it
yeah looks like we're doing it she's
already she's already rented so how long
do you rent the boat for are
you are you renting for the entire
half hour oh it's no it's can
you say what half hour it is
so i'm not on the water point
and then thirty twenty eight like youtube
like how to move a lot off
the water anyway i don't want to
be over here in the pacific ocean
to get you me
make it over here
just don't want to be i don't
want to be in my banjo and
they're out of control and suddenly rams
and you in the pacific so stupid
i don't want to be sitting on
the toilet
i don't want to wash my hands
you sit down to pee right oh
yeah it's people who don't i don't
understand sitting down his grab i don't
like standing up watching tv either i
sought to do everything no matter what
it is brush my teeth
i get on the counter and anything
in the bathroom hey brush my hair
yeah just have a seat it'll add
your vanity what if paul you had
a vanity the janie never used it
was just yours for brushing giving my
dream
and your big cat contacts will have
foundation yeah and then you just put
on your captain's hat the very last
second perfume with the bulb
so what are you going to do
on the boat probably get shit faced
drunk man yeah so we're gonna we're
gonna we both like boats a lot
and so we're just gonna drive around
and enjoy it you need to and
do they call it drive around or
sail around with our sailboat okay that
was what is what are they oh
that one oh but you need to
have a lot of knowledge
ej for sale but i literally do
not know what they could because it
can't be drive around stuff you literally
don't know because it is drive around
but yeah um cruise around does that
make you feel bad zoom around splashing
around just splash around to to round
around the boat so do you get
cool
do you not do not have you
never had issue i find sick i
know planes trains and automobiles okay motion
sick well isn't that just amazing do
you feel do you think the water
in your brain is perfectly balanced like
a level yeah oh why top it
up you know what i mean drinks
here i i have my fontanelle nh
never fully closed so i have a
cork in there and i just had
some fluid and you're you're a big
trepidation once i put soda in there
and i was awake for hours
so the reason why you get sick
is because your you need to be
looking at the bumps in the water
because your your eyes need to why
are you zoning zoning out i'm thinking
about what you say netflix documentary story
so the reason anyone gets motion sick
at all is because their eyes are
not matching what the bot what the
body is doing right so they say
when you're like check map and what
the body its america's dad here oh
my god that was fucking so our
ages did you see that he tweeted
because we tweeted
as others day yeah it's america's dad
here
people one person well did you see
o j simpson join twenty six and
getting even to do yeah yeah well
don't they're already dead some more getting
even shay yeah stay off twitter yeah
what is this i'm burning up
hs murderous day off daughter of the
good people
it sure is only the best people
i love the community i find
so then okay say you were rich
no causes say you're rich and you
just have like millions and millions of
dollars be awesome and you have the
house you wanted you have the life
you wanted but you were looking for
a hobby would you buy a boat
to the exclusion of something else paul
or like would that be the thing
that you'll like you
a rich man's hobby and i'm so
rich that but i can only afford
one expensive hobby yeah let's just say
that like everything else is taking care
of you don't have to worry about
money for the rest of your life
but you can only afford one sense
be it race cars be at boats
were you know whatever you want oh
yeah it would i mean in terms
of those things yeah it would be
a boat if i if i lived
by the water
and so it wouldn't be like if
i lived where i live now i
wouldn't be dragging a boat you know
to marina del rey or whatever right
yeah um but prep but i'm saying
that you would you would have the
house you wanted so if you want
yeah yeah on the wildwood i would
would you live by the water i
mean know your friends are out there
yeah yeah
yeah now i would love to live
by the water would you really i
love it where like malibu or what
yeah yeah jamie doesn't like that but
i we went what doesn't she like
about it it's so that because it's
so remote and so removed from everything
and i understand that but how would
you do as many podcasts as you
do just make it work well of
course i've built my studio oh yeah
i make everyone come to me that
read yes no one would do your
podcast if it was online with my
own banana nobody can touch
um turn off my conversation um but
yeah i would we we visited a
friend who was house-sitting ah at ah
i it was melissa matheson's house in
malibu is this judge judy screenwriter you
know judge judy real nameless emphasis
know your friend is just you who's
house-sitting
judge is house-sitting millis i'm wondering who
this friend is who's outfitting melissa mathison
zones none of your life might be
judge judy i see the interesting part
i found that judge judy is greenhouse
synergy i read today she's friends with
samuel l jackson
like my parents they're good for both
no nonsense no prisoners they're both good
friends so there's that weird so probably
because she's friends with you wait maybe
the most good friends to other people
no no they are highly-rated friends highly-rated
i don't know so judge judy was
rated the fourth greatest friend in the
world orbs yeah the
old yeah so this friend of yours
who i guess is gonna remain nameless
yeah entire podcast okay fine go ahead
it's the one you know really how
do you know i know so many
people i know who you know and
who you don't really picture of judge
samuel all like they're laughing together they're
having a great oh i can't see
any of this because my back is
to the screen and just turn around
and your swivel chair and you turn
around right then i wouldn't be on
mice the back of my head down
green
green eyes oh i see she remembers
is it right i don't know what
you're talking but your eye color my
man no blue shut up
i'm wrong you said that like just
in the middle it was more just
like wow i came to those wrong
wow shut huh how many times are
you wrong ever yeah a ton two
thousand sure lauren did you ever see
the tv show happy days yes do
you remember how fonzie famously could not
say the word wrong he couldn't
say the word wrong like i was
saying i was wrong always i was
rude oh no they're running gag on
the show it's funny i love ozzie
it was pretty funny i thought it
was hilarious i was rude so tell
us about your friend who is in
malibu's ah friend is not interesting uh
um so we were scribes doing this
house and they were they were on
the house was on a cliff overlooking
the water who and to look out
that window that e t money and
you felt like you were on the
edge of the world it was i
i absolutely could live there yeah
so cool yeah but i mean i
feel we should just get used to
it after a day like one day
you'd be like yeah yeah well that's
the thing we we talk about janey
and i talk all the time about
what if we you know lived in
look what we lived on sullivan's island
where she grew up where we got
married because we love it there right
but then it's always
it always comes down to well what
would our lives be what we're doing
day to day yeah we would have
complete we we wouldn't be doing the
same thing we do now we'd have
to have different jobs you'd have to
do something with your day i yes
think that when i'm home too or
i'm like oh this is so great
was so calm and so nice yeah
and then i'm like i would go
crazy because i wouldn't be
gl joe my dumb shit yeah and
i do love living in los angeles
i really do yeah it's home sometimes
i think about like moving to i
don't know i remember the final july
nah
so you keep talking another time i
was born and chi remember sanborn was
important sixty two
we are not that far apart only
forty years wasn't whore
i remember the final juliana margulies episode
of iar she ran out and she
like retired or whatever and and george
clooney came back for it right that
was the big surprise was like she
goes up to seattle and ah and
i just remember this beautiful house on
the water that like he opens the
door
four and he was right on the
sound i don't know where it was
but but he opens the door and
they're like they're together and that's her
happy ending right and i'm thinking like
wow he left the show three years
earlier and he bought this awesome house
on the water and so i like
sometimes i think about that like oh
goody character yeah yeah yeah he didn't
leave the show he left the hospital
yeah he left the hospital he retired
or whatever embodies bought a great house
up there he wait his character retired
i don't know what he did i
don't recall but everyone's move to different
hospital maybe yeah he went to a
different hospital who knows what weird like
such such a soft exit i watched
every episode
retiring i don't remember any details of
it well it's good to keep bringing
the shit up all i remember is
the house i remember that house and
i remember the goonies house at the
beginning of goonies up in portland ah
and as being two places where i
was like oh man it would be
so cool to live over there like
on the water yeah and but what
did it
yeah i did ultimately it would be
it would be nice but i would
probably get kind of stir crazy yeah
oh i like i like hanging out
at home i like me too i'm
not a person who's like oh man
i miss my friends or i you
know like i want to go out
to dinner with people you know like
just a person just like me write
these boring netflix documentaries
whatever man i don't know why you
got so upset about that i was
so furious your veins were popping like
crazy but i think i think at
that point like i don't know i'm
sixty i'm seventy god i don't think
i'm gonna make it but you are
but when to sixteen no i don't
know that far
but like being know i know but
at that point like the works dried
up
wing do not like milagro sure i'm
i'm gonna like be allowed to do
this forever so i can just sit
around the house up in seattle or
whatever now never leave and just do
whatever i do i don't know i
love seattle i do think of it
in terms of retirement yeah like if
i were but then i can't even
imagine retiring but i don't know i
yeah i kind of think like i
know so i know
no my friend's grandparents live in new
york city and soho with friends well
you don't know that described them to
me judy it's worthless what's a judge
judy though but no it's entergy but
these people her contemporaries um know they're
in there bernie sanders they graduated grandparents
in their eighties who live in a
five story walk-up
like on the fifth floor walk-up i
mean ah in a in soho like
and they walk up the stairs every
and like they they like have this
like active lifestyle where they walk up
well they have to walk a five
stars aligned by a loner in pairs
they probably take each step by step
you mean or do you mean they
walked together up i'm in or they
think he's
okay yeah there's links for legs who
are these big flunkies with googly eyes
and i love this
but my point is i want to
think about being older like the idea
of that sounds cooler to me than
being like in some quiet slake view
place like i think i'm like oh
i think i would rather be like
outliving in the environment with all these
vicarious move to the middle of nowhere
in their retirement and
and it came with a lot of
stuff that neither of them thought of
like what so they moved ah to
a very remote town in arizona and
so like things like being able to
buy fresh groceries they never thought of
all the groceries were like three days
older than they had here you know
i'm freaking like all the vegetables and
stuff as root i guess no but
that i would not have thought of
that either the ah the the hospitals
like if if anything seriously three days
older yeah if anything seriously in the
blood anything seriously wrong happy
and to them they would have had
to have been airlifted out on a
jesus christ drama yeah so an easy
way for old people yeah but like
it's something that when you when they
both retired ah i forget what age
you know sixty or whatever it's like
oh it sounds so great let's move
to the middle of nowhere and then
you get to be seventy it's like
oh yeah um but
yeah i remember my mom who loved
to cook was just like nothing the
part of the other thing was the
altitude there she's like nothing stays hot
here like of i will cook it
and within three minutes it is cold
yes we're weird things you would not
predict yeah i live right down the
cloud city of the spinners yes of
course now my grandfather or my parents
are low but my parents are low
but his grandparents because they're old enough
to be grandparents at this point probably
probably probably by the way speaking of
low-ball
but i sent ah was a great
trip spot low bot is a lamppost
buddy a tiny minor character in one
of the star wars movies and he's
a bald guy who has a weird
electronic thing he's got yeah yeah there
is i'm always happy when i don't
pretend to know something
yeah yeah no it's better now should
you ever see star wars i can't
we have this refers to explain what
this dumb thing yeah well i thought
it would be from like futurama okay
so what do you know about star
wars because i sent you both an
autographed picture that i got yeah from
darth vader that was so cool the
other day oh soo do is ah
yes it was literally a headshot it
wasn't even a headshot it was a
full
body shot but it was emotional shop
promotional shot but the size of a
headshot eight by ten black and white
glossy signed by darth vader and just
so funny that that's some other guy
in that costume for yeah oh yeah
it's not peter what's the name peter
moore david prout david prowse yeah your
morse who's peter maurin i don't know
but yeah david bray was
not david although maybe one who knows
i mean i guess i went to
i went somewhere in los angeles to
see him in nineteen hundred and eighty
and my parents said that i read
i bug them bug the bug them
and i really wanted to see him
then i finally got up to him
and i was so scared that i
could barely walk i'm sorry where was
he
i don't know like
i remember certain things like going to
the muppet song at the supermarket
it may add a little folding table
like a ball maybe i don't but
i don't know where or what it
was like a convention but was it
just him yes i think it was
just it wasn't like star wars right
no he wasn't i don't think you
see the table i think he was
standing at like i don't think you
sit like darth vader doesn't sit down
at a table i think he like
stands and yes we kind of imb
pose yeah yeah think we've seen him
sit in the movies a couple times
yeah when he's getting his helmet taken
on well also the meeting where he
chokes the guy is he sitting down
with them also but he's got a
big throne like i don't think he
was on a huge throne know they're
like a board room table
yeah music was the on a computer
you have a laptop yeah a child
what did we do before we could
just google anything we googled darth vader
sitting at least you had to i
remember you had to sit around and
like try to i remember doing crossword
around trying to find out vader was
yeah i'd go to that one second
i use
need to do the ah la times
sunday crossword i used to love it
but there was no internet and so
i used to like try to look
up i hadn't inside a full set
of encyclopedias and ideally having darth vader
i would be like okay v blank
d a let me look up v
a da let me look up v
i d v e a you know
until
you finally found what you looked up
under v
well you live e a e a
couple favorites little come on
your little funny idea v a g
yeah what if that was the only
way to jerk when i was a
kid looking up towards the jaya
and the because thing you just get
a definition
sure we're gonna have some diet without
um ah sure i remember i remember
hearing that the actor who played darth
vader in the car house was upset
that they didn't use his voice yeah
and apparently his voice is not great
well i'm your father hey bart can
you look at a chevron hey
well i mean the same thing to
say ray ray park with ah peter
sara benowitz right because raped oh yeah
ray park actually darlene oh yeah radars
ray ray park's actual voices are like
hey la up for some like me
off more what's going on to get
i have long practiced surfer it's er
did he do it in your sandwich
which i know he got so mad
me because so many is it it's
with the serafina wheel is which what
yeah yelled at on my yeah he
was so mad at me and i've
worked with sarah phyno i've worked with
his brother two years i worked with
yeah that's right yeah we know james
sarah fenwick or i've been saying it
wrong yeah but i've i've never i've
only
called him james for now seven years
or whatever i've never said his last
name and so peter took me to
task but i wonder did he did
he do the voice in han solo
and oh i would imagine huh spoiler
alert malls in that yeah that was
i remember hearing that there was some
big moment that happens in that movie
and yeah i saw that movie it
was kinda good it was over and
i was like i guess i was
the big moment it was cool but
i was like how does this even
work and so i had to do
some research i guess it all has
to do with the cartoon or whatever
we're getting very deep in the weeds
yeah we're sorry yeah sorry yeah do
you find okay away nice voice for
darth vader was another challenge
i should lucas had never intended the
onset vocal performance of aiello yeah i'm
both
what's going on thanks guys we cannot
watch this i wanna hear it we're
trying to listen to something
okay talked over it guys you talked
over who care i want to say
look so janky and i can't tell
what's happening but looks like a child
was in the darth vader suit lifting
someone who stayed have like perspective on
like him looking like he was looking
up really high have the perspective of
someone who's listening to this i don't
know what either of you are talking
about here's an essential perspective on me
and
zipping low are you gonna write austin
powers dr evil also frick remember his
exhibit thing that you stole he resisted
zippy darwin dinghy from alice the tv
show so dinghy yeah remember when like
all you had to do is come
up with just lie
like one sassy comeback for the cats
ready one at a catch what was
mel's diners doi dinghy was restored ruffin
stoic dinghy that was male the mean
co smells okay my grids kiss my
grits that was it yeah those are
the two big ones is that the
original placement i've just found yeah original
place no one ever say kiss kiss
no one ever said kiss my
yeah yeah and historically no because it
feels like it's just a now it's
just a thick southern know it is
a made up thing she did she
say it on the pilot we don't
know like was it a thing where
they're like kiss my grits i got
such a huge reaction like urkel and
i don't know if it was on
the pilot but it certainly made an
impact oh yes we're still talking about
never watched the show and i know
kid and it was huge like their
t-shirts alice was that it was on
petty briefly
lincoln with a little speech balloon yeah
wait was the mean woman on alice
linda lavin but then who is the
sidekick wasn't there somebody who had a
spinoff that flow yeah flow who said
the titular kiss my holiday yeah titular
intra-articular of our conversation
and it's the title of this episode
no he must be yeah why not
you can find student did i want
to get skin leave actually said so
many other ways that are so title
worthy that it's actually lame to go
with that one no internet i wanna
hear can i hear darth vader's original
voice oh god here we guess
start tearing the ship apart please like
to find those types fomo term it
sounds like see three people in my
life i want to i want for
my life wow it's so not loud
scary oh fighter he ship apart piece
by piece i want them alive gimme
dat sky walk up bro it's like
when you hear david beckham
voice yeah you have you see after
getting off to us poster for years
like what still sounds like
no oh i remember when i was
a kid there was going take a
break know there was a ah there
was a who shot j r t
all my guns here yes okay i
used to all my clothes shopping see
records and i remember just being like
you can put like
you can put a pop culture catchphrases
on a shirt and wear it that's
how cool i made my art oh
it's your school sucks yeah
when i made it but that's messy
you've been out of school so long
how would you even know it's ironic
when you say you made it did
you make it by hand or you
ordered it i went to a store
where they make shirts name i picked
it out oh okay so you bought
it i picked up the letters i
wrote don't want to say did you
and then they went downstairs and put
a little iron on it and then
think
oh yeah so by the way speaking
of irons i was thinking yesterday of
the clothes are wrinkled
can you remember there are iron and
glass the two things that are objects
that are called what they're made out
of
sand
no but a sand isn't an object
steel steel but hold a steel beam
i'm saying like a glass if you
drink out of glass it's made of
glass true and an ion is made
of iron you know the iron made
of iron i don't know but i
mean i would imagine they used to
be isn't that way it's called an
iron because it's made out of i
i honestly don't know
i don't know that i was a
tin yeah yeah okay a ten fifteen
of these skates chain is made out
of tin
eighteen made out of tin eye to
that ten out of ten stones break
into song
did is my data obtaining um a
glasses my dad glass but a gold
isn't made out of gold and steel
isn't made out of steel
someone please set this to music but
okie is made out of cookie
wears off book when you need to
think you mean base skates
oh that's right away english
alright let's take a break
welcome back welcome back to threesomes where
we're still doing the same show we
are not switched midstream and no mustn't
do it missing switch muster you do
it da seven
um i watched famous for not switching
midstream should always be my maybe have
you watched it on netflix i watched
it loved it i loved to to
watch five minutes i watched the keanu
reeves part oh well while i was
doing i guess oh okay that wasn't
finally was very funny partly like in
context even better it's really funny i
can't believe how much i left
oh there's a song in the movie
that i'm obsessed with i play it
and i know i think this is
okay to play a song yeah well
if we talk over it was fun
yeah yeah no yes it is if
we talk about it and criticize it
it's fine it's various size it i'm
gonna criticize it that way yeah otherwise
we're we're gonna run into copyright issues
well this sucks but let it play
for a goddamn oh i criticized his
announce good
huh
oh i don't remember this i'll tell
you where it was when they're when
they're making love it sounds like i'm
making love so i know it's when
they're reuniting like at the event and
he's like trying to find her and
then ok who who is it
who is it francis and the lights
featuring channel francis and the lights yes
very good love that time but let's
do it nonstop yeah and it's only
three minutes long so it's over and
splits what a bargain i know listen
to it three times in ten minutes
and still have a minute to do
whatever you want yeah
yeah now i go through my job
is showing us the track listing of
always be my maybe what's here's what's
funny what the soundtrack why is this
i feel like this is hurting the
show chevron and like looking stuff up
for you to get distracted to these
like facing the tv you wouldn't you
would love it yeah but i'm telling
you i'm hearing what the list
owners are hearing but you fighting about
it makes it worse like i've said
now they're like it is like kevin
is a listener of the show this
is what this is what people would
be doing listening to the girl just
a little googling random shit yeah while
they're not listening to us yeah what
are they talking about anyway i loved
the movie i thought it was really
fun yeah um i thought
randall parker is really funny i didn't
realize that he and ellie wang wrote
it with someone else i didn't either
till the end yeah yeah that was
to what the credits yeah i say
all do they turn to camera by
the way you wrote this
they say what if you enjoyed this
we have this um i thought it
was just a lay person puffin says
with me
me cry on point and even my
brother said he shed a single tear
was yeah hear that hardside motherfucker yeah
it's that emotionless robot that droid just
wait you know droid
oh no why what are you what
do you know from star wars i
guess droid okay you know who darth
vader is because i sent you guys
pictures i'll list everything i know from
it okay darth vader ublock see three
p o r two d two great
princess leia right han solo oh so
good um
well who's the new mokka the lead
character jar jar beings snow is a
delete i'm just naming things okay um
don't do luke skywalker that's who but
i thought he was han solo kind
of to read because you just thought
that i just thought you who are
camel is yeah i worked with him
okay and the big baby race
sure but did it where you like
are you han solo to him no
i didn't say a word about it
because i don't know enough about it
and i would never want to pretend
to and then look stupid right or
make him feel weird that i remember
that he was i guess he asked
bob odenkirk for copies of miss the
mister show episodes when i was working
on it and ah
i was i was a writer on
the fourth fourth season of mister show
and i begged bob in the personal
note that he wrote to him please
sign a sign it may the fourth
season be with you and he and
this is before may the fourth day
and everyone talks about may the fourth
and i thought it was so funny
and bob was like god didn't i'm
not gonna do that
make him feel bad about his badass
job on john no i'm just trying
to send him the tae actually think
bob was right bailey
but do you think that mario you
have to have my back on this
okay sorry yeah do you think mark
wanted the v h s tapes so
that he could shit on them
so you could put them in a
trash can and shit
i was like some of the worst
show on tv i gotta get this
out somehow he's the original headwater
um buh so you know so what
else do you know do you know
pretty much it honestly you know do
you know what they fight with light
sabers okay look i live in the
morals you know what who the the
darth vader's henchmen are you know the
people that used to like fly around
oh like coyotes kylo
oh ren oh you know kylo ren
okay i know that from like disneyland
from disneyland do you know why was
he there do you know like characters
mad all the time because he lost
his face do you know what he
says to luke skywalker i just saw
their obvious okay i'm your father
oh well good luck luke i'm your
father obviously look like here's a look
and look and repair that look and
we've done the movies but i have
to say like star wars or something
that i've like i haven't gone out
of my way to see in any
way but i you haven't no augusto
c right but i'm saying know but
you haven't gotten if it was if
it was playing next door you have
i'm saying
what else is like that like do
you guys have something like i've never
seen anything from it but i know
you know everything but i know everything
oh sure yours was like that for
me for a long time i don't
think i saw jaws until i was
twenty five twenty seven somewhere around there
but yeah i knew everything about it
from esa yeah same for me i
watched jaws recently and i think i'm
gonna i used to know about stuff
when i was a kid i used
to know about stuff from mad magazine
yeah but not ever having one yes
you know but you would know about
none i learned about from reading them
without ever having a madman because i
thought he just knew mad magazine oh
yeah i know if something parodied enough
like and that's the thing back in
the day being the deep you could
go three years before
was parodied and it would still like
go ah you know like nowadays yeah
if someone parodies something two weeks later
you're like boy you're late on that
show i'm late parody culture is moving
too fast but you know what i
mean like lamb of comedy like s
and l was parodying the godfather in
nineteen seventy six or whatever and that
was like four years old
or were like oh my god yeah
doing a marlon brando is rugged thing
that baluchi did on stage at second
city and it's like hey it's still
perfectly good impression yeah yeah why does
it people were like parenting something and
that's you know if you read the
one of the s and l books
they talk about how like no one
did fake commercials before s and l
and now you watch it in there
like
like their terrible early ones food yeah
well that's the thing yeah back in
the day everyone's like why would you
make fun of something like that lauren
would know more
talking about us alright
what
would you watch the star wars movies
for a podcast why did talk about
this on this and maybe that's why
it's somewhere in your brain i had
the idea to do a star wars
podcast where i watch each one and
then talk about them yeah would you
like one who likes it live talk
about it while it's happening like oh
my bachelor i may have asked you
happy when it came up before but
you already had the idea to do
so
yeah i think what do you think
you would just leave circled this would
you just be bored you know everything
about it now and it's just like
if you take everything you know about
it like yeah darth vader's his father
and they have lightsabers yeah love is
just a bunch of people like shooting
lasers at each other i mean there
are so many movies aren't there isn't
there a lot more to it but
also i feel that
i don't want to spend twenty plus
hours that's how i felt about the
lord of the rings like i felt
like it was such a con coming
out of that like really i spent
ten hours of my precious life i
see is ah god you gollum
i've i didn't feel that way about
lord of the rings i didn't feel
that way about the hobbit which i
i wouldn't even do it i was
excited to go to the hobbies because
in the same realm it is middle
earth but the the books are dramatically
i would say dramatically different the hobbit
is a much my lord is the
cartoon as a kid i remember yeah
those
oh yeah that was a weird cartoon
and then i read the book like
in preparation for the movies the lord
of the ring movies and i was
like this book socks why nothing happens
in it my journey was i read
i read those books in high school
love them i think i read the
hobbit in eighth grade i love your
popular i was ah i was okay
i did all right say anyway i
didn't read books in high school anyway
go ahead i was too busy and
it shows fucking girls on boats wow
we know you're lying so i am
i love i also didn't read and
i also didn't fuck
nothing going
i just had a blank room with
a blanket with john hodgman and justin
law
when i when i saw the first
lord of the rings movie i was
like wow that was okay i guess
i did an okay job adopting that
and i thought i would go back
and reread the books and i couldn't
do it it was because it was
too much detail yeah and that's of
course what people love about these these
bowling association yeah build a world yeah
so then i really enjoyed the rest
of the
the movies in that series and then
when the hobbit came out i was
very excited to see because i thought
great this will be a one-off movie
i love that but you going into
it you thought it was a one
off my head no idea no idea
it was split one that muah know
dan's i'm gonna love nothing oh i
was so mad i was so ma
they patted out this this re
really charming book into three fucking movies
it's ridiculous also a catch oh such
a really long time to see the
next one like you so anticlimactic what's
really long time to la that's a
long time what you think it should
be the next day there here's one
they shouted back to back just give
me all three just give me all
through on the backs of
future to give me a diaper like
that crazy astronaut lady war and i'll
just draw three yeah i'm not getting
up i'm not gonna miss a second
of it
the back to the future ones were
a summer apart or or were they
like summer and then like football futures
join remember it ends and you have
like it's not the same as that
where it just cuts off suddenly number
two does number two well guess what
no one cares what number three the
wire
old west i can't remember you don't
like the wild west with a no
wow is number two the future will
use the future and he's interested in
the wild you don't like any you
do you not like any westerns i
pretty much don't think that's worth our
time do you think ah so easy
doesn't need western is it because you
you don't like the trappings of the
old west you don't like yeah i
don't like dates coaching yeah horses yeah
i don't like the plot and i
don't like the like well you know
problems they fail the plots are all
like star wars is stagecoach in space
okay it's the movie stagecoach yeah he
he based it on the movie stagecoach
he based it on something wait no
yeah this
not true what does it what did
he base it on he based on
i'm like well yeah yeah nice yeah
the japanese movie yeah so i'm saying
i'm saying lay stunned by wise it's
a lot like he stole it i
think that's something else no but they
caught these calls thing are were stagecoach
no they called star trek wagon train
in space no but chevron doesn't
one thing i know you want to
show now look at star wars and
stagecoach agenda now you wanna shove it
do it ok here's my problem i'm
saying that the plots are universal it's
just you don't vote cooter mo down
the plots slow your work
paw tattoo a fucking okay yeah the
star wars movies are based on something
else well they're like westerns really but
he based them on these like very
specific japanese movie there i saw a
really interesting ah edited together version of
star wars where they took whatever the
shot in star was
ors was they they took like old
movies whatever whatever like he stole it
from and they think that is weird
like every movie is like a collection
hey but isn't that kind of disappointing
like like you think of it as
being like he created this world it's
like actually it's all based on this
japanese movie nobody knows but then well
to be
millionaire because but i also like that
he's given a lot of his money
away and stuff he's a good person
he yeah he he he built this
world but it was based on like
samurai stuff of like that's why you
know darth vader looks like a kabuki
kind of figure and yeah the swords
and all that kind of tree do
you find a reading on the stage
coach coach so i'm wrong
and to have any sort of negative
oh no no no no you just
you just googled star wars stagecoach in
movie
yeah how's everything going i'm not going
to get the answer that way but
i'm saying like you you you've never
seen it there's no stage coaches and
star we've never seen a western you
like but the plots are really seen
when i'm telling you okay i wonder
if unforgiven is the best one i
really want first i never used to
like westerns and then um ah until
deadwood really and then i re
only like i've never seen that but
i that seems more interesting i'm talking
about like they say that all the
seaworld movies and stuff like that they
say the seaward and deadwood yeah all
the time there's a lot of cursing
to seaward to see what they originally
gonna call it z would deeper than
just a dick i'll stick you dick
you see it
hey did kitsch not be already very
agro it is very agro agressive it's
intense i think ah i never used
to be into westerns because i just
was like well also you know growing
up in the seventy s west you
know my dad was very into western
powers
hey whoa that held in the fifties
like everyone got a davy crockett hat
and did you show steve i and
what isn't did you love yours
coola wasn't born yet kula wasn't born
yet
i read something about how like disney
was financed by all the david crockett
hats that they sold or something like
that data davy crockett show yeah they
did but then the they so many
kids by david crockett high z davy
crockett zone basically like finance disney for
years wow yeah um yeah otherwise they
were
gonna go to this same area nothing
they were doing is popular in the
fifth estimates down damn daniel you turned
it around does damn daniel
coming back at it with some mickey
mouse
but i'm saying if you found like
ah western whose plot you really liked
just update it and put lasers in
it and you're good okay i'm gonna
do that yeah i want you to
one genre you don't like and then
transplant into the other genre yeah what
do you what do what do you
like just movies there's that are set
in the present day talk sensibly use
do you think if i don't like
western like star wars
there's nothing left would you well what
do you like you like movies about
like queens and shit you like downton
abbey well yeah oh wow yeah movies
about queenie shit i don't actually have
family like movies set in the present
or the ninety eighty seventy sixty s
fifty s u b o thirty one
easiest to home is gonna agree on
zeroes
you need to take a break
hi welcome back let me i want
to know what let's let lauren yeah
laura never does it she never does
somebody somebody calls volunteer like how come
it's always the men who actually eating
new serious yeah what a weird fucking
problem lauren doesn't want to do let
me tell you
yeah i don't care because i'm here
and we come back from the break
and not paying attention she never does
eating a full meal swallow come on
everyone i'm swallowing i'm drinking water and
i don't care but we're back
we're back it's just the title it's
time for a feature the favorite part
of everyone on reddit it's time don't
acknowledge that now actually don't acknowledge them
i just know reddit hates everything not
i just mean everything um i was
reading on reddit by the way yesterday
this guy who's like who is freaking
out because
his wife was pregnant but he couldn't
reduce sperm or something and so he
was like she's cheating on me but
then they then see where this long
thing and everyone was like weighing in
with all the things he should do
and then he found out that like
it was his baby and it was
just it just worked or whatever like
it was just like people people go
to a doctor before you go salt
speed internet
thank you you know and then kill
her if she's cheating on you at
the most you were gonna play a
guy oh okay gotcha yeah gotcha hey
dr yeah here's my point continue i'm
bhagwat yeah just in case you don't
try to suggest me to me yeah
we're gonna play a game called celebrity
hunt some play this
well as a celebrities name everyone says
hunt than the next person says it's
celebrity's name that starts with the last
letter of this of the previous celebrity's
name so the last letter yes so
do it so let's do it and
how do we when you don't find
a good time oh good if you
if you like take two worst kind
of game you're out yes
if you take along your and how
long is too long it's obvious you
know we're gonna be very obvious like
pornography right alright and you feel it
here we go who's starting is lauren
starting yes lawrence okay the woman parker
posey hunt yasmeen thief hunt helen hayes
hud cigar
ernie weaver hans robert downey jr huh
ma hons wow richard dreyfus haas samantha
sarah jessica parker huh
ray parker junior huh and oh richard
beemer hi ra ah robert redford hot
dame judith anderson and ah neville
from harry potter yeah yeah wow what
does long bottom okay what was the
name use it those are the characters
know i was the name you said
dame judith anderson okay huh
hunt
oh ned campbell hoz lauren laccase hi
we celebrities oh yeah you got aquaman
always remember ah
nia vardalos hines um um um scott
speedman huh and the da da da
da da da da da da da
you're out slower and you keep going
until i can't do it anymore okay
no
yeah go i like this
okay scott speedman height natalie portman hot
nat king cole hearts um um evan
evan um ivo don't help bir evin
til your fake people yeah wow trying
to do i'm gonna hand raw seven
ross who's
diana ross's son oh from what the
reality show evident huh wait why ash
he's married to ashley simpson and they
have a reality show right oh i
actually some sort of pete wentz fame
yeah
have snell disaster chanel doing the hoedown
off stance he talks about it on
the show she started was she say
she revisits well she kind of made
her not perform for a while because
she was so traumatized by the experience
and now she's back to performing with
her husband evan that's not good yeah
yeah they sing a song together no
thanks um who occupy singer who's joe
gibson
with now she's with a football player
right i don't know does she ever
appear on the show one time one
time
one time um that's cool that's great
to hear what the simpsons people are
assume so huh da da da da
da da dan ashley nicole
should we do another round yes we
showed yeah okay started by you i'll
start at this time
that's what i said yeah
it's time to hunt for celebrities and
the first liberty we're hunting for is
is linda lavin hunch
the ends again yeah norman rockwell hunt
um ah lyle lovett hoz t a
career hunt earl miller huh ooh wait
who i'm thinking of earl who's from
deadwood wound
earl w earl w earl brown and
you're out you're out by what was
last one said i don't remember he'll
start over ah mike myers huh steven
spielberg hugs greta gerwig hot george harrison
hines um
um ah neve neve schulman from cat
from garfish huh she counts he does
know it's a he had no idea
he counts um um ah the neil
armstrong han's ah george orwell
well hot in leo dicaprio heinz leonardo
um orlando bloom hunts mich mulvaney hi
ah my favorite celebrity ah vous y
ou e yvonne or or yvonne
or orji what's her name vara georgie
i wanna know this girl from ah
insecure is orji her last name i
think what will j hold on i'm
looking at up i have to pause
because i was like ok that's okay
we need to know who yvonne orji
is it is a it is with
a j o r j i
o r j ai her name is
yvonne origin i've never heard said out
loud it can't be pronounced orgy okay
so i just hope not okay but
anyway hope it is alright okay so
it's within i i at the end
ivy and huh and the ian mackaye
huh was within ea um um eh
eric griffin hons ravines again um nicholas
brendon hans nick gillis cage hoz erika
badu
oh yeah yours so la
ah i don't know ah ursula i
want damn it were you thinking from
little mermaid or james bond
i was just thinking what to start
with you i was so andrus luke
in ursula phoebe's twin on friends oh
sure
you play again yes should i start
yeah
mahatma gandhi was um ione skye hot
ah eric swalwell hot lou is gossett
junior yeah huh
lou grant um um um robin robin
roberts
suzanne today's show oh yeah she's like
morning america ah samuel l jackson hunt
nah bird yeah sure
sure wow
samuel l jackson huh huns um um
um and natalie gains huh from ah
the music teacher dixie chicks sting hands
ah grover cleveland
hunt daniel radcliffe hunt um ah ah
erik estrada huh and ah elena ah
yeah about elena okay who because we
say it's within a shoes on
baywatch okay i'm gonna i'm gonna keep
going not urbana man is freed huh
and dame judi dench hunt helen hunt
hunt oh my god regretted we finally
found her we found the tracey ullman
hunt um um um
ah nea rivera hunt oh yeah ah
alice walker hines river phoenix hot oh
the end that's the note zaher cu
guys huh i'm just i said
oh that was fun we had a
good time was fun it was so
fun but we're at a time we
are we gotta go we gotta go
guys thank you so much for listening
ah we love doing the show and
we love that you listen to the
show and we love you and we
love you so much i'm that here's
the thing
miss love you show yeah you don't
let people know you know what i
don't think it's easy to say when
like a stranger is to say i
love you in utah i love you
back i feel like there's a stranger
you and when someone is being approached
by a foe and i feel like
i see strange when i see celebrities
go like when someone's like i love
you like i love you too
it's not right
all right guys on the person who
can look inside their hearts it's like
if someone's racist or not no as
a racist because you can't look in
their heart wow yeah i don't agree
with that even if somebody says incredibly
racist things you don't know what's in
there like you're talking about something very
specific that i don't know what you're
it's it's a thing that comes up
a lot on twitter twitter yeah yeah
it makes total sense
yes
um alright well that's the end of
our show i'm gonna wrap it up
as the only woman here lauren has
a piece of food that is just
she's holding in front of her mouth
waiting to end my life we gotta
wrap it up like she wants this
in her mouth so badly so phony
spoiler lap allows so phoney alright
right see you next i'm ah hey
a