three
ah
tutto
um
nah yeah yeah babies yeah bitchy roles
are back where the beach where the
beach and the bitches bag the trolls
of three-day are bad oh my god
we're here to show you the edge
lord shit posts
years of old ty we are doing
it we're little piggies for you when
you disgusting yeah wow we hate ourselves
and we love you too
i feel the braille with zeph luthi
god turn you to the cryptic oh
is that something you say hey yeah
so flow me
oh true she's dealing with some sort
of story holding low lowering into a
grade of fashion
what do you think he looks like
before
hey crypt keepers but i think he
was very handsome yet who is sad
beautiful fleshy cheeks yeah that long stringy
hair always had the hair his face
was covered with skin oh the best
skinny santa knows yeah two eyeballs you'd
actually ever have beautiful blue eyes absolutely
piercing your ice
cold yeah yeah he had hearing soos
being piercings he had earrings yeah yeah
let's had like big games hearing yeah
yeah big upi yeah when you have
you take off for a fight yeah
yeah gauges a new died as your
skeleton of big holes yeah of course
in your bud oh well yeah ooh
hey way i can maybe salah oh
my
my god this is just the way
the show is gonna be oh my
god that way i feel like it's
like that yeah huh i heard that
you got threatened over email hello we
introduce ourselves and say welcome back in
shu oh like oh my god hi
how dare i i'm scott oh nice
to meet you oh my god oh
you guys don't look anything like what
i imagined you to look like
i could say the same thing about
you but i'd be lying i imagined
you like the crypt keeper but with
skin that's what let's say you don't
look like thank you oh by the
way i'm lauren if you want to
know who i am
t w e t w d this
is three-day um the show where three
buddies we tell stories but i believe
jerk off well okay that's rosemead physically
paul did you get an email well
i'm glad you brought that up i'm
so glad you use that into make
a good segue but i'm so glad
should you use that into baghdad yes
i got this i got this email
sent somebody that i know oh and
it starts off very positive oh good
it takes a turn oh no why
do you walk us through that okay
greeting exclamation mark that sounds fun yeah
that sounds great yeah it's christmassy or
foreign just call me ask
automation or time traveler screw exclamation marks
excuse me there's a new pierce glider
works well while you're new i hear
the new period is no period but
by exclamation mark is like if you
don't have an exclamation mark you sound
like you're bored or sometimes i know
you hate to you period is starving
yourself to the point where you stop
having a peer
added right yeah because then i read
an article today about how periods imply
anger now till the conrail yeah it's
the younger generation younger than us they
are supposed to communicating through tick tock
dances my jam yeah and yes a
textbook soon traced his fist together he
thrust his fist again
it's the posts oh right still insists
he sees the ghosts oh my i'm
not familiar with if say that is
a rhyme that you say if you
are having trouble with a lisp say
again he thrusts his fists against the
posts and still insists he sees the
ghosts he threats his
fists against the posts and still insists
he sees the go oh no it
doesn't work oh why devin list character
why haven't you done why haven't you
think that's a great question i thank
you you really should make fun of
all those people it's not making fun
it's inhibiting inhabiting abide hooting of selling
company someone like me
alright so eventual being i got as
far as greetings then it takes a
turn oh real after one word yeah
okay so it's pretty quick i have
to share bad news with you oh
no paul is everything alright cool boy
it's not okay approximately a few months
ago i got from approximately somewhere
in the in the range of a
few months ago because that's sort of
feels like it was like five months
ago but i think it was more
like yeah it was either somewhere between
a month ago and six months ago
yeah
i gained access to your devices which
you use internet browsing
true true they gained true wow after
that i've started tracking your internet activity
or tonight after that well that's ok
after that i have started tracking your
internet in turkey slow down i can
yell yes since i've i need to
be off book with us after that
i've started tracking your internet activities you
wow you did it okay okay but
can we just get a series sometimes
when you don't look at it it's
actually easier
that's what doing voice over is like
for people don't nicole just get a
series it's like yes yeah two hundred
until you you feel it a hundred
times a hundred years not control of
your own performance at all i hadn't
actually a situation recently where i was
not in control of my performance to
the point where i was like i
can't believe what i was asked to
squawk like a bird so unexpectedly how
did it sound
horrible i could no no i'll give
us what oh no i can't did
you get the bird do it no
i can't actually to work on this
cause that it has to happen later
hear what you have though i can't
i'm actually see like you had to
leave no no you can't you didn't
get it go home i truly was
like i won't be shocked if i
get fired because i couldn't think of
how we're playing a bird or were
you playing a human who squawks like
a bird
kinda wish that situation yeah okay but
but the answer is man it wasn't
mentioned but no i can't do it
right now because i wanna hear ya
if it makes you feel any better
i don't wanna hear it thank you
anyway i was like humiliated i couldn't
i couldn't make a sound that made
any sense i actually was like i
gotta go
gotta work at this later i was
like a kid i had to hear
what a bird sounds like so what
did you do did you walk through
the park and listen to the chirping
i basically got in the car i
wanted to commit harm against my salary
care and then i um forgot about
it until now we have to go
back
so it made you feel bad for
roughly sixty seconds of the car i
feel bad for a few days yeah
he's really just kind of get what
you're doing wrong we yeah exactly here's
the sequence of events okay some time
ago i mean because i established it
was ah
probably a few months but can i
just say i don't think so far
i'm like what's okay say okay so
he browse on the internet yes on
the internet yeah well i've been tracking
my activities you'll actually like that that
that's sort of a little warning it's
playing yeah but maybe you've got wetter
expedia dot com and find like books
or dice um and we sponsored by
baghdad hotels dot com what are what
are some of our spa
others we oh really
let's see i don't have any this
paper says it's about our holes cause
we're held we are our own ad
our ads are just about our show
yeah i would like to come up
pills that cause the ad you'd like
to see in the world yeah um
sometime ago i purchased access to email
accounts from hackers purchase access
well hello say nowadays it is quite
simple to buy it online oh okay
i liked that they just explained to
you and you too if you want
easily managed to log into your email
could easily say my email account oh
my oh that they were emailing us
email they knew that part yeah they
should just send the password when will
be actually
a scary one week later i have
already installed the one week or so
so a few months ago plus one
week okay time is really adding up
and i'm lost where we march
i've already start i've already started doing
the thing that he's talking i've already
installed the cobalt strike beacon on the
operating system know of all the devices
you use to access wow strike stop
the episode right now you need to
take care of this lone beacon is
literally they know yeah i know blah
i'll tell you what i did at
the end okay
um it was not hard at all
since you were falling away from your
miami right yeah they keep saying how
not hard it was saying it was
unaware at all if you were following
his heart since you were falling links
for me inbox emails all ingenious is
simple and then in a motorcar of
a smile all night oh and too
late saying i don't all own genie
geology is simple emoticon smile such like
catchphrase sort of thing waiting period after
the emoticon yeah i don't think you
have to do that now i don't
know what the strunk and white is
on that but i do think when
you say emoticon we're putting ourselves back
like at least twenty years yeah just
saying emoticon yeah what a motorcar emoji
oh yeah move
emoji so we no longer can say
emoticon i can't say it we don't
say that anymore i just think that
they offensive to the kids maybe like
children or listening to them saying emoticon
like they're playing minesweeper what do we
care about what the children think about
us i don't how how young are
you out there how younger yo question
how old
i am i we are same as
our oldest listener was i think we
asked about youngest listeners and we got
a few that were like three and
four and they love us well i
was here on behalf of other people
kids if you're listening go to school
tomorrow we can't if a parody is
my three year old listens like we
don't know that yeah that's not twenty
they retain yes they don't know what's
going on if they
sauce on the street because they point
out the youngest listener who is able
to process the podcast and compose an
email i want someone twelve years old
to be our biggest fan why because
they can compose email oh tell me
our biggest fan
you're too young to be emailing it's
like if you're like twelve and you
love our show is it like when
we were growing up and you're like
you're into something like i'm trying to
think like a reference that's like yeah
like if i was like if i
was like twelve and i'm like obsessed
with howard stern i did watch howard
stern but yeah well you shouldn't be
doing that why nobody had a show
on e or he showed the big
teddy ladies guys were saying that was
nobody would be because marcy poverty what
this software provides me with access to
all your devices controllers example your microphone
video camera and keyboard that's bad or
paul or he could start typing on
it i will be scary that would
be a very ghostwriter did you watch
that show no no i was a
shove an adult by that i would
really hope that you didn't watch it
i have download
added all your information data photos videos
documents files web browsing history to my
servers i have access to all your
messengers social networks emails chat history and
contact lists that's everything paul it's really
getting this person did not leave out
a thing shit yeah because even got
the keyboards did you say accept
safari no really no he's like or
if you are an incognito mode i
don't know what you did he didn't
mention that i'm assuming and i'm so
i'm assuming it's a he it's definitely
a man women don't do stuff like
that my virus continuously refreshes the signatures
it is driver based oh it's driver
base and hence reminds him
visible lady is still playing you don't
owe me an explanation for how it's
like it was how you did enter
this to him yeah i'm gonna mean
oh yeah yeah exactly he's giving you
all the mr please give me all
the clues yeah
and hence remains invisible for antivirus software
likewise i guess by now you understand
why i have stayed undetected until this
letter ah yeah it's pretty obvious yeah
yeah i know where this is going
while gathering information about you i've discovered
that you are a big fan of
adult websites paul know you
love visiting porn websites and watching exciting
videos while enduring an enormous amount of
pleasure ahead for born enjoy it i
love it too you love enjoying it
well and having a lot of pleasure
oh yeah and that's one reason to
go sure
sounds like it make sense well i
have managed to record a number of
your dirty scenes and montage a few
vermont guys in them this is like
a mana hold on a second so
a cross-cutting he's here you're gonna triple
j i managed to record a number
of your dirty scenes in montage a
few videos would show how you masturbated
reach orgasms know how do you how
do you do my technique
the way i've always wondered why you
reach my reach orgasm is by masturbating
oh no that yes but that's i
thought that was obvious but from behind
it under
i don't want anyone to know my
tick me if you have doubts and
i did at first i can make
a few clicks of my mouse and
all your videos will be shared with
your friends colleagues and relatives and i'm
glad you didn't leave out a single
group i haven't received anything yet though
paul as well because they don't try
to shoot was done eating oh you
don't skip ahead hits you gave him
money
and considering the specificity of the videos
you like to watch you perfectly know
what i mean
it will cause a real catastrophe for
you oh my god what is high
draft porn reverse cowgirl race i watched
catastrophe and jerk off i say anytime
rob delaney takes his shirt off and
shows his bud by the way okay
that's normal i've been watching catastrophe great
show like love rob
don't make a show and show me
your bud if you're a friend of
mine you know you're in charge of
the show yeah you don't have to
show it in your pants there a
few times where on comedy bay where
they're like hey yeah so like this
in the script it says you show
your butt i'm like oh yeah cross
that out yeah if you did that
that would be horrible i would hate
it
ah um i'ma hate it by the
way it's pronounced catastrophe not catastrophic as
i thought oh that's an email i
know that's just the sidebar for me
okay this guy knows what you do
i also have no issue at all
with making them available for public access
nation exposed all data
no issue at all he is fine
i thought i was no reality i
saw you have some compunction yeah he
has no compunction with cheese and that's
like a period or exclamation point you
gotta have some compunction general data protection
regulation gdpr under the rug
did he write gdp yeah
no that does seem like the same
thing
general data protection regulation gdpr colon under
the rules of the law you face
a heavy fine or arrest i guess
you don't want that to happen i
don't know why i faced you hacked
into my shit i face no i
think he's trying to save the stuff
he watches because it's so disgusting and
because illegal oh okay yeah yeah so
that then there's
really only one thing that's illegal well
i gotta say what's up girl on
girl yeah greg sir
i gotta say like that's when you
go okay unless you're actually a pervert
but you get that email and go
oh i'm fine i didn't look at
something that you cover mint will own
estimates see i just got one of
these that's a little more like general
to i whenever i can find ah
that's just a little more like hey
you
no i have videos of you doing
this and i'll if and unless you
pay me money then well let when
you find out what would be the
word baby here that i bank so
yeah i'm gonna agree i agree when
you hear this let's settle it this
way you transfer six point eight bitcoin
to me six point eight bit okay
how much are bitcoin now they're like
fifty grand or somebody's i don't know
i also
i don't know where the point comes
in you have to get bit it's
like you have to work ten weeks
on nasional or something as a guest
writer just don't bring those bits coin
you transfer six point eight bitcoin to
me and once the transfer is received
i will delete all this dirty stuff
right away yeah right after that we
will forget about each other oh also
pro
a so i'll forget about you and
you'll forget about me that i don't
think i'm ever gonna forget worries i
seen i doubt that tool like sort
of like a movie thing yeah like
a normalized yeah good man and black
yeah i don't think are you waving
harry potter i've never gotten great man
blacks i didn't know what movie wasn't
know what to call it but i
was doing i was doing what you
were saying like like an eraser like
big racer yeah erase your brain he's
like you will forget about
me and i will forget about you
i don't think he forgets my name
either i know you don't forget about
him you forget about him he made
me oh i forgot you because you
don't know about him and because anytime
he spends some of that bitcoin he's
going to go this guy knows what
he's doing i'm sure he's doing this
to so many people who masturbate and
i think he will forget about me
but i'll remember this it'll be a
scar on my brain anytime i masturbate
from yeah well that's true
true you you are gonna worry that
he's looking at you he says after
that we've got about each other i
also promise to deactivate and delete all
the harmful software from your devices trust
me i keep my word oh good
okay so this guy sounds okay sort
of a gentleman so yeah sure this
is a fair deal that is a
fair deal and the prices
relatively low considering that i have been
checking on your profile and traffic for
some time by now if you should
promise to send pictures of himself doing
the same jerk off stuff and that
way it's like detachably assured destruction yeah
yeah we'll be good i was feeling
sad alive but if he did that
um
if you don't want to purchase and
transfer bitcoin okay use any modern search
engine o any modern one okay wait
how old not bear the shot ask
jeeves baby you get on google you
imagine asking jeeves that as we ever
i mean more like it to my
georgia jeeves how do i g g
old boy
transfer me to the business nursing jeeves
but i've been watched on my computer
it was very easy you see and
for using gdpr you need to send
that amount here bitcoin wallet b c
one q eight k y z l
n n f you don't have to
be cool and six
denbigh money hey everyone send your bitcoin
p g q x z g seven
u j u x j j p
w ever q you're right b c
one q eight
again paul is expanding so it can
be bigger just it's i mean it's
a long address well it isn't that's
because it's his wallet and you really
it is very specific alright here we
go sorry
b c one q h k y
z l n n f for a
six five k eight p g q
x z g seven u x j
j p w q zero l c
d v k three r a five
the price is not negotiable how much
is it six point eight
bitcoin will just want a big ego
you have five days in order to
make the payment from the moment you
open this email in us dollars do
not try to find and destroy my
virus exclamation that's a hundred and forty
one thousand one hundred eighty one dollars
and ten cents it's a fair price
and it's not negotiable could you get
them down
ten cents that's so i got one
of those they want me to send
them a thousand dollars yeah it's lucky
yeah but this guy is he's he's
hitting the people who are like really
bad pervert yeah yeah he's like you
yeah pay me off with your fucking
more i think it's by masturbation session
zoe that is if it does make
sense because because it's like tell me
do it like a thousand times your
guy you do at one hundred and
forty one your guy needs like one
hundred and forty one thousand people to
respond and pay him it was i
only needs one that's true he's kinda
got a it's better that way yeah
better business plan all your data is
already uploaded to a remote server do
not try to contact me
various security devices will not help you
formatting a disk or destroying adviser not
helped by the way since your data
something is making it longer but i
can't put my finger on it by
the way edit these down if you're
going to send these sensor data around
like if this is one of my
ripping things i've ever read no honestly
it is because it's crazy how it
he's really threatening you yes
and no way of getting out of
this ah so what are you gonna
do you're gonna send my automatic disk
or destroying device will not help either
since your data is already on a
remote server yeah i get it this
is an apc hacking group don't be
mad at me everyone has their own
work wow hey try getting a job
at a store i have empathy for
fish gotta swim birds gotta fly yeah
okay so what do you
dude what are you doing i will
monitor your every roosevelt yeah i'll let
you know when it's over cheats i'm
not gonna just keep looking at my
phone
i thought you were taking texts at
this point let's hear it um this
is an apa domain but i will
monitor your every move until i get
paid if you keep your end of
the agreement the agreement you won't hear
from me ever again everything will be
done fairly one more thing oh god
don't get caught in similar kinds of
situations anymore in the future my advice
keep ch
changing all your passwords frequently
how kind is there like a stage
direction of evil laugh yeah no i
added that oh like a guy took
a lipstick license um i did a
motorcar of the devil i um i
sent him the six point eight bitcoin
and okay ah one point two more
bitcoin just like a little yeah buffer
like and be like hey come on
you're like a pro
ali do it again so it's just
kind of yeah that's the only way
to take care of this kind of
i have yet to hear back from
him that he forgot about or from
anyone in the hacking group no i
think you're good i think you know
you're talking because he was basically when
to gets the money he'll never do
thing so yeah i think this was
this morning yeah yeah yeah yeah even
had time to respond yeah he's he's
out there he's working
ing right now this is nancy beginning
of the work that you dream and
it is ease his job he's got
you'll hear from him at five pm
yeah hell yeah cod yeah yo d
ok we have to take a break
we'll be right back
and we're back you know it's time
in the show for a very special
aura and be quiet okay you know
it's time in the show for a
very special segment yeah lauren took it
away this is called lorien the topics
now i have a lot that i
want to say today okay if you
are ever called love is blind see
isn't three yeah if you've never really
reality recap if you never heard them
before lauren quite frequently has a little
segment called lawrence topics and it's it's
really much how would you describe it's
really interesting it's really good i think
one thing that happens a lot is
that i sort of conflate my other
segment
reality recap with lawrence topics and i
will then throw out some sort of
reality information yeah just did when we
correct you and then you and then
that was good information to ninety percent
of yeah there's a new season of
love is blind and it's great um
but um excuse me your excuse too
so yeah have a topic today and
my topic is that i'm
i'm in this moment sharing my segment
and calling it lawrence topics whole lacking
talking of scots tops god's version the
scott edition why i'm in one-time only
one time way on time i'll thank
god hold on there's a present there
there's a parent that'll but we'll see
if maybe he ends up having something
else he wants to share in which
point we will assess the sich
situation oh yea wait till i get
tow okay you can't use lawrence topic
yeah this is your time to kind
of just share anything really interesting that
you want to talk about really interesting
it has to be one of the
most interesting of the art emf jaw
you can't just you know tell me
you know about your ma
running routine or something i need to
hear well like digging i went to
physical therapy this morning for my foods
okay that is interesting proud of actually
i do wanna hear about your morning
routines oh okay well you heard me
which wasn't you get my master basic
scam for my masturbation see married five
times every news i got skipped i'm
just gonna keep him in this
kind of bitcoin yeah you better think
yeah he's a major one ever yeah
yeah every time you jerk off one
time in advance like i'm gonna go
later well you go and yes sexy
movie you're gonna see i'm gonna be
excited but i'm gonna watch mr and
mrs smith on cable
ah when people went to movies just
to be horny yeah i do a
few names pop to mind um yeah
so yeah um let's talk about your
topics because i know you and you
not related to that tell me the
topic not unrelated to that well sure
i mean
guess life happens boy is that the
truth man gump happens gump happens is
that awake i'm sure those reinforce come
t-shirts that are you fucking y'all i
came out because because this company and
shit well yeah that was in the
movie that shit happens is what he
said but then they they wanted to
market it so they made it say
gump happen
did you miss my miss that time
of the forest oh yeah oh about
joe a bunch i've seen it probably
five times what yeah that is five
times too many that when i worked
at the video store i remember seeing
forrest gump that was like you know
people barely know see and i think
our age difference there i like thought
it was great yeah here you were
stupid yeah yes but i feel like
a
a big difference in ages is some
hanks come on freedom a thing you
do think if i were your age
at the time i would have made
fun of it yes yeah but i
think a generational thing is like younger
people i feel like people younger than
me if they liked to thing once
they like it forever totally don't think
that's generation generationally that's not true
you're saying or just i think i'm
saying i look back at the things
that i liked when i was a
kid and you up and i say
oh that sucks i know i remember
that be good again and remember when
i watched scooby doo episode and i
was like wait a minute this shows
terrible cheapest fucking thing yeah but i
loved it of course last newly i
feel like we had so much fun
being like
forest room now that is fine i
would do that on the playground of
course i just think someone pretended braces
and then run out of them yeah
well what made him ran a um
what made him from content are some
though the people were chasing him i
think he was being taunted to shreds
and he had to run just taunted
do you know you can you can
already gotten his ass kicked i don't
remember do you remember the movie mafia
exclamation mark which was a sort of
genre or others type yeah over yeah
in fact ah one of the editors
on mister show was editing a three
minute trailer to that for weeks and
ain't that a kick in the head
by dean martin kept
saying oh over and over next door
to my office
oh my god that was a terrible
time here's what i remember um and
i associate this with forrest gump because
it was a it was a a
parody of foreign come see of that
scene where i guess when he j
moore's character is a little kid he's
a florist he works at ah right
flower shop bought and i'm bad i'm
bad so honey nah not time there's
a litter
girl that's what stead yells run floor
wrist but she she says it just
like that it's like don't worry we
look you we we can't have people
missing this yeah that's so brutal really
really really enunciate yeah yeah you know
when it is softening what well
wow that is a laughing way up
though we need to be talking about
your shots yeah that's a real misuse
of scots topics yeah this the topic
is jay moore movie mafia i think
you're using it for yeah i think
i do think he just wasted his
topic let's go scott do you think
he is
genius i think he did it morin
mafia i gotta look this yeah yes
yes okay because the titular mafia mafia
is a parody film yeah of of
like goodfellas and they also threw it
got father but then of course they
would throw in any fucking gag they
could because they had to fill one
was like however many paid for it
yeah we should write one of these
movies it sounds easy maybe we already
did
we should check our desk drawers and
see if there's anything in there i
did write a draft scary movie three
so um who didn't after the fact
you're like here's why
you show the back data yeah obama
huh
can i say i was wrong yeah
so so you feel let's see i
die yeah um you know how you
have so there's one yeah we all
have these these catchphrases that we bring
back or yeah francis over no worse
yeah now there's one of yours that
i've never gotten but i will play
girls on film because everyone know i
get that every
but i've always accepted it as one
day i'm really gonna understand that i
know what it is so this is
kind of like you settling scores okay
which one is oh you want us
yes okay from a deli owner that's
rafe know how does that go oh
it goes know someone's l yoder that's
a ray lawrence talking about song are
you talking about something song things oh
and here the syllabus yes yes absolutely
so do can you think of one
that maybe i might be thinking oh
my god you argue so young girls
that you have girls on film yeah
baby come back it's just that this
brand-new joe semesters you have it though
we all have ghostbusters we all have
a way of these i learned i
had ghostbusters to see the doctor ah
in your goal
bladder yeah just have ghostbusters of the
gallbladder
bgp
um i know i know it juba
g i know i know it's serious
oh friend in a coma by this
yes wow i like this mess but
i actually didn't know that song and
it came into my spotify rotation and
then i was like oh i love
this and then i was like what
and i finally was like yo fine
oh my now
i'm like i need to know what
would set that off so i have
anything going data data data i know
but i'm like one two three four
five six seven eight if anything in
that rhythm that falls in that rhythm
and it's very it's a very specific
thing i can't think of anything you
know it's not necessarily a number of
syllables although it has to be that
number of syllables you hear it and
you know
it has to be the emphasis of
like the way you read a collection
of words if it scans yes that
that that that data i can't wait
to happen but ah well that's how
i know because you could take over
the no part if it's just that
debt debt debt data you would go
i know that's true you know what
scott you're writing i can't wait to
hear one because
and wait to hear what i know
or knew i know siri yeah right
there i just did it okay that's
amazing well i guess
okay so we have wasted scots topic
i think it's closed it's too bad
you have to take oil we think
we're great now just mentally and then
come back and go we should take
what's your top
preview redd it was a comedian mental
break let's say yeah let's take a
mental break your hands a break
previously on freedom preview previously on three
item so scott i hear that you
have a topic you're gonna want to
introduce when we got awkward yeah when
we come back for new season i
i want to have can i use
lawrence topics to talk about something yeah
i think so yeah i'm gonna see
the topics are full and what's going
on because i have a running list
of all the topics and whether it's
fuller yeah so
kind of hits a level so anyway
yeah we'll check in it okay look
in the seas easy yeah and we're
not gonna forget about it right i'm
not going to talk about something stupid
like the j moore movie mafia we
ever talk about that okay great you
promise pinky swear guys i'll think he's
almost thinking of that i promise thinking
thank you peggy okay okay see you
next season
lulu couldn't remember
ah amazing so that is what happened
so i guess i did say you
could do it i know the topics
are not full it's not full and
the mafia thing did happen that was
so weird i feel like yeah that
was weird we were able to muncie
because i think the flashback was important
because flashback was important i know wings
world
get away with just like there was
a bill in gland already yeah it's
not the same it's i would have
been very close let's see the i'm
not i'm not talking about that specific
thing i'm talking about the whole the
care whoa yeah you know you know
what they're really different well they're based
on the archetypes that you sign as
hi kara one has gone yeah that's
what i'm talking about
that's pretty much where this sameness is
end yeah okay those aren't even sameness
this is one is black-haired yes they
have that mirroring oreo situation they definitely
have real situation because oreos are you
know one color on one side and
one color on the other side the
one half of the ori know when
i got here early
it really sounds like generic cookies that
are like chocolate ones have a high
draw good yeah i don't know of
garbage supermarket oh my god i love
the three sixty five mismatched fuck yeah
one of those that's what i'm talking
about but it's like basically the store
brand version of chocolate ones have been
on cream in the mo
this got much back
okay people are gonna be mad because
they'll shake frame in the middle get
scammed you
ah greetings greetings greetings you listen to
the principle
so people have been waiting with bated
breath for i don't know how many
weeks we've been off the air but
so they need to know what is
your topic yeah alright well okay and
yeah i am surprising to me that
people still haven't picked up on this
or figured this out yeah sure if
you're not on social media though that's
true huh alright so the
one time i guess the one topic
that i wanna talk about is that
jay moore movie mafia have we talked
about something okay this and so people
on social media will have seen seen
the skits that you do talk about
this said alright i had a baby
boy when i had maybe it's a
boys reference i like today so one
hundreds of likes commercial oh who was
um i don't know if it was
cause he had a baby boy oh
yeah baby
oh yeah because it was so query
yeah yeah you look like call from
we had a baby it's a boy
but you had a baby it's talking
about remember that i tried to call
phoenix but i called fiji it's like
that could not happen how many series
call fiji so many picks up the
phone and says come on if he
sighed that's so correct amount of visa
you know i i think that's what
they suck
out of each side yeah they're like
at some resort oh i'll come out
of his helmet this woman is trying
to call miserable old phoenix arizona and
she this beautiful island paradise and she's
upset well because it's of course it's
a huge expense i guess but like
so you had to give her a
free girl or some and oh so
exciting she's so beautiful
will oh and did you share her
name online or you're not sure yes
emeralds such a beautiful name and yeah
we i mean you know i think
i think in a previous season we
talked about that operation where they drained
my balls i recall i think i
actually made fun of you
believe me it cost me some bitcoin
so you go home open your computer
say what
sorry i was listening back to the
listing to me but so good and
you had to just because i said
balls he hasn't farted said balls game
granted me listening to which and that's
really a lot oh get a dray
okay so it doesn't just get turned
off by the idea of balls they're
going to be drained doesn't cream dream
like the idea of draining balls is
so funny everybody try and make a
noise i want them to be shriveled
up and noise in the very other
oh ah yes
last day last day was it i'll
day doing the janet jackson with your
you have huge shoulder pads i just
noticed him but i wore shoulder pads
other knights beat lisa rinna for halloween
and i felt amazing yeah anyway gone
okay so cool love and i we
ah
she's talks about this on add to
cart if you want to give the
layer is long nice explanation of backstory
yes cursor story over the last ten
middle stories i think
ten years ago that ten years ago
next month was the first time that
we who we were pregnant and wow
ten years ago this very next will
this while it's been ten years and
you're amazing that it's litter jersey so
it's been a long been along been
a long time yeah lonely lonely lonely
time yeah um but then we went
through a lot of like ibf stuff
we went through america's funny oh no
sorry yeah we watched a lot of
that
um just to get in the mood
yeah but giggly when you really want
through a lot of eight and gay
gay no man of getting giggly with
it haha oh my god call out
this is nutshell
wait make the movie again um oh
okay you need to adding the movie
a long story short we had a
lot of ups and downs where we
had quite a few pregnancies that did
not work out ah we had to
switch doctors and the doc our new
doctor said that our old doctor
or ah performed a procedure that they
should not have done and then did
ruin our chances yeah yeah yeah ooh
anyway gang so we didn't have a
gang we did another round of ibf
and you know the older the older
you get the the more diminishing return
there are you know
like of like because when we first
started years and years ago we would
get twenty fifty one hundred no way
we get we would get a lot
of a lot of eggs and and
they were wasting them they were putting
in like two at a time and
three at a time and going like
oh that didn't work well that's true
you have a lot of acei so
by the end of this whole thing
when we finally went to the new
doctor we were
pull up went through two rounds of
ivf is shy identity as well and
it is not easy to a point
where she was crying one day going
i don't know what's wrong with me
and i was calling the doctors and
they're saying it's the it's the hormones
ancient and she's like can i stop
and they're like you can't unless you'll
just have to start over so she
just going through major depression anyway so
we aren't so i drained my balls
going through
just press oh he's not the same
mr hugh this was when i stopped
i mean just kid with this
and there's good coffee but the litecoins
are adding
expecting the episodes were doing so many
shots shots shots shots shots shots um
trigger shots areas i'm just getting looking
if you've gone through it you know
just how brutal it can be absolutely
anyway so at the end of like
several more rounds and me doing this
operate we we both she did a
retrieval and i did this operation at
the same time we were in two
separate rooms ah she famously heard like
hell say oh that's right she famously
heard them say get the smelling salts
because i was about to pass out
the smelling salts um i want to
say that and i was like oh
right now guess the selling itself yeah
because this is so boring
um sure but not boring at all
anyway so we finally were able to
get one little board we were just
able to get one no this is
where it gets interesting well good they're
able to eat were able to get
one egg egg thing
well you made an embryo an embryo
yes and we end and out of
all the ones they tet like maybe
we had two and they tested and
three were bad but we we had
one viable one ah now they want
you to have two because it cannot
work out but collect did not want
to go through the ibf again because
i feel like shit did it ten
to fifteen
this brings havoc on the bod yes
so she's like please i don't want
to do this again so then then
we ah our doctor said okay you
need to do this via surrogate because
ah because what happened you are ah
you cannot have a baby cool up
so we then went through the process
of getting a surrogate and that was
and this
it was right ah this was in
twenty twenty node twenty twenty twenty two
fifteen twenty twenty twenty one because the
the vaccine had just come out ah
so ah we had to zoom with
all these surrogates we actually got a
surrogate who was like
deal was you have to get the
covered vaccine before we do this because
we only have one we don't want
you know something come of it and
so we got one ah who was
like yeah yeah i'll get the co
vaccine and then yeah yeah for the
next two months they say like that
that's a red flag yeah for sure
i'll get the covert vaccine how do
you say that coke ko ko
isaac kevin um so for the next
two months while lee were you know
like settling everything and she was going
through the the doctor stuff that we
were paying for and all that kind
of shot ah she kept like everyone's
smuggling but what if i didn't get
the co vaccine we were like oh
yeah yeah because after all it's a
rule yeah and then finally right as
we were
signing it she's like look i'm going
to be honest i ain't getting this
cove vaccine well you know what that
was such a blessing it was great
worked out the way it was supposed
to it was great because whatever that
seemed like a bad situation and then
we quite quickly got our the woman
who turned out to be our surrogate
who was amazing yeah and so i
go
seen every morning you didn't you ended
up with somebody where you didn't have
to wonder you know yeah he's communicative
person she was great we really really
like her and her husband and so
this was her sixth baby her third
surrogacy wow it's so amazing amazing thing
to do yeah and she ah it
was really good i mean we you
no ah we got off tour paul
and i got off tour and i
thought i had one month until because
she said i'm giving birth on october
first probably because i have in every
other pregnancy and that's kind of my
fault because i kept reiterating that to
scott yeah that i was like you
says you have one
month yeah yeah um yeah i don't
mean that she would give birth on
october first i mean that that many
weeks in that many days yeah so
she she was like october versus the
target date so so we did that
tour and i was kinda like oh
okay a month leeway that'll be good
literally the plane landed when we got
back and the surrogate texted and said
my mucus plug just dropped yes um
which i said disgusting yeah i hope
so later a thumbs-down to my six
p m i yeah don't you want
to get deal with that you know
the way i never heard that before
in my life my mucus plug just
dropped well why would you yeah well
because intuition would you be you here
you know you know it's interest
eating um i got a first date
i'm doing something with leadership i'm doing
something i can't talk about but it's
mentioned and it's like i wonder if
it's if it's maybe or will it
be that thing of like what's that
thing where the mandela effect or something
where like you oh yeah barry chambers
was that mandela effects that's the that's
the one of the prime examples of
the mendez
l effect you think it is something
but it's not something it ever was
yes because i think you understand this
is something the wrong thing there's a
what's the word for when you hear
something and then you start seeing it
everywhere and it's like oh right i
forget what the thing but i know
what you mean
yeah but anyway maybe you're now that
you've heard it now you'll see everyone
talking about it that's weird anyway but
so so that happened on uncle's blog
and that can't happen on september first
and that mean it's coming very it's
coming very mercer it can mean not
it can be not so what does
it also mean so just
there's a chunk of mucus it's a
plug right it's like basically like it's
it's like you know it's really nice
you know how you stop up your
toilet with your big nest he shits
yes oh okay so protected i'm going
to describe it wrong say those go
down and you finally unplug your even
if you describe a rocket i hear
yours instead i think about shit and
toilet oh
i'm gonna just look up definitions we
can just tell guys you're gonna fucking
show me a picture of this plug
with a thick piece of mucus that
blocks the opening new cervix during pregnancy
is what i thought it was it
forms a seal to prevent bacteria and
infection from getting into your uterus and
reaching your baby think of it as
a barrier between your vagina and your
uterus where your baby is for most
yeah um so when i
i've heard my water has broken and
that's a different thing so the the
me that is that says it's kind
of that slight because like dry waters
never broke your water never bro i'm
so sorry we still have it oh
no yeah you're drinking right now so
i bought nutrients so when they said
drops what does that mean a dry
light comes out like you come out
and steam you mister your own underwear
and toilet oh no no no more
if you're gonna just make it around
the house your account but i'm sorry
women are very used to like various
things coming out of the vagina which
i know and various things going sure
penny so it's not that big of
a deal at that point
yeah so it's it's it's she you
know we we don't have to deal
with this shit i got home and
learned this it was comes out other
things okay whatever got home and learn
this news and and then it became
a race of like i was like
oh i have a month to like
record two months worth worth of podcasts
that's gonna take robot
you have a lot of podcast so
became it became a race to like
record everything so we would like you
vs that mucus plug yeah sure but
she was gone shannon i would do
several yeah it started several scary movies
a day right um anyway so so
then it took another month like but
basically to basically two weeks later
to say she said were three centimeters
i'm three centimeters and she lives in
riverside by the way which riverside is
close but if there's traffic just fucking
too it's just far enough where it's
like a two hour if there's really
bad traffic maybe a little bit longer
which would suck if like it's like
hey my water just broke and then
we missed the whole thing right saying
so
so we were like three centimeters and
we could probably like we were we
were gonna go in a week yeah
and then collapse friend calls and goes
cool up you are going tonight three
centimeters becomes five centimeters becomes ten centimeters
who you need to be there tonight
i have to say i
i i think club's friend group is
so fascinating because what i love about
them and i've really been like i
listened to the deep dive but it's
an a bitch so i like i
feel like i have a lot of
good sense in those nabbed card something
i have a good sense like the
friend group and then being at the
baby shower is another thing to witness
it a little bit more even though
i know all these women and they're
also funny they're the way they communicate
is so strong
with each other i love it like
i love it i think it's like
so i just like think i just
love that kind of energy that they
just like you have to go now
look at yeah no one really talks
to me like that and i wouldn't
mind if they did yeah i would
like to talk
you need to go now yeah but
i just love how they're like they'll
be like your hair was fucked up
and then like oh okay that's like
you need to fix it like it's
like there's this way of like just
like this honesty but but but it's
out of interest yes yes it's like
it's like you need to work a
little harder yeah like just chi june
will have the funniest conversations like yeah
i told you
i can't wear that color right like
it does not look good on you
and it's like oh my god i
just love it yeah so sounds pretty
rude so collapse friendly light know i
owe her so cluster and said we
had to go so we were like
oh okay so we got everything together
by the way i had a go
bag like at the ready ever since
i like your porn collection comic book
my my bitcoin all my collected from
paul i funko pops i mean no
i gotta find my focal pups for
emerald disease
i wanna do the first thing that
she sees on earth but i had
to i had to go back and
i hadn't it had like three days
worth of stuff and i was like
ok i'll put maybe like two more
days worth in there yeah because it's
happening i guess right yeah and you
don't know how long you have to
stay yeah so oh no but i
assume she was a shorter time that's
no that's me i mean like it
might be
a couple more days new yeah yeah
i was like oh yeah it might
be five days or something like that
we got to the hotel and riverside
and it was ah two weeks that
we were in riverside and we were
at a good hotel it was it
was fine it was good i mean
it was nice like we got to
know everyone there yeah we got our
waitress in the mornings for breakfast because
we got a free breakfast every morning
was like
take a look into that you're still
here where is this place yeah go
i now need to pay for the
real breakfast oh that's really good chip
so so ever and every day we
would go down to the the front
desk and go can we extend by
one night and they'd be like okay
explain no never explained although at one
but then in another point because our
our surrogate was also
so forty five minutes away from the
from the hospital and so then at
a certain point she goes to see
your doctor and the doctor's like looks
at her and goes and by the
way she's still three senate she she
remains at three the entire two weeks
the doctor looks at and goes like
wow the head is like really close
that's so insane um
yeah well i mean and the doctor
goes this is why people have babies
on the freeway alright see you next
time and we were like get good
glue were like she's forty five minutes
to the hospital really she is forty
five minutes ago the hospital come to
the hotel with us because though tells
by the hospital so we we then
get her and her family to go
to the hospital now
into to the hotel and so here
the hospital does it which is also
a hospital at it
um but but so they're seeing us
with this pregnant woman i think maybe
your hair is fucked up yeah thank
you and you need to go thank
you
it's like jesus christ we don't want
this it's like it's the kind of
thing like i was at a party
like a couple weeks ago and and
every picture my things are like doing
the weirdest i'm like can one person
have walking on the side that was
weeping a fixture
take your choice and say you want
to leave the party it was inside
but then we were outside and my
haircuts like but i was like one
if i was in that friend group
they would have fucking fix that yeah
and they would look at the camera
and the picturing gone oh no lawrence
harris mess up let's delete i went
we can
that's right yeah that's right you're from
yeah bad as i'm saying that too
they think i'm too chill i want
a little more yeah you want maybe
they're afraid of hair no they're not
are you sure know your little scary
know i'm intimidating enough
and we'd be doing this show because
you've frightened us into it yes you're
wearing spikes on them
anyway so two weeks two weeks later
we're just going day by day day
by day and our families know i
mean we're family's in the hotel and
i said it she calls us in
the morning literally the two week on
the two weeks after we've got to
this hotel and she says on the
fort and i feel like i feel
like it's happening tonight or it's i
feel like it's gonna happen today i
just had a restless night
um i just had a restless night
had a restless night but i feel
like chicken chicken night yeah oh okay
yeah chicken okay
sorry commercial really going to have four
gets around so we say okay let's
go let's go to the hospital great
it's happening we go to the hospital
she gets checked out and they say
you're three and a half centimeters yeah
they won't do anything until five right
there like look and size queens they
go they go look will set i
mean we
can maybe induce you in a couple
of weeks because this is her due
date this ah huh this is the
due date to the other they don't
want to induce until like maybe forty
one or forty you know forty one
and a half forty two weeks i
was forty one and a couple of
days when happy birthday
oh you're talking like came into the
world okay i had to wait a
full extra like eight days right so
there they won't endure they won't do
anything and everyone's kind of freaking out
because we're like we don't want to
be in riverside for another two weeks
but we feel like we can't go
get go now by the way i
have only had five days worth of
clothes so we have been going to
target every other day and buying clothes
that's actually kind of
and so we know every target and
riverside um a laundromat oh you will
go the same way twice like no
other merck like barrows every day to
keep my marvel sweatshirt you know you
can buy clothes a lot of the
time yeah you got to keep on
one outfit every day yeah so so
yeah the doctor leaves the room and
goes yeah well we'll fit
gear this out oh let me go
take care of the paperwork we'll be
right back where we were not allowed
in so we're outside like getting all
this information on the phone um it's
me sick the doctor comes back an
hour later checker and goes oh you're
five now
ah okay well stay and ah we'll
we'll like do it today and will
break your water if if we have
we will get you to the highway
and yeah you can have this wow
so so exciting so so you know
there's there's other stuff i'll save for
another episode but ah so yeah stuff
really exciting yeah
can't wait to hear the rest honestly
but we can be too but we
we do have to take a break
we do so we're gonna be right
back and we're gonna play three-tier i
love it fuck you fuck you
you awe oh
and we're back hippie kubrick we're here
with kuber with kubrick kubrick how are
you doing today bro mop although not
really
then what happened
oh did you say ah and what
did they say oh and then you
got above the floor
and then you ran for congress
oh no they stole the election yeah
and then you are january six
yeah huber was in there right now
he was there oh yeah kubert should
be the mascot anyway no shy because
that's really good queues everywhere times you
know when you think of some this
is the official podcast of kyoto anyways
which is sad
yep kuber q anon just to see
if anyone's come away as paul you're
a baseball fan you've you've been the
world series ended a couple of weeks
ago yes and i'm very sorry or
you're very happy oh okay before me
um when you see something that's like
via official credit bank finances of the
major league baseball why do they need
the bay
best is ah there's an official cbt
of individual teams
like it's really feels like we're proudly
and this is the official cbt of
the dodgers i'm like oh okay wow
congrats everyone happened he was telling me
that on certain days when you bring
kids to the baseball game they can
run around the field oh yeah we've
done this it's the best yeah pretend
to be a kid okay like a
big lollipop yeah you turn your head
sideways everyone arrests
you at the end nor nephew ah
nora nephew talked about last couple of
years actually spoken about it so it's
the best it's so fun it's so
cute it's a huge line around the
stadium and it gets people hot tips
and it gets people depressed like oh
i don't wanna wait how do want
to wait but they do
along with these kids are going like
twenty at a time around the basis
you know it's it's it's really a
lie and it's like many lines you've
been in yeah it's fun it's fun
to do
this ain't your grandad's line it's flying
for like a disneyland ride that has
five hundred seats yeah everyone needs it
why don't they do that on disneyland
it's like get everyone into every ride
just to it's like everyone has disneyland
every ride should be the the car
or whatever you get into yeah it's
the langs twenty thousand or whatever it
should be too
twenty people across and one thousand five
thousand people back and then every single
person comes into the park at the
same time and they go and and
the person goes okay go into this
ride yeah everyone takes that ride then
they go okay go into this raw
moss they all go over um ma
ma
okay we have to play ah three
we have to we have to actually
look a lot of people don't like
to three years and guess what we
don't either ah but we have to
do it our new producer matt makes
us by the way matt is literally
look is mallory this fist
to you it's really thrilling huh news
i leave there was a time when
somebody did that for real right and
it was actually threatening it was can
you imagine because like yeah right man
was looking at me in a dark
alley and start doing that i'd be
scared you lauper yes you can go
are you serious oh are you out
of your mind but you know
oh you're gonna mash my originated with
little kids right yeah like little rascals
it seems like i say yeah like
i knew your origin if you were
in fucking school and then use a
bully was newly mad at you you'd
be fucking across yeah it's going after
school for yeah looking at you wide-eyed
bitch i think this is the threat
of nain
gonna connect yeah this is why you
teach her to punch you with the
sand and i'm gonna i'm gonna like
put my this behind your head yeah
to create a lit this is why
lauren we need to teach our children
and i'm glad we're relating on this
show five ways yeah but we need
to teach them not to be related
not to be afraid of pain so
yeah they should experience every type of
pain yes
see that it's not that big of
a deal would be one thing related
to your topic yeah just before we
go there's this book called the art
of waiting i just wanted to recommend
that book if anyone restaurant roundup um
no it's it's about like trying out
baby but if anyone out there would
like to read that book if you
want to it's about waiting for baby
yeah yeah yeah you know yeah
and that connected with your resume and
monetisation as many of you then as
i thought that book was really great
okay the art of waiting what about
zen and the art of motorcycle maintenance
reddit when i was eighteen i read
it too and you're like oh i
remember the dude like rode around on
a motorcycle yeah that's about it and
his dad taught him how to fix
it or something
rarely yeah i remember it was supposed
to be like you're supposed to get
something out of it well i'm not
reading it but also realising that's when
i didn't know i was when i
realised i didn't know how to spell
maintenance and i really learned main teens
i remember a script i wrote that
i spelled restaurant rest and then rant
or maybe run restaurant restaurant somebody
many restaurants restaurant i hate that i
was working was nineteen or somehow in
a restaurant and someone made fun of
me for how i spelled it it
was how i learned how to spell
restaurant to this day on russell ranch
fun of is one of the best
ways to learn some yeah you're hairless
shitty hey well
i didn't dry bar yesterday so i
have come but instead it's not horrible
today but a lot of times it
does eviction what if you go bark
what it looks like shit what if
you taught your children to act like
they loved pain like the bully was
deployed like they're like a dominatrix yeah
where it's like my sob it's not
like they get sexually
ratified by it but it's awesome to
do like their fuckin their demented like
what if a bully give me another
one yeah oh yeah that love i
said it's a bully's worst nightmare teach
your child to be like a fucking
psychoactive yeah well that's because for kindergarten
for having it again blood running in
your psycho face give me your cycle
face you're a fucking monster
you're a fucking insane person no one
will fuck with you yeah that's what
you're gonna teacher yeah yeah yeah or
holly and emerald going to be friends
do you think i think so because
i think we've got a card from
holly she did how to know if
you knew the holly i think she
needed stamps but ha yeah holly santa
emerald the halloween card yeah no
wendy while if holly walked up to
you with a sealed envelope do we
have stamps like waving a rally address
and everything else yeah all that's on
the internet yeah it's true but um
she was so happy for emerald to
have her first halloween yes yeah she
was a little flower so q so
raw so cute holiday
i was a butterfly killen for her
second outing she was a harry potter
character that we had this customer moment
so oh really which cares yeah mine
with a tool skirt basically tools but
what's a tool so you know like
like bill but it's toolbelt what like
a ballerina oh is that what that's
worth like sticky u l l e
o t
g u l l e two yeah
i'm alright we have like creature yeah
one of these build a t lee
should that would be sweet if a
little re-brand yeah chicken with maynard about
that what does he did softer versions
of their existing songs that should you
know time new and cool up that
was her idea for the sloppy boys
is that day because we've been listening
to the rock a bye baby where
it's like rabbi lullaby versions of radiohead
or pr
i need to get into that she's
oh yeah they're all on spotify so
i don't know any but i listen
to whatever i want but she's she's
like the sloppy voice she put out
an album where they do hello versions
of their songs to rock a bye
baby get it rock a bye baby
yeah get it yeah love says they're
good
because instead of just like listening to
you know what's the abc song or
whatever it's songs she likes and well
that's what i really want because i'm
the abc okay this is great i'm
gonna add this to my shoe that
boys row vermont oh
alright let's play this reacher hip hip
hooray i love that so much so
good u p i e bay so
one of the best vocal ad libs
i've ever heard and then to have
so weird no what does that to
keep it in yeah yeah not be
like should i keep this look alright
the look of love i'm part of
every line
live show he's doing that yeah i
saw him live and by the way
i'm like he doesn't regret it
yeah maybe
i saw him live and he was
wearing a dinner jacket right and then
the cover with dinner the encore comes
on ladder with spaghetti he does look
of love for the encore he leaves
the stage changes into a gold le
made dinner jacket and comes out and
does look of love and does zippy
yeah i like when people do it
we want the idea of
of hip hip hurray at the end
of that song and then he's like
alright if i did that i might
as well do this escalated like oh
i just do when you're goofing around
at home yeah yeah yeah and so
good this array is so funny is
it a mistake or the editor lesbian
like sometimes you do things that are
like really funny like that but it's
like not funny at all
you because you're just alone but then
yeah then you kind of go hey
that was really weird ah i don't
think i don't think they left it
i think it was like he did
it i think he instantly was like
this let's leave this it's really it's
really making me like he's like that's
fucking hilarious don't do that for five
million i do this everything if he
did it every song
like deja kelly going another one and
then we would hate it yeah but
okay no it would be better oh
it would be better okay i was
willing to go hf either way on
this times a waste ok
moore's um the this is submitted by
rosalie m hello rosalie hi rosalie oh
she submitted a few but we're gonna
play noah's ark mythical creature edition which
is xiong chunk alright lauren's gonna play
noah wants a cubit if you can
believe it and
um breaking the glass ceiling your can
do male characters yeah her hair fur
and oh yeah no one else will
ever say okay you're the you're like
a bouncer on the ark and you're
letting animals in okay you will like
a bounce house for a second i
thought i was a bouncer mountain sing
on my arc okay it seems
to me that you live your life
seems to me on the ark
so where are the multiple layered were
the last two layers
happening at the same time yeah yeah
yeah we're the last two super genius
for the last youtube door i mean
you only have one spot syphilis and
you can only give it to one
of us and by the way paula
have to be mythical creatures yeah lot
of the same sorry mess and all
that i've never understood syllabus when tao
simplistic like siblings yeah she's doing
mike test yeah yeah because you need
to hear the say that does anyone
say that word or that was yeah
because it's like the certain like you
need to hear if this suddenly stuck
with me and i just was like
no yeah because they said it eight
million fucking for some reason that stuck
with
one of the most popular catchphrase is
to press odell and that's one of
the most popular people saying siblings yes
it does
one of be they were gonna be
in this model twenty that was that
wouldn't be she's her use for me
finish of s l that year of
that sketchy sketch i actually see other
phrases from that sketch including actually remember
what happens next i have no idea
he runs on to test the mics
i don't know what happens next then
aerosmith
it plays right okay oh that's right
i don't know your plays telling you
it was my zeal chinese gato gum
and jay was like no i don't
that's a good genie and then like
that at all no i don't show
and i've decided to make an impression
as i was talking i would do
it better if i really focused high
and no i don't want to hear
this
great access to paul
ooh
oh yes bitcoin my bitcoin yeah i've
heard the accepted impression of me it's
it's very strange the numbers i accepted
impression you know i'm be curious to
hear that yeah everybody who does it
sounds the same and i'm like i
guess that's what i said it's only
when your hello interesting thing you you
have a hard day stay
they say they seize on a specific
thing yeah yeah from your sanity to
fuckin do it yeah yeah i think
maybe what you're doing right now
yeah i don't like the friend group
i knew i meant i was starting
to understand how an impression can be
done yeah alright sometimes i think there
is no impression there and because you're
like that's just how he is and
then you're like oh if i really
wasn't impressionist i guess i'd really focus
up and take something and pull it
and extrapolate
go from there okay okay there's only
one spot we have to convince you
that we are the ones otherwise we're
gonna and i'm no and i don't
know really hardcore and you know what
i'm gonna say why don't you assign
to us what creatures we are okay
by greeting us oh okay alright
opening the ark duh
oh i don't know that i want
to go on i saw you're not
well i thought no it would be
like oh no i'll get em i
don't know it would be but you'll
get it i'll get him so wait
wait oh is the arc bouncer and
i write a noise coming can i
write down just quickly your names and
some information i see yeah see i'm
flying you are your see your flute
ah you
you are a um manatee with an
extra long penis
five legs and yeah an orwellian horn
and um your name gypsum gypsum i
see that you're an eel and you
were sort of an eel um what's
it called centaur combo yes so it's
like so accommodation of a centaur which
is a combination already of the solar
system
man oh horse's body let's write a
man's torso and an eels head that's
right okay it's a mess yeah alright
i'll get noah just shell out here
to name are we gonna i mean
i'll see you on the ark my
name's amber tamblyn tamblyn no relation to
who
anyone i'm literally just i you don't
have any weight i'm a fairy i'll
be right back i'll be right actually
i won't be back no it will
be here oh okay so you won't
see me again it's anyone's me now
and tell me okay amber tamblyn lot
of info over so i'm not gonna
let me oh can i ask you
um what what if i made it
worth your while to put in a
good word for me with how many
bitcoin six point eight oh by the
way i saw you masturbate via giving
me going i saw you match me
too oh shit let's trade bitcoin why
were we masturbating next to each other
this is inappropriate and looking at each
other oh he did it oh whoa
la routine
nah i do is what i typically
do but only have room for one
oh weird was not playing this outlaw
in the arc it's a flaw in
the idea it's not exactly a flaw
in the arc it's a little extra
annex i have i built in sort
of as a window seat that i
realized should be used by a animals
some sort
okay well we won't be giving up
your window scene for one of you's
you to continue population unless we blend
you with someone else or we will
have this extra long penis i do
see that yeah so i'll be able
to repopulate any kind of say you're
a manager you just get the length
you think that means that you can
mate with anything and no i think
that people will want
meet with me because they'll take a
look at that and be like oh
wow that looks like
that's what i'm hoping to see you
wanna fuck a man a person sure
if you're into it well no we
don't seal the deal right now can't
get into this again but here's a
wife noah i do know what
she's ah she's cleaning right now there's
always a lot of shit over this
she's cleaning yeah so typical gender stereotypes
yeah ah the typical gender stereotype is
that i have um lots of animals
that i propagate together on my boat
and my wife cleans the shit that
they x screen i mean you you
built the ark ceo orchestra
well that's what that's what i like
to say but when we get in
bed at the end of the day
it's only cool because i give her
the old what have you and well
if if you'd like me to give
her this well okay that's i'll take
that in consideration oh you're thinking it's
my lw colleague here ah but if
you're
looking to blend take a look at
me i'm three things okay so i'm
looking at the top and i feel
like you got the worst one on
top it is a yale's head here's
what i like about it and i'll
tell you what okay it's the latest
of all the possible heads that i
could have had okay so i'm not
i'm not carrying a lot of weight
but that's not even proportional to your
body but no it's like
like a gigantic regular yield yeah on
top of a human type of human
neck yeah and it's like tapered aha
and then you can see i'm ripped
to shit like you have a great
tour thank you thank you and i
think my bitcoin threatened her would be
oh yeah because i will talk about
what i saw when i forgot
yeah and i also have a beautiful
horse body i love that about yeah
yeah okay yeah real fast yes i
think it's about what i can make
out of you yes i think it's
about how the future of the animals
sort of survive and change but what
i want to know is what do
you bring to the table talent wise
because we do wish y'all show once
a week on the wall i mean
it's forty
right i mean so it's going to
get boring unless you have to see
if you have the heart to prepare
your talent and so will do for
talent shows for ten years give or
take and you have you'll have yeah
a few days repair would your town
cho a few days repaired to town
show yeah and we're here eleven weeks
is that right yeah yeah look what
do you know you've kind of been
annoying me
cause i this is part of my
talent allows me this is ceo on
your channel and i'll me to stamp
it out on the floorboards here okay
so you do a little bit of
a wow that's me counting i love
how many was out for you know
what's amazing about that theory you have
hands and you couldn't count on your
fingers but yet you chose to sit
that's exactly right i
i can't i don't really use my
fingers because my head is so tiny
up there i can't really see oil
and you have skies and i do
have size so it's hard for me
to see what i'm counting to look
um i gotta say this eel his
head is so small he sleeps twenty
three hours of the day because his
brain is so small he can't even
stay awake only
my head sleeps but the rest of
me is walking around like you are
man of like a headless horseman situation
yeah like enigma gone wrong kind of
thing headless horse man right i'm a
whatever i've never realised he's a good
heavy what about the headless horsewoman well
i mean he's a horse he's when
do we finally get one but i'd
love to hear about that you know
can you make a horsewoman
and i bet i could can you
make a woman horse while we recycle
yeah again with via oh here's a
here's a question for you this is
a little bit of a test and
okay if i want to make a
horse i mean what would you have
sex with
so you want to essentially say no
horse i do want to send our
lady right okay is that what you
said you have any horse women you
don't but i would need ahead of
me the question is that how the
question is mine
i would i know i would have
sex with the horse first and then
their daughter our daughter than it would
would have sex with a man okay
this is like so it's a few
years yeah when he says it's a
couple of generations so i would say
here's how i would doing i'm already
half person half horse right or third
per
person third works well even if you
are honest and then thank you to
those accompaniment i you know what i
wish you were my friend group
i know you talked to me i
like you i really i don't want
to be on this boat without you
i don't either could we get a
trenchcoat i think you're ugly
i don't know that tours here's a
trenchcoat snowshoe i make a horseshoe here's
how we make a horseman i'm already
i got i got human i got
horse i put a bag over my
head finally i tie it real tight
none of that gets in there
so far up there like your amp
you'd like to see what lauding well
i mean that's just for me but
it also prevents any eel from getting
in there use the smallest part that's
faster than your plan i'm just worried
you're gonna have like a now four
of like if he has sex with
anything else that's not a horse man
or an eel then suddenly you have
a thing with
for different things inside of it this
is just like
then then you have to build an
another arch dick and five arms or
five legs yeah which is kind of
disgusting you kinda look like one of
those like one of sid's toys from
toy story yeah i don't know what
that is just yeah even mush together
and a really nasty way i can
be honest i didn't know either but
i just acted like i did i
feel you i known that mean look
i'm all
manatee i'm all manatee with legs okay
and so you're i'm a pure blood
shed the slippers and leg slaps actually
make it so you're not just so
you know what they're not human legs
they're managing right they're not right they
looked low who's the racist now noah
i don't think that you lost bow
race
i don't think you belong on this
boat noah am i being kicked out
of my own your asian cancelled from
this art and and ah this year
some gypsum and and flu are going
to be driving this boat get off
they are no yuk no get off
your ah mr noah get off this
are now you're taking
both my spots so when he's going
to lay with my wife every night
yeah one of us both of us
baby the yeah ah what a great
three-tier what a great reacher thank you
so much to rosalie hall one guys
we have to go yeah we really
do this was a fun episode on
app going back to um follow us
on social me
media were at threesome usa on both
instagram and twitter usa gmail dot com
if you'd like to write to us
or three cheers send us three cheers
or you can call us at ah
haha ooh
i think and then if you wanna
hear ad-free episodes of this you can
hear him on stitcher premium and also
cvb world dot com and where real
reread real realizing that we released episodes
were doing this on and by the
way let's workshop a name here because
we're doing it on tuesdays we're releasing
threes on tuesday
three's these doozies threes on the twos
threes on the twos so three visions
three visit three visiting three ghosts christmas
carol
three ghost christmas yeah okay
but we're re-releasing all of our old
episodes once a week on tuesdays the
threes on the twos um like three
visits three visits three visiting yeah three
visiting three businesses on the twos twos
on the threes twos threes threes on
the jews okay this all makes sense
alright um you and if you want
episode
dhs has to stitcher premium and cvb
world dot com we love you we
love you thanks for listening thanks bye
uh