florida
what
fire
oh you're tired son was yelling finally
should help if i did i hear
we're in a movie theater people hate
that we do this by the way
in a movie theater yes while a
movies guy has anyone ever heard the
movie i always wonder that no we
keep his picks can you hear the
movie will check it out we've taken
on post but if any pipit can
hear the movie
a that's playing in the background if
anyone can identify the movie yes that's
playing and if you can hear who's
yelling at us to be quiet you'll
let us know because tell them to
shut the fuck up yeah call them
and tell them commemorate their voice then
text them at least well lease to
leave chicago at least yeah verily an
urgent now at the
very missed a letter by mail snail
snail snails snails man remember the first
time you ever ate snails yeah i
think there's any postal worker whose last
name is snail yeah probably i hope
so i'd be awesome i'd be so
awesome to be like fred snail i
delivered the mail
yes i've heard it all before yeah
yeah told me my ways like i'm
so lonely i forgot everything you said
why would you ever work at the
post office sometimes i think sometimes i
think it could be up a mail
carrier yeah sometimes i think he's gonna
be one of those annoying ladies at
the counter i could definitely be like
really mean at the counter um no
i i think i think working at
the post office would be one thing
that might be my bahamut what i
sometimes do think about being a mill
carrier yeah because well there's something going
away nice about it it's yeah because
you're like oh okay back to an
earlier time love dog but i do
think about the dog though like having
a bag of treats you give the
dog yeah shut the fuck up doesn't
it harken back to an earlier time
it harkens back to an earlier time
at what point does it go away
um god i don't know male yeah
not anytime soon
next i think by june you think
by june fred snell was out of
a job that's stressful you also i
would say mass for bread snail carriers
great calves yeah so well but i'm
already cherishing these bay lops yeah i'm
we're welcomed
oh my god what am i lift
drivers in portland was like oh yeah
well the lift ceo stepping down on
monday so this job is gonna change
a lot i'm like is this all
any of this true it didn't seem
true at all de lucio stepping down
so everything is going to be different
yeah i'll tell him to shut the
early round up and not talk to
you anymore what did you want to
say about your new calf
i've got a new care i got
a nude kef um i'm i'm i'm
on wiki fee today because i'm not
wearing socks oh my are you wiki
i'm on i don't know eat today
because i'm not wearing
i'm gonna post pictures your fee in
my stories oh um wait a second
we were talking about things and it
made me think of a thing to
talk about but okay let's go back
i can't think of the we are
not on there fred snail sorry to
everyone halves lift that's what we talked
about ft we now lauren and i
did
discuss this with ah bryan safi and
armory oh yeah on their podcast well
yeah we always guys about uber about
uber uber rating yeah and mine is
like numerous personal always on brian and
arden's podcast you know autographs please which
is a really hilarious podcast i highly
really mean um they
talked to the guys at the top
solid for your fam they talked to
the guest the top and then they
do improv with the guest and it's
always like a bad date and the
listener suggest bad dates lines things that
we say i actually heard an urbana
bad date which is so crazy some
of the things that are said are
so funny yeah and it's great but
um you guys were taught i was
dying because you guys were talking about
uber readings and everyone's was lower than
they expect
how do you mean how do you
see them i've never go to swimmer
when you already do i think we
should reveal it now so yeah okay
i went to mine and then i
had to send my so we were
all three of us were under five
point o which is five and the
best yeah yeah stars how do you
okay i'm on and then my and
click account in the bottom right oh
mine is five so
cars and so i had to brag
because i was a perfect fi i
was so jealous i ninety four point
nine three what do you do whoa
four point nine is bad not really
it's great minds four point eight five
i just wonder what the whoa i
tip these guys every time i do
the five every time a lot of
why whys i never don't give five
staffer one
the thing that happened to me that
i think probably bring me down as
is i i got over to the
hollywood bowl last year and the guy
got really mad because there was so
much traffic and he started taking it
out on me and he's like i'm
gonna get off the freeway i'm gonna
go the other way on the freeway
ago it's just as busy the other
way it's just it's just gonna waste
time and he started getting very mad
at me
you might have given you a four
stars at that point and then you're
done your average yeah but i mean
he's i don't i don't i've never
had i can't remember having an incident
like maybe forty third street i don't
know what isn't yes it and what
that's the song who is miracle miracle
on thirty fourth street not in fifty
seventh streets are a bruce springsteen oh
brew
springsteen it's incident on fifty seventh street
that was like was that his eight
thousand song he wrote it so specific
and random sounding what's your little bit
of it's specific yet vague into the
ground as long as i have things
start to happen sometimes you have incidents
on fifty seventh street
a fool out in the street and
everybody left to be
ah li li
a juicy details part or z li
li li li either oh he has
a leper time that places him sometime
to earn yeah hey wonder speed to
code only so only alive this little
light trucks because you know because he
brings them around um on tour because
it's kind of like a he dances
so
you know go with me today who
is
i think you know the leper
bring about dance leper contents is okay
is your ubereats rating the same as
your regular obering rate on a ten
point rating on uber eats i know
touching food will be funny this guy's
a real pig
she ordered too much i'm doing garbage
he asked away himself was this guy
don't want to pay by the pound
data e lead a lady di di
di di now paul and lauren are
both are on their phones and i'm
left holding the bag
what do you guys text each yeah
know it's like you're talking about you
how handsome you are oh my gosh
thank you said oh halfway house here
than i expected that's true we weren't
warned me i was handsome oh wait
you're saying how handsome i am went
out to buy
one-star you got pinged because you made
us go into traffic awe thing they
will come on man what am i
what the fuck did i do i
don't know i know you're just a
regular guy trying to hang out in
someone's call it makes me so mad
i'm sorry yeah i'm really sorry no
because it doesn't even look at it
you just do do well because they
see it when you get a draw
driver it shows you their stars and
so i assume they see you don't
look at them yeah i think they
do and then i've had people cancel
on me but i assume it's because
i'm too far away or something i've
had that too i don't think it's
because you're rating if you have like
a two what if it was it
would be well yeah yeah i thought
it would be forty three forget it
what did they do last time probably
farted i value myself up
ah
anyway guys if you're an uber driver
give me my five fucking stars yeah
if you're listening right now and i
hope that you are present well otherwise
why are we doing this yeah if
you're not listening right now damn kinda
don't i don't even bother listening to
it later if you're not listening right
now if you're listening now you might
as well not listen at all yeah
yeah
right i think so yeah i kinda
got an uber reese you can say
fight and we fought so hard in
it it was
you did that on purpose yeah no
we got in this uber and the
driver was listening to a podcast which
typically doesn't really happen you don't typically
get a rare yeah your podcast remember
how plenty uber drivers were when it
first came out and it was always
like you want some men's do you
want to charge your phone yeah you
want to listen to your own music
still get now it's like getting the
fucking car
i'll get this do you really yeah
they say get in the fucking car
any now but i'm like i said
i'm got in the fucking car that's
why they oh yeah his podcast was
like it was almost like an npr
type thing and maybe there's just npr
i don't know but it was like
and they didn't know it earlier they
didn't know if there were ghosts in
there but they didn't see one again
and they never saw goes together like
it was like just kind of guy
would love for you to do a
show just like that where it was
only meant to be listened to in
the middle of it yeah where there's
no context it's like a fall asleep
podcasts yeah yeah i one time we
heard a we got into an uber
and the guy was listening to conservative
radio that feels like you're trying to
signet you're trying to signal the new
yeah exactly message regime and then you're
arguing with him and gave you the
bad rating yeah see i said you're
you're a mindless drone
just listening to with the m s
m tells you
oh lauren oh what are we gonna
go
take a trip together wow where to
yeah we're we do a kitty trip
what's that where all the kids come
sure yeah would you be okay you'd
have to dress as a kid well
we know it's great for you is
like a big lolly i just bring
a big guy i think the great
thing for pelvic you could do whatever
you want yeah and then we couldn't
so i just walk in and out
as i play yeah it would be
kind of like just stuck in this
house wherever we could go to santa
barbara whoa zach too far but we'll
know to hawaii i like stayed in
the house all day no hawaii was
great that play that was so relaxing
several guys let's go there we should
i would love to be on a
trip with a little kid totally
yeah i can't go to y with
you could i could be that young
yeah you'd be probably easier now it
is easier because she'd can't get up
and walk she's just so dumb blog
no fish dump lod um no but
i traveled all blogs like forty nine
ah the flights not you know that
part's not great but you can you
get there and then you get there
anyway yeah yeah yeah i'm never gonna
go anywhere again okay that's your problem
is wrong with you i don't know
can't lay awake till eight thirty pm
your life's over and over thing it's
not about me and it's just be
glad you're true and that's really you
should enjoy yeah and freshly joy it
isn't that night frankly wasn't really that
much about you to begin now
i think it's like seventy about someone
else it's a dream to not be
noticed just simply not the focus for
a little bit let me just know
when looking at yeah you can do
whatever you want it's like a enough
paparazzi yeah no it's like a paparazzi
when the paparazzi comes when i'm with
my family and i'm like no no
don't take pictures i take pictures of
her yeah bus the puppet the bus
take pictures
i'm in the paper paparazzi a paparazzi
plea the big pictures gallery on da
da da i'm gonna go back to
italy public so you wanna go to
italy i've been i'd like to do
i went right before the baby was
born it was so fun our sideshow
picture the other day it was so
fun is that your baby moon
nw it wasn't technically was i mean
i would like you to have a
baby moon we did we went to
palm springs or i guess like i
don't know that it was exactly palm
springs but something over there and just
had a air bnb with like a
pool and a hot tub and it
was two bits um yeah it was
just fun and you brought our
cat or dog and made it a
whole thing and because we were bad
cat yeah yeah we do they chase
each other all the time for some
reason well um scott what no they
don't don't okay i don't know my
cats since but just i know but
those kind of her last hurrah
um they did from time to time
but not really it was like the
more kind of stuck to their own
because dogs chase cats frey how to
try to caddy chase turns bird chase
worm lose nothing and the amount of
warm rooms i'm doing well i you
know what i would have a pet
if it weren't for the worms the
way
firm you should just skip it skip
the whole deal get a pet worm
because they're hilarious birds gonna chase it
then i've stick here the bird
you're right remember the time that i
swallowed a fly and then it turned
into a whole thing i don't know
why you think oh wow song or
whatever that is what does it what
is that why do people so but
i always hated that growing up why
did people thinks it's not even a
rhyme what want the same song who
swallowed a fly i don't know why
i guess he'll die or something it
was like i heard it
perhaps hilton maybe this pair yeah i
remember pulling it out of my ass
right that's how you can tell if
you're an optimist or pessimist so say
it again ah the way and don't
sing it who swallowed a fly don't
i don't know why she's say it
there was an old woman i don't
know why she swallowed up by perhaps
she'll die she'll die what a fuck
what are we talking about why is
that
song we are talking about let's swallow
a spider what right like could go
to get a job that jiggle didn't
really good and squiggly inside her nasty
she's one of the spending cuts sneaky
lie hey i was wriggling inside nasty
i was jiggling that's yeah you know
my story where i drank out of
autumn holiday live spider got my buddy
yeah that's yeah sky yeah i think
about it a lot yeah i think
about it it will have i told
you yes yes and i feel like
if i just adore and i've said
who it was i won't say again
just because i it's not my story
but it was really funny my old
improv team we were like standing around
and one of our key
kitchens this was like ten years ago
and um someone said they could eat
a clementine whole without taking the pillow
i told you this i'm sure yeah
yeah and then he just flopped in
his mouth and we're like oh we're
good and then he went he's gonna
have another one and he opened it
was black inside see the one he
ate probably was too yeah if you're
all cedric share that
that tweet or instagram that was like
chair tweet instagram wow even how somebody
yes one of those little oranges they
would make you have one too no
i didn't share that but that's funny
i love specific shitless that's true but
i never think about yeah i wish
someone would do you religion yeah i'm
working i'll bring to next time can
i top three will bring tuna offering
me to their son kenny grade to
open up some big cans of tuna
right before we saw open up the
big catch a tuna
huh i love big cans of tuna
i love outta you know what i
love are no big can of tuna
oh just ought to be slimy pushed
down on that lid little earl come
up to cancer canto nerl i don't
know that term it's a way that
some people pronounce oil oh got it
yes i am a reading holly a
lot of
old golden books from when i was
a cancer so have you been doing
that too yeah and i was failing
but i was reading one today that
i haven't seen that was very cute
it's called grandma and grandpa smith and
it's about the city kids to go
to visit their grandparents in the country
but then they they become so specific
and maybe this
it isn't specific and maybe you'll say
this is a very common baseball related
family to see but the thing that
was that all relieved i was suddenly
very interesting i like it now i
was reading it and i was going
what
back in the back
hey
don't no no no no no no
no
no no no
hey jude
so it was this part where the
grandma goes in the attic and she's
like screaming
she's screaming leading summarize her life and
she said she's gone bad poltergeist up
here um
she's like oh look here's your dad's
old baseball glove you should play it
so you used oil and every day
now it's so stiff and then she
and then later it's like and then
sam oil but the sam put a
lot of neets foot oil on the
glove and got all loose glitchy gushy
or whatever so she kind of was
like that's what you want neets you
why
wanna pull your hand into a baseball
glove and feel like a pussy yeah
okay you know what but i was
reading it going i'm reading out loud
for the first time you know i
haven't read a line scan that he
put neets foot oil on it and
it became so like what i've never
thought my okay i mean i know
you oil your glove and everything it's
funny from the eighties and i ran
one
yeah it's mine from when i was
a kid why read a book needs
foot oil this is still in business
shutting in late but they put ah
they put a dash in it but
like foot dash oil needs foot oil
football isn't yellow oil rendered and purified
from the shin bones and feet of
cattle oh neat is the oil's museum
co in the oil's name come from
an old english word for cattle needs
foot oil huh where's the hyphen they
put needs dash foot oil but it's
actually you know dashing foot
separate word oil yeah nice foot oh
okay guys each foot and he's only
you were thinking it was foot oil
i was thinking it was some very
specific type of thing i didn't think
it was a nice foot i didn't
oil i didn't know i didn't have
any thoughts like that i thought it
was a tom you had no thoughts
no none like yeah none like that
i'm like yeah just a blank my
yeah it wasn't blink it just wasn't
like what you're thinking when i read
nice foil i thought it's literally some
old thing that i just don't know
what it is nice switzer extinct yeah
we probably wouldn't use that today we
oil with avocado oil so i can't
buy a house the ride well my
santa all my information has to live
in a studio that's right
why because we can't stop eating avocado
millennia ah i read a book when
i was young i think it was
definitely oh my god you're bragging about
this book again yeah it was ah
that it was ab something the bible
but it was we'd get that abcs
it was a b i b l
e it was called a a bible
um but it was amicable it was
yeah it was also my watch i
just got my stand goal i've been
sitting here for fucked up through like
you're doing this three year usually laying
down so they think
use sitting up as you standing yeah
um that's grim
yes i read this book and maybe
a listener can identify because i know
neither of you yeah wow but that
was really intense i'm sorry it was
about a it was about okay so
he hit his knee on the table
noise oh well they don't know that
because they didn't see but i know
it
i said yeah no choice
it's really israel so it was it
was it's like about a twelve year
old baby or a ten year old
who was on a baseball team and
the old baby on a baseball team
and a twelve year old baby he's
just been a baby for twelve years
he won't stop being a baby for
giving them baseballs we're letting them have
hobbies
i think it doesn't have a baseball
glove or something oh then one of
his teammates who just got a brand
new beautiful glove and signed it with
a marker um left it somewhere and
then he rimini signed it this is
a book which was a marquee name
oak yeah this is a book you're
reading this book who do i make
this out to o
me is this a ten page with
reviews resignation i mean
um so he he steals this he
steals this glow thievery he didn't do
that because the san and then in
order to disguise the fact that this
other kid put his name on in
kidding me he puts he does like
a pattern in marker of
like rectangle over the name and then
circle and then rectangle circle rectangle circle
alone and and then he takes it
to practice the next day and he's
like oh i got a new glove
and everyone sees right through it is
like yeah obviously miss but our friend
is maybe this one is love and
you're not telling me you just did
the math
walker you know of this pattern over
it and he was just guilty about
it and guilty but i forget how
it ends this is a big shoot
that's like what is this book i
think yeah it was not you pretending
you got a new glove
not you again it's getting retire to
giving me liar vibes
we got to take a break
we're ah speaking of childhood books okay
tell me about either a kid or
a book welling it it's kind of
about both oh this is not a
ladder yeah no this is right yeah
um this was this
it was a two book series that
told the same story series wins two
books it's a book and it's sequel
no it wasn't a sql dumb ass
because because we don't yes i because
it was the same story told from
two different points of view wow it's
russia ah fair it was a rochambeau
minus one and did you guys watch
the affair we did is i loved
it i was really interesting the last
episode is
fucking bonkers oh wearing houses to oh
my god remember when he's an old
man makeup and he does the wedding
dance the the the flashmob wedding dance
that he choreographed on her grave wait
he was laughed a flashmob wedding you
just have this operate no no when
young while
only apple sings the water boys but
one life that was my used to
be like which she did a great
doing the full opening of that she
did a great the affair we talked
about something yeah we are because she
she'll confuse oh because she's things you'll
see things the opening yes dream and
then you know it's really fun to
act out and within them everyone's watching
the show yeah in the ma
i would try to match it exactly
when we watch the show listen if
you are going to watch the affair
at some point this is very spoiler
heavy but see a skip ahead one
minute so in the present day at
his daughter's wedding marina he's not allowed
he's not allowed or whatever but he
he decides to choreograph this flash ma
diet cd
isn't real it is really decisive choreograph
of flash mob dance to the water
boys version and then in the future
when the world is so covered in
whiter today not watch this when the
in the future when the world is
covered in water he finally goes to
his wife's grave or something just kinda
then by
himself he's in terrible old lady's makeup
yeah and he does he does about
the same show lord i honestly don't
know i think a flashmob season he
does the flash mob dance on her
grave yes literally insane and that's the
end of the it's enough i the
affair because i think they they they
find out who killed her i liked
i didn't realize she was murdered i
i'm sorry what is more attuned he
gets murdered i know right no i
never remember anything this sounds so insane
pacing yeah she was she was murdered
at the end because you don't wanna
be on the show yeah which i
think is honestly like if you're gonna
if you're gonna say hey i don't
want to be on the show anymore
more you you the worst thing should
happen to your character yeah no flashbacks
ease i'm gone i think i watched
them all i'll revisit that that show
i haven't experienced that show which is
one of those things where it's not
the show's fault because i expected i
thought it was gonna be something different
than it was which is i liked
the idea of jews
story being told from two absolutely mind
when it first happens in the first
episode but this it was your hands
went black and there's been a murder
or whatever and they're they're being questioned
by the cops like what the fuck
is this oh i loved it murder
is i love it it's why no
white lotus it's so popular is because
i think he wrote it and they
were like
like put murder because people will want
i want to see what's going to
happen yeah but i don't care yeah
you don't like murders only murders in
the building ah well i went away
for that moment oh that's been around
the hey that's not no it's not
the phrase that pays it is very
close to them it's their phrase that
pays
it's there face to face yes if
you watch only murders and building yes
so they said it in the first
episode and they pay a million dollars
yes everyone whoever hears it that's why
they're very careful not to say yeah
but they say it they see it
a lot they say and that episode
still up yeah and you can use
one goal just watches beijing's you want
and gives you a million dollars every
time you hear
it yeah um wait you just hear
it and it's suddenly a check so
the there was there was two books
one was ah the bully of barcomb
street i read that and the other
was a dog on markham street so
the dog was being bullied the dog
was the
dog's perspective the first book is this
kid gets a dog and it's to
this great story but he also has
a bully that's bullying him oh at
school and everything the second book doesn't
kill him he murders him and then
the cops are questioning him knows your
hyung yeah nah huh
nah oh right she released as a
single
imo i think it's it's fifteen seconds
and she was ahead of her time
now feels way longer
that's a long that's pretty short but
it feels longer how long does it
feel to you it feels like it's
four and a half minutes no that's
way too my brain's messed up yeah
yeah yeah somebody took a chunk out
of it oh yeah oh this guy
but here's the take a bite i
read bite i take a binary right
eyebrow
the brain by the dog who commits
crimes um so the first book this
this nice kid he gets the dog
blah blah blah he's named bully are
you supposed to read them in this
order i think so it makes more
sense if you do because in the
second book when it's revealed oh my
god is from the bullies point of
view and guess what his home life
sucks and that's kind of
only way yes because bullies but are
bullied and that's why they're bullies hurt
people hurt people hurt people over early
scared people scare people have yeah tall
people tall people yeah your people hear
people yeah
it's all part of people people
i pay paid paper o six bags
full like alright can you fit bringing
your mouth give it to me or
you are the one coop be it
if i point at you and you
say i am me then i will
stay you aw
or it's sick bullshit and people die
fake outs oh my god reality tv
before american idol that was original like
rights equals reality shows yeah what did
he do those fake out he'd be
like it was checkout and the person
eliminated will be revealed after the break
oh yeah like that kind of she
loves yeah dealing like when people go
no and no to kelly
and is no more wef on it
ryan it's now going to be kelly
and mark her husband mcl yeah i
feel like this was her long her
long com to get paid twice for
one shit it's like fucking shit what
should be the third time would hillary
lot to do she morning show together
our would be fucking it's gotta say
start it starts at eight what can
you fake about today phil yeah
starts at eight fifteen yeah fifty eight
thirty it has to kind of be
on the johnny carson style
i'll do it at eight thirty
for how long fifteen years over for
weight it's it's it's what apes are
never showed it's fifteen years and years
yeah the the episodes are two hours
yeah no i don't know eight thirty
ten thirty many two hours better know
they're only one hour jesus what some
of those good morning shows today's show
yeah yeah yeah five-hour i'll tell you
i'll do eight thirty a m for
twenty minutes right
with chua two days a week what
do we do with the remaining ten
minutes and is it on youtube in
the half hour play youtube know it's
on youtube know play youtube the remaining
ten i think you guys should be
on youtube you should make the show
from home and it should be uploaded
tuesdays and thursdays and it's twenty minutes
we've been i don't think anyone would
would give a shit about listening i
remind you talk about
current events that happened on monday and
wednesday yeah on tuesday and thursday last
the previous monday wednesday okay yeah we
do it a week before yeah it's
old news but i don't know i
just like would you just morning like
paul you and janie do your show
together it's true which i really enjoy
i don't know if we could do
it in the morning morning as a
whole because you guys are yeah you
have to be
really really clean yeah yeah
mornings for sex yeah well after news
or physics nighttime podcast i do but
i guess nighttimes for podcast watch tv
yeah um i remember watching doctor who
doctor where on p b s dr
whitewood dr ho you have there what
dr dr m the what doctor get
the hamlet lay way dr witt
who what where when why because the
episodes were sometimes less than a half
hour they were that short back then
yeah yeah yeah why they're under a
half hour in and out but the
local pd station they'd like throw a
music video on there at the end
oh yeah that's great
i'd be pretty cool to see its
famous band a local band it would
be famous pants and the first one
how famous was the who eminence front
ah doctor grace of who was there
ever a doctor who episode called eminence
front yeah
i was i forgot they did it
right this eminence front means yeah but
oh well that is about all
i know that well but i don't
know why you're asking dear okay i
guess you're right i guess it's just
a push csea put on and the
theme song is eminence front yes eminence
front yes i put on
and it's a love crime who is
all about con it's all about like
scabies that songs by the who yeah
i'm in front yeah i thought it
was by an i'm epcot totally wrong
here's what i thought first of all
you already are totally wrong just that
let's hear that he's been re-established what
i'm gonna say makes no sense i'm
gonna try to figure
out why i thought this later i
thought it was wham part parliament funkadelic
it does sound like it could be
i'm a little bit frumpy it is
oh you're right i'm not i'm not
completely insane no no i'm just wrong
yeah yeah i'm stupid
like people come to my defense i'm
right
we want here for you if we
say the phrase the page or if
you'd like to come lauren's defense if
she's ever right she was right about
that bourne identity yeah that's right i
or j was apologies from both paul
and i yeah erato know there's no
evidence of my thing being right at
all
there's no version of the of any
world where that's true make my but
ideally a great pedal world oh yeah
would be cool where like things that
you think are just true yeah i
would like to leave the door orange
sliding door and riding don't know when
those sliding doors photostock shit the way
sliding goal surely obama don't do irl
where i thought i was you're not
selling
way
well the idea was we were all
talking at the deputy yeah well i
didn't have anything over here we want
to hear it though you'll stop talking
that's lawrence's let me tell you yeah
when no sliding doors sh ty knew
that that path was not for me
ah fuck yeah fuck yeah fuck it
why do you think she ever said
fuck okay okay okay i'm sure he
did can i tell you a petty
showbusiness story finding love to yeah um
years ago a handful years ago did
the london podcast festival love and i
did too
to show that i didn't show with
super ego and i did a show
with um spawn toyko with me and
jenna varney and um tony newsome eugene
cannot make it and the first night
super ego show was a lot of
fun we got a standing ovation wow
like for the people
great generous for the people listening by
the way who don't know a standing
ovation is whoa how would you describe
it well it's like you know innovation
yeah yeah i'm sure we're dummied by
usually done around for the listener will
learn a lot i'm trying i'm trying
i'm trying okay at the end of
the show it's typical to give innovation
yeah and everyone does that that's usually
with like palms slapping together yeah sometimes
yeah sometimes the the the where you
put the fingerprints on the finger yeah
i mean lamp invented your own two
hands you don't typically see other people
no no it's always your own hands
yeah slap them together so basically it's
the sound of two hands clapping yeah
it's an ovation yeah it's an ovation
sometimes if people really like
put on it
to describe it so you get a
clear picture what it is it's i
mean you wouldn't be doing it if
the show wasn't over and there weren't
people no no no have you ever
been alone in a room and you
start doing because guy shuts you have
i have been alone in a room
and just start clapping because i think
that i had a great but that's
sort of myself but that's not an
ovation because an ovation is always at
the end of something because
they have the same root ove over
ovation ah so that's why it's very
rude and just bad luck in the
theater to clap before oh clap that's
another word for it clap can't do
that before the end of the show
even if you really like although isn't
every second the end of something it's
the end of that second so you
can clap it yeah but it has
to be
the specific thing is over ok in
the second if you're standing if you're
getting a standing ovation can you talk
about more like what that might look
this is this is exact for the
layman for the latest just cover the
route give us an idea of what
that might look like if we were
to be in a room where one
must happen yes if you do have
to you this happy ground job you
might get really stressed
out if you didn't know what this
was my rights well this has happened
to me a handful of times maybe
two three four five okay and i
was frightened to death oh much like
the barn you were in the audience
or you were on stage i know
never on stage oh it's happened know
no awesome the audience actually the bargain
books i'll give you both perspectives i'll
give you the performance perspective signs
the audience okay so because you've seen
it you've seen it both ways now
yes very very there's very fun experiences
on both sides so from the audience
perspective what we're seeing is the thing
that you love you're seeing this performance
is over you're saying i enjoyed this
so much i just say i need
to go home when i walk out
of the room now
no if you enjoyed something very much
yeah oh scott no it's over i
need to go home scott honey no
i need to go home now see
you get really scared and you kind
of cry beg you o house
yeah someone take me home that's not
everybody's experience that's experiences photo gifts a
week yeah so scared during the interest
of the audience oh the audiences if
they're applauding they're giving the ovation yeah
and then they're saying i want them
to really notice that i'm doing this
and so if i slay me up
they will see how much i enjoyed
it
so all it takes is one person
to stand up than everyone else doesn't
want that person feel self-conscious so whether
they liked it or not they have
to stand absolutely i mean there's plenty
of times where you're involved in one
of those that you think yes i
wasn't really gonna stand i know happy
to clap for power i thought it
was good for how good it was
yeah you're standing ovation was everyone was
getting up to leave and then just
felt so good to the performers they're
like yeah we did it and then
everyone's like oh but actually we're leaving
yeah but people were like standing up
as they clapped like ok bye and
then everyone hopefully they actually heading for
the yeah yeah okay and and the
performers like this feel feels great yeah
well they were just gathering let's try
to get one of these every night
that feels very dismissive to be if
you were
clap at standard walker oh that would
hurt yeah that would hurt now you
see it happened people wanna get to
their car for you feel pointed why
don't i think basketball players are really
hurt and people leave before they even
shoot the link sasha the last because
they're like you have just the last
basket is always the best one you
have to stay to see what happens
like you kind of have to know
how close we got to losing and
yeah
yeah why don't why when you go
see a play and you really love
a why can't you like everyone claps
why can't you just go on stage
and shake everyone's hand yeah why can't
you come you can't like you people
do i can't you give him a
hug yeah people just don't do it
yeah it's an you are being nice
these are this is this one tricks
like this theater performers
don't want to watch or instagram this
is like hey yeah you're tiktok your
secret menu it in and out oh
my god yeah can i just say
i'm not and i know you actually
had a point you are getting to
not a point but i was gonna
say more things okay i was thinking
i ah during this girl's trip we
can i was just on yeah tiktok
came up a lot people like i
saw on tiktok day-to-day contacts i went
oh i really feel like i need
to get on
tick tiktok because i feel like i'm
missing out from like things they were
learning that were actually interesting like i
found it interesting exact and i was
like schwinn tiktok and then i'm like
last night and people were like looking
at how much screen time to head
on tiktok then they all said don't
do it
tick tock specifically because it's so authentic
down i find now i think since
i quit twitter and i'm just on
instagram that the more i scroll the
the sooner it feels gross to me
right the soon like it happens so
much faster than it used to and
even people like i don't follow a
ton of people
so it's mostly people that i know
right who are i know in real
life and it's just like what am
i i start i always have the
feeling what am i doing i know
when i have that feeling so often
i've talked about it so many times
everyone's like just fucking stop doing it
then but i'm like i it's it
is addictive and great advice i know
people have done assuming they're saying that
of course they are um but
you know i'm like you will you
will see yourself go i'm wasting my
time but then sometimes i just go
what else my doing i guess i
would like to read more books by
the way doing horribly on my channel
or if i'm being totally honest i'm
on my sixth book oh no is
april seventeenth or something and i have
to read eighteen more books
before jan for january can they be
short yeah i have to so at
the house german half halfway are you
killing the books you read holly yeah
laura and i've only read six
you get two pages in and like
so bored so from the performer's perspective
yeah it seems like oh my god
they're they're mad and they're gonna come
there strangle me yeah and then you
see that they're still clapping and you
think okay this is great i like
this so here's what happened to you
so we got the standing ovation and
for super ego which i thought
it was look i love playing with
those guys i think we're funny but
this this show didn't deserve a standing
ovation fine it was no different than
any of our other shows right which
never got standing ovations sure you're like
why but you're gonna say it's almost
free it's almost like hey thanks for
getting there yeah putting the effort exact
yeah so the next night doing the
show with ah
ah with tony and janet and we
had a great guest we had a
guest drop out and then we had
a last-minute replacement in starling time who
was one of my favorite interviews of
that of all the spontaneous nations looks
like a really interesting very candid interview
about her family and then we did
a sliding doors like improv fan
and through the hole it was i
know the whole thing oh we're playing
multiple characters and keeping the story going
multiple cap and i was like keeping
the stall we're gonna get we're gonna
get standing wow now you're making on
it and then we didn't yeah and
i was die was didn't get booze
or was it just no normal like
that it was just normal plus people
like nah man like good show
thought that was special it was my
hubris i felt special and i thought
will surely these people recognize especially yeah
in the did not feel the same
way as i did and i bring
it up to those guys to tony
janet remember when we did almost every
season yeah i say it still bothers
and they were like we weren't expecting
it because we were yeah exactly yeah
oh yeah yeah we figured you yeah
yeah yeah you never expect to stay
i'd imagine wanting a standing ovation for
improv i want one now give it
to me you to me
give me that stadium know me wow
we've gotten it for comedy bang bang
though which i know very strawberry juice
you're just hated what what does the
song because yeah hey wipe down doom
by open to
is enter boom to doom i think
it's about a which flights no it's
michael jacklin which sorry for all you
already know it's the ah heehee love
funk of forty thousand years it off
the wall i don't know anyway
you don't worry last of the beginning
no i don't stop saying it like
capable he was we haven't mentioned michael
jackson it's such a long time i
thought we were doing great i was
at a vintage store and i saw
ah it was a really great t-shirt
however the big flaw is that having
michael jackson just drawing on it but
it was like a really good drawing
and you know that was like this
is a shirt like so you liked
it on an artistic level yeah it's
like i was no judgment about those
guys a good find and general great
artwork and then this leg was i'm
innocent
and then the back said the wearer
believes the shirt
ah that should just be the recipe
on every teacher you're aware believes the
shirt we saw guys area where believes
the shirt m is the best podcast
in the back says the where we
use the shirt let's do it it's
aware believes the jerk so high
kerio the wearer believes that the oh
cherry oh where believes the shirt da
every yo aware believe
oh yeah alright we need a break
but the hell is wrong
i am or bad quebec quebec lord
do you ever want to say we're
back we're back and we're ready to
rumble this time we're gonna play a
little thing called a three cheer that's
right if you're not familiar with reacher
is a thing that we play away
and i'm not ready to rumble well
well let's go to uni and your
rumble pack yeah the rumble pak yeah
what does that mean to you
you video games yeah yeah but now
now controllers just have rumble packs right
it's pretty grouse i've heard of romo
pecking in your seat that that was
rumbles rumble seat rumble six rumble lumpy
seat seats can rumble e when william
l yeah exactly
i'd have roles on it not ridges
no rumbles not ridges rumbles ridges alright
so tasty this ah can i just
say yes guys do want to say
really quickly yeah video game controllers are
so good now they're relaying the subtleties
of yeah the vibrational shit what they
do it's really good it's really good
i'm really happy
for you because i feel like that
changes your quality of thank you yeah
yeah i knew imagine me imagine going
back and living during the seventies again
i mean it would it would be
simpler because yeah i bet if you
went back now and you were in
the seventies you'd be like ok all
of tv is garbage so i'm never
gonna watch it again whereas i watched
a lot of it during the seventies
i would probably watch ah dvd champion
cincinnati more of an eighty show i
guess yeah i watched sanford and son
watch good times
i will just watch all the sandwich
was all the stuff and also if
i feel like now having i've forgotten
at all peak tv of how good
it is now you'd be like i've
seen good tea i definitely bored enough
to watch it all again i don't
think you think i wouldn't want to
see mod get an abortion for the
second time
lady godiva was for you to do
some crazy that episode by the way
is twenty two minutes first two minutes
or her deciding to get it and
then the next twenty or her getting
it yeah wow so crazy yeah yes
really awesome and then she shoves it
in her husband's face the less the
baby i thought you weren't some bringer
for the hospital
why
it's only utility hey louie like that
okay is this creature
is this reacher this is called the
titular game tit and this is submitted
by luke mendez the lighting change in
her no no as it gets it's
three am after dark no no it's
your brain tumor just up
um alright we name a movie so
or someone names a movie than we
all improvise the scene taking turns doing
lines in character but not not as
characters from the movie it's just a
random scene okay um it has to
be totally made up have nothing to
do with the movie all the characters
are so wet so what is the
none of them so why do you
say a movie well i'll get to
that
okay so we're creating new characters who
are saying lines from move notes
so creating mean must lead to one
character saying the name of the movie
with as much gravitas as you can
okay okay and you and if we
all say it at the same time
bonus amazing okay great so we just
have to eventually end at the title
of the movie yeah we don't have
to say actual lines from the film
no it's
trying to find a way to naturally
say oh yeah they're easy i love
this is gonna be so easy watch
this so lauren do you want to
name the movie don't believe me just
watch don't believe me rebel shirt um
the wearer believes my the name of
the film is three men and a
little lady
hey dingo
oh pooh dang i thought you were
a ghosted first i am but it's
just you're standing next to your cardboard
cut-out yeah i know i just like
the movies the little lady what's that
i know gravatar
that was too quick that didn't work
ah that was wrong
also the cutout was from three minutes
baby i believe that i don't even
know the the ghost cut out no
the ghost the yeah it's the story
of the ghost on the set of
three minutes supposedly when you watch three
million baby you can see a ghost
in the background and but it's actually
just the cut out of the three
of them
just taking why is it pushed out
of town for pub for publicity for
it was just in the background like
when the yeah yeah in their apartment
he had like a giant cutout of
himself the way that i threw in
there because there's a window and there's
curtains on the window and you can
see this house window figure kind of
work again another callback to let's do
another
one okay my girl too okay scott
i was going to fucking say you
are i swear to god at the
same time we would have won that
scene
alright okay um gentlemen ah i wanna
just really talk for a quick second
about you know the semiotic use already
sorry the auto shop is home i
go having a lot of issues because
you guys have enough and thinks she's
she the the restaurant across the street
is on fire oh no whoa well
the subway
a problem i'm sorry to interrupt here
but i'm torn because ah worried about
this file bureau dual taco belle de
gaulle or you both guys got to
see this fire it's crazy i mean
i know you have your thing you
went out safely know there are burning
god alive in my girl two
ah she was there at the restaurant
she owns it though ono was a
woman you guys said you only want
own businesses across the street from each
other as we stay true to ah
whoa why is this is no good
all i don't know let's let's try
to exchange ourselves needed
calm scenario completed scenario successfully compulsive okay
paul you name a movie okay
raiders of the lost ark raiders of
law sir
um okay hey ah thank you for
coming look i know i know it
started raining we see thank you so
much for you by the way i
have to sincerely thank you all for
coming no no sweat i mean i
know it's raining out yeah we're at
work
come to where i know but i
want to tell you i want to
tell you that um
god has been talking to me over
the last few months and that's why
i haven't got that one from heaven
yeah yeah g gotcha josh mark you
never believe that it's really god it's
always god yeah why doesn't he talk
to me because well only talks through
him sorry yeah and that's why i've
been building this
this is why i don't believe it
he only talks to the one guy
no and he always says it's like
threw his big hat
i maybe there's a receiver in there
somehow well look here's one is two
feet tall by the way yes it's
a tall hat so it's in style
right now you know what two feet
tall it's not small i want to
push you against the walls i'm going
to see you fuckin try i'm opening
a shop by the way is that's
and i guess i mean mean is
this a safe space to bring up
the opening shot going to trigger me
or anything yeah i'm sure warning embry
i'm opening a shop it's called lost
ark
i've never want to talk about that
again hey you're not aren't you worried
about like how bad crime has been
lately i i'm i've been worried a
little but i still didn't start my
shop i'm not going to base my
shower i don't want to talk about
your shop anymore okay i told you
never bring up your shop last dark
ever had
hey
who are you to decide what shops
we can and cannot oh okay sorry
i'm late to a new guy meeting
i
leave jazzercise shop across the street is
me he's being robbed i don't want
to talk about this what my shop
thing get out of here get out
of my shop is across the story
here get out of here who are
they doing raiders of the lost
well how did you think you're gonna
get there you had a plan or
i was talking about my arc that
i was building oh and all that
shit i didn't know
okay call you judas
judas judas
come ishmael another guy going gill hey
call me ishmael why that you're reading
my book alright you learn you pick
a movie okay the movie davy pigeon
yeah yeah sorry jesus christ the movie
is called um
the movie is called whatever happened to
baby gene whatever happened to baby jane
thank you both
hey let me just say no skin
off minded t feel you know what
i will say you're welcome because actually
didn't want to be here on a
saturday i actually have things that i
wanted to be doing one day i'm
your roommate so i just have to
go outside my room and i'm your
landlord and i did not want to
be here today so you are very
welcoming here on a saturday i do
appreciate
both of you very much you know
i'm at a time of my life
where i'm well as i'm reminiscing i'm
thinking about the life i've lived in
the people i've known and you owe
me rent by the way yeah about
that too y'all mean reddit huge i'm
also thinking about that don't worry yeah
i mean i'm the one who pays
you i don't really care how it
gets to me i just want
it in my wife i've only paid
her half this month because you haven't
paid your aware what's been real pay
you the rent i promise you must
pay the rent i
i can't wait
yeah you must hear guys that u
k pay the rent
must
i guess you know a bullshit wore
a bra you would be taught heavy
guilty as charged
but the re by the way you
are a little top heavy i have
to say you're a little bottom heavy
too like what's that you've gained
one hundred and twenty pounds it's fatal
oh dying i'm dying a fatal we
know yes so when does the rent
being paid well it's going to be
left to you in my will and
then my roommate of course will pay
you landlord but i do i need
another room do you want to live
with me i have been wishing i
could have that room
and it overlooks the street so well
these idiots please it really does there's
so much traffic i love to see
the cars and smell the pollution i
have so little time loveday oh it's
like happening soon it's happening suit okay
like what's the e t hey if
you know you were to what about
your wife and that you used to
have and and that daughter of yours
they
leave yeah mildred and whatever happened to
baby jane she's by
just
it's gotta come up naturally but it's
also supposed to be like a dramatic
bogus
casual question
every time you like
baikal two is pretty trivial make guys
right that was mad i was i
said dying in a fire either way
thank you alright
no mad land
thank you both for being here no
thank you i'm i'm here under duress
but thank really so i've been dying
to come here well so you both
share teeth cleaned ray places yeah thank
you both for coming in for your
regular check you we we decided to
do a dual teeth clean well you
always do right i mean twins yeah
twins can join
twin join twain were joined at the
cheek because there was that one time
you had an appointment you didn't want
to deal with it and he wanted
ticket he's done and what but anyways
yesterday he was he didn't want to
come yeah he was he was being
a real baby about it yeah and
i said you can't be unhappy at
the dense opposites of no man's land
wow wow i think that was good
yeah guys i mean i'm supportive good
totally different game now but that is
fun alright one more one more one
more okay one more you get to
pick your move oh okay
um
let's start packing her things
come on i put sunglasses in a
purse but i know you're neither of
them are mine i know you're all
imo i love to leave that you'll
have to leave ten minutes before the
battle true i'm invested
boogie nights boogie nights
hey i don't want to thank you
guys for coming because
i don't appreciate you being here well
you're welcome anyway i don't give a
fuck what you i don't i'm trying
to sleep why are you here it's
one of those boogie nights
cheese
boogie nights
ah alright i guess we're done and
that's how you play that game for
some milk and thank my dell to
luke's in a row um will do
everything you want to plug yeah i'm
at first of all the the comedy
bang bang book just came out two
days ago so you've got to get
the book by this
weak if you can you got to
get the book and then i met
the chicago humanities festival this saturday yeah
being interviewed by a human by a
human being fun it's a no robot
festival no robes no ai no chat
gpp no droids no alexis no series
yeah
yeah no one named alexa chappie ah
hey chappie go back to your fucking
home planet hey chappie sit this one
out transformer and about you today and
don't try to come in as a
truck transformers
years leaving robot we won't be we're
gonna have those mirrors underneath your truck
and if we see a robot building
yeah and we're bound eminence from
it's all fun and thrive but i
also have a plug may fourteenth mother's
day i'm just going to watch succession
variety apia with paul f tompkins and
while you're you're like what i'm not
going to go see that show successions
on guess what you piece of shit
after the show we're gonna watch succession
as a family we're gonna have a
great time while hopeful
you mean a more functional family than
the family and the noise yeah yeah
oh that sounds great paul i'm sorry
clash live oh i don't mind it's
fun to be tickled okay oh you
again i don't know why
i don't know why people hate it
so much it's great yeah i don't
really have a plug right now i
don't think i mean besides i'm doing
shows you know around and about and
you shout there on my instagram and
you've got shows that are online and
my shows are online dynasty typewriter dot
com if you wanna watch old shows
or i've done a bunch to check
them out we have our two person
shows that we've done if you wanna
honestly if you want to see some
weird insane shit from quarantine times oh
my and i did these shows over
zoom it was some very weird times
we're having a really weird time really
weird times alright well if you want
to hear ad-free versions of the show
you can go to stitcher premium or
cvb world dot com and if you'd
like
to send us a three church like
luke did why don't you write two
three mossad gmail dot com ah you
can also leave us a phone message
a voicemail some people call them that
hag claims eight and follows her instagram
through to melissa yes yeah all that
stuff yeah and look for our shirt
coming soon and by the
the mammoth and greatest podcast oh the
wire where believes the shirt yes oh
we need that we need we definitely
need this so look for though those
should be out in the market in
the next forty eight hours today yeah
exactly tight turn around yeah tight turn
around on that alright we'll see ya
hey mo
uh