three
oh
one
ah meru oh the birds are out
we're back we're back we're back for
another glorious episode of the role we're
doing on whoa whew we didn't agree
to say that no we did not
agree but i did say i thought
it was heavily implied
let's eat into it though no because
i i'm a bad bad podcast ooh
naughty boy
nah her what if there was a
movie bad podcasters that we can it
gay would instead of because joe rogan
the podcasters does smoke cigars so he
was already a podcaster he's the baddest
last podcast to push push cotto is
a person who well you know i
don't want to
waste a second because no okay we
can't waste any seconds on this show
this is three and by the way
where mine everything ran heavily scripted and
we say everything that we're supposed to
say and not a thing that we're
not yes paul you are going to
tell us what i'm saying you weren't
allowed to
yeah you had a feature last episode
no but yes i had my feature
that i was gonna do my segment
but we ran out of time and
time and said i was gonna do
it twice on this show i'll didn't
but i don't think we get a
chance to argue with it well we
don't want to waste any seconds though
get to later
sort of
oh well welcome welcome was it was
it paulo welcome it was my this
is my segment you didn't want to
start with balls
a public whole james vanderbeek has started
life over in austin and it looks
beautiful congratulations to james vanderbeek one of
our best listeners congratulation james glad you're
listening dvd because you did it his
life looks so idyllic what's the why
what you do is like groping steer
basically really stoke a bunch of kids
lives no
rural area they have a lot more
than just whole property making those billions
doing some sort of craft or you
know not craft like some sort of
like i'm going to the river to
pull out this thing and i'm gonna
do this with that and i'm gonna
do this with that you know that
kind of thing sounds like a lot
of busy work are you saying you
want to live his life i'm saying
i wanna live in a van down
by the river okay
it's what i thought would you where
would not want to live there you
wouldn't want to live there where where's
it austin yeah but it's i think
he's joe rogan in a rural area
so right now we're lost him where
do you want to live there
i'd like to live in a city
i'd like to live in new york
city would you think to live in
chicago yeah cause you wanna have a
baby in new york city that seems
like a lot rich why what what
would you be able to do ah
make other people i guess hamster bar
have a car you know cars only
cost like twenty or new york's expensive
too
an extra ten parking dollars parking sure
but how much how much would if
i have a parking spot that means
i have a building i live in
a building that is nice and a
doorman building then i have to pay
for that then i have to pay
for everything if that involves which also
just do another movie it's not how
it works buddy
but that would be that would be
fun to live in new york so
cool etc it's a baby i don't
know you're right i know i'm happy
to settle down i lived in new
york for a year and i found
it very challenging well so did i
but i mean i was also broke
as a joke i wasn't and it
did not make things easier
you are an eccentric millionaire when you
did yeah that show right yeah you're
saying because i need to go to
the grocery story you measure the heart
to back with
yeah well because i i don't i
don't know that i ever dragged a
cart back i remember just carrying bags
yeah both hands yeah yeah til you
can fill your fingers yeah but also
it was like difference in space was
very challenging and also just moving to
a city that big that you don't
don't know your way around is like
that yeah big adjustment yeah well the
bronx is up the battery's now right
the people i mean they kind of
go they wrote in a hole in
the ground yeah so i mean that's
that's i mean that's all you really
need to know right it's a toddling
town yeah now that chicago chicago thailand
town yeah no chicago titles new york
new york though
new scale of a tack
wow
oh man but the seasons also i
do not want it to have again
yeah you like yeah i'd i'd really
like living in los angeles i really
like living in california one winter in
milwaukee and it was freezing no thank
you i could live in the south
but for the poetic well whoa you
lose more than this
but for the poe yeah you'd live
there just i live to celebrate the
statue politics yeah so be like this
is all bra heritage
with muzzle tail down those remodels how
will we remember all his draw
we got we we all should move
everyone in a city should move to
the middle of nowhere so it all
balances a bigger city yeah we should
exactly match was like over nebraska yeah
it would be cool i mean look
yes everyone wants to live in los
angeles because it's beautiful to hear a
voice for the shah it's beautiful except
for the sme
aw the architecture the earthquake the culture
of the people
but anyway we're not stops anyway on
snobs i like to live in santa
barbara maybe you're okay thank you well
no probably not no three hard for
me to conceive living in another place
well a lot of things would have
to happen i mean like to me
it's like when i moved from neighborhood
to neighborhood even that i think i
pay the neighborhood now could i go
to another place and then once we
moved to the neighborhood we're now we
never think about that neighborhood right and
we loved living yeah my old neighborhood
too and i was like i remember
saying to my neighbor like my other
naib about my naib i was like
i don't think i would ever want
to live anywhere else and
he said it's the best place to
live in the world and then suddenly
packed up and just took off that
now did or you did well that
name eventually did but we were both
out of the nabe do you think
that that nape left like when i
quit a couple the wife dies and
then the man dies of a broken
heart when i when you let an
ape he was like what i am
listening
please the world no he didn't like
me from what i can tell oh
well there were only six of us
and we all had to take turns
being the head of the h away
association or i guess it's all hey
was very annoying it was it's not
oh yes e cho da ho but
the whoa that's that always seems like
such a chore it it was like
when there are rules like when an
apartment building has don't apply to you
but then they're like and you know
twenty can have a doggy butter ask
us if you can write that kind
of stuff isn't ours wasn't like ours
ours was just us trying to get
through it but we all we had
to meet get through what just get
like like the whole treasury aspect of
a yeah like why do they need
that but you had to have meetings
because like legally you have to and
you have to like vote on stuff
and you have to you have to
say like hey guys we need to
pay for this this it would be
so easy to not like somebody in
that situation that i'd go yeah for
sure one of one
misstep he goes yeah yeah yeah anyway
so he didn't he he thought he
thought i was treating it like an
apartment which i probably was of just
like you guys do everything and so
then i had to take over the
h o o ngai in charge of
it for a year and then we
we just all have to rotate and
stuff it was janky friday for a
year yet to be in charge of
it yeah fuh could also everyone was
a lie
terrier everyone was fucking lunate because they
all want to be in charge no
no like most people want to just
be left alone like when i moved
there it was all a bunch of
old people in fact my neighbor my
name i'm sorry my upstairs naib was
was an older woman named violet or
some old shit
and she blasted her tv so loud
and it and the first day i
was kinda like huh but then i
realised it was great because i like
to blast off really loud yeah she
couldn't hear it real rock acts together
she had to turn over like any
of that black and black or white
music video by michael jack
jackson oh yes he is the wise
man once said
he but she she had to turn
her tv up super loud just to
hear it so she couldn't hear anything
i was doing so we she never
complained about anything it was great just
like shouting curse words and slurs
and if i could combine a free
you know we had talks about this
yeah i'd say okay i'm just saying
i'm good but that's gonna end the
other guy moved in my my nabe
okay he neglected like you why do
you think this guy didn't like you
so yeah he was he was very
cool huh
he's just kind of know it all
guy he's very cool and i'm a
dork yeah and that's really like me
i don't like noodles well it they
see hey it's like they know it
all okay it's one way to look
at it i know i know it
all unless they do know it all
yeah i loved ken jennings know like
god nobody like when someone um has
a lot of good tips and info
and it's a big know it all
but like someone who just seems to
know it all
i mean there's difference of being know
what he's magical versus just being someone
who knows though like i have a
friend who i'm like she always knows
a good thing to recommend for this
that you don't mean like well yeah
because the the phrase don't stick at
somebody for meeting somebody who just likes
to tell you what you should be
doing yeah you told me yes
i don't know i
you miss him i miss him
i missed the nave i miss the
name is monet mesmo der my gym
is today too much like this but
miss monet but you miss the old
emotions this nave and abysmal naval captain
know me a miss mcnair better miss
monet what about now me don't you
understand
now in the me part okay so
let's see where do you go wow
nail down
did you miss walking around we used
to walk rocky to get coffee every
every morning or i p the rockstar
i lost my cat yes oh that's
this is lawrence topics come back out
it was really crazy that kind is
one of the most beautiful cats i
ever see oh like sexy yeah yeah
i know choose the street
only attractive cat no she was old
and she just one day it was
just clear it was so sad you
scribble yeah well how how long was
it sat for ah still i'm so
you don't bring it up now i
feel said he was i was kind
of kidding about it that i felt
kind of sad but um i do
feel sad everyone's smiling we weekend cry
on this show
by the way i don't want to
i forgot we did say we could
cry we can cry this is this
is ah an open welcome i don't
want to cry on the show at
this time when do you want to
cry it'll just happen when it happens
but i don't this is not it
this is not it do you think
that we will all have a turn
at crying on this show at some
point at some
point if you say so yes that's
dark play i don't know it's like
why do we know that that'll happen
oh it's dark knowing that that will
happen it's like a part about that
you don't like the prophecy aspect i
don't know if i like that yeah
i'm gonna leave rice before the year
is done each year i owe this
ok we will cry a show old
witch but it's about something that you
can put on the witch and you
wouldn't expect
i'm thirty seven meat boy
but yeah hi rocky pass ah he
left right away chances
he he started to be very wobbly
you're trying to get me to cry
but that's what happened she got really
wobbly and then started to wobbly and
and started to list to the right
law and and walking into like bumping
into walls and stuff and so we
took
took him to the vet and and
they kind of they they thought it
was it was something they didn't know
what it was but then they gave
us hope where they were like oh
i think we know what it is
he was there for observation and they're
like we think we know what it
is if we do this thing i
think it'll it'll cure it and then
we were on the way to pick
him up and it just took ten
minutes to get there remember this
and we are on the way to
we were like ok well we got
to pick them up at noon so
at eleven forty five we're like okay
let's let's get into the car and
go and somehow he passed away in
that ten minutes and they were like
texting us and calling and neither of
us were on our phones cars driving
and all that and so i walked
in and eh
we walked into that hard to have
to be told that and everyone was
like i said hey we're here to
pick up rocky and everyone everyone there
had been like this was going on
everywhere and they're like ah hi have
a seat and and you know the
doctor will be shocking i turned to
my cat disguise
here he is he's much better ie
he's lost some weight
but i i said to cool i
go i think something's wrong and suddenly
i pulled out my phone and there
was like a message i go oh
no and then the doctor came out
and said we could brought us back
wow that's us and he had like
just in that just literally five minutes
before we got there if we've left
i don't know but because maybe you
want to take him then it would
happen the car's name
would be bad no no i wouldn't
want to take but yeah so then
they found it i think that it
was like a big giant oh they
tumor or something like that you know
so for gae yeah poor guy yeah
i think mine has kidney failure ultimately
she was she had kidney disease and
then that was getting worse but i
thought it was okay and then i
think that for a while there i
was
like i think she's got more few
years and are and then just one
day it was like no but then
we did one thing i remembered a
friend of mine telling me maybe i'm
just saying this because maybe somebody might
use this as a tip because i
didn't know about this my friends die
you can't die yeah don't have any
had somebody come to her home to
euthanize her i've heard of that i
didn't know but
so i was going to take her
to the vet and then i remembered
that she told me about that and
so i ended up finding some and
they were tons of on yelp um
and this woman came and we did
it in our yard and she was
like so nice and that was it
was nice to be able to do
it that way no yeah okay cutie
i know how what's died that you've
owned that you've loved my parents of
course you own them
right in a way you have a
pet i we did not have pets
growing up i had ah a cat
that i had to house with um
friends when i moved out here because
i didn't know where i was oh
go away so it was year old
cat from like you're from
pennsylvania yes right you were like bobcat
you brought the cat with you no
no no i left the cat in
pennsylvania with ah my cat in pennsylvania
the famous beachside yeah um and what
was the cat's name daisy oh yeah
thanks and this is your cat solely
yeah
wow she was a little kitten that
a friend gave me and um a
razor from a pup she was a
little light ginger cat like a blonde
cat kind of nice house very sweet
and and then your friend kept her
yes yes yes and yes and is
daisy soda still life really i mean
this was ninety ninety four
one old cat did you get a
call she's gotten bigger each year too
oh no yeah she's she's giant right
now she like quivers no
what if you own clifford oh can
you imagine why here oh joey yeah
i mean those shits must be huge
that's the hard thing clifford doesn't tell
you about he's like look yes i'm
big i'm adorable do you think clifford
shits are brown or like red
i wonder i may have it they'd
be red because he's both ragnar dogs
around this whole thing dogs are brown
and they have brown shit dogs are
brown cats are cats are grey grey
grey shit yeah yeah so it stands
to reason clifford has read shit it's
the dance let me ask you does
clifford speak to know any speak
no i don't think just just clip
pig that's his whole i was in
too many years cartoon nobody does speak
because somebody i know did the voice
i didn't know him but john ritter
was the always-on clifford he was a
character really why wait the tv show
the tv show hold on i'll wait
you know john ritter said i don't
i said somebody i know was the
voice meaning i know
somebody was i don't know what he
was the voice yes um but that
isn't many years clifford zone choices about
way i do know that there was
a movie this sounds familiar they tried
to make clifford several times but maybe
it was trying to make clifford happen
maybe it was the voice of liquid
was john ritter but but maybe his
thoughts now still thinking and got a
voice yeah
but he can't talk that was the
question do you think don't think in
english
they do things
same command no matter what country there
is there like i always thought yeah
they think in english yeah in english
i think it was like a talk
yeah i wish i could sail this
sort of these people saying spanish yeah
who owned me why are they saying
spanish ponyo
you know molly was a mexican trash
dog so yeah oh yeah yeah founder
the trash ah in ah in ah
basically live the first couple years of
her life like in a junkyard or
something fighting for the planet she really
hasn't made now yeah god lap of
difference i bet she doesn't even remember
that and because she's so entitled now
there is no way she remembers it
what if she's like i miss the
junkyard my old dogs have a memory
like that like i think they remember
people in smells but do think they
remember like i think back again image
of a place using those non-aboriginal smells
zhang qiong but if they smell into
the junkyard they would remember it but
what they remember it without smelling it
if they saw i think if they
saw probably
the somebody playing a radiator like it
was an accord
yeah yeah they wouldn't remember the cosby
kids right who
mush mouth you know trump favor biloba
that's
isn't that the joe here gang oot
it's of course it is because we
yes yes of course how much headphone
start to hurt i want i would
like to join the army so i
can come back and surprise someone
why don't you just go away for
a while but also to go oh
okay fine fine
you want to join the army so
you can come back yeah and then
you just i think we hope use
guys julie are three steps go away
step two step three combat full of
yourself and you leave the house for
a few hours
well first of all tapping cool up
on the shoulder first of all georgia
would still act the same and for
sure no sparking you chosen barbie she
barks at you if you ever leave
the room for two seconds right but
she gets very excited i will say
we were gone for a week recently
and she she gave me it was
like after about half an hour it
was like ok george i'm back
i'm back everything's fine wow like it
was so when people see guys on
the head when the troops surprised dogs
cod is amazing yeah when who does
when the troops when they surprised their
dogs are just anyone's dog oh i
don't know if i've seen but that
i think i've seen them surprise their
kid or something oh i've seen so
many videos so many dog services really
yeah when they come back after the
top dog being on the grave where
they're like
after someone dies in there the dog
lays on the gray no really because
they smelled it i don't know i
don't oh here it's comfortable it's a
fresh grave very well yeah it's like
yeah grass they're excited about they're just
excited the grass dogs love grass love
to eat and roll around and that's
why i can tell is is like
if i were to die would they
scott and i was gone for a
week don't do dogs is do dogs
just assume you're dead if you're not
there for a week and then they're
happy to be proven wrong or would
they understand like well that person's never
coming back i don't know i think
i don't know if they even are
thinking oh they're gone they're not coming
back but then when you come back
they remember that you were gone i
don't know molly
when klopp has gone recently was it
definitely took her like two days she
was like constantly at the door looking
around like what is going on stuff's
different and then after two days she
was just like coming up to me
and just like you're doing yes you
do yeah exactly yeah
so i don't know anyway it's great
to love things but dogs of course
to email this you know it is
nice to love a pet ah it
feels so good yeah but i mean
so hard when when i leave it
feels bad for able like three hours
know you're a sociopath
i felt bad you know i was
over the ah the break i was
reunited with my old friend tugboat yeah
and did you jump up and down
when you saw really really good i
advocate likes the dog and tugboat acted
like the service person who was just
like yeah you can do whatever just
you can do whatever to be you
can pet me okay fuck
can do whatever to me he ah
that he denied there was not a
glimmer of recognition
this is come ah it's bowie's oh
me too you're supposed to think honey
you want a goop twenty two
do you wanna do it they don't
good goop also my phone over here
record us
get gwen a video we're gonna go
how do you do a goop like
dick with the nice nice nice looping
lauren we gotta hey listen oh sorry
oh you renae we talk about he
just there was a glimmer of recognition
yeah
oh i was really excited i was
like man like remember me kid he
did why does she have matching outfits
paul doesn't have a dog outfit
take what i'd like coordinated something we
don't
you guys in college other one day
and say look you wear the color
all wear color to a gift that
is picture on it though
or vice versa by the way the
airwolf dog right and so no yes
renee you gave him what i gave
him a little doll that looked like
me that's the same does
say oh but paul i was jealous
i want a doll that looks like
you and i want to rip it
to shreds oh my teeth
he really tore that thing apart it
was wild to watch maybe thought you
were dead when you did that let
me tell you again he's ignoring me
because he thinks i'm a ghost and
yeah just play it cool yeah i'm
not gonna act scared that's for sure
i don't know why it's dogs ripped
some things to resonate like we had
a ah an apologies for getting political
but we had ah you know the
cheeto in chief
ah we had a we had a
little dog toy that we were hoping
that our dog would rip to shreds
on election night and neither of them
did did like they kind of batted
it around a little and maybe bit
into it but didn't and then it
took weirdly it took the entire time
for the race to be called like
you know ten days or whatever for
them to
then they found it and they finally
did it yeah well they just wanted
to wait for the results dogs can
smell death and they could smell results
well they want to go hey when
the networks are gonna call yeah exactly
because at that point they could shoot
up the secret service yeah it doesn't
look good doesn't look good they they
did kathy griffin with the mouse but
the path poor berada poor boy
baron feinberg errands like i'm baron pikes
eight poor barbarians poor pine barrens to
be lost in the woods he's very
tall very doomed giving birth
or you could ask me um tell
us about the aftermaths oh okay why
is going lawrence topics tell us about
the aftermath of you get back from
the hospital how long are you in
the hospital by the way did they
put you up for nine nights to
know i guess two guys yeah lauren
gave birth and spent two ny doesn't
my insurance cup
covered so i don't know if that's
really so if you have better insurance
you could like taking no i think
my insurance was good in that sense
that i could say to but i
think sometimes they let just say one
really okay um yeah so after a
couple of nights you're like let's get
out well yeah but i don't want
to get into all of that because
there's some of it that it's gone
talk about
yeah um talk a little bit no
but then the talk about the stuff
that you don't want to talk about
okay so here's all the stuff that
i can go where um way but
we when we brought her home that
was a very magical moment that was
very exciting wow but did you did
you do like what they do with
brides where you carried her over the
threshold we'd walk
ah
you think a video of it it
was really cute and then she the
pets were going crazy my cat was
still with us at the time so
how is your life let's talk more
generally go for macro how's it how
is it how's the adjustment how's i
think we're pretty pretty doing pretty well
with the adjustments a lot i mean
we're very tired and we don't have
help and we're very doing
my recent adjustment bureau yeah oh they're
gonna slide walls around for you that
would be great but it's going it's
going really well we're i think we've
got a bit of a rhythm now
and it's like there's still a very
hard days but i feel like at
first we were like totally overwhelmed yeah
how's the sleeping aspect of it we
figured out a sort of routine with
it
it um where i handled the mornings
and my candles the nights kind of
like we have balanced out but that's
starting to now run it's course a
little bit too so i think we're
both kind of tag teaming the knights
little bit more okay with me now
mush sheets mush yeah
pure milk pure milk pure fuel alternating
uncut loren lapidus
your nexus guys i think your meds
disgusting why it is has my tribe
your breastmilk
okay we need zuckerberg huh
wait guys we're back now we're back
josh just told me that there was
a time when tugboat dressed up as
paul and i said yes that's what
i mean and then paul said i
wondered if that's what you meant yeah
you didn't think jeff tried to help
her see the game as you matching
know because about that time we went
to the other thing of the dull
other
thing of the doll still other topic
all doll came up so you moved
on you know we both moved on
to want to say but you're probably
thinking that time tugboat dressed as me
but i'm saying by the time i
was forming that thoughts when we're gone
yes i would have i still would
have liked it i bet you wanna
okay well i'll say you're prob
only thinking that time the tugboat dressed
as me for halloween which is the
same as you matching know it's not
at all
because they were the exact same out
yeah but you did not call me
and say what are you wearing right
now i'm gonna wear the same but
you could have we could have but
we did not you you own the
same clothes who does oh yeah not
everything that he was wearing i also
had my closet you should address this
him for home so what check about
where i tie a hat he had
a jacket
and a little shirt how did you
hear the art the i've fuckin the
costumes were the dogs where they have
the fake we got anything mailman one
for for halloween and it looked it
was too big so it was just
flopping along with chip clip to hold
it shut and we have the indiana
jones a bit rocky head with a
fake arms and everything it's very funny
but that's it that's a pretty new
concept it is like when it came
out i was like this is genius
i saw a lot of this halloween
i saw a lot of chuck chutneys
a lot of checking guides on dairy
china yeah it's terrifying
do something that little like little girl
just as chucky she's like four something
and she runs up to a restaurant
window and taps with her fake knife
no she's like really small like a
doll do you think i want to
see that but i saw one dog
dresses chucky that was running and so
the
the arm with the knife is just
like going huh looks like that's good
i sent you that video of the
kid who loves michael myers right yeah
yeah oh the few kids who love
me where there are few who like
this because here's the thing they cry
at santa who is their main dude
yeah i don't understand this obsession with
the old
weepy man anything must know the the
movie because like the the one who
wanted michael myers to come to her
birthday party she's like four years old
and they play the theme that denon
and anna and she's like gets all
excited like he's here which means implies
that she's seen the movie and then
he pokes his head out of the
bushes and comes over and kind of
like real
the creepily and then just gives her
a nice little hug it's like i
guess you are here if you're a
small child and you're watching that movie
he does seem to be the most
pleasant person because he's the only person
not screaming yeah or having sex which
is yellow suit don't understand that he's
there to kill them all yeah yeah
what for these making the screaming stop
so you see this guy's great this
guys
your business
that checks out thank you michael myers
thank god my little anya's no expression
so it's you can assume that he's
doing fine he's neutral yeah yeah neutral
yeah he's not he's at least not
fighting like mom and dad he walks
very slowly not like there's nothing threatening
and you watch halloween kills i know
i did too i thought
oh my own i was a little
scared oh really
oh year of the tv i get
scared of scary movies yeah those movies
don't scare me that much slasher movies
i like that kind of thing more
because i like the idea that it's
a fake killer who dies thick
i know that's a problem for me
yeah but i like when there's like
a sort of bow on it and
i don't feel scared i don't like
when it's a ghost or something i
always thought it was so i mean
the first scream is such a good
screenplay right scary movie but it was
so interesting because i never even guessed
that it that there there was someone
under the mask
sg because freddy and jason and everyone
like they're just these kind of other
worldly killers and so i just thought
they were inventing one of those so
when suddenly it was like oh no
it's two of these kids i would
i didn't go into that first screen
going like okay who is it which
one of these suspects is the show
because you assume it's definitely something outside
of their group i yes yes
i don't know if i i
i guess i wasn't sixth grade i
probably wasn't thinking anymore but i remember
when i was dating my class i
have to report around the class who's
your who's your principal's kid named bill
he goes like this kidney bills your
principal oh yeah fuck yeah get your
classes the killer and scream is a
lovable i won't say it now even
if you haven't seen it yeah
that's no fun and then everyone cheeses
bill
we're like i say now but let's
just say that certain shooters of the
things that fly in the air were
pretty happy when they found out who
that killer was i can't put that
right now you not under yeah i
can't i'm yeah i got it but
he was only one
zay anymore but ah i guess what
i saw a movie called lamb never
heard of that oh it is a
lamb what does lam stand for
liar oh ass beef
that's it mate beef
b
let's all me let me be face
to face is a ah scandinavian film
maybe it's icelandic and you love your
icelandic stuff thank to bjork um motor
crash um it's about a couple and
this remote farm
and um how how remote are we
talking theirs they have no neighbors no
names new names already scary right so
they don't learn any nabe has no
names oh wait their neighbors who names
their name unto himself zoho you remind
me of a movie i can't wear
like um the train coming towards like
one where it's like the big rocket
goes moon moves around a circle um
no it takes place always with some
amanda c fred and kevin bacon do
you oh yeah i did see that
movie but i remember thinking they do
they address the age difference um i
can't remember i think she says hey
hi grandpa at one point and he
says we're married
i don't want degree of sedation i
will say i like that couple as
a couple in a movie in a
movie that works you like these two
guys in a movie like where do
you where did they ever talk about
it i don't remember men fought rounds
of the film what did i see
the reminded you of that just that
it was found nicole yeah because they
live like in the middle of nowhere
that house and i that freaks me
out well here's the plot of this
movie so your stomach was like a
sound effect
well yeah i'm recording it oh thank
you
what effects are we up to thirteen
we got this boy yep pouring water
we got with too many pouring water
turn eleven if i remember correctly yeah
um
so
so this couple they have a farm
they have sheep one of their sheep
sheep sheep go back
shipped to go cheap go bad they
go back well interesting that you say
that oh no one of these sheeps
that's how they came up with it
gives birth to age wow yeah but
the lamb is also part human know
it's know which parts no because the
man fucked it
we don't know that that's so gross
but you keep saying red in the
face anytime zoo
the documentary about the men who fuck
tokyo's i've heard of that i have
not seen it zootopia it's it's called
zoo
utopia is about an animated manufacturer
so what happened this half man half
lamb ah so which way should we
were all texas which part is
it's it seem like it's just the
middle is me both motioning to the
tits
because they're so big
the lamb is wearing clothes and it
seems like it as a human body
real i mean that's what that's what
really happens in the movie i know
yeah wearing clothes yeah they raise it
as a child they shouldn't
i don't i think there was some
slipping this is the baby yoda effects
you would you would throw it away
y f okay i'd feel guilty if
i threw it oh to raise lib
byu so hey um
then it gets then it goes on
with that song have been popular if
it was i want to raise the
white house
right up
like michael jackson came out was like
i really want a baby but this
is my new stuff you're like well
fucking you ain't t's pretty random yeah
but it it leads is about low
i mean p watch is pretty thing
just read of his baby yoda effect
but i would i recommend this movie
it's very weird it's very good yeah
sounds good and sounds it's scary but
it is sort of unnerving okay i
watched that movie that you recommended to
me on with her which ones recommended
a movie
on twitter or the movies on twitter
and you're eliminated oh it's it's a
movie that premiered on twitter like what
was it one hundred and forty movie
that was just moving a welder pp
yeah that was good well that's love
that movie yeah that's great
thanks a lot that's a good one
sam neill in it of course scores
alumni from jurassic park coming back gin
from me waiting on him at tower
were you jealous the entire time you're
watching going t got to come back
will do raise them be
you should go back to jurassic park
i haven't thought of that yeah you
should do it i'd love to what
have you heard every family one and
you found out where they were filming
in the you showed up to the
set did you get with vostok right
that'd be do you think people have
done stuff like that yeah
ah like shown up on a set
and said like here i am although
who is it what movie was it
that i was just reading about and
go
i think um robert de niro not
robert de niro robert what's his name
from uq graduate dustin hoffman
robert doesn't often
i make them ah robert de niro
but anyways josh hoffman showed up to
where he's he showed up to nancy
meyers set and it's just in the
movie looking at a blockbuster and i
guess must have been when hearing what
i'm learning him into one of these
movies
bad story house goes looking at a
blockbuster he is in the side blockbuster
looking at movies and picks up like
he's either i don't know if he
picks up the graduate or what but
he was he came to set o
o some of his foot being filmed
and then he gets pretty movies being
gone that's a dream okay i'm gonna
figure out what you want i've almost
done that so many times just to
see like
do i know somebody like right walk
onto the set but it seems like
such a weird thing to do yeah
it is oh the holiday oh maybe
okay oh don't tell me anything more
because we might cover it on my
other show university not know ah which
was the holiday nancy
cameron dia i know jack black don't
tell me i am a black actor
so yeah no no any of this
stuff come on you can know anyhow
it's a good movie it's a great
christmas film you're the second person to
recommend that movie to me and wagging
the second thing i'm doing is overberg
do you remember though when when will
ferrell came by the between two ferns
set
on just a random day when he
wasn't filming were you there i don't
know i can remember but i've never
done i ever movie though but he's
in the mood i don't do that
even when i'm in something i don't
just go visit it's people do that
huge he just he happened to be
passing by came by and then talk
to everyone on the crew and said
like
oh it's so nice to see you
again and i remember do you remember
megan our script supervisor yeah like the
stars of the movie never talked to
me and he talked to me he
hit the day he worked and then
he came up and chatted like chatted
with me but said how nice it
was to see me again i talked
to the script supervisor a lot when
i were near like what are my
lines
what is english i guess what they
always start of the conversation where you
just go i'm just looking what you're
supposed to say and um you haven't
said any of it i think i
told you that i worked on a
show where the the showrunner insisted on
the dialogue being word perfect oh yeah
and it was it's hard
achievable challenge well there was that great
ed asner clip up from an interviewer
he was talking about aaron sorkin um
he was on he was on studio
sixty or something like that yeah he
was like and listeners like he's so
over it he's just goes sigh do
the scene and they come up to
me after the show when it comes
over to the director comes up and
says
you know aaron writes like music it's
like very musical so if like there's
a comma even out of place the
music doesn't work and so i said
what the fuck do you need me
for that yeah that's good says shoe
let me
let me do my thing as or
do its thing do da do da
alaris ark and let him know yeah
that's there and zircon fled
a
aaron sorkin la usa
a great head hundred and one
we'll be right back
one hundred and one i know when
when when you when we're back we're
back to the dalmatian episode is special
we call creatures this is the part
where we do a game pong yes
it's a three star game it's not
a game it's not it's reward it's
activity it's called a three-tier and it's
not even activity it's a feature it's
a feature but we call it a
feature yeah it's a feature it's a
segment called a feature not a segment
it's a segment that's a three cheer
that we call a feature and we
make it our own it's the segment
that's a feature called with reacher and
what it is is a game and
we make it our own i mean
by having people send it into us
okay so
this is called this decision by nobody
nobody waves by our sar our number
one fed ya oh josh hello shoot
josh said he says okay
by the way now anytime because during
the break we we read some of
these and say do we like this
one now i'm worried that we're gonna
hurt josh's feelings if we don't like
what josh we're sorry in advance we're
sorry investment we like this one we
love the story events am i the
asshole sorry to this man's and my
dirty asshole is a fun reddit
it really area it really yeah you
ever go and read it oh no
what does it ah it's a website
people write stuff on it yeah i
always the segment or would you call
it like a subreddit or whatever it's
a three-tier oh where people say and
people story i don't like by the
score is this person an asshole wow
usually when people tell the story
or they make themselves sound good though
there are times we go know that
person is the asshole yeah because it's
sometimes it's complicated to do it usually
as a complicated situation where you kind
of can't tell right right or wrong
but when somebody is saying am i
the asshole and they are the asshole
it's amazing because there do they think
they think that they are i don't
know
accept it probably not yeah but they
would they think they are laying out
the story where it's like where do
you get a load of this asshole
have to deal with and it's like
no it's you that should be a
difference what you're saying is crazy get
a load of this asshole you ran
into but then you can respond no
you're the asshole right yeah that takes
the fun out of it haha man
man anyway you wonder am i the
asshole right now you are for not
knowing about that yes she comes from
superfan josh it's called that's not how
i remember it all right during a
conversation one player remembers an anecdote that
everyone in the conversation was therefore example
remember the time we all got stuck
in an elevator after the world series
we cut from the conversation to a
reenactment of that story for about a
minute then we come back to take
five minutes another player says wait a
minute does that ally remember it we
cut to another enactment of the story
where that player can occasionally interject corrections
to the story i e it wasn't
the way
old series it was my son's little
league game after that the that's a
huge thing too yeah
later however really have the author of
the well we don't have to pass
it around i'm just realising it as
everybody else knows is the original person
say like god i'm going ooh does
your base original person s do it
can't have nice here first zipper up
does it two things yeah very rare
rare wow
marina play they say bow after the
abra third layer remembered the story their
own way for a total of three
remember totally vander did baba wawa yeah
it was just making fun of barbara
walter's voice took the world by storm
when who did it gilda radner why
they said well no no writer i'm
baba remember when
no ann arbor writers on and l
she was a cast member of the
nineteen eighty sixty s that we are
a year it was robert downey junior
when new owner randy quaid anthony michael
hall was colonel sanders known writers yeah
she really well she did update
but she wasn't really on it though
julia no she wasn't okay okay thank
you ah no
that yeah therapy one remembers the story
their own way for a total of
three different versions of the story and
i think we all understand
wing it okay alright guys hey ding-dong
hey ding dong what's up players think
bay to see talking so you hear
your voice different did you have throat
surgery young men just go back to
college you want for you ding dong
so you went to college originally but
now you're back i hadn't completed my
my how many days
did you go are you also sort
of irish maybe
hi hud completed by degree i hadn't
completed my degree but now i did
ya oh well congratulate y'all
i mean i went for five days
this time i went for three well
we know that we were there with
you it's almost a year number one
went to the first day of school
yeah i do remember that
what's your recollection of it because it
was something like this
hi what's up what's your name
sarah
i see
hey do you guys know where the
squad is yes that square thing over
there oh that's the chua yeah i
thought it was like a little toad
those opposed to talk to
to get permission to go chinese money
this is jean this is sarah i'm
eugene what's your name stranger
mr incredible mr gretta bad nice to
meet you hey
i think we're going to be fast
friends look out push pull sables fellow
you
well ding dong hell's going on ding
dong that's such a let's play oh
so you know what you know what
sarah huckabee is like alcohol you using
oh because he's hinting oh i'll never
forget this you guys want some fries
oh i'd love some fries but if
i eat them have allergic reaction how
oh my god he's blown up like
a balloon he's flying away can't you
get him feel luckily i tied a
string on him irl
earlier oh hey thank mr incredible yeah
that was a close look
to remind myself that he's my best
friend are you a teacher here yes
alright classes in session but with class
now yeah i'll just looking for the
sharing bad
okay yeah i gotta go wade's role
does old yeah
no stick around eugene stick around cigarette
okay was that was it i don't
remember it happening that way you say
you don't remember happening no no i
mean i remember of course our first
day at college we all that's where
we met right but i don't i
remember the details being a little something
like this
shh
hi
wow you're really cool yeah i know
i'm i'm pretty studly aren't i i
noticed you admiring my bod from across
the quad yeah what's your name ah
yeah my name is ah mr genius
so matter mister genius matter yeah oh
my name's dara hey there
pardon me clearly your boyfriend and girlfriend
know you're not too handsome for me
to ask this but if you've seen
the quadrangle i'm a tune yeah of
course i know everything and it's way
over there ooh should i go over
there because i'm so ugly yeah you're
too ugly this is my new girlfriend
what's your name again dara but i
haven't agreed to this look out oh
whoa
flier you because you only have to
you only mine and you're just holding
oh whoops
this woman with big tits almost fell
on you
over there come on back dude i
just saved your life wow ding dong
delicious you're a hero wu did you
say ding dong alleges i did know
we're gonna call you dig down delicious
okay
wait a bit don't ever try before
we leave woo
that's what i remember
so it was it was some like
that don't you think nice i remember
and your name wasn't mister genius matter
that's not how i remember it let's
go back in time to how you
did
look here look
hi
why huh i'm reading sorry i'm so
are you checking me to work i'm
talking to both of you look at
his cool guy over here okay my
ooh hell yeah you are you're the
coolest dude i've ever seen i never
thought i was that cool do you
really think i'm cool oh my god
i do
hey i'm not good at picking up
on signals what did you just do
with your face if you said yeah
i guess my eyes went back and
forth like i wasn't sure yeah yeah
that i did pick up a correctly
i rolled my eyes when i said
but i said oh man i say
what does it i guess ah koo
that's alright but ironically that makes me
cool what's your name dude
my name is u g the great
youtube
yep i'm a king show don't tell
anybody i'm here to cover go to
college like a regular guy got like
the prince at the bottom that's what
a king and a college student yeah
i lost my toad
is it that obvious can i massage
your quads you please do but watch
out musket is poison so no oh
no sms boy yomi clunk oh she's
dead and oh that's so hey her
twin sisters right over here don't come
over here hey what's up players hey
ho ho ho good anybody got to
guys eat i do my purse i
could process the no problem alright here
you go blue
those are flies not fries well i
a bit understood she's doing well though
yeah you ain't let me try but
toggle the fries ooh oh that's not
nice but what was yeah would you
think ok how did taste
wow you're right that's how he remembered
how you remembered i died and then
you also know your sister died and
you took her play i mean that's
what i mean yeah i forgot that
that part of the store and how
come you don't remember that i'm a
king yeah well eventually we both kissed
you
and kiss you and until finally turned
into a human the smells came before
yeah no took you a lot of
tri-tip saying my prayers buddy i don't
think i got it
but because the soles of my feet
it was very intimate yeah wow's cute
anyway well we've known each other so
long congratulations thing dumb you're a college
grad yeah ding dong we proud of
you you ne yourself ah d o
e o
oh you yeah nah five years ah
wow that was the best song that
has ever been written in sung about
me and that's how you play i
don't remember that way that's a good
yeah
that's a good game dad so yeah
da da dad's a good boy josh
you're done
oh josh thank you josh you did
it again gotta use it again if
you want to join superfan josh and
sending it to three-tier right to freedom
usa jointly by the way join him
go to his house first and then
join him any growth right than to
do a joint email and you know
what you take different sides of the
keyboard like you're doing a duet on
a p
no yeah no one has ever done
that with an email i left true
oh my god you're right yeah making
email history just like bill gates well
guys if you want to get to
know bill gates or you want him
to know more about you get the
vaccine get the vaccine he will find
you wherever you are everywhere you will
your blood with microbes five g chips
five g g
are you looking sauce i'm tired now
sure that you turn the air down
yeah yeah ooh that's probably would return
the air-conditioning off so guise of ah
write to us at three of them
usa and change email dot com and
send us three church zoom usa on
twitter and instagram and you can hear
us anywhere you get your podcasts but
you can hear ad-free episodes at both
stitcher premium and cbp
world dot com and we love you
and we hope to have you in
my day yeah okay okay guys that's
all we have for you sorry bye-bye
episodes ending right now i press stop
press stop on this bus stop on
this joint
stumbled duck a job
uh