three
oh
you're delayed
i'm glad i'm delayed again i feel
like i'm before everyone except after c
before everyone yes of course
hello everyone welcome to three adam i'm
scott
i'm paul
i'm blown yeah glory glory i'm blind
eyed blah blah and i'm bored fuck
ga ga ga ga ga ga ga
ga ga ga hug aww show yeah
i get good guys but the naga
naga naga daughters my pup mad does
spinach brian we can get you anywhere
with your name in it get out
of here ryan yeah looks gay
you have to click hide non participant
hi ha i have to do that
yeah
what else do i have to do
this welcome to the show where we
figure out all of our technical details
right at the top
yeah where we learned zoom one fucking
year
does anyone else think that this day
sucks
business day just to say in general
this day in general i'm actually having
a good day you're having a good
yeah you seemed very cheery lord when
i'm having a good day um yeah
i'm i had like a nice meeting
before this and i'm having a good
day i fucked around and hit a
triple double i looked up at the
goodyear blimp and saw it said ice
cube's a pimp and i was like
like this is you know it's not
bad i fooled around and fell in
love whoa how's your day going bad
then ah because the person doesn't look
back
um do you want to talk about
your bad day ah yes to saying
that day was you talk about bad
days it's it's a first world problems
kind of thing oh let's have reliable
but here's the thing but it led
to me being extremely tired right now
my day was hijacked by something else
now it had nothing to do with
me
me and now i am suffering for
it which always makes me mad when
you have to go move a couch
yep for pizza and beer
which since your six pack of beer
right before the show i yeah i
had an entire pizza a six pack
of beer and i'm tired i understand
god what how old were you the
last time a friend made you help
them move wow it doesn't happen to
girls as much i went on my
way then
should a guess because i i but
i have made a lot of guy
friends helped me move many times over
the years but it's been i haven't
made someone do that in probably four
years someone said no no more than
that five years if you're in your
thirties you should just hire movers yeah
i think when i turn thirty that's
the first time i hired me
rvers i mean that's when you gotta
you told that to me you got
to a point where you realize it's
worth spending the money because it's not
look probably unless you know i'm moving
a mansion to a mansion like if
you're just moving apartments yeah you know
and it's it's not it is more
money than you would like to spend
but it's not a prohibitive
amount of money necessarily can i say
when i lived in new york i
had um i moved here three times
in fifteen months i had a strong
sob but i moved i moved a
lot of times for various reasons but
at one point i was moving from
one apartment to another that was just
around the corner i don't know if
i've ever mentioned this oh huh okay
but sean distin was one who helped
me did damage
now yes yeah oh ever talked about
this spanking pe talked about banking pen
but anyway i just wanna give shawn
a shout out for helping me move
a shout out to sha sha nine
chanel shout out to to shad yeah
chad chad cannibalistic humanoid adult dude that's
fun
other podcast show decimals
um yeah i think i think it's
i don't know what i was gonna
say but moving those but no when
you're in your twenties and you're in
an apartment you're living check to check
yes of course well let's all help
each other yes it's been awhile for
me i feel like i i don't
think i was asked as much as
i asked other people oh yeah yeah
i've moved a lot when i
as younger i feel like i the
last time was when i was working
at gosh cafe cardio
jesus fucking sin the bartender wanted me
to help him move and i assumed
there would be ten people or whatever
like a gather all of his buddies
it was just me and him and
i was so fucking pissed i didn't
even know him that well and i
was so mad i remember he got
taft-hartley by being an ex
ron melrose place but explain what that
means no
jimmy hartley is thrown into a prison
for being an extra on my taft-hartley
agency comes and they get they get
you to have charlie's what happens where
you get a job and then you
are allowed to join sag the union
for act i was half harley's friend
shoot me to have charlie's what happens
to you while you're busy making other
plans yeah i was taft-hartley when i
got my being commercial your bean commercial
beach ca
oh how did that go are people
using bing when were you on successful
being i make commercially successful but i
don't know if being i think being
is still a thing being still a
thing what does the thing feel that
blueberry pancakes animal house animal house that's
right and then there was a food
fight
i don't remember you gotta look it
up scott ah it's a great commercial
i forget when i got i got
tef heart lead for doing a appearances
on a show called the stephanie miller
show oh i remember she had a
late night show yeah sure late night
show she was radio person who had
a late night late night tv show
though
i feel like it was syndicated right
and why yeah right it was but
i appeared as ah as a sketch
player a number of times on that
show that's right did you know her
before or was that like an audition
no i did not ah woman that
i was dating was one of the
writers and she suggested me why that
woman um do you
i think you i don't know anymore
because she's no longer alive oh so
huh
her name in the chat to see
if it's put my name in the
gye jin seasons come in yeah like
wait times it'll mirror and see if
she comes back um just because oh
one of your ex-girlfriends paul look let's
segue to talk about paul's ex girlfriends
because i'm terry
paul's ex girlfriend segment yeah definitely nice
a name that is earning those races
her was it like a drag name
no
yes my girlfriend was a drag
i never found out until we broke
up i wish we could say you
ripped off her wig to say oh
i didn't i did not know that
she was no longer with she passed
away a few years ago yeah um
i didn't keep up with her i
i just remember ah she she drove
us to a party me and my
sister wants and she was driving
in eighty miles an hour down residential
streets and i was like if you
don't slow down you are letting me
out right here i was so upset
i was choose a particular person we
did not have a great relationship lasted
for one year um and i fed
the way i touched on this actually
in a pr
previous episode we were talking about previously
on through perusal we were talking about
people dying and and the feelings that
you have and how strange it is
when someone from your life in some
capacity passes away and you realize you
don't have a strong feeling about it
and how that feels so weird and
monstrous but ah it
but the that does happen sometimes in
your life depending on the people that
are in your life but that's um
she yeah she ah anyone dies i
feel bad about it and even people
i don't know anyone dies i feel
good about it all day i'm crying
because somebody dies
is that what a dieta stands for
yeah
all day i dream about somebody don't
you just ah
but yeah it was she so we
have been broken up for a long
time and then ah so many are
talent superseded that
no no are we still talking about
the stephanie miller show were oh we
really wanna go back to that yeah
i think that's why i thought you
were talking about she's lucky that part
she got me though she suggested me
and i was approved the the producer
at the time was ah a legendary
ah comedy writer who had worked on
the array
original snell and i remember the first
thing that i was supposed to do
was a richard nixon impression and then
put me in full mix and makeup
and everything um well there was some
story that just had just come out
about him that had been released or
whatever and so um the sketch was
very dark suggesting that
richard nixon was actually going to assassinate
j f k but the lee harvey
oswald beat him to it
so as me and nixon you know
actually oh i want yasmin i started
listening to last podcast on the left
episodes about the j f k conspiracy
oh okay what do you think oh
that you can eat well what's crazy
is that there's like six episodes and
the first two don't even get into
it so i honestly have no opinions
yet okay
yeah let us know when you become
a j f k weirdo conspiracy nut
yeah but it was funny cause mike
was like oh let's listen to that
let's listen last podcast on the left
and that's okay annie's like you enlist
a gf campuses and i was like
sure did you hear me talking about
that and you know and i was
like i just said i don't know
anything about that so just a weird
country so already the conspiracy seems to
be a foot
but anyway what so anyway what is
that the title of this episode so
when i'm away would when i was
brought up to um ah perhaps play
this role this richard dixon part ah
this producer called me on the phone
and made me do the impression for
her
yeah and it was horrible it was
really horrible it was like i did
not expect that to happen um and
i did the impression and she's her
immediately review was that's a pretty good
homemade nixon impression but my word like
it's not as good we're looking for
more of like a danny ackroyd nixon
oppression like something really good
good and so i said i'll work
on it i'll work on it and
i was so incense so i was
like who can't do a nixon impression
and then when i finally saw the
sketch after it was done i realised
i can't imagine
i did not do a good nixon
in french soccer to be
ah um and ah yes so that
so ah that was that experience then
but that was the experience where i
got to have a life mask i
had to because they they put prosthetics
on me and so they poured the
goop all over my face and i
was in isolation for you know a
couple hours um i signed
and i really enjoyed you did you
like how it felt when you had
it on i did i really cool
because i've never done that it blacked
out everything around you and you could
yeah be alone with you it was
a sensory deprivation thing like what i
mean like when it was done did
you like be having the face on
face no i did not because it
was still that stuff was still i
mean ah it's come such a long
way but it was like kind of
like you can't ah
you can't um you can't move your
mouth that much you know you can't
like wow you know you had to
be very careful and they had to
do constant touch-ups around any moving part
of your face um but yeah i
said you liked it when it was
poured all over you i liked the
experience you like having a stay still
face
i'm just saying i'm just saying you
when goop is thrown on your face
are escorted or shot on like what
he says come on you
you agreed to do the show with
us this is what you signed up
for a new says is it going
to be gross and bad and we
said yes yeah okay by force training
he wishes he was in the sensory
deprivation tank right now i feel like
what ultraman next that light blinking
it's like hey you gotta go reach
have you ever done one of those
sensory deprivation tanks where you're like floating
in the water no i'd like to
do it though it's like kinda scary
they have them around sailing time yeah
they're all doing good we recorded an
episode and they're like out on the
street it's like a quarter
you just get in the water's nasty
always an ever changing
um i would go do that with
all of you i say thank the
same tank or tank rose i don't
know if we can have sensory deprivation
do you have a legal order to
take the lead to do it together
we'd like to bob and weave into
each other
we'd be like those honors where they
hold hands
yeah
you don't have to hold your breath
though you do you do here it's
very minimal amount of water i think
i know really well you're floating in
it and then there's like an egg
capsule over the top oh okay so
your food star didn't give you something
to float on are you exposed to
water i think so you naturally flow
yes interesting maybe
like you have a raft in there
yeah a couple men it's the size
of a college it's very small it's
the size of your body it's the
size of a coffin but not as
nice i hope it's not the exact
size of my body because i'll never
fit it should be a little bigger
it's it's executive scott's body they they
measured you and now don't know if
you knew about that why they came
oh okay so you did it's like
an iron maiden and their spikes in
it
so um this friend who i'm working
with she has a ah ah history
of night terrors and she's doing a
sleep study this weekend and i'm very
fascinated about this she's getting hooked up
to all these wires and she's sure
like you watch i really wish i
could i'm kind of obsessed with this
and then she she was like i
haven't been having them
lately i'm worried that nothing will be
happening when i'm there and the doctors
say you're crazy yeah you liar she
says in addition we can give her
them if she drinks before she goes
to bed she's gonna have it she's
going to have some wine but they're
nice sleek nice that's the part i
want to go to we want to
drink with her in bed yeah bid
i have to do it so i'm
gonna do a sleep study you are
yes yes story interesting you're wondering are
i'm doing oh no sleep study in
the neighborhood kids
this doesn't sound good though they care
it was i'm asking me to tell
it um yeah i have i met
he has got actually sleep weird um
i have i may have sleep apnea
because i have breathing issues in the
night in the nae nae breathing issues
in the night this ex um wow
oh so you're gonna you're gonna find
out if you need to have a
machine yeah gotta see if i need
a micro machine and um i think
it's like you swallow it and then
it makes you breathe better yeah you
talk really fast yeah
so i have to go i mean
there were two options ah there's one
that i could do at home which
is like they put a house arrest
bracelet on or something and then but
it won't necessarily it it it's not
guaranteed to find an apnea if you
have one feels like they really need
to see you were yes
the in-clinic one you definitely watch you
the whole time and make notes or
they videotape it at least or something
i i think they just i don't
know if anyone's like watching me for
eight hours overnight always assume that there
was someone sitting there in a window
watching you i'm not kidding i really
thought it was like i think of
study you know right like i sit
there i guess
scratch your butt they go huh guys
a little alan partridge reference um i
assume that they just record it and
then watch it later rather than whoring
why not do it weird ate real
time wed so they can with bill
maher parts yeah exactly do we have
the best forty like boring boring boring
oh he's choking
oh and he's dead
i don't know i guess i'll find
out maybe they lie to you like
we'll be here the whole time and
then they go home well i mean
i think one thing just lead to
it's hard to think well no but
maybe on a nightshift but it's weird
to think like going to sleep sounds
coming down yeah if you were getting
the study done i think i might
feel i can be
harder to fall asleep thinking that there's
you know three men watching me through
a window three men was a little
lady
come here my house is haunted yeah
but from the outside i want to
see if the man that sits at
the edge of my bed will be
there for the sleep study my god
i don't want anything to do with
anything like that ah oh no no
my friend told me it's good to
declare that my friend i have said
i have said you can go now
and i'll just say
sage and say 'in your job here
is done in your current house wow
did you have an incident or are
you just this was a precaution no
it was like you know i just
have heard of people doing this and
i was like i'm i'm gonna just
do that i think they would just
feel good just to go hey if
anybody is here you don't need to
be and i before i even could
get scared i just you know my
friend stormy of my friends told me
about it a story we told told
some ghost stories recently and there was
one story about some people who bought
a house with their their family was
a husband wife and their kids and
then they were there one day with
the kids but
kickin was kicked in yeah they it
was only like five percent yeah i
don't find boxy look at hand and
they're like well candy work um so
so there were there one day and
the kids ah they they said hey
so what have you been doing they've
been like oh talking to someone and
yeah it was this
yep ghost and then they saw the
ghost and they literally just put the
house on the market one day after
they moved in wow my god it
was worse than that i mean there
were even worse things that happen to
them but that but yeah they and
then they sold it to like a
gay couple who were like a we
don't care
we emily here i think some people
are the idea of a child saying
i was just talking to so and
so that's that's they check oh that
was part of they checked with the
previous owner and they're like that's a
person who doesn't yeah no that's the
person who died in the house no
no no no no did i not
tell you that no no no no
no but
then people saying go start really i
have a hard time with that because
i'm like you if there's enough stories
of of someone who has no idea
having an experience and then being like
this is the name or this is
what was said and then there's a
factual thing connected to that that's you
can't really argue with that i can
okay yeah i think that
if you're going in a new place
the idea of ghosts is a thing
that we all know and i think
you do wonder about those things when
you enter a new space never heard
of him until like two months ago
goes yeah what do you think now
scary yeah they say boo and shit
i'm not afraid of any ghosts oh
really out of the entirety of ghosts
you're not
trade of a single one not a
single fun gray look at that but
that was it goes on the zoom
for most timeout dog zoom
for howells franny your dog she is
six i think what's your favorite toy
to play with i got yeah she
sits her favorite pushes like toys it
doesn't like toys she normally doesn't either
smalley doesn't either other than occasionally what
she's like phones really apes she loves
others
by me and watch tv and
does and she see the tv do
you know why did you get like
she she reacts to doorbells on the
tv so she has you know some
sort of connection to the television but
you can see in mirrors yeah she
she seems to recognize herself and she
sometimes you can see her hair need
some fresh and we have we talked
about i feel like we've talked no
i don't
oh some dogs can't see in mirrors
yeah it's just it looks like a
wall no no that's impossible i thought
let's hope there was a factual thing
of like dogs see their reflection not
understand what i've what i've heard that
again i'm talking out of my ass
but this is what i've heard you
know that i'm zoomed by the exit
really fucking gross just from your goat
not friends but from what i've heard
some dogs are able to see their
reflection in the mirror and they wonder
what it is and then some just
see it as a blank wall or
whatever well i mean she stares at
herself but i don't know that i
guess i haven't asked what she's thinking
so vain clean haircut well this is
i've already told you about this alright
i'll give it to her jeez oh
my
no i told you i tried to
make an appointment there like we don't
have anything till may and and i
was like i'll call somewhere else and
now mays knows man and i'm like
yeah she's it's she's got the longest
nails in their hairs once you go
to ah okay there's a place by
the comic store i go to called
you wash doggy which is really funny
it's like you have to
supposed to me oh yeah you mean
like a car wash itself i have
no idea i've never know hiring dog
plays it's just it's you dash wash
dash doggie and i've i've always wonder
no deal no deal yeah but i
don't want to watch ah over by
usb they always seem to have oh
yeah washer know watching them there
great call them okay well if we
when we are sponsored by tell washers
by the way we should say when
we really are not gendered this conversation
back thanks for all the koozies
x for all of our toys we
do have a sponsor coming up that
i'm excited about but we don't get
into it yeah let's not get into
it yeah i mean obviously we want
to talk at length it's gonna do
it right now lawrence yeah
do you have look we had a
very popular segment a few weeks back
and it's one of the most popular
segments that we've ever done and it's
called lawrence topics and i think we
wow yeah yeah ok let's hey get
away with your towns time for lawrence
topics the sleep study was kind of
one of them um let's
see what else i guess i'll talk
about that mainly yeah but i brought
it up i didn't know it was
that is lauren topics and that was
lawrence topics okay here's here's how
the gnome is thrive gnome is you
telling us that the gnomes in the
garden and everyone loves it and i'm
and honestly you know what's really great
when i posted it on instagram or
when scott did sorry um the comments
were all so supportive and laughing because
they finally
could see how funny he was
yeah he's so funny the greenery you
know it's like he really came to
life um and then somebody said the
head
someone sent me a website right up
to it's neck really came to life
as a discipline
dude huron bag when when i've come
when i placed him i thought yes
and i um someone someone messaged me
with a gnome recommendation for this website
which i sent to you guys called
gnomes of color and they're really cute
i recommend you will check them out
and they're only ten dollars which i
love to my name
was ten dollars i feel like that's
a really solid loan price or no
price because he no need start spending
sixty bucks i don't know and then
you're like what are we doing here
yeah i want a ten dollar gnome
um they're really adorable
um and their funny little guys go
outfits can i request speaking of the
text chain that we're on can you
stop texting at having texts when i'm
either sleeping or busy
sometimes you don't respond for line town
i'm like what the fuck is he
possibly doing well i worked during the
day and i sleep during the night
so sometimes it's hard to get around
that's interesting so is either of those
know you go to bed as soon
as it is considered night is that
correct yes exactly so yes the sun
goes down like wow it's like saying
i'm so tired
fifteen during the summer
um now every time we do that
and it's just lauren going back and
forth on a three person texts i
my first instinct is to make fun
of scott for not responding my second
instinct is oh no something horrible has
happened and that's we're talking i'm sorry
yeah not thinking i'm usually asleep i
feel like lately my instinct hasn't been
that you guys are dead when you
don't respond
yeah lately it's been good
well i will say the other day
for some reason i was up at
eleven forty five pm and i responded
to one and i was like this
is earth-shattering they're never gonna believe it
and paul i think was asleep or
playing video games auto but ah but
it was crazy i like watching the
things i do would react with like
oh my god scott
what's up he's finally respond to see
no i don't know we don't really
care or notice that you aren't there
like it's sort of like and it's
it's like ornish when you're there if
you want to draw me from the
chain that's what i don't know here's
here's what i mean like i'm not
thinking about what time it is or
what your schedule is but i might
go oh he hasn't replied in a
long time but i wouldn't think oh
it's because he goes to bed at
eight i i'm merely bringing up because
the gnomes of color for some reason
i i missed it entirely and and
then when it's eight hours later it
feels like disingenuous to be like haha
or yeah no one really needs you
to respond at that point but i
really going to order a couple of
them i'll catch up with some tap
backs i don't
care how much time has passed i'll
be like i'm letting you know i've
read this whole thing here's my responses
yeah i try to use all of
them so i'm trying to fill out
tax or topics are kind of like
a problem in a group chain because
yeah just go through and tap backs
if i remember like oh paul like
because
you know it disappears like i'd have
to try to guess what you liked
and certain point because if you gotta
go way up but by that time
she's already hundreds and hundreds of tags
yeah it shouldn't be a notification yeah
nobody should say it should say which
one you liked guys let's invent our
own phones freedom phone now we're talking
free phones what would
be on m would all the numbers
be on him all the numbers from
what anyone wants one to ten instead
of one zero to nine
hey ten bucks okay well already an
improvement you have to press the ten
twice for zero
okay or for twenty sure
this is already great you know what
i kind of want is that flat
flip phone from like samsung that's like
folds and had one that folds in
half those whores will fall fold in
thirds like a bill really yeah ours
are like a piece of paper yeah
and throw it at people and then
it bounces back to you know just
getting into covering
wait so is just a flip smartphone
lauren yeah it's like a it's a
flat like screen like a smartphone screen
and you can fold it in half
but then i'm like then i gotta
be a samsung kid and learn all
ah it takes up more space doesn't
it no it's it's it's like a
square where when how will the staff
yeah it's really cool
but it's yeah i want iphones just
to do that so i can just
get that what our phones have all
the apps on m for just four
you can only say so are we
get one and then we'll vote on
the fourth yeah which one do you
want people away we we decide what
apps other people who buy our phones
have yeah this is the apps that
it comes with you should we
say you can add a fourth app
you can add a fourth yeah next
one is your own adventure yeah but
if you add no matter what app
you add it stays there permanently so
you have to choose wisely yes even
as in-app purchases which app would you
pick maybe i'll pick up a redfin
redfin sega
sucks yeah hey it comes with the
freedom phone oh okay red fit
i think my book is going to
be postmates postmates no not not about
okay yeah so when you buy your
house on redfin and you get food
delivered to it makes sense yeah i
think i waste twenty twenty on postmates
though
okay yeah you do
move on you'll just like sit there
with that too yeah my app would
be anyway
on on that on that topic can
people send simple recipes to lauren she
would like some simple recipes to lots
of me simple recipe simple recipes but
send like the starks recipes to lauren
she'd like to start cooking for bedroom
that neighborhood yeah that is true i
do i would like to cook more
i just don't really want to actually
do it
yes right i wish i was already
doing it not that i will do
it well when yeah when your baby
starts when do they have like real
food daily so you're gonna say when
do they hatch when you're like y
ou like well like six months they
can start eating solids i believe right
but i know what i mean like
baby like dinner like when do this
yeah i've seen it doing
yes i guess i'd be closer to
the same dinner is you know just
a smaller ports eating the same food
finally we all start paying attention they'll
just be like okay i can't just
keep giving her macaroni all the fucking
time because that's writing right yeah my
mom i think was ah she married
my dad and grad
yeah yeah far yeah wait hold on
earth was created in the big game
and by the way we're still waiting
to hear what app pawns but yes
but but my mom married my dad
and yeah that's where i had no
idea how to be a housewife and
her grandmother or or aunt or someone
gave her the betty crocker cookbook and
she just was like in over her
head and looked through it and looked
at certain recipes that she's like i
think i could maybe do that i
don't know what hatch told us this
i'm gonna spank you but i think
that you know i'm gonna say learn
to she learned like four things then
she made those over and over again
made those over and over and over
yeah one was a wedding cake yeah
one was a darth vader cake baked
alaska huh
she did do a darth vader coach
in the pan what do you think
she brought that up out of nowhere
yes because it's awesome it's her bell
cake it is also a second cake
i always think of yeah um my
app would be etsy
okay good and then they can pick
one app for themselves but as they
switch partners into three-team phone they can
take one app but it's one of
three options which will give you goods
that's right that's right and then that
stays there permanently you can't switch out
for anything else ever so my my
offering for the selection is going to
be
b let me see what my like
worst apps are on my phone i'm
gonna go with compass
oh my god compass i've gotta go
stocks come ah i'm gonna go with
ah i-tunes you
university yeah okay great i mean this
i thought of you hopefully they'll be
in college um wonderful so let's get
these on the market we yeah yeah
jonathan numbers it folds and three into
threes we get these odd swag yeah
we get it by next week yes
yeah if we can get a cruk
a shoe charm excuse me if she's
being shoe charm um there are other
shooter ideas that are on the on
the well we got dyed ding dong
of course ding dong who hears my
girl's best friend had paid me a
visit
why as can be tight dress at
all
hello things like along well
we've already talked about things that make
you go hey traditional young daughter with
all the girl's best friend had paid
me a visit flies get me touch
dress at all she knew that was
so she really didn't have well that's
the dvds dvds
no no my girlfriend wouldn't approve of
my san carlos carrasco in the boom
she said
thanks for making you can i ask
you lauren do you remember the between
two ferns audition um when you did
the raps
no you don't remember vaguely that i
emphasized a wrap yeah this is the
first time zach had ever seen you
which is not true well but you
know what i mean like i know
as a as we yeah it was
yeah incredibly familiar with you so i
was like look i want this person
for the part i really think she'd
be great and he's like no no
no no
no and so you came in and
you you did a rap about trump
i think and then laughed all the
way through it
ah and he was sold
like yeah that's great like you couldn't
get three lines in without bursting out
laughing
yeah that makes sense i can't believe
lauren wasn't all i did yeah audition
twice i can't believe that you had
to audition twice when i was offered
a one line role i know it
wasn't online those two like you who
make your online and you turned it
into full chose to have to roll
lines they won't all go in
i edition twice i had to improvise
with sac and i had to improvise
by myself i think and then i
had and then i i pimped myself
into doing a rap i think i
don't know yeah like you it was
i think the situation was the way
it's got you froze froze oh lauren
okay let's talk about what we've really
think about scott okay so
that whole thing that he said about
how his parents got married was a
lie i know right i know it's
parents and they're still not married they're
like big hippies his dad was ever
in the military i know his parents
were so chill there so always let
him do whatever he wants yes he
like is he re
reigns supreme in that household
now he's gone it's just god this
is like when he got that phone
call and we had to just like
vamp for like forty five oh yeah
you left the studio wait and then
everybody left and it was just me
what i was just naming stabilizing i
left eventually as a joke
if i remember correctly or you just
bored
yeah it's my board but anyway yeah
edition twice isn't that crazy it is
crazy and janet feels like at a
certain point like what i gotta do
to prove it but you know i
got it how come i didn't get
to audition i mean manga wow i
don't know you didn't believe that's good
you didn't have to audition but but
no i'm saying i could have auditioned
for bigger role right
right that is true i mean i
don't know you think eating scott feels
bad
no i don't i don't i think
i think he i think he put
me in that movie to humiliate me
and i'll never think otherwise wow yeah
wow yeah yeah yeah he tried to
date he was in big dog in
me he's big dog in me yeah
he's like just you just say your
one line buddy oh scott hi hi
where were you guys talking about just
shakes
oh it's just shitting on you're still
frozen though really my internet so your
your max headroom me right now ah
continue well anyways ah what was i
talking about before all of that
before the zac audition we were talking
about the apps that were going to
the apps you could choose to portray
okay so i chose docs and you
chose yeah oh i tunes you okay
than we did yeah we did settle
that and we said let's get into
the store oh and then i got
into the the this things that make
you go hmmm ok ok we're back
so we're all good we're back okay
well it's time to take a break
have you buying huh okay hi bye
alright so we have all stopped our
video and now we're doing this is
like this is going after dark this
room after dark this is like we're
a sleepover and we're giggling in the
us like we're in the sensory deprivation
tank next to each other oh wow
this is like that yeah
you know i can see the room
around me and i'm like yeah turn
off all your lights it's broad daylight
there's my god
kiffin bed or you know or you
know lights during the day kind of
guy in your house well i'm in
my office and i shown there's plenty
of natural life so i don't need
the um the consider your office to
be part of your house
but it's not part of my home
drew okay but do you ever sleep
in there
sometimes changing identified
how many times have used have have
you slept in a different room
your times if you have um over
over the night never
you always make up we all we
always make up this scripture says do
not look at the sun set on
your anger yeah it surely does it
surely does it surely does surely i
want to see you guys ah you
misses us yeah i want to say
i don't like it i'm telling in
my own like it either i feel
very disconnected like i can
do whatever i want it's weird ah
i'm rapping you honest here like yeah
i wanted it's weird it feels like
i'm like free and i'm like that
makes me distracted i feel drunk with
power i need to be seen in
order to be on task oh not
me i was fine staring at my
laptop displaying my full name
i've done a podcast so as a
guest where it was on zen caster
where i get with your phone basically
yes i did that with you and
it's saudis wait what would we do
with that because i think was we
did that in zen caster yes he
did why did i don't because it
was at the beginning of the pandemic
ad
and i think you guys just invested
in zen caster
because i don't remember that at all
i did want to sort of reason
yeah for something else
well do you remember every day i
get to do you get to do
a movie i wanted to do and
then it sucked po
well mostly i wanted to evinces on
this upload saturday what movie did you
do i did um did i do
rise of skywalker or did the force
awakens the force awakens so i wanted
to do the last jedi but i
was your producer at other plants do
they just decide i don't know i'm
not blaming you i said the producer
is this your first fight no i
don't think it's is it a fight
yeah it's our first and from your
perspective it's this is crazy
wow
you're getting your friends over your zoom
background about you that's causing a problem
too you know i bet that will
help about that will help huh alright
i'll turn off my zoom but every
year i'm like a hoarders room full
of a thousand newspapers even know how
to do it how do i go
to turn it on and shiraz it
i know where i can find it
hit the carrot next to stop video
and then no two backgrounds hit dat
kino and there oh there it is
backgrounds and filters none there we go
hello guy there he is remember this
much better but it is better it
is better actually yeah okay um alright
i think it's time for a new
feature on the show and it's called
paul's topics
alright now we're getting creative we're getting
down to brass tags ah
my topics today are as follows
when in the course of human events
surely
one place owner since when in the
course of human events i will start
over every single time when in the
course of human events so interrupted yourself
that time and started over but i
still did i say whatever i'm interrupted
i booked start over all right what
are the goals of you at events
it behooves us all to see the
times in which we are alive and
say
say aha what do i do to
take advantage of these times in which
we live i don't have ah i
don't need any topics oh what's the
best invention of all time by bulb
my bulbs good my phone bills light
bulbs good can be fatal engines ah
sure i will say in downtown abbey
when they yeah sure no examples please
downtown abbey he does know what the
best don't fall for it when they
when the light bulb was invented it
didn't seem to make their lives that
much better
i love on shows like that ah
period things where there's a new invention
that we're that is old hat to
us and people are against it yeah
well that's like everything now electric light
why what is wrong with a stub
of candle it's like me talking about
lefties no but that's bad that's actively
bad but you don't know that maybe
i do
let me like that actually was really
good oh we know now that it's
know i know but it is like
i'm sure there are inventions that we've
pushed back on you know we're we're
like do we need him you know
when the other thing is i feel
like we we as humans we can
never imagine the next thing like you
can never be dancer
but i like this or are we
that yeah but you never go like
you know you always think like we
don't need a phone to do more
than it does now and then they're
gonna figure out a way to make
it do more than it doesn't gonna
go how did i ever live without
this why didn't want a cell phone
for years because i didn't want people
to feel like they could get a
hold of me yeah and now
when i was we can and my
friend said okay i'm not gonna get
one in less in a month i
three separate times think oh god it
would be good to have a cell
phone right now and if that happens
then i'll go ahead and get one
and he it ended up like three
times in one month he was like
oh god it would be nice to
be able to make a phone call
right now
so we got one and then i
got one and the other was right
alexander graham bell but like in in
the past you know um since you
guys were older than me when you
didn't have a phone yet you still
are yeah did you feel like i
mean i feel like you can say
yeah how much
any times doing thinking the day that
i wish i cell phone you once
you know it's a thing but before
that you got through everything fine you
figured out a solution to everything well
you know what i phone the thing
that made me get a cell phone
was being on a set and not
being able to call on a place
to say that i was gonna be
late ah
i was double booked this was i
think i told the story was i
was doing the movie magnolia and news
radio on the same day you're in
mongolia yeah i don't like things and
avoid ever seen magnolia ah you should
see it i haven't seen it since
it came out but i'd like to
see it again i've every paul thomas
anderson movie i watch and i say
i can't wait to watch that again
and then i never watch
any of them twice now i don't
think this makes this question make sense
but is that how you know me
man
no i knew a man first from
largo yeah lagosians yeah like paul thomas
anderson cast a lot of his movies
through the largo scene yeah well i
mean
not the main parts no but he
would drink he would sprinkle people in
it was like a fun thing yeah
yeah cool um but i was so
i was doing it's just a voice
overall really um but i had to
be there on the set ah to
do the phone call live with philip
seymour hoffman right and so i'm there
and i
and i'm like i have to i'm
going i i'm doing a news radio
which is a live multicam sitcom like
there's an audience there you can't leave
another chinese e f g yeah and
i can ask you to you know
i keep asking like are we closer
what's going on and of course they
just tell you like yeah and he
said this we're all
almost done you know and of course
most of it was just the setup
that was happening in another room you
know i'm just like sitting in the
kitchen of this place to be on
the job be live on the phone
and i got there i got there
late ah to news radio but still
on time to do the show but
i got there after
things like after the cats have been
introduced at the top of the show
um and you didn't get your claps
i think my claps like our claps
in the end um but i i
that have the day after that i
got a cell phone wow wow interesting
yeah
um remember how by the way there
an article came out recently vulture maybe
about the the start of the alternative
comedy scene which i thought neither you
or i paul were mentioned because it
was like two years before ryan got
there right before i got there something
like that but i thought it was
it just made me remember all these
things
sounds about like how we because we
we could only communicate about where we
were all hanging out that night via
phone we all had to somehow have
a big long game of telephone where
you had to be home at some
point during the day and around when
someone would call you in order to
get the
the automation of but i mean answering
machines existed
you don't have to you didn't know
yeah so you anyway i guess oh
no yeah yes
but it seemed like we always had
to like it leave your job to
the sterling draper cooper price and then
ah no but at the time didn't
seem like you were talking on the
phone way more than you do oh
yeah yeah yeah i went when one
landlines were where everything i talked on
the phone i would have no problem
talking to vote for hours and then
once it became cell phone
ones that i hated i grew to
the test talking on the phone right
i don't know it's just like so
how often do you talk on the
phone now with like people are hardly
ever just a business thing but hardly
ever yeah yeah like it's a little
foamy i'll be like okay okay like
trying to get off after five whenever
it's just like even when we're on
tour
or whatever it's just like i don't
know i can't stamping on the phone
anymore i don't know why yeah i
talked on the phone probably at least
an hour a day really your your
homies from back home or your mom
usually my mom we talked on the
phone every day um and then beyond
that i don't know i feel like
i end up on the phone
and i have like some friends who
i've had like like arden and i
will like send voice memos back and
forth which is basically like talking on
the phone and that's kind of fun
and i feel it but i feel
like not it's not my not all
my relationships are phone relationships but i
do have a few where it's like
alien and if and then i have
some people i just check in with
every you know
oh so often and talk with every
couple of months you know for an
hour or for a while instead of
texting i would video myself saying whatever
i want to say and send out
and that was fun but just like
me that's like marco polo exactly you
could've been rich marco polo was pretty
fun for a while like wild horses
we were using that for a bit
and it was pretty enjoyable and i
was doing with a couple other people
and then there were some people i
wasn't even that close with that i
was marco polo in with i was
like i get marco polo from ken
marino and mike hey you know it's
gonna we would know why would we
ever talk on face time um but
i got a few portables for people
i don't know that well yeah joined
they're just in my contacts or i'm
in theirs or whatever
and it's like oh okay is this
i felt like instant pressure like oh
no is this like a social networking
app where people are just you who
had to respond yes people are just
doing it out to the void whole
day yeah it was the i think
that app kind of felt like a
lot of pressure at a certain point
especially when i say we're getting to
know i never received a
marco polo i have no idea what
you're talking about so you got oh
so it's an app what did you
sign up now well then that's why
you never got one oh ok it's
close to you i thought i thought
it was like linkedin requests where luno
is basically markopolos so yeah premise is
like the game marco polo where one
person says mark when the person's polo
you send a little short video that
person responds to the videos and they
just don't the guy dude it's a
great guy he's just short videos back
and forth but it's kinda it was
really fun for a second but for
a second it's like remember to periscope
yeah so it was like going live
on instagram because a which is what
it became but periscope i thought was
cool for two seconds and then everything's
boring after a month isn't it yeah
now every three row ah hell yeah
i think so wish i could last
a month it's fun to last a
month like you wanna just fuck for
like thirty days straight
owning no food one please yeah
why are you showing me today day
fuckin
alright we have to take a break
okay
and we're back and it's time for
three church yea one part of the
show to some people and the worst
part of the show to others for
me for me it's why i do
the show really wow this is what
we do um this is called win
lose or
banana sides by submitted by rhys makes
words who i feel like has submitted
other things for comedy bang bang maybe
ah okay so this is how it
goes two of us are the one
one person picks is the picker will
say paul
while you're yawning the biggest yawn i've
ever seen you yawn well i'm glad
you called attention to it does it
make you want to yawn again makes
me wow
my
wow um
okay so one person is going to
pick between the other two people the
other two people yep scott i don't
understand we're talking about oh i pay
one one person is gonna pick so
like paul say you're the picker it's
going to be me and lauren between
me and lauren we text each other
or about about who is the banana
so you and i will decide who's
the banana yeah okay and and then
we both try to convince the picker
to pick us okay and if the
picker picks the banana they win
okay and so how do we what
do we mean by we try any
means necessary okay
alright alright so you would paul do
you want to be the picker for
the first one so for example sure
okay so lauren let's decide between us
who is going to be the banana
um and i'm texting you right now
my theory of who is the banana
about this idea of who is the
banana we got him in loser banana
we've got itself okay all right paul
oh hello potential bananas
i understand you'd like to pitch well
you certainly have to make a case
to me the bigger well i am
dying to be picked and i wish
you would look i'm gonna give it
to you straight i'm the banana i've
always been the banana i want to
be picked i want to be eaten
i want to be peeled these are
all banana things that only a banana
would know please pick me if anybody
who's really the banana would not need
to say i am the banana and
i like to be picked and peeled
okay it's a given for the banana
to like those things i am the
banana i'm not even gonna tell you
about that i'll tell you about other
stuff that i'm into being dipped in
chocolate
being put on a peanut butter sandwich
i'm like she doesn't even know that
you can be frozen as a banana
i know these things i'm a banana
pick me i'm obviously the banana i
can't even spell it be a n
a n a a e
that's not how you spell it spi
a n a n a e
no two ways from now but by
now i'm fellow band ban on ah
look i'm paul i don't need to
convince you i'm yeah no you do
i'm afraid pot over it i'm gonna
be obviously scott is a liar i'm
one hundred percent the banana i am
not lying i swear
swear to god i'm gonna read you
the text exchange that we had earlier
okay i sent lauren the text that
said i'll be the banana and she
wrote back sounds good alright actually happy
news that that texas but i'm the
banana and wrote the word you and
i put a thumbs up on it
meaning me
okay why don't you show me your
phones and then i'll make my decision
unfortunately we don't have our three-time phones
yet so we can't show you the
phones but you did text each other
and then you promptly disposed of your
current phones we use them away because
we know we wouldn't need them anymore
personally if all you want to ask
any questions to kind of get down
to business with yes yes yes yes
yes ah if you're a banana ah
what do you like best to be
yellow green or brown look i love
being brown because i know you know
then my my life is almost over
i know i'm either going to be
eaten or thrown in the trash at
that at that point so i love
being brown i'm up at dan
anna
i love being yellow because that's when
i'm at my peak and people all
want to pick me when i'm yellow
which is what i am right now
which is why you should pick me
the answer was green butler and was
closest alright second question i would all
be green that's for me to know
and for the banana to find item
equipment maybe he's the banana
second banana question banana split what goes
on top and what goes on bottom
like the maraschino cherry is at the
very peak of a banana split and
at the bottom there is a layer
of chocolate syrup and glue and melted
ice
cream banana lord now the way i've
been asked what it works is there
is a layer at the bottom of
not melted ice cream it's nice juicy
big plump rolls of ice cream with
a nice thick banana on top with
melted is obscene okay to hot glue
all over
the top guo stuck with two little
cherries on top as well and it
is so good and everyone loves it
and just because scott is confidently answering
first doesn't mean that he you could
have done that as a banana it's
true i just know the answers and
you're both wrong the bottom advantage flip
is
the serving dish and the top is
a risk own coming in
i don't consider the utensils if he
part of the is something non banana
would say
no no no sir no sir i
obviously do consider those to be the
final question
what do you why do you think
that more americans can't find america on
a map
laura as a banana my answer to
that i'm gonna jump in here i
think that this is mainly due to
america's educational system because more and more
money is going towards things in the
government that don't matter like ah you
know our our armed services and computers
and defensive
of time that paternal ok a banana
wouldn't know the answer to that i'm
simply a banana i want to be
eaten that's my only life goal i
don't really care where i am on
the map so please eat me and
pick me i'm the banana alright i'm
ready to make my decision alright i
believe the banana is scott but i'm
picking lauren
yea it's me yeah
you won i won i won ba
na een okay so for the next
one i think we should be a
different fruit or vegetable but this idea
hold win loser banana yeah but because
we already kinda made banana based topics
i don't think i want yeah banana
suffered reese makes words and we make
our own rules whoa okay who's the
picker
i am okay so and the topic
is coconut cocoa coconut cocoa not all
right so are your next gummy you
three texts me
you text me your choice and i'll
i'll agree or disagree
of tension is palpable
yeah it's okay almost don't care i'm
helping it
okay okay okay great
okay first question is am i the
banana
no you're you're not the banana we're
talking co i mean coconut am i
the cortina no you're not the coconut
you all been out as though huh
okay so um whoever wants to start
please plead your case as to who
is the coconut alright listen a lot
of people give me a hard time
for being in some easter candy but
look
i didn't ask to be put in
there and when you grow up you'll
probably grow to like me so shut
up also i got milk in me
that's not really milk it's water but
for me it's milk for you it's
water but please call it milk outta
respect i am a coconut
cayenne brown and furry on the outside
and inside i'm delish
okay
wow look i sure do i remember
when scott ackerman went to hawaii for
the first time with his parents and
they got one of me and thought
it would be really cool to put
a straw in it and wow coconut
milk straight from the coconut and it
was gross yeah i remember that was
i insulted no i don't care about
those kind of
things because people love me i'm a
coconut sure i follow on people's heads
and give them amnesia all the time
probably ten percent of the world has
had a coconut fall on their head
and has given them amnesia and they
forgotten where they are for the rest
of it and who they are for
the rest of their lives but look
that doesn't bother me i'm a coconut
i'm cool put sunglasses on me
i look fucking awesome i'm a coconut
pick me thanks a true coconut would
know that i also fall on the
same heads and bring them back out
of amnesia this is coconut amnesia one
one i love to be chopped in
half with a machete i love to
be scooped out and then i like
like you to make a drink and
be drinking with a fancy straw
okay look i'm a quirky whoever can
say with the most conviction that they
are the coconut looking arise yeah okay
which is the webcam yup i'm see
me i'm looking right into your eyes
yes lauren is looking at money out
without hesitation
i can tell you i am the
coconut you have to pick me if
you want to win
okay
laura
you know in your heart who the
coconut is and you know that the
coconut is me i've never lied to
you before but i'm not starting now
i'm the coconut and you can take
that to the bank baby
lauren he's lied to you before hazarding
i'm sure yeah yeah we obviously knew
someone i'd you before the zone and
i don't intend to start now
i would never say i've never lied
because obviously i've lied to you i've
lied to every single person i've ever
come into contact but i never say
who can ever say i'd lie to
you okay
um i'm ready to make my decision
oh my god okay if it's me
cool if it's three he's out you
know whatever now i believe that it's
scott but i'm gonna say it's paul
it's got garza
loser you are the loser that sucks
this was our text exchange politics and
be me who cares and i wrote
back no
so it was
okay
fair enough scott is the picker i'm
a picker i mean okay dare we
go pineapple next i don't know to
tropical i feel like i want something
not a coco nah no but i
want an avocado guys yeah okay yeah
guys text each other
her who's the avocado and if the
other person agrees that that person is
the avocado and it takes ah it's
a bold move to disagree
last time
alright they're texting each other we have
deleting come to an agreement okay
hi guys i'm a very busy person
i want an avocado today i'm not
going to tell you what i'm gonna
do with it but i just want
one and i know one of you
guys is an avocado so give me
your pitch who's the avocado which one
scott let me just say
you know why guac is extra because
it's made out of me baby and
i am a big deal ah millennials
can't buy houses because they love you
so much
i am a strange texture that you
think you don't like but it turns
out you do like it you can
put me on a sandwich you can
mash me up and put me on
chips you could do whatever you like
with me i don't care just don't
cut your fucking hands off while you're
trying to cut me in half please
i want you to be
happy tear me to pieces and enjoy
no sky scott scott scott scott makes
a compelling case i might just pick
him right now i don't know i
am the avocado and i'm gonna be
really honest with you i'm not always
good sometimes i look like i'm going
to be good and then you cut
me open and i'm nasty little brown
mush and my little rock-hard middle is
the main evey
went okay
finding all of these very sexually
i people want want me but they
when they get me they might be
disappointed because it's ah there's a small
window of time where i'm fantastic and
when i'm fantastic i'm fucking perfect and
everyone's in love with me but that
window passes by so quickly so it's
really i'm a risky thing but i'm
telling you by being
so honest about it you know that
i am actually the avocado
it's interesting you're looking you're looking down
into the left every time you say
you're the avocado oh lee harvey oswald
i am the avocado
that was cross-eyed
sky sky lauren is full of pretty
words but you know she's not full
of a big crazy rock hard marble
that if you don't if you don't
get around it right you're gonna fuck
yourself up look i'm an avocado and
here's another fact about me
that i know and love is that
rats can't get enough of me so
if you have an avacado tree you'd
better be prepared to have some avocado
rats because they love me and aren't
humans and rats so similar in so
many ways
we both like to be in houses
that aren't ours we both like we
both like ciara's we both had songs
sung about us by michael jackson i
am the avocado and you can say
for sure that i am not the
mikado because that is a cancelled opera
beretta by gilbert and sullivan avocado out
i don't want to
belabor the point i'm the avocado there's
nothing more to it it's that simple
when i texted i said i want
to be the avocado please let me
and paul said okay
huh i remember differently i remember when
we texted lawrence said should i be
the avocado no way it should be
you and i said are you sure
if you really want this i want
you to have it and she said
no paul you should be the avocado
i don't want to be selfish ooh
la sounds too long for a texture
change that yeah mine was it really
was present during it was a lot
of predictive phrases oh that's true that's
a good point he's a liar okay
i'm running as a lawyer's lawyer i'm
right no fight a little more he's
a liar lauren lies all the time
she's friends you know and as the
prince of lies we don't have to
insult each other really get personal laurie
guys a lot more thought allying lauren
wouldn't know the truth of it fuckin
put a fuckin fear and shouldn't even
ask him a question because i always
always gonna lie for no reason it's
always best to ask what her name
is she'll say it's roger
what's your name roger
oh god i tell ya alright i'm
ready to make my decision okay um
i think paul knows the most about
avocados but is not a lot like
ourselves we don't really know ourselves that
well you know so i don't know
that avocado would know itself all that
well and really that
whole text exchange was way too long
i thought it was you paul until
then i'm gonna go with lauren lawrence
the avocado it was a u eighty
yeah
i won palsy only winner two out
of three congrats paul thank you it
feels when you won one out of
three
no i want to well yes i
mean i guessed correctly i picked only
a winner if you guess the avacado
otherwise there's my god
and that's how you slay win lose
or bizarre na january speaks words lesson
thank you everybody as of this recording
the shoe charms are back in stock
so get those there's a lot of
other fun merch but the freedom store
pouch wag dot com um so make
this the year for the rest of
twenty two
any one you are going to be
decked out head to toe hand treat
him gear we talked about marino cherries
earlier were selling freedom hats with instead
of a little button at the top
with a maraschino cherry at the top
that say three m on him so
go get us based on you if
you don't have crocs yet we are
not sponsored by crocs we don't have
crocs yeah inexplicably i know you need
them now because you have to fill
all the holes with giblets every hole
that you chose she kills the hell
every hole with shoe chai every hole
with shuichi oh arms clery imam by
rocco
i had fun i also had fun
i'll see you guys soon right like
all right we'll see you next week
love everyone vi
uh