sorry
dementia cinema
i think you said
that's an i didn't say well i
watch it every single time except for
this one
oh my god she actually did not
say predicted the future i
i'm getting goosebumps i'm getting goosebumps i'm
getting goosebumps
ah goose flesh so gross pimply goose
flesh we've talked about that right i
don't know already have that time she
gave me goose flesh now i'm in
my head about have we talked about
everything
there's some idiots why everyone i ever
started telling you that we have i
think i have something i think we
haven't talked about oh i'm lauren by
the way hey i'm scott i'm paul
and i'm intrigued okay so this is
a test for men um just remember
you're in for an interview
um yeah it's just me
um ok so i have a question
for you about a pronunciation thing but
i don't want to i don't want
to show you the word i don't
want to tell all the words he
was really no no no so it's
a gynecological um pussy procedure that women
get yearly okay hysterectomy
says the key is it perhaps smear
a homo how do you say i
say pap smear i know my girls
i don't see cause two people said
that in the last couple of weeks
now is like new both men yeah
and i was like men think gets
pap smear they think it goes on
a bagel it's the only time they
hear the word smear
schmear yeah yeah and so they think
schmear is smear i think they do
interesting yeah you're the queer
terrible game from our youth um alright
well then i guess it wasn't homophobic
at the scene that i never thought
it was when i never did i
always thought it was the odd person
i mean i thought you have talked
about this and i know we've talked
about that thanks i know we have
there was an episode long discussion was
on a very special three
oh wait i'm speaking of the head
in front of your face yes what
i i when i was a kid
i remember hopefully we was a teenager
prime age when you're like am i
gay
trying to figure out like what if
i think about this does it do
anything oh wait that kind of thing
haha and somebody said um oh look
at your fingernails and so it's the
oh so how you hold your how
you hold your hand yeah right like
because women will hold their hands out
and look at the nails like what
their fingers raised
men is like see will already girls
are fingers in and look i beg
your pardon you know how inglorious bastards
they could tell that someone was a
spy because he said i'll have two
drinks seem to this way was it
it was because i don't remember that
it sounds dumb as shit yeah because
because germans do with this way all
right like key european
out with the thumb first and then
yeah yeah and he said i'll have
two more drinks and they immediately zeroed
in on him and said you're a
spy pretty contest pretty good test if
you make it up it's a pretty
good test actually meeting enough the number
one thing in spy school though is
the fire re the fingers remember where
fingers go in different countries yeah like
this one for instance
that's really in certain countries the middle
finger that number one they start with
that yeah you go one ten thinky
second merch then you get the pinkies
out there for if you if you
really want to get away with your
spine you get the barney so i'll
have two beers your mouth
or just don't hold your fingers up
oh my god you say tail please
yeah wait how were your fingernails when
you did that which way how are
they right look at them i think
i looked at them the lady woman
and i was like oh no no
sooner than i ever get to it
then i forgot about it and i
just remembered it the other day
i go no i got barry doe
oh
ah the only way to really know
is if you if you try it
out right not true she'll know speaking
of men we owe those rascally oh
okay what did they up to now
this new segment paul's men that's right
ladybugs take a breather huh umm we
women can't listen to you talk about
men no i'm talking about men to
men oh okay well women will be
interested okay women won't be interested i
don't think so alright let's test it
out alright look at your nails okay
um if you're thinking
with your fingernails up don't listen okay
ah we were on a we went
to las vegas well yeah that's right
yeah so the concert i don't wanna
say we saw miranda lambert's velvet rodeo
you didn't want to say because if
you want to keep that private i
didn't want to say just a personal
thing that happened to you i don't
think of it that way i
i try to be more restrained about
what i say auto mike everyone's oh
sure every once in awhile you all
say basically anything to us but you
won't share you know miranda case that's
private other people's things i don't want
to say no it's true it's true
it's his journey he went on so
how was that thank you for respecting
that yeah
um on the way there ah we
were boarding the plane southwest ah what
i love about that is you can
board from the back in the front
and ebay it's true about burbank and
can you access it from the back
you can depending on when you get
back upper butt that's right no exit
only oh so
you don't put tp up there
your home is just a winch this
isn't dry wipe isn't very right
just are judging women not to listen
yeah
yeah but entertaining the men so great
here's what happened we had separator oh
yeah sneeze we sneeze
should we tell people what's going on
i know signing the fucking book yeah
neo beeps all she's signing my pages
right now and i'm trying to do
about talking great job you're doing pretty
good paul did half the books and
he did so many things so many
here's the journey doing ah plus a
small pool shares the journey with i'm
so
scott
whoa like a pro on border posts
come on that um yeah so ah
it's so scott asked me emails me
and says would you like to sign
some books you don't have to do
it would you like to do this
and i said yeah i'll sign a
bunch of em but i said it
like you had to do it yeah
because i might know more likes you
will sign them yes in march
ah so then ah korean um what's
that the baker you call her the
back the baker yeah so the baker
said but cut the previous part id
yeah um beep it so the baker
ah say less room by the way
scott
graham oh man wow he doesn't shove
and we miss you shadow air for
the show um she okay you don't
have to chime in quite so much
to prove you're paying attention so um
so so the baker says is doing
the baker says ah okay i'm going
to drop off five book
five boxes of books and i was
like jesus christ and then she showed
up with the five boxes and i
carry them inside i'm like god damn
this is a lot of books and
then i opened the buff
i see in the book it's not
books it's endpapers so it's joe billion
papers yeah it's likely not changing much
as like twenty five books i'm only
way like books for sure what any
of the books so i really i
laughed and i texted lauren almost immediately
i said look what happened to me
when i was a high use
yeah i don't but paul you did
them you did four boxes in the
first night yeah because yeah pupil yeah
i mean i can definitely get lost
in a task like that it's short
it took me less time than i
thought it was going to take me
because i did twice as many zoo
and of course you zoomed of course
you did anyway okay see you in
vegas you saw miranda what to vegas
we get
on the southwest here's what happened we're
on separate reservations on the same flight
so we can't check we can't check
his privilege and interesting rangers so you
meet anyway oh this was this yeah
we're both wearing trench coats with no
closing you always fly southwest you can
like try to find each other yeah
exactly like oh you already growing we
get by joining aisle seats though we
start make
going out furiously across your trench coats
come oh yeah and your raging hearts
rights come out you don't know where
it was going
so i see that the early bird
option is available for you pay a
little money you get in the eighteen
because otherwise you have a seat yes
exactly which is exactly what happens so
you so you because do people get
mad if you save the seat you're
not you're not technically allowed to do
but when you're a you know ones
trying to sit next to each other
yet and then just you have a
minute you haven't so people are trying
to really fill those middles or cheney
we do she was in group b
and she was like towards the end
of group okay but beginning of b
is great yeah and to be bad
news right yeah so be for bad
news so she um ah also we
always
do adjoining aisle seats instead of sitting
right next to each now why is
that sweetie it's just easier it's just
easier because no one has to be
in the middle we both liked the
aisle ca and nobody has to be
in the metal and you're not jumped
up on each other other than if
you have kids and you need to
pay attention to them yeah you have
to sit next to each other anyway
i don't know a whisper about the
flight attendants also
we went to we went to a
restaurant this is fast forward and we
went to restaurant great restaurant called ah
rounds a taste of siam i forget
the name of it but it's so
good and we sell our was it
in in las vegas i can't remember
where in las vegas but in the
city within the city limits isn't okay
good to know all right well so
some sort of chinese restaurant it's
thai restaurant yeah right yes and we
saw multiple couples sitting on the same
side of a tow yeah which never
came up likes it that's early relationship
stuff for me yeah sure it's a
treat for her when i allow her
to wow that's sweet of you to
do i find it very weird and
even when we're meeting another couple and
we will sit
on the same side to wait for
the other couple i'm like praying please
let them get here because i don't
want people to think because it's not
about it's just weird why are you
how's your knees might look at each
other it's like weird to be sitting
side by side is like any island
copilot of dumb man take like your
body can you lose next you know
let me very few
dj it out and let me feed
you in the bay my in cold
places of horse we will wear a
big sweater together and sit next to
you when you have a sweater with
forearm exactly exactly so so okay so
we want to jump ahead okay yeah
go back i get on the plane
first i save a story heating up
put my backpack backpack on the seat
next
ks to me oh perfect on the
seat across from me i mean so
oh that's hard yes that's harder you're
trying to save an aisle people want
the aisle i think you're saving a
middle so i don't know semi know
this is where it's getting pretty difficult
day exactly exactly exactly but two people
a couple get into jane's row they
sit down to the aisle still open
okay right that works
so she finally gets on file oh
and she's got a rolly bag and
now of course there's no room in
the overheads and so above my my
overhead mug my seat there's a bag
that sideways right and so i go
to can turn it the i go
to turn in the other room and
then i hear this little voice oh
was it a rat was
that amount i wish
it was a it was a big
baby who'd grown into a man but
was still a baby oh no biggie
yeah he's a couple he's a couple
of rows ahead let's see any guy
he's a couple rows hey i even
know yeah he doesn't even pro what
exactly i can't i hear this guy
go it doesn't fit that way put
it back yeah and i'm like
what would i turn around and also
you got on my plane you'll come
to that conclusion if that is true
yes like shop so i i i
so he sees me trying it and
ah jane anyway so i i turn
around and get out where janey yelled
to you
now you've got something out of the
story you were like yeah anyway no
no no i'm i'm i skipped doing
it for length so ah i'm telling
i was out of order for a
second we were all at abortive
and that's out of balance sorry life
out of balance so i turned my
life this guy and he says this
podcast ah it's major score so i
look at him and he says again
it doesn't fit that way we'll turn
it back i'm sorry back are you
this is where i shot
his thing off the plane and i
say i say okay man so okay
pardon he's saying put it back because
you're touching his suitcase or no histories
yet are nowhere near you know his
note this is a suitcase oh okay
so that's why he's mad okay i'm
just being sure he has a reason
to be charming but he does jack
still does it he doesn't ever really
listen but i'm saying hey it's his
item yes
this item and he's very protective of
it and it's in there he's those
kind of jane's theory wow guys i'm
going to commence still do yeah i
never for a second thought that it
was about what was inside i'm sure
it was just like no just my
luck yeah no i'm yeah sure it's
not so i say okay man okay
we just you
no we're looking for room to put
the suitcase away and that happens every
second yeah right and so janie then
has to like go back behind her
herself and put it in a in
a in an overhead bin a few
rows away feed antigo then more people
get so janie sits down more people
come on the plane somebody tries to
do the same thing with this guy's
bag to z l m
yeah he's watching this thing like aw
hey does it fit that way put
it back you think you would relax
so but i think now he had
to do it again because he's shown
that he cares and janey tells me
she reveals she finds out from the
people ahead of next to her that
he did it before janie got onto
oh i didn't know so this guy
just been watching this back
so this high reporting process or like
this guy's now yeah exactly cause also
what you should do if that's your
bag is let it be fucked with
because you look like you're wrong for
bringing the wrong sized bag and yes
don't just make it exam exactly you
have to wait do you get the
here's what you flight attendants then the
authorities involved well eventually i mean this
guy this guy got his way yeah
you're quite right and he's he's sitting
with a woman next to him she
says nothing right of course she's like
yeah stoned silent ignore terribly i think
my husband is a pri husband is
in charge the bible tells me so
so um yes my husband is just
so at the end of so we
land and uh
i'm at the end of the flight
when it was all worried that story
you just were going to fly around
your way we were still on the
plane yeah and now you're on the
plane too
so everybody's getting their luggage and then
i'm i'm talking to janie and then
i hear somebody say excuse me and
i turn around and it's the guy's
wife now she says oh could you
get my bag please and i say
loudly oh this bag this is it
this one and people are fucking laughing
it's so
it's so satisfying it doesn't fit the
other example i can touch it now
yeah exactly oh my god that's amazing
so then ah and germany look he'd
know it bugged janie so much it
stayed with her for such a long
time ruined it for me not not
quite but it was like ob still
thinking about that yeah
but to me it was it was
so funny because his voice was so
pathetic they put it back was really
as really what made me like she
was trying to be so my go-to
layer so janie was like a bunch
of things going on vegas that weekend
there was a rodeo convention oh okay
answered yes and there was also a
big one rodeo well my rope
and stuff i mean yeah
my ropes are they all or y'all
are a bunch of different rodeos people
come to do what you can you
can buy a bunch of sheep that
are already on their side how does
this increase your practice yeah um yeah
there was like a rodeo event in
town okay and so that i've never
seen so many cowboy hats in my
fucking life it was incredible that's really
really really scared i saw like a
guy who was like a classic
ic bow legged cowboy little old guys
spurs absolutely yeah the whole bit so
there so this guy this little baby
man was wearing a ufc hat because
usc oh i saw her tweet about
this and so she said well in
the moment she was like i hope
it's fucking team loses
owe us money so yeah and then
they did they were crushed she cursed
she's got power yes oh they were
on our return flight as well no
and what happened with em were you
just there for the concert we were
we were just there for the country
yeah we got we were there for
two nights and left d did he
do the same thing he did not
do the same thing that
we heard we were much further away
this time ok um and but we
did show we did see that we
fuckin they got on first and we
looked and there was the back sideways
again i don't mind what did it
fit i i don't know but then
this happened janey was trying out a
new suitcase those like a slightly
bigger kerryon it was still a carry
on and then when we tried to
put it in our or overhead it
didn't quite fit and you had to
do it sideways ended up being sideways
wow sorry oh yeah it was perfect
you're a hypocrite you're an asshole but
i think the i think the flight
attendant turn it sideways we didn't do
though
okay so because you you we we
all because like the jewelry dorm would
include we put it in and i
feel like i got it to where
it did close but then i think
there was room enough that the flight
attendant just turned around but i when
i saw it when we opened it
up it was very funny to me
wow contents may shift during the flight
as well well that is something man
that's so true
that's what my tattoo says can i
say i got a bunch of air
air or play-based to just from the
trip because they're so excited there's another
one like right on my pelvic bone
that says low tide across your lego
yeah before you get my tone is
fine okay okay we have to take
a break before it before you get
into what you want to say we're
going to take a break we'll be
right back
and we're back yes you can i
just say that i think if one
of us has a repetitive task to
do it really helps out the others
because we tell story i got through
that story in record time believe it
oh and fair yeah maybe i need
some hey i interrupted a lot i
think we should all but not as
much okay i'll play
maybe you still interrupt it
we ascertained with the problem with show
ya but i think i have the
thing we still have interruptions it's just
not as manageable and so if one
person has to do something we take
turns okay so okay so for the
next show i have some for you
to sign as well um i want
to tell you guys about something i
ate because you said that it stuck
with janie for a long time
that thing happened with the guy i
had listed one day sorry hold on
a second so when you brought that
box in and lauren said are these
for me to sign and you said
no that's something else is having human
i'm having that sign them oh okay
yeah but i wanted some that could
find them know what is he doing
he is doing them oh i want
to sign
i well i want my guy to
sign together my wrong to ah to
i want some three-time ones producer it's
my apologies to offer user friendly smell
um i ate something yesterday that i
did do was a deal that's okay
you're playing me i see um
me for the whole day because it
was the aftertaste was so nasty oh
no that i almost threw up and
my i've never eaten before it was
they never had it was a okay
so i bought um i bought at
whole foods just randomly these keto cups
i don't care about keto i don't
know but that was like a healthy
peanut butter cup it was like hey
grandma chocolate
um thing yeah and i was like
whatever i'm sure i don't give a
shit and i ate it and i
was like it's hazelnut butter which i've
never really had i guess in a
i don't even know if i've ever
had that and if that was a
little bit odd i was like okay
it's a little chalky it's a little
not sure but this yeah after taste
was like
i guess know if you've ever had
i recently had to drink because i
was playing a game show thing where
it was good to you you eight
things you didn't know if they're gonna
taste better or not and they were
like tainted and it was it tasted
like gameshow like expired know it went
no no tainted with it a flavor
is that oh what he would say
no flavored yeah
painted sounds really spooky because it's gross
you were risking your lights bad um
it was like flavored with them that
nail polish or that stuff you put
on your nails like when you heard
the song tainted love you thought it
was about a nice love like sleep
oh i'm telling you tainted his bad
because it was tainted with gross flavors
put in the flavor of like a
bitter thing that you put on your
nails to not buy them right which
tastes horrendous i recently tried that the
aftertaste of this is that it was
making me sick if anyone knows why
it was like that because i was
really like i was going to join
a brand on blast keto cups they're
called that breaky either enough i think
so i don't know what the brand
is called keto you know ryan
abra those was suffering or were the
things we ate in maine that he
he loud with hazardous kids where they
love eating it it's like oh you
gotta oh so it's like cream you
play it again yet still wheels like
the gross jelly beans were one yeah
yeah yeah but i don't know if
it's jelly beans i can't remember it
was some yeah something like that and
but you
they made a game out of it
where it's like if you if you
believe we land hear ye eat this
or whatever and it could be the
good one or it could be a
bad one because they're the same colour
yeah he was like always the game
let's do this and i said no
we did why would i willingly do
that yeah but it's funny to watch
people was fun it was fun yeah
and he says
just really enjoyed yeah that's for children
yeah like what flavors did you get
everything i was bad like like i'd
never got a but but flavor like
bud and ass and toshi battle battles
that though battle battle the bad hole
that's where batman lives come robin go
to the battle oh hey natalie me
don't think i'm going
go to the bat hole a shout
out to the gotham knights video game
which i've been playing oh how is
nice isn't it supposed to be good
it's the thinking of video games i
just got a matt knows this i
just got a switch due to nick
weiger and his insistence i have a
switch and this is the moon and
a switch and ellen barker's yes it
was yeah i
got that i got the dvd madden
see you on animal crossing island yeah
we had fun i've been moving my
arms and she sort of moves the
same way some oh fun yeah it
seems great so why do you get
a switch what are you gonna play
on there i have been playing mario
kart and that's about it and then
matt was like yeah here's my user
name and whenever we are online together
we can play again
impression he's never here never online i
see him online sometimes not always looks
for you i see i see i'm
not alone so lonely there no i
don't know la da and i will
often see matt was recently on like
that was recently sure it makes me
think does he bail he sees me
pop up there and he's like i
gotta get off here yeah it oh
this guy
blogging us guy from work ruining my
fun time yeah but but i don't
really love all the fighting type games
like gotham knights i don't either the
thing is like this game has a
couple um ah like bosses that are
really hard the joker joker this plant
tours out there can coop in it
cool if they like donkey kong isn't
golfing knight i someday i hope that
everybody was owned by disney so that
mario can battle batman
i hope they fall in love yeah
oh that would be cool why are
we just having people fight shout out
to the chippendales movie it's actually really
fun and they do mix all the
little worlds together on the who manage
human males movie no chip and dale
yeah you see a paul schrader paul
snyder who murdered arthur strategies there with
the guy from
garage door having fun this is content
for me yeah chip and dale the
movie written by dan gregory gregory yeah
and also thin girl or i did
a poor man great great people great
movie wonderful times i really enjoyed it
i had a lot fun putting for
holly she was happy
fun show
tv we let marguerite screaming or sometimes
yeah so she'll watch she's watched frozen
she really ended up looking back like
oh she was so excited she what
did you think about the wickedly talented
adult disease
she thought she was amazing
you know it's always funny to me
i love that was one of the
ones in tea later when he pauses
he stretches out wicked as long as
he can he's like please let it
come to me please come to me
damn i think i wanna just mouthed
the
and pretending like i was on a
trapdoor and just to be though clearly
talented
zoe just disappear
oh oh know i know you could
tell he's a real star because nothing
noble and happened no just funny we
just like go like him to me
yeah did he ever apologize because you
really think you should apologize to her
directly do you ever say i like
what she walked up he was like
i bet hey i'm sorry you know
i bet i met a central something
the next day this is
a good followup story we knew where
were reporters he walked up there he
was like how close was oh yeah
that's the man don't tell me don't
tell me because i was i'm just
i feel like it was close i'm
not sure just how close that's the
way to play yeah that's the way
to play if you focus somebody's game
i was like oh yeah he's got
this great grovelling apology i do
think like really rich celebrities are out
there sending huge guy he must have
he bought her a plane like who
did i see like so many like
sheryl lee ralph from abbott elementary you
just risk celebrity you can think of
no but i'm saying she received flowers
from oprah oh and there were flowers
huge trunk opened up and like these
big flowers being delivered to her
house and it was like so amazing
wow like chunk of our flowers cobra
what dan whatever i don't know why
is that weird why is that when
she got bars i've been doing some
drunk bringing him up filled with loose
flowers they were beautifully arranged anyway whatever
but i'm just like they must be
doing like people with like billions
dollars just say but why does oh
she just because she thought she's great
now we want analogy right up to
sheng right no no no it wasn't
apology yeah no so in in any
case holly is able to watch signing
she's watching a little bit of screens
she loves bluey um it's bluey bluey
is an australian cartoon it's really sweet
louis i know what
bluey is i don't know a bluey
looks like and i kind of hope
i never oh okay blue is actually
ever seen a picture only show we
were letting her watch for while because
the episodes are seven minutes and it's
really cute and sweet and it makes
deeply adults kind of like feel something
like it's like just they're very straight-up
up as well be the judge but
the dad is like the best dad
ever and the mom is mister feelings
and it's like about a little these
two
the little girl dog like they're like
shit like shepherds like they're like you
know previously ice and wood dogs or
something like i don't know what
they're not domesticated in real life are
they like the tasmanian tiger i don't
know what they are so they live
in a house in the show and
they're very cute imaginary situations screen on
the other day and when you let
you let em little miss but blaster
ah was she looked seemed like she
was looking at little miss yeah blaster
would you call your daughter okay yeah
it's your house she had some real
buff blasters real but blasters today yeah
i mean she's a baby yeah yeah
food huh here's like thinking about like
this is one thing about her she
shits all the time
yeah it's like the toy so do
i i was thinking today calling little
miss or big miss but plus being
this low pastor that is mrs butler's
thank you i was thinking today that
she's two months old ah okay just
six of these is here yeah
if i can get to eighteen of
those you're afraid of diapers no just
like being rid of the responsibility if
i can get to because you six
more of those and then eighteen of
those then she'll be out of the
house just put a lot of the
how to train right now i think
it's like eighteen months i thought so
too no just six
two six of these two month things
and then if i can get through
that and then do eighteen more of
those she'll be yeah and then you'll
just be gone hanging out doing whatever
you know i'll get there at some
point right yeah yeah what do you
are you feeling a little wild because
like two months ago you were able
to do whatever you want all the
time it's a little bit of that
so is that kind of like a
crazy adjustment for you are you feeling
like
whoa yeah it was in your life
exactly the same
i had a friend who yeah was
like my life's not gonna change oh
well that's stupid or whatever you tell
ya oh unless like i'm like all
the help in the world and you
don't do anything no i mean it
is a little bit of an adjustment
where like especially in the first couple
of week a couple of weeks you're
like asking permission if you can go
to the bathroom yes house like sigh
you don't raise your hand
we're still like i'm going to take
a shower is that okay does that
bother you right now not really but
such an adjustment why don't you call
the adjustment bureau that's a good point
all those hats yeah they're just behind
your walls
yeah from stout the premise was sort
of like sad where it's like the
world is a big set essentially and
you can cut through the backstage of
that's cool the earth or whatever it
maybe i didn't see it i don't
i didn't see the whole thing i
saw part of it okay when we're
together where you just ask us if
you can go to the bathroom it
just yeah it kind of go right
now but right here yes yeah
how does if you did hilarious
you would not imagine if if you
want to be one of my best
stories yes
funny to think about what like go
to the bathroom be on my side
about it or wow okay they would
want oh funny i'd be like i
only wanna do it anyways gonna do
it then he just started shitting in
the middle of the runway because if
you laugh at it go to your
ticket i loved it go to the
bathroom as a phrase i love it
or at least like new go to
ya hear me
go to the bathroom as you go
there in but it did it used
to and then at some point somebody
was like i went to the bathroom
but right here
the back of my pants
in high school i always thought to
be really funny you just say i'm
gonna pee right now and then start
peeing but it's like how hard would
you always thought that would be very
funny conversation that we brought up a
bunch of times like what if what
if like could you do it right
now like if everyone's right to you
and just go like
huh guess what if you're in a
movie you can piss at any time
there's there's always scenes in movies of
like some bad guy like pissing on
a guy he just killed or something
like that lucas witnesses in shortcut was
just watching
where wait hold on what show was
i watching where this guy's walking on
the street and then he pisses in
the street and his friend bachmann the
cops roll up
wait you just watched it too yes
because i didn't feel like it was
something someone's say it again someone's pissing
in the shit reboot shit reboot it
was reboot it was rebel riser paul
riser yeah keenan i really like that
show keegan michael key yeah keenan ivory
wayans yes you know keenan wynn's junior
okay keen
kenan kel kenan thompson yeah cal lee
raw kelly lee rip huh
ripa jack the ripper you ripper this
shoot i break you face
i'm enjoying reboot though i'm like i
wanna be on a show like that
it sounds fun well why don't you
get cast in something the big question
but me and three of the three
but i just want to put it
out there in case there's guessing people
listening i'd like to be in morning
shows people know i'm available to work
on television hey my schedule is clear
i can't please
i can't tell if no casting people
listen to this or all of them
do and go yeah just to make
sure every week like nope nope still
not good on the naughty list all
right we have to take a break
we'll be right back good
and we're back and it's time for
three her and this is i forget
what it's called doesn't matter we can
name it a different thing every time
yeah let's come and call our show
george know i'm gonna call it oh
not sure what's called george w bush
the third yeah call it george w
we're just virgin ole boy
george w bush point five because it's
like half and half and half yeah
i love that i don't even some
yes i don't think my brain cells
from huffing all this learn that stuff
from huffing shuttle art permanent marker where
did you get this
never the bread yeah i thought shire
i was really good and they're good
but i thought i was ordering sharpies
and they are now this is sound
out of ink a little quicker while
thinking of fifty five yeah um okay
so this is a game where we
do a scene in one minute and
then we have it and do a
scene in third
seconds the same scene we try to
do the same stuff then we go
to fifteen seconds then we go to
eight seconds four seconds two seconds one
second this fun and so the first
one that we do is a min
along and we just we just let
it ride it's about whatever mat we
need a suggestion of your favorite thing
to do when you're alone be honest
not on mike texted to us
um also in case you are hearing
this for the first time in this
game everybody loves it yeah you should
know you should know where they're going
yeah and you have to love this
or else you're just saying like if
you don't love it something's wrong with
you yeah yeah so when does this
episode come out in curiosity it comes
out i'll tell you
i believe it comes out ah december
fifteen okay wow the eyes of december
i'm gonna play a show that i'm
doing trying to plug one that i'm
going to while we're waiting for yours
and you because here's this after fifteen
you should yours is more important to
plug the mines a month later
lunar well variety apia is happening um
in mere days the eighteenth of december
um at lodge room in highland park
it's going to be a really fun
show special surprise guests people that have
knocked on the show before but i'm
thrilled to have for the first time
and we have weird stuff planned comedy
music oh it's gonna be great
and i'm taking apollo tacos dot com
slash live thank you i'm doing my
first own show at dynasty typewriter it
is an improv show i'm compiling a
group of improvisers and it'll be different
every month i do it again i'm
doing well there they each have their
strengths and weaknesses of course everyone does
this person for this
weakness this is like no show january
fourteen and you should get tickets now
i haven't announced it yet and i
haven't announced the cast but it is
really good and i'm very excited and
tests me so fine and i guess
we're not rescheduling are but we need
to do our two-part well as i
was saying i'm looking like we need
your own show again well because of
what happened me where was i i
was out of town or something yeah
it was just a bad time
yeah but um yeah no let's do
it again obviously it's done um but
i decided to branch out and do
my own things but everyone is doing
this and i was like you know
what that's really that's really fun it's
really yeah alright let's start here we
go ready and go hi guys i'm
glad you're here um i yeah i
was here before you
yeah but i'm showing up and i'm
saying i'm glad you're here i was
actually in the closet oh i'm glad
you're here i was here first watching
both of you arrive okay yeah now
we're all here yeah yeah you're late
i know so i'm glad you're here
to tell me the horse we're here
look start meeting waiting for twenty minutes
to begin how do you know that
she's been waiting for twenty minutes
shouldn't come in the same time she
said she's been hiding in the closet
out her hi there i have a
bed pajamas toothbrush and my glasses all
in there so it's been a whole
night hard bristles are so sharpish
a backyard shaft pressure shaft pressure visuals
anyway why did you call us here
and then get here oh twenty minutes
you're both fired yeah i love working
here but i know i love happy
i love having we love calling people
and begging them to sign up for
our underwear mailer i know i know
and you guys are my two best
employees
paris
i keep ran at a time huh
ah what a grade see what ah
fascinating scene for the ages
alright so now can we do hilariously
cuts out by monday alright ready i
can see out ago i'm glad you're
here yeah i know i was here
peek-a-boo i've already been here in the
closet i'm glad you're here too you're
yeah you're late to call the meeting
you're twenty minutes late i know but
that's why i'm glad you're here isn't
worth thing i slept here with my
glass
uses my toothbrush soft bristles are hard
shaft fractures what chef rich's shop racial
shift visuals anyway why are we here
well first of all i'm glad you're
here yes i did so any time
but secondly you're fired
will over here
my best employee that was really good
alright fifteen seconds
are we yeah and go i'm glad
you're here why yeah we've been here
for twenty minutes in the closet sleeping
with my toothbrush and my glasses after
her shadbush okay well the reason i
called you here is you're fired know
we love working here
you're my best employees love having you
here no and why are you firing
us wow
ah layers a little old thing called
miring i to be frank i knew
was trying to happen and i was
trying to hit the state lab for
a few times so we had a
little extra time on that so oh
my god sky it felt like hours
yeah what a bombshell okay here we
go eight seconds and go
so glad you're all here well we've
been your name and soft bristles are
harsh shock pressures when they fired whoa
i love you but i'm firing you
because huh
alright four seconds ready and go glad
because chicago shopper show buyer anyway we
love it sir
we actually got more in the right
two seconds and go shots fired
one second and go fire yeah hey
ah that was good oh good let's
do one more yeah you should do
one more than like we go to
two minutes oh fuck no
i feel like i feel like with
the one-minute everything afterwards is gravy
yeah let's go to two minutes go
to everything's just pure gravy flowing off
the dish fuel we didn't use messages
from you we didn't know we didn't
but it's funny it's like a little
prank we played on him we made
him text us something personal and then
we'll just ignore it anyway
question was do we want to say
watch me now that sharp suggestion for
this okay here we go
hey um i've spotted a giant
but a giant what i bought a
giant a person yeah is that sleepy
dude it's slave owners he's no that's
not good but it's like just like
okay right dollars can't you they can't
talk and shit well i mean giants
only say fee fi fo fum braille
been
yeah like i'm brown but rubin this
is exactly your properties you can't just
be buying giants and they're gonna live
in our two bedroom what are we
supposed to watch tv when you go
perform for us yeah trained to cut
you bought your firing order training how
long have you had this giant fur
about three
hours i think you've already trained him
to do work so what is he
a robot or an idiot
good question if your robot are an
idiot i these a little bit of
both honestly bottom half robot top half
idiot no women tree highway bottom half
robot means we could fuck
exactly fuck a giant well i wouldn't
do it
i fucking did you don't want to
take advantage yeah
well anyway i'll look look like yo
go away double ren have a giant
live exactly well he's not going to
be in his own room he's going
to be in my room that's part
of the price i'm eating my chex
mix and he's going to be stealing
my beans where'd you get those beans
by the way my bottom from someone
in exchange for a cow
wait where is goodbye the being i
sold our cow no not cow yeah
monsieur robert roommate we have milk so
every morning i know when i'm milking
every night no giving the afternoons know
who's gonna do it morning noon and
night that guy's been built
male cows shouldn't be milk for me
i know this should it's really upsetting
you have any of us get near
him yeah but he likes it at
the end yeah by bio what he's
drinking his milk yeah yeah you loved
it well are we out of milk
yeah oh
that was fun because i remember a
word okay so that was wonder a
word i remember i'm a roman word
sorry that was two minutes that was
two minutes okay thank you too this
is one couple danced or buie hey
guys um come in here i bought
a a giant giant what no that's
it just a giant you bought a
giant yeah
that's like slavery where you can buy
a dog well since dogs can't talk
program and you can't buy barely talks
he just says fee fi fo fum
and whatever rhymes with it smells knowing
well okay i'll send them back but
i mean what else are we going
to watch tv come on brisbane yeah
wanna watch him do the trick so
what did you train
i'm already yeah how long have you
had three hours and three hours he's
either a robot or an idiot yeah
i think it's a little bit of
both robot on the bottom idiot on
top he's a robot on the bottom
we fucking you can't like hey well
i don't want to manage okay alright
well he's gonna pay more rent yeah
you're gonna pay double why he's he's
gonna be in my room he's neat
oh my checks my steal my beans
were
get all those beings my macguffin for
so i'm training the cow robert robert
robert you traded our cow yes i
love that cow milk him every morning
milk him every night imo come in
the afternoon and welcome morning noon and
night
it was actually perfect perfect alright third
we should actually transcribe that scene because
it was really good i think we
should write it making a movie
that's that's a feature that's definitely if
he's like thirty survey sign one hundred
and thirty seconds here we go hey
guys i bought a giant y just
a giant that slavery was not yeah
he ah you can buy dog lives
you can't anyway we watch tv yes
well um you don't wanna watch him
all these things well how did you
train him so fast
three hours how did you train him
so i just did it but hey
he might getting a robot okay yeah
beans it's robot ornate can't fucking if
he's an idiot now we don't have
a county more wow knows huh wow
bean tried to milk him in the
morning i'm malcolm at night milked him
in the afternoon and welcome morning noon
and night
fifteen second really sticking the landing on
that one here we go and a
great time go hey i bought a
chinese slave right gee the giant just
a giant
tv
can we watch it yes i love
to watch j toby yams any of
them well you're gonna pay double theory
what does the show are an idiot
zenga
i agree that we sticking
second we we did not take the
beginning
hey guys about a giant slavery no
t b o rabo milk mean new
dawn oh alright for a second i
think the worst part is when we
hold waiting for the waiting for the
big four seconds here we go giant
slavery no robots suck em idiot wow
oh right goring mamou night morning momo
night alright two seconds giant wow gone
kao cow da morning to night and
one seconds cow male giant ears
just get your whole deal
ah fun la fun was gonna need
that the new delete leader yeah you
did easily yeah maybe i mean everybody
thank you for listening this is three
of them if in case we didn't
say at the top yeah and um
mopey are out there having a good
good holiday season yeah if you're not
holiday season and will do and hickory
huh and don't forget to hang up
your xy yeah the job does have
a job did danny down the chimney
down so yes again those shows ah
sunday december eighteenth at lodge room tickets
are available at paulo tongues dot com
slash
alive january fourteenth at his typewriter but
it's a saturday and nasty typewriter dot
com there's nothing great you have us
friend who isn't that somehow and we're
all going to go out this week
so i'm happy about that yeah the
dinner together it's gonna be very fun
making i've never been to tamashii oh
no or never yeah this is great
yeah this is there
as everything um like beans in a
pot everything okay yeah it's they're famous
for like metaphorical but the menu has
a millionaire jonathan beans in the but
whatever you order it's beans in a
pub yeah um right if you are
following us online it's at three dm
usa and if you you know on
tuesdays we're doing our very
special revisiting three visiting on the twos
where re-releasing all of our previous episodes
in order on tuesday does anyone know
why we're doing that um because they
don't want to be behind the paywall
oh i think it's great for everyone
who doesn't want to pay one p
yeah absolutely but if you want to
hear ad-free versions you can
ear them at stitcher premium or at
cb world dot com and that's it
for this episode we love you thank
you for listening you will see you
next week hi
uh