um
uh
ah
a
ah da hae
oh yeah why are the houselights up
this is weird they want to tell
you don't want to see these assholes
turn the lights huh
did you say do the hustle do
the hustle everyone now who high bravo
hi pablo hi pablo can you not
hear anything that is happening cause i'm
gonna get nervous that we're gonna be
like wait what the whole time could
be king let's do our traditional can
we turn the monitors up during every
show we do this everywhere we go
here we go this is much better
thank you so much hello bravo
it alone okay la bo piper parvo
coyote ugly remember that can't fight the
moonlight upside the moon laddie bema sega
okay
i saw the movie coyote welcome to
freedom my name is paul f tompkins
ah my name is lauren lamkin dance
and i'm sky gourmet
and who your love spotify yeah
ah it was exciting to hear how
many people loved spotify
i feel like there were like ten
i feel like they were shy at
first and then they realized the second
time i really do love spotify
i love spotify i know lawyers and
i love spotify no no no like
a literally pay for premium um meteors
are good i love spotify hello
it's fine
kit before you get into your piper
bravo opus my pied piper robbo i
just caught on to what we were
talking about
can i can i say that as
a compliment to this incredible crowd we
heard from stage matters someone was talking
about you from someone at the festivals
that you were the most well-behaved crowd
they've ever seen
threesome fans are so well behaved it's
so nice we heard that you guys
made up and enforced your own rules
about the line and watch it happen
and who should go where
and you all agreed
that makes us look good so thank
ya thank you very much newt
alright so welcome to three dm this
is the show where we talk for
an hour
paul you were you were saying about
now who remembers bio na na na
alley now
oh already your knees
please take off your shoes and knee
along the forest i'll open
dorf is a character jordan his character
when i was doing birth i was
in character
you have to understand i was dinner
time i was literally dorf i was
doing character and that was one year
ago that you were doing that his
tim conway alive or dead oh yes
x's for eyes
but we love him we love him
for it we live in for right
both ways will come alive we love
him dead that's not something you can
say about a lot of people it's
true he hasn't been dead long enough
for us to know how much we
love him dead i think he's off
to a great start
who do you love dead the most
my answer is michael jackson
we got to him yeah la dealer
showing the same amount of time we
gotta get cosby
we got em both this is this
is much more power to not do
no we have to mention them every
episode no i don't like you but
i still my answer who fair enough
i'm not going to take that away
from you so paul tell us about
piper parvo i'll tell you all about
her
is it perodua or para bo oh
someone's somebody here's a parable
is she here just like it's terrible
it's terrible
um i watched at a double feature
at my friend's house i mean you
call it a double feature if you're
hanging out at your friend's house two
movies came on like yeah we watched
two movies in a row can not
call it a double feature
i mean is it mirrors of him
yeah
watch your zale like it's some sort
of curated double feature that like well
what was another wash put we had
control over it so it was cody
ugly coyote ugly and battlefield earth
it makes no sense i watch them
back-to-back we started watching movies at ten
pm
and my friend did not make it
through all of battlefield earth she just
went off to bed i was like
what was that first let myself out
no we watch all the coyote ugly
and then substantial amount of battlefield earth
that's not a double feature why is
it not a double feature you watched
one movie and then another one was
on and you all low know we
we did not
all leave there was two of us
we selected the movies
in advance you selected them you through
two movies on you didn't select them
but that is selecting we knew which
we knew which movies they were we
didn't reach into a pile of dvds
just like aim at the dvd player
i did you have like a dvd
party where everyone puts a dvd into
the bowl and then leaves with whatever
you then you go and you have
just the person who brought the corky
romano
yeah
but you also get their dvd player
yes you go to their home you
have sex with them then when you
leave you take their dvd player yeah
i want to do it anyway because
people don't have dvd player i wanna
tell you tempe
i watched a double feature yesterday of
the real dolby yeah it was the
news and the view
i'm gonna slowly end up on top
of this okay so we had a
big discussion at all but let's get
this was huge i wasn't gonna get
into it scott but let's get into
it we had a big discussion about
the seating arrangements before the show because
we knew you wouldn't be able to
see right here and then we said
we don't care and i said good
i said i want every fourth person
to not be able to see because
of stage equipment what how do we
think about this does this how do
we think about this how do we
think about it when we think about
this how do we think about i
think hard about this i think soft
about it
now scott scott fields and if i
may and i will not misrepresent my
spot oh god i'm nervous
scott fields at the lower chairs are
not as stage friendly in terms of
the picture that is presented on stage
i feel like we look like a
bunch of lazy fucks
just chilling when we should be entertaining
you all but i feel like what
he feels is more entertaining as sitting
on barstools
which i gotta admit when i say
out loud it's pretty entertaining yeah
so lauren and i have been biggie
him bay yaghi scott for the kodi
bay thanks jos please can we sit
on comfortable chairs and he said no
yes he's in his nightcap and his
nightshirt is candles oh no
i throw open the sash he threw
off his tattoo no i'm her handbag
was the sash
one time he threw out his pot
of pee pee on us
it wasn't good therapy
did you say part of pp he
said puppy you call it pot of
gold
i've rich
every mooney it richer in reach yeah
so for good reason the vault fabi
for this show
we said you know what it's our
collective show not comedy bang bang so
they voted me we have voted him
for these comfortable chairs you know what
i feel great about it yeah and
they're they're always feels good they're couch
wedges individually their couch wedges individually i
love that do think stay here
are you saying together they make one
couch um i don't know but they're
going to show a wedge of a
couch if you're saying this know it
was not her saying it's you you
saying this no no because they're all
corners it's impossible it's a good point
although i from what i understand maybe
there's some pieces that were taken out
of it hey from what i understand
my beats jingle from what i understand
used to be way bigger now it's
little just because you guys don't do
any prep before the show and i
have to take care of all this
stuff wow
you want to fight
what do you mean you had to
tell them we want to chase it
on a comfy chair that was the
prep and then i heard a lot
of information about these three things were
on and you told us men
do you want me to be the
chair guy from ellen
but for live three items for what
for live three yeah i'll be the
chair guy you'll get a chair guy
yeah i'd like to continue having no
responsibility
done great works out yeah so double
feature story time wow there's more i
thought it was over no no you
thought that was the whole huh
it was so grounding how did you
i did think that oh dare you
so we watch this person mad i
want to know which one the people
right behind these monitors i feel bad
person whose mount you are you mad
we're gonna find the mad person
whose matters come up here and fight
us
who's mad dune new new
wow that's who my god you should
be an impressionist go around a little
party isn't
really do you think so said the
joker that's michael jackson no
johnny carson roddick johnny carson michael jackson
joker to niche market where's my wawa
it's a niche market sue tells the
story the song the the ah the
movie coyote ugly contains the song can't
fight the moonlight this is what the
marianne rye-dark
are played by piper perry bow
it's all she wants to do she
wants to be an artist and make
the crappy music of alta hey i
liked that song you like that song
yeah i did what was it about
that song that grabbed you all the
sluts dancing to it hold on a
second
don't shave those slots or shame those
slots i liked about it i'm not
shaming them um no i don't know
i mean it was you know a
fun jam i got it on limewire
sure yeah not spotify sorry
a
so
a week later the same friend in
ire in ikea you guys were close
you know lauren we still aren't wow
isn't janie no she's my best friend
ah my best friends rob
some guy i'm sorry you didn't get
to marry him your best friend yeah
i'm married cool up instead
we were in ikea and um who
was looking for what break it down
i was looking for yergin
i cannot remember what was being looked
for i might have been looking for
the entertainment center that i put together
and then worried about for a solid
eight years of my apartment that it
was going to topple yes said it
would yeah it would crumble because i
had pieces left over
and i was like i cannot break
this down to start over again this
is it i think they sometimes give
you extra pieces know yeah that was
also the time that i early in
the process of putting this thing together
i um realized i had done something
wrong and
i had to dig out one of
those wooden dowels that i really smacked
in there like it was it was
in there good and i'd get it
out to start over the process and
i didn't know what to use than
i thought ah the perfect tool swiss
army knife so
i am so i'm digging this thing
out and somehow i managed to shut
the knife on my finger e and
it went like it went deep enough
in that it looked like a a
novelty gag you know what i mean
like oh i cut my finger where
it was like it was in there
and i just
stared at it for a while like
this is not good and then i
took it out and there was so
much blood so much blood and i
believe you're supposed to leave it in
and go to that place she say
who you you said that i said
i believe you're supposed to leave it
in
the first time somewhat first time they
had sex yeah i believe you're supposed
to leave it in but i'm still
me but oh to indian repeatedly this
is my belief
and you can't make fun of people's
beliefs you can't you have to respect
them you do
so we're in the kia and ah
we are due on our individual shopping's
and then the song can't fight the
moonlight comes on in the ikea and
i knew i have to find my
friend
and we must acknowledge that the song
is playing and so whatever i was
doing it was like where where she
wears she and then i went out
and in the aisle she walked out
the same time and we were both
doing this just pointing at the ceiling
that's us it was a wonderful moment
to to everyone at the ikea it
looks like you guys are like
thanking god for but i mean we're
not moving our heads the way you
you're misrepresenting the scott and show for
the listener i want you to know
scott's misrepresenting what happened at the ikea
i rest my case
your honor this man am i the
judge
and i would actually like to do
a segment where you you look at
me like so seriously just like are
you a judge or no
are you settled already settle arguments yeah
but chocolate goes up to a dump
truck are you the judge let's do
it remember that book are you my
mother yeah the sad book yeah that
is the most children's books have some
kind of point what was the point
of that did did it find its
mother i've read it so many times
i don't
member the ending i'm assuming but now
now you ask me i don't know
i don't remember either does anyone know
what happens
he finds them okay if that is
a paris paper scenario jesse finds his
mother thanked his mother
jesus god damn
but i remember as a child that
book bummed me out so much because
little tiny adorable duckling just walking up
to various machines and inanimate objects saying
are you my mother what's that book
were like it's like the mom is
holding and hugging the baby lengthy end
it took he's a man and he's
whoa
holding his dying mom do you know
what i'm talking about
what
what i got right nah what is
it
that loves you forever fucked up the
title is terrifying so sad and it's
like the i'm talking about spotify
the mom's like holding the baby and
it's like i love you forever i
love you for always bubble and then
at the end like he's holding his
own mom and she's like old and
dying and he's like repeating the same
poem
ah love it it's so weird like
the last line of that book is
how to you like it
he's i've been holding a grudge since
he was a baby i hate this
poem you helpless invalid isn't it
is it because the giving tree was
so popular and have that sense of
on we at the end there are
a lot of knockoffs of the giving
i feel like i never read that
book well let's act it out okay
i'll tell you what i know from
it do you want to be the
tree or do you want to be
the jerk
the chirk yeah
leah driven i'll be the oblivious asshole
sweet hugh hey i actually don't even
know how it goes so you know
you're about to find that like wow
and then you'll judge it
hey don't piss
okay i'm gonna sit in my judge's
seat ah a little kid ah look
a fucking tree and do it like
play around here i take a little
nap or whatever give me that apple
so long asshole
that's wow i love you yeah i
know of course you do i'm adorable
then later the guys like gay i'm
a teenager i'm in love i got
a knife fight me i got frown
we probably were not even gonna last
by i'm a teenager like why am
i memorializing this and a living thing
anyway fuck you
i love you yeah no shit stupid
when it comes back he's a man
hey look who it is i need
a house now so ah i'm gonna
chop you to fuck damn right
ah he needs a howard stupid i
love you right now you know
he chops down a tree to make
a hat not over oh shit
i'm an old ass hole
my time is very short on this
earth book a fuckin stump
i just sit on yeah well i'm
dead so are you
they both die while the tree trees
chopped down old guy we can assume
definitely forever yeah
so what am i supposed to say
judge it judge it i think it's
fucked up
this verdict is in yeah i don't
let ratio verdict
about the giving tree fifty years later
yeah um speaking of gifts i i
was gonna tell you this story i
sent my grandma a birthday gift this
week gift or gif
i almost i sent her a gif
she couldn't see ah it was wasted
she has poor vision i named my
stall is it a still or again
it just stalled out so
is give his dough out
this
it's still an out
okay so she's ninety four
yeah clap come on guys yeah come
on now she wants to live in
twenty point of us doing this live
if you're not good lawd at the
applause prompts yeah my grandma is ninety
four
iraq's iraq's iraq iraq's pit old people
rock dude i know
they're here tonight cheering it's all senior
citizens i don't know if maybe surprising
that's we'd find out that's how it
would be incredible i would be so
delighted just walk out everyone is eighty
to one hundred now that soap operas
are all being cancelled your favorite thing
you're consistent and you always make michael
jackson
jokes it's the same show and the
only place to hear michael jackson songs
okay so i sent her i often
will send her a card with money
and she loves that but i wouldn't
how much we talk and i'll i'll
send her one hundred dollars that's fifty
twenties
uh wow but she she likes that
she likes to go to walgreens and
buy stuff she likes walgreens gift card
gift cards but i was late this
time was sending kind of forgotten so
i wanted to send her something you
say you forgot or did you say
no no so i sent it really
early i'll send you send her one
hundred dollars
then she goes by she goes and
buys walgreens gift card
she would prefer i send her walgreens
gift cards or cash oh as per
her rings he should one
do we have new rules here
do we have the song new rules
by any chance we were playing right
before the show would be great to
hear it at this point of the
show if we have yeah we could
say her but her birthday rules continue
on so you can just play and
you can interrupt lauren at any point
should it should you find it on
the computer please don't interrupt me if
i'm talking in you find
if i'm talking please don't interrupt me
to buy up to me lauren is
cool zalora and said to us she's
very cool i'm just really cool she's
laid back
so i sent her a box of
chocolate covered strawberries though like ah just
a treat you know and i get
the concept yeah
and but i i sent it so
it would arrive three days before her
birthday while my aunt was in town
so i knew she could share them
with her i had ah it was
thoughtful and i thought i will get
there early i get even more brownie
points because it arrived early she's very
obsessed with receiving gifts she will always
act like she's not but if you
don't send her something she will
guilt trip it to everyone like an
lorna and remember you know so it'll
be like a thing so i've always
on top of it wow yeah and
i hear about it about other family
members so i'm like i'm not gonna
be that person i'm gonna send it
really early i call her on her
birthday a few days after the strawberries
arrived and we talked for five minutes
and it felt like fifteen and the
the entire time she just complaint oh
no
uh
of one cent a hundred dollars oral
walgreens gift card please who knows amy
chow
now hobby fritos early
we didn't establish the order in which
we would lay down the new rules
okay thank you thank you thank you
thank you that was exactly as we
rehearsed it ah it was really wrong
i gotta get down yeah that was
like a brisk walk
my heart is racing okay um so
you're having a chilled expectation receive the
strawberries and she was like lauren don't
send me those they're so big there
are switched she said
she said there were six of them
that's what she said yes that's what
she said she were black they were
dark brown um chocolate
and i was like somebody sent you
black chocolate
and then i said well i thought
you could share them with my aunt
and she's like she only ate
actually she only ate half of one
and i eat the other half and
i said well how about my other
aunt who lives near you she came
over and she a one
i was like well that's fine and
she's like there are too many and
i was like just throw them out
i just thought it'd be nice surprise
it doesn't matter it is all about
the merguez six right yes and then
i was like then she's like and
i called your mom and i said
lauren should not send me these they
came in a box with ice around
and then your mom said how about
you give them cheered neighbor and i
said he doesn't like chocolate
then she said how much neighbor and
i said he is
please you can't i said grandma and
i kept interrupting her grayling it's fine
like i don't i just if you
threw them out it doesn't mean you
know i don't it's okay and she's
like and your mom said why don't
you break off the chocolate and eat
that part i tried but the strawberries
aren't going to last like she was
just it wasn't it was i was
like i'm
punished for sending this is a nightmare
i'm like i should be getting so
many points it arrived three days early
it's like it's like excessive and stupid
but you guys position instead of the
money yeah okay
but it's all about being on time
then my other cousin i guess ah
at another holiday centre chocolate and she
complained about that because there were only
there were four in the box but
the box they arrived in was so
big
and today mr coster sixty dollars and
it was like aren't you glad people
are sending i think you should only
give someone something that they would
use money to buy as a real
yes that's the stupidest thing i've ever
heard what does this again you should
only you should alien cool up like
groceries yes
gas
grass
yes no one rides for free
but it doesn't that driving do you
have you ever had the experience of
someone complaining so much about i was
like yeah okay well my biggest takeaway
from the stories yeah she knows that
her neighbor doesn't like chocolate she knows
them all well to take community itself
like it
i don't know drove me nuts i
got i was going through old stuff
yesterday because we're moving
and i looked into my ducks my
destro art and similarly there was a
gift in there and it was three
years old i saw the date on
his three years old it's a cartier
gift certificate i don't know who gave
it to me that i fancy it
stressed me i started i literally started
hyperventilating
because i was like what am i
supposed to deal with this how much
was it for i don't know he
has to be a lot to go
to cardio like here's fifty bucks to
cartier you can't get anything i don't
i don't remember if it was like
a gift from a person or a
robot to work
did god give me this aware will
lose it
terminator i don't know you started shaking
and hyper event i honestly was like
this is too much responsibility i don't
want this can i have it yeah
that worked out
oh wait no i'm i'll give it
to kula what the fuck oh that
was a close one what the fuck
fuck you're gonna go to you getting
with your wife i asked first
just call up even know about this
no no but i from your mistress
she's like buy me something nice come
on daddy i'll give you a gift
card you've depended on me
i don't get how this works
uh
it was right next to a barnes
and noble gift card that my parents
gave me four years ago or something
do they exist anymore i don't even
know wait are you one of those
people who like doesn't use gift cards
sounds like it exactly i've given you
two examples to sit here i'll gift
cards in a dry county judge or
you well benevolent um
i have a friend who never uses
gift cards and they just pile up
in a drawer at her house i'm
like if people give them to i
want that like i'm not about using
a gif well who is i understand
i ah that's the problem zao put
them in a drawer to to do
it later i want to use them
i would definitely use them there as
good as cash yeah you should go
on bn dot com and get yourself
a nice book
i will okay idea why don't you
put your gift cards in a bowl
by the door okay when you're walking
with your db douglas giftcard i actually
carry all my gift cards and a
teeny little pouch and i'm not kidding
in your body and it's in my
stomach yeah so it's like it's a
skin flat i shit it out when
i want to buy something
thank you thanks for that sound
casey didn't know
yeah do you like gift cards do
you think they're impersonal what's your take
i don't like getting gifts what i
don't like getting it really yeah i
don't why i've i've reached i feel
like i've gotten to the point in
my life where if i want a
thing for myself i will buy it
yeah you know what i mean and
jit my my
if cheney and i will exchange gifts
very rarely we do it on
because you'll like this story we exchanged
gifts together like he isn't like to
any of this tours yeah yeah we
interesting ooh
we exchanged gifts on christmas and that's
mostly it we eat some anniversaries yes
some birthdays yes but we barely exchanged
gifts janie and we barely exchanged barely
the fuck
alright okay if you don't give my
wife gifts to my one cousin
ticket the other way
no cool up and i think we
have just started saying like let's just
not get anything for each other ever
again it's wow
ah well if you're married it's sort
of like you get to a point
where you're like we're gonna keep doing
this like no and and not only
that but three times a year yeah
my reaction times ms valentine's and anniversary
time about birthday oh and birthday too
i forgot about the st patrick's day
what about fourth of july our nation's
birthday
i like gifts yeah i'm weird but
yeah i'm sure that ah i don't
know if we're allowed to say that
you have a husband but i'm sure
like to play said of the bunch
but i'm sure like he's really good
about the people who can hear someone
talk about something or notice something in
a window and go oh that's really
cool and
then months later it shows i mean
yeah yeah he's definitely good at that
i'm fucking good at that you are
yeah i know that about you yeah
i'm great at it so what have
i talked about in january michael jackson
he got you a madame too so
yeah i would love that lets you
can enjoy michael jackson's bones
made ah
oh god that's a good point how
would he like it like right well
he had the elephant man's bones what
you don't know this no i don't
i don't know that he had them
he tried to buy them well wait
what is that the ultra man is
like that person who
ah begun it by the elephant and
the full moon happened
and you got the proportional strength no
i don't think i really know what
that is the ulfa man was a
jets act it out i believe david
uh i'll be the tree
here lie am any hopkins looking for
an elephant man but he's real yeah
he's real guy okay
ah tree pod me tree you know
where i can find a man whose
whole hideous sip call him the elephant
man
try over there thank you tree
i love you
beat me to it so cut to
smash katu so let's right there smash
got to london carnival freak show times
david merrick is this guy who has
ah i can't get home and he's
got elephant places i guess elephant titus
he has a huge head um and
included a mouth his bones are all
kinds of fucked up
and his balls he's put on balls
on this guy oh yeah and nothing
a woman likes more than huge ass
balls bigger than your head but he
was rescued from the the sort of
carnival circuit by this kind doctor
her um and then he became michael
jackson wanted his bones yeah just this
is disturbing yeah really
that's the only disturbing thing i've ever
heard about
what yeah and then so he died
in michael jackson was like one please
buffy
ah he died many many many years
ago like the early nineteen hundreds like
the late eighteen hundreds i think
i believe please don't get mad at
me i'm doing my best let's talk
to robbo wow am i doing just
like it was eighteen ninety two
but he became he could not ah
sleep ah until he got the bones
i gotta get the phone i can't
sleep it's all i'll think about those
bones
once i had that waking moment once
i had that i won't have any
more strange desires
i can only get those phones up
at cure
if i could only arrange those bones
so they were been to go for
i was gonna say that about his
wax figure but i had to arrange
it like that yeah you would why
didn't were the bones fucked up are
worthy know their brains
they were perfect this is a real
question the elephant titus yeah it's just
skin you say is it is it
skin is it like a swelling of
the skin where everything is fucked up
or did it or the bones gnarled
and twisted as well i'm gonna say
as gnarled and twisted he had eight
he may have had more than one
issue
q
um
but his skeleton was on display somewhere
i think in a medical college and
michael jackson wanted to buy them that's
so that's so cool i mean look
say what you want about the guy
that's cool
i love that i do love it
i love that is there something that
you would do if you got that
famous who's buying
bones you whose skeleton you want
if i could get anyone's skeleton yeah
don't say danny devito because that's mine
um
imagine
whatever so like what's that skeleton that's
danny devito
how much do you think it would
cost i bet i actually bet if
you donate it to his favorite charity
yeah danny here's the deal you're not
gonna live forever nobody is nobody is
nobody look no shade no shit
i will donate a hundred dollars to
the charity of your choice that's a
grandma birthday gift i will don't also
need a already gift certificate
if your neighbor like chocolate i will
donate six chocolate covered strawberry tin can
i bet you could though if you
paid enough before they died you could
reserve someone's bone can i get yours
how much twenty dollars seriously though how
much how much would you pay for
ticket your bones display it in my
house like a biology class do i
can i have any sort of issue
you know with how you display them
like you or are you just allowed
to do whatever you want i could
do whatever i want but what kind
of issues would
you have well you know some sort
of clause in the contract about like
you can't do anything we're like oh
make me look like a dinosaur
toe tap depart put them in a
different configuration i would need to have
the ability to fuck with the bones
it there's no fun if i can't
fuck with the okay okay okay so
i would be willing to pay five
thousand dollars that's true probably yeah can
i say this is disgusting that we're
talking about money when we're friends and
i feel that they shouldn't eat donated
to me it should either be yes
of course you can have my sketch
button or you can't but the idea
that money would change you're so tacky
ah i need the bones for free
now
wow it's an emergency and i need
them for halloween it's coming right around
the corner the kids are going to
want to see the bones
and rye where are they going otherwise
what do you want to happen crimean
i want croatia let's get into it
yeah i want cremation but i think
just the idea of all these cemeteries
is so weird yeah isn't it just
all these dead bodies littering the earth
stacking up rackham packham statham and yeah
well but if you want to your
bones if you wanted your bones separated
you meet meaning i want them to
carve the flesh off my body right
incinerate that i would want it to
be like they dump acid on you
like itchy and scratchy or something
and you're like
i run around for a little while
with the sound of xylophone and all
the bones
yeah you won't be buried in the
casket
um i don't think i think i
used to want that and i don't
think i want them to yeah that's
your ego talking yeah everyone to see
you i think i'd just want to
be burned up wo and scattered scattered
where as i was in life
ah
the usual places the ocean the library
church
our libraries filled with cremated actually will
be
oh wait whoo what did i hear
the apparently on disney's haunted mansion ride
um they periodically have to clean out
people's cremains yeah because oh yeah you
did you know about that when you
worked there i did not know about
it when i worked there what was
the coolest secret about disney that you
learned
in your time as breyer bear
well they sit you down at the
beginning and they tell you every secret
about walt disney himself
first day of working there was a
basketball court that i win that's like
um you can play out or harder
yeah
good luck so far
you guys are allowed to play basketball
on your break you cannot take the
suits off
did you see the video of like
maleficent like roasting peter pan do you
guys see this i did see that
yeah it was so weird she was
like they were going back and forth
like a long time like roasting each
other i feel like they really hated
each nobody was enjoying know the kids
were like i need your autograph and
she's like i bet you can't see
your shadow
very sassy and weird they were doing
full-on rose jokes like he was saying
how old she looked and i forget
what she was saying about him yeah
it wasn't memorable it was just yeah
i mean it was just something that
shouldn't have happened that someone put on
video
like most of them but then there
was like buzzfeed thirty two best maleficent
roasts or whatever
lauren what do you want done to
your body after it's dead yeah
i don't know man um i think
i always wanted to be buried in
a casket and um now i'm interested
in cremation yeah you're interested i'm interested
i love to see the process yeah
i love to sell you as much
all of six feet under which is
so devastating and um yeah i think
that's kind of
what made me think you'd be better
just to be cremated on it's just
fun if i could if i could
have anything i would be embalmed and
put on display somewhere is that true
yeah
oh cool i don't know obi i
would i would be happy argo it
would make me
like am like ah like an egyptian
you're just there for the open piano
when i was a kid i read
ah did you read the book of
lists when you were a kid noah
said the book of lists was ah
sort of just it was a collection
of lists it was like a a
trivial book and it was a big
hit in the like late seventies early
eighties when i was kid i was
fascinated by for my time was that
before my time ah sure
i don't think us generation z millennials
ah had that you were just born
so one of the things was um
one of the lists was the weird
dispositions of ah certain people's bodies white
and there was this guy like well
like things that people that weren't just
buried or cremated like their bodies were
something like a weird thing happened with
them there was this guy
named jeremy bentham who was a british
i don't know if i can remember
he's a politician yeah what
philosopher la sophia huh
two people leave in
and he was like okay it got
too real will get up and dance
to new rules again if he'll stay
please stay please my love you oh
cool that didn't work um he was
involved and put on display at a
i believe at a college right university
bridge yeah it might have been for
all i remember show that stuck in
your mind as a kid and you
were like i want that i think
in when i was a kid i
don't know i don't know that i
thought i want that but i was
certainly not a fascinating yeah you could
go into a place behind glass was
dead person that would be so weird
for the family but i'd be very
cool if you were an ancestor of
that person and you got to see
them here's what i think of even
cooler is long after anybody even remembers
who i am that i'm like an
like an a bar somewhere yeah like
as a weird curiosity does it never
rot i guess it does i think
you could be stuffed could you like
an animal because we do that i
had a friend who wanted that legal
i had a friend who wanted to
stuff her dog after her dog passed
away and she was planned on doing
it and then chicken out of the
end was just like i just can't
do it i was gonna do it
herself know do people do that regularly
does anyone here know anyone who's done
that
i don't the silence finally wow that
was actually interesting it was another one
like example that left yeah they're about
to talk about stuffing our dog got
off from the taxidermists attacks there was
a young guy here he's already
gotta go close in ten minutes
ah
it's so disgusting what they do they
like pull out all of the guts
yeah
and replace it with like newspaper newspaper
its magazines
it's like aussie benghazi glossies they go
around to every dentist's office and they
pick up whatever magazines are there from
three years ago why does it have
to be that why you have to
be dad that nobody had to be
dead i don't do this
why does it have to be dad
ah hello
oh oh oh oh did you save
any fur from your pets that i
have fur from my cat died and
oh okay i
i saved a blanket that smelled like
my dog
oh do you casually take ne i
was gonna put it in a vacuum
packed bag and then what in fifty
years open and go
or did you intend to send it
to space
along with that gold record dear astronauts
this was called a dog sees smell
till civilizations that this is what my
dog smelled like
ah what's going on with ufos by
the way i know there's a bunch
of marina tomorrow we're all supposed to
storm area fifty one isn't that right
oh yeah is that tomorrow it's tomorrow
get what we fuckin here what are
we supposed to do get the truth
yeah well what
it wants to get the truth lay
here for the cheers me and tom
de longe
we're going out there yeah that blink
we need to go tweeted it and
they were like that's illegal to share
something area what that that's what happened
i didn't blink when any two guys
share oh yeah the ufo picture then
area fifty one was like or whatever
will they said government was like this
is bad they said the we don't
know how you've got this smile i
only read
read tweets for the news
they said we don't know how you
got this you shouldn't have shared this
but yes these are unidentified flying objects
cool
which doesn't necessarily mean spaceship no they
just mean i can't identify they can't
see
what is that we have a blip
on the radar it might be a
frisbee we can't see
uh it might be a weather balloon
wearing a beard
it could be
ah i think i really believe in
aliens like a lot yeah
i just decided i honestly don't know
yeah i don't know either so no
i'm like yeah for sure i feel
like logically it makes sense but i
don't know how i don't know how
much we have been visited by them
i just love that we're obsessed with
one image of what they look like
and we don't come
up with any other option yeah we're
like they're basically us but they have
big eyes there are a couple options
they're searchable it yeah yeah the most
everyone talks about little green men for
a long time but now it's just
like grey the greys yeah the lesser
grey asic alien right there yeah be
bop boo boo boo
what a beautiful song did you ever
see that movie close encounters of the
third doe new acted out for me
yes i can scott
uh i'll be the tree
what did it do on richard dreyfuss
oh tree
i'm a regular suburban guy a fee
later
i love you high time for that
i gotta get my car yeah right
like what's going on on my half
my face is sunburned go onto my
wife high trees see my wife
have you checked over there i was
about to listen tell her i'm gonna
start making weird shapes in my match
potatoes oh lol i love you yes
i know
sure sir i can see the shape
the shape the shape that i see
on the tv devil's tower wyoming i
gotta go there and he goes there
and then um there's aliens oh wow
that's a that's a brief summation and
so was he drawing the shapes out
of
his control like it was like yeah
but he was compelled to do it
he was compelled to do it and
then he leaves his wife and children
to fucking alien to go
we don't assume a bully i mean
that happens off screen if at all
he goes off with them at the
end so he probably he has to
was like she makes once he decides
i'm going to check this out i'm
gonna go to this place that i'm
i feel compelled to go to we
never see his wife and children again
like were because he goes nuts i'd
like
to think that he gets on the
spaceship and you like takes a look
around while he's taking his pants on
like alright we doing this how does
this work
what's the etiquette here when they pull
out the adal pro but he's like
oh he's like i thought i'd be
doing it to you okay i think
it would be a great school though
is for that character to come back
now yeah and like what happened what
happened
and piper paramo is involved
karibu para boo berry bo bo roles
alright
wow
you don't think it's time for a
three-tier yeah i think it might be
i do
i think it might be time for
reacher what do we call this one
the visit gotten play or something got
lauren baldwin forgotten player or something yeah
it's called without a script it's called
actor's nightmare that's what it's called actor's
nightmare and this is this this is
the game where one person has
as the lines of play in the
other person doesn't and they just make
up their side of the scene should
we do it to people in one
person um do you have a three
person scene no let's do one on
one because is that so what is
going to hold the book what does
the other person do this game is
natural this game is fun this game
is best when it's one on one
the other person you my lover you
wear a rubber
you guys learn you missed it and
everyone was so scared of aids ah
we're not scared now no no one
is
the other person um watches in judges
judges yeah they should be a judge
you know that commercial i'm sorry was
a commercial for a prep where ah
i don't know if you guys have
it here but it's ah it opens
up with a couple of women saying
i'm on the pill i'm on the
pill and then it's a guy saying
i'm on the pill but it's not
the pill you're thinking of
yeah it's like well if you say
the pill that's been taken
yeah because that could literally mean any
yeah so i'm not the idiot here
it's not the pill you're thinking of
well i am yeah you could you
call it the pill
what this is i just saw a
billboard on the way that was like
you know the name just ask for
it viagra
okay you know the name you limp
dicked on your ma show i think
i say it and maybe it'll get
you hard don't you like i mean
why shouldn't ask you guys because who
knows i don't want to get into
it but i wouldn't ask ask ask
to ask go ahead i'm just saying
if i if i needed it i'd
be thrilled to take viagra oh yeah
i'd be like whoa no i think
i know you're you're right i think
people have taken are extremely thrilled yeah
i think that's dope just take it
who cares but tom which funny that
they decide to shame the people i
think it's more like don't be afraid
just ask for it but it comes
off like very pride for sure who
are you you know the name to
not
i'd say my day just say my
name i buy viagra say my name
are you fuck i dive ah so
it's cool it's cool it's really cool
really cool
i loved that pugh
um okay so how do i how
do we play this lauren um do
you want to be the reader firstly
the reader and and ah do you
want to go first or she either
says the actor in the nightmare what
you guys are close to each other
why don't you okay okay the most
shui stand i believe so okay as
i am already
and i'll judge yeah you should perch
i should perch yeah to judge yeah
it's the judge's chair okay
be the tree the tree that would
require holding his arms for a long
time alright alright i found a clue
in little logical reason why he shouldn't
be the tree
i found a two person scene okay
are you upstaging me right now
oh is that bad yeah it's the
term upstaging someone i'm judging and we
do the scene please do you want
to enter should i enter a both
or spoke enter this okay oh this
will be surprised that we see each
other
huh huh
well duh sorry i thought you would
be pleasantly surprised that you saw chen
do you want that we can we
can make know if i could give
a note yeah i mean i want
you guys to find it yourselves but
if i could just make a humble
suggestion
maybe you're not terrified
oh ah well ma the day has
come you're losing one of your chicks
you're gonna kill yourself
the groom's up shaving himself only there
ain't an awful lot to shave what
did you shave him last night
i told you shall we shave him
before your big day whistling and singing
like he's glad to leave us every
now and then he says i do
to the mirror but it don't sound
convincing to me wow
you think he's you think he's doesn't
really want to leave i mean i'm
i'm a little worried about that he
he's getting married in a minute to
you
i was remembering my wedding morning julia
what
i think he just said something i
would say
i was the scariest young fella in
the state of new hampshire ma yeah
it was she was a mean lady
i'm glad you got out of that
and you're back home living with me
but now you're gonna leave again and
marry your brother
i thought i'd made a mistake for
sure yeah when i saw you coming
down that aisle i thought you were
the prettiest girl i'd ever seen well
you know i was the first woman
you ever saw and it makes sense
your eyes i am printed right on
you yeah the only trouble was i'd
never seen you before
do we have to harp on this
i went away for a little bit
i was there for a lot of
your childhood
why julia hersey french toast
don't call me that i will smack
the teeth right out of your mouth
how did you sleep last night julia
hard as a rock
call me ma
yes i get a shock every time
i think of george setting out to
be a family man that great gangling
thing what a god you're so horny
you get a shot every time you
think about it i tell you julia
there's nothing so terrifying in the world
as a son the relation of father
and son is the darndest
awful warmest wird ist hey you said
it
look i know you hate your dad
and that's why you're gonna marry your
brother it's safer he's your age there's
a lot you haven't come almost they'll
have a lot of troubles i suppose
but that's none of our business everyone
has a right to their own troubles
yeah i mean you're talking about the
town they're gonna be upset i mean
no one's found out yet and i'm
surprised
you kept it a secret i saw
your instagram
julia do you know one of the
things i was scared of when i
married you
you did call me mom
so yeah i guess one of the
things you were scared of when you
married me was that it was incest
or bad
i was afraid we wouldn't have material
for conversation more ended last just a
few weeks
i was afraid we'd run out and
eat our meals in silence that's a
fact twelve you and i've been conversing
for twenty years now without any noticeable
barons so i don't i've decided i
don't want this i was on meth
and i went for it get away
okay what no you're marrying your brother
and that's that only day of the
year rebecca hasn't been managing everybody's business
up there she's hiding in a room
i get the impression she's crying
she said she's always been in love
with you
yeah
good morning everybody
yeah you know why don't you go
put your tux on and and get
ready for your new life okay five
hours to live so you aren't gonna
kill yourself and see
hey when i was touch i was
from our town by julia child jordan
wilder judge what do you think i
judged that to be terrific wow
okay so now you're gonna read or
what um
yeah you don't want it you read
okay and i'll judge and i'll be
the other person this is waiting for
godot
by samuel beckett
okay okay now how do we want
how do you want us to find
each other
i would love for you to be
expecting each other and then disappointed that
you're not there but then suddenly you
see each other you're in an ikea
and you're pointing up at the the
radio yeah alright
yeah
wow they've changed i know it seems
like yesterday that they were different and
now they're different in a different way
those two
just the two of them no more
it's a manageable number
haven't they
they have i believe
changed yes those two likely it's cert
and i mean didn't you see them
i saw them earlier and um you
know they looked good
yes you you do know them
no i do i saw them and
i know them enough to say that
they looked good we know them i
tell you you forget everything unless they're
not the same
alright i don't know
what's happening with you but you're making
it like i'm the crazy one and
i'm telling you i know them i
saw them they have changed we just
talked about it
that means nothing i too pretended not
to recognize them and then nobody ever
recognizes us what is this idea to
bullshit
we're not on the same page here
unless they're not the same
are you fucking kidding me
they are
approach my child
ah
yes
what do you want
you who called me over here
approach when you're told can you
what is this mind game
will you approach
what kept you so late i blocked
a step
what what is it
what is what
oh let him alone
okay man you know
i'm just trying to live my life
and whose is it mine no it's
mine it's my life
afraid of what of us surbhi
i'm not you know what i am
a little bit afraid of you i
don't know what's going on with you
and i feel like you're trying to
pick a fight with me
i'm unhappy
ah the joy
i had forgotten forgotten what
i've seen you before haven't i
ah yeah like now
you don't know me
i thought i did but
it wasn't you came yesterday
yes i came yesterday and we had
a very similar conversation to the one
that we started having earlier just now
and now i don't know where we
are
this is your first time
doing
words words no no
i know lots of words and lots
of them and i've used them for
almost all my life other than like
the first couple years i would say
i've been using words constantly
is that all
no that is not all
because what you're doing is i think
it's very undermining and you're trying to
make your review like gaslighting me or
something
you work for mister godot
now we're getting somewhere yes of course
i do what do you do i
do his he's got like errands and
you know people to call and stuff
like that you know busywork is good
to you
he's right you know
he's very particular about his birthday like
what you can and cannot give him
he doesn't beat you
not
any more
there was a strawberry misunderstanding that has
been sorted out
whom does he beat
ooh who me
d
uh oh yeah
how do you judge it scott that
makes about as much sense as the
actual well i have to confess that
it became a three person scene halfway
and i just switched care to okay
hopefully there is a two person scene
in there if not you can use
the third wilder book which has two
other plays in it think i found
you found one okay now how do
you want us to approach each other
i want you to um walk like
crabs
ah
ah do we notice each other these
crabs the crabs see cheddar and they're
happy
ah he doesn't know
bondo the c o
of the storm such peace in the
air where's the doctor oh you're here
for the doctor um yeah he's he's
a little he's running late so it's
probably going to be a few a
few minutes sophie
do i have a name tag on
had
how long are you going to go
on being short with me we've done
no harm to each other why should
we be enemies don't you feel enough
look i can yes
he's just he has a few more
patients that he needs to see but
i can move up to the top
of the list because i know he
wants to see you because of your
condition
i did too
good yeah i mean that that works
out
with all my heart
well um he wanted to see you
that's the reason he called you in
i think that he i mean i
don't want to you know tell you
what he's going to tell you but
i think he has some bad news
for you
no he's still sitting up
weeks at a time we don't speak
to each other god only knows why
what's this
that that's the um those are the
starbursts that we keep in a bowl
over there just for you can have
as many as you want if drink
with me
like do you wanna meet up later
as oh you're asking me i get
off in about twenty minutes or so
router shrift out of the same glass
will you kiss me
this is so sudden but to be
honest i've seen you come in here
every single day i don't know what's
wrong with you the doctor won't tell
me but and daily there must be
something really wrong but i'm really attracted
to you so yes i will
whoa why are you crying shh
now i feel like you're sort of
negating my feelings about this i'm crying
because i'm so happy that i finally
found love
shh shh
there now look
i've cry too
you are angry with me because you
think i married your father for my
own convenience if we believe oats i
give you by oh thought this that
i married him for love i was
drawn to have a famous man amount
of learning i was captivated by it
and it was real the love was
not real but i thought
thought it was real at the time
i thought it was real and i'm
not to blame sophie but since our
wedding day you haven't stopped accusing me
what you're the woman who married my
father
you did
i saw it in your eyes you're
clever and suspicious eyes looking on
i'm married my own father why don't
i remember that
you mustn't look like that on people
it doesn't suit you and we must
trust how can we live if we
do not look i trust you i
definitely trust you though i married my
own father and then you married my
own father
and now you're in love with me
and you want to drink with me
out of the same glass but what
does it all mean why are we
doing this yes
oh i see i see i know
the answers all along is that what
you're trying to tell me yes i
know the fact that that this is
all just some sort of sick twisted
game that you're playing with me is
added no
okay okay so this is a sick
twisted game that i'm playing with myself
i'm i'm punishing myself is that what
i'm doing what a school girl you
are
see
beautiful thanks chekhov three chair three chair
yeah thanks chekov
it made no sense
yeah is a good spot
feels nice which makes us approachable i
think
guys were running a time here we
are we are we got the light
i think we're out of time i
think we are because i've been going
for i literally have fallen we have
one minute left wow how do you
want to fill it let's count to
sixty
one two three four five rolls six
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen
twenty twenty one twenty two twenty three
twenty four twenty five twenty six twenty
seven twenty eight twenty nine thirty thirty
one thirty two thirty three thirty four
thirty five thirty six thirty seven thirty
eight thirty
thirty nine forty forty one forty two
forty three forty four forty five forty
six forty seven forty eight forty nine
fifteen thirty one thirty two fifty three
thirty four thirty five thirty six
fifty eight de vi
saturday ribeye rabbi ya thank you to
everyone to the queen elizabeth theatre thank
you to jaffa forty two thank you
i love you so much thank you
for coming thank you morocco
uh
a