three
florida huh
ah hi welcome to three-time this has
got less florid this is wrong we
are all eating chips yummy
let's change this show to yummy oh
hey kevin ready here we go again
and the moment's gone yep thanks seven
joan don't ever do oh no no
earn that offer the trash throw yourself
in the trash we get into that
trash can out that should be pa
out of his punishments get into that
trash can right now but you're putting
it down to pull your buddies rough
put your butt in that trash can
chevy and chevy is putting his butt
into the trash can lauren's gonna take
a picture that's what you hear that's
on it get in in it in
it this is what you deserve oh
you fell over
well he fell over from putting his
button a trashcan oh it broke
oh chevron is so fat he breaks
a trash can when he sits today
huh
seven so fat
twenty sits on drive daddy breaks it
too far too far sorry seven welcome
to threesome this is a show where
this happens and to you nothing are
not on board with this well i
hope you and i'm sorry to all
the people who hate when i eat
but you know sorry will give you
a hard time about that i don't
feel like you you don't make a
lot i think i'm high on raceway
i hate when you yeah
oh yeah i know you're always wanting
me to never do it again please
stop make this your last you starved
to death please don't ever eat again
don't drink water either
you're just a mummy next time easy
you said
and that's all you say you said
thanks sorry bye see you
euro mummy like pull up in your
escalate your mummy you said
escalating wave right yeah you got so
successful for being
you you leave here you never eat
or drink water again you biden escalate
shaking you're so stars for me you
know because it's money out of food
obama biden escalated with this
how much is an escalator i don't
know one hundred chevron look up how
much an escalate is what if i
bought you fifty dinners i'll say eighty
thousand eighty five i have no idea
i'm not a car person meaning there
i just think of a car shiny
it's nice
i just think of a car it's
shiny and nice so you're hanging out
the exit to the car wash just
like wow
gleaming seven what do we got seventy
five thousand hey was right there one
dollar i did five for a new
sunroof
new one may have only old spruce
ah chair this old sunroof i'll put
in a fresh new one
mom pop chips sea salt flavor yeah
they're really good i love them we
should be sponsored by them should we
yeah i'll say anything they want
say that you like anything they want
ah but cure my leukemia
thanks luke
i'm your father i am your demeo
okay we've already got oil okay the
idea of someone hearing that and then
only eating chips to try to fix
a problem
i guess it works paul f tompkins
said it was like if you got
that from those jared commercials for subway
like i been eating five sandwiches a
day and i keep gaining weight i'm
doing he's getting his ass beat in
jail
isn't ian saul is even better cause
i don't know i would think so
with no solitaire own ass yeah i
hope he's looking as odesk hope you're
trying to his higgins cottons but you
probably went to one of those country
club prisons were all the commercial guys
go yeah like who are the commercial
guys papa john's super dogs
what did you do i don't i
saw some tweet thing yesterday about and
he say he said a word i
shouldn't say yeah you said the word
on a conference call and then later
said he was pressured to say come
on come on say it pop up
you've got to do this job that's
so insane what how could you ever
be pressured into that come on say
it lord
yeah see how easy this papa john
look look what lord what do you
talk here
look i am your father look that's
like saying the whole time i'm your
father look let me say this there's
no difference it's just a film flub
everyone thought it was luke don't flub
but there's absolutely no difference in intent
between luke i'm your father and look
i'm your father same thing yeah when
darth vader was being real reasonable look
look i am yeah
founder the day
more
your father do you you know have
you noticed that after like since the
obama presidency when it started when obama
was president and now people do it
all the time on tv you see
pundits do it you see politicians do
it stuff like saying look all the
time i've noticed this look i haven't
noticed that it wants you
notice it you see it a lot
huh
ah i'm so sick joke right now
oh i don't want to watch that
i'm just really sick of it all
drag i just really want it to
be better remember when everything was happy
because we didn't pay attention or mindless
sheep i was thinking i tweeted
it'd like a joke a few years
ago i love it now and i'm
so proud you know that i had
that moment yeah
please play this song for the speech
just play our song or speech songs
chevron keep these cute guy goddamn you're
gonna sit in that trash can again
if this doesn't come on right now
but even a stronger trash will have
you break every trash canada's okay so
if years ago i made a tweet
wrote it i could say
no talkie name composed the composed crazy
they said what are you up to
i drafted i captaincy and i tended
to eat with words from my own
mind that were as follows this is
fucking insane
so what you're saying is hazy pretty
alright good buddy house i wrote
everyone can make a difference but it's
so slim that there's basically no point
that was your your boeing it was
my bio for awhile but after trump
it wasn't funny anymore because i feel
everyone should try to make a difference
getting up before i goddamn rosa it
seems so easy to be alive before
trump was in presidency
today my speech is alright speeches done
we all have to say our speeches
done and then that's how we know
the music gets i just it was
like the kind of joke you could
only make when everything was easier of
course there were a lot of problems
at the time but i'm just saying
now everything's so crazy every day that
like
just that kind of joke which also
was an app there's a joke about
apathy i was i'm not really an
apathetic person but
you have any more qualifications to this
story i'm five ten are you really
yeah well you know that how would
i know that i'm not sitting around
measuring you well yeah you are first
of all you just never went down
i guess um be
you went down you are constantly measuring
like i measured the year ahead yeah
and i never went down your feet
yeah
say well that's good enough right there
man i guess my villiers keep doing
it my feeling is of course you
know that because ah
are you often asked how tall you
are yeah i guess i feel like
i'm asked that all the time when
people meet me but i don't give
a shit i know you don't but
i'm saying if i would have would
have come up and you would have
heard it at some would have come
up
yeah sorry never asked anyone who told
their look i did a good day
never said look look look look i
do that to a woman who is
taller than me and i was like
i hate to be who's this woman
she's a new actress on crashing oh
miss maddy wise and she's taller than
you so she's like five one or
above
oh but um she wasn't positive about
them she wasn't positive that she was
six one what does she need me
to measure the top of her head
yeah she needs you too does she
need to go to the doctor maybe
i don't know but i was like
i've never been sick
people out because i'm always asked that
and i'm like who cares but i
was like well you're taller than me
and now i'm curious how tall michelle
you really are shrews are both also
wearing heels it was like to have
you ever asked anyone shorter than you
how tall are um i don't think
i typically do that
you know you're like how tall are
you down there yeah shorter you the
shorter you are oh were you always
tall were you always yeah well you're
on my whole eighth grade i was
five eight sophomore years five ten so
leveled out it just takes off where
you oh
he's tall i think i was always
tallish yeah taller taller than most of
my friends i mean i you know
i was a baby at one point
i was a tall baby i was
the longest baby anyone ever seen
bizarre
i was taught in grade school now
i'm getting sure you're getting shorter are
you really i was six two in
grade school why disgusting whoa hey that's
freaky but i'm just doing the best
i could and that makes you one
what is the tallest child all this
under terribly yeah tallest under ten according
to variety
are the telescope smallest kids under ten
dollars kids under ten seven look it
up god damn it or else you're
going in the fucking trash
do you think anyone's ever been one
of those thirty under thirty who lies
about their age yeah yeah yeah yeah
what are the thirty under thirty like
like mix under three yeah or whatever
we're just like forbes like i always
seem to remember the friends when they
first came out there i seem to
recall there was a rolling stone article
where they all gave all the women
gave their ages
and then all of the ages after
that disappeared and then they all said
that they were like five years younger
than they actually were or something wow
yeah i don't ah i don't appreciate
that you don't how old are you
thirty two and my age is well
out there now there's no well that's
the thing when i was thirty i
was like
fuckin just put my age out there
but i also don't i don't i
mean we've had this we have we
have talked about this i'm not getting
spanked for this
we've talked about this but i just
think that i'm a parent when i'm
here i'm just in case i'll find
it a little more um you'll be
able to share it as much but
i'm also like but i don't really
care i like i admire older women
who are their age and i'm like
i'm i think that's cool i'm like
yeah you're interested in knowing oh this
act
iris is fifty two and she's been
doing this for this long and this
is her life and she's you know
i just like it's it's cool it's
life i was friends with a couple
and when they broke up um i
was more friends with the guy and
then yeah bros before yeah wait well
because i knew him first yeah and
and then
then it was before but i but
i i did remain friends with the
with the ho
catches yeah yeah ah
ah i would hate difficult joke verbal
that's why it's so delightful
but she
she's an actress and she accused me
of
putting her age on i m d
b y
right why wouldn't you do that i
i don't know why she thought this
but she in her mind it was
crystal clear that because i sided with
him in their breakup i did that
she told me this years later and
then i i was like i did
not do that and i could tell
you that i could tell she sounds
like
you're soooo leaf she didn't believe me
and she's still might to this day
think that i did that i i
don't even know how you would do
how you would do it you could
go at it as information there you
can oh okay oh yes i guess
although i don't know how you go
about doing that will you do this
oh yeah alright maybe i just now
i know
i don't know if i've talked about
this but as on this topic japan
i just know somebody who's who lies
about their agent drives me insane and
she says she's ten years younger than
she isn't hey me wow ten years
so she's younger than me according to
her like so she says she's in
her twenties yeah and
and there's proof of where she went
to college and when she graduated in
something like so you got your mfa
at fifteen like no i know i
there's facts out there presented as a
mirror held happened
um no but it drives me nuts
i also feel like it puts a
riff i think it creates a rift
that i'm unable to cross in terms
of a friendship where i'm like i
can't even like i don't feel comfortable
asking you basically anything because because if
your bios basic yeah but but is
it something where she says oh no
i tell everyone i'm professional or just
short she would have told me does
she act like oh no i'm twenty
whatever
what does she do she does she
sort of come from that's the spanking
ten oh this is not the spanking
good baby it's a shame because this
cool cat on the it's okay is
that the spanking pet it's not even
a sharpie it's just some capitalists ballpoints
yeah oh this is no that's being
paying me indeed we need one of
those things a little hand
on
she has one share at one point
said she kind of said like i'm
actually older than that and then and
then when we tried to find out
the truth she wouldn't not go further
and then then i just my own
sleuthing online so you're you're a creep
yeah but it's most out of my
furious anger oh okay so far a
furiously angry about it that bothers me
which is like the idea that you
get a lot of credit for being
as good as you are at a
young age oh so it's like twenty
two when you started and you're so
amazing and that twenty two and you
got this thing and you did this
yeah and
then like then everyone's going like she's
like a like a prodigy over the
other kids but she's not and then
i also feel like it's also fine
to have been working at something for
ten years and then get success yeah
that is impressive exactly what are you
trying to
i gotta guess who this and i'll
tell you later now i want to
guess on it yeah
um that's crazy i don't have any
weird friends like that well why did
you look at me i'm just trying
the i'm db thing is crazy to
me a weird friend nah well i
guess so i mean i'm a weird
guy right d is annoying though because
as it's very easy to add information
but difficult to delete it is i
that's why she would be so annoyed
i did a show um a show
for mtv a million years ago called
super adventure team where it was ah
before um ah world police that ah
that ah trey parker mazzone america to
america it was it was a ah
a parody of those super mary
nation's jane ghouls nader yeah dana gould
and it was it was a really
funny parody of thunder thunder yes yeah
yeah yeah and it was really funny
but it was ah super adventure team
yeah i feel like i've heard of
that but i don't i wanna look
at and it but because it was
nonunion we all use pseudonyms um and
mine was francis
mt pleasant and so it was credited
ah on the on i m d
oh i remember this so i made
up a whole like bio for francis
mount pleasant and then at some point
my bio and that bio got merged
so i
had listed francis l pleasants height as
sick i think six five or something
like that then i would have all
these people everyone's want not all the
time but everyone's well somebody's seem like
you're not six five like i know
i'm not six i know that why
what how what am i gonna lie
about your age yeah i'm gonna make
it that
extraversion live on my timing yeah i'm
sub six foot five so here's what
i have to say about most easily
does yeah lovable thing what i have
to say about your story so you're
already up to i m d b
highjinks
it does check out you know when
she didn't know that i had done
this but i know that i do
and now we can go home soon
just a little bit fish is good
shit anything just seemed a little bit
fishy a little bit machine fish if
i swear to you to that i
swear not a trash can play the
song the song swear get in the
trash you're not getting the trash gallery
because i've done nothing wrong
i swear to you solemnly i saw
i do solemnly swear i may see
the two the both of you my
colleagues my companions my friends i did
not post that actresses real age on
the internet movie database while we're here
yes say paul f tompkins said i'm
coming to see dad
i just think that if you my
speeches are almost reaching no but maybe
speech to start from the beginning no
okay start from the beginning you're getting
a trade-in
i'm sure i can just use the
back arrow ok kit ou can't do
it he's making a speech my speech
begins as follows
i feel like in a relationship easy
you need to have some rules that
will help some new ones perhaps
just rules letter there's room just to
help you kind of navigate so number
one i would say one doping up
the phone he made you know he's
only calling because he's drunk and alone
what already sour sad yeah two don't
let him in you have to kick
them out again on me so you
should have no contact with this purse
isn't this just until he figures it
out let's just recap one to pick
up the phone you know he's only
calling cause he stabbed alone
okay we gotta go to overtake the
crack hole to fire
we'll be right back
and your name
ngannou rosa county
welcome back we have some exciting news
seven just announced he has what is
this now seven it sounds like by
the way you're asking for a ransom
i have the world's tallest child below
ten years old all i need from
you is thirty thousand dollars we don't
have any money are you willing to
ask twenty minutes
his name is ah koran singh from
india he's eight years old and he's
six foot six my wow
oh chez devis much what do you
do check it out yeah i hope
this info isn't coming from i m
db yeah i added that to check
it out chevron this is a true
chevron my god look at that he
looks like a teacher he looks like
the teacher that is the most like
confusing
image yeah okay fused i don't i
feel so bad for him yeah my
brain break may do you think he's
going to get even taller or does
he remain that's gonna be it i
think that's i mean that's it and
then i think the other kids are
gonna get taller than him by next
year
do you think this is some sort
of like nuclear reactor yeah owners yelling
what is that it's crazy what is
that man are you glad that you're
not one of them we are glad
we learn you're tall for woman ah
we're we're you aren't and have you
has that always been positive for you
know i think i was um self-taught
can the firestone
i think i was um i know
i was self-conscious about it growing up
and what slouch a lot real still
feel like i'm working on that now
but working on slouching let's see you
try
but um you nailed it i also
think it was one of those things
it's like it's difficult to be taller
than boys and like um also enacting
rules like i think that that it's
bad i find it to be bad
and actually tell me about this on
this show yeah no oh i
chevron i feel i ah okay we've
talked about it maybe in life okay
i don't know i don't think we've
talked about on the show okay okay
fashion but i was saying that i
think i have lost a role here
or there but i feel like we've
heard us say i think you've talked
about this on the show sega chef
and go ahead and speak yeah
works seven
and that's not i will definitely time
well that's definitely talked about you brought
it up you said jay loves it
i recalled you into i went to
i cannot be thinking i will not
be spanked for that chevron stay seated
knocking dead man then indeed me is
kinda what it feels like
we do that during sex baby skin
can finish kinda ooh
nah do it can abuse
i'm not gonna do it come on
just do it if i do it
don't finish the whole time they're having
sex is going back down dead nah
are you guys kidding me
if someone were if there was like
remember the ma boom guy yeah unfortunately
yeah um nasa guy on the bachelor
if someone oh wait what is that
i don't get this guy who just
big love oh man he was the
word was his catchphrase he wanted he
would sell t-shirts saying wow boom and
he was always like ooh
oh boom you will see the titular
bachelor the contest on the bachelor i
i see um he did not win
no he did not win how long
did he last pretty long too long
i would say he lasted like six
episodes it was crazy how long he
looks because of wow boom yeah it
was hell but um
if someone actually like that like how's
say you are on the bachelorette i
think this is a fun exercise to
imagine yourself on the bachelorette okay oh
those guys coming after me first of
all first of all would you like
just this would you like even fifty
percent of the guys that are on
the bachelorette know and we've talked about
this you need to get spf
hang in to any i'm not getting
spec but what i'm trying to say
is that high log them all off
immediately i'd be alone in the wow
how long would wow boom guy last
one millisecond he would look at me
and you'll get out of here not
happy when you get to get out
of here my only goal in my
late twenties lay on the bachelor i'd
be like you gotta find twenty five
of the
the funniest most interesting cool people that
would be so like football player we
have abs of steel looks like nobody
would just be like oh look like
foot i know i want i don't
care what they look like i want
to have i wanna have like the
best time and then i would see
i that would be so interesting you
weren't if you weren't in a otherwise
in involved i think that would be
ah that
it would be a show to watch
yeah like real like people who actually
might connect on a personality level i
don't know if i would want to
watch that i would watch lauren do
it i don't know i'm not saying
like hey john i don't know i
feel like you still wouldn't watch it
with me i don't want to see
any raining ah i mean
i don't i don't watch those shows
but i feel like a big part
of their appeal is how horrible the
people are right sort of but i
can there are so many would you
like me to chose when it's like
oh my god they're can't believe they
haven't had a deeper conversation than that
at this point they're gonna get married
like yeah watching the bachelorette last night
i'm not giving anything away but it's
like they i was
the one of the guys says like
oh she's so deep like we've shared
so much about our lives and was
like if it's anything that i've seen
yeah don't you think kids out though
maybe but i was like just kinda
things been deep enough that like it
really because they can't set up the
cameras used all the time i know
we've talked about it so but also
i think that i don't think that
they actually share i think the cameras
are on most of the time
i'm what they're when they're interacting with
the guy but no remember they eat
off camera before the dawn camera private
i think i don't think it's yeah
but that's what i'm saying is i
don't think they're together oh they eat
separately i think they didn't bring essay
arrived the date having a separate them
and they just eat before they just
all day dates i'm saying that they
eat first with the cameras off of
it
well yeah it was never clear how
you just put on your jack i
did i'm i have to go
guys are talking on the bachelorette conversation
ah yeah made me uncomfortable um yeah
i don't know if it was if
it was i guess it would be
i guess i would feel more invested
if it was people whose personalities i
enjoyed yeah you know i guess i
would be more but then i don't
know if that would just make me
more uncomfortable the idea
of them competing i think what annoyed
me would be interesting hurtful if he'll
yeah had to have brain but well
that's the thing because it's also a
fitch people that if it's the type
of people that are not usually the
type of people that would be on
one of these shows why would they
be on the show hey you know
to watch them compete it's like you
really can't wrap my brain around warren
was on the show
show yeah and then she got duped
by one of these guys like the
bachelorette always seems to get duped by
someone who has ill intentioned yeah there
is not there for the right reasons
he would be so interesting to see
lauren get duped by way this is
a common saying on the show yeah
yeah oh mean like for for weeks
wannabes what other reasonable like to be
on t because they want to be
the next
the bachelor some yeah bachelor in paradise
so they did that how was this
ram girlfriends back home who lawfully come
up and go what the fuck were
he and i have been dating for
ways to summon have handled that well
does the show know this or no
maybe yes or no but i think
it'd be really interesting does the show
act like they knew it or did
they act like they're surprised
super surprised yeah but it'd be really
interesting to be like a friend of
yours and be watching at home going
loring i fell for z you fell
for the wapo guy he's the one
boom guy in private and he has
a heart of what it is when
i'm watching a show is that i'm
like they i think what i don't
like is watching people fall in love
think like i'm like oh i think
i've talked to the guy at a
party and like not hate him but
there's something about watching him fall for
her i think i have to say
fucking eighty i feel so uncomfortable watching
anyone kiss i don't know how anyone
does it you fast forward through don't
you
i actually do i know what i
like i was like brought i fast
forward through everyday like watch that but
but i don't know how anyone ever
gets together like the first moment where
someone's like come here yeah you know
especially can't even flirt any more i
haven't used camel used to be commerce
like that with
as someone i was working with at
one point who said oh it's so
hard now because you can't say i
was like you i said you know
the difference between everybody does it's just
everybody does i didn't really know him
does like i was like no i'm
the feminist who doesn't assess fucking good
fucking argument drives me crazy
easy it's like a lot either you're
lying paul you are a very dumpers
no route
have you ever you have seen yourself
kiss on screen right yeah yeah yeah
that is really weird it's weird yeah
it doesn't feel real seeing other people
kiss it looks like i think i'd
like in a movie and we're like
two attractive people in a major hollywood
motion picture
it's like this is hot yeah stop
people kissing this they see me and
it's like yeah yeah usually it's usually
the council that i have to do
it with are also you know friends
of mine are friends because because they're
like yeah yeah yeah you know so
it's been like natasha lucero or ah
or coops good friend
and ah you know like it's howard
yes the only like straight the only
stranger was abigail's spencer from that time
show or whatever that was the only
like stranger who we had to each
eat a hot dog from opposite ends
in the middle and catch kiss with
a hot dog in her mouth so
glad that show got cancelled and
oh ursa know she was great but
kershaw oh myself yeah no but she
was great because she was like we're
bonded for life because of this weird
thing we had to do it's just
very funny yeah it's very fun she
made me feel comfortable about doing it
but i hate just like yeah i
wrote this and you have to kiss
me it's it's gross it's terrible
yeah yeah who would have to do
a handful of ah gross ones that
are funny and then i've had to
do a handful of actual ones what
were your actual ones pete holmes
pete holmes
john cho when you kiss on show
i mean no one will ever like
that sound like i was doing yeah
i know i know what you were
doing a little a little boy we
do a little voices that wasn't so
what unfortunate timing kind of out what
unfortunately this is kind of a say
let's get a clean john cho john
cho
oh no you can't not do it
and adult swim thing
um are you searching through your spanking
rather for ah
a guy in some music video a
guy and so the they might be
jolly yeah that's one of the most
watched either post it in our mouths
just a case of really bad what
and what is fixed big it's some
like like glycerin yeah and it was
just glue sue rusting i don't know
been a bunch and i actually always
feel surprised that i'm ever in a
situation i just never assumed i'd have
to do that yeah that you always
thought that you would get into acting
i never have to kiss it like
i would just be like like do
you know what's funny i've i've done
a couple pilots i've done a couple
of pilots where i played here ver
you can't even do that anymore
you gotta like try to kiss someone
and they go harder in your face
i've i've played i've played like husbands
a couple of times in pilots and
one i remember one where i hot
where i had to kiss my wife
and it was the first time i
i had kissed a smoker after not
being a smoker oh yeah and that
was our row
i've been realising like oh how many
girls have i gone out with that
about it where you kind of let
it go but yeah it's like yeah
yeah i've dated when you think about
it smokers and it's always gross to
start but then i just think the
human drive to do that shit just
must be so intense that we just
use the old gross shit you just
end up going like
who cares yeah but then i played
a husband another time where ah we
didn't kiss there was nothing written in
there but there was also like there
was a scene at the end where
it was like are we in real
life we will be with kiss yes
yeah but then we were both kind
of on the same page of like
we don't need like one noise telling
us to do it so we're not
gonna do it right but then i
remember thinking it's weird do you know
what avi yeah like if you were
watching that you'd be like huh but
when they don't would you miss it
if it wasn't there yeah you know
but it seemed because i remember like
spending a lot of time thinking like
are they going to make us do
this i'm ok you don't have a
re but
then after it was over i was
like oh we probably should have because
it seemed i think it is weird
sometimes when you're in those roles and
you don't have any physical yeah yeah
yeah i always i also think it's
your number if not making me doing
when you're improving and it comes up
and you do it is always never
done improv i know i'm oh you
mean improvising in
and i've been able to get on
stage like so easily i'm like i've
never once been in a situation where
that had to happen did i tell
you the story i just want to
ask about the first time i had
to kiss on stage i don't yes
so i didn't tell that story about
my creepy teacher yeah oh yeah yeah
got away because everyone dolls you get
up here and show and i've done
yeah yeah
but you were you just saying oh
that they're kissing during improv in pro
yeah oh it's like an unscreened like
i like i always find it like
because the moment is there and you
know you should and you know you
would as the person yeah hey but
then again it's like usually for like
janet varney i think was in something
we were just like we're supposed to
be walking down the street arm in
arm and having a good time and
we're
we're married and it's like at that
point where you're like well we would
okay and it's just what it's like
the kind of thing where i think
it's difficult with improv because part of
what makes it easier as an actor
is like talking about it beforehand and
knowing it's going to happen and mean
right okay then won't kiss someone do
that right yeah i don't know but
i i find that when it will
do this
so what i owe finger au plus
au lait pour song too far but
play oh look we have to take
a break on bud play as fair
we'll be right back breaking bucket but
pause but pause alright we'll be right
back
welcome back paul you have teacher i
do have a feature my name is
paul great i don't have a feature
my name is woven
oh feature
my name's john cho
alright this comes to us from j
t justin timberlake twitter handle is bet
the turner don't know what that don't
know
me and my wife my wife my
wife says bore out
since speak and spell
borat says my wife
my wife played pitcher sit song pitcher
said song it's time to play pitches
hit song one gives the name of
a song and the other pitches of
tv show based on the name of
the song now i'm going to assume
this these are popular songs yes you
take ah pop songs that we all
know the titles to and then you
make up a sitcom
just based on that titles man somebody
wrinkle at the end somebody calling themselves
certified huge boy johnny brad johnny briars
says i like this thanks and the
reverse someone invents the sitcom and someone
has to sing the theme song well
guess what i don't like that but
but here's the new wrinkle that we
decided we would do no rank to
do to z and take a sog
you take a songs take a song
title you have to make a sitcom
about it then come up with a
theme song for the sitcom then i'd
take different i think the person who
came up who who pitched the song
title then has to come up with
the theme song to the sitcom that
the other person has invent interesting okay
okay again i'm an interesting guy okay
so so we first start with a
song yeah exists yeah and you and
so you know what i'm sorry kevin
we play the speech music
damn it
i just want to say thank you
to the listeners sri for submitting back
these feature ideas okay that's the end
of my speech okay good speech
like guys when you say can i
ask if you want the speech music
to kevin play that speech music or
you go into the trash i also
really want to thank everyone who sent
in suggestions because they're really helpful for
us and shove it to beat up
the right things
alright who's gonna come up with the
song okay so you play outside you
just say you know you just say
this okay so the song is smells
like teen spirit okay and you're looking
at me yes i'm gonna be okay
okay here's my hi guys thank you
so much for seeing me sure it's
fucking tiny water really appreciate it did
you need a tinier waugh
iter we have smaller ones it's just
a cap with water and you look
like a little cat yeah okay yeah
i'd love that yeah to say meow
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
thank you so much i'm i'm here
to pitch a show it's a yeah
we know half hour multicam like the
more cameras the better as far as
multiple cameras yeah so one hundred cameras
behind the bullets so
it's all right sort of matrix usually
they're all in a circle bobo this
so comfy you want to do all
the time yeah alright okay
this is a show called um smells
like teen spirit okay and it's about
a detective who his name is smells
it it's strangely enough is and it's
detective smells and doesn't know how to
conjugate
he sure yeah i can work with
that he has no idea how to
conjugate um smells like teen spirit um
oh it's smells like comma smell but
it was smell like likes teen spirit
no no no no it smells like
properly in that context mills like someone
else named
teen spirit no i mean anytime he
introduces himself someone says oh smells like
teen spirit got it and why because
he's he's introduced himself as detective smells
and they're like what does that snell's
spells they don't know what it is
he says no smells and they go
oh smells like teen spy
garrett god yeah got it okay so
what's it about it's about a detective
who ah when he gets to a
crime scene he's blind he's deaf but
he's not until he gets the crime
scene once he gets good crime scene
he basically knows he's at a crime
scene when suddenly i do right right
his finger
chest who turned out the lights yeah
he says who turned off the sound
his his fingerprints have been shorn off
and he has no feeling in his
fingers he says who took away the
feeling and all you can do to
solve these crimes is to smell the
various bodily things that are out there
the blood okay piss the law come
i don't know what's the theme song
so every crime involves these bodily fluid
yes fillers but i love it
so you have to develop a i
live it to ice will show what's
the theme so you're the one who
wrote it to go ahead i thought
you know i wrote it well i
guess i wrote it together okay
what is this theme song smells smells
smells smell
smells smells what's in your life ya
gotta grab life by the hoe or
self smells smell smell smell smells smells
as well seeing your life you gotta
grab life spies be online
the smells smells
smell says you're alive now your god
who investigate the crime scene by smell
smell smell smell smells smells smells by
law guarding the skin it's crime scene
by the dell's mouse but unless god
this smells will buy it yeah i'm
rich
that's great
alright now i do as you tell
him a song okay um
it is ah a song by the
name of i'm already dreading when i
have to come up with no why
can i think of anything i'll hold
on i'm gonna go into my itunes
that the perfect solutia and go into
my i tunes so into my eyes
okay
a this is a song called
ah the sun always shines on tv
really do wanna hear a little bit
of you know
whose things it's aha
ah huh
this no does not mean no
whoa wow the metoo movement caught up
with you do we have that drop
cut that out
paul f saying no does not mean
no
alright um hi welcome hi shane
tom so okay so we're in a
bit of a rush and we're a
bit of rush i'm his assistant um
and he has someone to be so
i just wanted to be very clear
that you need to get in and
out as fast as you can i'm
now taking pitches as well um just
as a test oh i hear alright
will you validate my parking yes i
will but every man thank you some
oh yeah
um we want to see if this
is a good pitch before thank you
oldie sure i understand that that you
know and i think you will not
be sorry understating thank you for meeting
with me i understand you have a
limited amount of time so i will
make this brief
people who watch tv like to be
reminded that they are watching tv they
also like how do you know that
i think that's true as a research
or my personal research i like to
watch tv oh hello do i reminded
of it so right wow i love
it i love the style i love
this thank enough people also like
like nice weather this i think is
a very combo you're pitching us the
weather channel that's a good idea that's
a good idea well i just got
sold we need a new one there's
a new one there's the new weather
channel i'm glad you liked it weather
channel two point because there's a lot
of weather channel's stuff oh come on
here good here's what else people like
they like stories about themselves okay so
great so three things they love to
be reminded they're watching tv yes they
love weather related things that's a local
race whether it was nice weather nice
weather so okay this is the first
second person television show oh okay so
second person as in you
you're walking down the street and you
think that this is that's second person
in in literary right yes yes okay
go ahead yes go ahead i think
all right you talking down to him
no i'm agreeing with the way your
face i'm kinda freaking him in yeah
see i just i just can't believe
i'm here as all kick him out
so if i look encourage
oils to get the fuck outta here
get the fuck out here and button
up the back of your pants by
the way what is it
are you an old grandpa from a
western
yeah you're reading okay right well i
was totally wearing but you lie on
your head i was told where unions
oh so dress like johnny appleseed for
this bitch okay you're right you're right
we shouldn't be give you just call
me a bitch no he's ed page
you are told to wear loose sagan
i was i was told firmly on
the apathy for this bitch
okay let's continue we'll see where it
is so so i like where you're
talking to her so good yeah and
so just to be clear we've all
lost track of what you were talking
about the first second person television show
so
every thing that happens on the screen
is addressed directly to the viewer so
everyone's looking into the camera so all
the other actors like jackie o fourth
wall there's none taken
second person no fourth wall and what
about first and third yeah are there
the first walls and the third wall
who ah third base so what happens
is you're watching the tv show yep
the the characters in the show say
thank you for watching the tv show
got it it's a nice day out
do you want to see god that's
a camera swings around we see the
scenery outside great swing back person says
it's always like this here haha and
there's giant santa time so jokes no
jokes radio we wanted to pitch you
a theme song for it because we
yeah because we love by tom i'm
not gonna buy
it but we do want to sing
you a song like how about this
if i buy the song yes will
you buy the show okay yeah that's
a good trade yeah because the exact
same amount yeah right damn right here
we go the sun is out i'm
talking to yeah oh the sign is
out i'm telling you yeah oh the
sun always shines on tv the sun
always shines on tv mad and real
at the sono chan til finma s
over
well get the fuck out of your
office bye-bye
great
eyeball it's your turn to come up
with the sra i forgot already yeah
look in your eye to give me
any pain the wicked be literally anything
should have been new rule no kevin
okay hey don't bring that it's just
only wearing a book shit to shipment
to this show don't do what i
wanted to do with chevy
okay
the song is stairway to heaven hey
thank you so much gentlemen for meeting
with me i'm so great to me
what's your name i'm a woman
i as a gentle man i'm so
sorry i was only directing him i
didn't see you hiding behind him i'm
a hiding woman so mister and ma'am
think mr mr xu were married mister
and missus grendel snatch i'm so thankful
for this opportunity my name of courses
peers um hello pin courses
his piss i i mean of course
because i'm sure you got an email
explaining my oh we know everything about
you please know and know that i
started the first roller coaster company in
america don't piss on my head and
say it's rating your child prodigy yeah
i did that when i was twenty
it's wrong but actually thirty
well that's that's not true um but
i won't really get into all that
okay now got it looks tasty with
some references okay so my show that
i want to pitch you i'm getting
into tv now is usually we do
call it a soft page um are
you soft i married man i feel
you may feel your day
yeah i feel you
very soft yeah that was you feeling
high five a wet hand hey of
course lotion on it of course lotion
wet hand with like microbeads yeah and
that really sloughs off the dead skin
making it very bad for the environment
yeah it says beat the don't call
away yeah yeah thank you so is
it okay so the idea is this
show called stairway to heaven okay religious
actually not oh so i think speaking
it's a show about people who all
are atheists okay who ah when they
died they realised they because they don't
believe in god they have to climb
all the stairs to get to heaven
instead of just going right now shore
and so along the way
way they saw the only difference in
trying to be in make a difference
here on earth is you have to
climb a few stairs to get to
heaven well i basically say i'm sure
it's more than a few right page
well that's the thing it's pays but
is there's a page that i'm making
there are hundreds and thousands of stairs
so of course episodes go lower because
on every
a few stairs is a whole new
love so a hundred thousand episodes could
it could be i would say probably
do the buy a fifth because i
think we can only make like ten
so okay total ten yeah so that's
great so i'll just have one episode
of her season no ten episodes one
oh ten sees ten seasons of one
eps
okay so it's very similar lost in
that everyone's kind of struggling with their
own stuff and as you climb the
stairs there's different sort of platforms of
of existence and they're all struggling to
battle their inner demons in order to
get them to heaven what about literal
demons are they battling though and of
course sometimes there are literal demons that
will jump out and attack it's very
similar really jump
pick up out from either husbands okay
was there a on hills or angels
in this oh you hispanic know i
am oh okay um there are olay
there are on health um and angels
so we both want to shoot it
in both spanish and english and
i'm playing the spanish and spanish speaking
countries bernie skeletons like crown she reverse
that play the english and spanish speaking
countries and vice versa well because people
wouldn't really understand exactly what they have
to do a little research okay i
think it's great so would you guys
wanna buy it
did we get to the end at
the end everyone gets to heaven and
it's clear i'm it's gonna be very
clear what the whole allegory was in
that it's very blatant that it is
just climbing the stairs to heaven because
you do not do not believe in
god yes okay okay thank god well
right well i don't know that i
want to buy it but i definitely
want to sing i wanna sing
about it there's a lady who knows
no let's sing the real song please
because i can't get the rights to
that song and i can give rise
to the title but just need to
be a different song okay here we
go so this is a beautiful duet
here we got an i'll start it
great
i never thought that i could believe
in anything a i never far that
i would have c and on his
way means i never thought that i
could afford ah piano for my
ho but i bought a piano and
you can buy one to come on
over to my piano store is we
gotta be you
two pianos for two pianos for jews
please buy pianos from musk where the
piano brothers and we have be yeah
nose foe you
oh yeah oh those piazza yeah pianos
pianos pianos for you
what do you do
they say pianos
because i don't remember susan we make
you upset me i just so remember
some mommy where we bally's pissed his
where we bad i thought you show
up for his yaddo know it's short
for pizazz
oh sorry
i guess do you want to buy
my show no oh we want to
be singers oh yeah okay
you can
and we want to sell pianos jews
so specific
well
get out get out jones
and mr and mrs you want to
see your next
yes send her in belligerent or him
to man okay send him it was
too close woof thank hello
hi where were you just crying laughing
over having sex a little bit of
both if i'm honest
i want thanks for hiding behind me
while we did that because i won't
charge you for something special it was
easier whatever you want
whatever you want sir you seem like
a trustworthy solar yes sir answering a
surprise party i need a good song
about everything good hey where are you
from
yeah is that hawaii
do you have any parties please
in the song about having party
oh please think i said i'm having
party hard e hardy when the zaydi
be gay it seems like it'll be
fun oh a party pirate out of
some gin and some tonic for you
i only brought tonic but that's okay
because somebody
bull don't drink some people don't drink
they stink the pain but still strain
your living group is a great piano
sue precise can we sell you a
p yeah oh i knew piano make
some room sing
pianos pianos reina sofia
woe be for you was perfect for
me
okay that's all the time we have
wow wow listen i want to say
i had a good time i had
a great time and i had a
grand time piano grand piano time my
canada article that you know we talked
about stuff that made sons for
full hour
do you want your theme song yeah
you wanna make a speech free i
just really appreciate what we've all done
and like the way that we all
come to this table was honest bear
willing to share it's so great at
your nude
yeah i'm baron raby share
okay we'll see you next time
a yano please
uh