three
sorry
three never remember
three oh shit meal or lunch guests
hey guys it's me paula
hello everyone i'm scott optimise
who gives a shit who booties
a
three
hey yang rye was cool that was
very cool thanks to as cool as
us that it knows cooler than us
you think it was cooler than us
my god yes by life scenarios ah
that was said to us via twitter
by ten or brown tanner will always
to kill tanner and brown yeah
wow that's how i mean he's so
much tanner that he is breasts with
brown at this yes wow what's his
handle that's what i'm gonna look up
right now oh bobby bobby boop boop
boop planner evading his phone tanner forty
one o five on twitter wow what
does that sound or and he's got
around for sound for it sounds for
you
ooh
it sounds for thee the bill that
he's got a patreon if you want
to support it oh no thanks go
go go chum have any money for
that santa i but my budget is
very tight very entitled tanner very tiny
thank you everybody j tanner ten page
i support ten patrons mum and they
each
do different thing what are your patriots
my support the patriots that is the
bank that is mine
ooh very clever lord very clever
i'm paul f tompkins i'm broadway and
ca i'm plumpy plumpy thought people opperman
that's going for your fans poppy lawsuit
hey it's cool for your fan you're
so contemptuous of my fans i just
can't least say hi c'est i'm gonna
take them all down one one oh
get your own isn't it
funny to think that we all have
we have fans in common yes but
then there's also probably people that like
us each into yours there are people
do not like the other two and
there are people who like us each
individually and don't know the others even
exist yes isn't that weird those are
more common i think then the people
who hate us
then the people who like like one
of us but hate the other two
my fans all they they like me
each they each like me for one
thing and are not very aware or
interested in the other things that i
do write my fans each like one
thing chocolate
their chocoholics check a holiday fico they
call you their chocolate goddess yes they
want me back and they gonna take
a minute at the time
ah i advanced from the tv show
balance i imagine
yeah who don't even know there's a
podcast yes yeah and that's why it's
like it's funny i was just talking
about this with um you know somebody
i guess not me scabrous on raised
by tv and we're saying like how
it's so annoying to always have to
promote your podcast but then you're like
every time i've hosted someone goes out
a new podcast and it's like wow
i guess i gotta
tell you my podcast everything dung day
so that everyone out there finally learns
one by one they had twenty eight
in my case ding dong dae every
ding dong day like i got there
and tie you got a podcast every
day is that your podcast easy nature
pied right now i have a podcast
that comes on tuesday wednesday thursday and
friday and that is my illness that
has mystic too many podcasts to be
arrested i talked i talked oh okay
um i was in philadelphia recently i
did some shows there was super ego
and you know is a big theater
and it's the dead of summer and
tickets were moving slowly and of course
i have a stake in it it's
my hometown i wanna sell this thing
the fuck out yes you want to
walk out on stage and have everyone
give you an old philadelphia
aafia cheer ooh i don't want that
that fill it i'm no fanatic going
crazy in the crowd i did want
him to be there yeah that one
is next on news show am i
oh hey we're we're playing philly with
a comedy bang that's right and just
we looked out into the crowd that's
in november oh right and we just
looked out into the crowd and there
was like yeah he bought a ticket
it is a city you're not doing
any antics right now he's just sitting
there watching the show she does yeah
he doesn't laugh he ticks every space
inside the theater cause i love it
i love while his tongue his tongue
would shoot out when you like nobody
doesn't laugh he's very polite i think
he doesn't laugh but when he that's
how you you know he's you know
he's not laughing okay because his tongue
is not
shooting i concede to what you know
thank you i don't want to be
challenged on the fanatic he is your
lord and saviour he is indeed look
like laurence meyer laurence lord and taylor
easier robin lord taylor he's my he
is my robin lord taylor one that
was with robert laura taylor was a
man
ascot for sports yeah i like him
to be our message that hey if
you're out there listening he's a wonderful
actor he plays penguin on gotham oswald
couple pot um friend of billy eichner
i've met him on a plane once
very nice guy i've met him in
a radio station we were crossing over
he was lee was show as i
was yeah with john edwards i loved
that show
did you wait we're gonna say you
were trying to sell out also i'm
trying to sell the place i'm promoting
it every day online multiple platforms any
others there's a there's a point where
that feels bad you feel yeah just
end it also has you feeling just
bad to you if it feels like
it looks pathetic like yeah hey i
guess this guy really can't sell tickets
to the show and think it looked
pathetic i thought it looked strong thanks
masculine silence i thought if i looked
powerful yeah it's human but that's all
i want to appear as powerful and
human and so
so the day after the show i
posted a thank you to everybody who
came out to the shows with a
picture of of a super ego made
you look weak
at the end i think you look
subhuman the guys said oh man it's
been like a middle person so
you haven't evolved for overachieving share
flour sack over my head
so i i posted this picture said
thank you and thanks everybody for coming
out and this guy said oh man
it's been ah the bucket listing of
mine to see you live in philly
i gotta keep my my eyes peeled
for this kind of thing and wow
you will be you will be mortified
when you discover how much that fucking
show
wait i almost lost my goddamn ma
yeah wow maybe it did and you
just don't know do you think this
is this you my secret visitors coming
to ninety nine my visitors may come
to witness oh it's one of those
shirts at the supernova show okay that's
cool lauren we have to talk about
your hair your hair is red it
is
gotta tell you about the elephant in
the room is the red elephant in
the yes my hair is red i
dyed it red for i say i
did not notice it until you were
talking you guys were talking about your
but here's my piano gerwig said a
word anymore were you eavesdropping on our
conversation you were sitting right next to
me so it doesn't matter mansion jones
yeah something came up and you said
did you hear
that i do not want hear but
these loopholes we were having a conversation
me and paul na to you it
was a and b conversation so why
didn't you see your way out of
it
next tuesday i realised even twenty years
ago that i think i have like
hair color blindness ah huh um
where i don't know but and here's
how it happened i was i had
a girlfriend who was blonde when i
start dating her and then three months
in i think she changed probably she
changed her hair to read and i
didn't notice it wow and then then
i was like describing her at one
point and i was like she's like
how would you describe me to people
or whatever i was like
oh you know blondes z and she's
like i have red hair and i
looked at her i was like in
my head was going
oh she changed her hair color and
i was like oh it just i
meant when i first started dating you
you could you see it then though
when she said yeah once you said
it i noticed it but it's happened
with cool up to wear like shifter
magoo i don't look like here is
red i don't get their hair know
i like you ignore the top of
the
the top of that i'm i'm ice
frame anything above the eyebrows i'm not
interested oh cool i like that sheriff
my wife is there i will look
but if my wife is not present
i will not look at the topics
we take khula has changed her hair
like when she comes home from you
know getting your hair done or whatever
it usually takes her saying like what
do you think you
you know yeah i go like oh
you did something you have to wait
for it to put down all the
bags and hat boxes yes well what
do you think and you're a typical
man in that sense it's very that's
very like hiring a typical man i
don't think i did not stereotype writer
hey i don't i think it's weird
i don't know why i'm not i
don't look it is odd i know
kind of thing like we're like in
like the typical sort of thing where
it's a woman going notice anything different
about me and he's like yeah did
you get feather and then you say
no i made to you by the
way i wanted to ask you did
you get better yes i got better
um i dyed my hair red for
a job that i can't speak of
and um
and i kind of it was kind
of interesting because i like have turned
down dyeing my hair for jobs multiple
times we were playing bozo the clown
yeah fuck yourself ah my subtle yeah
so yourself
i've like i've been asked to color
it multiple times for jobs because a
lot of times their sitcoms stuff will
be as basic as a situation priority
to people who at the santa clara
harris yes yes yeah if you tell
told apart yeah right yeah so they'll
be like ah can you get your
docker for this and i'm like no
and then they would do someone else's
hair like that's happening with them so
where
dye their hair because they like already
dyed their hair a lot and i
always got out of it because i
had virgin hair because i never colored
my parents and they'd be like ooh
we can't ruin it and so then
this job i had been thinking about
possibly changing the hair color excuse me
huh huh
and so it was kind of in
my mind but it was still something
i probably would have taken months to
even consider doing for real but then
they said will you dye your hair
red-faced and i was like sure and
then everyone was like so fucking happy
about it and then did you suspicion
oh yeah oh they like so much
they it was
the character because the character has red
hair and it's because she's a firebrand
it's supposed to be that way and
so i was willing to go with
it but the second it happened i
got because it was like so it
wasn't like i spent you know a
while looking at pictures and choosing the
exact shade or anything like that it
was really just like the chose for
you yeah but
was like kind of weighed in but
then they kinda ignored it like it
was not this ended up not being
the color that i thought it was
gonna be and after it i was
like i'm sorry my thoughts really
annoying today but after it happened i
went i was like truly like i
couldn't leave this lawn fast enough because
it was like it's hard to like
look at yourself when clearing your throat
sorry for being gary it's hard to
like look at yourself for me to
like look at myself with when there's
been a change if i'm not sure
i like it i don't want anyone
to witness what i'm going through with
my deciding whether i like it or
not but i don't want them to
once you've made the decision you invite
people in yeah but i was like
true like i need to be a
home alone
don't looking at this in the eye
i need to be flopping along my
face yeah i completely understand this and
i think like if if after you
got your hair cut if the person
would walk away and just like give
you the party
so like get a section like a
local little bit and be like oh
yeah put your hands through and kind
of think about it yeah because you
feel so much pressure when the ones
that take you to look at it
look at to decide to i mean
like my typical going for me typically
going to the salon it's pretty basic
i do like the same for variations
of a thing over and over again
and i'm like i know if
i like it i know that once
i washed it it'll be different i
know what's gonna happen this was like
so unusual because i've never colored my
hair that it was like okay i
have red hair and he was just
like i don't even know what that
means it's suddenly like threw everything i
knew about myself into like another dimension
and it was so dementia strange because
i was like wait so i guess
i've been holding onto like my hair
colors being a huge part of who
i am
really what i didn't know jar is
is ah how would you describe it
like ah blond ash brown like yeah
dirty blonde sort of hair but i'm
filthy filthy dirty dirty dirty blonde while
she blonde hair but i've truly was
like i don't know don't you kind
of take your cooler for granted like
i would just never really think about
but if your hair was suddenly like
a different colored bic well
okay mine yeah mine has started like
the grey is really come in in
the front and on the sides and
a pie in the back i still
a party in the
but i but i i like it
because it was a gradual thing yeah
you know and i don't like you
woke up well no no no yes
i know you just my shockwave my
essay dark for a really long time
for a really long time so it's
not really like the last year is
when the gray has really become like
noticeable
you can see it in the front
um and i'm ok with it but
you know i i think that but
i i've dyed my hair in the
past like i've done my hair when
i was younger i did it just
to fucking do it you know like
what blue i dyed it i dyed
it blonde wow when i was it
how it was i like so eighteen
something like that yeah you were eighteen
to try and ah you know horrible
the scabs on my head oh my
god it was sort of a homemade
job that's really yeah yeah yeah it
was it was a horrifying procedure um
that sounds disturbing and it looked ridiculous
on me like it not it didn't
seem like mgm blonde yeah it was
like platinum blond yeah yeah and then
i let it grow out and then
i for a while i had
like
i had just like blonde tips on
my hair and oh wow i was
like a porcupine that's awesome how old
are your wills that was that was
like a year later like i'd let
it just gradually come out without like
sort of philly style
i don't know just like oh either
i don't know it was scarce but
i've yeah um yeah i've dyed my
hair seven me tea by the way
which is very kind to die for
a role much like you ah what
was it oh hey did you go
black for the ah sarah sarah silverman
yeah did i talk about yes yes
so that was
they did it several times was that
i'm at all i do so yeah
if it doesn't look like cut it
too fast i wouldn't say look great
yeah but ah yeah it is easier
with shorter hair because you just like
let it grow a little bit and
yeah yeah and it kind of made
me look too pale i think that
sort of look like a vampire if
i've had my hair black and i
looked
like you like somebody from an indeterminate
country like who this guy is yeah
he looks like he's from somewhere else
yeah but god bless and thank god
blaming him for coming and go back
where you came from
um but yeah i used to for
fun i used to cut my own
hair for a long time yeah yeah
and never done anything like that yeah
i think it would be harder when
you have long hair because it's like
there's so many factors of like yeah
it's like you can do mess it
up really yeah and when you're shitty
when you're just cutting short it's just
kind of like you know yeah i'm
not tossing what
never you took a you took a
picture and posted last gram after you
have to die to die and i
really i thought it looked really good
and looked appropriate to your face and
then i saw you not long after
in-person here and it was so much
less a dramatic change well because i
got it um taken down between them
oh wow okay i like initially it
looks like little mermaid read like it's
truly like very rare and then like
some of that was coming out in
the wash a little bit legs yeah
hannah likes yeah that was during a
seashell bra yeah that's what i was
wearing now no connection to that and
you couldn't talk yeah and you know
thrill you could
man you gotta tell you now jay
you get talking to wire exactly you
should yeah well i went to a
different salon because it was closer to
my house and i was like can
you strip this from my hair and
then ah they did something but it
took forever and it cost two hundred
fifty dollars and then it was oh
definitely read but when i was in
the salon it looked like she like
blew my hair dry
i like looked browner and i was
like you got it mainly like this
looks fine like it's for the most
part and then i went like i
went to target and then i went
in the bathroom at target and my
hair was red like it was just
like okay i was like praising this
woman so much i was like oh
you saved the day because i was
like really worried about it once was
that while there like process was having
to stand
i'll come out and then a did
i thought and then i was like
it didn't and i've just like gave
for all this praise and money yeah
and a hundred and fifty of those
dollars you love i know i love
them so much and then i called
the original lady and she told me
to use prowl like cheap eve
the original lady steve more like um
and i just bought some prowl on
the way here and i'm gonna go
home and hope it oh man but
now you know your hair will be
bouncing and behaving or no that was
pert yeah that was her plus yeah
prowl by the way supposed to be
cheap shampoo still how much how many
dollars
love those dogs that was one of
those inflation things where i was like
shah if i think about a sham
a cheap shampoo if you're thinking ninety
nine cents yeah oh yeah everything i'm
using this cheap i think to us
as ninety nine cents yeah anything above
that is i had to get a
perm once what's why when i was
in oklahoma i knew you were gonna
say that to play currently of course
yeah but
they can't they just call him curly
does he have to have in it
all it made you know i've sort
of wavy hair it just made it
like slightly more wavy you know it
wasn't like it was a tight curl
or anything right yeah and then it
was a whole summer so it all
just gradually went away right you know
also who cares yeah about the entire
store not you whenever he ever said
you die
higher story okay look at this teabag
oh hello
this is so fancy don't you think
it's like an little sashay sashay shot
anyway all i wanna say about it
is um i can't wait don't look
like dumb people in your life just
say you look you look yes but
then there's the here's what happens sometimes
and this happens anytime anyone changes anything
and tell me if you get this
with anything where someone just goes you
changed your hair and then you're like
yeah and then they're like alright yeah
and they don't say you don't know
where the other oh i have had
this multiple times with this red where
someone's like oh you changed your hair
color and then i'm like yeah i
yeah it's maybe thing day they think
that you
you are unsure of how you feel
about it so they don't want offer
an opinion because you're like jumping the
gun going like yeah it's fair thing
you're not going like yeah and it's
fabulous here's why i think it is
i don't know go on here's why
i think it is also depends on
relationship of the person yeah you have
to the acquaintances i would i would
because more quincy i think that they
are
you have from their point of view
like from my point of view would
be the same thing that i hadn't
seen that picture on instagram it's not
that dramatic change it doesn't look that
dramatic no it's not like i'm a
guy who doesn't recognize hair it's weird
because it's taken from him the original
red yes so ratliff that i was
i walked around being like
like all great everyone thinks i'm i
think i'm quirky now like it was
like feeling like wow like every you
know i realized all my life i
don't actually don't judge people for coloring
their hair but there was something about
doing myself i was like i guess
i want everyone to look at me
like it was like so read if
you're gone like blonde no i've never
known she's never colored her
and that's why this is like having
a real done highlights note but ever
show piping natural and highly mortar hat
no wonder what a hat i changed
my appearance
i sleep with my like the elephant
man who is my head up yeah
actually i've always loved when other girls
will like change the url like i
think it's so cool and i'm like
hey oh that they yeah why aren't
you allowed to do this that's what
i always would think and then i
did it i want do you feel
like you stop who me me i
would like to close the causes you
ever came to doing it of your
own volition
um scott that means because you want
to oh thank you i really have
never bow what now i've never really
come that close to doing it i
usually am just like but you've thought
about it idly because my mom has
always been a big thing about me
not dying my hair because ah she's
like oh no young guys do it
you'll be on this
thing your whole life of having now
you'll never get that back you'll never
get that original color like i have
a cousin who's like always trying to
get my color because she used to
have that color right but it's hard
to get because it's like natural doesn't
just grow out yeah but then like
you have roots and so it's like
this kind of constant like dying process
okay your roots grow and then you
sew but anyway you're gonna let your
roots close you don't have to
to do that it's gonna say this
is gonna fake semi-permanent so it'll just
like go away supposedly but i want
to go faster right um but my
when i try most dye my hair
for this job sean know and then
i was like stop i'm hoping this
is a job i said yes it's
championing was trisha to say she was
going to
thank you um she said nothing of
the sort yesterday i couldn't even i
couldn't even go along ah um but
now are you do you don't you
do you have any of those things
like things your parents always said that
like then it's hard to change it
in your mouth i eventually was like
i have to go to hell or
i'll just forever be
like because i think as an actor
i'm like i want to be able
to be versatile and like change it
and like i don't want to feel
like i have to always look the
same yeah no of course i mean
it's a bit like the ingrained and
meets yeah not changed well i got
in trouble when i was in joseph
and the amazing technicolor dreamcoat for getting
a haircut and they were very upset
at me
gave me a talking to oh wow
yeah because it wasn't a cut that
was like it just kept it it
wasn't bible appropriate but it was a
mohawk i think we did it for
six weeks or whatever and i got
a haircut around week three and it
was short it was shorter than when
we started and they're like you can't
do that we you need to clear
any haircut through us you know i'm
just like my
hair isn't a huge part of this
yeah just seem interesting for that but
be upset but it was a lesson
of just you know you can't i
guess it's because part of it's the
way you looked when they cast you
yeah cut they they felt that you
had a certain look that was part
of the appeal of you for that
character i think i was a warm
body that happened to go to the
school they just put me through
me all excited a sort of arm
norm
did your parents have any things like
you could never do
it's tough because my
parents were
my first of all my dad who
knows what he thought about anything but
my mom could be very contentious and
so is a lot of rather than
me if she told me something like
that i wouldn't think oh i should
never do this i would think i'm
going to do that for sure oh
yeah but the closest like i remember
i came home from um
there was a thing called senior week
which was after you graduated high school
after yeah after you graduated high school
years ago i am sure i know
it's it's weird to me now but
we'd all did this it was a
week after dread after the graduate high
school after graduated i'm just you i'm
astonished
anyone learning right back you could ruin
my duolingo v o a week after
you graduate you all the pieces of
this of like the fact that you're
going to be roped into doing something
high school related for an entire week
not just a day of let me
there's there's more details let me get
them all out i want a new
can
express your incredulity because none of it
makes sense okay
this happens a week a week out
wilmer
sorry
i mean it's one thing when we
do it just like you can't help
yourself you say think this is different
this is not ah so this graduation
was when like usually i guess in
juice and desert rats' scripts in june
and so i think not long after
that and i don't know if this
was common to this amendment coming to
catholic schools in the area where you
were
would rent a place ah the jersey
shore either like you'd get a beach
house where you're all together you get
like our williams or something it's just
as high schoolers yeah it's also fun
yeah why would you not do it
see if you've heard all the details
exactly on board because it's a big
it's a weeklong party that sounds great
you know and it official through the
school
all or no no no this was
just like there's like a weird custom
that we all knew about and took
part in like three hours away or
something or no not even that long
no not like two hour drive maybe
something like that and um you would
yeah the idea was a you and
your friends would converge on the same
beach area so like we went to
wildwood
new jersey and um there was this
was a place where you knew you
could probably um drink under age kids
are having sex you know because they're
away from their parents it's your it's
like a weird living as an adult
kind of although i have to say
and maybe this is um the fact
that i'm a woman but when i
i thought that sounds
so fun and i thought oh god
something horrible what happened to me or
somebody at that yeah sure i'm sure
different for like for a guy it's
like hey we're gonna go down to
the beach we're all gonna have sex
yeah but for a woman's like oh
i'm gonna go down to the beach
and be pressured into having gas or
something bad with her son goes a
wanted and you know hey i know
some people aren't
loving relationships while others from people weren't
having relationships now me as a tee
totaling virgin yeah i don't know why
you wanna go does it because my
friends are doing totally always sounds like
alcoholic to me like it's like the
word sounds like someone who's well i
mean i know it's the opposite but
it should be a word for being
drunk yeah
yeah right doesn't it ap sound yeah
you know in the old west he
used to call ah a um a
drunk a tangle foot really why because
he's always getting tangled up yeah falling
down because he's fucking drunk because he's
tripping over his own fate hey dangled
foot lew this triangle fully this tangle
let's shooter a tee totaling virgin did
you have fun no
oh and was it everyone in the
school are now i remember it as
being a bad experience yeah i was
hung up on this girl shirley sherwood
had a bad time yeah yeah yeah
i'm sure we've had the worst time
because i would have liked somebody who
doesn't like me and then they're fucking
somebody else and i'm like i did
have a hookup with this girl that
was confined to just this was this
is like a very fraught thing where
she was my best friend and then
we started having a physical relationship exciting
and then it was very it was
so dramatic yeah it was very dramatic
but we it was so it was
a big deal we went like farther
than we'd ever gone before which was
not very far at all her spacey
touched her face
site
she took over vale um
and ah but the rest of the
time was just like miserable i was
miserable but another custom that happened during
this time was that dudes would get
their ears pierced they would get pierced
ear wow by another student no no
no you go out and go to
a place and do it and so
i got my ear pierced this is
like nineteen eighty sue did just yeah
can you
add your earpiece on throwing shaders and
i was just listening yeah yeah yeah
and i and i came home and
was it the thing where it was
like you gotta get your left not
your right oh yeah yeah and i
can't remember which was the one to
left was the one where the the
right was where you're gay right so
i'm gonna laugh here because i was
straight as an arrow doing yeah fucking
i like fucking girl
girls meanwhile oh wow yeah exactly like
so um when i came home and
my mom saw the air i said
i like i don't know why this
was like a real lucy and the
child been on the football thing yeah
where i would say something to my
mother like hey look like this and
she'd be like no so she set
her response was at least it's not
a tattoo
she was smiling when she said yeah
but it was you know she was
not on board did it ever get
infected no never did oh kitchen never
did yeah they did a good job
now you do they will think well
they tell you you have to twist
it yes it twisty twist like the
gold ball and i can't had a
pierced ear for about
probably two years and then i did
a close target of it yeah yeah
miners died yeah yeah like i used
to i can still feel feel where
the hole was you have piercings i
have like three at least yeah that
tracks why yeah when i was in
joseph's yes when i see the old
picture of it is and i was
like wow we're kind of a um
punky brewster what's your grateful your little
girl huh bit of a punky brewster
a little bit like a scar baby
like you're like i like the idea
of skateboarding i won't do it myself
you were kind of your friend that
you were kind of a blossom yeah
um no when i was in joseph
i think oh webster i probably got
a couple of them for that too
because ever
joseph yeah everyone was like encouraged to
like grow a beard and heavier rings
and like oh oh could go go
go joseph can know where say um
your left you're not the right one
or you're gay
i remember sort of on what paul
was talking about i remember being inspired
this fifteen and and going up to
a speech because that's how you write
in every conversation oh she's saying that
because of what i just take grip
pride
yeah whenever i went up to stanford
for a speech competition telling somebody later
and so ah i what i said
inspired them to talk about a different
topic and it was delightful how much
she felt comfortable chair because of the
platform i had thought
guys like my turn can be gonna
tell your store
i finished i he's gonna finish oh
i know huh
g o p
that's a real g o p r
ib allows a real but that's a
g o p r i p and
we were ah he was ended he
was independent yeah you guys voted for
him oh my god i was like
almost ah convinced on that i had
a friend who was like who's like
you ever heard ross perot and i
said no
and he's like he's he really makes
sense because he either the tequila you
took the lion king is now known
this i mean this year's university de
rosa now he was like he really
makes sense because he's going to run
this country like a business like successful
businessman like ah like ah one that
got no votes because he was so
in the middle he no he did
he's the mo
most successful independent i think of all
times yes a lot of people believe
ah that he he enabled bill clinton
to be president because he you split
the vote he was the only he
was the only independent who's ever been
like allowed into the debate to like
the final debates between the two parties
suddenly there's three because yes so popular
and it was because like everyone was
like every politician is stupid and this
guy's just a real plain speaker and
he's speaking wrong yeah it was sort
of the pro-trump trump and i got
snookered into it a little bit and
i was like it actually made more
sense with him than it did with
donald trump yeah maybe i don't recall
the data really seemed political right like
i mean like or you're dating na
steam
aimed intelligent it was like he wasn't
he was a business menus from outside
of politics but he was using all
of his own money yeah right and
he talked and he talked almost exclusively
about economics and ethics which is all
anybody gives a shit about right and
so it made it made sense plus
oil no fillers i don't know anything
about politics at the time i remember
once i was like going into one
of my college
which courses i don't even know what
course it was and someone was talking
about how like this is eighty eight
at the time and they're like going
to be voting for bush the piano
year and um and he's like why
wouldn't you vote for bush i you
know because i'm in orange county and
it's yeah a republican and i'm like
two words dan quayle he stupid i
don't want him you know but that
was yeah well potato
oh yeah i was mine were that
the extent of my knowledge about politics
is like this guy's dumb so he
can yeah it's so insane by the
way like potato was enough to ruin
it for the ruin it was more
than that i mean but i gotta
hit a bunch of gaffes but like
that's so nothing and i feel like
it's the one everyone should love talks
about yeah it's like he's remembered for
that
yeah well what's so what's so great
about that and what mustn't be forgotten
is that he was correcting a child
who had written potatoes at a school
then he was like up i think
you forgot something any droopy or the
yeah yeah okay well that's worse that's
shown down the e
i drew a book huh i do
everywhere i drew everywhere in this book
please buy my book look at the
book the book where i draw my
signature on my check
do you remember the debate the vice
presidential debate that year with stockdale yeah
ah is who is the one who's
like who am i yeah i'm yeah
he picked this ross broad picked up
his running mate this guy admiral james
stockdale who is an old man who
am i what am i doing here
yeah it was a great opening line
that's because everybody laughed yeah but then
the ref
east of the debate he couldn't hear
so well so
he would wander away from the podium
i think to go somewhere where you
can closer to where you could hear
you but he would why he would
walk off screen so it would be
al gore and dan quayle and this
guy would just walk away wander away
it was nah who am i what's
going on and then you walk away
um hashtag walkaway you are gonna say
something you don't care all right let's
take a break wow
j li se da da da da
said inspired him to say something which
inspired me and say yeah alright we
take a break and enjoy oh well
let the lady so yeah
well i'm a woman and we're back
on three to a woman's telling us
that guy three now this is the
show where we just riff the three-time
boys are back maybe she likes that
art that somebody made of us yeah
thanks if you have some
art center to it just sort of
animaniacs or no i liked that one
but i was thinking of the one
where it was like someone were like
them three them boys like the freedom
i don't think i saw reminded and
someone wants to play faggot think it
could be a shirt if i'm also
the animaniacs one can be assured to
on yang got a lot of good
co boy send us all your stuff
if you can
man if you can please send us
your stuff well we understand hey and
if you totally dust your stuff send
it hey if you can't send it
don't send it but we understand if
you can't send us all your stuff
if you can't send it don't leave
but send it only
all your stuff are belong to us
i was two years ago oh this
i want to see your sta blue
so guys i was in a car
accident oh yeah ooh where and why
in new york city new york state
just a few days ago just few
days ago is the situation i will
tell you exactly that okay start with
the who the
what the where the when the why
i'd finish up for the house went
to see why i was there to
do some shows at the bell house
in brooklyn my favorite venue in america
by the way it worked out well
with your philly show i gather yes
it did yes it did you get
the old philadelphia hello no they did
not throw batteries at me
i can say rang your leverage from
there ooh la lang lang the kingdom
i'd like to have my liberty bell
rung by there's a cracking i do
some man ass crack
so we super ego took the train
down to or up to new york
we did shows there the next night
i did my shows from toyko what
did they say everybody in
many famous than famous conductors cry yeah
everybody yeah i was being the audience
today show like oh everybody yay everybody
in here lapping it didn't make sense
but you weren't supposed to know what
so it was a very tight scheduled
tightly scheduled trip but i did want
to go to the see a broadway
play or very much wanted to see
hey
east town and i thought i was
you i would like to even though
i might be back there later in
the year the my only shot was
sunday matinee i wanted to see hades
town out of all the things and
so i invited the people the cast
of spun tour code to go with
me what if you invited the cast
of hades town hey guy you want
to see your show
oh by the tickets
we're all in the audience and nothing
happened oh they got yelled at um
so we went saw like we were
everything was was down to the minute
like we got there right before the
show started right sweaty sweaty i actually
did pretty good i timed it very
well where i dressed for the day
like
i was wearing a suit linen suit
got out of the hotel into the
uber to the theater right inside it
was perfect boom sat down lights go
down go down hades tau that's possible
shutdown lights go down
sassy on every poster what did they
do what did they say like like
go down hey sound come on guy
and so on the poster they rhymed
down with down yeah people are skeptical
of the show this is a musical
right
oh sat town yeah it's good time
to think of a better rhyme for
the poster so um we call a
big sep uber to take us all
to the bell house takes longer i
would imagine to get an s u
v uber doesn't it's new york city
dollars rolling around the sushi vehicles all
over the pleasure enough so
we get we get the ah the
car pretty quickly all pile in we're
having a great time we're talking about
the show um and we are on
park avenue where we're about to ah
i think get to the tunnel to
go to brooklyn and boom we get
hit ah
uno sinulog oh my god i don't
want wow
i feel like i heard that kid's
voice in my head and bill and
where did they hit you they hit
right they hit us on the side
like where it was ah me and
janet and her boyfriend brandon was in
the front seat um we were all
in a row we were on that
side and i think the impact probably
was mostly wear but like kind of
bit's
tween me and janet and it was
a hard hit and we stopped and
the traffic was barely moving so i
don't know where this guy came out
did work up secede yeah lastly i
feel like he was had turned a
corner and was trying to get across
but it's it's so it was so
crazy there's really hard to
and you did he never said oh
what happened was i did this or
did that no we they blame it
on he kept going i don't know
if he was trying to get away
or was trying to pull over okay
but he went he went like a
little over into the side to the
to the curb and um when we
got out you know we were up
while checked in with each other everybody's
fine the driver was fine
um did you check in with him
last did you check the drive friends
first lo the drywall the driver got
out of the car okay immediately so
we all checked in with each other
first okay i know you're trying to
catch me scott i know you're trying
to catch cares about people i would
check in with my friends first i'm
not ashamed we checked her with her
friends i would i would push my
friends heads down and go
where are you okay
i don't care about these people or
you are late did that thing where
be you know we just suffered this
weird trauma where we we kept asking
each other over and over again yes
if it was a new thought yeah
you just gotta be a better it's
so skew there's gotta be a better
question settling are you okay because everyone's
first instinct is to say yeah who's
president
now well you know anything you like
like anytime anyone falls or whatever and
you go are you okay everyone goes
yeah yeah yeah even if they are
very hurt i don't think so
i think you're waiting to hear somebody
wakes you up with a phone call
and you say it was asleep no
or like if you're embarrassed by the
way you are hurry like i'm fine
i'm fine i'm fine know like everyone's
everyone everyone's first instinct is to say
i'm ok i'm ok well i said
on the question i think a better
question might be like how how did
you get hurt or where are
did that hurt you or so i
don't i even know but i know
i hate to debunk you feel any
impact from that
what injuries do you have if you
do have them yeah and answer me
honestly because i please
right questions such a time waster to
get through the yeah i'm ok is
to know i actually cut my my
hand but here's the thing not everybody
said i'm ok people were like i
think i'm ok you know what i
mean it was like some people because
as the day went on some people
were feeling things some people were not
right um i never really felt anything
i feel like i ought
almost felt a twinge in my neck
and janet had because janna you already
had a crack
janet already had a pinched nerve so
she had all kinds of stuff with
her shield like ah like ah ah
all this like cbt bomb that i
put on my neck and i was
fine i don't think anything happened to
me at all when we got out
we asked the driver you are right
yes we were all right we asked
each other a few more times um
then when i saw
the the the uber that we were
in there was hardly any damage and
then it wasn't until we got an
a new uber to go because we
still go to the show yeah so
we saw the cab that it hit
us and the and the entire um
left front of it was demolished yeah
and there was just like broken ah
plan
thick and shit all over the place
this is where you become someone just
walked in it wasn't another podcast tried
to walk yeah oh they always try
now but that's not what the freedom
boy if this were a different podcast
we would say come on and get
on mike whatever why not just chat
we won't do it on this nope
this will only be us and only
us shoving
get to speak or zig which orion
say when an hour and jordan think
never devin will say that right now
never never you haven't never seen this
show devin and sam were the only
two who will never be heard from
never never so so when we got
out of the when we got out
of the cab but we got her
the uber
or you know there was a guy
there who has he has a specific
look where it's like this guy might
be i don't think he's homeless he
might just be who's this the other
know this is a different guy who
i there's just a guy standing there
who was on the other side of
the street who is saying hey i
saw the whole thing you know i
got you
guys gotta get yourselves checked out and
we're like yeah we will we will
and he seemed kinda like yeah he
he seemed like he could be maybe
not all there yeah but then i
looked and saw that he was he
had gotten off a bike so he
was dressed he by aware with autism
a million degrees yeah but he was
like that's why he looked away he
looked a little unusual because yeah
was sweating and wearing but yea yeah
but he was not a wild-eyed but
crazy amount of new york city yeah
of which there are many and it's
one of the reasons i love and
that's what you're gonna get but he
said we said we will get ourselves
checked out he said no but really
i'm a veteran do it a veteran
yeah he said do get yourself checked
out
implying that i know what you may
think that you're okay but you could
maybe not be okay okay wow so
did you get yourself checked out no
i will i will when will i
have to make a doctor's appointment anyway
so i'm going to have my all
my would you like an examination now
should you fit why don't you do
the thing where you throw a briefcase
just fast because he had a physical
physical when did this happen today i
didn't hear this this pre me talk
yeah it looks like and i couldn't
go earlier you'd want to take earlier
but i didn't inspire this last kid
physical screening not add further ah lads
good
he was like please you have to
stop singing you are like let's say
he joined in they call the physical
i have me ah physica oh my
god and ca please give me your
physical budget to our body
well that's the thing i was telling
lord
state that all of the advances in
modern science fun sigh and they haven't
figured out a better system than a
guy putting his finger up your butt
oh yeah so we did use a
fast because of the thing no-nos for
the blood test but i'm sure look
i don't know i didn't understand honestly
maybe the blood test is
as a shield and they just don't
want like you know dupe up your
bus duty but i mean there's they're
all there's no machine that can do
this yeah it's gets a little crazy
that's all just some guy going i
feel good me and my my guy
is like he always tries to make
a guy make you feel comfortable
will he always he always has has
a joke at the ready my finger
guy the jokes don't it's not a
it's not a joke like oh this
isn't he always has like a single
ring whatever yeah whatever is passing the
time so it's not weird for him
either how long does it through his
stories going because ah hey you hear
the one about a finger that washed
into a buttle
ah areas so finger books into a
buttle
i think anytime that you're the situation
to the doctor's coming like okay now
where was i was yeah i don't
want to hear a story where do
we put on music and just relax
a little but amanda like i like
it you trying to humanize i understand
but like the feeling of what is
good imagine a machine going haywire and
you don't know the finger
machine i don't i don't mean that
there's a machine a metal romano like
i feel i'm not saying that i
want a machine those spy robot like
dildo owing me in and out of
my butt i'm saying there's gotta be
like some sort of thing no one
thought you were saying that um i
that is very specific oh you did
yeah i stand correct so i mean
there's gotta be
like you know how they they the
advances in taking your temperature are so
wildly different than when we were kids
yeah just like rub it on your
forehead now they just like rub something
on your like do that for the
prostate rub something on my forehead turn
on my temperature taken it's been a
really long really my thank you yeah
you gotta get your temperature ticket bro
how
what part of a physical the last
amount of fiscal no no no i
just had i had to take in
recently i can read did you have
a fever i was ill so why
did you have it i went to
urgent care because yeah because big guys
urgent care you did which a virgin
care ooh la la i can't go
there um i went to urgent care
because i was worried i might possibly
have a tick bite which i didn't
owe but i had chris newman ah
yeah that's hit i was in rhode
island and um with arden and that's
right the biggest little sleep she isn't
she's from there and she just when
we got there she was like making
a whole little blue bow wow there
no she made a little speech about
ticks animal wilko for them
she had this antidote in case we
did get a tick bite and bubble
blah and then i was just like
yadda yadda who cares like i kind
of was like that won't happen shut
up barden up and now you're talking
hey this is our way of our
trip i was aware of them and
i was like you know i had
my whenever i wasn't wearing long pants
i would like check my ankle or
whatever but i got back home and
then i had this
big bug bite that was like said
swo like swelled up and then like
it looks like it had red because
swo where it was just reading i
mean i had a muscular bug but
yeah and it looked like it had
a ring around it which is what
i was looking up with yeah sign
oh i went to urgent care because
everyone's like just go just like but
it was like sunday at ten pm
and it couldn't see me until midnight
as a whole big to-do turns out
it wasn't that but i was still
kind of nervous about it but then
they gave me some claim but they
did check my bottle time huh but
i was also like ah in retrospect
because it like basically went away the
next day it was truly like
like wow god i was like it's
better get it's better yeah but i
was worried that possibly i was just
a little stoned and thought that it
was yeah right around it wasn't really
there was because your eyes were red
around because
do i see myself into a tizzy
over for twenty yeah because for twenty
one hundred and twenty have you ever
had hives either of you know but
i had shingo i know you're thinking
yeah i had chicken pox i had
hives one time with the last the
last comedy special recorded i was really
i was stressed out about a bomb
so
feeling i'm stressed out all the time
and then i noticed these um these
ah red dots on my arm that
were itchy and of course janey thought
they were bedbug bites and that we
may have been terrifying course which is
the bugs at home the sailor is
better rome i say like
convinced moyes said it but budget home
sales go wrong bed bugs away silicon
play
don't you think you could convince yourself
that so easily though if he'd yeah
well we were doing it like tariff
we were absolutely doing because you look
at the pictures and of course that's
exactly what it looks like yeah yeah
when i was in new york for
like five days i was convinced when
i got home that there were bedbugs
yeah but they were they were hives
and they the next day they were
gone gone
completely like no evidence that the things
that we've discussed that you've had on
your body you've had mirza mirza yeah
that's the one that's taking on torsion
testicular torsion right that's right thank you
i'll always remember
and sure if you will always have
that's right
wait but why did you go to
urgent care i was just well i
was shy attitude was you go to
urgent care ah nu da da i
was do you have a fever or
did you have a rash as you
go changing and taking up your ass
yeah exactly there we go i was
taking going to disney
lands with our nephew and the sake
of going to come no said it
manifested itself physically i was i was
going to disneyland on monday and saturday
land sickness saturday i just felt so
sick that i was like i gotta
get some meds um and i just
can't wander to those cute cheese
the cute some videos of him and
i he's just cheese a charming nine
year old funny do yeah he's in
your shoes like todd he will worry
about that yes so he that was
the first stop he made when he
got here into town he loves cleaning
she was he went to the kids
that their weird little thing he went
to
the store where they have the shoot
this professional jason mark is what it
is shoe cleaning liquid and he bought
it and then he wanted to set
up a business of cleaning everyone's shoes
and he kept like he kept trying
to renegotiate the deal as well you
know so we go like he'd say
like hey he come to you and
say hey okay it's five dollars to
get your shoe
clean but yeah
but because you're sick i'll give it
to you for two oh i go
okay well right here you go better
than l a x and then he'd
go you'd you'd you'd agree to it
then he'd go well actually though because
i'm using so much of this stuff
i think it's going to actually be
five and i'm like well i don't
want to deal anymore said it was
too he's like no no
oh it can be too and then
you give him the two and he's
like what about my tip so then
my tip right so but then he's
like okay now you can be in
the shoe cleaning club where i clean
all of your shoes for an extra
twenty dollars and i'll do as many
shoes as you have for an extra
twenty you know where is he getting
in this show that lie he's nine
but he just wants to clean the
shoes that's the other part is it's
like he thinks it's fun he thinks
it's really fun to do because like
i'll spend an hour on it and
i'll do souls and i'll do the
top you know was so cute you
miff yes he's a mouse it takes
a part that she's supposed to bite
yeah you want to be part of
the toaster dismantling club but he loves
it
it was so fun yeah exactly and
then we went to a shoe store
because we hung out all day when
cool up ah and her sisters and
her mom went to like i guess
vanderpump rules yeah taps or whatever yeah
together so her so i was tasked
trump with hanging out with an der
der der
palm right right nah ah ah sir
well i don't know if you've heard
i'm gonna go to vanda pa barato
laser van
duh
whoa
sir sir is the other place so
that was perfect right it's perfect perfect
and you know why it's called sir
why do they call always stands for
something like sea urban resto yeah i
don't like it cool i've told me
that this disgusting shit so stupid do
so do you know the restaurant jar
in west hollywood now
oh i love that platypus um but
thanks for just another restaurant oh that
saas masters microphone away it's not going
to talk the rest of the show
two years i've been the face and
i will say i was gonna say
so we so we went into we
were hanging out and we went into
a shoe store first of all we
were we were going to dave and
buster's because that's
oh yeah something you really wanted to
do yeah and i was like okay
let's go down to hollywood pylons or
um he would call it david busters
by the way david beaudry investors i've
got a david busters it does make
more sense yeah who's this i'm david
buster welcome so we were i was
like let's go down to hollywood and
highland and i was like trying to
show him oh this is the walk
of fame that's where jimmy kimmel
and he's just so anxious and think
about all the shoes no not the
shoes yet he's like when we go
to dave and buster's i'm like we
literally just stepped out of the car
i'm showing you around i go let's
take our time let's we got a
lot of time to kill let's look
at yeah let's look at some stuff
he's like okay and then i point
out literally one other
thing he goes let's go let's go
david buster wow i'm like okay well
go so i can't leave a nine
year old would have so little respect
to the golden age of hollywood they
don't you think even kai doesn't want
to see all the stars didn't really
like the handprints at least where's olivia
de havilland so we were going to
dave and buster's but the one thing
that did
heard him was there was of ah
an adidas or ah van e-store ah
writers like oh let's go in there
first right so what was killers yield
what was interesting it was i got
to see how the pressure of so
of someone trying to sell him something
was working because they were like hey
what size are you like immediately
to a king man yeah like that
and and look like your feet yeah
and so he's he's like looking at
these new shoes that a basketball star
whose nickname is spider whatever he made
spiderman theme choose and they're like have
you seen the movie yet i go
no we're seeing in a couple of
properties on spider salley maybe yeah maybe
okay long out of the game right
on spider salley yeah it's like he
was just no that's not he was
a guest on dag okay so they're
like i said we're seeing the movie
in a couple hours they're like oh
man he's buying the shoes to see
the movie you know they're already putting
it is and he's gonna be wearing
those spiderman shoes while he's watching spiderman
also has joy
to experience the vo so manipulative you
know fucked up you basically okay well
no to to do you have to
buy that right did you pay those
guys to say that so they're like
let what you say let me go
get him so they go get em
and he's like as they walk away
he goes i didn't bring my family
back with me and i'm like it's
okay we we don't have to buy
any
thing like they're just trying to sell
you the shoes but we can get
up and walk away and say we
don't have to i'm like okay but
then they buy him and he tries
them on then they don't quite fit
so we they bring him a different
size and he's just feeling like he's
putting them out or whatever and mike
and i'm like whoa it's i went
to pressure yeah and and they're like
so what do you think should i
wrap these up or whatever i'm like
wow
well he doesn't have his fanny pack
with us so we're gonna we're gonna
come back if he decides he wants
to buy yeah your plan backfired assholes
yeah but i don't buy him anything
he buys everything himself with his shoe
cleaning money i wait for array audio
for me and i was like should
i be a cool uncle and buy
him
these shoes or something but i think
it's a better lesson it's a better
lesson because he was he had enough
money but he was just like i
don't know i'm also saving up for
your pods you know i think it's
just better for him to be like
yeah shoes buy your own shoes yeah
i'm sure he got plenty of other
fun stuff yeah yeah i mean everything
it's like yeah plus it was like
he does fine yeah he's just fine
for
yeah don't worry about him he ain't
worried about you we get to dave
and buster's and he's i'm like how
does this work because he has he
his mom gave him twenty dollars spend
a dave and buster's i'm like so
how does this work he goes will
you put in twenty and i have
twenty i'm like alright so i'm already
on the hook for twenty eight yay
for him yeah exactly oh yeah i'm
sorry i have this money you match
it yeah your part
of the religious like it felt like
a scam it really did look like
he had thought like instead of going
like oh no i spent way dollars
and they give us this card this
dave and he's like well you put
in your twenty yeah that's good he's
good businessman yeah it's a good business
like look we need to take a
break okay let's come back right
welcome back it's time for a three
welcome back lauren you let me walk
in the back first and then you
can do newbie i want to welcome
everyone back by the way scott
i would like to i began the
process of opening the back i would
like to do interested do you welcome
back everyone
three germ aged three to one what
is a three-tier let's explain this to
new this okay who are we playing
this one every time except for the
times we play we've already played before
that's right and that's a three chance
a three-tier send us your three cheers
to on twitter you can send her
to sleep at three m usa tweet
us a game that you
want to play and tag it hash
tagged three cheers t h r e
sending the eighty you want us to
play our history yeah you just talk
over valuable information send us the game
you will play would you talk over
valuable information
boom sit down let's go down like
you get your snacks go
think of my snaps
snaps go look at my snaps go
episode title to the left to so
chef gets right on the keyboard look
at nice maps go this do we
know who sent us this one we
gotta know we gotta give never had
we never will we'll find out
god is my witness this is a
three-tier called inside joke okay inside joke
and how does it work tool in
it's lead up to hosts are chatting
and one says something like don't let
grandpa near and then the other ugo
la then the other remaining host says
what's so funny
then the first two hosts have to
explain the details alternating sentences
that provide the origin situation behind the
inside joke let's see do i think
i get it but you guys play
first now this is the fourth time
you've heard the explanation let's see what
happens now huh yes and that was
really the pinnacle of the moment right
well you must get so embarrassed well
i was truly a
pines guy ah hey what's what's so
funny guys would you say oh pie
in the sky in this sky yeah
wow that's what you talked about it
so yeah its thinking it was a
joke you wouldn't get here yeah between
the two of you yeah yeah well
we were in college together oh yes
there too i was in college with
you right but you weren't there why
would you stop
yeah when you were sick and you
missed the big party i was you
missed the big part yeah yeah so
you weren't there for the story well
that was the night when pie in
the sky was formed it was the
night when everything became the funniest thing
that's ever been because yeah we were
at a party or the party
yeah that's my sentence
you're at a party and i we
everyone had to bring a dessert it
was exert party yeah and everyone had
matching desserts yes and everyone hadn't matching
desert we were at a party everybody
had matching desserts but they're all pies
and i brought a pie that looked
a deck like everyone else's
except that it had
it had a significantly ah unusual crust
on the top oh and the whipped
topping was so high some said it
touched the sky yeah because lauren had
stolen some helium from the party store
you're getting at see your lie
life and injected it into the whipped
cream so anytime anyone ate it their
voice would get really high and they
would say
a
yeah so but so everyone said pie
in the sky it became embarrassing because
because people's voices did not change for
forty eight hours oh now whenever there's
like an embarrassing moment we say it
was a pie in the sky yeah
because we had a funeral the next
day oh and we all were making
eulogies but we had a really high
voice we couldn't get out of it
yeah
yeah like what were what the eulogy
sound like that's when you want to
know you want to relive the time
when our professor die that you didn't
even care about professor tie you were
in his class two-tone to remember i
just thought he'd never came back your
tear you are very unobserved that i
was sick
or are you sick with disneyland sickness
i mean on this one i shared
this one here the butt of you
share this one
and see
now do you get it i get
it now okay you trick question
so um how did your date go
it was
it was fine i'm gonna ignore that
during my talk okay
it's good that you ignored it who
you mean yeah where you come from
i'm just saying we're partly where they
were when the controversial and we're having
coverage forty percent real friend to come
along i'm so sorry i just um
it's okay that i set the table
not really we're saving a seat for
our friend okay did you say set
the table just to say that i'll
just
oh i'll get up it would have
been okay if you want to set
the table please continue i'm okay sorry
we're just in the i'm i'm telling
the end of my story totally in
the beginning because he just asked me
about the date yeah we're we're friends
and we're we're doing the back right
he's telling a story okay then get
out of here yeah i'm just gonna
say mitchell kirk i'm just going to
turn this way at this counter and
just stand here there's no other seats
and you
just took my seat so i'm just
going to stand here and it wasn't
it was never your seat because well
it could've been until your friend arrives
because i could actually be done eating
when you're not our friend i know
i just mean i could sit here
until your friend arrived yeah i mean
you would get up you'd be physically
able to but you're not allowed understand
at this counter and not listen to
you great we're gonna stand at the
counter pretend you never exist
thanks
so sorry about this if so you've
finished your story and how was your
day my day was fine ah you
know we went to the movies but
i'll tell you one thing we didn't
do ah we did not take a
helicopter trip into the volcano and you
know i think i grow up da
sang mean
oh hey
lauren what does that mean you're here
you don't know you've heard to say
the hard man you can't this is
our friend lauren youkai to sit here
until your friend oh wow here or
i'm just shit hirer lauren i'm sorry
this guy i don't know if this
is so much like me she has
she kind of dirty blonde hair yeah
i have friend you have wonderful readings
match your personality i can't tell my
friends look like other people i feel
that we look like um yeah i
think we actually sound identical so like
barely just an imperceptible i honestly can't
tell the difference yeah in any case
ah hey waist scram get lost okay
i'm leaving now and i guess i'm
the bitchy
doppelganger or something yeah that's exactly what
you are wow you guys look exactly
like to see matter and that's what
we already covered scott is this some
sort of parent trap situation
guess we'll figure it out later i
wanna know what you're talking about oh
are interested in this why does she
just family exactly like your date didn't
end with the helicopter
oh it's an inside job but look
at that possibly mean well it's gone
i used to be roommates yeah this
is like ten years ago this is
ten years ago i went there i
was your roommate to yeah but you
were sick one night remember
you're saying what i'd never give out
of your room right yeah it happened
on that very oh my god that
now you guys had an inside joke
i remember the day warning we said
we had a great inside we were
trying to have one just happened but
so now you're ready to tell me
what it means yes sure we'll tell
you what i mean so this is
ten years ago we were roommates and
we won a free helicopter trip
that's right we stayed up all night
to win this contest it was a
radio call-in show yeah and i called
in with the right answer which was
what radio station are you listening to
yeah wow i can't believe so many
people didn't get it it didn't understand
well they didn't look at their radios
also a lot of the calls were
wrong numbers right that it had no
idea that contest was calling for pizza
calling for whatever happened ah well they
say congratulations you've won a helicopter ride
and what we didn't realize was
it was a twilight zone themed
contest yeah so it was a twilight
zone theme contest where they were determining
who sounded the most like rod serling
and we didn't know that i mean
that's i guess the right answer didn't
really matter was just i sounded the
most like rod serling he was even
trying to do that no but continuing
with the theme the helicopter ride we
didn't we thought it was just a
fun hell
the copter ride yeah we'd like see
the city you know of course you
know is taking a trip through the
bermuda triangle but we didn't think much
of that but you thought you were
just going to see like boise yeah
from above we saw we could finally
see boise from above
and instead they flew by helicopter to
the bermuda triangle where was i we
had you were sticking your sick wow
me to make multiple stops to refuel
and then they lowered us into a
helicopter refueled it in the air yeah
which was so bad another helicopter fly
up
thank you guys i'm going to have
to do with the story you told
about the date well because we did
not go we ended up bailing out
of the helicopter before it got to
the volcano oh yeah so parachutes we
sold parachutes but the pilot who is
this beautiful woman jumped out with us
you to fall
i mean gorge i mean gorgeous head
i mean tos was slammed angers oh
wow so no hero hair and all
the right place but first i remember
she didn't have legs or feet or
just probably i don't remember i just
thought i was head toes finger
yours did you have open toed shoes
she was flying the helicopter doors or
shoe no she had opened back choose
gross but she puts my backwards yes
so
so we didn't we never made it
to the via airmail to the volcano
but we ended up all doing a
triple kiss in mid air yeah which
turned out to be good like hey
we fixed the bermuda triangle yeah we
kissed so people can just since we
took the boyfriend you didn't you didn't
fly a helicopter into a volcano what
does that mean we didn't trip
i'll kiss with the person we've been
on the date with yeah yeah you
both went on the date no we
didn't go on the date together but
i went on a date with a
couple yes
see if that's nice come on parents
as me it's okay to like you
are so similar prize you didn't do
that right away i know she's your
heading down the street and a little
evil looking car i know you're saying
to the inverse of the color of
your cuts true you are so similar
ahead toes hair and all the right
places and you really
pay better attention to people and mc
theme okay great great okay one more
alright one more and then we'll find
out who won yeah and show into
the judge
ah oh my god what my god
i'm so embarrassed
that's my boss and i didn't recognize
him well he just waved at you
for like a minute he weighed your
fruit and i flipped him off i
was like hey why didn't you just
say hi to you know stop waving
me you fucking weirdo my god this
is the most embarrassing thing that's ever
happened to me well this job
penguin in a sandstorm
yeah yeah so yeah you're right about
that but wow what are you guys
laughing at yes me richie hey ritchie
yeah what's up guys hey i'm flushing
your money at us you will hey
here's twenty dollars twenty dollars a kid
but i mean ostentatious okay just see
my shoes oh behave
i'm enjoying the shoot club yeah oh
really yeah i think that's a wise
investment i'm only a member for for
different extra twenty dollars you get all
your shoes clean out your twenty dollars
just want to thank you thank you
thank you so much for ya where
were you laughing laughing inside laughing man
oil jumps how you won't get anywhere
in a sandstorm yeah yeah it's been
one in a sandstorm like me or
in the bathroom no i mean a
lot like it we you know this
joke now i don't know the joke
it's inside i'm outside you're a fan
of the english beat and you load
this show i love the english beat
i don't know the joke
you're a fan of our inside joke
book that we wrote and you want
to come tell us a fan you
guys just to get devers i don't
know the joke you're paying us twenty
dollars a piece he started copies yo
bark jokebook you it's for whatever you
decide it is if you give me
the joke book great if not i
don't care here's our inside joke book
you read it i'm not going to
read it it's page ninety six three
oh your the penguin is dad what
does it be like that's what the
joke is about okay so actually it
was like when i was little i
took a long time learn how to
read yeah and i was little with
you we were a little looser you're
sick you're sick i was sick yeah
sick when we're all brothers this girl
little yeah when we were little your
sick one day and we had this
whole thing which he was
thursday this wednesday twenty rheumatic fever yeah
i burn my stuffed animals exactly so
yeah they did to br exactly
and they had to burn zoo plea
and they had to go burn alrighty
then
anyways i couldn't learn how to read
really easy yeah but i decided it
was my responsibility to teach her to
teach her how to read and he
tried but you know i ended up
having to go to school where all
the other kids were racing ahead of
me and i felt like a penguin
in a sense of just how did
i can't understand
i mean she she came home and
she told me that and that's what
i said i don't understand that je
suis last let me accept she said
let me explain it to you so
eventually continue this can't be the origin
of notes so she continued and said
what she actually meant by it but
i still never made sense and so
for years and years and years we'd
quote penguin in a sandstorm because
that time when i seem to have
lost my mind and was talking random
so i committed her to a mental
health facility and now anytime somebody seems
to not know what's going on or
they're confused we say it's like a
penguin in a sandstorm and then that's
include for me that she's off her
meds and i need to maybe call
a pre-doctoral is my safe word and
i need help yeah
so signal is a signal that she's
going a little kooky and she doesn't
feel safe so it's not really a
private joke at all oh shit we
staff and laugh at it even though
it's a signal your in mental distress
yeah pair i've already called her doctor
who's on the way and here he
is doctor's orders hello doctor doctor's orders
how are you hello doc
actors are doctors orders doctors orders said
to burns orders exactly hello doctor's orders
good morning everyone doctors always awake he's
awake he's awake who won this test
when the inside joke book contests penguin
in a sandstorm watch yeah see that's
our word that's our word but did
you have a straight jacket here you
go yours
here's to check it it's i don't
want to put it on or you
put your your doctor jordan's huh ya
gonna put it in your the one
was yeah you're insane
i don't know a penguin in a
sandstorm me you eighty yeah this is
some way made it up this is
like something out of the twilight zone
helicopter ride
consider a man
i told you i had a good
impression seen and see
ah that's great that was fun it
was nothing but great that nothing that
was on a hamburger bun i loved
it i lived in my bun guys
were at a time we gotta go
we were sad about where to go
we gotta go many days a lot
and we thank you so much yeah
you know while you're done for for
real thank you for listening to the
show and all it really
it tickles us and touches us when
people are sending in you know remixes
of songs or artwork or whatever it's
it's it's always appreciated you guys are
the best and thank you so much
and it's nice i did some live
shows this weekend and met so many
freedom fans and people told told me
that it means a lot to them
and that's greatly appreciate so nice yeah
so thanks for
listen guys and come out and see
us if you want to on the
comedy but you came over there hey
and thank you to ted daughter's dead
daughter that said three chirk you thank
you two daughters i made funny name
before you got a little bit of
a baby about it but now you're
back in everyone's good yeah it gets
the glory bay blah
hi great dismount
a