three
yeah welcome to yeah um this is
the podcast where everything gets potted and
nothing gets left on the cutting room
floor we had yeah to the end
of yelling freedom can we or did
we well it happened one person did
and
i'm saying should all of us and
should that be a permanent energetic at
the very end let's try again okay
right okay here we go ready three
two one
ah it's whole you didn't press play
well
jesus christ huh
just just keep doing you know your
what a great episode so i think
an episode for the record books most
annoying good episodes ah hello i fucked
the record books i want to think
i congratulate you three two one three
thanks and i'm not doing this this
is humiliating are you hearing it all
or barely know it's really fucked up
this is what people need to understand
where on zoom but we need to
explain why because we are not trying
to be back on zoom we are
not trying to be able to know
when we are not zuma know we
had to be back on zoom you
know that
t-shirt of bugs bunny holding a revolver
and he says lord helped me but
it's time to go back on my
bullshit
no but i need that
wow you ever see that i feel
like everybody is so but you can
see that okay we wait i've only
seen it online i've not seen it
like out in the wild on somebody's
body should we sell them with us
instead of bugs bunny doing it no
because then it's just us holding guns
and saying what's wrong with it i
just love
you could just type anything in it
like knows i wrote lord helped me
bulls jit bugs bunny bull
that's the share we should sell lord
help me bulls shit bugs bugs bugs
bugs bunny bunny lord forgive anybody but
i'm taken back to the whole league
okay but i found ah i found
a woody vs give a little bit
i'm bounding my oil shea or what
yeah i'm here oh toy story woody
from cheers lord forgive me but i'm
back on my bullshit that's being a
one bullshit bugs bunny is holding a
what looks like a flintlock pistol from
the revolutionary war yeah
everyone was out there meeting hi i'm
lauren i'm paul
and i'm ted kaczynski the unabomber oh
shit this whole time yeah he's you
know bomber was either you to robber
i can't remember the last auto bomber
yeah he was he was oh no
bobber the usa once she was a
huge figure in my my childhood i
feel really did he babysit you yeah
i went his cabin ally and
wrapped packages i wrote i didn't believe
in him but my parents told me
don't spoil it for the other kids
no see what it was is that
he was creepy pasta but in my
neighborhood he had to come to my
house and say it was concussed but
they would get to know him and
he was really good guy well this
creepy pastas catchphrases hello i'm okay huh
yeah um is he in jails
oh yeah you mean jeff the killer
oh yeah just killer killer phrase would
go to sleep go to sleep right
jeff the killers ah who's really tugged
he's really taught client i am oh
i'm i'm creepypasta now look at me
alright here's the thing here so now
here's the story everyone and saying here's
the story to all the piss pigs
i'm very sorry that we're on zoom
this time but again the audience chose
the name pixie didn't ah i was
recently exposed to covert nineteen the novel
coronavirus
yes and guess who guess who had
it that i was sitting right next
to that may have infected me who's
this william tani this is a ah
no not tony she was sitting on
the other side she may have from
the same person oh my god
it's none of them than major kira
nerys herself nana visitor from star trek
deep space nine texting wow texted tawny
i almost said connie but the her
name is connie that's a crow oh
it's one of those like alerts that
you got that you had and i
got that later i got the lido
um
what i wondered about this okay so
she texted tony yeah i have copied
did she so she does you take
a test and then i'll alert somebody
how do they know she'll alert the
exposure people this here's where i didn't
know how this works either in janie
kind of figured it out and i
think this must be why
what it is is that if you
test positive and you put you put
it into your phone if you have
that enabled to say i just tested
positive again then up it i gotta
get that app and then it will
i think it tracks locations so it
tells you hey you were near somebody
who just said that they were positive
and now look
your stared i keep getting them from
hawaii and i haven't been to hawaii
in years
it's very straight that makes no sense
it's it's the only alert i ever
get regarding covert is that hawaii is
telling me someone i've been around his
head covered wow
yeah um but paul you're feeling well
i feel fine i had a um
ah i found out yesterday took a
test negative had woke up with a
tickle in my throat that was gone
within an hour i feel totally from
scratch it just put a pipe cleaner
down there yeah well i do that
check the pencil down there i shove
i tie a pencil to a pipe
cleaner and then i erase erase erase
all of the disgusting things that get
in my throat it's great you guys
use tongue scrapers know sometimes i love
you i love a tongue scraper i
kind of do too it kind of
looks like if you go i went
too hard ah with it like i
want to know and i feel like
i like
like wiped off a taste bud okay
i was like that word was like
can you not taste right now no
now everything's fine they grew back but
about a month ago i scraped it
so hard that it was like it
was almost like i'd been burned jesus
christ
i had a little fun don't do
that that doesn't sound like fun but
you know it also sometimes it's that
thing where it's like the first couple
scrapes you're supposed to just do super
lightly kind of getting get out and
sometimes you're like let's see if i
can just let every single nook and
cranny up in this piece and then
suddenly you're like gagging on a piece
of metal you know
it's like a potato peeler you're just
shit in slices of tongue coming out
yeah it's great that tongue stuff grows
back yeah yeah you know if you
if you cut off the tip of
your tongue it grows back threefold
yeah so if you do it too
much you can't even fit it in
your mouth anymore yeah so be careful
it's like a fruit better food source
oh yeah i used to love doing
it when i was yeah how was
the cruise paw the cruise okay so
i was on a star trek cruise
i joined times tony
yeah we try to get the boat
to go to space they built a
big ramp in the ocean um tawny
newsome and i joined it halfway through
so we were there for three days
and nights um and it was really
fun everybody was super nice i got
to meet many of the actors i
got to see many more of them
um
from a distance ah family was really
fun yeah
oh it looks love beyond a boat
the the ocean was a little choppy
on the way back and which i
love you love really yeah i live
it's my army city favorite thing ever
we've been over this but i'm not
a moat fan love em i don't
i don't get motion sickness so i
really really enjoy it that's amazing
thank you
why do you think you don't get
motion sickness i think because my center
of gravity is impeccable you have like
we'll see he had this surgery where
he sort of had like a sandbag
put into his like yeah between the
stomach and his but my whole family
yeah yeah and so sort of creates
this like this sort of
of rocking motion already it's an um
i'm a little older than you guys
but that was a common practice back
then like sic rayyan yeah you're right
circumcise you then they put the sandbag
in when you say you're a little
older than scott what do you mean
like five days
i let my four years older than
you i think i'm four years old
somewhere on there yeah yeah alright yeah
really yeah huh did you i lost
track a few years back i think
i will do here yeah i don't
care how old i am i don't
care how old you are great that's
what you've been saying your
all right guys do it a lot
of situations
well did you see any ah sea
monsters too did you only two but
one was one the big one nelly
yes nellie with like the the seamaster
with a bandaid on her face yes
se as i do i'm trying to
think it's like the loch ness monster
yes
it's just jodie foster huh
hey
because here's what i'm asking did you
see any ah anyone making any viral
videos on board because
a new washington post article i just
brought up
well cruise line was we i know
you just brought it up yeah that
time we're talking about it brought it
up on my phone me okay oh
carnival cruise line has a message for
spring breakers planning to set sail if
you think you can get away with
the type of bad behavior that goes
viral on social media think again fuck
yeah does
going to do they're bringing on drug
sniffing dogs where they're drunk yeah hey
there any have that yeah the you
know what i did we flew into
mexico so we could join the boat
and ah a drug sniffing dog to
come up to me at customs and
i want of course all you just
want to pet the dog because it's
very yeah looking dog
um and he didn't find any drugs
in my application i said sorry to
him wow it would be fun to
be a drug sniffing dog because it's
like shrug smell good right this is
also good because it always kind of
stressful when like you're walking past like
especially okay bremer you remember when you're
walking past the drug sniffing dogs and
they're like
they're very much like don't touch them
i feel like i get nervous when
they say that even though i wasn't
i wasn't going to touch the dog
i'm not carrying any drugs but there's
like this feeling of like don't touch
them and there's like this energy that
makes you nervous i get nervous just
when they come near me even though
i've never ever had drugs on my
suitcase i just it's it's just that
the cop thing can you ask the
officers if they can also smell dirty
underwear
yes
and what what you mean the officers
or the dog either
you're allowed to say the officer can
use dirty underwear are you able to
like you know he can smell drugs
what about you what can you smell
if your underwear if you're under the
lights bread your underwear under four days
old can you say anything yes driving
stroke ah can i watch instead if
your underwear some more days you think
you think it yes i have i
have done ah vaudeville laundry in the
hotel sink noises can you stink it
stink it like instead of smell it
was supposed to go under the radar
i wasn't supposed to repeat it again
this is a story this is a
situation with no this is the situation
room i'm nor you if you are
that's what i wanted no ignoring yeah
i'm here to ignored but did you
paul did you throw anything over the
boat like oh my god so many
things
yeah i walk when i i would
fly when i'm gonna trip like that
i take the clothes i hate the
most and then i wear them for
the trip and then i throw them
overboard as i go so then i
don't have i have empty luggage that
i can fill with duty free tequila
duty free yeah you heard me no
duties allowed
am i saying duty or duty duty
duty duty duty jenny pudding danny put
any putti danny tom yes i want
drug drug sniffing dogs ah and then
yeah they're they're ah what else are
they going to do are they just
gonna slap phones out of people saying
oh yeah
i was gonna throw out another article
that i glanced at the headline of
much like what you did here okay
um paul said he and jannie are
being super safe and sleeping in separate
rooms while there's wait while he's making
sure it's an epp code wow we
here's the thing we did sleep in
the same room last night so you
will
there at all were staying in separate
rooms today while we missed each other
to my horse but so today you're
doing that yes today we have been
in separate rooms all day oh like
not sleeping you're just saying kind of
like but tonight you're going with your
tonight i am gonna sleep in the
in the guestroom okay goodbye rather mattress
i read an article and by that
i mean
what i said which is i saw
a picture of a headline no that's
writing means now we all know the
article was about people ah married couples
having their own bedrooms so we talked
about this i don't know we may
have talked about it a while ago
like if we would ever want to
do that and i definitely see the
appeal of it
i knew a guy um back in
my improv days who was a bit
older so he was like married and
had like a life you know and
um he and his wife had separate
bedrooms i remember going to their house
and i thought that was so interesting
he had he had a railroad yeah
well his his room didn't have like
you know his toys and things
because you know all you guys like
your toys high heel shoe bed
it was he just hits was like
his personality and hers was like her
personality and then i you know they
go in one room to fuck i
assume and separate just sex room like
fifty shades of grey know i think
they've i think they would have sex
in her room because it was the
more adult room and and the bed
was cheating one look at action figures
while she fucked you
hopefully not well because they're looking good
ups yeah but the they have their
opinions did i read there yeah they're
throwing away sixty thousand funko pops in
a landfill but doesn't care they weren't
talking about
why why are they throwing them away
and sell they didn't sell them just
so dollar what are their dollar why
don't they ship them to the poor
countries in africa like they do the
world series winners that were wrong and
all the teachers yeah two t-shirts all
the yeah all the t-shirts of
things that didn't happen what what that's
why we have the mandela effect that
exactly we're talking about separate bedrooms and
did that seem at the time that
seem very strange to you oh well
stoy someone here with the funko toy
was oh okay i don't know i
think they're grey goose aka are you
looking that
that's crazy that won't sell yeah right
i anyways the the roku was all
the other ones please check around the
article oh um but at the time
i thought they got you i didn't
think it was um well i didn't
think it was normal i'd never seen
that before but i didn't think i
didn't have a judgment against it i
wasn't like you did i mean i
just sort of like oh i've
ever seen anyone do that um but
i thought it was interesting because i
also didn't know you know i hadn't
been to a lot of like um
homes of like thirty some things at
that time so it's kind of interesting
just like get a little glimpse of
that um but i also noticed a
handful of people i know are we
where we're liking and reposting that and
i was like i'm curious if people
have
separate rooms
if we had like a huge house
i could see doing that jamie would
never go forth though yeah i sort
of like i assume no idea like
um when we're like ah work like
mike's been shooting a movie and he's
got a lot of night shoots where
like he has to yeah and because
he's that whole time
when i think about it if somebody
has to be up super early yeah
you know so we've been doing that
he'll sleep in the guestroom because it's
like he gets home at five am
and he has to sleep and then
meanwhile we would all be waking him
up you know if he was up
in the room so yeah what we've
been doing lately is because we have
the baby monitor on is like i
can i wake
up for anything here's the problem so
occasionally emeralds babbles in the middle of
the night for you know ten minutes
before she goes back to sleep just
blah blah blah blah blah right what
she tells you about is she possessed
yeah pretty much that's what i would
say i mean we tried to get
her possessed when she was born i
think it took okay
but um so she babbles so so
on the nights where i'm supposed to
have the baby monitor on in like
half you know sleeping half you know
checking to seeing oh being aware i
can wake up really easily here's my
issue i can't go back to sleep
oh so this morning three forty five
babbling
that's the end of it i'm up
that's really hard so conversely collab won't
wake up because of the baby monitor
so now she's been sleeping in emeralds
room so she can so she can
hear it and then also to give
me some sleep on
yeah that's where i'm not supposed to
be paying attention so right so that's
sort of like maybe every other night
we've been we've been in separate rooms
you know so i don't know yes
that's one solution we're trying right now
i yeah we did some of that
with um with baby early baby stuff
to have like just letting someone sleep
longer so go in the other room
so you can actually
really asleep but this is a totally
different thing this is like you have
your own style you have your own
decor i don't go in there oh
yeah i mean everyone knows your beds
even you don't like it
you're like this sucks i hate this
everything i chose
i can't choose good things i've accepted
it you just choose it
that's growths decor choose it all for
me wow but that's a that's a
relief it's a blessing to not have
to worry about that shit me more
or less the michael cores thing of
like i'm always gonna wear a black
suit jacket and a black t-shirt and
whatever and so yeah he wears the
exact same thing every single day i
love that and yeah the same thing
every day i would love that he
eats the same thing every day
no i just just that's a separate
topic it's like wow same thing every
day i would do that i just
saw a clip of someone else's eat
the same thing every day but i
i'm i'm totally opposed to that if
it was something really good but you
know what even that's that's not true
that's not true i think i used
to be like that and i'm not
like that anymore i think i could
very easily do that because i eat
you know for dinner that's when i
probably wanna mix it up the most
but for breakfast and lunch i eat
strictly from hunger it's just like yeah
to not be hungry anymore and i
could i could without thinking about it
same thing every yeah i mean i
eat the same thing for breakfast every
single day me too so although i
mix it up on the weekends
oh get low crazy yeah make my
little breakfast sandwich what do you eat
every day oh yeah we have talked
about your breakfast sandwiches because yeah they're
famous that's impressive yeah thank you yeah
we talked about them with what what's
i just remember being we we don't
want to re talk about somebody we've
talked about but who
shit guinea i i make gift to
you you make it a handheld
an egg is involved is it like
a full leg do you weigh the
egg just watches yep
and then two pieces of red that's
right and toasted
it
egg in the shell two pieces of
white bread sounds is a lid and
every morning you yes it hurts my
mouth
it's hard to bite into the shell
scrapes why the roof of my mouth
um no i make a i make
a scrapple egg and cheese sandwich on
an english muffin
wow i was taking breakfast orders for
a while ah collapsed and then after
a while you're like i take breakfast
orders from no one
clip sister lived with us for a
year
and during the walls right yeah during
the pandemic yeah in the ah yeah
bad ronald style um ronald mcdonald was
bad yes not good
he's in the walls
um she lived with this for a
year during the pandemic and self for
a while i was like taking breakfast
orders of like how do you want
your eggs and doing them however everyone
wanted i think that lasted three weeks
and then i was like you're on
your own it's really long time to
be dying people along absolutely did you're
like a fun thing to do in
the middle of the pandemic manage just
got to be such a such
a dragon yes who tells me i
can't work in a diner as a
fry cook oh but if you're getting
hey maybe you could maybe i should
see if they would pay me if
you're a diner if your fry cook
at a diner you're also behind a
wall with just a little slim opening
where the people can't really see what
you're doing so you should do anything
ah
oh my god you have coven scott
calvin it sounds like yoke having just
arrived i i just got it
um i feel like when i make
eggs in the morning if i'm going
to offer them to mike then i'm
like what kind of eggs do you
want how many do you want and
then i'm just making that style but
it's usually your scram we're just going
to go across the board not going
to be doing different orders for different
people i was doing different orders for
everyone yeah ruin one somewhat like coop
would be like
like i want an omelet with cheddar
cheese this this oh that's a foreigner
and then yeah her sister would be
like oh i want eggs over easy
with this this this it just was
too much cheeses for three weeks you
did that i know can you believe
it even if they ordered the same
every day doing that for three weeks
as a
yeah that's what i figured out but
it sounded fun to me when i
started well yeah nice you're not just
crinkled off you're a really good guy
alright we have to take a break
and we were but oh gray we're
back and it is great scrum i
just took holly to a little birthday
party for a child and it was
so adorable we were at train what
does it
what's it called travel down to that's
true travel town chat it's so cute
i've never been there because i guess
i don't know why i would end
up there but now from what i
hear from the other patrons is that
there is birthday parties there all the
time so it sounds like a place
i'll be going to quite a lot
absolutely
it's it's very adorable i loved it
it was so cute and yeah it's
in it's in ah in griffith park
here in l a is that yeah
and it's like there's these huge trains
that are just sitting there like old
style anchor the normal trains you know
what they're so close up they seem
bigger
you don't normally get to last that
close to right that's right there circle
sup and then there's a train that
you get to ride around a loop
twice and it's very adorable and as
it was really cute and holly loved
it ah and then they give you
they had little like goody bags with
like um engineer hats and bandai
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
it was just very charming and then
one thing that i thought was very
interesting is as you're riding the train
around the loop there's so there's the
highway's right there on the outside of
the thing and then there's a little
sliver that um fenced in where people
are riding horses that's like the width
of a horse
and then there's like the traffic on
the other side of them so there's
like this lane in the middle of
the highway that's like for people to
ride horses i just found that very
interesting i used to go horses famously
chill animals i'm sure they love that
part yes just being surrounded by whizzing
cars i bet they just they're in
heaven
yeah i used to go hiking there
and it was always like a sign
of oh wow i've gotten this far
when you would get to the part
where you would see the train tracks
yeah yeah yeah the horsey signs yeah
um i've seen the horses from afar
but it was interesting to be on
the inside looking out and um it
was delightful and i also you know
one of those things i
feel like scott i'm curious when you'll
feel this because you're still early and
with emerald yeah we haven't joined anybody
she doesn't need to go to a
lot of places but i feel like
now holly is at a point because
you can't walk around that i'm like
she needs to see some stuff so
like even if i'm really tired i'm
like we're go into the thing you
know it's like we're going to whatever
thing i have planned will be
be accomplished that day because i want
her to see something and experience something
and you know some whether she wants
to or not yeah we sometimes try
to walk around with her
yeah yeah i mean yeah but at
this point yeah no but she doesn't
have like that pent-up energy where she
like needs to run around you know
she's not crawling yet right so i
know she has the pent-up energy where
she wants to like sort of stand
up and wave yams and go yeah
that is the bounties she's been making
now what's the noise
i came here to say it's so
so high-pitched we can't hear you
take it down an octave ah
i don't know i'm terrified doc it's
like
that's cute
it's like saying
it's so funny though the screen it
just looks like why can you not
hear this i don't know this island
here's what it looks like to me
she goes like this
hey looks like making shows like mickey
yeah and the sound it sounds just
like it sounds just like the thing
with donald duck scandal duck ah energy
she always got the big deal again
she's got a dd
i've never been able to do the
donald duck noise
i've never tried and i'm not gonna
try now let's all try once come
on there i hey
okay kerry kerry kerry kerry kerry
ooooo
gonna i do it wow right right
here ford score and seven years ago
you sound just like him when he
made that speech
a lot of people don't know donald
duck made that speech and everyone attributes
it to well aber honest abe lincoln
co fair enough a wrote the speech
oh yeah sure that's true but he
was too shitty shit to deliver is
too shy actually yeah used user shy
as president that's my big hats yeah
over his head
eggs exactly and people would come up
to say mr president is president even
go ooh do you call the hat
down
um i in the internet turtlenecks and
you could just do it with that
let me but oh and then he
died then he died right this the
day after turtlenecks came out john wilson
was pulled his turtleneck up and tied
a knot in it and he suffocated
wow um it's here's let me tie
some things together the first time i
encountered
a person doing the donald duck voice
was when i was a little kid
and my father worked on the railroad
um and i saw live long day
all the live long day but he
did it just to pass the time
away he did not get paid
um i was at his i was
at his work at the ah at
the train yard and was it fun
to go to work with your dad
i hated it anytime i had to
go i thought it was cool i
was you know i like trains and
i thought it was really neat and
see where it was like seeing where
the trains lived you know what i
mean yeah uh
um and so engine trains house yeah
i've been trained makes you take issues
off um which is weird
there's no carpet yeah i think it's
wheels off and no when it comes
to my house no um and my
father introduced me to one of his
colleagues and he said that he introduces
man as ducky and then he said
you know why they call me ducky
and i said of course no i've
just fucking met you idiot
and if i had to guess it's
because you are a duck and then
he did the donald duck voice and
i remember being amazed at the oh
like wow you know it must be
nice to like not be in the
entertainment industry and you could just do
one little thing and you get a
whole nickname for it i know like
we're expected to do so much be
the hilarious seeing dance
if i'm getting the team incredible actors
award-winning actor i know i have to
be like i have to be if
quadruple threat yeah take our standups that's
transcribed them into a book yeah
but i wonder i don't know that
he necessarily got the nickname because he
did the voice he may have gotten
the nickname first and then he was
like oh i can also do this
voice yeah but he's but the whole
question is who would choose not do
you know you know why i'm here
oh yeah and then he did the
voice of that to make some kid
i'm sure there was a filthy reason
they called duck oh okay
we will put the pringles ah and
the duck lip formation and then shuck
and be yeah they're um duck like
dogs the formation only lets for darshan
mag duck lips like gothic slips like
dicks
duck lips lick dick okay now i'm
ready to do hamlet that's when you
when you're doing your american idol audition
video backstage yeah panicking i like the
idea of amber grey emblem
it's the hamburger is a hamburger hamlet
i help her hand you're doing hamlet
and he's doing hamlet yeah that would
be great i was pleased that as
we live that hasn't happened yet and
if people don't know there used to
be a restaurant in los angeles called
the hamburger hamlet yes are there any
still i hope i don't know if
they're
any left yeah should we make t-shirts
that have the hamburger ham hamburger helper
hand saying to be or not to
be yeah of course we should yeah
okay good yeah because it's like a
huge thing for us yeah
our friends used to work on the
at the hamburger hamlet on hollywood boulevard
across oh the chinese theater that's right
was it like a fast food or
like a sort of sit down sit
down sit down place that specialized in
hamburgers really delicious hamburgers ah lot of
like frisco's style sour dough zapped
ah yeah it was what's a frisco's
hamburger it's yea
it's gay and hilly
still do and it's cooler than you
think
is that your you have to have
san francisco i've i've always felt it's
exactly as cold as i've thought i
think it's always it's always really cold
but i think if you've never been
there you would think it's not going
to be cold for a long time
i would forget how when i started
going up there regularly for sand up
and stuff like that i would always
forget how cold it would be no
matter
what the time of year was yeah
and i always ended up like buying
a scarf yeah and that's why you
have eight thousand scarfs that's trying to
stay and that's why i'm making my
own quilt the coven quilt
and they're all san francisco forty niners
scarves that's that's right that's what i
would always buy
oh man now the hamburger hamlet i've
told this story before that's where i
got ah my id checks i got
carded well and um you know i
was born in nineteen sixty eight and
the server said oh nineteen sixty eight
the summer of love
so i said actually i think the
summer love was nineteen sixty seven and
you know it's nineteen sixty eight and
i said well you know what they
say if you if you can remember
the sixties you weren't really there and
she said i was really there and
i remember it was nineteen sixty eight
why got mad at me and then
what is the truth it might be
sixty seven yeah i hope she's dead
sixty eight m l k was assassinated
r f r f k was assassinated
like ninety six gay was not the
summer of love nobody may be sixty
nine of consumers so of course they
should wait and they didn't know
okay we were having a really good
time right now but those put it
off for two yeah like they're realizing
early june they're like this is getting
good like let's go through some hard
things together
make sure we really want this let's
reschedule all of our orgies all of
our lsd soaked orgies for for another
couple of years yeah but also hamburger
hamlet was where dean martin used to
go for dinner i think every night
of his life in the last years
of his life really really was just
like oh withered shell bob hope used
to
go to bob's big boy that's right
that's he nose and he was like
that's my house yeah i'm a big
boy too he thought that the statue
of the big boy was him yeah
there i am you get your if
you had to like go to a
place a lot of times like yeah
like that what would you pick like
if you're like you're old and you're
like you
have your fel a sort of restaurant
like for vibe or food or a
combo it's just what why do you
think they chose those places i don't
know because they feel very old school
so it's kind of like yeah it's
yeah it's like reminiscent of their there
when they were growing up and times
were good and all and
they weren't old pieces of shit that's
so depressing
what's depressing being old yeah i think
being old and reminiscing about the times
when you were young why is it
when you're just gonna accept his theory
yeah why is it they make fifties
diners but they don't make sixty s
diners they don't make seventy s diners
and oh yeah like there are diners
that are reminiscent of the seventies but
it's just they haven't updated them yeah
yeah fun let's let shit down estelle
jic let's do eighty diners ninety dinars
two thousand and one i think make
any colonial themed dies
winners there's not a lot there's not
enough orange and brown happening i would
say i really like the orange and
brown combo and i remember my duncan
really know why i grew up in
the seventy s and everything was orange
and brown we have talked about this
i i kind of comforting i find
it comforting to an hour that read
i like thee
the i like the aesthetic personally but
um my dunkin donuts growing up was
was definitely like probably an eighty's dunkin
donuts or something i don't know when
duncan started but it had a sort
of step with you it was brown
and d three just so it was
the seventy s let's rice roll around
these es gramps himself went to dunkin
donuts every dunk the first one in
by accident he had the he had
the shakes from drinking
ben affleck's coffee yeah
um
i don't want to have one duncan
was founded
i ok wow duncan yes can we
guess can we guess okay giving yes
can we guess caliphate yeah okay i'm
gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna have you
okay but i have a little quiz
for you i've a few just popped
up a bunch of different places when
they were founded so i'll i'll do
a little quiz okay duncan
when was it founded
it's a very straightforward quiz
wait just said duncan what dunkin donuts
but sound called duncan oh meaning when
okay to me to do like what
which one was doing to do just
guessing what is happening when it was
probably like you said i have a
quiz for you and you said one
word don't be because literally
because you know what is the quiz
we are guessing when it was found
to vary talking about you don't tell
me and then i said i have
other ones here because it popped up
all the other okay you have other
business but i do wish one came
first i'll do that okay dunkin or
krispy kreme or dunkin obviously i'm gonna
buy krispy kreme verse wow okay yeah
um
i would say paula's right now do
you want to guess years oh yes
for christina lee only started hearing about
krispy kreme like in two thousand oh
in the north perhaps with him the
south huh it was when the salem
north carolina but baga came through
yeah winston salem i'm gonna say nineteen
sixty one for crispy green sweetie pie
crispy creams nineteen thirty seven oh and
duncan nineteen fifty and mitch's hometown of
quincy mass wow i was gonna say
sixty s for duncan but krispy kreme
i should have gone
rest earlier because that like spelling with
a k for no reason is very
much of that that can two cases
so close to three k's luu and
get away with it now okay let's
do these two against each other okay
seven eleven which came first seven eleven
or tim hortons
seven law seven eleven or tim hortons
god this is a good too i
don't you know i didn't know anything
about tim horton still i started going
to canada it's so huge there there's
so many of them but there's so
many seven elevens seven elevens were only
open from seven to eleven but tim
or i don't know i'm gonna go
tim tim tim hortons result from
tim hortons
you got your tim you got your
hortons um okay seven eleven was founded
in nineteen twenty seven wow okay jesus
wow and tim hortons was nineteen sixty
four
these aren't even close i know um
but isn't it fun how you think
they're okay how about okay how about
these two shit like these are very
close okay chick filet okay these are
very close i'm gonna guess i'm gonna
ask you to guess which decade it
was in chick filet and baskin robbins
oh als
i'm going to say ah ah where
they both in the same decade they're
on the same decade i'm okay guess
seventy s i'm going to say sixty
s
forty s chick filet name forty six
baskin robbins nineteen forty five wow isn't
that crazy it would be so fun
to go to chick-fil-a for lunch and
then go to baskin robbins for for
lunch disaster yeah always scobie so cool
there'll be so fun and you would
say to both did people behind the
counter both that at both establishment you'd
say this was established in the forties
yeah you'd be like you you wouldn't
you would have it you wouldn't even
believe it yeah and you'd say and
at the second place i bet your
mom would you would say i also
said this chick filet yeah it's clear
you would say i'm also going to
tell this to baskin robbins yeah
and then they will probably talk to
each other via yeah call each other
up and be like yeah some weird
kid just come in here hey look
out weird kiss on his way he
may be armed i might have to
go to fucking crispy cream after this
because the sun is so great
yeah but like can how i would
get in the car you can just
take off during the day not i
would take hollywood with me wow we'd
go over to the burbank empire center
leno
um working fucking every night so how
many donuts can you eat before you
feel absolutely disgusting and full of self-loathing
oh my calf of one
i would say two is where i
start to go you got a really
calm it down we i'd have been
talking and get there after one after
one why one is where i go
let's be real that was enough we
found lighting really wanting back of cutting
the doughnuts into like eight pieces because
you really only wa
don't like you see the them all
in one minute yeah yeah you said
that i do like i want to
try every single one but yeah but
you you really only want a taste
of what and they all taste exactly
the same thing for me is doughnuts
as as a sweet treat donuts are
never fully not worth it they're not
fully worth it like a piece of
cake or a piece of pie some
ice cream and that's why i don't
the dream is different because they're heated
it's not that different though but when
you get that melted your mouth hey
my high school had this thing and
i'd never heard a crispy cream but
then in my high school day was
that there was a thing where i
was like you could buy a box
of krispy kreme and they would be
delivered on a certain day they get
like a hundred million boxes it's everyone
bottom yeah and you get your own
boss
box and then that would be like
who doesn't donuts yeah just dozen doughnuts
yeah i would just scarf from down
i'm i wouldn't eat twelve in a
sitting but i'd eat gu three and
then i take them home which and
then really it's probably i take them
home and put them in the microwave
you put them in the microwave for
like three you're gonna eat eight
but i'm in the micro for exactly
six seconds right and it's like like
is that how long just melted on
that
bucking bronco i believe that was eight
oh that was okay sorry yeah i
don't know the reference it's a very
nice reference actually this movie was not
as measured there was a luke perry
started in a um a rodeo movie
ah called eight seconds because that's the
amount of time you have to last
i believe on the horse before like
them
throws you off before you can get
off of it isn't that right it's
like if you can last eight seconds
you can jump off because you've lasted
as long as isn't that isn't or
i think eight something like minimum i
don't know
i think eight seconds is the minimum
yeah in order to in order to
qualify as anyone anyone on one for
like like three hours anyone of us
yeah not me i have to wait
a minute i have i lost a
lot of ninety minutes the layered longest
i've gone is like two and a
half hours and
and my brain fell out of my
head oh what i do the way
i do it ah is i i
take a book to read
so the time yeah cdi yeah yeah
i usually plug in my ipod on
top of it's head yeah yeah so
yeah focused on it yeah yeah boards
of the horse yeah yeah
did you like me out the devil
what were we talking about
oh don't wait it does eight seconds
on a horse but then there's also
bull riders right i thought i was
thinking of i thought it was a
bowl i don't know i don't know
how long those guys have to stay
up there bishop cutter and half the
whatever it is cold and half the
time and the bull yeah lengthwise if
you stay out there for five seconds
then they cut the bull in half
and they're like what have you want
you did it
they're like this is my bowl no
this is michael got the bullet and
hat that's right a king comes out
yeah yeah would you cut it lengthwise
like a hotdog yeah i kinda diagonally
nobody just wants to connect for style
pretty sneaky sis
ah we all agreed i don't think
don't donuts are a good treat although
if you're craving one i don't want
to harsh your your craving right you're
not gonna i do i feel don't
do it okay i really yeah if
i'm really going to use those calories
i'm gonna like do it like caviar
in the finish
champagne
yeah i mean look
the finest champagne yeah i start my
day with eggs with caviar on top
yes and i and we have your
sandwich yeah and it was caviar sandwich
and caviar mcmuffin champagne caviar dagwood and
then
it's just a gigantic every other layer
is caviar
it's pastrami it's a roasted turkey it's
a good good black forest ham
yeah ok we have to take a
break okay there i don't care either
and actually i'm the one who cares
i'm not funny episode going while this
goes to break laura and the most
am talking i'm actually tell bra i'm
telling paul something really important now
and that's why they called it the
spanish puppy love puppy love
and they called it puppy oh ooh
i think i saw donny osmond saying
that on the donny and marie show
wow when i was a child when
i was but a wee child that
was an era of siblings singing together
yeah
unlike man really he's ever seen saying
yes who do we have now the
avett brothers
are they even brothers jonas brothers
are they even together anymore yeah they
are they still do some performance oh
yes
what about ah one direction they were
all related by blood but that's this
is so yeah they were all created
in a lab but this is different
i'm talking about brother sister standing on
stage singing a little ditty brethren sister
feels very rare like i don't know
if anybody is doing that these days
there has got to be some
many out there i got ask a
question true is just part of the
episode or are we just talking
yeah mother fucker this is part of
the episode part of the episode because
yeah it's supposed to be doing a
three-tier and no one has found one
i was looking at the document as
i was looking to you yeah smart
card doing two things at one women
can multitask oh wait just listen and
i did hear your
earth shade that you just threw but
we just got a new um some
new questions from the three via that
trivia game where we have to know
things buddy oh sure sure sure sure
anyone here is what i was thinking
do we have enough for the future
i mean look here's what i was
thinking we should do the old questions
and see if we can remember oh
my god i like
that idea we can ah oh no
these are great these are great to
me to leave the game
yeah one yeah let's let's do it
um okay so you guys just get
here we've gotta get a pc sure
if if this is your first episode
of three-time basically we've talked and talked
and still same just told the same
stories over and over again and we're
a listener has compiled some trivia questions
about stories
we've talked about on previous episodes to
see if the three of us can
remember anything that we've talked about on
previous episodes okay so the first round
is scott questions so scott just write
down the true answer as you know
it and poland will do the same
thing trying to guess one what two
sports did
scott's parents make him participate in against
his will when he was a child
i know this i know it's
this is a two parter what if
you get yeah do you get let's
say that's just worth two points and
you get one point per okay got
it
why don't we make it half a
point because okay other people the other
people only get you know for sure
sure sure yeah stop you guys having
an advantage over me to get like
suddenly you have six points and i
can only get any degree going
scott's roommate the i have parties guy
had a friend with an unusual nickname
what was that nickname
ducky okay what musician did scott risk
getting fired to see a disneyland when
he worked there oh wait i sort
of remember this these are good questions
i know them all okay ready yep
one of scott's former bosses was seen
drunk
crying whilst wearing an all yellow outfit
what hilarious question did his coworker ask
after witten witnessing this i know this
one
a classic this is a classic
ah and the final question as a
teenager scott called into a radio show
as popeye to tell jokes what was
the name of the show bonus who
was the host oh shit oh and
each one you know each person has
a bonus question so i would i
would ah save that the show was
not called this the the segment was
called this
okay and that's okay yeah yeah and
then the i'm the host um the
host was okay
yeah ok
okay do you want to give us
the answers yeah or do you want
to go on well we'll get why
don't we guess first yeah okay yeah
right exactly yeah okay paul watt to
sports did god's parents make him participate
in against as well one was baseball
yes and the other was dad dance
i said
baseball and soccer
baseball is correct you each get half
a point the other one was gymnastics
christianity matchsticks that's yes christian gymnastics okay
alright um what was i have parties
friends nickname i said that fridge fridge
i said
i'm sorry neither of you get a
point the nickname was bagel yeah that's
okay what musician did was legally hired
i don't know i you know like
legal never asked okay what musician did
scar is getting fired to see at
disneyland when he worked there paul i
said billy
joel i said can you imagine but
i said you too yeah this was
a david bowie no it was roy
orbison ah rye fifties themed this is
nineteen eighty eight they were doing fifty
themed ah concert series and where
there were several luminaries of the fifties
were playing concerts and roy orbison to
me knowing see i forgot that it
was at i thought you were going
to get fired from disneyland but okay
um okay what was the thing said
to the all yellow outfit crying person
lauren why is that banana crying
i said who bruised the banana yeah
yeah frozen bananas correct because of the
mascara running down her huh damn it
dark mascara yellow total yellow sweats that
she was wearing i got banana right
you did oh i pictured it as
a yellow dress she's wearing yellow sweat
she's wearing yellow sweatshirt and yellow
sweats yeah it's so different all same
um ok and as a teenager you
called into pop to tell jokes just
popped by what was the name of
the radio show and who was the
host i said it was friday funnies
with finley farrington i said it was
a morning zoo with buzzy
it was the boogie line with russa
dong line there's no way we would
know that i know that's a tough
that's too tough okay yeah bowie's who
was the host the host okay
okay right like i want to have
points i have point five it is
time for the loring round oh boy
oh my god it's so funny to
have these questions right and that's just
hilarious
okay and what country did lauren have
the first cherry she ever ate
remember
but there's another country it's santa
ah alright
why did you never eat it too
okay well because we don't get taught
how late game show what are you
gonna say i just wanna know either
show
okay
in lawrence first ever appearance on the
comedy bang bang podcast who was the
special guest oh shit jesus i don't
know this i'm not sure if i'm
gonna get it right ah um okay
i think it's i think it's that
person okay ah why can't think of
his last name oh should i give
you a hint um
okay ah shit what's his name
whatever okay three what did the evanston
police officer give lauren after crossing paths
with her the third time
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay right right i do sort of
remember this but i think i got
it wrong but anyway oh okay i'm
getting this next one i'm sort of
getting credit for slaying paul kind of
did what delicious treat to lauren bring
into the three-time studio for scott's birthday
we did it together though yeah yeah
ah but this is almost a question
about me like well yeah does the
tree gross liked that's true it's kind
of getting my infringing on my moment
yeah gets stolen valor
what movie did lauren go see when
she slipped on the restroom floor and
suffered a concussion
ah robert kiss yeah yeah and then
bonus with whom did she go to
the movie
ah i have to um
okay
okay oh yeah okay
um ok what country did i have
my first cherry um i'm gonna say
italy
i said greece it was italy whoa
and i had just never had one
and then we picked them off a
tree and it was amazing wow nice
can't believe what essential memory it was
sensually i could see that i could
see that in an independent film about
coming of age too
totally who was the guest on my
first cvb
scott do you remember ice i said
marc marron i have no idea yes
special i said um adam brutes that
is correct oh yeah yeah
okay amazing were you happy to see
him i don't remember ah could i
get a boner
um no i was of course i
was happy to see him he's ah
he's a wonderful actor um okay who
what i didn't know what i was
doing by the way i hadn't i
had no idea what was going on
and i didn't know so i was
just excited to get through the moment
um what did the oven simply officer
give me the third time we crossed
paths
scott this is tough because i first
said trading card and then i changed
it to phone number
i said trading card
what's your final answers got trading cards
yeah fuck yeah that is the answer
thank you that's not fair okay what
delicious extreme
my delicious treat did we have for
scott's birthday what a millionaire work that
way i know i should but your
final answer was not that yeah of
course it was whipped cream and chocolate
chips yeah i was saying chocolate chips
and then what was the movie that
i hit my head on the floor
before i got too lazy i
i said it was goonies and you
saw it with josh brolin
oh i said house to the second
story with adam brody
no the movie was ladybugs starring rodney
dangerfield and i saw it with my
dad and brother well i didn't see
much of it ok okay now give
i'm gonna give myself half a point
for trading cards so i'm gonna say
i have two and a half great
thanks for your honesty paul woody how
much do you owe i have
have one two three and then ah
four you had from before i have
one and a half and a half
so four and a half four and
a half and you're locked in four
and a half because the next round
right out you say long have i
need to get four i need oriented
tie two to tie two and a
half to win
okay let's go people alright here according
to paul what alternative name should he
have based on how he looks
what
oh my god this has been mentioned
a couple times actually i did has
yeah
um
okay
can we each have two guesses and
then we get a half point okay
okay to call erroneously referred to the
movie last vegas by another
what was that title
there's a movie last days yes and
you referred to it i know why
yes yeah these are very obscure my
questions had more facts but ok um
ah these these are facts i mean
when the things you said but it's
not like like it's like mine was
like what treat to have for scott's
birthday
a who was on the first episode
you know that kind of thing you
could just know that but this is
well you could just know something that
i said from we discussed it yeah
okay three paul's mom had a reception
job i'm sorry receptionist job and his
uncle's business what was that business
uncles oh god we were just talking
about your dad's train business
yeah that's what we'll call it his
train business
ah just make a guess we gotta
move it on alright okay for what
book did paul read that helped him
quit smoking for good like i can
never remit you can barely remember the
title of this me yeah right no
no he says it yeah regularly ah
okay i know like a better question
would be how did paul quit smoking
and i would go he read this
book yeah remember the title of
and you'd volunteer that information
five paul comes from a family of
six children whereas paul and the birth
order bonus how many cousins did he
have living next door okay and the
birth order
ah
right right how much do we get
for the bonus by the way is
that an extra just one what so
it's one in one so it's six
points total we can got it many
cousins day of living next door
okay are we ready okay yep ready
according to paul what alternative name should
he have based on how he looks
i guessed the most handsome and gorgeous
gentlemen who ever lived wow
i guest roger
the name i think i should have
is dennis j peacock oh shit i
did know that it's j p ca
i did know that okay so i
really gotta get all the recipes right
in order to have a standing fighting
chance okay um what was the other
title last vegas
was he said another title what was
that title
i said vegas baby i don't know
i said goodbye vegas the answer of
course is old vegas nice vic because
it was about old man going to
las vegas and i was complaining that
old vegas isn't really a play on
anything and that's why they didn't do
yeah exactly that's why
last vegas which is a play i
didn't know that that was called last
week the only thing i remember about
that is the entertainment weekly interview where
morgan freeman said that he would allow
a director to tell him to speed
up or slow down and that's the
only thing a director would ever say
to me that's right the crazy okay
um paul's mom had a receptionist job
at his uncle's business what was that
business butt plugs piano piano business piano
tuning lawrence correct piano tuning wow
i got one oh alright i gotta
pull this out with
honestly the only chance i have is
the last question okay what book did
paul help or would you paul read
that helped him quit smoking for good
hey dennis j peacock stop smoking okay
how weird you are able
i don't know how to quit the
smoke games change i think it was
just one odd thing i do i
truly did not know it until i
wrote that i think it was called
how to quit smoking or you can
quit smoking quit smoking i actually think
the advantage general i can accept an
answer with or something in it how
to
quit smoking what actually wrote down was
how to quit smoking in fifteen minutes
but that's insane
the book
at the end of the book it's
like ed go yeah um the easy
way to stop smoking by allen carr
damn and if anyone out there wants
to stop smoking this book work like
a charm for me i highly recommend
it
okay i'll say it again i'm gonna
say it again the easy way to
stop smoking by allen carr okay alright
if i get both of these right
i can tie where is paul and
the birth order of six kids
i said six
i said fifth
scott you are incorrect lauren your correct
said news five high x if i
had been the baby i would not
even know you guys because yeah and
all the attention i needed that's true
we in and how many cousins lived
next door i said five
i said for seven damn yeah yeah
yeah yeah i got none of paul's
okay what's everyone's final score two and
a half two and a half four
and a half you win again you
um you one last time yes i
did i will say if i guide
my patients i would say if i
had
yes i would say paul has the
best memory i still do have a
pretty decent memory it's true he does
it so that was really fun i
love that game didn't want to just
give a shout out the game is
created by nathan diffie and yeah i
believe question i think he might have
just added new ones because doesn't say
but if someone did
id and i'm wrong and please let
me know anything if he of course
very talented are we don't know my
weight well
it was submitted by lee augustine those
questions were submitted by me housley thank
you lee alright it was amazing and
please submit more of those are hilarious
was going to say nathan duffy a
very talented artist who does all of
my posters lee hawke scene i don't
know shit about you but thank you
for submitting those questions that was a
lot of fun
that was really bad about lee hoxton
though yeah we need to know one
fact and then we play a trivia
game oh by the way when you're
submitting these three cheers quit one fact
about yourself yeah
yeah and then in future games we
have to give the answers to the
one fact about each of those
and it can either be a fun
fact or it can be a sad
fact yes no middle ground no nothing
in between no no just random facts
no just like i have brown hair
yeah it's gotta be either fun or
sad or sad
well yeah we did it yeah we
i i thought it was great i
had a great time if you would
like to send us a three cheer
right to three team usa at gmail
dot com you can also call us
at the phone number hag claims eight
um you can follow us on the
socials at three m usa and don't
spell eight
eat right it's that's right the number
eight hag claims the number eight and
if you wanna listen to ad-free versions
of the show you can do so
on stitcher premium or on cbbc world
dot com listen but by the way
because listen listen to all the ads
that we record we we spent so
much time trying to perfect them and
rehearsing them yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah so like a
lot of times ah made-up producer will
write to us and say hey could
you do this ad and and we'll
say matt we've recorded the ads way
in advance on professional equipment and took
great care with them um so we
don't we definitely don't need to do
a voice memo on our phones and
sometimes no no worries yeah cool
workshop them out of town for a
while yeah well sometimes he'll like he'll
say hey this brand reached out are
you guys interested in we'll say let's
let us get together and rehearse a
few times like what we might say
if we were to do an ad
for them see if it feels natural
and then we'll kind of get on
the horn and good yeah mouths yeah
yeah we haven't we have the sophia
we have a storage space that we
rent that we use is kind of
a lie
lab for the products where we will
all go and sample whatever it is
together we give it like two or
three hours and then um and then
we we are able to really feel
the ads so do listen to those
ads do listen yes please please check
out the ads because they are so
so so well rehearsed and also i
would love to just give a shout
out march twenty
second paul and i are doing a
show for dynasty typewriters fifth anniversary year
doing a two-person improv show up and
you can get tickets to the livestream
or in person on dynasty typewriter dot
com that's right yeah we're looking forward
to it it's gonna be a lot
of fun i'll give one does this
when does this come out i'm sorry
gotcha day thursday thursday thursday listen there's
still some tea
tickets left for my show ah if
i don't have covered ah sunday march
twelfth um at um lodge room and
highland park it's going to be a
special st patrick's day ah version of
rancho pia we're gonna do irish music
um we have great ah great musical
guest and great comedy guests it's going
to be a lot of fun
that's fine wanna shout out i have
a copy of it the comedy bang
bang huh scott showing it to us
you guys i was going to show
it to you when you came over
but it's gorgeous wow looks beautiful so
excited early guys really good in ah
i can't wait to see ah
dang it looks really cool it's really
calm if you wanna go to comedy
bang bang world dot com slash book
and i just wanna say the history
of the world part two premiered on
hulu and i'm in the first episode
it was a four night event and
tonight is the last night of the
four night event well catch up and
watch the always out wide people keep
posting about it
um guys we love you we love
our piss pigs especially the where's the
beef lady yes honorary pest repeller across
our ah
well rest in piss rest oh my
god rest in power piss
alright p b rested our best car
feller oh via pie
uh