three
three wow wow eye contact direct icon
it's scary it's scary and it's not
necessary and i do wish i didn't
ask for it yeah but you asked
for it it's scary idea scary and
unnecessary it's scary so scary and unnecessary
how does everyone's tell me feel i
feel ok let's catch the listeners up
because it's been a week
since they refuse little freedom let's get
check check check
yes yes yes yes yeah
we all will get chicks chapter this
is scott lord and paul we all
got shake shack shamble in between epstein
lorin we all got shake shack we
all ate shake shack we didn't just
receive it and then say let's just
roared and then we'll eat it after
a lot of times we'll order food
we'll throw it away yeah um yes
just as flicks yeah but
listen if you don't know what shake
shack is it's a restaurant yeah what
a fancy restaurant yeah it's it's fine
i think that's all shots i think
of it as healthy
because they have like better seats than
burger king yeah yeah if i didn't
make it at home is healthy you
know honestly if the seats are so
important to your health because if you're
sitting there in burger king and you're
constantly squirming you're like oh my wow
my tiny but supported and cetera et
cetera you can just relax it shake
shack you know that your bud is
going
you saying it right yeah the burger
king chairs are so uncomfortable because he
when they wanna remind you that you're
not the king you're a peasant you're
a peasant you're a bigger person here
is that here in the burger kingdom
yeah well i think when people think
of burger king the one thing they
think is the seats are not comfortable
and yes and yeah sure i mean
dan says he used to try to
make it like have it your way
like they they tried that to catch
on it was like no guys then
it was like c turn rise or
third best and then it was like
our seats were uncomfortable and that is
that really
yeah so anyway we all had shake
shack ding ding ding ding ding junhui
yeah j jag go but down but
um but um tom note and about
and a half you heard let us
learn in a barn but have you
heard worn in the barn and have
huh jesus christ is my id boo
one of the best birds and is
one of the best birds
that's how we've loved to have it
he actually was a bird and everyone's
like this does your god talk into
this whole fucking time ah chao cheese
steak to philadelphia cheese steak can even
see it and you could order this
hat with onions or without onions and
i order with onion that because that's
how i like my pants i have
a hotdog oh hey char puffins
being molested
sorry moleskin yours are being molested um
so we all ordered a shake shack
let's run down orders get lord chicken
bites six piece flies crinkle cut your
prisoner of war that's chicken by six
piece crinkle cut i had the chicken
sandwich and the buffalo fries i had
the
aforementioned hot dog the only person to
get it that's right they did not
send mustard with it so it was
a little disappointing what it was for
my in the kitchen it no i
didn't think to look for mustard or
i don't consider if your client yeah
i don't consider offices to be mustard
rich environments well their sandwich plain hotdog
so it was a plane
hot dog i like it i'll really
a freak like you like just plain
hot dog yeah no bun just read
out loud like the bug like a
bomb i don't like the right out
of the what about grows about butter
um butter um you know it's actually
been a recent introduction my parents were
visiting and my mom some butter on
the thing and i was like what
are we to karna
vol i really thought it was like
next level but better a hotdog on
the bun to kind of like add
like oh well yeah but before you
before you owe me toasted or not
to toast but yeah that's what when
i was young i was like that's
what my year and now we're putting
butter on this and then not to
toast it but just as a con
just as a condiment you ever heard
of this yeah it was good
i will say but i could feel
myself getting fatter yeah you're closer to
rip
like lou ferrigno my dad used to
put butter i would turn it off
by the way her the minute his
closed starts around yeah anything interesting please
full yeah exactly oh man that show
lou ferrigno i just like to see
that one guy get mad
and they'd go to another town or
realized now i have it backwards the
way lou ferrigno was in the in
the news in the offer yeah he
looks he's what he seventy years old
looks exactly like lou ferrigno he hasn't
aged it's raised to be a comicon
ah like midtown comics or whatever you
can be signing stuff and so and
you just kind of pass by and
go it's fucking lou ferrigno and he
was
i heard that i know i
hi lauren do you get any of
this stuff there you go yeah so
my dad used to put butter on
peanut butter and jelly sandwiches oh no
that's so many many layers a lot
of stuff loop you also used to
eat liver worst he says um it
was called bad guy and well right
now six feet so now that she
yo right now he's busy pushing up
the daisies um but yeah butter on
a hot dog to two bits of
course yeah but yeah the hot dog
and i had a smoker and a
hotdog
i a smoke shack and i crinkle
cut fries and then and then what
happened and then we all separately went
to the bathroom i hadn't gone yet
so you you're clutching your side
you're touching your phone you look like
you have happened to me i feel
good yeah i like doing this that
was a coincidence but my so doesn't
feel perfect i'll say it doesn't feel
right it's not just like chill and
how it was before we ate the
food it hasn't hit me yet but
i also eat very fast so ah
there's the food has not yet reached
my guts so if you eat super
fast right it slows down right that's
the bottom line is that your theory
i yes my theory is super fast
furious
so the food will slow down as
it goes down food the food doesn't
know where to go
it got there all at once say
well alright let's wait the whole sandwich
and we're already all here
let's chosen you happen to us ah
ah my gosh so shake shack if
you're listening why don't you sponsor us
because we've talked about you listening here's
a deal shaker if you're always doing
the former president remember russia if you're
listening russia if you're listening yeah who
is that i don't you know yeah
that guy one of our former president
yeah yeah oh
that guy jay jaffe lizzy
so you only do present impersonation now
yeah all i do you're just a
you're the new rich little yes i
remember seeing him when i was a
kid i saw him on some special
it was like fourth of july thing
and he did impressions of all these
presidents like going back i think even
before like whoever we had recordings of
of right but it's like no one
knows what warren was hoping like calvin
coolidge human knows it sounds like i
get i'll take away rich little doing
an impression of someone you've never did
like truman like okay sure well like
we do lincoln who do who do
we know lincoln lincoln i've been thinking
but that's debatable isn't it who who's
the first guy
we know for sure that everyone could
go like oh yeah is it fdr
fdr yeah what did he do well
i have nothing to fear right right
yeah joffe and so you gotta sound
really far away and static we were
doing very different voice i've never been
to butterfly
shit i gotta take a shit right
all over the movie i forgot and
i tried to stand up ah i
brought huh might
bowie who is after fdr yeah broken
foot that's why he's in the wheelchair
yeah don't mean for so long yes
who was after after year i can't
do this i memorize it all the
way back to the to nineteen hundred
and nine i've totally forgotten it let's
hear it well okay so you got
to you know the dude who's in
there now brandon i'm just kidding oh
ma
yeah joseph robinette biden forty five and
then you have ah robinette obama and
before that is george w bush and
before that is clinton and for the
bar that is george h w bush
and before that is reg and bandwidth
that is clear
and before that is ford ford and
then before that is nixon before that
his will me day before that was
john f kennedy let him do it
when i say yeah we i need
this i need all the help is
these oh i need this okay before
that was dwight david
eisenhower right before that was harry s
truman yeah the eu before that was
franklin delano roosevelt okay so then we're
back to it and before that we
heard hoover because bird up all the
money and that's why yeah that's how
i was doing it like with little
tricks in my mind i want to
say before that was coolidge in them
before that was wilson
but i'm niles are the order of
those guys coolidge was i remember there
was like two double letters around coolidge
and that's how i would remember it
or something like that but yeah coolidge
was like h and w w yeah
so coolidge was in the middle coolidge
and but he's got much back and
he was ah he's come when he
was like
nineteen oh eight or something like that
through sixteen zero it was nineteen years
old he was nineteen years he was
he was just seventeen and you know
what i mean so i would your
cutest present
guys whoa
oh everything's easy try the new twilight
zone episode about the kid president no
not toil i don't watch it
you know what were you in in
president thousand yeah i was the president
oh you so adorable they put a
filter on yeah
ah i wasn't one tony newsome and
i were in the same episode with
ah journey smaller otani news i faced
a tommy newsome and i was like
tell me newsome from the tonight show
band
has been probably dead for many decades
it's like you might be alive i
always have it yeah we have no
idea um yeah it was about and
journey small bed with somebody who she
had this ah she wanted to be
a singer and so somehow law etc
yeah and so and so right
it's something like that yes and that
was the thing was um people she
wanted to be like famous she wanted
to be like have everybody loved her
so then what happened is people were
just like cheering and clapping for her
wherever she went and it wasn't about
the music anymore more it was just
about the the feeling of being loved
and totally fee
feel with this podcast tom lennon was
in that episode really when it was
almost like a singing competition that she
wins then i was a talk show
she goes on the talk show everybody's
clapping so much that she runs out
in a fright oh and what did
you do i clapped i was under
the spell of the dialogues oh yes
okay that's really that's really freaky stuff
that's free
freaky fucking myself it felt freaky at
the time because covert was happening oh
as it still is yeah yeah it's
like it is now i wanna mean
away we're still in i want to
be the last person to ever coven
like it ends with me oh they'll
be like and i just put a
period at the end of this sentence
and it'll be like you'll be reported
on the news like children
and yeah the last guy ever open
to not get coven has gotten covert
and overt know i know i'm meeting
no one ever gets it after me
yeah that's why i said it's over
man oh i see as i said
superman i did i was saying i
didn't want to be the last person
to ever get covert and i know
you want it to be the last
person to ever yeah there can be
other people out there who never gotten
comin own
only way that's gonna happen is your
the very last person to get it
you're probably right i know it
you're probably right that's i think when
the last person to get it
and then that was it the animals
would like take over instead of i
think they would bow down to me
to be like that movie thirty monkeys
all creatures great and small would come
to me and bow before their master
like what's one would you want to
do it first which one would i
want to bow first problem yoke why
the ilk because there's
horns and everything would be so funny
it would be like check those out
an elephant this huge creature bowing to
you he's gonna be in the back
so we he's gonna block everyone he's
gonna block the field mice and everything
if he's in the frog they're fucked
anyway then you could see over the
elk como okay i want this guy
you're kidding yourself i want the ants
and the mosquitoes and the net
it's first also size order yeah smallest
to tallest smallest to tallest thank you
they all bow at the same time
they all arranged themselves at first like
a wave it's you know how anytime
you see like ah you're on broadway
and everyone's bow at the same time
it always happens in the middle and
then like goes back yeah exactly yeah
i do know that yeah so that's
what i want lauren give it to
me well i guess we could see
what i won't
i'll be here i'm not going to
be dead i'll be here i'll just
know you'll be dead in this scenario
oh hey why when i already had
kava you're saying the animals and i
doubt you until all the humans are
dead or just lauren just like have
you killed lauren because i'm not bound
you dude if you got a job
ahead off ok
we didn't hey lauren would you if
you grew up on a farm yeah
and you had to like kill jiggy
yeah he's like oh well we have
different approaches how would you would you
like you know if you had to
kill chickens yeah you know that would
you be cool that if i grew
up on a farm i'm gonna go
ahead and guess that yeah it would
be yeah because it'd be ingrained in
eve when young age yeah
perfectly to be a killer i always
remember hearing a story about my great
grandma chopping off a chicken's neck and
it would run around you know just
go
oh do i use two axes chop
self go pick out the chicken at
the at the place from the big
thing at home and give it a
slap give the slap first us snack
the next slap oh old knife of
sorts let me
oh nice and then eat the chicken
you know sound like a grandmother right
now hey i feel like one right
damn i feel like a grandma there
by her minute you now can i
tell you that that song is very
funny to me it is funny but
did we really talk about this i
think we did yeah yeah on this
show can i tell you
very sure yeah i would please go
even thinking about it and so we
spoke about it i have an abrupt
change of subject okay pay anybody pretty
pretty pretty pretty is this paul topics
know what was my thing was a
cool post title or did you have
my head was basically take off like
lawrence topics take its ponytails new let's
do it let's do it during lauren
that's not news yeah paul's new you
know what this is this is a
what to think okay this is paul's
what to think and you're going to
take our temperature on what we thought
about whatever your your your thing is
you know what you think yeah okay
what you think about curtain calls because
recently a friend of mine
fine we were having dinner and he
went to see a play and before
he went to see the play a
friend of his said art curtain calls
weird like when you actually look at
it isn't it a strange thing that
the play is over and then the
people come back out and i was
like i get that should do it
in movies
brad pitt and sandra bullock and damn
i'm just bough why i want them
away as other cares well that's the
thing it's i don't think it's weird
yeah like i like it as the
tradition of the theater i think an
audience would would be stymied and would
would feel unsatisfied having not being able
to thank yeah these people lie
i think that we're so used to
it that it would be very strange
if it wasn't there yeah but this
person's point was if the thing is
over why do you why do you
go through this this moral rigmarole or
whatever um i will say this though
that the individual curtain calls i think
don't need to happen meaning wherever i'm
coming out separately everyone
and getting around somebody somebody gets more
clauses really
i still think it's ok i think
it's nice to slap for the people
and have them feel that energy i
do too and i think if anything
come out one by one that's also
nice because i get that moment that
excitement but it it it tends to
be a combination like how it builds
like oh the person with the least
part comes out first and well you
know what i you always you always
know who is
is going to get the most of
what what what i used to hate
that yeah so then take away from
seeing shows that though just had that
one person come out but it's also
a collaborative school will get you in
a second it's also a collaborative art
form so i think everybody should bow
at the same time yeah i do
think approximately the same to me like
the idea of you're seeing these people
do this in ff
front of you they've worked on it
for a long time and they're actually
there that i think that's a great
moment to have the curtain call between
you know the performers and the audience
what have we did a curtain call
after these we have been nobody knows
i always bow after every podcast they
do things like leave the zoom and
then i back to your
computer yeah well i when i used
to see shows at the la mirada
playhouse they would always to get people
to come to them because you know
la mirada california is not like a
cultural yeah you ever go there um
to get people to go to them
they would cast like one famous person
and i remember seeing ted launch as
isaac your bartender yes as ah
the drill instructor in biloxi blues neil
simon's play that matthew broderick ah did
fantasy broadway did he do the play
or the movie i can't remember too
he did the movie okay so wait
did he i don't think so i
think he was replaced for that one
and the superman did we yeah yeah
i think silberman didn't like the single
guy silberman from your girl schedules yeah
little partner in crime so the issue
for me is when ted launch who
has a a showy part but a
supporting role these these kids and especially
the guy playing matthew broderick's role are
the are the backbone of this show
yes but then ted launch because he's
the biggest star is that the pronunciation
maybe huh
ten launch l a n g he
gets the last bow and everyone and
he gets the most applause and it's
all because of fame yeah fuck that
if i were an and i and
i saw it and i was like
ten launch i don't respect you anymore
because if i was dead launch i
would be saying let the let these
kids have the bow yes i'm gonna
go firm
yes yes yeah the first of us
shall be like it shall be last
yes and let the applause your ow
yes and i still win yeah because
they wouldn't cheer louder food makes girls
claire for turtles i think it's insulting
to to if someone were to say
to me if i were in ted
launches place i sincerely hope i am
so
someday i would i would refuse it
definitely refuse would you refuse refusal so
noble noble yeah um what i refuse
it what i refuse getting a ton
of applause for work that i put
in um but more more more than
like you've only shown up for an
hour a day meanwhile this kid is
there eight hours a day i would
then motion to the kid and i
would say cheer louder for me
him yeah that's a way to do
it actually if like okay i know
i'm the most famous and i'm getting
the final bow but i'm gonna bring
him up and go like no no
no but how's about it but how
about him i would ok here's what
i would do and it would look
it would make me look great yeah
i would come out at the end
of course because you expect me to
expect you to you can't throw off
when you're ted long
sharks i would of course yes i
do the point from the love boat
yeah yeah you're a ted launch you're
going to have to come out last
year olds people will be very soon
yes so let's get that wow ted
lounge and i will when when they
applaud i'll act surprised and then i'll
like cross my hand what about row
known what about rubbing your eyes absolutely
rubbed my eyes
yeah happening
then when i will start i'll start
shaking my head going no no no
well you do the kimi much kobe
of course and she wag your finger
up and say no i don't know
audience and then i'll pay eventually hey
individual individual i'll make sure i make
eye contact with every single person the
audience i wagged my finger
every style and every single person dad
when i get hit every single person
i point to the kid and i
go and i started like him
not everyone is like yeah by the
way are you kidding me everyone knows
they're ah they're onto it they're like
oh man he's gonna make good yeah
yeah yeah z committee glued to their
seat but the first person you do
do is probably going to be little
bored in the middle the first person
know they're gonna be looking around to
see like who's doing it you know
okay because i'm not gonna do
an order row by row i'm gonna
do oh randomly but in the order
that you've memorized i will
i mean i'm pretty good memory for
these things i'm ted alone and i
will give everybody the kobe um and
and clap at the end your collaborate
kid oh like gesture towards him like
you should be clapping for him they
don't get mad i'll hack like i'm
getting mad like oh will say my
good i buy like give them this
innovation
right yeah get up there get up
on your feet and then when they're
clapping for him i'll like crap my
heart like something's not quite right
and then topple to right to walk
off but just before i get to
the wings i fall down oh and
then everyone walks out of the theater
while years later i have them i
have them close the curtain and then
oh and thanks on your head a
couple of time that's a dignified they
pull you back here tv
i mean did they ever say he's
not really dad or he's okay no
they make the audience wait for newsday
ever come so they're they're checking the
papers every single day saying is ted
launched dead yet launched it and i
do it every single day and every
so often show him sit alone in
that situation you're not you deadlines you've
been pulling
if i were me i would just
take the plunge yeah yeah have now
lauren do you know who ted lounge
is if you're not no no i
did not you've never seen a little
boat i've seen me know enough to
know that the little pictures exciting and
new yeah i'm gonna google he is
camo bow good where expecting
yea hello dumb ivs her sweet as
reward it takes a little bit of
burma
nah girl seventy it says no and
so doe let us bow soon we'll
be making no row i'm sorry am
i going the way of bo
ood i don't know oh oh funeral
some bruno i don't see the love
boat or anything have you looked at
what did you look up and jazz
funerals in my area i googled re
oh em gee gee what okay how
do you spot l a n g
o i googled l o m g
long ted
now i see now i see you
guide and it was all that there
was about that person wants their obituary
and video of the funeral okay video
wow let's watch the entire una i
know is ted launch still with us
yes yeah you've been put on blast
head launch
arena boys answer for your behaviors i
feel ah it's so odd how the
internet just has these little pockets for
people and that's just like that one
guy just has mad internet yes it's
that's where he goes yeah so who
was his name again tad lounge ted
launch halloween g yeah you know what
about ted waitt l o n g
i was dead deadline
but this guy we've been talking about
my lunge is i actually say it
so i have no idea you get
it can you look at pronunciation of
ted launch i'm just realizing that the
love boat theme was an entire song
with a chorus and a bridge in
several verses yes yeah got the show
has been what forty oh minutes long
yeah but you would be so disappointed
when you didn't hear if and
you would never not hear it exactly
yeah but what do we got yes
what what are we got in pronunciation
we're not finding a lot on that
front but i'm going to zero but
is there like a youtube video that
says pronunciation of ten launch on shed
low lunge lying lounge longhi longhi that
would be one revealed that would be
his name is pronounced longhi we would
have to go back and re-record this
higher episodes like flange lancz yeah lounge
no novel head you will say flies
they phoned us if longs
well ted launch if you're out there
look we apologize but at the same
time you deserved it so yeah you
got that come in but you and
paige davis come by the show sometime
are you you're inviting okay so what's
the order it's paige davis first i
might ted launch to the show as
long as he doesn't take the last
bow there was somebody else that we
said if paige did it then we
would have this person
on y'all and merry hell no we
will guys we're never having mary holland
on tattoos we were showing it must
not have been though it was somebody
else because we we we pledged and
vowed if only i had some sort
of like producer who ever listened to
the show instead of whatever he's doing
now like a chef
even easily yawning literally yawning hey it
was for a big man i don't
blame you
it was for a bit it was
a okay ted launch we need to
take a break i ted we need
to take a break ten flange flange
we're gonna be back and then we're
gonna put someone else on blast and
i'm looking at him right now fuck
that's right how dare how dare he
this judas comes back into our site
yeah we'll tell you who we're talking
oh i think you've guessed it if
you're a real
oh listener yeah okay we'll be right
back
guys we're back and yeah we're looking
at this treacherous fellow this snake the
snake and the round yeah trader who
left us and when he said and
i quote i'm leaving the show goodbye
forever you all suck
if i ever see you again no
i didn't i'm paraphrasing he said i'm
leaving the show goodbye forever you all
suck goodbye with cherry peppers me yes
he actually got on stage when you
came yeah the new oh suh yeah
did people rant graph damn he put
out an elvis jumpsuit yeah it was
a leotard
underneath yeah good yeah i mean it
was quality working on roy scheider all
that jazz guitars any guy yeah it
was good and i wasn't paying attention
to what he was saying at first
because i was like this is a
great note six costume changes yeah it
was a lot of effort um just
be mean which was interesting because i
didn't yeah taking for that guy was
drenched in sweat afterwards
did seven curtain calls yeah he wanted
louder applause each time for himself than
he had before and we gave a
joy because what else could do we're
cowards
anyway he's here in the booth right
now next to chevron are wreaking havoc
in the ribs and saying do it
this way do my ways to his
name if i recall i've tried hard
to forget it is josh joe shoe
yeah
he's here roche exacting like a real
innocent yeah easy he's shrugging like what
else could i do guys twisting a
finger in his dimple like ooh yeah
naturally huh
he's singing the good ship lollipop right
now the good ship lollipop and says
hey champ do okay shop where gun
jobs play all the golden shores back
bay because i've literally gotten ten spam
risk guys while we've been i think
chicago
i think it may be serious alright
here we go hello
hello my name is gregory
his wiener mobile homes maybe when you
remove homes
we bank chasers changed roofs shit could
you make my downstairs my upstairs
yes sir i gotta say i'm intrigued
by this business yeah interesting interesting so
keep an eye you can just switch
floor yeah yeah he just launched right
into his campaign yeah what we do
is
hello all we do is
so it's interesting because he sounds like
he has a legitimate business but it
comes up as spam risk yeah i
wonder how that oh yeah because to
me i was like you should hire
him and honestly if he could flip
the downstairs to the upstairs oh my
god yeah i wouldn't have to walk
up and down stairs anymore you've stopped
to do that to go to places
that you like to know
even think about that yeah but going
upstairs with dow not be such a
chore because you're going downstairs that's true
yeah yeah because they turned the stairs
upside here's what you want happen you
want to you're never going up stairs
so if the house can just keep
switching yeah and you're always just going
like adam gorillaz garage where it's just
like cars keep want you
know this and why is that and
what is it better karolos garage i
tried to kill myself as boys do
all this garage is he one of
those guys that has a bunch of
cars i think so i think he
doesn't like ah as ah rodney dangerfield
said he he's got a warehouse wow
that's rodney going to say yes really
that's from ah you do need to
get a room you do need to
get a warehouse oh i thought it
was his friend wally sparks so many
not sure meet wally sparks what the
fuck was that that's a movie did
you mean meet joe black and they
sorry i'm thinking brad pitt was the
dad in that i'm thinking brady
buy a car eighty times yeah wait
meat while these parts i remember that
title what was it what happened well
we should watch it and livestream it's
entire yeah yeah um everybody go rent
to meet while he's far we're gonna
do a watch along to talk about
it right now if you have to
go to like some russian ah pirate
bay
i'm an american comedy film directed by
peter baldwin whose that does that tell
you everything you do oh burt reynolds
was in it oh boy as well
as debi mazar michael enemies are weller
on instagram her life seems fascinating reading
and full why would you do she
lives in italy most the time she
also lives in new york she uh
um she has italian citizenship shame like
is best friends with madonna and she
has like an amazing life and are
like she's a beautiful family wow completely
impressed by her good for her family
she's a fun follow on instagram because
she posts a lot of like throwbacks
but also current pictures and she really
figured it out yeah move to italy
be friends with madonna yeah
yeah um yeah if you could be
out oh if you if you could
be friends with madonna would you me
yeah i don't like saying that would
mean she was equally interested yeah like
we maybe had fun together and stuff
well i'm not saying that you'd have
fun together because i'm just saying the
opportunities but it might not be fun
yeah
um i would probably try it but
i think i would know enough that
that it wasn't a match yeah yeah
but i'm not i wouldn't close the
door because you just never know you
know what about you guys gee be
best friends with her like what i
don't think so yeah i think we'll
we're a good match you ever die
yeah deep house yeah i think that
she'd be equally interested in all my
podcasts
yeah like equally uninterested yeah right as
uninterested as i am in her music
yeah there you go oh easily i
see yeah yeah and then you just
talk about p people people p p
people
p p p p p people pp
people pay baby p bo um ah
you know she's never changed a diaper
why that always sounded how weird to
me as long as those nannies who
just did it yeah yeah no we're
talking about her own
no she's oh no she just listed
the toilet
she goes through never chase down diaper
because guys wore one i know it's
a riddle i know this came up
earlier on an earlier episode but i
went to the ural toilet over here
and it says you know don't flush
down sanitary what we talked about that
before but then says don't flush down
toilet paper
doesn't it says don't don't flush toilet
paper put it in the bin next
to the toilet does not die and
i looked in the eye your paul's
going to check take a picture while
you will it will certainly last longer
why would it say that's so it
says don't flush toilet paper and so
i looked in the bin next to
the the toilet thinking it was just
going to have like
a ton of shitty toilet paper in
there but no one is following them
no one's following the rules that says
that's disgusting it is discuss companies wants
us to empty that garbage first of
all or pulse gun okay now that
he's got oh shit he's back what
does it say
okay this is really weird scott was
right haha that is weird attention please
do not flow well first of all
three exclamation points a temptation for exclamation
point shut that door oh sorry
i mean that soundproofing master
primary shit
ah yes primary
talk into the mike while you're doing
what you do okay man
he likes everything goddamn pie just bought
back in the room shut the door
do this do that and here's the
one that i got now
yolo
oh the little oval oval lobelia lobelia
okay will love a lethal level
three exclamation points attention space three exclamation
points please do not flush many explanation
exclamation points yeah feminine products comma toilet
paper coma trash or disposable wipes please
ever be on pleasure to happen have
you ever heard the like of
this is this a new rule it's
mad who rolls ling dank dank dank
dank dank jan jeng jeng jeng jeng
jeng jeng j h and jenkins children
so yeah plus your toilet paper flush
your toilet but i you should start
with that over tampon because it's actually
we're used to seeing signs that say
don't flush your tampons yeah lead we're
like guys you can't even flush toys
toilet paper yeah i would say put
the poop in the sink yeah but
to pupa nothing but sometime in this
thing i was in milk i was
think long gone and i was staying
in a bed and breakfast which of
course ozy the worst yeah and um
the toilet in the toilet there was
a sign you were not supposed to
flush toilet paper you had to put
it in this little trash can next
to
and it was frankly the school's oh
god i cannot match a vile horrible
names on my job to clean it
out but i didn't like but it's
your job to open it up and
it's my job to make a dirty
add to it yeah and add to
it god i would just never i
mean i know they hired to add
those arda i was hired to add
two yeah they must have
needed money but i there's i made
two thousand pounds of poo whoa yeah
you would make thousand thousand i was
not eating no going to those that
day just a poop
so stupid so stupid
ah yogurt i'm starting to think that
eating greasy fries and chicken isn't really
like good for you because like my
energy my eyes around
expand on that i don't know it's
like i'm just thinking turning fully away
from the table
i'm gonna take a nap what happens
if we don't look at each other
at all yeah for a while i'd
like that alright okay alright i'll turn
eight we'll see how it feels what
is called a bat and improper the
lights are out when we don't see
each other why is it called a
bad because bats like the dark i'd
assume so that's don't like the dark
they're just able to deal with it
and that's don't knock the door
dark match don't like the dark or
the way they come out during the
day asshole they don't come out during
the day no then there's only maybe
they take a look and think of
na so they don't like the day
or the night they hate both like
their suicide like the day then this
doesn't really i don't like different yeah
i don't like i gotta look at
it rolling zoom again
zuma zuma zuma zoo come on gave
it a try we're going to teach
you to fly huh kimono zoom con
zoom zoom is the asia is the
reason it makes everything that happens the
fetus boy can we talk about wordle
yeah let's talk about it well it
needs to be
this happened several weeks ago and we
just think do it yeah this is
called off the presses okay up to
this segment oh cold off the role
of the presidents oh huh so drunkenly
for more pico
wordle came out and their word and
this happened but this wasn't i wasn't
the word i got no because they
either they'd switched it by the time
that we did our world but the
world that they the word they used
for their world was fetus the word
is on mother's day and everyone mother's
day suh which
is really good very rude really rude
should've been fetal should have been fetal
or should have been in mama my
mama with two m's in the middle
m o m a m m a
is what it should have been making
our social art some ah yes why
would have been
anything anything other word fetus on the
feet mother's day yes o e t
u s thesis wow
what absolutely dead mother's day do you
want to be thinking about your kids
as fetuses oh you wanna you wanna
be like trout in the run-up to
do that we're no one no one
wants a thing that word you would
want to be near you were shine
a little shy more no more like
shame or shine mr bertel or whatever
his name is who create josh ward
josh bertel massage oh yeah who's down
down shamed of yourself shined also paint
your picture i would really love it
if he were to billy bragg
x if he were to and if
you were to donate everything he's made
off in world to charity because of
notice to a fetus he should donate
to a fetus to one particular food
was little i feel it should be
like a charlie chocolate factory thing you
know mo it's like one lucky fetus
get something chameleon portals and gets to
come to his world factories just use
office
ooh oh so pie to the jaw
hey sky was gone but so what's
wrong way you should know some guys
i don't know what's wrong and you
guys were doing billy bragg must i
paint you a picture i didn't know
that song and how sad i was
i felt left out and i felt
like gosh
what if i never hear another song
again wow ooh what chuck yeah wally
shitty lol i didn't hear that one
maybe i'll never hear another way i
got into the cold off the presses
r e wordle okay yeah um the
word today as of this recording was
already did you do it yeah yeah
yeah yeah right yeah i
did you didn't get it i mean
editing i did not get the word
sad for yeah really i was so
annoyingly sad yeah it was just kind
of like wow can't kill you in
deep depression i can get through this
day week month year and i think
you've seen me sir
yeah but the word was slung switch
i tried i got first i got
sell try to lose sell words then
i've got so you tried a bunch
i sell you words what so like
what did you try slot i'll show
you yes luck yeah he's strictly a
lady chaplin i mean guess what you
put a slurp oh no because i
missed the the
our was already gone okay sweet what's
yes sla yeah i sell you alright
started with smear boy then i went
to slick slick slick then went this
way loop star wheel stop so you
gotta go slower paul what are the
lat so what are the last slow
three what's the next slide the first
letter like sweep john b's kind of
oh well what letter because you've got
a couple letters right in the next
line and sell you so i think
you put sluice slow my god fly
home and i couldn't figure out what
it was slump no no because okay
slow slung sly come slung no
yeah for
you didn't get slunk because you didn't
get because you didn't get slunk how
about cars also you don't think i
to be fair i did not see
that word like i didn't see it
in the letters that i have other
words i can't even think because you
don't think of past tense words squirrel
lot s l news flush no blunt
no slim design in there but what
i might have guessed it what was
written here the words i do sla
slub slob slob in their slugs slots
or uvb really guys how about slugs
slugs is not in there because they
don't deploy they don't nobody thought maybe
you were just trying something no never
never tried plural
okay um what did you try my
first guess was slush then it was
like i don't know if slub word
is a word wasn't the answer slush
and then i write i put in
slough s l u f f slough
yeah yeah i when i hear that
word i think of s l o
u g a g two but accepted
you
accepted it that's it's marital it's crazy
mash wordle
oh gosh you you had paul and
hello
and he
i put in hello didn't get it
to work
that's really wrong that's wrong that and
now meanwhile we got it in my
three or four i got in five
i think because i put slunk first
yeah it's only my second batch i
was really confused i put slunk than
i was looking at i'm going why
isn't it said good job y hey
hey phone and you start hitting your
phone and it was like actually you
can give him like what and then
i was like
what advantage my low slung
yeah gabby slurs slung i don't i
i always associated with low slung and
so i don't like like balls yeah
like some balls do you mean like
what what are the shooters he got
them low slung balls shooter sacks
shutterstock shutterstock sort of turned me god
some la oh yes he got but
that's what came some high tier days
we know and it's tell me so
wet in the middle
say that the song the time huh
yeah these are the songs you doing
the battleship in the video ah yeah
yeah the stage yeah it was a
battleship with it with like obese talking
about yeah with a g string g
string yeah those atlas sharpies yeah my
godson blows long balls new address
yea his dad tommy
say it to say hazel no i
agree
yeah but to be low
kidney damage but the paper don't go
it's right yeah wow song
into the tremor so now should be
forcing the yeah anyone walking if you
need to go to the bathroom and
then sing the song and then point
down the hallway
with this person it's oh she's seeing
i got some low slung balls first
okay when you're thinking wow shit she's
gonna get the bathroom stole my grandma
may start to ask and say sure
question reception says finger keep singing
ooh back reach la bo
the verses are there
it's like the love boat oh my
god anxiety yeah oh my gosh alright
we have to take a break we'll
be right back alright but
and we're back we are back we
got we sang that song five hundred
times got it out of our system
we're definitely not going to sing it
again right now i no i'm not
seeing that again i'm sure it's affected
it how it was yeah it was
beautiful it was stunning the last time
we checked we did it it was
incredible and people
so from all the other offices came
all the other shows you've ever been
on airwolf yeah showed up to listen
to it from all other offices so
now it was up to listen every
show that's it was throwing shade it
was ah every show that's ever been
on it was the one where people
called in on the phone
number
it's beautiful just left messages here people
oh my god they all came and
they were crying they were crying and
they loved it so much and they
were really happy they loved it you
have found and lost and found again
they loved us they loved eyes anyway
that's all over that's done now and
we're never gonna sing it again i
know i know we are gonna do
we're gonna play three char yeah and
let's before we play the three two
though not the prayer again no no
to satan yeah no no no no
he knows okay we gotta talk about
his agree
the thing about satan is that you
don't have to pray to him all
the time yeah yeah he's good guys
i'm the guy you don't have to
break these opposite everything he unders like
please don't pray to me yeah yeah
no we gotta talk about the other
guy who's like satan the b islam
k p o fucking k p k
p okay
hey katie frankly i'm katie frankly zoe's
name yep your ball frankly mister frankly
i am appalled ah that we have
begged you nicely but some people here
to just your three teacher for us
and our entreaties fallen upon deaf ears
it seemed because we have not heard
a word from
nothing now have we typed all of
these before he ever would have heard
these instructions yes but that's material the
point is we have not heard from
have not heard from k p early-on
or her notes a guy we we
yeah we knew is cpy frankly if
you frankly so a woman frankly keep
the hotdog and our friend i p
freely as well
if you haven't heard my p freely
i p loosely you know in any
case so loose new business by you
know the next time
the next time we we do an
episode he may have heard i hope
at this but maybe not who knows
by the time we record again
god k p i hope we hear
from you please know mr reflects poorly
on you yep not only not enough
totally yeah that's great now we're good
okay so we're gonna play ah game
it's called hit the post right yeah
we played it a couple of times
it's really fun it's called radio d
j on his first day yes and
now what we each have our phones
and we
i have songs in the phones yeah
and we're going to whichever flows with
soldiers and those we typically songs and
the fun definitely songs definitely songs so
ah like for instance i'm hooked up
to the dongle right now and i'm
gonna play a song and then lauren
who's never heard this song before maybe
she has who knows yeah is going
to try to guess when the
singer starts singing on it and is
going to try to act like a
radio deejay talk until literally a millisecond
before the singer starts singing and we'll
see how close we can get to
it but okay it has to be
literally millisecond yeah and we're going to
go clockwise right so yeah okay so
this is i'm gonna play the song
and this is for lauren and this
is a song and
i'm gonna play this for lorin and
this is a song i'm gonna play
this for laura okay here we go
everybody listen up it's the big day
prom is tomorrow and we want everyone
to grab their best dress and their
best texting or whatever you're gonna wear
to feel so amazing so you can
dance with your partner we got to
dance to prom with a limousine and
a free hot dog machine and shoots
him out you grab me your mouth
they have to stream down your throat
doesn't count everybody listen up let's do
a call
umm ahmed almost not bad actually where
you went longer than i thought you
were going to be and i was
like ooh she's gonna talk over but
now and he started singing a little
bit to too late i think i
was pretty good that's pretty good yeah
that was human tetris okay can i
add that god was human tetris yes
man i'm gonna hook it up
and this is what's going to happen
it's always got shut down and go
halls turn alright already paul yeah i'm
ready i'm paul in in three two
one just reminder out there there is
a lot of traffic right now but
it is not on the highways it
is just on the surface streets so
why don't you get out and walk
to work today we are going to
be
having our contest again that contest is
to have my job i'm against it
but what can i do
elton john and dua lipa signal old
hard it's a combo mashup of rocket
man and i think it's gonna be
a long long time i think it's
him returning to do to get a
number one hit out of this and
i love it it must be number
one
and then really rocket man is a
part of this yeah we think it's
gonna be i know a rocket guy
do you know harlan williams
ah yes be oh i see but
then she sing it yeah she she
admitted oh my god he admitted she
thinks it's
alright
well we can't just listen to this
song forever anyway i know you love
alright may i have the dongle yeah
my i have chirped don't know actually
a good throw but some would say
it was perfectly so i'd say it
was perfect alright scott are you ready
for the shit
growing up yeah i don't think you're
ready for this year we go yep
hey guys i'm back here at work
after my fifth time having coven i'm
back on the air and i of
course ah had three limbs amputated i'll
let you guess which one i begged
them to let me keep yeah that's
right it's the right arm it's what
i use all the time to write
my name on checks
and those oh i got sucked out
oh bitter dissapointment i thought there would
be rather more going to get okay
alright here we go this is i'm
gonna play for lauren
i forgot where i was because i
was thinking about how my girlfriend just
broke up with me i had a
rough night you know we ah well
we we made sweet passionate love but
in the morning so she's in love
with somebody else who you wanna know
my landlord if anyone has a story
worse than this please call because i'm
feeling rough today
a let's hear it on the lines
it's one two three four five six
seven eight nine that's the number we
got today my scary amador facetious let's
go alright people come on call i'm
waiting for the lines of layout and
they're not letting up i see dead
air here you know it's it's all
the lines are now you know you're
telling me that i had the worst
breakup story in the history of all
somebody call it with the word story
in mind
ah there we go there we go
huh that was the scorpions with tease
me please me that was of course
this scorpion with cheese me please alright
lauren's gonna play a song for paul
yell okay dong dong dong dong da
da da da da
a no nine lo li
paul oh shit back it up okay
i was like i was looking for
exactly for scott okay start over okay
i'll start over at home i haven't
saw my new song because there's no
telling what's happening right now because yeah
you have too much information yeah too
much matter
okay everybody we hope you are in
love and loving someone right now we
hope you're holding them in your arms
and they are holding you and putting
their face in your neck
so you watch
as good as you want to use
a dongle please wait around bouncing on
banks don't lend them money do you
have to give him that thing oh
i'm sorry i'm not saying give them
that fact that st paul's gonna play
something for me
and same thing i told you that
level one again i'm amazed at the
amount of sound effects
library says yeah it's just happened
i don't think i've once out effected
my you have ward sound effect in
in the middle of a song and
everybody has one alright you ready yep
here we go
hey guys anyone watched tv last night
i know i did i saw a
show about a vampire who made love
to aware wolf and boy the hair
went everywhere and they had a little
baby who had the biggest things i
ever saw and and i've seen some
things if you know what i mean
i used to go down to the
reptile house
out at the zoo and i used
to check out all of the boa
constrictors and they used to squeeze everyone
in my family all my family are
dead because they win too close into
the cage and they all got squeezed
by all of the snakes and then
she thought there was one day and
you do that stuff i know never
know i was psyched out into thinking
there was one more let's see one
more okay this game is always fun
bow but nobody but allows bringing me
graham greene dunk ah right um this
is for lower
erin and ah i am playing the
song for lauren and here we go
well i've done it again ah yes
i did enter into the company's sweepstakes
and i won i know it's illegal
but i did win the prize and
i'm driving home and a fresh maserati
they have to catch me on the
streets if they want it back i
love you america and the cyst
items we've put in device this is
my favorite country you have to be
fired somebody say one last thing
i hate my boss he's a tool
a prick i'm doing it
oh
ah didn't realize you could just say
dude you dude you do
soon to be alone i was dallas
hall
and that was the de la soul
that was dallas so i'm gonna i'm
gonna lasso tissue okay
no one knows what that means the
dongle ah line went around the tissue
bago
gonna lasso a tissue i'm ready but
hey everyone we know that today was
a sad tragic day but we don't
have guinea pigs anymore and that's good
because they frankly were cluttering the place
out and buy the place i mean
planet earth guinea pigs so long we
won't miss you anyway if you're a
kid and you had a pet you
don't anymore so
time to grow up and tell your
mom i said hi
yeah yes no that's what i call
hitting the post yes and that was
lights out words gone by bombay bicycle
club bbc wow can i hit one
i wonder
i think you can i think you
can try and find goodwin here for
trying to find a job find a
non sound effects exactly what's this one
called boiling
wow door slam is that a song
it would be funny if ah if
an artist or a band put out
an album where all the song titles
were they look like it's out of
absolutely absolutely
woman screaming or actually this is more
like maurizio woman screaming man fainting all
right um
yep i don't know what's going to
happen here alright let me go and
here we go
hey everyone we all know what this
trump means it's time for me to
tell you about my tragic tragic story
that happened to me when i was
but five years old that's right everyone
thought i'd drowned in a pool but
instead it was a big vat of
vaseline that's right i was slimy all
over
if everyone thought i was dead they
pulled me out of there i was
a slippery is anything you would ever
see in your life i would just
wow was that the opposite for this
is the song called for doomed men
right out it's from the bone tomahawk
sound she's like yeah you love bone
tomahawk so much you got the soundtrack
because the song there's a song at
the end that tells the story of
the movie it's so fucking right
for doomed men right out
oh well that was fun while we
did it i love that game that
was hit in the boats yeah was
great toes jamming whittam i hope you
all had a good time listening to
us because we're funny and sweet yes
well that's our show thanks for listening
if you want to hear ad-free versions
of freedom you can go to stitcher
premium or comedy bang bang world dot
com
tom and vb world dot com cbp
world dot com or comedy bang bang
world dot com and if you want
to call us and we don't know
why you would but please ah what
was it la la la input ty
law input top la la la la
input of your own birds oh is
bud
um and write to us somewhere three
m usa gmail dot com when instagram
instagram and twitter we love you and
thank for listening you and goodbye goodbye
uh