three
was that one
oh threw up during the boom so
sorry sorry it's time sweet urge that
was not oh you purchased nine times
first time oh it's all davy perch
i see i feel we misunderstood the
assignment
hi everyone welcome to freedom oh my
god hi everyone i'm like yeah oh
my god sometimes i can't remember if
something is a thought that i've had
or something i saw on twitter
i feel like
let's hold on his ticket no let's
not need to you're not sure if
it's a thought you had or something
you saw on twitter's but i can't
remember did i texas to somebody as
a joke or did i see this
on twitter or did i tweet it
am i drill
i don't get tino never mind what
does that from cars yeah yeah yeah
from cars the character drillbit taylor cars
huh
who's famously on twitter that's right
drill
i'm just here for you
you're so you're so online and you
don't get it yeah sometimes i don't
get stuff i got to say when
you had your baby i expected to
never hear from you again and you
are constantly texting
i'm very available when does anything with
people have babies they don't text anymore
just on my phone all day i
would imagine you would have like retreated
from the world a little bit but
instead we thought we'd get a break
as what we're saying oh my god
um i feel like i retreated in
a different way than that who tell
us just physically i feel like i
were rich you go
smaller um i hope that's to continue
but i don't mean in the old
bell department the bell bell bell my
god you mean you've proceeded like your
gums yes much like my gums have
receded and anyways whatever here's i just
wanted to say i feel like the
only thing i want to say was
that
i can't remember what tweeted this or
not is that company like if you
work if you are a social media
person for a company at this point
oh to be at some point you
have to do is go my understood
the assignment and posts like a picture
of someone in the product you're selling
and then that's it huh wait but
i guess i don't even know what
the original thing you don't assume
did the assignment you know what understand
the assignment is is at ah is
that a meme of some sort through
the taylor says it in cars oh
okay i misunderstood the exam that's made
her oh i'm sorry who's drillbit taylor
and corey taylor sells like this wow
what's all the boldly allowable old i've
already sent like this ah misunderstood the
i would know
that's famously paul newman from giant what
ever he played the same character in
cars yeah usually he was a giant
and giant yeah he's a giant car
and car giant what is scariest movie
i've ever seen that giant shows up
oh my god i would love to
see paul newman and giant battle the
attack of the fifty foot woman why
wasn't he an iron giant
this is good you know what point
i'll say you know james dean was
giant right yeah but it wasn't paul
newman no yeah he should have been
here you should have been though will
you agree with me on that i
will agree with you on that and
hud was a giant so he should've
been in there what's that movie with
the big white thing also cars have
hoods speak big hero six zero zero
six yeah
absolutely big hero six never even big
hero six can you imagine and if
you're wanting something hero sandgren tokyo biggie
who is a sandwich this is well
hell but right now i wouldn't even
need to say hero so so much
arsenic before the show i'm high so
a euro sandwich beginning hero is endemic
haha like why are we all talking
at the same time because this is
freedom oh right now what i'm paul
i'm lauren i'm scott hi welcome to
another episode thanks for i hope you
had a lovely thanks for i hope
you had a lovely yep
yeah it's not a big thanks to
everyone who asks you have a lovely
oh my god i never even thanked
them for i was gonna say thank
you for listening i hope you had
a lovely holiday and you interrupted me
and you can hire anyone to see
other person says oh they reckon hold
on wait oh huh you can drop
oh my
oh yeah
this is like a curse like oh
sexy genre that's certainly a funny way
to be
yeah just say half of theirs
ah this is good
it's good oh my god is what
you will hope everyone had a happy
thanksgiving yeah thank you for listening to
us on thanksgiving hope you had a
nice holiday we're back in the flower
patch yeah oh i liked that i
liked that um what are you guys
doing for thanksgiving where what did we
do because it's over
we're doing two days we're doing a
two-day celebration that's so mao it's like
going to disneyland and then california adventure
right next door is that what you're
doing yes okay are you doing oh
fun i've been thinking i want to
go to disneyland not right now what's
the best day to go what's the
day that nobody wants to go well
here's a christmas right now and so
bad because i feel like everything's different
with the pandemic there's all these different
rules have you tried to go with
kai or anything no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no okay well
what do you know why having to
oh oh well my
hey funnier so i tried to get
on the bit very quickly before they
go onto their own cause
anyway
ah so my my sister's a nurse
and she oh nurse she is like
some people say to her when this
year it's true she sometimes has to
work on the actual holiday but she
gets the next day off so like
hey and my parents are coming holiday
from blackfriday yes she gets black friday
off so
you can celebrate black friday yes exactly
but she she gets that day also
they're coming on friday so so we
had nothing to do on thursday so
we're going to get together with well
yeah we're gonna get together with a
friend so you can do these grand
because you go to see great now
and they're drilling speed drill
are you are going to get together
with a little bit we're gonna get
together with i realize i was my
my mouth was not working ah you
were gonna say ariana grande i thought
it was someone special or were getting
together as frankie and area on a
gras day wow the brother and sister
duo we all know and love i
didn't know about this brother he was
on big brother did not see it
keys
the brother from big brother celeb big
brother i would imagine yeah yeah we
became a celeb no no he was
on celeb by her was he i
don't know about big brother i don't
know either i don't know i i
feel like i never got into that
show but i have seen it on
tv when in london where i feel
like they have it on like a
constant sri
and it's always on which is cooler
yeah me slightly off either i also
got in you can watch that here
in sta concentrate when i was in
london years ago working there i got
into their version of last comic standing
which is so much bleaker than why
is it so bleak they were standing
in a house together right and people
were just getting drunk and depressed
there are a lot of like drunk
late-night talk oh that's bad like in
this fake backyard oh it was really
yeah if you hear noise in the
background it's because there's a monster here
yeah we're trying to kill it while
we do the show yeah it's the
final battle yeah and then after this
we win yeah
yeah and then morning boss what do
you monster when we when we when
the credits of the video game that's
such a bad price it truly is
they should give you back the video
game i've never come close to being
a video game and i don't care
what video game have you most enjoy
in your love
um mario kart do do do do
do it yeah of course and when
i went you little i was no
i've never like beaten like i play
i don't even know what you've to
do like play every level and then
never level and beat every level i'm
not as familiar with mario as well
and is mario kart game that you
exclusively play with other people know you
played alone himself yeah um but when
it was needed
yourself i'm hearing bus you can play
it alone and you can play by
yourself you can play by yourself are
you also without other people you could
do it solo life is there
um but anyways when i was little
i was really good at bowser's castle
and i could beat my brothers friends
at the oscars wow no wow now
your brother famously older than you so
you're talking about older boys yeah or
maybe they would let me oh congress
ooh i don't know can we get
i want confirmation on this i'll
i'll get into that yeah we need
him to tell us if it was
real or fake we'll see if he
even remembers that he'll reveal special to
me he'll remember yeah he'll we'll find
out we'll find browser is he mario
adjacent but oh you don't know about
mario you don't know any of the
lore patches p i know so what's
happening she could take it to gospel
she didn't
someone's was to do nasty stuff do
they gotta get it out with the
flagpole just in time i know ah
mario and the donkey kong world from
the video game donkey kong but i
know very little about so it's interesting
you know about um urkel from when
he was on family
the matter yes but i know about
urkel from when he was on
so paul knows him from the most
famous show
yeah it was it yeah no i
know i don't recount was the original
donkey kong's before mario yeah memorial comes
from i need to eat a hat
because you told someone no way was
mario from donkey kong why just why
would i set that right now you
only you didn't occur to me i
mean i feel like i did is
what i'm saying yeah he's jumping barrels
i mean i know but i thought
he was you know marrying monkey up
on top of the building
yeah he was guy they could try
caliber action if i were to now
think through my boy beard i would
think oh yeah he was in that
documentary about that guy who played video
games that's right king of com and
that was before mario do you know
i saw the the villain of that
documentary one time yeah who was in
san diego billy something i feel like
i saw it recently the coin
coin billy coin
so the villain ulster a video games
just fill oh okay i love you
is the villain of the documentary billy
sobering right what the fuck is his
name but he was a coin in
your mind no because he had coins
because yeah yeah going play okay you
know billy the kid didn't have kids
in his holes
yeah we know we know sites like
wow now when the urine wow they're
distracted then he pulls out a gun
and kills right and i'd be cool
um i was doing a show it
was comecon adjacent in san diego at
dick's flowers or you're doing a show
at dick's last resort me roll no
else
why it was brutal why would who
i asked you to know and why
did you accept i did not know
because you don't know what it was
like a bar it's a choice to
disgusting when replying me like the theme
is the beach is yes but also
the theater it's like one of those
places where they're rude to you in
a funny way read to you and
they throw toilet paper
everywhere so there's just toilet paper all
over the floor and i didn't know
maybe they weren't doing that this time
they were like literally just throw it
across all the waiters like throw it
across the room that's so it's like
i that and have it be like
spiraling it's so great did you do
the bob odenkirk used to work at
idea ethics agenda i remember going to
antibiotics i'm sure i've told the nicest
guy in the world acting name to
pee
people i'm sure i totally different than
everybody else
i don't want to be a jerk
but i took the manager i think
it was really being mean that one
really hurt he says something cutting it's
definitely going right to my core hey
buddy this is just bullshit what you're
doing
i'm searching back through but he would
be at genetics like looking at the
tv when snell would be on to
see if any of his jokes got
in really yep
wow that's really cool it is cool
it's like a movie moment like glenn
do you ever like that's my joke
and then someone's like table five just
threw up goddamn tired
the whole table
or the table itself will be rude
to them about it
so i was doing the show and
then he walked in who the weight
who oh yeah really didn't build really
the coin billy mit billy mitchell and
that show that guy remember him of
course he's wearing an american flag really
long black hair and black beard in
case you can't remember i made the
audience observe a moment of silence for
him what he was what he passed
by did he wow lose her duty
when i can't remember
he was the guy who supposedly allegedly
cheated or no the the main guy
cheat i think the main guy cheated
right i'm gonna say hey lee da
blurry
is that bill cosby correcting someone about
his crimes allegedly free then
yeah by the way michael jackson news
or always are no news that guy
from the january six yeah that's true
it was was found out because of
his very specific michael jackson tour jack
oh yeah he wore i said i
am over like your that suka you
guys i tell you my brush with
michael jackson fame know that happens in
the brain with michael jackson know my
my brain yeah it has
opened bream brush with a foreign i'm
not stupid that you called her more
right
no it was able to call you
moron no they didn't willing
so what happened was and i think
this was at least a year if
not two years ago paris jackson tweeted
she took a snap check but a
filter remember the filter that could make
you a woman man and child baby
a guided to you oh yeah oh
yeah yeah remember i moved baby
yeah she was using that with her
boyfriend and then tagged to the picture
of him as a woman and said
it'll take me she wrote she tagged
me whoa she tagged me she wrote
my name whoa and that was really
big it was big moment that's what
people call you a moron nope
it makes things stories together so do
you think michael jackson ever thought that
would happen i think when franklin jackson
died one of the things he was
hoping what happened was that paris are
gonna boyfriend huh they always use a
soft yet there's fire hell he was
like hey they would snap chat filter
and then
i'm paris boyfriend and then he would
look like lauren laccase and at the
time i was i was a mere
babysitter in new york city when he
died i remember where i was walking
like a week before you and movies
yeah a couple of weeks yeah but
i was walking on the street my
friends are subjects and die mike oh
i think i got gotta go out
at a concert the bird and the
bee
be an afternoon concert if you can
believe it in the young field time
when i was walking down the street
yeah sure you are no wow i
don't at an arbitrary him and and
i remember arbitrage arbitrage yeah what arboretum
arboretum arboretum really my burrito burrito burrito
come on over
identity six arboretum was open to the
public no i was there with cool
op sister and ah in another desperate
attempt to make her like me of
like hey this is a this is
a cool fun thing to do right
oh my gosh she's staying with us
this month by the way she's still
just like you no no she likes
me she's she's she's like almost thirteen
year old dork your thing it's
cause i wanna you wanna go you
wanna go see board in the be
in the middle of the day and
i remember in the bean there we
go ah now i remember we went
to we went to see conan on
the tonight show because oh really hey
it happened for her i lived over
there and just meeting her because the
price is right we're gonna go to
disneyland and she's like i don't like
new let's
the walk yeah we so we walked
there from my place which is not
that far i would say a mile
and she was so upset with how
far it was and and i asked
her about it the other day i'm
like hey remember that time that i
took you to the conan o'brien's tonight
show and you complained and were upset
with me the whole time and she
goes
it's a far not letting it go
and the musical guest was burden the
music and you're like who was gonna
see part of the beacon that code
and now with your favourite i feel
like was natasha on it because natasha
was on the jay leno tonight show
when i went and i think she
was on the conan tonight show when
i went natasha lucero yes yes from
boris fame
why are you always saying natasha is
only famous because of a man because
i can't think of her last name
or they marry him enough no no
that's that's why we have made a
new bullwinkle rovers i made a bilingual
new bullwinkle they made a bowling ball
a new bully did with the robert
de niro ah he was like music
my
name's boris to see who's who's all
doing facial robert jager but this worlds
i mean that's cool do my lys
bullwinkle when i was little like two
unless you want to have sex with
it
he was sexy fuckin weird yeah i'm
over body he was he had a
great body he was very he was
a butter face
also those handlers they're not doing me
any favors too big i like that
sometimes it can be too big okay
if so if size matters it does
it's not the emotion of the antlers
he um i liked that show because
it felt very like it was geared
at grownups as well
a lot about it i didn't understand
yeah sure and that's that's how i
felt when i watched this but it's
good when you're younger grownups oh yeah
i think you like the six-year-old sure
that the piano i've never seen the
piano what's that about a man who
can't speak but plays the piano it's
about a woman who can't speak yet
sexist
yes the piano player was a woman
the logic puzzle and that's why everyone
loved the movie you can thereby learn
a lesson about myself hey yeah but
you get to see harvey cartel naked
in totally nude and holly hunter welcome
what are they doing just looking at
each other it's at separate times okay
yeah yeah and how old was harvey
chi tell when this took you seemed
a million
eight years old that he was probably
thirty five technically yeah he might be
forty now for all i know and
didn't you see him nude in the
in the bad lieutenant was already jerked
off the girls at a car absolutely
the hell not the good lieutenant erling
he had like one year where he
was just like if i ain't newday
dune gonna get knew it was his
idea every
a single time what am i going
to do if it ain't nude i
doing it
a nude a dude
if i lay naked i'm not using
that getting a single frame me
why wasn't he naked in cicero why
was it a little but the habit
on his dick i heard that they
were all nude under the habits ah
so how do you wear clothes under
their righty so freeing all nother noon
how i would like to wear dresses
what about none stands for nude
under
nice
those close ones delphi got their real
squeaker should to enter the top of
my head i've never worn address i
have worn a kilt which is very
comfortable yeah it's comfortable right yeah you
know what i'm gonna wear for dinner
what's better gene search yeah yeah oh
yeah what's better jeans or dress jeans
or dresses what would
and you have experienced at this point
will because this economy because i am
under biden's america has i'm still recovering
from having a baby i haven't really
worn jeans in a very long time
so i kind of like to wear
just because you don't you don't wear
baggy jeans you anyway virginia georgian bay
but i mean none of my old
jeans fit but i got
some new genes and they do fit
but i haven't worn them yet that's
just my my girl these eyes right
but i have been wanting a of
dresses like this whole past year from
being pregnant so i'm excited to to
find top doing it because you like
to wear jeans better i prefer jeans
and a t-shirt as my sort of
outfit but just has
hasn't been possible without sharm boy i'm
such a guy would you rather wear
shorts than jewelry a backwards baseball cap
and would rather wear jeans than shorts
but i like shorts but yeah why
what's what's preferable about jeans to shorts
yeah we need less body showing to
whom the public although shy
it's been you know has to be
pretty hot i'm saying around the house
or on a house somewhere and swats
babe yeah ma'am so you're you're just
sweats really no one jeans at home
virginia i wear what we call what
we call soft clothes which is not
necessarily it could be switched like anything
made it fell java's yeah we were
puppets a lot of times
i was talking yesterday puppets but make
them close i was getting my haircut
yesterday and i was talking to we
were talking about christmas presents and and
um my friend said you know it's
it's she has two boys your friend
cuts your hair yes she said you
weren't getting a haircut with a friend
no no no she she was
yeah i consider her to be a
friend they get the same hair not
a pee on yeah forced to tunnel
i don't always go to the same
person right i have the same person
so she was saying it's very difficult
to shop for her boys as they
get older because they get more and
more specific and i was saying like
i like to shut from a but
i feel like that's easier in some
ways because you're like oh they like
this this
this well i just and i said
i said i remembered one year in
particular where i got a present where
if it had been one year earlier
i would have been happy but i
was like upset with not upset with
it but it was a ventriloquist dummy
and i think i was like fourteen
eight and it was like yeah one
year earlier would have been good when
you please tell me what the dummy
was
like jerry mahoney was charlie mccarthy what
was it was not charlie mccarthy what
what is already known quantity no i
think it was known but not one
of the famous ones but jerry mahoney
was the was eventual acquisto mean you
will have paul winchell who also are
josh could develop an artificial show me
a picture oh interest he he he
worked on developing artificial
arts and he also did ventriloquism first
the special msm
but he would do a voice for
the heart of course he put it
in he is a dummy heart yeah
okay alright like but i just led
this by the way led her to
saying oh my god i had a
ventriloquist dummy and i got really good
at ventriloquism and she hadn't thought about
it since that and she's like oh
my god this is all rushing back
to me
i got really good adventure ventriloquism and
i like did it for a year
and then i have as i was
like have you told your family about
this have you told your kids and
your wife and she's like no i
have not even thought of it since
then what did she try to do
it nah well i said next time
she called yeah mom i'm gonna need
her to brush up on it yeah
you'll bring
your tummy yeah i think it was
jerry mahoney yeah i think it maybe
it was it was no calm smiths
when i tell a story not sure
yes tell when i was home one
storied my godmothers your one story we
see i'll get one for the sour
yeah well but she got when i
was in second grade she got me
a and she was much older woman
she got me am much much older
than me
lisa was nine she got me a
windbreaker style jumpsuit with aladdin on it
and i was so upset and then
i had to go to the bathroom
disney on yeah because it seemed like
for babies or what yeah we got
a boy on it no it was
just dorky it was not cool however
i would wear that now
now you are ny
nine doesn't seem too old for that
am i wrong it's not completely off
like i'm sure she went to coles
and was just like in the section
and it feels like doing stuff sure
and then i was like humiliate i
remember going into the bathroom and having
to put it on
my sister one year got me of
like a full outfit of like i
guess how she thought she should dress
oh wow like as an adult yeah
i like i was like a writer
early twenties but that miters jack what
are you like what she was wishy
thinking oh he'll really appreciate like free
clothes it's like as a gift like
maybe yeah she probably yeah probably yeah
she got me it was the eighty
sep i don't think i was in
my twenties yet i was probably still
living at home and it was like
at the time this was a popular
thing like fabric that would have it
would be like flicked like to like
so yeah tweedy sort of flecked with
you know whatever that was the pants
back then it was like a school
i you know what i would wear
those now yeah if i had them
yeah um then it was what we're
getting uva chris i'm getting new latin
windbreaker you're getting flicked pants like it
was like connect shirt and get over
drilling and then a crew neck sweater
of like a like a real ski
lodge kind of pattern sounds good it
wasn't
good but honestly it's a great outfit
now now you should watch it i
don't watch it i don't mean you
should watch it wow i don't like
my crazy oh you don't you don't
put a button down through a crewneck
no i don't like i like i
like i love hard again okay okay
fair enough fair enough i'm just giving
you guys hints because christmas is coming
is so don't get him a crew
neck everyone i once everyone i hate
shopping for presents for anyone but um
right well that's what cool up gives
you a list as we know from
address harsh oh did she mention this
on adguard oh my god there she
said about you on that
yeah don't stop to this
i remember one mother's day when my
dad was like you've gotta go get
your mom mother's day yes davao
but so yeah wait what i wasn't
listening he was my my dad was
like yeah oh wasn't listening you should
really go get your mom a present
from other day and i was like
okay and i didn't know what to
get so how old are you twenty
eighteen or something like that um so
and nothing was open because he was
a son
today so i ended up going to
like the gas station and just like
going like oh my okay what is
here that i could buy so it
was like here's a gallon of gas
ma it was like i would be
good
actually i'm going to use it no
i would take that but it was
like you know those ah coca-cola cozies
yeah you know like they were really
beer cozies probably is but like oh
your mom this will keep your drink
cool it's like stuff i obviously got
it's like yes station city rapid it's
like a comparably not i'm horrible at
writing
to the point where now they would
much rather not even wrapping gifts i
even know you cannot wrap a gift
well it i could if i took
the time but it's such a waste
of time i just hate you think
it's likely probably be the best at
it you know what you're you'd be
the best if you got your future
tripping thinking about the the wrapping being
torn i know that sounds so you're
not
putting your focus into god that's sad
it's sad sad man
you make me sad just live in
the moment and to give them a
beautiful gift you know what my uncle
is a fantastic gift wrapper it's actually
the point of most of the gifts
is how beautifully ornately rasters groups like
her of his own socks in there
but look but it's always the presentation
is amazing you i am a decent
rapper and i used to when i
grew up i was i would help
my mom route presence and split a
finger for the bow and spit some
bars yeah presence of the presidency presence
though i like
chevy down so hard she just but
yeah yeah yeah i was wrapping christmas
gifts last night just oh
for my baby i had she doesn't
know she doesn't she's even know the
euro thing i know that jesus i
know i'm boring i just have to
save her some presence so that she
has him under her own tree and
then that's will she get and we're
going to tradition will she get jealous
that it's a different baby's birthday uh
um yeah i don't know if i'm
gonna tell her yeah but don't tell
her budget what she'd go her entire
life without ever hearing about jesus probably
accept someone like good honey except for
your step two i stub my toe
jesus got domains
i have guys i have a new
coven dough i've covered too
put so much ice coven
it's a job as hell
cavuto is the thing aaron rodgers supposedly
has shot up fulfill like his balls
getting big no no it's literally your
toe it's a symptom of of it's
like a long-term symptom of coven once
you're telling her toe swells up in
your toe like really hurts and it
hurts to wear shoes no that's balls
nazi oh no so that's the vaccine
i apologize yeah that's if you you're
also hoping to get back home and
your toe gets big yeah either way
okay where are you exactly
fred flintstone over here
paul can you wrap gifts i think
that i'm very good at it until
i do it and then it's never
as like the wrapping is never as
snug as i would like here's what
you gotta do as a bug in
a row you push you you've got
everything you put the paper down pattern
side towards the cart put paper down
the present
yeah already do that oh shit fold
the paper over but then yeah marie
it crease it along the yeah no
shit he doesn't know this you know
about the crease that keeps it from
flopping you crease it very tightly then
you tape a piece of the tape
and the piece of the vapor to
the president i've done them then it
keeps it really taught then you get
to look at the corner to go
really tight and you
usually take them i tried to squeeze
method it's gonna work i'll try it
because i thought that's the only god
was coming roast me until he realised
it was actually a good tip classic
scott roasted really realised paul didn't know
i'm sure listeners didn't know when christmas
and hanukkah are coming up and news
is getting fat the jewish goose is
getting fat too yeah actually it's already
hanukkah
jews hat
i won't say what my brother and
his family you smack yes i sent
oh that's happening with everyone's ears it's
just scott i think he's hearing a
lot of things i'm not saying i
sent them a big blue christmas tree
with hanukkah ornaments whoa and it should
be getting there but like at least
i think
oh okay so i'm really excited um
i thought is real check to make
sure he would want that and he
was into it he was into it
what about the wife we didn't check
with her but i think it'll be
a fun bit of hanukkah cheer and
then they can put the christmas ornaments
on it cause the kids celebrate boat
is or the both of the faith
or like originally or no one convert
now
no shit his wife is jewish he
didn't convert the celebrate oh please and
the kids are jewish okay but they
celebrate christmas because my family goes hard
on christmas yeah they go hand they
go hey golladay i'm right if you
want brazil to him that's clever sky
i like that it is just really
clever well we go we don't have
to take a break how did you
how did you know it felt like
it it did feel like we weren't
really running out of gas so we
need to do what got me i
was talking you're like this renowned yeah
i don't know i tell myself not
talking for a while other people really
just being disinterested yeah that's okay when
we come back i have a new
segments oh incredible
okay we we have to take the
break right away then here we go
and we're back we were just talking
about the upside down actually and how
fun it looked do you remember when
the video was wacky yeah they have
to downplay the sunken place in softball
um i have a new segment guys
oh my god i want guess on
the way over i'm clapping to cover
when you're doing it's working i'm assuming
to cover my clapping
what's wrong
like a rutting pig
um this is where we discuss moral
issues and it's not called morality court
because that's already okay that's a thing
already okay yes so it's called paul
aldi court okay paul aldi court play
the jungle
and no colletti court pallone corn may
need a fine one sandstone so i'm
coming
now play the real jingle yeah hello
at a court below lake or how
old betty betty's can you fit in
a jar that one didn't make sense
are you sure it's not well we're
younger the savings by there might be
a third poe lady cord how many
ounces are in court
perfect nope and there's another one oh
okay
cool it if you can guess how
many ounces are in this court do
you get a prize that's very close
oh god you have to guess i
bet a year's a man has left
to live it if you are correct
he will die thinking of your face
here's i think there's one more oh
bilal eddie card bilal any card we're
all going on the tennis court to
play bow any guard doctor don't don't
get the tennis pros over here because
we want up like oh wow any
court
and now for the real one bola
louis vuitton dupe below lee court buddy
newt we're going to talk about things
that are more alone we're going to
do it in court but nuk vario
here's our issue today we've all seen
body switching movies yeah yeah let's say
you switched bodies yeah with a non
family member you switch bodies with a
friend it seems better like screams of
a good friend or yes a good
friend okay like yeah a good friend
yeah okay so sort of like the
one where ryan reynolds peas yes but
okay what's the hell it's called the
swift p switch
instead for pussy switch they go to
a factory and switch emphasis oh yeah
depending on which characters exactly exactly yeah
so
you switch bodies with a good friend
you're in the body for like a
week okay something goes wrong this is
my question and and you know you're
going back or you're you you're working
to try to think and there's no
you're going for this for this exercise
yes you know you're going back okay
but you have to of course take
care of the body that you're in
sure
if you're in the shower
do you look at your friend's naked
body paul ho because you gotta clean
it paul yeah yeah no doubt in
my mind absolutely
and this is a this is a
woman to you and amanda us i
don't care what it is i am
going to look because it's the body
i'm working with now and i think
i should know what's going you know
you're only going to be there for
a week
i have so you ask for i'm
if you wanna switch bodies of course
you have to go to the bathroom
to the bathroom i'm pleading but i
don't touching it i'm not looking at
at any you're touching things of course
you're touching things you can't avoid that
although my phone you're not looking you
don't look at me yeah i'm not
looking at my body while i'm in
the bathroom you'll never look at your
body in the bathroom what about what's
gonna look take a shower
are you wash your body
through but your look she introduced the
bath the shower dressing it i'm just
saying if i'm going to be in
the shower i'm going out of the
bathroom look at my please body i'm
working with and if i'm going to
take a shit i'll probably just glance
down while i'm doing that too
wish you wouldn't so because i wouldn't
do that to you it's not you
and me well that's gonna say it's
you and me let's say it's us
i think i did early you did
it's like okay let's do it let's
do it why the toad started let's
say it's you and me it's okay
let's do otherwise well that changes that
i'm in lauren's body wrenching and being
very
vague though that's just the changes all
the rules okay oh no let's do
a counter cool i'm now working at
shear in my body i can't add
anything buddy i'm using a stick to
wash my ass and stick to watch
wash cloth on his dick i think
i think i wouldn't get out of
bed that entire we would be in
a coma
go into a medically induced coma and
say wake me up when i'm out
of his body this is a usual
request but i actually bought a switch
with a friend it's only gonna be
a weekend please put me in a
coma so that you do
i typically i would look at everything
when it gets to be who is
it really and it's like i feel
like i'm violating you yeah yeah is
it weirder that we are to men
like what anyone here i was like
mary i think either of us i
would say whatever does but you mainly
have the same body but if if
it were me and scott i would
feel like i'm not gonna look yeah
we're not kind of friends
yeah i mean yeah you're like probably
you're just you're in the wrong not
looking down i don't know i'm looking
in the mirror guys i don't know
everything good
like
but you ain't looking off in the
distance watching like would you would you
put stuff in front of my results
i'm in the shower nobody you know
what my mother used to close your
eyes in the shower because she was
she had like a water fear oh
yeah she was afraid to swim yeah
okay and i this was like sent
late in her life i said
ed did you ever use to swim
and she was like no i'm terrified
to swim and i said really and
she goes i close my eyes in
the shower so she hates water but
i wondered now what she when she's
always she's like i really that's how
much a yummy yeah she's being sort
of just facetious know it sounds don't
know hyper like when she said it
it did not sound like hyperbole
right it sounded like she actually closes
her eyes in the shower because she's
worried that she might drown in the
shower like like i cauterize in the
shower just like water anywhere close my
eyes in the shower paul coming out
of the sink
well
she took me over what did you
do that perfect don't leave your body
weight wasn't it with you on my
my old podcast spontaneous nation you and
tatiana yeah we all are not good
at swimming and but we did we're
gonna take us she also had a
thing where she had a fear of
like something coming out of the showerhead
oh yeah like a show like you
also related to that know that just
the swimming thing well it's just nick
coming out of the toilet what about
that i don't like to think i'm
tired of these motherfucker snakes coming out
of my fucking toilet and biting your
butt and australia there's a risk of
something like that have a big old
tarantula coming out on yeah but yeah
i tell you in costa rica how
the lizards just like
like sleep right above you you did
i don't like that and you didn't
have a mesh net over you know
i don't know what they're doing and
they're not gonna fall on you or
anything it's just like you look up
there and go you could fall it
is rude it's great yes it's rs
i was i was talking to rudeness
yeah it feels like camping nowadays sign
up for yeah oh yeah woo it's
like camping when you didn't sign up
for
a forgetting which way so whose body
would you look at
i'm not famous person of course like
oh yeah like a famous dude like
if you were in ryan randle if
you're in brad pitt's body oh look
him down i guess a word yeah
just to know because they're like a
stranger shit them to you that kind
of person is just a commodity they're
just the first sale that's right they're
just on display on the
yeah sure i'll look a soulless collection
of light
shining on a screen for my amusement
yeah i'm gonna look at that dick
i think if it were someone like
ryan reynolds or brad pitt who had
a great body it's like that's the
only time you're ever going to be
in a body that's a great body
yeah didn't you like got let down
i went alone on a shirt for
sure ever for the entire week no
just everywhere without a shirt and being
famous it's like the only time in
your
feel that good also i would give
everybody the impression that i'm super approachable
knowing that i'm not gonna begin a
body yeah yeah hey i want to
talk to you because i'm famous oh
hey come on let's be friends
cum yeah so i don't know i
wouldn't look at you i wouldn't look
at you but like an opposite sex
famous person person that you're attracted to
i imagine i'd look at any i
pretty much would look at anyone's body
except for if you're saying would you
look at my my say no thank
you would you ok how about this
you switch body like so
with this with a famous woman that
you're attracted okay that you are attracted
to do you then as the famous
woman go try to have sex with
yourself because you want to have sex
well i know famous woman i know
that this variant is my body small
joined-up sex with no but she wouldn't
ever want to have sex with you
because um of of what you're like
but now she's you know she's you
and suddenly you're hurt and she's like
well now i'm attracted well no i
just fucked myself yeah honestly it would
be it would be interesting to see
what it would feel like yourself like
to know what people feel like when
they get some teams yeah yes other
people
sorry honey
you know what person feels ah how
one feels when having sex with me
but you would be mad you would
be mad if like that if say
it was angelina jolie whatever sushi yeah
okay i know but like younger you
know my favorite yeah or no
yeah but so say essentially you know
it's like yeah it's like jennifer aniston
and like you know the personality so
it's just fun she's going to be
around late she takes over your body
are you upset if she has sex
with janie wow because she's she's unattached
she marries knows i think that's fine
what
and and by the way you guys
i wave you guys know each other
it's not like you just woke up
and angelina jolie like angela you're communicating
is she's in paul's body weight no
no no my friend i was trying
to janie your friends was anyone know
this or alcohol and she cannot hold
back she's like
i got to use whatever body i
man and we're doing it now and
then they have sex my wife is
very attractive so again i'm not saying
she would be attracted to janey i'm
just saying you if you're in the
other body or she dies avenge ah
right i'm responsible for the body i'd
be doing it do you think she's
like say angelina jolie is corny all
the
in her old book cats just say
she's she's she's horny when she gets
into your body
or does that or does her or
does your eye their body sort of
yellow nose i think bernie i'm i'm
very low t like it's through the
floor um i think that um hoarseness
is a state of mind so i
think that yes she would still so
she's she's just like look i got
it i have sex with someone and
this is the only person willing to
so
maybe janie is like jamie's like no
genie is going link because she doesn't
know that the bites which happened and
i don't think she'll be human so
even if she didn't angela generally such
a good actor angelina jolie
good actually gelato jay leno
gelato such a good actor jay leno
that ah she's able to do a
flawless ability i mean even if she's
acting a little funny age even if
he's ideal funny she watches your old
stand-up tape she does janie is kinda
going you seem different lately different oh
hoodie this is classic bodies which stuff
you kind of serious tonight
let me loosen you up and then
cheney gives you a massage but it's
an angelina and then he knew it
a thing that happens all the time
of course the yeah she's gotten loose
hope honey loosen up on and here
let me come up behind you into
angelenos going
he would have it in the eighties
yeah you never know you set an
african youth you really hear something okay
just going missing yeah yeah they're my
something i broke up with brad pitt
ah
michael jackson is like oh my god
yeah we'll be ready yeah whereby old
blood roman yeah yeah bill coffee apparently
because be a parent
alright we need to take a break
huh
it's time for a three cheer and
you know what that means i'm gonna
read some oh finally oh dad i
like i felt it yeah i did
too chilly like i was thinking i
don't even know what i was thinking
you're like a great white sharks just
rolled that milky white membrane rolled over
oh the year that terrible high-pitched scream
and this isn't this is a game
feature excusing me learn just spit all
over me by though
all the way over there because we
are the same friends covidien let's look
at our private sorry for the coven
coven sorry server cope
digg is submitted by zach segal zach
siegel's spitting on someone who's really from
the olden times it really is it
says it's the highest form of compliment
fuck a state can touch your friend
now is the days before the mass
i say you spit in the faces
a couple of
you would take you leave one pieces
of food and then you would throw
it at him it's been in his
face oh my god i'm having trouble
forming words guys some even cognitive issue
okay
i made more i'm not even sure
i use that term correctly i think
you did right yeah it may be
maybe neurological issue could be
your brain cognitive up into a prune
nat she's getting smoother zak's eagle portman
portman totally awesome do you see i
do portman totally awesome it's a memory
game in which the players build on
a collection of words slash phrases by
adding on a portmanteau a word that
builds on the last
the sound of the previous word not
technically what a portmanteau is but no
it's not the edition doesn't need to
make sense as a coherent thought each
player repeats the entire collection of words
or phrases before adding their own which
gets more more difficult as it gets
longer and now we're going to start
playing oh wow paul second off his
glasses that's so really
so serious i don't need to read
anymore
wow eyes are getting worse i'm anywhere
so that's with that level off glasses
you got there thank you for those
readers or they prescription these are prescription
these are progressive lenses so i have
progressives as well transitions i was told
no transitions are oh that's what my
sunglass progressives they are tinted if everyone
out there
there are two the privilege to laugh
but progressives have three layers top middle
bottom
ah yeah i think so i think
they do i mean you look out
the middle but i don't think there's
a special layer there's like two like
resistance and then close yeah too there's
some fine vocals essentially okay yeah but
i was told i was told paul
that like very soon because because i
at my last appointment they were like
yeah getting worse again haha well
you know in about a year or
something like it'll just like level off
oh i mean mine has gotten worse
my entire life and second grade you
have haughty but your butt but i
think you're younger than us too i
think he was thinking at a certain
age maybe younger than me
hey day we were talking about that
i feel like you might be i'm
not even sure you should nail this
down at some point but not not
gonna come from you never hear three
any dailies ah distance vision corrected itself
wow it's your lessons for years and
years and years and then one day
i was doing a podcast with them
i showed up he wasn't wearing glasses
and i was like what are you
doing not a glass your glasses guy
he's a glass a day everyday for
this guy yeah then all of a
sudden no glasses doesn't make sense must
feel really freeing for him but it
does but it does so if you
have glasses to only see dis i'm
confused some people have glasses to only
see this now does that makes sense
i had i i can only see
very close up you are far-sighted know
your nearest i'm near which means you
can see things that are near only
very near if right now i will
be able to see your faces we've
no glasses can you read um hey
with no glass j k k three
dora okay baby and hear from my
face
race you know i had a family
there was a family friend family yeah
i had a family one time
we have this family friend he was
the organist at our church organised
yeah hey yeah use your aghanistan our
church he was a friend of my
mom's and it took me many years
to realize this was a bad dude
you like guys
oh that type of that yeah yeah
there's a lot of bad people and
it's like this guy was horrible buying
my way over to the church but
here's why i thought of him because
he would he wore glasses and sometimes
he would take like hang out on
our house he's over for dinner a
lot of stuff you take off his
glasses and he would hold a newspaper
like an inch from his
why was it your house because he
had nowhere else to go i guess
but he was wait he's a lonely
creep down what day on what day
but
was it a holiday but day was
this now you would be our followers
but he would be there my mom
would invite him he's there all the
time he's there a lot he's there
a line he would read the paper
one inch from his face one inch
but why but why didn't need glasses
to help them read the he didn't
have glasses but he would take the
glasses off and he would hold you
to hold a rapid change from his
lawyer day he wasn't walking racist weird
he was a racist weirdo
ah when we were doing i had
never had glasses and when we were
doing the the comedy bang big television
show in between takes i would always
wait i remember that show you were
only a couple of times yeah tv
show yeah it's funny that was fun
i would always take out my phone
and i would be reading it and
i'm holding my phone up like as
far as my arm will
ah like as far away as and
i would be reading it and just
going like oh yeah and people would
go do you need glasses ago i
don't think so this is just this
is normal this is however like this
is how everyone reads on their phone
i'm holding it at the ah the
extreme length of their arm sending a
text but i'm at the point now
where i have to do that with
menus where you like yeah you just
have jamie hold it up and you
walk across the room and go okay
i'm i'm the pastor why don't they
make restaurants dark either rent a movie
from you know but shouldn't they shouldn't
if it's going to be that dark
shouldn they come around and go like
oh here's a flashlight by the way
oh you don't like that little tiny
candle on the table let's play the
game okay
who would like to start us off
with a word i would do it
i dare you
are we going clockwise yeah that's gonna
tell everyone out there what position we're
in wait hold on a second who
what how do we determine it's clockwise
i'm six from the position of your
six okay then that makes me what
three everything's caught there's no determining it's
it is what it is but clearly
you'd be twelve b die if i'm
looking at a clock and then i
have to go like that no no
no
oh right now i don't feel like
we've had this or sitting in a
circle so that means there is a
clockwise or counterclockwise i have this jane
and i had don't devoid this week
we had we had this type of
discussion i can't it was something exactly
like this so you've tried to learn
this a lot and keep right on
sites you know but this time i
was the one who understood it and
she did not
not what is there to understand them
i'm not quite sure i i'm i'm
having trouble like if i look at
a clock i can say what's clockwise
look like if you're sitting here in
a little circle yeah it's always i'm
not sure what is clockwise like left
is clockwise yeah a clock clocks hand
goes like this if you're if you're
if the clock is i don't know
this
if it's only going to see that
guy was great it was so it
was made out to do ma yeah
now the clocks on it's on the
table flat on the table it the
hand goes around this way yes that
oh yeah okay so let's the closest
basic was yes so if you're six
than i'm nine he's trying his twelfth
save me time reid added
there's no twelve yeah it's more like
these clocks with it's more like six
eleven and five but at this time
no one tax numbers are wrong it's
like whatever six ten wy six ten
and two six ten and two okay
six ten two and the first word
is washer
ooh washer good word and i can
add onto that i think sure
that's the last syllable in washer
huh
yeah just tell them you want and
i'm gonna say wash rod brown
sharon brown yeah sen okay from ohio
right sure wash sharada declare throat
washer rod brown yes i'm gonna say
brown is the first part of a
word oh yes i know how to
do it washing right yeah i got
one wash a-rod browning
wash a-rod browning
the thing i don't want i think
it would hold on your smar was
sharada drowning and beautiful smart foresee i
got it when you were poor you
haven't oh wow sharada browning lind
white in england england
wash a-rod browning lind and share know
it rot rot washer rod brown england
share i think we picked words the
land share and share glint england jungle
and share land share and share and
share sonny and cher
that's not a word it's a phrase
which is allowed portman totally awesome not
sure submitted my back but wash your
butt now you're wrong what okay it's
what did you say i said washer
you should be washed wash your odd
browning glens
and share not lind and share i
have no idea will end in england
share england share oh so you're using
and and then you're using it to
make the phrase man's calf raise of
a different yeah that's exactly what i'm
doing wow alright and i did it
wash a-rod brownings
squirrel
given this is gland share screen
y sharada browning land share screen saver
wash your rod browning gland shares screen
save very funny tps your gps i
know that i'll do it too oh
okay alright um like this guy wash
your hands
browning and glenn to share screen save
very funny tb ah don't go you
are allowed to not see oh yeah
so yeah yeah i just started thinking
about the that eric clapped
in song that sbs
ah yes oh man that's so late
i'm going to take this b yes
no no we i was trying to
fit that into it but you can't
i can't okay so what is it
it's tb ah doh very funny we
can't tell you when it's okay wash
your rod browning glen share screen save
very fun ne
cap
okay wash her odd browning land share
screen saver
the funny be funny yeah bridget jones
yeah
according to jones v funny what was
the last part rare coin capricorn yeah
record record who's this
record of touch
why is it wearing so many caps
what
law shore rod browning gland share screens
say very fun knee cap rick corn
on the cob
okay
it is nice to wash your rod
around england share screen save very funny
cap rick corn on the cobblestone washer
rod brown england sharers screen save very
funny cap recall
corn on the cob ma
oh gallstone
close one
cobblestone stone and
y li z
um
should we have done this show huh
no this is from archives from the
trailer oh yeah he doesn't do anything
for you cobble stone or snacks stoners
stoner sex famous race i trying to
lead us into our what we said
in our trailer in our faktor i'm
so high right now should we have
done this show high see there yeah
wow
we made the trailer true that's gonna
be the rest of it the rest
of it will come true as will
come true and one episode of the
time my mom is a shit okay
wash a-rod browning glan shares screen save
very fun knee cap
brick corn on the cobbles stoner
snacks saas
i made it worse
yeah ang cheek
teams get back i want to i
can't do it
donors
ah
paul do you concede defeat give me
one one more moment one more moment
accidents will happen wow
wash erupt and grounding gland share screen
say very funny cap prick car and
on the cobble stoners snacks and dense
will have pen is mightier than the
sword nice oh fuck
what sharon rowe can control what she-ra
brown
sam
screen say every knee
ah ok
like that yeah guys just that was
net income washer odd browning
land share screen saver free fun knee
cap rick corn on the cob or
stone or snacks since we'll have pen
is mightier than the sword in the
stone
rebecca stone
this game go gone forever wow
yeah wash your rod browning land shares
screen save ver e money gap back
on yarn
capricorn on the cobble stone knee
what no yeah um
i'm gonna try again yeah you probably
don't say anything this time okay don't
fuck with mess me up i thought
of that little guy and i got
so happy he's a great guy from
the other from the black lodge that
gum you like is coming back again
style twin peaks yeah i know you're
saving it for the next season of
newcomers we decided
we're doing by the way oh and
it ain't that washer rod brown and
company land share come on guys
watch rod brown england share screen save
very funny cap rick corn on the
cobble stoners snacks the dense will happen
is mightier than the sword
sir in the stony tony tony
okay wow that's good thanks is it
tony tony tony
now it's twenty twenty twenty twenty tony
tony tony o exclamation or what am
i thinking of though words like tony
tony tony that's it but it's it's
tony all spelled differently oh muss your
silly ass
washer rod browning gland share screen say
very funny cap rick corn on the
cobble stoner snacks against will have pen
is mightier than the sword sword in
the stone anyone know
ni toni tone need to know basis
i'm okay
was sharada browning land share screen savory
knee cap for corn on the cob
or the newcomer oh nurse now they've
been in this well high chance mightier
than the sword you sit down and
tony tony
a yeah like to know basis
tres doing it for themselves
ma ma ma ma boi we have
a holiday specific last silom right here
we go well don't just get on
the answer
wash a-rod browning gland shares screams say
they're very funny cap oh record on
the cobble stoner
snack sedans will have pen is mightier
than the sword in the stony tony
tony
e yea i remember oh he's out
now it's your turn just okay
wash a-rod browning's plan share screen save
very funny i should be kept for
his horn on the cobble yeah
one it is more standard is and
this will happen pen is mightier than
this useful bit of difficulty and those
people are dying did you find it
that way telling me i oh okay
i didn't know beta sisters are doing
it for themselves on the shelves okay
huh
elves on the shelves
okay
la sharada brown england and sharing on
wu y sharada browning land share screen
saver a fun ne yeah corn on
the cob old stone nurse snacks will
then will happen
and is mightier than the sword and
the stony dhoni dhoni to know basis
sisters doing it for themselves on the
shelves in the sleigh
why is that about missiles elves in
the sleigh
the famous the famous raise well and
share i would argue is it a
famous phrase sunny chair come on but
an shared but it feels like you
would have started with sunny with like
if it was grand sonny and cher
it feels like that comes on the
shell right scott wins why we all
lost know we all love liz
the listeners really lost well they lost
they listen to that um oh and
you're saying no well i think it's
time to wrap it up yeah i'm
a lot like those christmas gifts but
we were talking better right oh yeah
the crease maybe the crease alright well
we we just want you guys to
just like you know me here next
week so if there's something else consideration
in your life at
least there's this sort of increase due
to wax i was just giving our
listeners some hope some hope finally man
if they need it from us some
sad shit like we're in the middle
of december this you can tell by
how cold we are december i'm bert
and ernie
yeah i'm pre rumor na names of
these them
a well you know this i knew
what time is it i do what's
wrong yeah yeah thirteen years can record
on the lunar i don't know why
maybe the sword in the stone no
hs in chocolate cakes and then falls
down tan chocolate cakes and pains i
don't know what you've been taught from
sesame street i don't know what maybe
statuary about there was a there was
a baker and who would hold like
a bunch of pies or whatever he
makes say cakes yeah he refused and
they cut out from the show
yea okay man okay pm me
a food like chocolate cream pies and
he was at the top of stairs
talk like grandpa who thought on the
stairs and get the pies all over
him that's funny when i was a
kid i remembered it as chocolate like
christmas theories and in actuality it was
like three steps ten chocolate pies in
your face whole candy i like today
a