see
oh my
ah mama mama mama mama mama mama
mama moun moun
three of the season last day
i'm like yeah always in chili reminds
me of when gianna summer played webster
last dance you will hate urkel and
unfairly matter what did aunt myrtle or
something and then sherkle know it had
him they they really fucked up shop
merch if it's not merkel it's not
worth a fucker we do not but
she came she's like a nerd
then she gets on stage she goes
last day and then she's like did
i do that exactly
she thinks the whole song is really
fun wow that sounds so good probably
her crowning achievements so she was you
know it's what i remember the most
um hey welcome to threesome this is
our final episode of the season important
little end of sentence there and perhaps
any season could be the season of
good be this season of our life
lives yeah you know to everything there
is a season turn turn turn from
the bible originally but time to cast
away stones a time to gather stones
together of course these guys with all
these stow and why why do they
want to keep him you know and
why are they trying to cast them
in what the casting couch for stones
come on
not on my imagine if to be
a stone you had to do an
audition
you had to self tape oh boy
self-paced the bane of my pandemic existence
with less self tape you did never
done one never done one this is
why i do not work nye because
your offer you still offer on lincoln
sterile still stir style stir style mister
nice girl and it turns our industry
show
ah midnight cougar identity i did a
cartoon recently of which was very fun
to do and whoever it was i
just got offered it so you did
it oh and i was waiting for
it and they're probably listening right now
but i was waiting for like why
i got this part and at the
very end after i was
i've done um everyone was saying oh
my god you did such a great
job in the creators like ah i
really love you talking to me i
was like there it is yeah thank
you thank you for the job love
it thank you for the job love
god bless you podcast fans who come
into positions of power in tv shows
of it happening you lots of animated
shows yes god bless you god bless
you every single one
god bless and keep you yeah really
appreciate is it cool that i'm listening
lesson i think it's cool right you
know so they're they're also prescription yeah
you were talking about just like tom
cruise and risky business those are prescription
that's why he wore them on the
poster so he could see the people
looking at the poster yeah so you
can read the title below it's lucky
for the
you are talking about the map at
the mall was hard to read with
them yes it was these sunglasses too
yeah yeah you were talking about the
map at the mall this was on
doe off boys de da boys and
when he went to hotdog on a
stick at the mall and couldn't read
the map because it's glasses or tend
to
and of course the map is a
screen is not friendly to that yes
and so i couldn't find the lids
and finally i wanted to go to
live and she just ask every single
bullshit that has excuse me know because
i never found it i really did
look why walked our hell i think
i know where you could ask anyone
who worked in the mall and they
would tell you where i kept thinking
i was gonna find it but you
didn't but that mollis no i didn't
and i gave up that mosque a
major problem imo
all is amaze which mall which mandela
galleria it is like how you turn
a corner and it's crazy anyways like
yeah and you keep thinking okay this
is the end and then you you
like walk a little further and then
there's like a hallway where there's a
bunch more swords i want to fuck
oh scott that song is not good
artistically artistically and morally
do you know it's awkward talking about
no the doors the doors based on
the doors knowledge is limited the classic
oedipus rex
yeah
the whole song is based on it
or just that part i don't know
i just know that it was like
shocking video and father i want to
kill you mother i want to
a shocking it sounds disgusting it's well
it depends on your mom like it
proves he he read your ma that's
nasty that proves he reads but more
on that das nasty but if he
didn't read it his own new thoughts
and guess what i oh like oedipus
rex
oedipus who who tapas february first that
band was popular
he's a model who read three books
write the doors of perception yeah abstract
and do you think he read all
of them or do you read the
back of the book
good question what was the third though
because he has to have ups like
a song based you know the compilation
do you think if you never read
like your brain starts to die in
little parts
i think we're our brains all start
to die every day oh no i
don't think so you don't think so
you gotta you gotta stimulate high girl
inkling i'm reading this book and i
was thinking of recommending it to you
what is it it's this do you
spot run do you know i know
some of those words it's great because
i learned a lot of words because
of it yeah like dick jane etc
yeah
yeah jane etc
all the words yeah um it uses
a lot but let me ask you
because i don't know we probably have
talked about this in the past but
do you like fiction i love fiction
and drag show on march then i
also like some nonfiction andrew sean greer
is the name of the ride i
know this yes is it less less
which i which i lux but i
i'm reading a book of his short
stories call
oh how it was for me oh
i definitely want to read that yeah
it's so good he's such a good
read i loved lend the sql to
lessons coming out know it's coming oh
my gosh um even less you scott
you might like less more than i
don't know like what you but i
read what you want to read you
know i would say this it's because
it's a it's it just sucks you
right in and it's pretty quick
read it's a great read sexy right
oh good sound like a good i
like turn to phrase what do you
like to read you lord thank you
cause you're setting know what i don't
know what i'd like to be
what's a book that you like honey
don't say comic the bible well of
course that's great book john three sixteen
it's a book of books yeah she's
great i don't know i like ah
what's the last book i read i
think i read like six when i
was on vacation but i didn't read
casey wilson's in front of her and
she's mad that i still have never
shown oh i read it she's like
you were reading books in front of
me and not my book but that
would be a lie
not to be reading her book in
front of her she wanted it but
she would want to know what you're
thinking people who write a book about
themselves they want you to read in
front of them true church true no
always not do oh yeah parts
yeah um i do have to read
that um i don't know what i
like to read okay i hate having
to read something i'm i have to
have read something i classically buy books
at the airport when i'm going on
vacation like ooh this is gonna be
a good one like richard north patterson
never read it but no no i
mean my flyers know
i just got gift to the memoir
which who's learned by who um sam
was ah what's his name from happy
days story okay we're happy days anson
williams ron howard oh huh what's called
memoir memoir and my mother-in-law gave it
to me and it sounded an interesting
i'm actually excited to
sure it's i love celebrity memoir from
opi jan yeah i'm actually thinking about
moving back kids icast about such topics
have you heard about i think it's
chelsea advantage has a podcast about celebrity
memoirs other podcasts because we're about to
take a break on this one i
don't want someone to have people listen
to other ones i'm going anyway i
heard her retry her on yet another
their podcast deep dive and i thought
she's really funny and i was like
oh this sounds like my kind of
podcasts i love summary memoirs but i
don't know time to read all of
them and some of them are fluffier
than others and maybe you just want
to hear some what do they do
they they summarize them hey okay i
don't know i haven't lived through to
the book but they read and they
talk about well you are rude to
books by completely ignoring them i remember
hearing a conversation between two people that
i knew
a man who intrigued were both saying
that they do not like to read
fiction books because what's the point because
it's almost like you watch movies or
tv exactly but i don't think we
thought to have precious that's how i
felt after pressures because precious precious is
set up my based on the novel
push by sapphire but it it feels
like a true
story where it's like oh this is
based on someone's real life i want
to say other you but it's it's
filmed like that and then all these
terrible things happen including aids and then
at the end it's like you read
it's just fiction it's like well yeah
i could write someone having a bunch
of terrible things happening to them that
movie i might have said this before
but that was like the one of
the first times i hung out alone
phone with my sister-in-law we went to
see precious and we're both like
yeah i was like this isn't really
what are we thinking writing right carey's
moustache a moustache and a chimp a
mustache and ah i don't think super
mario brothers oh that's right super samurai
brother
right so we gotta make that mean
oh no it's a race to make
this guy to make that mean well
you gotta make that me like zama
to legs have a mustache in that
movie ah he should but i don't
believe me very over he didn't duty
i'm kind of seeing the poster in
my mind yeah i say deal and
i think they're all from
new jersey when they say mario
i think that's simply not the name
like maria lopez so what did i
say just no you said mario okay
but people say marrow and i think
it's only on people i know from
new jersey maybe other states saying but
i'm like that's not what the name
is yeah why are you saying that
you know what's weird is right yes
it's like saying if somebody's name is
steven and you call them stefan right
i can't figure out my friend kerryn
everyone always when they read her name
goes crying wow come on it's insanity
and like everyone does it yeah it's
arrive arise that's really weird very strange
it's very clearly to oh not a
name no one's ever heard in their
life i know i don't mean that
more unusual but i'm saying yes
yes i you could kind of guess
corinne probably isn't it
yeah it's very it's very odd i
can't figure that one out but everyone
does this corinne first or like something
like that maybe it's korean morrison no
it's never quite clear marine or coast
can't lose corrina corrina but never heard
of course you did i can see
that which joke did you like i
liked parker lewis can't lose the tv
show yeah sure yeah because korean may
maybe
we think of corin nemec i don't
know what that is play parker lewis
and partners one where is he now
great question he's right behind you ah
he may have passed on i'm looking
now and it looks like he did
not oh thank you fifty and he's
fabulous really good looking
and hey yeah you and i would
leave mike forum yeah i'm checking to
see if he's available marker lewis can
get it nice doing great dude great
great he's the opposite of dead he's
fifty he's alive he's great well somebody's
dead and i can't remember who it
is let's go through it somebody let's
go through
vaughan adam eve my grandma their anatomy
steve cain abel
anal able before cable can able never
forget i played abel and lucifer
a classic team i never forget did
i watch it i remember oh you
should watch if you haven't i think
free you don't need you did you
would remember if you watched it i
think i did i don't know she
does the thing i don't remember if
i've watched you in lucifer how am
i supposed to remember a book you
don't know what books you like it's
true it's true can i tell the
listener that i ate
ninety nine percent of that hamburger cake
yeah which was a ton of frosting
it was a ton of frosting guess
what i feel horrible and then you
offer me a bite so kylie and
i said so any that right now
because i thought i'll have to shit
frosting ah i wish we shit frosting
i said
but then we think we would think
i was disgusting no but then we
wouldn't put it in toilets we would
like just eat it oh you wish
it was literally crossing i wish it
came out like stars my body and
it was like colorful
shows like rainbow yeah okay so new
suite if we're made in god's image
yeah god shits yeah he's he has
to eat like god gets hungry like
oh look starving yeah come on come
on guys this is bullshit yeah what
if he loves it though because that
is what it is fun to
eat things maybe he's like hey i
want you know this but he has
to shit no god there's no way
maybe he operates like three hundred years
god i hope so but there's no
way the supreme being has to like
yeah food and go bathroom everyone says
rain is when god peas and not
everyone says that yeah
i've actually never heard it
i think i've heard it twice in
the second time was also from you
what is god shitting though is it
is it mudslides yeah that's right that's
right i was i'm having really bad
di di di di da da da
da my dog ga has had die
die for now two weeks oh no
when i was dying inside what's going
no outside okay let's go
controllable oh yeah no it's controllable it's
just like soup yeah from soup to
nuts
sorry sorry paul give us your ide
already gonna throw up eating a cake
um when did we start by the
way josh here never pressed record because
we're so
are supposed to know we've been bad
little children and we've been taking our
breaks at the wrong time so the
past six episodes we've been trying to
take them at the same time what
we we need to take one right
now all right oh wow jesus let's
go to break early we'll be right
back with more three
dad we're back and we're back we're
back took we took a break too
early yeah isn't it weird did you
feel it listener did you feel how
soon it was too soon i say
seems really soon too soon ah didn't
i say that we were doing the
wrong thing and then we did it
anyway i didn't ninety didn't
a cry letters to cleo o abc
e f g h i j o
d w but i believe it yeah
remember when um gilbert godfrey recipes got
in trouble for doing tsunami jokes you
got fired from aflac always only got
fired from affleck for doing now
eleven jokes i think on nine thirteen
i think it was tsunami jokes oh
wow big one and i and i
tweeted and i debated whether to tweet
this or not because i was like
i don't know yeah i went ahead
with it thing i know i mean
like gilbert got fired i know but
i was looking good when it comes
to these kind of jokes to tsunami
and i was like expecting a lot
of backlash and then no one even
responded to it yeah yeah anyway yeah
that's that's a mori simple way to
look that happens to be more than
anyone else will do now sure i
tell of claim to fame no i
only watch the first episode and then
i've been too busy no no i
liked oh that
the celebrity relatives thing yeah it was
you know perfect perfect i just hope
that show doesn't get too popular so
my relatives don't go on it yeah
that'd be really oh why was i
really thought it was the oh no
lauren's yawning filing we knew we would
get there
we would get there eventually i really
didn't want to be called out
well yes i did expel air
only air um i was looking at
out of the mouth to make sure
fired at the same time and of
course of course you're correct but i
really enjoyed this little headline well the
headline is gilbert godfrey fire as aflac
duck after japanese tsunami tweets then there's
like a subhead that goes offensive japanese
tragedy jokes get aflac duck voice fire
fired one round about way to say
it when they already said it and
they also have more clearly we don't
know who he is now that he's
gone he and they was worth it
i mean look at the picture they
chose for him i mean come on
thinking that on purpose they choose an
unflattering photo that's not right it was
worth it though like all things being
equal he should have made those jokes
he loved
like in that picture he looks like
the guy and i'm realized it's kinda
look like um but maybe with um
this covenantal tony mater about it
not gonna say it i don't want
to offend lauren did you have posters
on your walls um no i wasn't
allowed to i've talked about oh yea
okay what else can we talk about
wallpaper i had like nicely framed art
or some artist like like finest volume
picasso i don't know i had some
art and then i on the back
of my door i would like put
up some things but did you have
posters i'd busters for sure i don't
remember like for like pamela anderson and
ah i was like that was my
nine year old girl oh i know
you
um i had the two posters i
remember fairfax right off the bat i
wish i had a poster of fonzie
wow that's good and i had from
dynamite magazine yeah i used to love
dynamo three d poster valve werewolf oh
and did you put on the glasses
scars oh yeah and then i couldn't
sleep
but honestly your room sounds like a
tv set like yeah we'll hang up
the funds and a werewolf was like
are all sort of like public domain
yeah what part was sticking out of
the werewolf like his dogs were reaching
he was like losing forward as tongue
was not sticking out more he was
more
about things he wasn't like yum yum
yum
thought about fonzie every day or do
you like it because it sort of
became like background noise i thought about
fancy everything
every day every every day i think
about fonzie and he
today i dream of but i'll dance
otay on the on the wall behind
my bed yeah so i would like
wake up look i would turn around
and i would salute funds and begin
my day and did he ever wink
back or something every time wow everytime
you do have and i had to
go to therapy for a long time
yeah and i would never i would
never change my story i said he
winks at me every day
did anyone ever walk into your room
and you were underneath funding they would
talk to fonzie and then go oh
wait i'm sorry no paul every day
wow every day every day every day
yeah even sunday's the lord's day twice
on sunday
shit what are you thinking about like
you're lost in thought i must have
had a style is like actually go
back to therapy ah real same i
don't know what crossed my mind but
something you said really he mentioned going
to therapy and then you started about
therapy there any connection yes
that's so weird i don't know what
to say i kinda like a couple
little thoughts and then went there and
then i think i was hearing you
but not fully absorbing somehow my background
noise seeped into your subconscious yeah we
we could do therapy for you you
what did you say about therapy he
went to therapy every day when i
was a child that is no i
did
if they're insisting that funds when i
did hear that we could do we
could do what you want yeah do
you wanna know what my brain does
things like that just bring tell us
one of your problems right now no
no what if you want to therapy
and you played this episode for the
third yeah i see how i didn't
hear but i did and i i
didn't know how i got there but
my murderer but was extremely clear i
my therapist had
stop had to say you have to
stop asking if you're a murderer wow
because it was my number one question
every time i was speaking up reward
were great new show i would just
like tell my murderer i would tell
her ending my problems and then i'd
go do you have to call the
police for that ya know i would
end every sometimes you're not gonna tell
anybody right
yeah he's mature work you're really cool
about all this right god what what
have you actually did that to a
therapist every single session and how long
would it take them to say fire
you okay stop sept yes say i
guess you yeah i feel like i
just can't hear the fucking joke are
you caught up on news a bit
yes with my crush don't know galicia
more likely he hidden patient he's
is doing great i haven't i will
watch the first two but i loved
it his accent amazing jackson is so
good which accidentally doing american yeah no
he's younger yeah buddy yeah i have
been taught that but i gotta say
everybody i didn't recognize him with this
look you know the look changes him
so much and sometimes i'm wearing flaw
api here disappointed when he'd say yeah
it is it's like sloppy dark hair
yeah and it completely changes his appearance
oh duh yeah because he's read well
but but he's great he's doing like
that ah what's that netflix show where
black mirror yeah oh yeah he was
great on that one with hayley attwell
yeah oh hayley attwell she was saying
why peggy carter yeah hard
peggy dot carl will go but yeah
i watched that more recently situation i
didn't know that that's right um i
she's a crash of i should rewatch
someone i could hear it in your
tone yeah i thought i'd spell it
out you see that movie the incredibles
with my crush elastic girl
she can bend every which way to
wu said it no you
this is gonna be the last time
we ever hang out with each other
so we're trying to have fun
fun because we're packing probably going to
get cancelled but yeah we do a
new show like if we do another
season should we like change it up
or keep it just the same let's
let's change like like i'm not here
anymore and just you guys like ten
minute episodes will do calls okay so
you wanna hear change almost every morning
com right now and we record a
season in ah
today's yeah
oh yeah hello freedom you're on the
air alright hi who's this on what's
up the throttle yeah this freedom who's
the sternum
freedom who's this trail yeah this is
three to moses no item hey yeah
that's just three them who's random i
can hang up i don't know what
brands um yeah this thread oh i
don't know what i'm three to write
your freedom your name is dreaming trick
huh no this was lit up what
and your name is freedom wow
what oh wait we're getting to the
call sign hey also check out a
whole dr yeah yeah freedom euro hi
i was just climb because i mean
you guys are taking suggestions which will
do next season um well yeah i
guess we are honey or yoga on
the phone with three on my way
i remember the same oh my my
grandma's calling you to
what the fuck is that no she
was already on the line but oh
well this is my witch now oh
ne hello which i eat anything spells
oh you touch my face
don't you want to be paid i
remain fat don't worry about it do
you want to be too i guess
huh yeah
okay can i can i get some
fitter cancel after every other guy on
the street like hey i'll take some
of that hey i'll take some of
that fitter
what kind of curses that fit my
doctor toby get cursed
i'm curious to watch the trailer for
that now and see how the just
do it i don't want to watch
it all again let's do it let's
watch the trailer right yeah okay yeah
here we go ready josh can you
blow the seller for thinner in a
world where everyone's fat
fountain i'm going to stay that way
forever there's one which oh no you
don't who said that not everyone should
be fat but everyone minus one person
hey what are you doing fim it
be it
this movie is the whoops thirty seconds
long we ran out of money i
think the fable mins yeah the fable
men's i'm like it's the fate i
meant to tell you guys i'm one
of the fable yeah unfortunately like no
let's watch the ads so many visions
shaving their shoulder let's wash his ass
for this show that was cancelled
anyone's to unwise because it's already bindles
over the trash oh my oil or
why why is it so loud and
go and saying all right spelling film
was it was this aaron spelling it
kind of
okay guys taking his food out he's
a big fat so he take these
wow four he gets on the scale
he's obviously wearing it i don't know
who's like comedic at all it's not
this trailer feels like silly the school
oh joe montana isn't this hey you
taster chicago way over new so fatty
deep dish that criminal minds i love
the idea that you know fat people
talk with food in our mouths all
the time road yes it's horrible yeah
it's really it's so now he okay
so any like
it's this old woman in the middle
of the car in the middle of
the street i truly had a midweek
when i was little this was like
the scariest thing versus archie bunker shows
silly son archie bunker it's michael constantine
who shaped his room constantly too yeah
this diet you're on okay its think
you'd like it henry so now
getting thinner this is like goofy it
is good it's goofy as hell are
sorry i'm so thrown you
there is this be interesting thing there
was a close above a little wrinkled
voodoo doll and i'm just the guys
getting out of hand i'm just a
guy okay back in oh and then
joe mantegna goes on a gun rampage
this is incredible because i've gotten rid
of i can't watch it there's so
much noise turn it off god damn
it off turn it off let's remake
this movie it truly
but here's what we do really and
rude here's what really rude they're using
fat suits in this in our version
to three of us played the fat
guy at the same time and we
just want head poking out yeah with
one of her head spoken out and
then we take away a person for
each time we do we each get
like equal screentime though it's of course
it's different as i saved up yes
yeah and then what we're just like
hugging around each other say yes like
oh like wearing a horse face
don't you want to do this loring
dance is really fun
ti ne ne ne ne ne if
you can be cursed what curse would
you want if you could be curse
what curse one i don't think that's
possible
like you have one in mind for
yourself what if you could what if
i could curse you and make your
horse i would not want that okay
would you what weight would i have
the same brain i would i would
have my own thought i just that's
worse you'd have your own constructs and
everything that related to people in your
human brain related to horses now so
you would remember things as if
sure yeah yeah i would remember things
as if they were horses yeah so
you'd remember everything in your life but
like when i break which is cool
i would think i went to a
horse yeah
so if you were a horse you'd
picture in the time where you learned
how to work yours horse horse horse
horse
hey okay lawrence out on that mentally
you guys are interesting
getting low weird any malware
well what occurs would you want i
don't know give me one would you
want to be like every time you
open your eyes they bleed yeah i'm
on it
i want that one jimmy jimmy or
do you want it to be like
a curse like whenever you think a
sinful thought everyone hears it haha yeah
i want it sinful thought what's the
sinful like dessert yeah you're like i
gotta have that cake move my knee
ebro wife ooh i covet her can
we just say if you're a server
up there in a restaurant and you
bring the dessert cart around or the
menus or whatever stop saying that things
are sinful we don't want to hear
it i want to hear it why
it's someone to feel like i'm defying
it off into someone pushing a desert
cut cart up to you saying it
sinful how's this chocolate cake oh it's
delicious it's sinful like when they say
it's decadent
it's like the fall of rome you
would just say this it's good it's
chocolate
everyone most but it's not always good
no no no just good shot oh
good good good good note jonathan gold
when chocolate is bad it's not good
when struck with beth when if a
cake is
jai
it's a chocolate is old old baker's
chocolate maker actually had ah i bit
into a chocolate bar that was gifted
to me yesterday and it was almost
like speaker chocolate it was it wasn't
like ninety nine percent cacao it was
like eighty five percent it was just
too dark like too much cocoa i
i could sometimes do it but it's
very thick
ik too so it was like really
like eating a baker's chocolate bar how
thick should a candy bar be thin
it should in my opinion should be
about like this thick i think rule
of thumb wow like the bible really
so no thicker than a thumb a
candy bar that's right no what about
rollovers a rollover stickers in law school
religion my my dad's failure
hello to the fingertips rules are the
fingertips of the candy rose like a
knuckle roles or the eighties finger of
the candy world can we agree on
this at least he's big guy he
loved leases pleasing your daddy rolo it's
so ironic or only on special occasions
are you gonna always have some around
i don't think we did not always
have we always injured
overall loaves but like holiday times like
christmas when there was there was chocolate
mouse he would eat all the roll
my sister by the way makes these
great peanut butter candies that are in
the shape of peanuts they're so delay
eats a candy the city i look
like they're like no they're like creamy
lie
like it's like chocolates almost but they're
peanut flavor hey pee and there's it
and they're in the mold of a
peanut
it sounds good it sounds good you're
saying that has mold on it so
that's what i mean yeah it'll give
us some hope so
they're so delicious that it's just it's
bad you can't have too many of
them is it sinful know it's like
peanut it's good is it is it
kinda thing that kind of gets you
sent to hell
do you think the devil would imagine
you eating them and go
ye i mean my plan that's one
of the commandments is about eating them
one of the templar number nines like
those peanut things your system makes stay
away don't do like avoid it a
little bit hey don't do double duty
thirty those bullets don't do that they
that do that the that the body
you're on accent coming out though but
yeah did you start talking like chicago
person when you were just say i
did find my accent coming huh yeah
because also everyone was from chicago so
the zanskar geeky definitely said stuff like
that for sure did you say it
on film and people were like i
know we're filming this in europe i
always like tone it down a little
bit i'm feeling okay
a the press
hey hoagie oh did you grow up
with hokey um i actually said have
ah you know what well like the
bears sketch on us and they say
oh no dog bear right or the
bears sketch they say grinder whole gazing
grinders i thought hoagie was just where
i grew i never
i ate that so i don't know
i just meant the word dear know
i know but i'm saying i actually
don't really know it was never like
sam never ate it but it was
in the chicago sketch so i can't
think of words that i don't eat
yeah i eat so much fucking pizza
when i was home those kind of
getting out of control pizza for lmao
bodies pizza around lunch be different if
you've paid
on a bale you can have pizza
anytime i have heard that um i
didn't have any big old wives' tale
myth yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
not true so we got a great
song you can't have when you're asleep
you want to sing it anyway when
he's in the morning please any fan
please at supper time okay wait a
man on ebay
oh okay any pizza yeah pizza in
the morning sure i get it yeah
evening yeah but then what's the difference
between evening and suppertime
well let's talk about lunch it's regional
differences okay some people supper is lunch
some people suffers dinner either the weather
be hot weather the way because a
supper is lunch know i know yeah
i lie here elia oh restaurant last
name in the menu said supper we
said no lying on this show when
did we say
i remember our first episode we were
like everything we say is gonna be
true
alright first episode of freedom wow what
do you gonna do ball well we're
definitely not gonna lie everything you say
should be true agreed three million farc
the judge pulled that clip up so
fast
theme in scenar movies suck also you
know what you saw can actually stephen
king actually kind of suck hey why
don't know you don't know anything so
good i don't think he's that good
he was good for like a good
ten years but even the stuff that's
supposed to be so bad i don't
think i know but it but it's
good every ending is tara
able i know but it's hard to
end things like look at this episode
it's hard to end it's hard to
end things but like i think if
you're me you have things like that
you should find an ending feeling of
it is so bad but it's yeah
i can shrivel up into oil or
something i can't remember what
he dribbled up into oil shriveled up
oh it turns out he's a big
alien easily luckily oh yeah writers yeah
he blew up in all those bugs
something like that yeah his head got
really big he should just swap endings
with his other books so it's like
okay christine yeah he dribbles up in
oil he dribbles out of total oil
yeah that makes sense yeah because
yes he dribbles up in oil yeah
cujo cujo happens to be a big
alien cuyo he was up in oil
hey doubles up in oil ah firestarter
yeah she goes to prom and blood
gets spilled i try to put out
the fire i asked that because this
all makes sense steven
the trailer for kerry by the way
gives away the entire movie yeah some
like an age i think they did
that yeah dinner he gets old one
gets thinner more and he escapes from
jail with his best friend i start
through a poster railers for that reason
i thought i'm just like go through
the bars because he got was getting
yeah that's right he doesn't need the
poster see this makes more
sen steven oh my god
you know do you like to watch
a trailer for something or do you
rather i swear i have no idea
i did watch the secret invasion trailer
but i stayed away from mandalorian yeah
if it's something i'm kind of excited
to see or if i've heard it's
really good i really don't want to
see anything if if it's somebody like
whose work that i always enjoy yeah
why not i try to stay away
from every if it's a hype i
try to learn to watch trailers so
i watched a great movie
a what the worst person in the
world have you seen it no i
still haven't seen wanna see it i
loved the purchase really good was honestly
reminded me of when i was in
college i would go to the art
house movie theater and be like i
just saw a movie called once and
it's gonna blow your mind you know
one but it was like that movie
gave me that feel
thing again which i haven't had since
i was much younger when i was
more impressionable yeah yeah and this was
just like it was just great i
just loved it it's wonderful and it's
darwinian and what i loved about that
was that shit the language was very
unfamiliar to me so i was very
swept away i feel very real because
i was doing anything i'll ever say
you watched with no subtitles yeah i'm
just going this this seems
a real i like doing that because
you could just put your own plot
oh yeah yeah you just rely on
mute and just do whatever i want
what's going on over here oh this
is crazy man of your work person
i bet you're too i bet there's
somebody out there who just has the
tv on mute and does that all
the time someone i bet puts via
neutron does this podcast over in something
that seems good
that would be good right let's in
case that's happening let's do some movies
right now
do some movies ah so put on
e t right now huh it be
better to keep my imperator divorce oh
yeah imo use it an alien visit
you oh yeah did you curse me
you know alien alien
but kurtz an alien yeah you won
won't he never came back and say
wow guys but never try you never
eat he never fucking came back we
don't care that he fricking was back
with his mommy he was he had
such a bad time on earth he
never came back i found he isn't
the best friend elliot he's back with
his mummy i thought he was an
adult he was an adult do
does enough novel mom looking for him
to novel goes into it isn't there
an alien mom on the board on
the on the surfboard board the ship
whose like combat the alien like goes
i'm doing it with change don't alien
know the book goes into me see
does the book winners oh yeah what's
their chief export
sweet
ah he's the person i was talking
about is our t's mom uses space
ship
special get a special visitors visitor yeah
e t's mom on the sushi cheese
mom on the spaceship everyone calm down
i'm looking for e t's mom is
she on this show e t but
with boobs
remember when e t dressed up like
a lady it doesn't look like that
i'm not his mom's nipples light up
like the finger i'm not getting a
lot of info oh you're kidding me
wow what is the what does the
top hit for is tt's mom on
this it's all about the mom from
e t o d you all stow
d well yeah d a lot of
stonewall exam grade flintstones name you gotta
admit it where's the stone i'm only
seeing dee wallace wells well she fucking
got married and she became dee wallace
stone to who to sharon stone
roger stone you remember this shared some
register married her i don't remember you
know rebels who goes first legal trouble
it was the only legal trouble
oh scott you're so naive troubles aren't
legal oh yeah sometimes if you know
the right people they are i don't
think so
well she's married a third time to
skip the skip bolivia bolivia skip lay
up sticking to my newly shaped sulu
myself fake baba named by someone writing
a bad movie skip i like that
i like yeah okay look we have
to take a break by
and we're back and we're all back
i wanted to say we're back i
needed oh okay yeah i i heard
you say that just now no i
thought it was before it's i don't
know what you guys were talking about
but then i had this thought that
i wanted to say we're bad yeah
yeah and what's funny is that when
you say i wanted
to say we're back it's that you're
saying it in the in the desire
i've said it like because i wanted
to say whereas i'm not sure why
it might come out of your mouths
maybe with some sort of do you
understand the words coming out of our
mouths i do
um well i already have a voicemail
i heard that too camila i didn't
hear that i heard a rumor that
went like moisture when it's heard
okay yeah last man you get voicemails
at irma has a duty at our
number haha in poo haha lion poo
jack da da da da in mood
too good to reach out and touch
me learn a lot too is also
wrong right
yep oh cool
alright let's listen to this
voicemail to i'll look at it here
we go okay you could have one
girl starts with okay okay like in
the matrix what would it be what
if you could have one sleep over
down okay let's listen to it again
let's talk over at less but still
talk over it okay okay he's talking
wow dude why
yeah ok tiled okay let's hear a
little more to let's hear it it's
very good because we were talking over
part of it okay na na na
skills girl scout scout matrix is my
duda bones all the do dah daisy
mean by that social drinks
is my duda bones alright but for
this should be the title josh qatar
qatar mice
mike they will listen to this voice
okay
okay you have eleven
rejected in your head like in the
nature injected in your head will be
okay i got it i got it
i would i would have it be
the skill of how to inject people
with skills in their heads and then
you'd always be hired yeah you'd always
be part of the economy
what europe has to be economy you
wouldn't do it to people for free
i mean for starving children yes okay
a lot of catfish studies because i've
never seen the matrix so wise in
the matrix which is did you do
scott every psion but about you
you've seen the matrix yum yes and
went to so what hallows we don't
don't give it away it's computer lids
you know that was that cut out
in the corner of me with my
but there's a hole where my mouth
is yeah this is like that but
in the back of the head so
they put whatever they want yeah they
just stick in a thing just an
idea what skill
he yeah he learned by elaine chao
mode something he all of a sudden
he knows how to do kung fu
great okay mine would be oovoo that
i would um yeah i would oh
that's cool i would like to like
know what is in every book that
i touch and like know the acknowledge
well it's not they're not downloading you
know magic and dear
oh they're downloading like the that any
such skill oh okay um then i
guess people i've never yet seen it
you fucking moron you know what the
word skill means though right stupid my
skill would be they could fucking cook
huh i guess my other ideas suck
have you been cooking at all um
well i did fall off when i
was in chicago because i wasn't able
to cook but i knew i was
sir well i we were ordering food
item says yes but i am big
macs every day going to exactly i
was into it before i'm bunking back
now i'm bringing back should we cook
for each other and just swap meals
no okay i'm not not confident enough
about what i really would save time
wouldn't it know why i guess the
driving back and forth
yeah and also you're cooking yeah no
it's way too much for me would
absolutely be piano wish i could just
play the piano feel like we talk
about this all the time we do
and i never do anything about it
i know oh i don't know i
wish i could play an instrument by
the way my mind trying to i
don't want to talk know a friend
of mine i was talking about the
piano when she the day after i
had this conversation with her she like
k
em to me with a plan and
an email about like okay i've looked
up this teacher this teacher never wrote
her back is it the same one
that was gonna teach some doctors will
try to really help you it shows
you how much you don't care
yeah and it shows in that too
like well noted never again i'm going
to dinner with her very soon and
i'm gonna see a lot of answer
to everything and go go go go
go google okay here's how i'm gonna
handle it by the way ignore it
i'm never gonna do that yeah how's
that sound this is that rude tour
let's hear another voice i had somebody
reach out to weed until she's got
skill was
i need to touch faith do you
have a real inner know it is
probably piano i've said it i'm on
a million of these episodes or maybe
lead guitar lead guitar lead guitar i
want to a bat brett promise to
help me set up a electric guitar
rig oh yeah that's right you are
gonna stare at them i'm a witness
i'm a witness to that it was
good i was hoping he
was gonna promise to buy it for
me but instead he just said i'll
set it up if you buy kevin
kevin t porter of ah of good
christian fun asked me he texted me
on i'd have not responded to me
up but he asked me okay yeah
any show they made it feel good
he asked me if i ever thought
about taking piano lessons and i wonder
if that means he would he is
voluntary does he play piano he does
play piano does he mime along with
it when he watches bruce springsteen concerts
yeah i bet yeah yeah yeah and
nils lofgren gets so mad he's like
that's my job either fuck are you
making fun of me
because he makes a dumb face too
but he's really doing the fingering i
didn't know what i didn't get back
to kevin about a bruce springsteen email
that he sent me for probably a
week and i felt really bad about
this one's going on three weeks probably
from oh it was during the tour
though do you want to take some
time and write back right oh yeah
okay rta i say bup bup bup
bup bup bup bup bup pass a
birthday text rolling through over there for
paul we see his phone lighting up
the marine it is fun and i
respond to them at the end of
the day ah oh good nice like
it's over asshole
you're a little late i didn't say
something yay in twelve or one september
thirteenth i'm like what is this till
you missed my birthday three child and
talk should we hear while you're doing
that should we hear the next voicemail
i'm asking should be absolutely sure yeah
oh hey so i got a question
for ya let's say that after
or you die you get to live
that one day as any person who
christian any time that you like that's
my answer luke john malkovich rules apply
and if you wake up one speaks
another language you will know and understand
that language doctor who rules yes this
day is done you get
eternal nothingness who do you pick and
when do you pick
madeline by the way thanks madeline so
you want the eternal i was saying
being john malkovich rules i recently watched
a movie for the first time all
the way through it i really loved
it um so you'd seen parts of
it before then
um i had just seen yeah a
little parts of it but i don't
they like when they called by the
way it responded with one word they
come out of the chute that was
june thirtieth that text oh my lord
and you're just saying one word yeah
and not even apologizing for how long
no no jay send you another text
but since then
there are many yes and you've responded
to those yeah oh well then snow
is weird and sounds weird you just
wrote back to me immediately waiting you're
back already
when we finally circled back to the
important things
um but in being john malkovich when
you when you're like portals out of
hand this isn't a movie podcast you're
all wet jesus so he's saying really
oh wait remember oh and don't like
the highway like ah oh that's oh
i thought it productive ludicrous know ludicrous
i don't know if you end up
all wet was humid and wet do
you think
if ludicrous i would assume he's taking
a bathroom to it's room the idea
to live out ah day as someone
else yeah it's like we've day i
died i would do that it's like
if i died i think i'd want
to probably be me again and he's
yeah people i love but i guess
if i had to be somebody out
if you could be one of the
people you loved that's weird i think
i would
choose if it has to be someone
you're not related to and it to
mean you don't know i think sbs
like a celebrity but wait so in
being john malkovich or you you're not
controlling john malkovich u r l r
as much as you can as much
as you can yeah but you're kind
of like in the back seat right
yeah yeah yeah i guess i would
pick if that's if that's the idea
i guess it would be
the peter o'toole and like ah a
time when he was on stage ooh
cool what's interesting and doing ah offense
like a fantastic play somewhere i would
be the person opposite peter o'toole on
the stage fun yeah same time though
exact same time okay i tried to
upstage you i would be
donna on the lake of virgin tour
oh that would be so fun not
going wild for me madonna but to
be like one of the beatles or
something yeah when going fun can be
brewing the beatles are already annoyed all
day imagine being in the show you
get back there like
oh yeah true
la quit touring because they didn't like
it so that would be bad to
not play at the beginning but it
was pretty cool they liked it for
a long time now yeah this is
fucking great okay what era of the
beatles would you then would it would
be like shea stadium or would it
be in the cavern club
i don't know what that guy's a
cat well the cavern club was when
they just started out they would go
to germany it would play like five
hour sets you know maybe they were
like don't think i would chuck in
teenagers just having the time of their
finding i would choose that
but then what about a person from
hale had a cough that like was
really i mean i wouldn't shoot i'd
be jimmy carter the peta president running
for reelection
yeah i'd be george herbert walker bush
and he's rolling up on the prime
minister of japan you pick a day
though like a specific day or is
this like something i would like to
come like someone who is alive yeah
but neither scrooge
is this what will be or what
may be here's what i think what
we chose is what the rules are
okay i like it i be jesus
christ okay so which day are you
he's crucified
gotta be los oficiales de about to
be all mad i'd be so hungry
it would be like water and wine
every single day i'm so hungry right
now i guess i'd be someone eating
their best dinner they ever had were
the loaves and fishes in the water
and wine the same wedding or was
that whether it feels like it was
a different days like he's showing off
almost like do you
think that the people at the wedding
when they got close like hey what
am i why do you need to
think the bible is fun day the
bible takes place over twenty four hours
like before out of his pages yeah
yeah and then huh john sees all
those icbm jesus it's on the scene
the following takes place based on clean
jesus on t v the somme the
scene would anyone v us did i
get angry yeah you know don't be
my mentor don't be oh don't do
that when like down on my head
don't do that out of my head
mean nobody guy's gonna miss most about
not doing the show
yeah but what do you miss the
most about doing doing the show you
know gotta miss the not being able
to do the show i guess yeah
nus the slot um i'll miss our
fun silliness together for sure yeah probably
too
probably me
are you going to miss all the
references that we make being old men
that you don't get it yeah i'll
have to like turn on the news
or something and i'm gonna have to
turn on abc family yeah news to
watch all the nineties sitcoms yeah hulu
has a lot of them do you
remember how much you hated the news
when you oh my god i know
oh man i'm a huge fan listening
to like the news was on a
lot when i was home and like
the one local news one story after
the next just really a murderer was
murdered murder a car jack this person
died this was sad and on this
side of town another bad thing happening
yeah he used to all the time
you might think
now you worked for the local news
you are worse than garbage as long
as frasier crane who said if it
bleeds leeds i believe all those stories
do lead in chicago well it's his
depraved town
yeah and you'll notice that if the
strictest gun laws and yet they have
all the gun crime huh i've made
a point
yeah but the news is like i
do i kind of like what we
watch local news sometimes wouldn't it be
no saying if there was there's something
really like to fry us news network
don't they talk about how never happened
they they originally the news was supposed
to not sell advertising and it would
have been so much better for the
company for the country yeah the company
i call it look
the company we live in the company
of the united states of america you
know if but but because then they
allowed everyone to sell advertising on it
than they compete for ratings and they're
enslaved by corporate mon tresor yes but
imagine a world where the news had
no advertisements and then they were
are beholden to no one like the
newsroom yes will mcavoy making a speech
imagine if you were flying a plane
on nine eleven
and then you want to end the
show yeah this is a newsroom reference
yeah
no not nine eleven one wasn't it
was when osama bin laden yes yeah
yeah and they're trying to get you
to land the plane they're trying to
get you ally on the plane then
someone finally just knocks on the cabin
door trying to get you to land
the plane or its talk of it
oh yeah he's like hey start over
i would be that guy i auditioned
for that scene doing what i was
supposed to be one of the passengers
on the plane going like hey shut
up dude yeah yeah he need not
gonna hey dude
this was your idea like hey hey
new to you maybe don't like would
you please read the words that are
on the strictly like okay i'm sorry
i'm sorry let me try
wow you better know their shit up
what if you didn't do the dishes
just did that would you ever get
another one time it has to work
yes and they go like this is
crazy but i love it hey hey
dude phil do yeah cannot afford this
beatles ugh
parody you can say you do you
have to eighty out of his weight
out of the bay yes he does
hey dude you see is my ranch
oh
why are you talking about a rat
dredge oh
okay it's making more sense but still
is not part of the script hey
d i guess i'm gonna miss this
um should we play one last reacher
yeah yeah okay for old time sake
this is count your words submitted by
nobody apparently
um we do a scene and where
oozed we're ah first of all pick
a number between one and ten for
paul okay oh wow yeah thirty thirty
three okay i heard thirtieth okay i'll
pick a number between one and ten
for me seven okay i'll pick a
number between one and ten forlorn nine
oh okay and really high number choice
your last one not the highest no
no nine nine ninety one good what's
happening so we're gonna do nine nine
nine nine nine nine nine if you're
in imagining t yes ah one degree
in here
i'll say that it could be zero
of kevin bacon
walking through the door i make it
right outside the door his instagram is
fun it's a crime is fun yeah
yeah don't follow it um okay we're
gonna do is follow i don't follow
it it's kind of you command don't
don't fall don't follow this please please
don't follow him we're gonna do a
scene and we can only say the
amount of words every single time we
have a line we can only say
the amount of words that gray
said okay which one did i have
i had seven you have nine you
you have three yeah okay okay hello
my good friends it's so hot
i can't believe how hot it is
i'm dying yeah for sure
are you wearing those sweater paul f
i'll answer for him he is wearing
a sweater yes i am take it
off then because it's hot
it's hot sure but he can wear
whatever chooses
whatever chooses that doesn't make sense either
well i find let him speak he
hasn't had a chance yet he just
spoke are you not listening i am
listening look i have something i wanna
hey shut up
say the
no way the world is working is
not bad
things are bad in the world yes
they sure are
i want to make a change i
want peace okay kill yourself then it'll
take care hey that's rude no he's
right i'll do that i think that's
what i was talking about oh no
oh no lauren goodbye sweet princess it's
been so nice
i'm one last thing i want to
say is gone speak
never continue through him without me head
won't be same we promise to only
do episodes with two
well i don't
ah
she said scott
so we should still do the show
yes of course
okay bye i'm going to bed now
bye bye you
eternal bed
turn open i'm joining lauren as well
know you too
me too goodbye forever
goodbye goodbye goodbye hashtag me too hashtag
me too goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
wow
just me the end wow i can't
play
five points
thank you nobody for that three de
ne um while everyone thank you so
much for all the fun you've had
this season yes we love you thank
you for listening using giants and by
the way altogether to well together to
get all together when the new season
comes if and when i think i'm
going to have an exciting ta
like to talk about storage words oh
wow that's i'm getting used to lawrence
topics feature if that time i let
you it depends we'll see but i'm
i feel that their next season is
going to be our biggest one our
biggest one yet if we do one
if we do one it'll be the
best it's ever been if we don't
it'll be horrible so i got i
got i got some
i really want to get off my
chest why i'm willing to and we
have to wait months people like i
don't who knows how long it's gonna
be but i'm i will debut talking
about it on this show and if
we don't so you're not going to
talk about it off mike known whenever
we're back as well i'm just going
to grunted people if we don't i
mean ever like not talk at all
if we don't get another
or season will you ever i will
never bring it never bring it up
the only way to hear this is
if we get another season yeah i
hope we do i've been keeping something
in reserve for this show and is
it about lauren or it's just you're
going to use loren loren topic because
topping the segment it was so popular
yes i want to bang segment but
it's kind of mine like i'm i
look i might share it i'm just
saying like it is
my segment i can't you have scott
no minute you had scots scots minute
so if scott and the last minute
shopping guest host lawrence topics are you
gonna hold a grudge against him like
johnny carson did against george i don't
know i won't i it's okay to
have a man do my topics it's
not going to make me cry man's
plane whatever i'm talking about yeah your
topics yeah it's your
people will be aware that i had
nothing to do with it yeah yeah
okay what do you think is going
to happen next season firm like anything
i'm gonna announce or i want to
talk about yeah what do you think
we're gonna talk about do you think
will tell what stories do you think
will retail these are good predictions i
think i'll probably tell stories that i've
told before i think that might happen
and i'll probably talk a lot
about you know just my life and
stuff great ball what do you think
it's going to happen well my goal
is to repeat zero stories and the
next whoa i mean that's a big
challenge i really do want to encourage
the listeners out there to create a
threesome wiki where if we start telling
a story it lists every story we've
ever told yes and if we start
telling
never say this we can look it
up on the wiki immediately and go
oh i did i think and also
what how many times you've told it
has to be a code where it's
just like two words that trigger the
idea of the sword because i don't
want my whole stories all typed up
sir no no no just you just
need to do like the headline of
the story what is their threesome wiki
i don't even know i don't know
either look it up right now if
i could stop
typing three from can you helpful apparently
not well in any case we gotta
keep we appreciate that you've stuck with
us for this entire time lawrence taking
stuff out of her bag because she's
mentally done she's pushed the mike away
from her face i just i need
you guys to know that the new
season is going to be so amazing
that
if we get to do it it's
going to rock everyone's socks it's going
to be very different yeah totally really
oh my god this can be so
much different about it i didn't hear
the first part of what you guys
say because i was looking at my
phone yeah but i agree with the
last part which is it's going to
be very different i will have new
stories i swear the there's a list
of three cher's yeah i found this
wiki years yeah we we do need
somebody's got to add
to that page the stories that we've
told several more and more than one
occasion or just every story we've ever
told about our lives a lot of
homer out there i think it's okay
but there's some weirdo who wants to
do it alright probably will thanks guys
thank you oh we love you will
ah see you next season keep the
faith babies we hope to see you
soon by back bay
uh