a ah more back if you don't
think we're back then you must not
have been listening to that shit i
jacked up
gizmo guillot ou
oh guess he's bow bradford is it
wait you don't sound like him i
don't know what does the robot sound
like dogs various yeah oh okay wait
but what when they when you feed
them what do they sound like after
tony randall oh hello
there's that was my initial attempt to
tony randall it was love the lips
very sexy she was oh that was
can you imagine that gremlin slaving on
your knob lord oh i could i
mean can you stop imagining it's virtually
is welcomed back to the show this
is threesome i'm sky i'm paul i'm
all the freedoms that's check check and
check rosenberg wasn't in present yeah actually
we should say that we received a
great gift okay and the person even
went above and beyond by getting the
amazon gift wrap which costs five dollars
whoa right we don't need to do
the if you're gonna send us something
but it was but it would be
naive if you're going to send us
something it had lying around to scrimp
on the on the gift
or should i say i have a
question and you can answer this in
twitter um do misa phony people hate
crinkling bad so phony oh me so
phony oh me so phony okay well
you're sent spanking pens oh yeah her
pen i'm going to get a picture
of without kid
the little hands are on the hills
there are different styles unwrap them yeah
you should right into the microphone there's
no way not to why are you
on revenue you don't have to unwrap
every single one every style there's every
style to get a good picture just
right okay all right this is very
he's are and they are actually pens
i i don't
see the writing implement hidden within the
fat bass ou shot piece okay lawrence
taking a picture thank you to whomever
sent us those i'm sure lauren has
the info it's a spanking fan or
whatever yeah yeah the failure speed fans
have spanking you've found our podcasts they
don't
ain't even like us probably a parent
making fan also we want to say
kevin is back he's over here anyway
hello is back hi john you show
him what okay have we taken care
of all of the business yeah lauren
is also back lauren has been away
for awhile i know we know this
sir yeah this is our third episode
back but we have not seen mean
yeah we've not seen lauren since our
last episode for a long time yeah
it's good to see you did you
miss us at
all you know
you're in the debussy in hawaii unifil
land of hawaii was i will say
it was so busy um that it
made it hard for me to get
homesick or feel like i want to
get out and were you in a
hotel room yes or a house hotels
but we moved like three want a
hotel room in a house no it
was a hotel were going to huh
in a house in a little tiny
house that was built inside of a
hotel room basically a hotel read a
whale's belly you saved for the game
um but it was really fun yes
really so you want us to save
this for the game but always mean
you want to have a conversation but
just saying it was really fun yeah
um it was one of my favorite
experiences what wow i just had a
great time it was very challenging um
for me as an actor and a
good way i fucking really mean
myself it was very fun um you
know of course there's no predicting what
happens next which is something i really
learned about mm i don't know what
you're talking about right now yeah that
just you don't know if it's going
to be good or bad and um
i i've definitely had the experience of
having lot of fun and then something
being bad but um i'm like yeah
everyone hates
but i'm ah very excited that just
you accepting an award right now what
is going to say thank you on
board
okay they're they're playing you off no
nah you start talking
anyway finally my accompaniment that's all i
want to say about it okay well
welcome back and this one what somebody
was getting played off at an award
show the music started and started singing
oh ya la la so take my
age huh
sorry i had to fire you i
stabbed with double oh yea talk about
what we were talking about right before
we started yeah what we're i don't
even remember about your wife being your
best friend oh okay so you you
mentioned your friend thought something about you
my friend bill w
you mentioned your friends on something i'm
sad to hear vague way of started
and then i was like i don't
i don't have permission to talk about
what you talked about my my friend
casey who is the ah the executive
producer sandra z tonight know she left
with such
she and i used to work together
on best week ever with paul f
tompkins and the sunshine yes the sunshine
was a house band for the show
that would be amazing casey would not
appear just the sunshine but just as
sunshine thank you yeah it's either choose
name in front of it yeah casey
yeah we also had the hermits without
herman
lawrence patience is at an end since
she's back where where is the hollow
feeling is there i'm just a little
tired oh hander johan of these family
ah halloween so um and so i
for some reason ah
was talking about
i think it was about wardrobe for
the show and i said just for
fun i put on a voice and
i said i want to work a
cream colored jacket and that that affected
vocal effect like grossed her out yeah
roast her out yeah it sounds like
you swallowed a cadbury egg whole i
wish i had so she was she
was a key
cadbury egg she got nauseous from this
or it's easy-to-do i think it made
her teeth itch sure like that cause
she was repulsed she's repulsed because she's
such a robust so she is repulsed
by you now ever since well no
if i do that voice oh it's
only the oh so doesn't permit didn't
trigger it no she didn't real
like ricky wanting snowflake so it's not
like a rimless ninety one knows that
i'm gross
no one must ever know please your
real best friend knows my wife but
you mentioned your friend and i didn't
hear who you were talking about i
said oh janey and they were like
that's not my friend that's my wife
but she is my friend she's led
us to talking about this whole new
thing which i think is about ten
years old no taller than that is
it older yeah yes but it's so
like some at some point a decade
or two decades ago peoples thought it
was invoked to start saying to be
ten years ago i was say i
mean it was pretty much two thousand
and nine
tip ten years in two dec ten
dances two decades
more than twenty years so no one
cheers was
really it's only been max twenty years
people have said that i think no
rajan mystic before no no no i
just remember i remember before by the
way we haven't even said what we
said but basically it's invoke now is
to say that your wife is your
best friend and i thought your husband
your wife your hook out the other
women's i'm very sorry very clearly do
not say
my husband's by bedtime thinking of myself
so i'm missing but but i wrote
this true yeah but yeah i remember
it i remember it almost as if
it were yesterday but ah but it
was ten years ago or more it
was somewhere in ten years because back
then people would just say like oh
no this is my wife or this
is my husband i love them and
then suddenly
people started saying this like well you
know what she's also my best friend
yeah i know i have a best
friend let let there be categories in
your life yes your wife can not
do it all people yes women cannot
have it all okay i feel like
you're it's forbidden i feel like your
spouse is your de facto best yeah
the time when i also have a
best friend g you and you've implied
that you love them at best friend
level because you want to be around
them yeah yeah and fight in them
i'm not married my best friend no
why would you i married my wife
and i love her the most if
i married my best friend will be
a disaster how long have you been
friends with your best friends
huh well how long have i known
you ah yeah um i the the
guys who are my best friends i've
known since the late eighties yeah ladies
hey late eighties um i i'm not
one of those people who i still
keep up with people from high school
but i'm not one of those people
people take such pride in that of
like oh no my best friends have
been my best friend since i was
eight years old it's like come on
when i've asked for changing my best
friend since i was five really yeah
who's this natalie is her nah nah
nah she listened to this oh well
then she's not your best friend right
now there's you know
there's only so much she can do
right um she not gonna send us
gifts she's definitely not oh sorry i
like this natalie law but yeah that's
my like longest best friend my next
my second longest has been my friends
what does she mean let's break this
down i know this is a recurrent
relationship for you so it may be
difficult for you to talk sure she
won't listen though so it's okay
so she is she yes she's your
best friend are you calling her your
best friend simply because you have ever
since you were five like is she
taking that best friend slot right now
she performing the duties of best friend
that a best friend would do yes
and she lives in chicago now she
lives here oh alright and you guys
see each other
for all the time pretty high all
the time so we text all the
time we see each other like every
couple of weeks okay but that's how
much i see any but surely she
know who we are yeah okay and
why have we never met her because
ah she doesn't i don't know come
to the things that you guys do
just she liked it you do comedy
yeah but she's
using a totally different like you're saying
she's a pain yes i know just
real pain in the ass but she
isn't like that art community it's totally
different like i only know a certain
things about her community and you know
just kind of there's not we are
crossover do you think do you think
if suddenly a new person came into
your life where you're like i think
this person is my best friend no
definite
have people that i think are my
other best friends right so what did
you think you could not say that
to her because it's like look we've
been having this going since we were
five we cannot stop this train here's
what it is she will always hold
the place of my best friend like
i introduced her as my best friend
but i don't introduce like wild horses
as my best friend if i'm introducing
like here's my best friend mary
my best friend three p i just
say yeah i'm just like you this
is my friends these i'm stay with
her i will introduce her that way
to like if ah sure to meet
you i would probably say she's my
best friend well you don't need to
because now you know best friend is
a weird term many ways and like
well we qualified
yeah here's why i say it about
her i like it because it contextualizes
her well also admit i'm bringing her
into a comedy party or something that
i'm like this my best friend like
well she's not part of your your
regular crew right as well so it's
good to yeah like yeah let everyone
know if he jumped him severing relations
yes she's actually somebody else to fire
here's why she is worthy of being
yes yes i feel like it's it's
it is such a it's a it's
a thing you say when you're a
little kid yeah but
as you get older you realize that
really is a true thing that it's
a way that you feel about certain
people in your life that you're like
this these people are my best friends
and there's no other way i can't
stop i can not think of it
that way or did you how did
you meet natalie wearing hat why kindergarten
um we reporters questions actually met on
the fur
we already saw each other on the
first day of school because she we
are going into different kindergarten classes but
we had the same haircut
just grabbed his haircut a mohawk
so blonde bob with like straight across
bangs okay and we both just had
the same haircut and no one else
had this haircut i don't owe anybody
any standards sep for children was just
like when a bird sees itself in
the mirror it was kind of weird
i thought that we looked like and
i went i went to check here
but only for mike my mom took
a picture of me on the first
day of school and she's like in
the background with like oh what kind
of camera some bullshit fuckin was in
these camera so it was it was
it wasn't a phone it was like
she actually like brought a camera eight
i don't know we've never talked about
it we ah the regular cameras because
we can we talk about very briefly
you're not eight years old no i'm
not okay alright i'm just wondering if
it was like a disposable if it
was a you know like yeah it
it real real real camera real camera
cool that she would develop the film
at osco what year was
this but um this was nineteen ninety
period there yeah oh period okay so
nineteen hundred ninety yeah i remember cameras
back then yeah okay good stuff and
um we became wearing the same class
and first grade that's where we really
became friends and there you have it
so you guys what do you remember
talk
looking for the first time no i
don't remember any of my conversations from
that um age you don't you don't
have transcripts
read them back remember many of my
kindergarten track conversations i do i remember
my first conversation with my ah friend
doug
otherwise i still talk to you well
this is when i moved to my
new school so i was ah third
grade i was eight umm what's this
new school i wanted to school when
she's home i moved look i grew
up as everyone knows i grew up
in cypress california and i was right
there on beverly drive was dr beverley
and when i was
eight we moved can i tell you
something i didn't know you grew up
in cyprus i never would have said
that we all know this as we
all know i would've said orange county
joe brown listen yes you were born
in georgia though why do you always
always deny down there you make scott
to make scott
the devil went down to joe dad
to make stuff
end
and there was no battle no i
moved away from georgia when i was
six weeks old or so moved to
ah i think los angeles is you
get into that first second okay you
have okay you're i don't remember georgia
you're a young couple you have your
you knew else were you the oldest
sibling no so middle child you are
parents are a young com or young
couple yeah you have a child already
yeah you now have a six week
old baby and they're like move you
have to move well it's horrible it
sounds miserable my father was in the
armed forces and so for service guys
are you've never said that has you
haven't never asked me any questions about
myself
yeah
yeah that's not true my father my
father we did go there but there
are a lot of things scott that
we have to wait for you to
tell us okay okay my father was
in vietnam okay okay he went to
vietnam he wait he he signed up
before the draft in order to get
a good seat
like southwest on the way don't have
anything i want first-class vietnam know he
he wanted to he knew that the
draft is coming so he wanted to
fly helicopters so he heard that if
you signed up before the draft that
you had a better chance of flying
helicopters so he he signed up flew
helicopters and v
phnom ah um my brother was born
in sixty seven so i think while
that was going on i'm the dates
of vietnam are sort of fuzzy for
me but the like late sixties and
early seventies the fifth to the thirtieth
may yeah enough um it was quick
and so
so my belt long my brain and
out my brother was born in new
mexico okay hello education didn't change georgia
i was born in georgia then i
think he was out of vietnam and
so we moved away ah to ah
to california where he where he grew
up and met my mom back to
l a ah then then got to
get your mom after having you know
you know yoy yoy yoy yoy yoy
yoy yoy real real situation that he
grew up and met my mom
that happened to him he ah he
had a different ah he had a
different mother than than is his adopted
mother really adopted i she adopted him
but it's like no one cares about
all this stuff i do i'm actually
doing really okay well anyway we literally
questions and then you're deflecting he moved
out
he moved down to orange county because
from l a looking for a soul
to steal
and ah because the ah the the
what do you call it the the
the airforce not airforce base the national
guard station was is there an orange
county and he got he got a
yeah national fever
yeah to have it baby and he
got accepted there he got a job
there he worked there for many years
ah that's and and that's how i
grew up down there oh cool i
also just discovered that these pens can
bend and wow this is more exciting
than my story cool to you and
the pen at the same time and
i meant them both equally you can
ask me and then and then he
was in the
as as i've talked about my other
show he was in the movie king
kong because he flew those helicopters awesome
yes um i did have a follow
up okay now do you feel which
side of the war was yona vietnam
oh well that's very important he was
for charlie
do you feel like he almost was
killed i will say i found that
out recently i we had a long
car trip where i was moving them
out back here to california and at
the very end
like by the way here's something if
i was gonna kill say aiya christmas
i i took the opportunity to ask
him like questions about the work because
i'd never really heard any of it
and he did tell me a story
about flying a helicopter and suddenly ah
there there was a combatant who picked
up a machine gun and pointed it
right at him as he was hovering
there and jammed at
as he was firing right at him
and spitting in your life flashed before
his eyes right you'll never have to
go i gotta get back there i
gotta get back the emmys needs me
kind of leads me to a question
why do you feel did you ever
feel like a pressure to follow in
his footsteps at all or like even
just from yourself like oh i should
do something like that like because it's
so serious and well i think there's
a small bit of pressure of like
when you grow up in a family
you know that's in the arm for
cases where it's it's not even like
we i mean my grandfather also was
in the armed forces so ah and
in world war two so my grandpa
to ah my dad really yeah really
wow amazing but i don't think it
was ah you know being the third
generation i don't it wasn't like i
had pressure to like you should be
in the armed forces too because i
don't think my
dad ever even necessarily wanted that for
me i think it was more of
like the culture of like our enforces
like manly stuff yeah you know and
my dad is a is a guy
who likes art and and and stuff
so it's not like he's like you
know what do you do and look
at paintings or whatever but it's just
more more like you know hey can't
you like sports
or a little bit more like that
yeah but but not not too bad
yeah um yeah boy um my dad
because he was so much older like
military service was not a thing i
ever thought about my older brother was
in the navy um and he was
lucky that he was in it before
all of our current wow
wars yeah what year you got it
now that's like like back when you
could actually do it to get money
for college right right and he was
like later yeah there's very little danger
of you being destroyed over so yeah
yeah was this pre like ninety word
yes before the first gulf war okay
before the balkans ah that or i
think might have been pr
okay so i get like mid eighties
or something this is a good question
and wish we didn't honey i can't
i wish i had an answer for
everyone just be in their country and
be fine
stay there and don't try to come
into ours horse i remember my mother
used to say she thought that every
every i think every yeah every young
man should spend some time in the
military interesting i mean that is a
point of view it is a point
of view if you're not if there
isn't like conflict going on but because
it's like you're what you're just getting
trained on how to be like punctual
and yeah orders yeah make good harrison
and bounce a quarter
my brother and he's yeah any listened
to the ship right after all those
workers ah let's change the subject and
let's not say we did my brother
who does listen to the show right
hello hi i would say same his
name is mark mark mark mark f
tomkins mark
that's right oh that would be great
it's not my middle initial our last
name is f tomtom yeah tom he
ah you you are not you know
he's a good guy but it's not
like you would say well he he's
not the greatest he's the man he
is today because of the nature right
right you know what i mean yeah
would you say that though would he
say anything to the effect of like
oh yeah
it taught me i would save the
two years i'm sure he got a
lot out of it two years i
spent you will let me know in
theater school i learned how to be
punctual because at the theatre school that
i that i was at they they
drilled it into you that being on
time is five minutes early and if
you were ever they would lock the
door to the classrooms at the
the literal stroke of when it was
supposed to start and you the first
time that happens you were sent to
the office and the second time it
happened you were kicked out of school
ooh so i was laughing because i
was like did he i was thinking
did you like being drilled into and
then you said the literal stroke
nah man i know i couldn't get
him in your eye today your life
or your honey what i am know
when i o rez whoa i'm in
the freezer
yeah i was also letting you finish
so i'm not here to manage can't
stand with you
do you make so many sex jokes
because you're horny all the time yeah
maybe it's like awesome powers
but but i wonder if he would
if he would i wonder if mark
would say oh those two how many
years was there two three something like
that fifteen fifteen fifty though but i
wonder if he would say like oh
yeah i learned you know i think
maybe forty percent of my personalities because
of that
wow my personality percent of my personalities
before he was basically a show anyone
and got forty percent here he was
an amorphous blob in the navy made
him into a human being yeah and
he still wears a sailor suit everywhere
he goes well that's your panties like
daffy dates it's it's filthy it's just
tatar the only this one yeah
yeah when i was seventeen about to
turn eight
when i was seventeen about to turn
eighteen in high school um the army
recruiters would come around all the tours
seventeen going on eighteen and they would
tell you strung that one guy along
yeah they would take it would take
you out to lunch to turn yeah
you're enjoying all the stuff oh shannon
will come in at chow in this
spanking pen
come on show like you saw these
pens
i gotta get these up my butt
you gotta get up shoving you're wasting
no hold on hold on what did
you mean this is on the whole
spanking thing let's re-examine this because it
mean to wait let me come but
what if tied up what are seven
doesn't enjoy doing this seven do you
enjoy and whose big smile loves it
it's not about you know i kind
of enjoy it
it's it's competitive as a job yeah
cause i mean i don't enjoy my
job
it shouldn't be part of his job
to to you came up with this
i know
fine if he doesn't like to do
it yourself i will spank myself and
i'm gonna take a video no you
have to get dough i don't want
a video no one will believe you
serious still don't still photo no photos
or video boomerang no boomer
over
oh
the capital often the thing went flat
or across the room towards lauren okay
i call that a spanking fail would've
been different shaven spanking fail oh that's
a great playlist okay guys we need
to take a break doing we're gonna
come back and then we'll talk about
and being in the armed forces you
you're you're in the israeli air force
briefly okay we're gonna come right back
we'll be right back wards right
welcome back welcome back welcome back deck
we love you one thing i did
want to say about the helicopters because
my grandfather flew them and my father
flew them they both flew me in
helicopters growing up ah ostensibly as a
treat sometimes
and i would get very very air
sick and that's where i really felt
like i let them both down right
because yeah i just like like their
thing this is their thing they're like
hey you know i mean it is
kind of it i remember we went
to texas to carlsbad to the caverns
and all that my grandfather flew us
there and i was just like grandfathered
in i ran further into tech
ksas how it works and i was
just like i to go in without
a grandpa i dare type i fucking
dare you literally there and i was
just like oh grandmother oh tears
you know what do you ever say
you are worse than i am did
you know oh this is an interesting
question that he which of you is
whose mind is has been worse because
it's sick when he does it
yeah yeah do you ever does it
never did that ever make you think
that you are not your father's son
that your mother had an affair because
your i will say as your grow
my parents gave me my parents gave
me the twenty three meas stuff the
other day and that leads me to
believe that that i am truly
there yeah because i don't think you
get that from your parents unless you
you i don't know if you read
that i'm gonna give it to you
like they don't they're going to be
like let's show him the the yeah
well i don't know if you were
there was some twitter thread about ah
of a woman i believe who gave
everyone in her family twenty three me
stuff for christmas and suddenly the mom
started like
panic panicking and going oh we don't
have to do this you know i
think one of us go like why
don't we'll we'll just do it and
then you know it's a waste of
money if everyone does it right oh
my god and then suddenly like went
upstairs and started having like loud conversations
with her husband and then finally after
a few hours came downstairs and let
them know that they were adopted
oh wow
but they were like were they adult
oh and they were adults yeah and
they did not know that they were
dying just that's not right i don't
think i mean maybe not i don't
know i guess i can't say that
one hundred percent yeah it feels like
something that you should have the right
to know it never occurred to me
that people would not tell their kids
at some point that they were dead
i think it was that that was
just too but it was maybe now
feel that i shouldn't say that blanket
i guess
you don't have to yeah well i
suppose people like actually it's my right
now too and then i had to
like deal with i started thinking about
the i started thinking about the major
life changes or or things in life
that could be incorrect that you just
assume about i started writing about like
oh i a technically i wonder if
i could have a kid
out there and i started like going
through every relationship that i had and
you got to two and then you're
like dumb
oh ah but i started thinking about
like okay have had i seen them
after nine months after we stopped re
dating and have i seen you know
and i and i i think there's
like maybe three hanging threads out there
that like technically i could have like
a twenty
five year old kid out there somewhere
but i think it's very unlikely i
think so sure yeah i think so
but i know lauren like that you
wouldn't have that experience but um no
because i have a vagina
please tell us more no
um i don't even know what you
mean yeah but i mean yeah like
are there any but that's really wonderful
goodnight children you know if i did
yeah um but it's one of those
experiences i mean of like oh are
your parents actually your parents yeah it's
crazy because my parents did twenty three
and me and i just read those
results and that was like i'm fifty
percent of this
oh yeah um i we we did
it janie and i did it too
and it was very it was disappointingly
unsurprised i was exactly what we've been
saying yeah but yeah it was like
i was convinced though it was gonna
be some some something different i don't
know why on my dad's side i
was like i don't think we're as
irish as we claim
to be and then it was yeah
definitely was i grew up okay i
grew up saying oh yeah i grew
up saying i was german and polish
and i remember always having like deep
shame about the polish part of it
because of all the polish jokes and
when i was growing like that was
a big thing i would tell yeah
well for some reason that was really
big in the eighties doesn't it
i had a book why there's a
book yeah you could buy it like
airports and i remember having a book
that was ah it was ah no
one remembers jokebooks but julius were a
big deal there's a truly tasteless joke
book yeah this but there were a
lot of ethnic joke books and i
remember one that was um it was
an italian joke book on one side
and then you flipped it over
over it was a polish joke on
the other side and the joke part
of the joke being that the covers
on the wrong side because it's the
polish book right right
and i was like hi it was
so weird literally it was two books
i see what you're saying you flip
it upside down it covers going wrong
but i will show i see just
why do we hate polish before that's
that's the thing you really hate them
i could never figure it out because
no one i knew
it's more of a metric maybe it
was more of a metropolitan area type
of thing or or certain areas but
like we people would tell polish jokes
when i was young even though no
one we knew was polish like i've
heard things like that but i don't
know why i understand it as being
a part of the it's it's really
weird and it's weird how much of
that was just like oh yeah that's
fine i remember
reading some book of facts that the
same jokes that are polish jokes to
us in france are english jokes right
there they're just english people yeah every
culture has like has like the cursor
they ate yeah it was demonized they
say this guy's really stupid but anyway
so i always have big shame of
like people say what are you i
would go out german and then if
i felt like
you look violation i would say oh
a little bit of polish but i
guess because my parents did the twenty
three me ah it's mainly swedish or
something well you look swedish tomb yeah
you'll see that i did not do
my own because if i ever murder
someone i don't want that information came
out though that like the name i'm
gonna use the dna yeah for like
all sorts of stuff
incriminate people for murders i mean that's
kind of good i don't know i
don't like that the murder part but
the um ah
just the concept of murder that's kind
of good people kill me no biggie
what do you think about it guys
something we're using it also for like
like ads and like shit like that
where it's like you're basically using it
as sort of a um like way
to like demographic yeah okay but then
like using your data for like information
so they may be yeah but like
i but
it's all evil i think finding a
murderer is kind of a good thing
i don't really know who should get
away with so do you think that
the government you don't opt for do
you think this is a very childish
world i know who should get away
with murder and i think anyone any
thinking person or do you think the
government should have a database of every
single person's dna like
the moment you're born you get your
dna on file it's coming to that
don't you think no like big brother
bullshit they're gonna we're now we're using
our eyeballs to check it on a
plane like that's weird it is weird
i had you know we have an
alexa at home we have we've done
twenty-three me um i've given my my
fingerprints you know for t s a
pre-check though
the the final thing for me is
the is clear yeah haven't gotten clean
because i feel like ejaculate better what
do you have to do i'll be
if you go you can you can
go clean so you have to drink
lots of fluids yesterday and you also
have to become a scientist do a
retinal scan and it's like i don't
know why i'm dry i've given you
know given my already like but i
really draw the line at that
that what do you say pre-check is
enough of a pass through things like
you need to go so fast i
got to look at something and then
walk through like where am i going
like i'm always early for the airport
it's fine like i don't know well
maybe you could come late one day
and then just drink it with my
eyes and get on the plane thing
it was time you could say anyway
i don't know you've i kind of
feel like the older i get to
it's like you wanna go ahead and
have it this stuff is worthless enough
oh my info is worthless off surrender
you know it's like that's why i'm
saying i think it'll happen i think
it'll be a thing where everyone's in
a database i don't think they can
i think the governor i mean it's
the way i keep having psychopaths and
charge the problem is is we're giving
a willingly that's that's so that's yeah
exactly you know like
we're giving up all of our freedoms
well but because of our egos i
mean like twenty three and me is
like a fully like ego based ah
project well exactly also i love what
i'm like now over social media were
telling everyone where we are and what
we think all the time yeah so
i'm saying it's all part of it
is this the joe rogan podcast
i'm not saying i'm going to stop
doing any of that stuff i'm just
saying i'm aware do you remember dan
re i don't know if you there
for this conversation danna doute from jerome
data dude yes time isn't visually deliveryman
um yeah he is he's ah he's
iranian of iranian descent and he said
there's like in
iran there's different jokes about different regions
you know like like you would tell
polish jokes like lesson jokes and so
there's like one region where people are
really cheap there's one reason where ah
reach more people really dumb but there's
also a region where the thing about
them is they're scared scared so they're
easily
frightening yeah don't make your cowardly jokes
or the book slade is like this
person from here is scared that's funny
i had my friend in elementary school
i suffered from iran and then she
moved back and we were pen pals
for a little bit and she um
cut her hair to look like a
boy she'd like to like kind of
get like i don't even know exactly
what i was just like a bulkhead
with bangs oh yeah essentially i mean
now you're describing my shit noel children's
haircuts are excited
could i had a bob bob though
that is way more like that's what
i you said yeah yeah um anyways
but i just remember like very vaguely
this glitter issue talking about shit pretend
to be a boy to like get
through and do certain things in her
town whose oh huh i know do
y rural i can't remember i'm sure
i saw the letter so i'm going
to pretend to be avoided is
stand up to pee i'll find the
letter
anyway you'll find the letter yeah a
lot of you had a lot of
info i did and i save every
single year you still have already wow
where do you keep my parents' house
but my mom would love it if
i would take them also
i have a lot of them in
my house now how but it's a
hassle how many but it's a hassle
to take it out of your parent
yes yes shit like but where are
they boxes yeah i have a lot
of boxes like big um like rubbermaid
containers full of stuff could you digitize
them and that's more work oh shit
actually that's up
i can send you want i should
do i should send it to one
of those companies that does it and
then more i'm starting a company you
are yeah one hundred thousand dollars if
you wanna digitise hundred thousand it's all
lotta deal my friend
family discount i did do legacy box
for all my home movie what is
that i somebody had an ad for
it on a podcast and it's it's
they take your home movies from another
format and yeah format at all and
photos and everything great and so but
i sent in i had all these
like home movies that were on like
um v h s and also like
those small camera to view as a
child or yeah
yeah and then i'm just sitting around
right now oh yeah anything that took
place in my home
no i didn't even know what they
were really because we didn't have a
camera my aunt had the camera so
she gave me all the videos and
she talked about your mom had a
camera this is very pseudo camera which
there's different kinds chicken tikka tacos when
you make movies yeah have a video
camera and the camera there was a
potato oh you learned about it in
science class i saved him off
for christmas and showed everyone on christmas
the home videos oh really how long
was it um i wasn't able to
edit it because my computer kept freezing
so i just like was skipping around
to parts that i marked oh okay
cool and um dirty parts yeah the
dirty pots they already part um dirty
pop and it was very wonderful because
i'd never seen any of them i
didn't even know what they were going
to be and so
it was really cool i had you
know like sometimes i think people have
home movies that they've watched over and
over again like throughout their life because
yeah it was like a special we
didn't have him ever so i never
even knew and they were so much
cute stuff on there it was only
really sad it made me feel i
make you sad because it's just like
growing up as it's sometimes just da
so sad i could just cry it's
just so easy write rhymes looking at
like nostalgic things is like oh my
god oh okay yeah i would love
it if you cry okay okay we
need a tie breaker we'll wait and
we're tied i said don't cry music
crimes suddenly she's crying you guys stop
fighting um yeah
i don't know do you feel like
you look back at things like that
i feel wistful for youth that you
wish you could go back there and
you don't like being older i feel
wistful for it but i also just
feel like just looking at everyone it's
just like oh everyone's getting older and
it's like crazy and then see my
nephews who are like the age that
i was in the videos and i'm
lying and they're gonna be looking back
like yeah it's like too much too
are you are you not a nostalgic
person in general i'm very nostalgic oh
but i feel much that's the yeah
i think like really i'm like oh
i will if i see we didn't
have any home movies we have no
home movies but there's you know there's
obviously pictures when we were little kids
and obviously more pic
pictures of the older kids and fewer
younger kids know yeah my i think
my brother had a ton of pictures
and then i'm the middle so i
think i have like a few babies
yeah and then i jumped to six
or so yeah but then i i
i remember there were and i think
i may have talked about this before
i remember i got a pen ready
i remember bringing it
find things they would ah they would
like get out the camera because we
loved having our pictures taken but we
didn't have any concept of pictures getting
developed or anything so they would just
sleep them in real film in the
camera it would just be oh my
god why me so you loved having
your picture taken you just like the
original you for
get about it you know what i
mean yeah nah six years out from
no i do think it's weird that
little kids now can immediately see the
picture and they want to yeah i
think it's weird i think gives you
a weird sense of yourself from a
young age pile be really funny shit
future because it's like just because we
grew up having to develop pictures you
think everyone should have to know
ellen yeah but don't you think that
there's something about your the way self
is a strong stance but the waiter
ran away yourself esteemed develops without like
having a ton of mirrors cameras that
you're watching the video back and forth
like pictures that you can look at
directly after they take them so you
see what you'll like right now instantly
you think that you your self-esteem develops
without have
owing any concept of what you look
like to other people i think it's
better i think i thought i was
gross and that's fine but i had
to choose know your gross you're gross
i don't think it would have been
helpful for me to see a bunch
of pictures as when your brain is
really like developing when you're really little
like babies whenever want to see it
i'm like why do they understand the
concept of there being i hate
pictures of me we had um five
or six family photos you know like
every three or four years we would
go to our church friends who were
of ah he was a photographer we'd
go to them take the posed family
photo and we put five of those
framed in the hallway leading into our
house and i hated
because if you knew anytime i had
a friend over they would go through
that hall and they go huh you
look like a dork and i hated
those photos and it wasn't until you
get older you go oh those are
fine they're just like they're just kinda
young a moment in time lecturing about
but because you're like three years younger
weird thing oh no it's so embarrassing
like baby pictures and stuff when you're
you're still it's like don't look at
that but i also we went to
see her one time problem with that
i don't know what it is i
was a cute kid i don't know
what it is if it was here
whatever just you know a lot of
kids felt like that i think with
a big yeah that's so embarrassing my
mom has all these pictures up on
the walls yeah but why would other
kids make fun of the dork it's
fun
um
we have one where we went to
like sears or whatever and my brother
and i looked so we look so
dorky it's so funny to me and
i'm assuming we hated we were so
mad oh why are you glasses about
idea actually i think i didn't take
them yeah no i don't have em
yeah oh but my hair looks dumb
and like it's all like done or
whatever you're sorta like and yeah and
i'm like hey and
how like a really big overbite system
yeah my brother was like hating it
and he's like smiling like like like
will they be over yeah well i
also hated about the family photo part
of it is like invariably ah i
had poor relationships with every single member
of my family while we were taking
the picture yeah yeah so
like you like these people is just
exhausting or you think oh wait god
give me we did some sear session
where ss
we did this it's a real blir
stash we went and um ah i
haven't seen from this session the entire
family but i've seen a picture of
my mom with my three sisters and
my dad with me and my two
brothers and in this picture my dad
looks furious really it is she
feeling like i hadn't i'd forgotten about
it did you see the whole roll
and he was furious no three was
it was like it was just a
snapshot that was in with a bunch
of other pictures wow and i looked
at him like oh my god why
is the sun spread it's it's not
but who knows what happened right before
that i would take a yeah
just don't have one i have a
vague memory of it but it's like
i think i was i think it
was like after high school like i
think we were all like young adult
like my yeah there's no we're young
adults it's it's weird but hear that
it's just one photo that's why anytime
you see like a photo from the
white house or something like that where
people are like staring at the president
and they're oh
you can tell he's hates him or
whatever yeah it's like it's just one
image it says like two seconds later
he's probably smiling right but yeah i
hated going to those things in the
poses you had to do and the
put your arm on this and put
your arm on this but now they're
fun and ironic yes although i think
there are ten people who still do
it for real right i never liked
the ah
the school photographer like the the yeah
the hell i because i was i
was embarrassed of my teeth because i
had i had a gap of my
teeth and i had a broken game
for longest i had a broken tooth
for the longest time and so i
didn't want to smile with my teeth
right and so the the guy would
always whoever it was every year would
try to make my
i don't want to do it and
they have their stupid as york today
like bonuses if you smile there are
some i mean i think it's more
or is it just a pathetic you
know it's if you don't yeah not
now do like a thing where you
can pick what you want like i'll
give you three digital options or something
because maybe i hated that it was
very still on and done and if
you didn't like it like
you could do retakes and that's your
only other chance here i have i
did it there was one for my
senior portrait
that i actually see this shit there
huh
i love it and that phone huh
you look great i wish i looked
that good did you hate it yeah
i did what i picture i did
that was not like the one that
got printed up this was like a
proof yeah yeah yeah i hated every
single year the photos i hated when
they would come out i hated when
people would make fun of you after
they come out i mean ah
it was kinda nerve-wracking felt like that
was that was unique to me but
maybe it's universal but i don't know
i just felt oh i felt ugly
yeah i mean it doesn't help that
every single kid i went to class
with told me i was ugly and
said that andy was just accepted that
i was like the nerd and really
yeah
and the envy least desirable person in
my class well that's very hurtful so
we say this is why you do
this yeah hey i remember picking on
that about you being a weird combination
of ah excitement and dread like i
was very i like the idea of
like i'm wearing a different outfit
than i have to wear because i
went to school where we were younger
cats like yeah and there was something
about it that was like i liked
the idea i was you like peacock
think peacock so you were my very
last thing my goggles yeah steampunk goggles
you do card tricks it was like
a day where you'd be like oh
i gotta wear my coolest shirt
like the shirt i like the best
slipping a teeny black and white so
i need a menu i didn't know
how to dress and my parents didn't
know how to address me so it
was like ok let's go get you
an outfit for picture day yeah and
i never felt like i look good
in them they didn't you know what
i mean it was yeah it was
ah that's that's a very specific childhood
thing to when you
are you're trying to figure out your
own style yeah and also my dad
a little kid my dad because i
know that i don't want to wear
this thing you want me to wear
yeah my dad cut my hair until
i was you know fourteen wow whatever
and then i then did he do
like a buzz cut he would do
bowl cuts he would do buzz cuts
he would yeah and then i think
around four
these gods these nuts these nuts around
fourteen supercuts opened up on my block
and i was like oh let me
try to go in there and i
went in there and they gave me
like okay haircuts and then when i
was eighteen my friend who who cut
hair was like gave me a real
haircut finally when i was in college
he was like why do you wear
your hair that way
i remember yeah yeah yeah talks about
this so finally ill in your head
yeah so finally at eighteen i remember
i was working in knots berry farm
and i just graduated high school and
i saw some girls from high school
and i had my new haircut and
they were like wow you look really
good it was the first time i
ever felt like i actually looked and
could have been looking good yes this
is a thing appear
parents i don't care that you don't
know anything about fashion or whatever you
just don't understand hire a stylist for
your children all i'm saying is hire
a stylist for five thousand dollars in
one month and would it kill you
to get a publicist for your charm
yeah i know it was the point
of taking those pictures if you're not
going to get him out and pack
that label wanna see it yeah the
hell right
need to take another break we'll be
right back
welcome back to three-day you and me
it's time for us to play a
feature ah we have no choice we
have no choice but to play a
feature told you we will do it
every time so we're gonna do it
now this one is called how's yours
i think your prime law how's yours
or just keep it
laura just gave me a look like
place like sort of rolling her eyes
but then also like huh can you
believe i said you aren't i a
stinker you get a mammal it'll stay
cream colored track alright in this screen
game feature it's more of a feature
more of a feature that game um
a group of people that would be
everyone knows the distinction
ah this is going to be two
against one we team up against one
guesser to give clues that strike a
balance between too easy and too hard
it's kind of like twenty questions but
the only question the guesser can ask
is how's yours so here's what it'll
happen one of us will leave the
room i i'm guessing it will be
paul
um paul leaves the room or i
could cover my ears and hum a
tune it says good but i want
you to leave the room meanwhile lauren
and i will come up with something
that everyone the three of us has
owns or has a few examples might
be an email account a passport i'm
assuming we all have a passport of
astra i think we've all but yeah
we've all been out of the
entry together we all passports right we
yeah australia together strong or australia we
were down under a refrigerator or a
degree well why would everyone have a
degree that's a little rude that's really
elite game league game once we've decided
lorna and i decided um yeah paul
comes back in and approaches
approaches us with or or one of
us great trepidation yeah approaches scared like
someone from a certain neighborhood in iran
ah certain neighbourhood in iraq yeah we
take you now
so ah you approached us with the
question how's yours the question person i
guess that would be you come to
one of us gives a truthful clue
that will eventually help the guesser figure
it out but nothing too vague or
nothing too obvious the guesser is only
allowed one guess per clue given and
the guesser can either go around asking
if
fair circle or pick on people indiscriminately
for clues was only a couple of
us so vague clues like minds made
of matter or mine's pretty good are
pointless because the guesser will never get
any closer beings made of matter who
would say that nerd it's got if
you're close to obvious and the guesser
guesses the object on your clue then
you lose and you're the next guesser
if the item is a passport for
example you probably don't want to say
minus full of stamps why wouldn't you
say minus full of stamps well yeah
because there's already knew anything no one
else is full of stamps my spa
container boxes stay up in there at
them pretty fast better clues for past
budget tramp here's some here's their examples
of better clues for
passport mine might have been worth something
in the black market or mine has
an expiration date alright get out of
the room get out so now just
to just review the only question i'm
allowed to ask is how's yours and
you have to ask it to an
alternate and go back we assume you
have it okay
i'm not but just assume it's something
i'd have is something common that most
people have is we're not gonna say
it's something that all schools yeah it's
gonna be it's gonna be
so i can only ask the oh
yeah hold on i just want to
make sure the only things i can
do are i can ask how's yours
yours that i can make a guess
yes i think you guess every single
time there's no consequence of you getting
a wrong get out get the fuck
over one
i'm gonna take along
passport
sure we know i was thinking like
a dvd player oh great exactly it
should be a dvd blu ray combo
or
sure i mean sure okay or could
be known to save it so it's
okay but really yeah yeah we've hit
on something okay okay yeah amazon thing
huh
yeah turn those lights off so i'm
like making more romantic yeah turn the
lights off i like that yeah i
like those so much better so nice
and cool yeah no but now i
try to tell everyone for years you
did
how's yours
it's it's this she was looking at
me lauren i don't care
was so clearly i thought it was
at the group i didn't know was
literally looking only at
yeah i get where
your your siblings would think yay yeah
yeah i know i think it's all
about me baby that's the problem all
right scott how's yours it opens and
shuts
you can guess suitcase that's not lauren
how's yours
it likes when you push the button
left a like so we need that's
not a good clue laptop i know
what it is okay fine it's not
a guy and he does not like
it
keep lying
as far as it's part of these
guys who's happy to be truthful and
these are not anthropomorphic items as well
nine it's shiny shiny come get him
too close and one of their shiny
mine is i said laptop is that
not true no that's not true scott
how's yours
it breaks after about two years
it breaks after about not even true
ah have you ever heard of planned
obsolescence is booking yeah is it your
phone your cell phone no
how's yours it's black and
um
not the size read all over books
but not the height
wagons the size of a breadbox but
that's it
yeah we tell you about the two
dimensional properties of it yeah no way
bread but i'm like hello breadbox but
not the h
ah
come on so obvious
from from shiny don't you know this
is shiny and black
opens and shuts opens shuts breaks within
two years
because of planets lessons i just realised
that they are they're getting keeping the
power we discuss with it yeah the
audience knows okay okay it likes when
you push the button
yeah asking the question isn't guitar no
longer how's yours it's provided entertainment for
the entire family
is it a cable box ooh no
no no so close how's yours
it
it accepts
it accepts flat rounds
roush
it's
is it a t
yeah yes get out lord by get
out deleting yeah sips flat roads
no time for love doctor jones ah
what do you think
maybe one of the penis
she mentioned vagina earlier in the show
so yeah yes yes good catch maybe
piece of clothing
i can boot
a boot month or about a scarf
okay gva scarf masker i'm a scarf
okay sure why not start yeah great
barn
lauren is reentering the room
lauren sitting down and placing her headphones
how's yours
um
it's practical as a pencil
how's yours is prevented me from catching
cold
is it a jacket no this is
a jacket your dog ho shocking is
yours
it's
stylish is it a winter cap no
how's yours
my grandmother made it
wacha ny how's your its
scratchy that a quilt no
how's yours
it disguises my aging scarf yay howtos
howtos
a guy by
i can't really make it really fucking
hard okay
germany scars
oh my
let's make it
um
we've done clothing we've done electronic item
how about like a hamper
why not okay
yeah could be
ooh oh i'm da he's running around
the room
going crazy like a chicken with his
head cut off lauren
how's yours each toll in thin
is it a comically exaggeratedly large pencil
fuck no oh really
missing paul how's yours helpful
isn't one of those guards at buckingham
palace ny
aren't house yours it's it protects
it's good for sorting
huh
is it the sorting hat as the
wizarding world of harry potter everyone doesn't
have one of those
just you how's yours
it's used every day
sorting and used every day
sorting tall then used every single day
can you hear him no i can
hear is it a mirror no
lauren how's yours it's
used by the entire family
is it
he i have of her even know
i'm not even gonna guess paul how's
yours no cass well turning the game
on today see it's heavy sometimes sometimes
sometimes
sometimes only occasionally heavy so fu up
with water it would be heavy i
don't know what else could make something
heavy i guess
ah is it a scale some scales
are tall and thin lauren how's yours
it it it becomes heavier as the
week progresses
is it a trash can a recycleable
recycle oh you're not okay hello paul
how's yours
i mean
ah it's so
shh
it's handled
useless motherfucker
it's made of hand that old media
has handles on it zeh what i
mean
is it the rid the recycling no
oh it still isn't well i didn't
know if i was allowed at the
last time did you guys go away
lauren how's yours
it contains colors of all types and
shapes
flat rounds huh
fly around here fly around no he
doesn't accept it doesn't accept fly round
no no no no no it accepts
soft shapes is it the garbage disposal
no because that's not tall like although
my sinkhole ten sorting taught and used
every
de handles that's the gosh paul how's
yours
sometimes
it's smelly
got this it has to do with
the garbage and oh hey hey ask
me how mine is because the garbage
on the brain because it because i
can change something that might change lauren
how's yours it's not always taunt and
mine is tall and thin but some
peoples are short wide
this is a breadbox
no paul how's yours
it's tall and thick
it'd be something new it's mine mine
has wheels
i'll give you something new okay
mines hidden away
this is the garbage can i don't
know what else it could see okay
it's a garbage can of people
this is a coffin you don't know
if you have a maid
oh is it
do you mean a toilet garbage can
of people no way a vacuum or
wow think it has handles any short
and wide or tall and thin it
take accepts many soft colors it can
smell sometimes it gets heavier throughout the
week the vacuum
dude did
you give me some males come on
guys um and when it's empty you
got everything you need for the week
is it a shopping thing i might
try murder my wife and dogs yours
how's my wife and i each have
one of our own
this is mine are segregated by color
segregation
oh wait is a laundry hamper yeah
oh it's used every day smelly oh
we kid of people yes people think
i suppose garbage i don't use mine
every day sometimes oh okay you keep
your stinky yeah someday sometimes i wear
my underwear on my head okay well
that was far
less what a feature what a random
adventure how's yours and everyone can play
that at home you can play that
at home very easy vienna work and
yeah fired safely weaker
give me more time to listen
alright that's gonna do it for us
we will see you next time on
three-day oh
a