yeah
oh jesus
oh i know the song so well
that i was doing little noises i
say know all the words to that
song
i'm not even cheating i swell is
anyway you know what i want i
want lets you really really want more
musically inclined to go fuck themselves george
cover our theme song live yeah you're
in a band put it in your
set don't say anything about it i
want an acoustic version i want to
see like the deejay that you send
us doing the local car commercials i
want to see someone put it in
there d j said yes and hype
up the crowd
home from
okay we're almost too on the nose
exactly i think it would work yeah
but somebody doing it at a at
a show where people are not wanting
to hear our themes yeah i wanted
to go to number one on the
singles chart my emotions can handle the
moment where an a live concert venue
they start playing the three-time song i
no one reacts and i'm talking what
is
i'm ready for that i'm ready for
that i do also include a pan
of the crowd so that like me
one guy like i actually listened every
week i went to a weird al
show
ah without knowing that he was gonna
like little guy i went to a
weird al show without knowing that you
know how do you know you are
so strange and the songs were almost
like how they usually are like bad
but a little bit different i thought
it was we ertel yankovic
but i did not portmanteau game i
didn't know remember that he plays like
comedy sketches that he's been in you
know so he played something from bang
bang and i was in san diego
at a show and just watching it
eat shit was like wow so humiliating
to me which was not the big
ah the big hand well you know
he it's basically just like a mon
taj of stuff of like kim being
mentioned in the simpsons or him his
cameo on the simpsons you know or
like nuts for that yeah yeah pretty
good little history up on the wood
culture yeah cv
but to show a whole sketch from
the show and have people just laugh
stare at it just and a whole
stadium because to fuck with you he
he so mean to me he's mean
yeah i mean so many have you
seen them work in progress he's great
on that show yeah yes yeah yeah
groucho yeah i heard my job if
you had to pick one word you
know how we picked weird
yeah and you had to pick one
word to describe like i pay professional
now i'm trying to a closet of
words dumb lauren lacus
don't lauren dumbledore laccase like everyone everyone
on my mtb had to make one
word like yes huh word word darwin
no um i guess lovable lovable scott
and paul loud loud paul lad paul
f tompkins yeah wow both of tomkins
a few think of yourself as loud
um no not really do you do
you think you bellow take sol do
you think i bellow ah no it's
my reference idea what bellows
well you were making impression of me
well in previous episode and it's you
remember that bello usually last there was
a week ago same pressure ball oh
i'm just whispering hello
wow didn't even bellow
oh boy huh
a high moors bring it doesn't teach
during oh i'm always spraying do do
you think everyone who's ever had an
impression none of them gets upset at
it the first time they hear it
should i mean here's it's not upsetting
so much as it is it's shocking
like when you see
more than one person do an impression
of you and you're like i guess
there is a consensus in what i
assumed what i what i'm i was
actually wondering this the other day if
someone would do it impressions mean what
they wouldn't do besides when you're just
mixing hundred jackie kay well besides just
making fun of someone right um you
know i think didn't ashlyn be
b do it in like do an
impression of each of us isn't a
day she dubose very like a quick
kind of thing it was crazy it
didn't end up in and i was
doing character so i didn't get it
wasn't it wasn't during the episode is
when it wasn't during the episode oh
yes she didn't know much and made
a mean face when she did it
but but i but
i was listening to her impression me
i'm like i don't recognize i don't
hear myself in it because she was
like nah i'm scott and i'm nervous
hey really scared like he really he
leave it
have some choose
cheese i don't like that
i think i think considering that i
think she was trying to like capture
a flavor of everybody very quickly right
right right but it's hard it's hard
it's also hard i think um four
like male to female or female to
male to do an impression of someone
if if you can't get that same
tone it seems like it's easier to
do an impression of someone when they
are a comedian because they have a
certain cadence that they their comic cadence
that they've perfected you know actually yeah
but so like you know when you
hear someone do a loose gay
ca impression um you know like change
like like james honest yeah guy is
so funny not james austin johnson james
austin john yes yes he's so funny
and i have i've watched us and
ella every episode ever since ever so
i do watch it all the time
the coneheads hi come i get excited
i don't say i come i come
back i was gonna say but i
guess i come which is something i
want to say something else but i
ain't getting interested to watch him every
week and i can't just do he
doesn't one week his first week he
was so good and the next week
you can get to do it much
i was like we need more games
that people are here for jane music
is getting too much screen time i
don't know but the first
but he got to do like three
or four things debut episode and it
really crushed and it was her it
totally raw rachana ruled and he crushed
it and he just like judge judy
like hydra right she that was the
impression sanlu when i was in seventh
oh judy let's know i don't remember
now you said i was like ironically
i remember thinking on my leg and
tell me during my teachers those really
funny
lauren with you when you were a
kid if someone asked you to do
an impression would you do it or
you did you get shy about it
um i went off and end up
doing it but i would feel uncomfortable
at first but when we went on
this trip to england and scotland with
in seventh grade it was glenn share
what the fuck it was a special
trip it wasn't your family or the
school no it was a school trip
it was salt entire spleen on a
higher school
cool yeah i'm sure you had to
pay the money and you had to
be in the your head to always
have movies a book club saying that
we were in like a reading club
and it was like the only books
in england know what the fucking both
women whatever it was it was super
privilege for sure but i got to
go to england and we had a
tour guide who was this goofy guy
named parish and i was
as perry and i really hated him
and i was like why did you
hate it cause he was really annoying
and then i started doing impressions of
him and really liked what were some
of the sketches please be quiet stop
giggling
he was just a weird guy and
i started doing hi i'm penn i
killed with the impressions you didn't to
him or no no no he didn't
know he didn't know you think he
here is listening right now hi parish
or bing chow i think he's dead
god i hope not how old was
he he was young oh okay so
it's possible he was probably in college
and he hears your voice because it's
her that she's little child child did
bedevil to be ah was fun it's
very hard for me to not go
into by andrew lloyd webber voice but
i think the fact yeah so with
your live shows you were you did
andrew lloyd webber
wbur yes and are you going to
do a character every time or is
that just you just change it up
every time i'm going to say i
was thinking i'm gonna do a character
every time but i'm not going to
trap myself into doing that because then
i will start to resent a thing
yeah myself said oh it's it's open
it's like a good thing like doing
this show yeah guys i'm like it's
optional if i am i'm going
be on an episode i'm not going
to tell you why you sons a
bitches i throw my arms like tabs
real tired yeah coming over here and
i was like how am i going
to do it well we shouldn't schedule
these at like two in the morning
she is trying to gobble machine scott
i'm glad you brought because i don't
know why we agreed on that we're
all free of course anyone's still going
in there has like compliment
tos yeah oh see can you say
with say he's hunting
the other thing is is we said
we would only do them on major
holiday okay what are you gonna say
you you are home and you're like
i don't wanna go i don't want
to go and then they were like
you know what i have a great
time which i don't know i do
have a great time every time no
i i was stuck by me wow
yeah parrish
pippi
yep
i say it puts a pit in
my dog to be a quiet little
girl i've tried to do the tour
yeah absolutely yeah he worked track jackets
now do you like anfield i think
they were just track rivers just track
yeah his name was reverend
ah um reality recap yeah who's watching
the bachelor it ah it's boring i
know and she's so great yeah she's
so great great but it's such a
boring seat it's a really boring season
and the guys are random as hell
if i do they're all random is
it open by now by the time
people were listening to this oh no
i don't know if it is just
end before christmas
who knows maybe it ends on christmas
that would be great that makes everything
fun for the whole family to watch
yeah out of respect to who people
tend to people or jesus or earth
fare like look yeah you should have
a nice christmas season we're gonna end
the bachelor before that starts yeah if
jesus was real and do we all
agree that he was real you keep
bringing
you want to go to church son
do you or do you have to
go to church this christmas season right
now i haven't had to go to
church since i was little yeah so
much time so much time wasted there
yeah i honestly didn't waste too much
time there i did a few you
know major holidays a little sunday school
as a kid i did a few
meet and greets a bit say yeah
remember to pause take a few ins
early sunday school for like two seconds
i probably wind so much that i
want darned and then i went on
christmas eve and easter and that kind
of thing and then by that point
i was like i'm not going and
nobody could convince me otherwise yeah sure
that you know how everyone gets religious
when they get older so they they
turn sixteen
and you know just on famously the
opposite she got last religion became an
e she got religion less raw dough
is more special right for your dad
looks you're putting in all that time
about heaven and what yeah yeah man
shy she like it started thinking about
the iraq war this was in the
inches like why would god do this
during the iraq pretty much she was
like this was during the iraq war
yeah
just like hey you're saying this is
the mid two thousands because yeah for
like i mean that's when she was
she was thinking about it as it
was half right right that's what i
meant right
oh it's it's like trying to tell
people when the war hey guys in
case you haven't heard about a world
record that happened in the two thousand
um and it just said a study
saying wow
um so she was trying to think
about she's trying to she was raised
to believe that god had a reason
for everything yeah she was trying to
think about what reason he could have
for the iraq war and she had
a right to take she was like
thinking all night it just like unravel
because it's like that's i think that's
really interesting because if you if you
think god has a reason for everything
it's fine that the war was what
finally did it for her but like
i'm sure she witnessed a ton of
bad stuff it isn't the reason isn't
the reason that free-will like he gives
us free will and so bad stuff
has to happen in order to have
free you know what else that's the
only thing is that you don't think
about it
too much yeah i mean that's the
only reason the sentence right that stuff
yeah you know because if you get
into all the horrors and hurts like
why would this happen yeah it's that's
hard yeah it's hard when he's when
bad things happen and you don't have
a reason why it's a devil's advocate
where he's like he made a church
follow all the believers right a church
fell on
all these believers the devil it's not
mr beale hs elba bill maher did
it it wasn't it was not mr
bean because it was not that was
out tareen there's no church over v
if mr bean was in the devils
that sounds like something he would do
that clumsy and very clumsy or trauma
turkey on it comes into using of
the friends
to me when friends did that friends
did the same thing mr beeman did
the mr bean gag with rock yeah
um that's a clamp doing that but
i mean how do you fucking funny
mick yeah how do you revise the
way i think of it as a
friends bit it's mr bean and you
in the field of comedy i know
should know your history
and now it was it was i
mean when i saw that movie at
the galaxy theatre man it just brought
down the house it did and those
repeat gag yeah cheese the friends na
movie is just called mr bean movie
thing it was called bean i think
wasn't a thing yeah only i was
just reminded me i god think that
you ain't a pain no i was
when i was with some boys in
middle school and we got tickets to
see bean who was not into it
i was with some boy you said
you were going to go see bean
and you saw something we rarely pretend
to see beans so we can get
the tickets and then we went to
something our raid what did you see
it but i need to know it
was out at the same time now
you probably know okay you know anybody
irl intentions are some
shit well that was probably e g
thirteen krillin tennis pg thirteen probably right
i don't think they mean what anybody
might want to they want to cruel
intentions was rated a little hold on
did you you just want to see
those two girls keys current dishes ready
to the line of spells right now
but um what was out when bean
was in theater
others humming starts being what does this
mean movie theater didn't see it snuck
in being moving cruel expression eats weekend
the google really b-movie didn't see it
it was released october seventh nineteen ninety
seven october seventh go to nineteen ninety
seven in films
um okay wait because i want figure
it out go to nine nineteen ninety
seven and film go down to october
seventh you'll see what's out at the
same time october seven slate nineteen seventy
oh wait this is like a special
website no one in wikipedia nineteen ninety
seven in film in film there you
go boy this
is riveting podcasting i think it is
because it's like an a mystery that
must be solved okay well if they
okay wikipedia has like every movie that
was listed in a year by the
date oh okay hold on hold on
so the contain seventy five and you
go down to like wide release movies
every this every single movie then go
down to october bean
hello we can cut this out of
for him but i am picking good
love you guys okay so hey bean
heads oh why didn't release movie again
this then we can go get down
to feeling like a minority report over
wiping everything lesson right everything is shoulder
high as well we got a red
ball wow red ball
the color red give me the red
ball red ball red ball red ball
thank you to rebel rebel rebel
rebel okay so here's what was out
um lima bean bean by the way
i don't see being on october seventh
john seventeen she's seventeen okay here we
go he was so here's what was
out october seventeenth bien my brother best
men know the devil's advocate now
a yeah okay la la why wait
that is weird that is where the
weird talking about being in the devil's
african i got a chill that's crazy
cool back here is up
i know what you did last summer
that's it that's yeah it is scary
to booze yeah
but wasn't that it's rated r that
might be what it was that's probably
rated r just because it's yeah it
probably had a gory thing in it
but i think of those movies is
like pg thirteen because nothing really just
gravies i'm just scared for stupid babies
who are thirteen years old oh my
god if your thirteen year but baby
if your there this year i'll be
believing and yet so it is rated
r so would you
think of it when you can hear
a bit of mr bean did you
have to okay this happened to me
when i went to see mr bean
over cost a murder in one of
his skits i hope so but wasn't
that the most fun when you would
buy a ticket or something else then
go to something but oh yeah but
so did you have to come up
with a cover story because i remember
this happening to me when i'm pretended
to see what sweeping many filled the
room i'm frenzy
okay good
i don't care about being
i pretend to see gu li's and
instead what i saw already came out
of the toilet cause i was only
other poster we had to like talk
to friends about okay what happened in
ghouls in case they incase she goes
so how is gewesen you go huh
i was alright and she goes well
what happened in it you know and
then you gotta go well the ghouls
came out and i tried watching coolies
the other day by the police kick
but can you imagine
what happened in it is that just
a way to make sure you actually
make sure you actually went to a
yes so because my pins on the
parent mumps very suspicious and she should
because you were lying cheating that she
was right little people around you know
but i do remember this at this
particular time all my julie's information went
to for not because she did not
care if i'd seen ghoulie yeah but
um yeah you had to
prep so did you have to prep
about bean i don't think i did
i don't think i didn't a bean
prep um i stopped being an hour
say it like that i took the
movie bean in a bowl of water
for four hours and then i put
it on the stove
and by then it was all as
moses from there buddy
and you live in saw as moses
jones and i didn't and i said
that part was good when the thing
happened do you think anyone's ever seen
that movie
what about orlando jones maybe he did
think he was one himself and was
like oh i got to see i
wish there was a way to know
what the least they can smell like
teen movie that was famous but um
the movie that was most i was
a popular film yeah i got the
lowest box office yeah that they've they've
they've put that i think
we i think we saw feel like
i remembered what held that title at
yeah because we like because we rented
rented a theater to watch it because
we made a whole bunch of jokes
about it oh shin during the mtv
awards ah it helps ah and well
jason masuk has kept writing jokes about
this one particular film and it was
um it's animated god what was it
and we rented it and we were
like chacha shit no he made so
many jokes about it and were crying
laughing about it was like familiar i
remember and we were we were like
let's rent it and then it turned
out to be a bummer to watch
but um because it was just bad
it was the cowardly little toaster
yeah that's not it that was that's
not new at least not the one
that was pretended to be dead so
that it wouldn't get hotel software dad's
friend he's like main chords frayed it
won't work
anyway da delco that was it still
go oh we made so many jell-o
josh so many telugu jokes and we
rent a doe who just emailed us
well go formerly known as del close
i'll still go about i don't remember
delco eight you baby
i got to write it down though
because i don't think it's on my
list of movies i've seen delco florida
only loses it to the second del
went down one day without the joe
rogan
more like dell far more like delgado
more like dell didn't see more like
delgado worn thin and spanish more like
dude did you see delco no of
course you didn't because no one dude
where's my doggo dude where's myself though
isn't it my ashton kutcher
is it in my ashton goodyear like
we still playing that game from the
last time i honestly am keeping like
i can't stop alright we take a
brain disease can't stop won't stop we'll
be right back can't stop being is
okay and when you go outside you
are there
alright we're back we are back and
paul's got funny glasses huh
but he glasses on i'm a mysterious
character who am i your friend the
guy who says dr jones mister magoo
may i tell you a story about
mr magoo i'm taking i would love
to hear a story about mr magoo
do you remember the late lamented jumbos
clown room yeah where the city's hang
out
the tidies just hang out more
just hang out and have fun because
i didn't it was a ah a
sort of indie strip club in la
where it was kind of acceptable for
you to say to like if you
were dating someone hey let's go to
jumbos that sounds fun so turnitin sometimes
it will be your person's idea yeah
cheney was a big fan of jumbos
clown right so clubs are a blast
well not really for men we had
a great timeline oh yeah we went
to one in san francisco gave me
a sec i remember that through it
all i gave you some yeah it's
really fun
i've been to
maybe somebody gave it to you as
a gift now thanks so what did
i know these tax okay did i
have it ready or did i go
to the atm to give it to
you i don't know but i was
because i was doing a lot of
money and then you gave me money
through i think he went guy i
remember hearing about this and i was
also very very dirty he wanted it
to be thrown but you didn't want
alright when you guys hatched the scheme
to go to this place were
you there yeah it's the oldest woman
doing with this guy you know because
i went back to my hotel
why did i even go i don't
remember oh you got no gas at
each other up like always fios dave
is dave tony i remember him yep
and he was on my whole team
mangos your whole team and i don't
and and so we went with us
somehow i remember ah yeah cool yeah
someone was telling us about what maybe
it might have been um
ah thomas lennon no no no no
um i'll i'll come back have to
but um it goes in a barrel
it calls for possible but it's ah
the specific ah the specific type of
wood he's still it's cherrywood it looks
like mahogany cherrywood
um yeah i remember that marc evan
jackson remember that time oh he was
that he wow that really sounds correct
yeah he was there i think it
might have been him and so we
had a long ass conversation where we
were drinking and then we went to
that strip club which was across the
street or down the thirteen i was
later to it we overt we whoever
we i actually got in a new
kitten
q v so excited yeah we didn't
sep uber yeah yeah yeah and why
were we all there sorry sketch fast
talk but what shows
come we go when your entire life
oh you know why it's your blog
i'll do it
and
and what did we were laboring comedy
bang bang and when i get home
um and i was bang rang oh
mister magoo yeah as i write so
we write about what when i started
to what you were doing you put
those goggles you know right richie mccaw
famously did not use anything to say
he should have he didn't have glasses
that didn't work no he didn't
smell magoo at those famous broken glasses
i'm in jumbos clown yeah you at
the start of every cartoon is like
i broke up again so i'll just
be walking around it's just annoying like
like backstory they have to fill in
every time you don't think ever happens
to be i don't know why even
worry about but when you see someone
with like fixed whole body original mr
bean that's true
when you see someone thick books are
difficult mister before that don't like standard
comedians when they see someone with thick
glasses in the audience go look at
mr magoo over here yes they do
but he doesn't have glasses so no
he says he doesn't this is where
we got to uncover this week so
it's online here i am james conroe
i'm standing by the bar one of
the dancers gets upset
wait she's collecting tips from people she
sees me i'm wearing glasses she's walking
past me i give her a tip
she does like a double take looks
at me she tells my hair and
says oh mister magoo wow
so it is a glasses but if
you if people need glasses that makes
them mr magoo
that's a funny thing to say to
somebody it is it is money to
say okay mister magoo yeah that is
funny it's he says people with lower
because the the words are funny and
it is funny to say to somebody
without glasses too yeah yeah mr magoo
they're like why because you don't have
glasses like good huh
anyone with how close this game got
when you were on set and you
were looking at your phone it was
like so with your whole arm someone
should've gone okay mister magoo now someone
should have yeah especially because you were
i would have hired there and you
want a murder that was being but
this guy did you fire someone for
being rude to for being rude i
there are a few times where i
should have
yeah and i really regret not doing
it but i didn't want the confrontation
or whatever you know i just heard
on deep dive podcast shop with jessica
st clair and june diane raphael raphael
is that they were talking about the
advice i believe is from june's father
which was or maybe it was jessica's
no justice if if you have the
urge to fire sir
someone do it the first time you
get off that because i lurk get
better from that point i learned to
talk about that all the time i
mean i don't really have a lot
of people that i could fire but
yeah i remember one show that we
did the show that between different started
on it was it eben was the
musical director hitch letter i should have
fired his ass for no no no
no no so he was not even
as a joke i guy he put
together a band and very talented musician
very talented musician he put together a
band that was the live band during
the show i walked in and he
was like doing sound check and it
was me arriving and he had been
there for a few hours doing soundcheck
with the sound guy and i'm like
sitting there and this is the first
day
on said i haven't met any of
the crew or anything i'm sitting there
i'm like bopping along to the music
and the sound guy looks over to
me and goes this guy your friend
and i go yeah he goes get
better friends
yeah yeah and i'm like what and
i go what do you what do
you mean and i guess they'd been
having a disagreement about the sound or
something and i'm like why should hire
this guy but then i was like
no no just calm down the guy
was the worst the entire show and
during the actual show in front of
a live studio audience was taught
being so loud to his buddy that
the audiences like going what they're like
league there and he's a sound guy
it's very rude to say is this
your friend and you say yes and
then you continue to say something rude
yeah and he didn't know that i
was the executive producer of the show
oh okay i didn't know who i
was um yea all he knew was
you are a human being and that
wasn't enough yeah but that's
an insane leap to make like now
i'm gonna say this thing yeah dusty
so it was he the sound guy
for just a music or for the
show for the show okay so that
was that was where i was like
you know what and it's happened to
me a few times since then i
haven't learned my lesson where it's like
if someone is a problem the first
time you meet them yeah they're there
it will affect their work as well
you know what i mean so now
yeah but i just don't like firing
anyone so i just haven't i haven't
learned my lesson fired one person i
think was i fired a manager and
it was nervewracking however five shots when
i fired my manager i was in
tears oh god i cried it was
horrible because he had like helped me
and
and loan me money to get me
out of debt and stuff like this
and and he didn't that's why i
fired him he totally got it and
you me like five thousand dollars this
is my problem and i'm making your
problem give me five thousand dollars or
else i walk around yes no he
understood and he was like yeah i'm
not i'm not right for your manager
anymore but that's happened a couple of
times where people's like like he
he's one of the big creators of
game of thrones you know so it's
like well he his reward a totally
different direction of that he doesn't you're
wanting this is your ex manager yeah
he created i'm starting creators executive producers
still pretty lucky yeah um june was
telling us about firing her agent on
her podcast and this and she said
she sent a very
strongly worded it well strong and that
there was no arguing it was just
our relationship is terminated i didn't mine
in person because we've been together for
a really long time and it just
wasn't working for me anymore and i
felt like i owed that it didn't
feel right to do it over the
phone and it was fucking horrible i
like went to his office and yeah
you know he didn't want me to
lie
leave the gino's coming or no no
no i feel like my new
it was coming and so didn't you
know so it was fine to be
a call but yeah it's a bad
i mean you know we're did i
never thought in my life i'd be
in any position to be firing right
way where three horrible bosses because they
made that movie about us wait they
should make that's well anyway they may
alone but this is laws of the
bin mazes rpo he made what is
this is our preamble for firing josh
by the way yeah what's your heart
not easy for any of us and
we are gonna cry ah but we
want in person we've made this whole
fake episode just to fire you so
let's make sure feel good right do
you remember on bang bang there was
a scene where um it was it
was supposed to be an emotional moment
on the show this is one of
the ups i don't remember any
that you weren't there do you gotta
do a newcomer
i was unseemly be the podcast there
was an emotional moment on the show
yeah yeah the director said
why would they have doing newcomers when
you were filming the show that's not
it doesn't make sense i'm saying do
newcomers about comedy bang duh you don't
give a shit about it i've never
seen the program it's not true i've
seen a bunch using the two you
are on no i've seen more okay
some money yeah yeah i've seen clips
ah i see a lot of gifts
i haven't watched all hundred and whatever
episodes i'll say that yeah and yeah
yeah multiple times i had to do
getting loose yeah
i do know some people who have
shows
who acted them they're the creator and
executive producer and then they go okay
put it together and then they never
watch it after the weird when you
five minutes know how it was because
there might be stuff you find annoying
no they do not care i've never
quite understood that anyway so emotional millennia
mon mome on the show and then
one of the guests said who is
actor said umana cry and everyone said
went whoa and then that actor called
their makeup person over who had one
of those blowers
right those don't work on me they
don't tell me either it drives me
cray cray if you don't know that's
a thing that you spray in your
eyes um and it it's like somebody
even sprayed a menthol lower and someone
comes up and blow the tube into
your eyes yeah and i it does
not do anything i've used the fake
tears or whatever those don't even exist
oh yeah englishman i can yes it's
brutal because it's so unfair if they
weren't real it's like go you can
just be crying oh yeah oh yeah
yeah some people expect you to be
able to cry on cue and that's
such a weird expectation yeah never understood
anyone who can
i mean i have i'm sure i
told you the story that breaks so
it's okay right with whichever i find
out what's the matter he's crying with
just yeah is he doing acting okay
he's trying to cry i'm trying actually
zack can have it has never did
that to him yeah
yeah boy
ah did it during a dramatic dramatics
that is like one of the funniest
people on earth once you agree i
don't agree one of oh my god
he's so funny but yeah it's really
weird when you go of the funny
because just just give me just give
me a second and then he'll just
sit there and then suddenly like a
tear roll down his face it's like
how are you doing me of something
sad or is he just
i'm able to control i don't know
oh don't cry
did you see that episode of the
other two were drew tarver cries at
the end it's like supposed to be
like um call me oh yeah i
did yeah it was wild but he
really he was really crying well he's
got a lot to cry about yeah
people like us you know it's like
hard for us to cry because we
generally think
if anything saying we have such love
in our lives has never been said
anyway the bed nope nope nope nope
try we we got to cry during
this show you know what i even
done the recent episode that came out
i said i don't want to cry
yeah show by the way i think
i i've started crying on two of
my last scott hasn't seen show
no one would marry and one what
was making you cry because i was
talking about that goddamn song again when
i brought up on this show bbq
stand my way
the applebee's cookie oreo shakes oh no
no no this the the brad paisley's
i i've talked about but okay yeah
because i mean country playback singers the
adoption the adoption he didn't have to
be i started talking about the the
whole reason by that because mary was
like why anyway but yeah ok don't
get into it but i am making
a country place
this and i got so many submissions
for my instagram story that i cannot
possibly go through them all i screenshot
like a few pages to mine i
did because i think they put people
that i follow at the top mine
was a good one yeah not not
like a bad one what was it
again anything by ah bobbie gentry
okay well i'm gonna start putting the
list together and i think the thing
is my actual interest with country is
the really bad country that's coming out
nowadays where it's kind of like um
there's like a remix element to it
sort of you know i just
it's via the oreo shake guy because
in all of a sudden in the
middle he has that hip-hop be going
boom boom that's the kind of thing
i like that shit what's the name
of that song because i think a
lot of people in ramble bees and
the milkshake and stay around and we
get baked in the road and that's
how we like it
i'm gonna play it i do like
the recent cool up in fancy like
i think at this chancellor suggestion a
few to have and i were talking
about the recent ah yeah i don't
know if it's a trend but ah
or at least something that's happening which
is good about um black people are
being country stars yeah yeah i'm getting
into this because dancing with the stars
yeah allen i think it is yeah
he's got so i started listening to
it yesterday on the american music awards
there were like two other singers that
were okay here's the song charlie pride
pioneering black country artists right
guide to povich at the hundred years
i don't think the songs to country
music he got covert and i don't
think be playing under those thing she
still remain wow wayne go going green
take out most brick of brain lol
she wanted item fries and a frosty
so this song is basically all about
pow
normally they could only afford to eat
at wendy's sure but on date night
they go to applebee's right guy
and they got his name the shy
or you was the last time you
think this guys doesn't either of those
places so shy he might probably the
day before he wrote the song and
then he's never been yeah does applebee's
loved that they must love it gotta
love it because it makes me want
to go to applebee's even though i
can what was the last time
you ever went to an applebee's i
told you that so i when i
had a gift card to applebee's and
i was with i think i told
us laura wilcox and i were in
austin texas doing an all female ah
improv festival and we were really broken
we brought sounds like peanut butter i
used to pick up chen bread to
our hotel that we were eating mostly
peanut butter
sandwiches we were making but i had
this gift card for twenty five dollars
to applebee's and we were like let's
go use it we took a possibly
one or two buses and then we
walked on the side of a highway
and then we had applebee's and we
probably both had hershey squirts and then
we came home
right i bet at all female last
time i remember an all-female improv festival
has to just be filled with hershey
squirts na boy example bees i think
i also ate there actually weirdly i
think i also ate there with mike
when he was meeting my parents when
we never go to apple in chicago
yeah but it was it was like
a random thing we were doing so
it was just a we never got
to eat at all and we went
to applebee's and then and mike tried
to show my dad that he was
learning lithuanian and my dad was like
oh no he said something else i
knew
my dad goes no
wow now and then early but they're
they're the best friends they went to
cambodia together they went to cambodia together
and containers going um i think you
would like marin morris somebody that you
should get hi i'm aaron morris is
great she's one of the highway remember
all she's one of the high women
what's that like the high women put
down
hi women brandi carlile brandi carlile you'd
love to mostly we just saw her
guys on the beam a r c
i may arrow in m a r
c
w t f m a r o
n okay i got it i got
it i'd follow um yeah aaron morrison
and the high women so already finale
of dancing with the stars did you
watch it yes i lie my way
to the jiggle
are you here this time reality rico
it's your segment we recap yeah so
the other starts watching every week i
love it so much just umm aiman
this is the only surgeon we've ever
watched my way he won
he went on cheung part in my
ma david bowie zima that's the only
amount in my life ok he is
fantastic his dance to this house freestyle
style of us the movie oh yeah
the us that's an dad was oh
my god they did like a horror
nights following year's halloween mckinley did a
whole us dancing you don't know
i'm gonna turn into later it's fantastic
they didn't do much for me they
shit out dirty but it was my
favorite night i got such a crush
on i mean was so fun to
watch he was so like happy and
like being really funny and like having
good timing earnest and like really good
dancer it was just gracious basically you
and i was you know i've talked
to nikki glaser about this but like
would you go on dancing i have
said
i say to mike all the time
i would like to be on dancing
with the stars i think it'd be
really embarrassing ultimately i think i would
because you ready so bad but there's
why do you think you'd be so
bad though i don't know but there's
two types of dance that i think
are fun that i would like to
do cha-cha jive okay and then that's
the other one that's really fun like
that
if you remember but there's another one
that's kind of foot master okay yeah
and i think that's really fun when
they're like kind of like put up
a football but i like but but
what if you were good like you
couldn't be as bad as the worst
guy this year well yeah because i'm
i'm a performer i would at least
like be trying i just don't know
that they were good they work with
you to such an extent that maybe
you'd be good i mean nicky
a glaser talks about how how hard
it was yeah i think physically it
must but don't talk her out of
how bad she might be i think
you will be done
i think paul and i are never
going to get the call never you
are the only person who's going to
call it for us right now i'm
intrigued what so what is our colors
are almost over oh god oh what
my life is what makes you think
now does she she likes it she's
glad she did it she pitched she
pitched ah
she's often pitched the producer's like doing
a best of the worst season because
she got kicked out first yeah sure
which is just humiliating but um but
yeah i mean it's i mean that's
what's weird is like on her season
she happened to be kicked out first
like this year the dude from cobra
guy was so fucking bad which links
you know
the the tone crease yeah crease what's
the actors name i can't remember but
he he didn't even dance he basically
walked around the room pointing people
it was like to that but like
melora hardin yeah he was losing some
guys im on fellow what does these
guys play play oh okay he's great
i'm going to send you the dance
how tall is he really tall six
probably five and then his partner was
five five i heard that tall people
can't dance very well that's the things
about he wrote because it was just
his frame the nba players are honestly
usually really bad because they're endearing but
they're they're not um fluid in the
way that you think because their center
of gravity's in their chest i don't
know well it's their center of gravity
is usually in the basketball that they're
holding but a monsanto but so what
mom is the first
the enemy of human they let him
hold a basketball the entire time that
he was dating this coaster one one
bomb i feel like i'm all caught
up okay fine we have to talk
about it for another year you wake
up no i like that show it's
a good show i used to watch
so you think you can dance oh
yeah
that was cool i loved that make
leads to watch this guy got him
into dancing with the stars so let's
all day i mean i was horrible
at dancing alright la la la but
let's get onto gosh
see this let's get on dancing with
the stars as a trio um what
if we add and then we have
we have to dance it we have
to dance with three other three professionals
all in a circle do you ever
feel bad for josh it's interesting you
look over and just go poor josh
listeners toxic he has food he has
fun what about the listener
listener it's different than these
yeah that's about it
um i also tv recap yeah textures
back i loved who gives heads i
love dexter as my favorite shows oh
my god you are the monster that's
what i'm here chose too much and
the new one is good
dexter you're talking like texture did you
watch six feet under yeah i love
six feet and a good i didn't
like sixteen fucking orologi all of it
no you didn't need it i watched
every episode maybe i just loved the
last i didn't like it but here's
why i didn't like it you didn't
like leptin know i love the last
i still think it's one of the
best episodes episodes one the best episode
tv has ever been
what are the best episodes even if
i would say man the last episode
of comedy bang bang like the two
last step sounds or if you watched
it all you will be sobbing paul
didn't tell wow but ah the reason
i didn't like the show is ah
first of all um dysfunctional family not
always fun but i'm not
baby i can watch a show like
that sure but the thing that bother
me about it was that gay people
the gay person oh well jada husband
how do you meet whom you don't
think that sounds good about it was
they never had moments of unity among
the siblings or solely with my mother
real ever like you know what i
mean it was like mature jackie that
would have made it like they just
hate all hated each
other all the time and it was
it got to be very depressing from
always like nate like there was love
for nate every day spoiler alert sorry
you've had your chances you've had your
teacher try jazz to me your jantzen
your jack get another nar nar i
like
good to see peter crouch on other
shows because then he's not dead anymore
sure has he ever done anything is
oh my god as good i don't
know but he's had a lot of
stuff he's nine one one oh paranoid
who's gonna you know it's nine what
do you like okay so you don't
like watching shows where i don't like
it when everyone just hates each other
all
the time right well that's what your
you'd like ted last show yeah
david had to turn a guy into
a villain on that show wow they're
likely to be realise that everyone's do
nights we gotta make this one guy
bad now i'm watching
ah well if you if you had
a show yeah and i think you
should
if you had a show like would
you and you what what kind of
family dynamics are you interested in exploring
i think the family dynamic i think
first of all i think most families
are dysfunctional i think and more people
you add to them the worse it's
gonna get right um i think that
i like to see the alliances that
people have that's more
interesting to me because people team up
yeah on each night shifts you know
like depending on the situation like things
move around like six feet under that
a little arousal sister sometimes they were
they always liked each other but i'm
trying to think of other shit like
to transparent do that a bit about
what i didn't watch much of that
okay but i think
paul i was thinking about this the
other day i think you should have
a show what should you think that
should be it should be called mister
gould and you do not have classes
and everyone understands it but is he
looking for glasses what does he want
he is you and you are looking
for mister magoo i am mr mugu
but i'm looking for mister mean you
don't realize
lies that you are because you can't
see looking for measurement error i would
know there is yes the body swap
and you won't look down but i
don't know mr magoo you don't know
your mister magoo i don't know mr
magoo but i know i have to
find me because it's basically you saw
a sign just like mentoring mister magoo
so i could see the sign the
movie's called missing mr magoo momento now
it's ah it's not true anymore
no
an experiment to movement it's a theme
park
alright we have to take a break
yeah
and we're back and i want to
be a little game called three teacher
and this will be my future
awesome that we do we play together
to wrap up the shoe and this
one is called name that one word
mano tune name that one word mano
to what manatees a minute by j
d one person strange juvenile wonderment oh
wow
one person sings a song using one
word not related to the song and
one note you may only change the
word by longing it were not to
alter the note example okay examples like
that oh i think i was like
wow i was so lost drug frog
frog frog frog i added a melody
a what the fuck why were you
saying frog so that's what was listed
here you still use a word that's
not in the song that oh so
you're singing an actual viability of a
brownie stone some frog frog frog frog
frog frog dr pepper frog frog frog
w proper ra stock ra ra
okay so huh
nah it's supposed to be monotone fof
oh proper frog frog frog frog frog
frog frog and so frog is not
related to song you're singing where you're
nutting the melody okay i got it
and you weren't modern national anthem
so what you're just we're supposed to
know it by the beach the word
yes stick why did i oh by
the way downwards hotel california my what
usually we talk about this during the
break clear it and go do you
wanna play this you just said okay
here we go one
okay let's do it alright okay i
think my funny um i will do
it again just to get everyone excited
and get into it do the same
thing
i mean think it was solved
okay and then my word is when
give me a word sure young piano
will be one yes sydney once it'll
be an m p n o oh
no no no no this isn't a
thing how about shirt
about shirt
shirt cheshire teacher church church are but
okay are your jew lotta you're not
doing my shirt chirp chirp chirp chirp
chirp chirp chirp
no no no this this doesn't work
try it it's my child that was
that's the way haha i like it
she gestured chirp chirp chirp chirp chirp
chirp shirt but you did a melody
did i shirt chirp chirp chirp chirp
chirp chirp chirp chirp that time you
did not do that what actually
get figured out okay i go i
go i go on give me a
one syllable word
but we're going counterclockwise but good but
okay because they feel like dummies is
a little yeah but but but but
but but but but but but but
funky that that that that that that
that that that that but but but
but but but but but but but
buddy
ah
oh my shirt i'll try her chirp
chirp chirp chirp chirp chirp chirp chirp
chirp chirp shirt shirt shirt mister roboto
yes see thank you very much mister
robot shirt okay mister robot shirt your
turn
okay a word a word so where
it is please oh this is we
learn
you're tough
wow here we go please please please
please please please please
jingle bells per minute
please please please please please please please
please please please you're still a melody
please please
please please please se mato please please
please please please please please please please
please please go see
alright do it do it do it
do it now
okay i got i got what i
got you don't worry we're even gonna
guess what i did or were done
with i wouldn't know i want to
do it do it do it do
it now please please please please please
please
please please please please please please please
please please please
when you begging for ah
i can get it dealing with the
melody okay okay yeah maybe that'll please
please please please please please please please
please please oh the gambler yes yeah
wow lightly gallery links
yours mine give me a word
barn you so mad barn barn barn
barn barn buying buying buying buying buying
buy
yeah you do
bond buying the sheaf buying buying buying
buying buying buying buying buying buying buying
buying buying
but
damn it this sucks i'll do it
do it the bill
fine buying buying buying burn buys
bang bang bang bang bang boom boom
ramp and mine ban boon i don't
know barrel gone oh or were you
doing the whole thing that every time
i see you that no one knows
that yeah it was
chorus your sar wherever you are or
you do and barn barn yarn barn
barn barn barn barn yeah nah yeah
oh my god any word bow nail
nail and barn barn barn
barn now i know nail nail nail
noise
nail nail nail nail nail nail nail
now now now now now now now
now now the bodies
i don't know nowadays you know just
knowing that now do the valley
no no no no no no nail
nail ne ne ne ne ne ne
ne ne ne ne ne ne ne
only make hates that i'm listening to
this country so okay with i'll do
one more round everyone
everyone everyone okay let's do one together
i'll whisper the song to you guys
in the audience is to go okay
yeah or checks i gets
oh you know it gets
josh has to go
ok okay i'm gonna text you texas
this secret song and this is one
we'll do together like we're going to
do dancing with the stars together and
we agreed to do the chorus and
not the first okay mine um
i'm hiding my phone from josh yeah
me too which i usually do okay
now now now now now now now
wait what you're doing it what's the
word no josh word okay josh josh
josh here we go josh josh josh
josh
josh josh josh josh josh josh josh
josh josh josh
josh josh josh josh josh josh zsa
zsa zsa zsa zsa doesn't all go
together when at the time i was
doing the course why yes josh josh
josh josh josh josh josh josh josh
wipes yeah yeah but i did it
you mean josh josh josh josh and
that is how you play josh josh
josh josh and that's the game called
josh josh ya thanks you're losing everybody
we hope that you have a wonderful
holiday season yeah it's coming it's all
happening now baby we're in the main
now we're in this with your family
see how
long they can take it yeah and
then you'll end up like the family
six feet under oh my god alright
we are ah threesome usa on instagram
and twitter three m usa gmail dot
com if you want to send us
ah if a three-tier we love you
and make sure you sign up ah
to and subscribe to the show and
you can hear ad-free versions on
both stitcher premium and cbp world dot
com that's sounds great to me it
sounds crazy and instagram and be sure
to comment on every thought i this
ago and we probably have a new
intern at this point right or we
have only do she's in madison was
terrible madison she's been fire she's madison
was hired how old was she i
gave her talking to on the phone
does that mean you
hardy was using bringing this up when
we were talking about firing you like
she was ten years fired so many
fremont to bring it up she looked
like she was ten years old she
might have been troops used to show
me a birth certificate tell me she
was eighteen more you got played i
know next time i'm not going to
get to the world for the next
intern or they have to be older
than eighteen they have to be um
live within the state because she wasn't
ohi
yolo to the problem for me intervention
that but it was it was an
issue yeah why does that matter if
she's just don't want to be able
to interact with this person so i'm
gonna need them to leave the music
scene in our time zone and they
might have to show up to a
recording or two okay demand i've learned
because i need them to know the
shows about maybe twenty one so they
can like twenty one side drinks myself
i think they should also be hot
you said the last time but i
did not follow that obviously i chose
a child let's try
let's try to try at this time
like an adult who is hot like
a ten because real easy to work
with les ten and la ten na
ko chali canton illinois million yeah so
like make sure the like million paul
and i sign off on this intern
because the last couple have been okay
so it wasn't
to be a woman the next one
i will be sending to you to
review their resume before i let them
have the password let the bodies hit
the floor let the bodies hit the
floor alright alright everyone remember this holiday
season let your bodies hit the floor
a