sorry
oh jesus
hey where are the whoa boy whoa
hey oh that is that good oh
good is that running dangerfield hours yeah
boy who did that turn out to
be that turnouts arthur morgan of course
because arthur legendary
wedding band loops i was like are
there more more course of course politician
i'm not aware oh he was
you know now you know almost every
politician you i do but i try
to stay open order do you have
a thing where you tell your fans
try to stump me with apologies i
do and i say semi okay lauren
yes and try to get you and
if they stop you they get to
punch you in the stomach stars the
exact style ou who do houdini oh
yeah third base d
the who's who is who teeny thing
a really small shirt it's a ring
houdini who cheneys it disappears into my
stomach so i say it's a mississippi
museum hearing hi everyone welcome back freedom
and the spoken much today we're here
we're back it's freedom huh i'll come
back let's introduce each other i'm lauren
that's funny she's just she's
lauren new guys do this is laura
this is lauren okay you're saying okay
well she's lauren i'm paul all this
is paul paul know yeah paul paul
paul i'm prepared in a very specific
way i had no idea that your
name is paula left yes people mispronounce
it all the time la la la
because
oh my god you're drawing fluff i'm
scott hi everyone that scott welcome back
welcome back to three of them were
here it's good to be back guys
is gbp gbp for sure she's you
have the most giant water thing and
with the with the biggest lift makes
the mohican water thing i suck
water my gaping wound wound um this
is a beautiful water bottle and actually
the other day at comedy bang bang
i had a different with a straw
and we were talking about how it
was explained to matt walsh that the
struggle was great because if i try
to drink in bed with this one
it spills all over me and because
it's the it's the widest mouth mouth
yeah
um of anything perfect receptor like but
wait you like to fuck this i
do i do
it's time for you like to fuck
this i'm a great water bottle it's
called a hydro flask keeps it super
oiled okay so it's great because it
keeps it cold yes that's probably i
mean but if you pour hot drink
and they really get all cold yeah
what are the point keep it whoa
yeah i believe there's a bigger mouth
and nick kroll over here does but
you know what it's great because i'll
show you
yep i haven't gotten an opportunity here
love to hear do it okay
wow i love this water bottle because
i like to drink water all day
long and it's being so i'll have
a lot of water all day so
do you does it just go right
through you are you like peeing everywhere
all the time i poop it out
but you really if at yea you
asked you just solid water waste yes
it's just splash every time like ice
cubes yeah franklin
sleeping right in the toilet so when
do you remember the penguin of that
old bugs bunny cartoon l it's okay
to suck you little one when yeah
he would take a shit and yeah
he takes a shit and they were
ice cube because it was cuz he
bugs bunny and for some reason is
in the fucking arctic or whatever and
this penguin is is who's wearing a
top ad it's one of the cutest
kart
dunes out there right up there with
the the bulldog who was forced to
adopt the kidney yeah i love that
arrow yeah that is the thing that
led to a bunch of great memes
that was original i was wondering where
those mainstream yeah shit yeah but the
penguin he bugs bunny trying to get
rid of the penguin and the penguin
christ ice cubes ah
they make a very adorable little tink
tink tink sound when they fall in
love thinking about creative people coming up
with things like that it's so cute
i bet they didn't come up with
it though because remember remember the day
the clown cried way was in there
too the jerry lewis concentration camp movie
it was when he went it was
so cold in his cell in the
when he was
jailed right before he goes to the
concentration camp no he was in the
country yeah yeah that's right well he's
he's in the concentration camp and he's
got a private cell with a sink
and stuff and it'll suspected say cold
yes both the spigot say cold and
when he turns it on note to
sound effects sound of ice cubes dropping
into shore shore shore i
member stocks were frozen to yes vote
the upstroke to prop so to prompt
discussion yes oc sneak discussion it sounds
different to me ah yeah i see
the same thing i can imagine that
cartoonists guys smoking cigs with their feet
up on their desk what if i
christ in a fucking ice cubes coming
okay what if he shits and he
shits ice cubes about this skyway are
we allowed to show
paying with shitting and because i don't
know if we have a big enough
hole guys what are you doing
are you saying it depends on the
size of the hole i do i
think of the whole size it's lunchtime
were already guys want to eat of
course we're going to smoke out to
get drunk
i'm already drunk but what how did
you get ahead of us it's nine
am yeah i've been up for ten
hours at this point are you okay
no i'm worried about you
hi yeah
um cartoons cartoons i mean this isn't
raised by tv but all open it
up what was your favorite whoa shit
um you know i'm a huge brennan
stimpy fan really that's like my cartoon
from childhood and that was when we
got to have billy west on which
was amazing oh cool i'm trying does
he do he he actually did both
at some point post mp ulta
honestly i think is that the john
ah i mean i know i'd never
be able to say because hinske or
whatever it was john krasinski john krasinski
yeah he created it right yeah i
don't know i like just might this
back in the day um it was
a great show really really funny and
really um gross rose yeah that's how
you got your sense of humor yeah
love
it
auriga is when i was a child
i loved super friends that was a
big battle super friends was essentially the
justice league um this card but they
were friends it was to make them
a little more like hey guys can
watch him the concept of justice was
too big for kids like their super
in their friends yeah justice league meanwhile
kids are all reading it in comic
books yeah no problems with it superman
batman wonder woman aquaman okay and win-win
the wonder twins were invented for work
this ah cartoon and their their space
monkey gleick yeah zan and jayna were
the wonder twins now now are the
phrase wonder twins activate when yeah powers
activate yeah have you ever actually seen
that
cartoon i don't think so they were
one of them could turn into any
animal any animal and the other one
could turn to any form of water
now that became then because it's very
it's not very cinematic to turn into
water it became he would turn into
anything that was ice so form of
an ice latter ice a lot of
ice you know if they ever needed
anything to get form of an ice
go when they would travel um the
one would turn into an eagle and
would carry a bucket carry gleick the
space monkey who was carrying a bucket
where the other person the other wonder
twin a transformed into water well because
that was less heavy than a human
i guess i mean buckets watering is
very high
is very heavy but i guess not
as hard as a person because her
heavy as a person not as hard
as a person i've always said that
i can swim in water but i
can't throw in a person
yeah so much of our bodies are
made up of water so much so
i mean a good amount most of
it's in your head
meaning we're imagining that we're all made
up yeah it's not really thank you
everybody's two percent water but we're almost
every game all gone and saying yeah
what was your cartoon of choice i
you look goble all of them them
can turn it off i was a
scooby-doo guy oh sure you know yeah
look at me
i'm a scooby-doo guy obviously scooby doo
was gay when scooby-doo started having celebrity
that fascinate me when i was a
kid when they would have celebrities what's
the labs came on scooby-doo i don't
remember loeb trotter oh yeah they're their
own adam west was on there i
think sonny and cher yeah all of
all remember yeah how easy it was
to be a celebrity back then
like if you became a celebrity in
the seventy s you just stay to
celebrity well there were also people you
would watch old game shows there were
people who are famous from being on
the stage right right you know what
amy yeah it was like not a
thing today maybe lin manuel miranda but
yeah every you have to do something
else in order to be famous from
the state oh yeah i mean yeah
you can't even get on like celebrity
big brother you can't even get on
the stage unless you're famous
mr try to get on the stage
this year celebrity big brother norbert leo
butz did you ever learn did you
ever have to audition for who got
that listening for a musical i didn't
ah audition for a musical ever like
sing a song right yeah musical interesting
did you ever say oh yeah um
i had to sing song i never
got into my singing song
i never got into the musicals you're
so nervous about thinking about sia song
i can you can't even talk i
couldn't get into any of that i
didn't get into any i wasn't cast
even as in the chorus okay it
was horrible what i did which ones
were they doing oh god you know
do i even know at this point
i don't know um i honestly can't
remember fuckin push it out of your
mind yeah yeah
i want you why should you wait
a fuck yeah i yeah yeah um
but you know why wouldn't you why
didn't you even make it into the
course where it could probably so nervous
but the addition in front of everyone
else which having to make sense because
you have to see in place it
would be better if if no one
were there to watch them but i
mean all the other kids true like
it's weird to have like here the
people that you're
and watching you audition that is really
weird it's the same as an audience
it's like these are my peers anytime
you think anyone's judging you yeah it
makes it ten times harder yeah but
one of i wasn't chorus um for
a while and one of the like
it just acquire whatever and one of
the songs that i had a solo
of in the competition was um
i'm a girl ah what does that
say i'm just a girl gets hello
i'm a i kissed a girl i'm
i'm a i'm not gonna i'm just
a girl in the world you're not
gonna say oh no i'm gonna sing
it oh like where it goes like
i'm a girl and i'm it's only
grade and i enjoy being a gay
girl yes i enjoy be a girl
sang it yeah so you
sang that i did in a constitutional
yeah and how to go i placed
okay i think it wasn't embarrassing and
then also my other song that i
always had to sing a duet in
middle school was um oh god p
a su
why yea the is that latin or
is that ah yes p su i've
never heard this oh my god sarah
brightman sings it oh yeah it's it's
like an ave maria tiny kitchen play
it for you okay is it infantil
no i think it's like a some
sort of some ladies singing and some
lady i wanna hear
brightman are you okay fine hold on
one of the some ladies is susan
boyle situation she'll never seen it she
becomes famous from the show
what are your way now suddenly we
have to hear a pre-roll ad wasn't
i made a brand-new hair do i
know that's for himself oh how weird
is that no child it's not specific
what i enjoy being ah come on
riot riot definitely knows
or now they just played into the
thing it's found take two seconds but
i'm i'm happy to go through the
survey yeah okay read the survey hello
uh three back
he just did this part yeah it
had to be the flower drum song
distraction noises yes flour
uh
he's already too harder so
you sound like a beautiful woman
ooh
i can't imagine a citizen i was
like thirteen
now i can imagine it's a little
better because like i'm too weird now
ooh
can we can we hear you try
to sing this like seriously not no
i don't i don't think so i
wanna hear you try to want us
what does set up can we can
you please earnestly sing this i just
like to hear it sing the song
please no um no sing please
okay whereas i enjoy being a girl
for firearms that's from flower drums yeah
well what's p h xu from church
it's a church yes it's like it's
all in what does it does is
spelled like pi yeah the villain church
it's pi jesus basically so it's like
hi jesus something jesus and then it's
like four
jumpsuit i mean pulling or poor geez
ah yes
you guys ever have a soloist it's
ah it's ah ah from the him
ah da saray yeah yeah okay well
not really directly up yeah um i
yeah i remember those additions i forgot
about that aspect of it that you
were in front of the other people
who are auditioning and it was like
you in the piano
just you and the piano it's so
so horrible yeah side note it means
merciful jesus and then it goes on
to say lamb of god is he
really merciful well you can hope he
is he's the most merciful oh yeah
god is the one who were the
real chip on his shoulder except the
one time jesus got mad at the
fig tree and he cursed it oh
that that poor victory is still around
no well it might be like the
wandering jew it might be still alive
but know things i don't even know
what you mean there's there's a passage
in the bible where jesus gets mad
you want to know or not i'm
trying to get you the good word
yeah you just want a jesus once
in figs right in this fig tree
doesn't have any fish
gs and he's like you know what
fuck oh you're baron forever crazy whereas
that nut and they wrote about it
in a book yeah and anyone else
like him definitely have to include this
part yeah i mean it's crazy it's
weird it's like a main bad yeah
it's it's amazing in the sense of
like if you were watching a movie
it would be a cool part of
like him just like thumb
thunderbolts candy out of his own air
yeah it's a very mob boss kind
of thing to do like as an
example to like you're not gonna get
my babies you can do that same
thing to you but why included like
it just makes him seem like a
dick i don't know it's very petty
i want to go back to what
song you saying if you can remember
one from an audition or well we
would sit in high school when i
was doing the shows
we would sing the songs from the
show although i remember i remember this
girl rita who's in my class i
remember her auditioning love and she's saying
you don't meet
do your own version
had a little fun with that yeah
a little leave a little further north
she did ah rainbow connection oh and
she did a thing so mad oh
not that one o different one yeah
same same title did this thing where
um that that i see that you
said people do where they they they
assume like a singing accent oh oh
say yeah why aw that's so many
like her val choices were different she
wouldn't like say a hard r and
i think that's usually because they're impersonating
someone else who's singing it like there
was someone who was that time only
kermit the frog really so
well well that's true i had a
friend who would sing and she would
do all over ours really hard and
i was like you don't do this
when you speak she would always be
like when the world you know and
i was like wait i don't understand
and then i realised it was because
she was imitating elephants chair old or
something like that you know sure oh
yeah so yeah now that there's
is that style of singing that i
call the baby cajun and we talked
about the oh what's out you will
want to hear it gugu gaga
yeah okay it's take off your clothes
oh okay you put them back on
why were you wearing that diaper with
the gigantic state waiting for any oh
i'll do an impression of that on
google while you're the sasha says twenty
nineteen
happy yeah it's where it's it's it's
women do this female singers do this
where they have clarifying they do they
do this ah sort of ah accent
that's only for singing like they'll say
toyin instead of turn
tony lean oh you tying to allow
as many luxembourg zia know she has
like a joyless yeah yeah but you're
saying that the they don't want to
they almost like who does this who
did my name's yeah who is this
i don't know anybody i don't know
if anybody famous that does you'll see
it
oh no it's out of your friends
who doesn't
well it's also it's hard to sing
the word turn so it's very hot
so it's easier to sing in a
vowel so it's like toe hey was
like easy tonight so ter yeah an
audience member i love that oh hi
it's hard to sing turn here to
say teun does everything tie game die
die
there's a youtube video that allow you
to have so many making fun of
this and i think it's called how
to hip sing and this yes it's
this ah i don't remember her name
but is this young lady who ah
has these gigantic fake glasses on shampoo
clothes she's choose
yeah you thought i was gonna say
yes gigantic gigantic failure and he has
these
he has his gigantic fictions
um like when zig fake tits about
you when yeah you want the house
all day i would just shake her
it's always the weirdest thing people say
about that like i would never stop
touching when i was like why yeah
i think you would yeah i think
you'd understand it was your own body
well because you also have a dick
and you you could touch that whatever
you want right and still matter
to leave the house why if they
were your own tits would you be
like if your dick was on the
smaller your back but you couldn't reach
you would be terrible this is on
the bigger your bag
the bigger your bed
bigeye your back
remind me of that mop commercial mop
good mom
the lesser isn't it so good for
lily that took a big sip out
of your body can only be a
big series mop commercial from that swiffer
commercial which one they like they don't
want a baby oh yes we're the
oh law may mom is jealous yeah
i'm sad i hate when commercials like
that live forever in my brain yeah
yeah
like they take a song over and
i'm like that's what that's like what
have you forgotten in your life that
you wish you could remember i wish
i knew i was in it's a
very challenging question is this a riddle
what have you forgotten in your life
i'm sure there's stuff that you're like
i wish i could remember i wish
i could remember i wish i was
like marilu henner whatever were written yeah
it's not great that i got her
wrong and she's gonna knows everything okay
she never forgets i rarely enter yeah
fuck you okay i thought i thought
i was wrong which ones merely written
she's wrong you've never okay no honey
you're never wrong thank you you do
it it's a shame i'm no good
coup every
and you're wrong
marilu henner she remembers everything good weather
yeah everything is total recall and i
sore i mean while that's probably very
frustrating on some level i'm sure it's
a difficult thing and also i think
it makes her o c d or
whatever it was just hearing somebody talk
about this but i also kind of
wish that i had that because it'd
be so cool to remember us today
oh
yeah like because i forget i forget
everything and i forget like important details
of like experiences yeah i forget the
end of every movie i forget like
every thing let me test you on
a movie see if you can remember
the end okay alright ah
citizen kane
i saw one time i one time
i know that the sled is rosebud
that's the beginning baby and then i
don't remember anything else oh no you're
right that's yeah but that was the
whole point of them yes yeah but
i don't i only just like know
that you know i mean it's not
like i okay okay those raiders of
the lost ark i never i don't
i sell it when i was little
i'm okay and read more reason movie
sixth sense i mean okay that's like
remember how that ends either i know
that it that this i know what
the secret is yeah but you're right
yeah no i don't do you remember
when he puts on his wings and
he goes flying up to heaven why
you're thinking of birdman oh yeah expected
virtual racing gif michael
michael michael that michael when he put
on his angeles angelina to have is
that great that when we die we're
gonna go get to hang out with
michael jackson oven every so-called celebrity he's
gonna be so fucking cool so are
kelly michael jackson not dead he will
be by the time we are how
do you know i can't tell you
now but
watch the news you think in heaven
everyone exists in all like all future
dead people will be there and all
yes dead people are there so it's
like it's not like you're you're going
up to heaven and you're waiting around
twenty years for somebody to get there
it's like anyone who's ever going to
be alive and going to be dead
oh let's see your eve
heaven and honor at the same time
how it is i also don't know
if it exists in a different plane
of ah time i don't believe in
hell what's the point i tried john
lennon do you believe in beatles you
just imagined it he just imagined that
he did believe i was very developed
i think it's about i mean you
might have read my interview which you
did because
idea your mouth off about religion i
asked me about it i didn't know
that was gonna be the question i
was happy that there were more interesting
question but but if those of us
who have not earned those people out
there who have not read your interview
what is your position on after death
i believe that peoples an animal's soul
lz exists insects
sure but i'm not blind in really
wanting through animals yes i'm saying i
don't want to interact with them so
i don't really care i'm saying like
pets of mine look like things that
have died already cared about
i feel have a soul and exist
in the a plane that is on
the imperceptible to me but i don't
really believe that everyone is gathered round
but sometimes i do picture a heaven
like thing and think like okay but
i also think i don't really at
the end of the day i don't
really know enough about anything to say
that something is or isn't true
do you think it's feelings or do
we have cases in which our souls
reside or are we just kind of
floating along and and it's we don't
we can't even imagine what it is
i think that's what it is that
it's like some know science has not
science yeah in our lab late one
night
are you guys ah
yo me to go you know you
you out with us huh yeah i'll
talk about this or i just minds
a bomber i don't think there's anything
well i kind of feel that way
too yeah me too a little bit
but i don't think that's okay because
then you don't you aren't conscious of
that and that's okay yeah i nobody
in pain in that scenario true i
think that i think that the others
know like devils know poking peace
with pitchforks i believe only in hell
that's what they know haven't but there
is it by the way that's what
they do with the pitchforks is they
poke people yeah and they they they
pick them up like when you poke
a hotdog and put it on the
fire when you poke out talk and
put it on you know i mean
sounds yummy yeah it is a little
yummy but you know what i mean
that's the worst part they're not there
frills delicious another for decan
operation like a lot of people think
because they're not there for like hey
i'll stick you with this if you
don't get in that fire they're literally
threat there's care having people no litter
let's hear what paul thinks um i
don't believe in an afterlife i think
that this is it um sousa but
i you know when you get into
two energy can be neither created nor
destroyed it's like well that's a lot
you know a life is a lot
of energy and i don't know what
happens there but i don't believe in
i don't know i don't believe in
ghosts subtle believe in you know that
kind of thing that that people are
like stuck on some you know ah
loop or whatever that they have unfinished
business or i don't know i love
other people's ghost stories i love ghost
stories yeah but i don't believe any
of them well even though like friends
of mine who have like
i experienced this thing i'm like i'm
sure that you think you did it
while you pat them on i think
i think here's i also i always
come back to
there is so much about ourselves that
we don't know there's so much in
science that we don't know everything could
have a scientific science scientific explanation and
i get into an argument with ah
my wife and i will get in
this argument frequently because she's agnostic something
i'd say i'm eighth and a an
atheist and show it and she'll say
yeah it's we talked about this every
single day
right before bed risers wake up
um are you still in like nothing
ice like i say if someone were
to present me with i don't think
there's a god but if someone would
would present me with proof of god
i wouldn't say well i don't believe
that do you want yeah so it's
just she says that means you're an
agnostic because you don't know and i
said yes i don't know for sure
of course no one no
is for sure but i don't think
that there is i don't believe that
which is what should tip you in
atheism that's what tips me right that's
why what if jesus wearing isn't courage
what if you saw what did you
saw jesus walking along and he curses
a fig tree would you would that
be proof yeah see you're both ain't
what it takes for me yeah i
think so alright
i don't know i don't but i
also don't i thought it's kind of
i think it's just ah it just
ah but i was raised with religion
and yeah it's still the way that
i live my life you know by
those by those principles and the the
thing that drives me so crazy as
is you know false christians and and
people who
just won't acknowledge that they are not
in line people who profess to be
in line with the teachings of christ
and are not at all yeah insane
yes i'm whatever the laws are that's
what render unto caesar sure i wanna
say something i'm thinking about please that's
how we introduce every idea we want
i want to say something i'm thinking
about
thinking um i was thinking i'm just
thinking about friends of mine who are
raised by atheist parents and i think
that they're fine and they have but
they they from the get-go have the
belief that there is nothing and i
think almost for children it's nice to
believe that there's something it was
like santa claus someone's gonna say like
he's very comforting for me it's kind
of like just kind of good like
i didn't know much but i thought
by the time i believed in god
you're probably right but by the time
i got to be twelve or whatever
then it became very oppressive to me
of like oh god i can't do
anything that i think that i want
to do because
i'm going to be burning in hell
and it just became yeah i sort
of think wow i buy i'm happy
with how it went for me and
that like i believe that there was
god but i didn't really know anything
about it i didn't like go to
church or like read the bible's like
i didn't have the right to remain
liable i saw my list and it's
movie night stanford i forget did your
family sensibly have a ri
religion my friend my mom is a
greek orthodox my dad went to catholic
school right around sounds like they didn't
i went to church like to greek
orthodox church like for eastern christmas right
but just how much i know and
then we didn't
and they guy they respected yeah yeah
it was like i want to add
them and i was like okay but
like and and it was pretty much
just like come sing hymns while it
wasn't a different language which i think
is part of what yeah was kind
of interesting but it's so boring to
kids and listen to something at church
in a different language but it's also
cool because i've i'm not taking any
of it in
kinda going like this place is pretty
and there's you know like you're kind
of the ceremony yeah look at those
hats and there they're there elements of
that that i still think are really
cool but i bet all the hats
of course in the senate balls that
they wave around i loved i loved
my mass when i was a kid
i loved it i love it because
you remain right or there was that
asset
act of it but there was people
were like packed in there you knew
the next day was christmas it was
it was so like they had the
big ah nativity scene up on the
altar it was very exciting it was
so much ceremony meanwhile you know santa's
at your place and you know santa
that your plays yeah
sanchez going through my underwear drawer and
shit he loves that what if he's
a nasty little man he goes to
catholics homes on christmas eve when he
knows they're midnight he just fucking rubs
his face in their tenders to see
puts his balls on the butter
with those white cubes if i focused
i could throw up at that idea
could you yeah i wanna talk about
throwing up yeah i'm santa claus i
wanna talk about throwing up when we
come back hey alright we sure need
to take a break though we'll be
right that sounds great though
okay we're back okay we're young three
adam scott paul lorne okay i want
to talk about throwing up because i've
noted the same thing that we say
when we want to talk about some
oh i want to talk about something
i'm thinking about okay i went inside
yeah
i don't want anything okay so i
have noticed a correlation between loving something
and not throwing up okay now when
i weak are you new to earth
ah so you hate something in you
might
throw well no when we married i
thought i would just be throwing up
when they come to the kiss the
bride part i was like ooh i'm
sorry i didn't know okay so we
have to we have two dogs and
you have to pick up their poop
right have to yeah you should you
should okay but i i as you
know i live by the laws
that's right so i pick up the
poop okay so i am able to
pick up the poop and put it
in bags and whatever okay now the
other day i go out onto my
lawn and there's this dump there and
i get in my head that i
think a coyote has left it
okay yeah and i'm in so i'm
going to pick it up and i
cannot stop going like ah
like retching yeah because it's something that
i don't love and it's gross that
i'm picking up poop yeah yeah and
then later i find out that it
was one of my dogs and i
shouldn't have been retching but there's something
about like and if i'm ever like
going and i see another dog's poop
or like a homeless guy's poop or
something like that
i just go start going ah yeah
sad but if it's my dogs it's
like oh let's pick up this poop
right here what is that about and
then i hear it's like that with
babies too yeah it's like after you
know they're shitting in there whatever the
fuck they wear ah denver's type oh
yeah that's what you call them and
you're just like mine and you don't
mind because it's like your sue i
love this baby
so much yeah so what do you
what goes i mean i do think
there's something biological to that i babysat
so many babies and change diapers and
it did make me want to throw
up many times because you didn't love
them i mean i love them love
the money i've been yeah but yeah
but i mean no i love them
ah sorry too if someone were to
say there's an extra twenty dollars would
then you feel it
but like it would be like yeah
jackson chad worthy the you know but
i think that's probably true but people's
own babies too sometimes but um actually
i know somebody who can't change their
own kid sniper really i'm not gonna
use a madonna from them um yeah
that's what ok let me think of
who you know but they they feel
sick at the idea wow
i just mouse over i said no
just in case anyone heard the whisper
um yeah i just think there must
be some sort of biological thing to
protect children or something otherwise cavemen would
have just let you know let them
die or whatever your dogs or children
i think they aren't showing your fur
babies
i think there's something about when it's
your own it's your dog you've had
an sara puppy you're probably really familiar
with the scent of their specific yeah
but really that like then like a
dog that you don't know i mean
my dog shits but that's what i'm
saying is it was my dog's poop
so i do it's a weird shape
and you made up in your head
that it wasn't theirs
well it was shaped like a coyote
it was because he was the morning
it was like put together biscuits of
their shit what that looks like cody
it's like a cookie-cutter of a coyote
this is what look okay when a
coyote shits in the shape of a
coyote yeah that would make everything car
so much easier if whenever any organisms
shit was in the shape of what
it was because he
pooped little people shaped poops i don't
think out like what if it looked
exactly like you i'd love it and
what if what if your bud hole
had like a fingerprint you what if
your bud holes a probably guys from
everyone stick to their light show
my family had a thing a discussion
one time about if you were to
ah take a bite of something that
somebody else bit into like a piece
of toast or something i think that
i tend to not like that i
tend to like that but if it's
your if it's your like my my
siblings who had kids were saying
they didn't mind it if it was
like their kid right because and this
was raising another because they are of
me yeah right your significant other yeah
but but sibling to sibling know you
have to say what's on i use
my brother's deodorant and he was like
why don't you just keep that i
was like oh i didn't know that
was so busy other thing you think
like soap in the shower with a
roommate bizarre right but but soap doesn't
get dirty but here's the thing i
mean that's such a weird thing that
you should say that not to interrupt
you but i am but just because
it's exactly what a bad take for
seventh grade i remember in science class
really wanting to ask my science teacher
about if soap had germs
on it right but i thought it
was a dumb question i never asked
and i've honestly thought about it my
whole life well let's figure it out
come on right sidebar yes one of
you said when i was in when
i was in um a chemistry class
jew i was a junior in high
school the only class i ever failed
i'd go to summer school forget well
you didn't know much about chemistry that
sound macho
that's the that's the only i think
that's the only i don't know much
about science i don't know much about
science book don't know my friend chad
took um i i had this chemistry
teacher and i he's he was he
fancied himself a very funny guy and
like a cool teacher
yeah and it sounds rad that was
my seventh grade times youtube he was
like he would say bullshit in front
of us it was like oh but
he's dude rules he said he used
to say there's no such thing you
can ask me anything there's no such
thing as a stupid question and i
remember once asking him because i'd heard
this and of course it doesn't make
any sense when i was
a kid i had heard that hot
water freezes faster than cold water oh
yeah i said stupid shit like well
i've i didn't think so and i
was assured that there was no such
thing and i asked the guy in
front of the class and he ridiculed
wow that's some fast and that's it's
shit one more thing my seventh grade
science teacher he was also really funny
and i loved that of course and
i was reading i was in seventh
grade did you have different teachers for
different subjects yeah okay i had sort
of like the same teacher first through
eighth it was it was one teacher
for every class that's so much pressure
on one person it's ridiculous um i
was reading the book sign language by
jerry seinfeld yeah and i thought and
i loved it thought it was so
fun
any and then i gay i've always
thought you have a very very cycles
since i was thirteen yeah but i
gave it to your boyfriend with six
yeah i lent it to him i
lent it to my teacher thinking oh
you'll like this too because you're funny
and then he never goes back i
was pissed what i think though i
gave it to him and i was
like i never ask for it back
i was overthinking that's a very specific
thing when you loan something that someone
made you you realize oh they think
that was oh i didn't make it
clear yeah yeah did you say like
hey i wanted you know if you
want to read this or like i
have no idea how i how i
phrased it i probably had a crush
on him or something so oh so
you know how back to the show
sharing food and all this kind of
stuff gotta get i have always wondered
and i just just just happen me
two nights ago i went out to
dinner with friends and i've been out
to dinner with probably both of you
you've probably seen the play dinner with
friends probably you probably think we've answered
every traveled many times different continents i
think i might have been out to
dinner with the interview
yeah but it you know ah with
the whole double dipping thing and everyone's
like suddenly very aware of ah getting
this spit although your language sharing each
other sports sign language yet any fancy
restaurant when they bring a dessert what
do they do give me your son
they just give you spoons yeah and
then you're sharing each other so
i don't like that because i've had
that happen with like people that i
don't really know and then it's like
you're basically all biting until like there's
like a chunk in the middle that
has like bites on all the sides
but most people don't even do that
they're just like up all bets are
off go everywhere with this yeah it's
i don't get it like chop up
the desert into ico
equal that would be great pieces i
don't they do that why don't they
chop up the desert into equal pieces
well like say it's ah you asked
for that sansa like chocolate dessert into
equal pieces yeah we're gonna get a
chuckle is for the table and just
please chop it in equal shame sometimes
yeah pile of slop that fills a
little yeah chop it into four separately
liberal four ramekins why not
why can't or bring a serving spoon
and separate bowls for do you love
going out to dinner
yeah i do cool
what you were about to say that
you don't is that know what i
think about it i think it can
be great but other times like me
it's you know what gender i flashed
on from the tour was you and
me together at the hotel oh yeah
we work i wasn't there no you
weren't there like a really nice dinner
and yeah you might have to check
god damn yeah we did have a
great dinner and that well maybe even
watermelon without any you remember
for that watermelon skirt yes i do
remember that was a woman had a
skirt sitting at the bar looked so
cool i was like a big watermelon
and we complimented her yeah when it
was a photo but guys guys tell
me but the skirt it was a
shape of a watermelon the color of
a lotta shape of a skirt but
it looks like remove an ice bridge
yeah and i was kind of shoe
sitting on the stool was kind of
draped down like perfect
early and it just looked really cool
she was trying to get us to
like it she was begging us for
ten try this dinner sounds so cool
i was there i think that was
the first time that we had done
a one on one yeah meal like
that yeah well and it was so
great sorry and the conversation flowed so
much better and like there was something
falling there was an impediment missing yeah
yeah weird yeah oh lol grants take
another break
this sucks yeah we'll be right back
okay we're back
i'm sorry right when we know i'm
sorry um a one thing that we
should say is that ah chef kevin
is not with us today so he's
out of town but we got big
over here and zig has an answer
about whether soap gets dirty zig hold
on one second where is he he's
he's got a high what to do
with those men he's with those
alright hashtag those men are zig what
do you got does soap get dirty
alright so it says i'll get dirty
it says germs can and most likely
do own live on all bars of
soap but it's very unlucky that it
can make you sick or calls sin
skin infection they recommend using liquid soap
not bar so ah okay so if
you have a roommate out there and
you're sharing the soap
hope you should use a washcloth
and liquid that's what one logical all
this for but but i don't i
hate liquid soap for your body like
body wash yeah like i only ever
encountered hotels really you hate it yeah
i don't like it i love candy
yes it feels it feels wasteful but
i use a loofah oh bill o'reilly
what was his oh that's right what
did he do bill o'reilly want ipa
he said he said falafel instead of
loofah i forget it's it's yeah he
wanted to like use a loofah on
you know what cities you will way
yeah i think it's like i'm coming
to lawful like will feel awful each
other
oh my god i love that wait
haven't i told you how i had
this site there was like a year
where i kept saying balloon instead of
umbrella y a year i yeah sometimes
still haven't all fear that i said
it like all big today to say
balloon that's very nice i mean like
as an adult you're saying this yet
on a rainy day like today
yeah it was all but paralyzed longer
know what happened initially was as babysitting
this kid and this was when i
lived in new york and i said
look at that umbrella and it's about
a balloon and i was like why
did i just say and then i
haven't got hands multiple times and like
oh my god now i still make
i think about both of those words
together so so for either of them
you may say
the opposite yeah i don't know that
i've ever called a number like a
balloon but i've worried that i have
i mean they're they're definitely on the
same plane as far as you still
have straight up what was your silly
words go yeah they could just as
easily have been other idea we have
double l's just like whales just like
you i do love that oh i
called you a balloon one time yeah
when i was talking about you well
my body's waste getting in my heads
really big why sprite used you as
an umbrella once yeah and i held
you by the ankles are gonna wait
i wanna hear about why you don't
like loofah you don't know something i
don't like loofah you don't like liquid
loofah i don't think liquid soap because
it feels like because boring world when
you have to keep going back to
the senate i don't like that it's
wasting plastic bottles yeah that that too
but you know what am i gonna
do not using i mean look i'll
use it if i have to hey
but i travel with my own bar
of soap in a little soap coffin
so clad you do yeah a surplus
like it's dead yeah i remember i
was when i closed a little i
say silent
prayer
and i'll throw throw dirt on it
you strike me as someone who has
a place for everything and everything in
it's place it's true yeah it's true
i like that yeah ever since i
was a kid i liked so if
you were to open up zipper compartments
in your junk drawer do you have
a junk drawer every everybody got a
jump everybody john draw if you were
to open it up is it just
filled with stuffer
or is everything no it's great it's
just filled with stuff okay so so
the junk we are all medicine provider
marie kondo save me young tories are
crazy though that's just like well that's
what they're supposed to be this is
that yeah but i mean one drawer
is for the silverware because there's so
much so draws for the suva away
so sure
where jaws is junk but you can't
have an entire drawer for rubber bands
you shouldn't and you can't do many
rubber bands but you know i mean
you can't have an entire drawer for
a tape measurer you need a junk
drawer yeah that yeah i like the
rubber bands go bad like yeah yeah
yeah after a while they'll just
just yeah right yeah one time my
cat ate a rubber band when i
was little and um she was scooting
all over the floor trying to get
it out or just hanging out there
is how oh really did you like
pull it back and snap it yes
torture know and then um way to
get it removed by the bad i
believe and was about to just pull
on it but their teens yeah
alright it's time for a feature oh
if if there's a first time listening
to them welcome to our last welcome
welcome welcome in our in our last
segment one of us finds a feature
and paul has found a feature for
us to play i signed a feature
i don't remember where this came from
um but it's it's not like i
do
don't have an attribution so i don't
think this was a listener one okay
um but it's called no to no
no to no no to no easy
rules great just ban everyone from saying
yes or no huh choose one person
to start he or she has only
one minute to answer as many questions
from the group as
possible without answering yes or no if
they make it to the end without
tripping up they get a point all
questions need to be answered any hesitations
ums or us impose a ten second
penalty come on amzn us layer with
the most points wins that's the whole
point so the points are kept by
what how many questions you answer
oh no if you're doable round to
get one point yeah and you end
if you do amore ah you get
added ten seconds that you lose you
lose time now but it would be
gaining time because it's losing time would
be to your advantage because then your
time would be over quicker but then
that means there's fewer questions that you
get to answer so you you have
to but you don't
you get points per questions you get
points for getting through the entire period
without fucking tripping up as if you
have more time you have more time
to say yes or no so yeah
i think it's i think it's having
yeah no you're okay okay let's do
it alright oh bless your silly ass
paul said we need to remember the
weather everybody that's quite alright i appreciate
it and it's a re
rainy day and paul's out in the
rain what is happening here your commitment
to this is incredible well it's like
ah told you when we first heard
this podcast neither rain nor sleet nor
snow nor gloom of night will keep
me from ah again together you silly
acids okay so we're doing one minute
or what how long is it yeah
one minute and we just ask any
qb
questions
okay okay one million person start they
have one minute to answer as many
questions from the group as possible without
answering yes or no so who's gonna
you're gonna answer for i'm gonna answer
first okay okay ready and go are
you a man i believe i am
how old
how old am i do you like
your age
i think that my age is sufficient
for the place where my body is
at is your hair long my hair
tends to be short than long depending
on when i get my ah haircut
do you like shirts shirts seem fine
to me do you live in this
building of course not
are you a white male
please are you seven feet tall
why would i be seven feet tall
are you five feet tall somewhere in
the middle in between those are you
an alien
my tybee do you like me
sorry oh so visitation even negative seconds
add ten seconds of course i do
like you paul
um that's it
wow i have thoughts about okay alright
what are your thoughts i think that
should be a one word answer how
would we how would that work like
you could say i mean stupidly yes
so you're just kind of trying to
come up with synonyms for yes or
no i guess i was yeah how
did you how did you feel on
your end i felt it was a
little difficult but i
i believe i successfully did it alright
let's try let's i'll try at the
same ok let's try okay okay do
you wanna go next yeah me to
go i'll go next friday and go
what color is your brooch well it's
not a yes or no question so
i'm not it didn't say he asked
yes or no question like it actually
no i didn't say to ask this
many questions does it say yes or
no
question i'm gonna tell you it's much
easier to not say you know no
question i always tried i thought i
would throw him off with one okay
and i'm like get him feeling comfortable
started good i feel closer i'm the
closer then don't open baby alright
you can don't open your stupid mouth
oh shit hurts ready whoa i've never
seen this version of the clock oh
shit i never swiped over there's a
style i want to say that for
now
we're all checking everyone we got to
take a break although the stopwatch what
do we do timer yeah and we
yeah that's fucking great that's cool looking
beautiful i don't have it yeah update
your phone no no you're not in
the right thing go to the stopwatch
one stopwatch okay yeah don't go oh
look at that go to your ninety
alarms i don't have to know what
am ten
yeah sure what were you benchmarks we've
thought about my alarms syllable alright who
are you ben shorts go who are
you ben schwartz
i don't believe i'm benchmarks are you
interested in karate i find karadi interesting
who's your favorite karate person my favorite
karate person mister miyagi is here friend
i wish are you believing in god
i am not believing in god currently
are you ah wearing a hat i
do wear a hat now yes yeah
oh dad and addington tickets ah no
he didn't get through it he doesn't
get a point oh shit yeah it
didn't get through it didn't hitler but
i didn't owe more ah stray terran
ready oh
i want to use my stopwatch ever
whatever to you
nervous and reset if you should i'm
freaking out ready here we go are
you wearing a hat i believe i'm
wearing a hat why aren't you wearing
a hat because i am wearing a
hat what color is your hap blue
are you sure about that i am
absolutely sure my hat is blue why
are you not wearing a blue hat
because i am actually wearing a blue
i don't believe you are tell me
you aren't i am wearing a blue
hat do you think your grandparents are
in heaven i believe my grandparents' souls
are around me
do you think your mom will die
i do not want to think about
such a thing have you ever seen
a ghost i have not really seen
a ghost i have believed that i
have seen one boy actually i believe
it was a figment of my imagination
why are your eyes not blue my
eyes are blue my good man you
got
soccer i do have toxin are you
wearing underwear
disgusting question for you to ask it's
disgusting
are you sorry that you came here
today of course always am did you
drive it ty kid wow well we
both get points okay so two points
and one zero for you and then
what and then what are let's do
it again until one of us wins
but let's use shorter times and okay
um faster questions shorter times faster ques
tions till one of us wins shorter
times faster question this thirty second round
okay and ready get set go um
are do you love your wife of
course i do did you murder your
wife of course i did
um did you drive in a car
today i believe so is it raining
i think it is do you like
us i don't know do you eat
lunch d allen eagle lodge i believe
that i was successful in that endeavor
do you like my accent do you
say yes i don't think so do
you say no i can't remember if
do or don't watch star no star
wars and you do
star wars
i was ready to go off on
a treatise about what's ur thirty seconds
on the clock thirty seconds out oh
wait oh no for me oh for
you that's right because paul's eliminate he's
out i'm out okay gotta end it
here we go is paul wearing a
hat you betcha what star wars i
don't know tell me about star wars
i don't know anything about the thing
you know technically
but you said k no w that's
different
why is that the same it's not
the same do you like your husband
yes of course you love
winner winner that's see that's how we
do we badger them that thompson's question
you know what that sells power raisi
your love is nice at least i
said yes yeah i believe i can
fly and i believe i can fly
cancelled your castle never yeah sure
shit lauren got married since our last
episode is real true that's true in
lawrence married now
you love it yeah you love it
it's awesome yeah what's what's awesome about
it um i just love him so
you ah so you wake up and
it gives you a feeling of comfort
yes i'm very happy um that i'm
with him
yeah you feel the same but your
lives yes yeah i feel the same
about paul's wife that's so fucked up
about clock and love it makes me
comfort that you're married yeah yeah i
like knowing that your married ah to
both of them
you don't think sometimes it gives people
like some crab though or like they
have a great wife that feels good
like i'm i make some yeah i
think that they're good and that that's
why people would rather murder their wives
then divorce them
because they're standing with their friends will
go down yeah you know what i
mean like kill them it's like it's
not about it's use i don't think
it's about money sometimes maybe it is
about money oh my god i can't
get divorced because then suddenly i'm not
going to have all only have half
my money or whatever but i think
if you're talking about people who really
think they're getting away with they're gonna
get away with it yeah like she'll
she'll
disappear i'll get all the sympathy no
i don't think i'm a bad i
really think it's because they want sympathy
i think it's because they're like i
can't imagine a world where i have
to go to all of my friends
and family and say remember that wedding
that we had i think that's a
big part of it for a lot
of people i remember what a friend
of mine was getting divorced after years
of
marriage and he was the way he
was framing it was i have to
face that i i am in a
failed marriage right i failed and i
was like well i don't need any
kids and everything yeah and it's like
but it's like you can't look at
it like it's a personal failure like
obviously the thing wasn't working and is
better for your kids that you
i don't stay together somewhere for reasons
like full divorce it's like yeah your
microwave hey if your microwave isn't working
you don't have to like carry guilt
about it like i have to accept
that my microwave isn't working yeah and
like things change i don't know i
don't think it's like ah you know
your perception of your existence changes as
you get older and your relation
kinship dynamic changes and if you have
kids that's a whole nother thing that
changes that it's like the idea that
you're expected to just do something because
you said at one time right is
actually crazy yeah but i think there
are people out there who have like
they they love their standing in the
community i mean i think about people
that were in the church when i
was growing yeah who
who there was one oh that aspect
is a whole yeah there was one
layout like there was one deacon i
remember who's who was dating someone my
age i mean after she was eighteen
or whatever but like a married deacon
who who's who was like fifteen years
younger or whatever and it all came
out they they'd been having an affair
and stuff like that
it's just like some people cannot imagine
the world where you a world where
you come clean about that kind of
thing and so they go wow let's
just throw her off a boat yeah
i do not you have this thing
i you know throw your life you
know couples that are they seem to
always be at odds with each other
but they're still together and so you
think i have fraser hold on i'm
horny guy friends who argue about being
agnostic in atheists all the time all
all the time the moment i wake
up before i put on my make
i'm oh man i wake up but
they but you think to yourself and
maybe this is just me this is
not much rather than thinking well they
should get divorced you think
they're making a work yeah like some
kind of always assumed that people yeah
ships are fine but then they end
up splitting up and you're like oh
yeah of course yeah like they shouldn't
have been fun they should have done
this a long time ago yeah right
i'm always happy when there will be
oh i feel so silly when i'm
surprised by it i think i'm ready
the first fight the cool up and
a half boom cut so you've never
had
i'm never gonna find out if it's
amazing i won't allow it yeah it's
pretty so no i was gonna say
i known people were like they seem
to hate each other and then they
get divorced some like good yeah it's
like whoa lulu the whole town like
they're gonna get divorced and they do
it i'm like sweet and then everyone's
better and it's happy but i never
think anyone's going to get divorced because
you when you meet the key
couple and you you meet them as
they are which is always bickering or
whatever anything i guess that's just their
dynamic know what though i think okay
having been divorced i think that i
can see it more like i was
like oh they should get divorced and
they don't like sweet so you have
like the dare devil divorce radar yeah
because
a divorce x but i just think
it's like with toxic waste bourne is
completely blind deaf she cannot speak
this is all echolocation
whatever so you think you're able to
see so do you see it with
us i don't i don't actually but
i i feel like it's i mean
i don't even want to talk about
people because you know i wouldn't want
to i don't hope for people to
go through a painful experience but i
do think that the people i know
who've oh have been through
a similar thing as me are happier
than other side because yeah it was
not a good situation to be in
i think if you can get to
sixty i think you're good like sixty
years old it's like if you can
get there do whatever you can to
get their sixty you know what i
mean if you want to stay with
the person until you're sixty no no
i'm saying like do whatever you need
to do get divorced stay together whatever
it's like it's
so hard to even just to get
to to you want to just live
yeah just let just try just let's
all just lit like you know what
i mean like by the time we're
all sixty what we all have dementia
and we all have it you know
what i mean that's like just what's
our clock is totally ticket let's all
just stop i know let's stop judging
each other's what i'm trying to say
and people are people why should it
be you and i
hey look that's gonna do it for
us yeah am i right yeah you're
right let me apologize to the listener
for anytime i have sniffles on mike
i apologize i'm not always conscious of
it you sound a little like you're
in a cave like i'm older cap
i'm a little bit in a cave
and i would like to say you're
welcome to everyone for not eating on
mic yeah you did not you've had
some i've actually been looking
look at your crackers and i haven't
had any you want to look into
your cracker imo you've been pointing them
at me since this started all i
care and that sky the waters the
barrel of these crackers is right i
had to write i have to be
honest i've imagined that that is a
cracker gun that you're pointing at me
and you're gonna shoot a cracker into
my mouth oh you just ain't on
mike
you accepted someone's thank you by saying
you're welcome and then you turned on
them for masterfully played can't believe the
masterful
meanwhile i'm not eating nor my sniffling
all right that's gonna do it for
us you're annoying
this sucks when i agree to do
the show again with you guys it
was a drop i would drop by
drop by
uh