oh
history
yeah twenty twenty one dumb happy new
year but every twenty twenty one unless
you're listening to this on stage but
everything's better now and everything's good and
yeah it really isn't that great life
is amazing yeah here he behind us
for ny twenty twenty was a dumpster
fire and i'm the first one to
say it but wow
one oh i wouldn't even put it
that way but when you put it
that way that's so funny it's not
a really unique and cool yeah twenty
twenty ending on their twenty twenty bingo
cards i got mine and i got
a big old bat being no bitch
yeah but the mega pigeon bomb angio
motherfucker welcome i'm lauren bolsa i am
paul i have scott and this is
three of them the show where we
talk to each other um we were
just talking about scooters and i have
to say i rode lime scooters around
germany last year at this exact time
of year that were recording november
it's december what were they called their
limes but how did they say it
climb i actually don't yeah i don't
know but it was just like a
climb climb but it was such a
fun way to go around the city
when it's all us were you wearing
yes what does your concept of the
german language i owe him a terrifying
just put
ah a guttural h in front of
every everything i'm
you know what i'm doing when i
do it merry christmas
so you were you wearing a helmet
no lorimer and you'd be dead with
your head cracked open in a foreign
hillary but there used to be there
were a couple a couple dead people
calls close calls not with me falling
and dying but where i was in
traffic and where i was like i
didn't mean to
be over here and i'm like i
shouldn't be in here kind of really
saying that as you are in the
i didn't mean to be over here
when they were honking at me it
was kind of implore huh
i stepped off i almost stepped off
the street in england and got confused
on which way i was going to
be moving and cl up grabbed me
and a motorcycle would move and would
hit me and she started she burst
into tears like i can't do this
with the first time the jamie and
i went to new orleans together nor
we were biggies were standing steady
oh those sort of traffic islands hot
up where there was like a sort
of three way traffic thing happening right
yeah where they have like the diagonals
yeah but for some new in january
involved in a three-way in but other
lives
it's a dream yard that's right i
fucked you both oh my god oh
yeah on the between two ferns
ah
so we're we're trying to we're waiting
to cross and um it's not clear
which light we're supposed to be looking
at right and so janie starts to
step off the street step off the
curb and a car zooms by and
she was like startle for
a second and then a guy nearby
said you can just above the tree
like that this new orleans like wow
that's not this is new orleans big
so that's everywhere this is traffic that
long as we do things around here
the unique character of america you hi
i'm a crawl daddy and your bargains
you want them off the street
people love to make it like this
cities like this yeah like every city
has some sort of that's one thing
i can't stand in movies where they
go this is new york and remembers
yeah especially even like spiderman two after
nine eleven it was like when we
were new york we we have a
certain character no matter what you write
is you
you can get pizza in four in
the morning here when i hit it
at the most was in united ninety
three i was like yeah
you can apply it today it's a
field in pennsylvania
there's a better god and what he
didn't know on trying to fly into
this thing
ah moray or in senor mercury co
gary ne so yeah so i don't
think so
it's funny generationally i think it has
to me was not a big deal
totally so you were you were like
ghostbusters you were tootling around in germany
yeah where you buy your loan summer
was no like you're with me and
we tell you it's very cold and
it was mike tyson and grady it
was freezing and we were riding the
limes as a way to like get
home faster one night we're like let's
just do this
because we were walking yeah we have
a mutual right which we were going
faster like good to walk for an
hour i got ah we have a
mutual friend who goes down to la
piu belle walks there because it's downhill
and then takes a lime scooter because
too drunk to drive
yeah that's what i was picturing them
doesn't hitler um
um oh maybe the lie if you
get down that lifestyle i stop at
la poo bell why don't you just
go a couple more doors down to
burbs what about the other one franklin
color one i like frank da and
oh birds remember when the our dear
departed friend robin williams who go to
usb and then yeah and then go
over
birds and dance on the tables after
shows
so fun really yeah i remember meeting
him in san francisco at sketchfab yes
he came into the match game mat
he came by to match game yeah
and i had met him at that
point because i did a few shows
with him through jeff garland i didn't
jump garland usb shows and there's a
picture i saw like oh jeff garlin
i was
fox
jeff garlin i was like job hugs
he's doing youtube users but i have
a picture of like robin williams with
his hand on my knee because i
just told the story about loving him
when i was young hi guys so
anyway so so he was there match
came and i'm like hey man do
you want to come up and do
this is exactly what i was going
to talk about because
his response was no one wants to
someone wants to see me with this
we're like robin why yeah everyone wants
to see you do anything no but
he he was so self-effacing that he
thought that we were the cool comedians
and if he were to go up
people would be disappointed because the cool
comedians weren't oh what a nice first
week yeah he was like very sweet
dude just
share share a seat with me like
lego man the audience say sit on
my watch it on my face and
williams not you guys
yeah but he was just as a
fan you just want to watch it
yeah that's nice oh yeah nice guy
really nice guy nice um so you
were so you had a buddy and
you were known around germany um yeah
we were zipping you're my best buddy
my husband yeah but buddy yeah yeah
sure we robots from time to time
it's pretty pleasurable my wait till marriage
yeah i'm good but it was so
fun and then we kind of got
obsessed with them but we were like
where we wanted to go to another
city and use them because we don't
want to do a lawyer because we
want to take the ones from germany
to another city yeah we wanted like
travel again those are last big trip
before the pandemic
yeah and and i'm glad we wang
it was kind of impulsive but like
god man it sucks i haven't gone
anywhere i i found this list on
my phone of all the six i'd
written the year we went on tour
i wrote down all the cities i
traveled to that year because i went
other other places as well and it
was just like i have places without
us yes and i traveled to like
forty places are more like a very
abusive travel a lot yeah especially during
the tour and it was so fun
and then i was like this year
i've gone to philadelphia where i shot
my scene and happiest season and then
to it thanks good job it was
very fun thank you we have to
talk about the weird coincidence oh well
next thread i didn't think it was
that weird cheney thought it was with
janie dee thought it was i thought
it was a fun one it's a
pretty weird janie janie was very she
thought you'd like did it on purpose
so both of us was just set
up ah this movie that mary holland
co wrote the happiest season that lauren
is in i think it's just called
happy isn't whatever and so sweet so
we watched
it and when lauren came up both
of us took on different days both
of us took a picture of the
screen screaming home separate separate rooms took
a picture of the phones of your
different ipa fingers
now you both use the same same
finger oh that's right now close your
seeing finger it's a riddle
we both took pictures of lauryn dressed
as a cop i took one planning
on texting into the group chain yeah
right and then call two days later
i think took took ah posted his
picture to the group chain and i
immediately like oh yeah i took one
night and i sent mine and they
were the exact same
same second second of the show now
to be fair and janie thesis is
very weird she's like you took a
picture at the exact same time i'm
like the was short lauren was only
in thirty seconds yeah of the movie
like we picked one of those thirty
here's what it was and because this
is what i said to jamie
that it perfectly it was the perfect
amount of time together cameras noticing more
and other shit yeah getting the phone
sending it updating the textures are yeah
like of course it's like i did
it immediately and i'm trying you didn't
i didn't really too yeah so it
only stands to reason it would be
that but janie was extremely amy thought
it was fishy as fuck yes she
did she was like you guys plan
this yeah i think
i don't know what to do or
were impractical joe of all time um
but so so yeah you were still
a practical joke of all time was
that comic city was nine eleven it
wasn't oh hey i didn't get that
i thought that was a weird joke
and anywhere else i think i think
i've been twenty twenty i was in
mexico when i was gone thanks to
that one place and that's so that's
a whole year and i also keep
thinking december was just now like you
know it was just like a month
ago yeah and it's already december again
and now it's january i know but
i'm like yeah i i didn't ever
like catch up with
what part of the year it really
was yeah it's what i will say
is is like i would think back
to oh remember when we were in
tokyo and i would say about to
cool up and instead we would be
like oh thank god we went like
this i'm really glad we didn't just
go like oh we'll do that you
know on another year in the future
we like and i feel the same
way mike is really
the more impulsive about travel than i
am and i really appreciate it because
we've gone to a bunch of fun
countries together and functors functors
it's been like to be able to
have those memories yeah this time well
we were cool up and i were
supposed to we had a big italy
trip for april dan and i remember
in february talking to a mutual friend
and i said yeah
well we're supposed to code
italy in april and they're having this
big outbreak of this thing he goes
you ain't going to italy wow yeah
i think we we could still go
probably like you ain't going to italy
yeah and i thought we'd be going
to tokyo again we wanted to go
again in the spring and that was
disappointing i went to and i wanted
to go to lithuania and greece i
one to go with me this summer
with my family and that was me
a big family things my dad's from
now that sounds like that would have
been fun little funky um i went
to ah san francisco portland of vancouver
maybe i was in san francisco in
january for sketch fest oh you probably
were i did not go i don't
think i went anywhere other than
i came back from mexico like the
first couple of days i went to
vancouver was weiss vancouver was my last
whoa the second trip was the last
one and that was that was right
before everything shut down whoa this is
what passes for interesting and cool yeah
whoa you went to vancouver i'm also
just i'm looking through my calendar
in january i'm like what is fucking
bullshit i was doing yeah well no
idea well i think i mentioned i
mentioned to you this pool i went
to idiot i want to deal with
c and i went to philadelphia i
mentioned to you that in february we
i saw on the internet that ah
sting
he wrote a musical and was playing
yes i mentioned this yes you did
god what i went yeah oh yeah
you said that too
well maybe i should i would love
to go see a play i love
to go see a bad play i
love to go see like a christmas
show i know christmas is over for
you listeners but i'm sure these binges
out there who are mad that they're
bingeing you have control you know all
you people who say oh i got
five episodes of one say let's zoom
on why do you do that that
way
why did you do that you don't
have to let yoda that um i
can't say this about happiest season which
i really enjoyed um and it's just
one day after the after the holidays
everybody this is relaxed yeah sure well
it's january seven when people it's one
yeah the hot trends in these the
epiphany oh okay yeah the
iceman finally made it to dealer when
you celebrate your stable it's like the
wise men want didn't make it until
weeks later they were there until a
week later yeah it's not totally tell
us that in the bible they do
that's the aware that because the only
place that information is contained
wearing like like really wrote the bible
we used to when i was a
kid we used to wait with our
activities seem to put the wiseman in
really old january seventh yeah oh that's
really you wouldn't have knocked it down
by then we used to we used
to keep the baby jesus out of
the manger until until the day that's
kind of fun yeah yeah who would
sneak it down could put them in
on christmas eve
well it's not surprised surprise jesus who
who is get down there little baby
jesus separate channel winter out oh no
to live by living eminem like it's
just like santa claus sneaking down and
yeah just like that yeah i mean
santa claus essentially is jesus but wait
now he's jesus
gss well yeah what are you talking
about santa claus yeah only reason birthday
yeah but the oh wait santa clauses
birthday is december twenty yeah that's why
he's so crazy about christmas he's like
he's really saying what every sane person
was he wants cookies for his birthday
so he figured out a way to
get him yeah
i don't like cake i'm gonna kick
guy i love cookies i love cookies
and like with my reindeer fed avail
of carrots crazy forward like a carrot
or two they might take one bite
out of it read the rest seminars
just over there and they've been to
a lotta house ah the privilege to
think they eat this one bite that
they'd die for that's the best
not just it's gone putting them back
to the fridge right
so so interesting how cena eats all
the cookies though
yeah the carrots not really yeah reindeers
paced themselves were gonna go a lot
of houses wait so who wrote the
bible chomp yeah who did we did
we all all of us together isn't
it great we wrote one word to
tides the people's book
no like who okay so they say
it's like oh even if you said
ok god and jesus don't exist but
the people who say they wrote each
books wrote it is that even true
you know like matthew mark luke john
oh no like who like some guy
wrote a lot of it write me
some guy oh you zero theory as
it was one guy oh
i used a bunch of different pen
i know i think it was a
bunch of editors like one guy wrote
genesis and then an editor got a
hold of it it was like let
me cut this but let me add
this and then it just like kept
being passed down throughout the i mean
i believe that's essentially true is that
the they've been all of it has
been like heavily let's do some cuts
to it now you know
i mean like why is that not
exactly in my lifetime why hasn't there
been a revision of the bible where
we cut out some of the dumps
walt whitman never stopped writing leaves of
grass wow that's right he was crazy
was like we'd just mystery mentioned he
was like santa claus he what he
was born december twenty fifth i loved
cookies
um seriously like if we the three
of us know a three-time bible yeah
ransom cuts i know what i would
cut what would you cut part where
you can't fuck a sheep
okay so now is it a sin
if you don't fucking shirt no it's
just like wow why are we talking
about this
like why even bring it up as
gala where you brought it up in
the first place
back then there was the only job
was being shepherd and it was like
look look we know it gets lonely
on land you get to do so
much already just don't do this one
thing just come i guess the sheep
don't like it the bible was the
sheep specified when we talked about the
documentaries zoo uh
um tell you about bestiality know okay
like no thank you urs they fucked
two guys battery monday guys that fuck
all horse i can't remember exactly wow
it breaks down but they all get
out of focus for standing what's a
good example if i remember it
all cracks they have like a a
meeting and they they all want a
meeting some kind of make a plan
and then i think one of them
gets clan possibly to death by the
whoa god i hope so i can
remember though like i'm truly hopes were
they filming it yeah there was like
hitting cameras in the stable
so the horse didn't know
and at the end they were going
to be like see there's a camera
there there's a camera there no but
the christians in prison because they were
like i want to watch this later
how weird um it's weird to want
to fuck a horse for sure yeah
and to find other people that also
want to do it how were they
filming like the plan being made or
is this all in retrospect
they're like so he came to me
i don't remember i don't remember who
starts filming what the minute one of
their friends says hey what if we
all fuck doors i have to look
into this when they go to cover
hello
well we say oh i thought let
me i'm like are you saying no
um also have you seen the new
trend in reenactments in um no crisis
friend they it's a lot of cartoons
some animation really okay about that because
still having an audio can't be ah
filmed now so there i
i don't think it said i think
it's just an an effort to live
as like holy moly sway they filmed
the entire season other than the steph
curry meeting the contestants like that day
i think they had planned to pick
up when steph curry was free and
the home it happened i forget what
holy moly is holy moly xantia golf
real shot watched and no one else
did
oh yes okay it's the best you
guys should watch it anyways funny yes
it's it's wait like is funny cool
i love and i was our favorite
like we cannot draw thursdays little bit
of drama
real quick the documentary was ah was
about a man who ah was a
seattle aircraft engineer who died in two
thousand and five after performing a sexual
act with a stallion the filmmaker interviews
a number of zoo files died because
of it you're just happened to be
after more dramatic reenactments to illustrate their
anonymous comments dramatic reenactments
oh and it was made i came
up two hours i mean two years
two hours and you already watched to
hear this guy died
what have you had a google alert
for any documentary and counting stars so
and it's really good apparently yeah a
lot of people like it
so you're saying i should watch holy
moly now it well if you can
hear you saying this i don't i
don't know where you would find it
maybe like ah ah sort of wipe
out type show sort of but but
rob riggle is really funny okay um
yeah i pull up and i were
really looking forward to like that but
um so i don't need you but
what i'm trying to say ziel i'm
not i'm not talking down about it
as much as i saw and i
understand that i'm just making a little
joke i'm just trying to keep things
light sure what scott train levies and
i see myself as the peacemaker because
i would say i was trying to
you know patch up what i had
done
you're the peacemaker what scott trying to
do he's i'm trying to move forward
like a shark i'm just trying to
move forward like a shark he's a
four mover on the peacemaker what are
you more i'm the patchwork or i
go back for stakes we all have
are aware of issues are unclear thing
the peacemaker the patch maker the mover
forward this is not as cool the
pieces when i said that was a
shark
yeah that sounds right the patch but
the mena togo okay i'll be the
midnight or dust shark but i'm saying
that steph curry they couldn't the very
last day of filming covert happened so
they had to animate him for the
entire very live filming covert happened
that was a weird day but what
i but might to my larger point
paul i remember maybe animating things up
that morning they may be animating things
now because they can't film them know
you're not listening to me you're not
listening tiny which i think is your
steph curry story frankly it was a
disaster okay
i thought it was the peacemaker with
her toys they have audio like old
tapes and things sure and they're just
that there was never video for it
okay and they're just animating these okay
and what are they doing this this
big hot trend they're doing it in
true crime documentaries like such as like
such as things my wife watched
that i don't know the titles i've
ever seen who the bleep did i
marry know i've lived it
it's what the bleep do you know
about the bleeding docu series tapes but
it's it's about people where they go
like seeing got home with her husband
carl not believing that he was just
a dude from ah believing that he
was a bad guy you sound like
the dude who does he said yeah
the guy with white hair who's on
no no no no not keith whatever
works and the other guy the other
guy who's like he's got kind of
this week so yeah that pasternak oh
wait john is yes yes no no
no i don't and i know who
you're talking about major learn guy yeah
he's um hello sorta yeah i don't
want to say he looks like buster
for know he looks like um
he looks like what's his name i
think it's weight but that's not john
no no that's the kunis who i've
been on a plane with by the
way um i can't believe buried the
stores right oh my god oh and
everyone was like i love your show
he's like well thank you very much
what would you do yeah the way
you would you do i know this
this is a dateline guy yeah
kind of talks like i know the
guy yeah i think i thought that
was him no
what's the deal with basie he's like
half seinfeld ah josh manco half man
he's like a centaur epstein felt janey
loves shiny this picture send me the
picture and i will confirm or deny
god i send you this picture oh
wait how earth is at the song
you just say i've been listening to
that song on repeat a week now
so we're now almost was gonna play
it today
a why didn't you i forgot you
were waiting for me but that was
really force it's the the fourth guys
josh mankiewicz yeah mankiewicz yeah make-a-wish maybe
um who's related to xiaomi miui ah
the writer of citizen kane he's oh
he's a monk yeah really yes yes
yes he's just descendant of that
at manque citizen kane say saucepot so
why did you say rosebud at the
end of citizen kane well did you
watch us slick
it's because it was my slight but
i think he doesn't sort of look
like that guy to dunkin donuts look
like what guy he has never seen
joe jersey they just blend together because
they all are they all told damon
that yeah yeah but anyway yeah the
he talks like it sounded like you're
doing something like this it's like it's
like and and he asked questions
he knows the answer to buddy doesn't
let incredulously well you go so incredulous
don't by the way they don't not
look alike yeah they are sort of
their hands so palace maybe there's a
lot of the same faces all the
same like like a suit survive name
same like grinder
same grinder profile
yeah i've seen these guys before
matches played today mary it's like it's
basically like i just haven't watched an
episode on hulu and it's just like
um you know those little types of
true crime stories of a person who
marries someone who turns out to have
like a dark secret or that co
fuckin asshole like what it's too late
you married me what kind of see
secrets yeah you could do about it
what kind of secret is too dark
to keep um
until after you're married you know like
you you should be able to have
some secrets that like after you're married
you're like oh yeah by the way
this happened to me in my life
okay well what's chewed i know i
don't have what i'm saying like what
if if if you found out because
this because you're gonna have some weird
conversation with cool up later
number nine cool what's not cool to
tell chua i mean your spouse one
spouse um you know what i mean
like if you found out that oh
by the way before we got married
by the way this this was my
lifestyle or this happened to me like
when i was a bigamist ah i
am married
harry doyle sound like a mirror before
notice during before and that is married
to many people in the genus know
i like to be in the nudd
but but
i've never said it out loud so
if i say something
but i guess it is married before
is that's something that would be weird
if like oh yeah he was american
this you're married to my know what
a big mess is what i have
changed the fucking subject okay with you
ma
when i'm going back to my original
original question before you start doing bad
the secret would have to be something
really something i wouldn't care about it
all because i think anything that is
like my lifestyle was this or whenever
i go why have you never brought
that up we've talked about every single
thing right and then you're gonna tell
me like how often this a question
for you guys since you've been married
moe long time how often
often do you have a new story
that you have or your spouse that
you like oh wow i feel like
it's so rare now yeah i mean
it's rare i'm we've mike and i
have been together like five years yeah
it's like it's it's ah rare condition
in this day and age to find
news especially spend
so much time together now but i
but i feel like it just happened
recently where cool up is like deaf
you ever done that and i said
oh you know when i was especially
because i had you know forty years
before i met her before she was
even born so yeah i loved a
lot of my time and come on
roadways even freaking bribery free
um i feel like a prompt will
sometimes shake a story like that yeah
yeah um but what's funny to me
is you're so used to hearing the
other person we're so used to hearing
each other stories told to a third
boss right yeah that it's like i
sort of enjoy that in a weird
way of like okay she's going to
tell that story yeah you know maybe
i have a little pardon where i'm
supposed to i know because you can
rebind at some point you know yeah
um i sort of like that that
routine that happened recently yeah we're talking
to i'm planning by the way about
not knowing a new story we were
talking to us conquering crazy and
the wife started telling a story and
the husband like kept interjecting going like
you forgotten what the story is even
about he he knew the story way
more he's like you're missing every point
it's important to it and she was
like well i'm just trying to stay
you know and and of course like
everything all the details he added in
were like i'm just trying
huh trying to tell star
always relied on the cognizant strangers i'm
trying to keep a thought in my
head but it's not possible
um but no i mean yeah club
and i've been together or twenty one
years i guess so yeah yeah wow
will be hard you've had most of
your lives together yeah shit man most
of hers mostly hers you've had most
of coop's life together i'm almost so
you know all of her yeah you
might have some story
no honestly i was not interested in
anything she was talking about okay so
the first fifteen years you didn't hear
a word no but i mean there's
your busy talking i think it would
happen it would definitely have to be
well there's two categories that would have
to be stories before we met each
other but also stories that were told
early on in our relationship that we've
forgotten yeah like so
every once in a while i'll timidly
say hey could you remind me of
the story because i
i guess i in previous please say
these lore stories no but i guess
maybe in previous relationships i would have
been lambasted for your not paying attention
to me when i tell you stories
but i'm like damn i've had i've
had previous relationships like that it's like
well no i just forget details you
could remind me maybe yeah neil campion
co op is always really good about
oh no yeah of course this was
twenty years ago i told you this
well okay so it happened this way
i was eleven hey
thank god she was ten
um we need to a break
welcome back everybody it's freedom still you're
still listening to this that's right can
you even use getting chilly out here
in the pet teal and yes we
had to do this at a very
specific time and the sun is starting
to go down and lauren starting to
get cold so pretty soon we'll be
ah it will be hollywood nights in
the hollywood
yeah they would de yeah that's always
makes me think of you guys bobs
yeah i used to play him i'm
sure we talked about this before but
we used to play bob seekers greatest
hits as we were on tour with
three-day was awesome it was awesome then
was i really miss that so muck
and awesome well whenever theaters open back
up again let's go back out and
do another one
okay or love to um but not
until then no i don't know where
we would perform you would be stupid
but where would they perform and why
do you have any desire to do
stand up in front of a bunch
of honking cars i i really don't
know are you saying honking like big
honking cars i'm saying in place of
fucking
ah i really don't i really don't
i mean it seems so not fun
to me i say more power to
anyone who wants to do that i
i'm not i would not if if
it works for you i'm not going
to try to talk you out of
it but it does not appeal to
me at enjoys it as much as
like they just feel like they have
to keep going yeah i mean
seem like working on their actor would
be hard if you are so bad
so i'm gonna stay home and keep
getting fat you have things to do
but my priority right now honestly i
want everything to stop yes i have
this desire of just like everything stop
can i guess everything dying didn't i
mean i know what you mean i
wish the world would stop in my
life who did i wish
i just want like a free pass
to like have a month of just
fuckin watching holiday movies i'm i'm so
i'm sorry he willed the summer passed
and this january we were in december
when we're taping this but summers kinda
like that nothing happens really it just
feels like we have to do a
million podcasts oh i haven't really
yeah december is my busy mom and
i have a million other little things
that keep popping up like you have
to watch a million i actually do
watch my little banks
so to catch up on that and
then i have all these like voiceover
jobs and things that are very simple
but it's like a kind of wig
the pandemic makes it feels like it
just fills your day if you have
one where you have this like stress
of weight everything should be shut down
because we can't do anything but then
you also have responsibilities yeah so you
feel busier than ever but
but you also feel like the stress
of not being able to do anything
means that you shouldn't just do anything
which you should just be on a
cow right you know but i had
yeah i should be on account and
you should be on a couch like
a month i always say in july
and august where i was just on
a couch and didn't do anything
was that when you hurt your butt
that was my ah post law just
think of injury he could have i've
been talked about but i talked about
well yeah when you host all fell
out paul funny but
how does that even get in there
while he was trying to do something
fun for himself he tucked his ball
right up into his bow
it fell out when he sat down
on it out to moms nobody rolled
down his slide all the way into
the pool you guys knowing why i
was out makes this really insensitive
ah sorry i have no sense of
time and i have no idea what
you're talking about i'm had surgery i
told you guys
to put you all back about it
just sort of
really for lunch oh my
ah
guys i would not have done that
honestly sounds like five years ago yeah
first of all yes second of all
oh my god
so yes it's like oh oh my
god for the listener i have not
talked about this but i had a
surgery in july and ah it's an
i'm so sorry it's it's side is
the front of human centipede that's right
i'm a seinfeld center now seinfeld on
the top what's the girl and a
horse from the bible
centaur fuck me zoo now i have
horses
i had what is called a tizi
surgery ouch ouch indeed and it was
ah part of ah cool up and
i call up has talked about this
on her podcast so i feel like
i can talk about but it's part
of our continuing ibf saga yeah and
a tizi surgery i had no idea
what it was but you knew what
it was i have heard about because
i listened
to this podcast sperm cas which is
a really good podcast that my friend
molly hockey does um all about her
journey to get pregnant which has been
a couple years of this podcast now
she's been trying all these different paths
and and she has guests on who
talk about their journeys and someone did
talk about this surgery so weird named
tizi it's like
pleasing and ttc tct are you ready
for surgery
but they they okay so what it
is is essentially they get better sperm
if they from me you can say
it from me from paul i'm great
i'm not gonna be shaped straight to
the source because they got bingo right
at the wedding and travel through the
pain i'm full i don't know what
it is about the pain that dirty
is up this
yeah but they they want to get
a straight from the sport the source
rusty in there it might be like
paulo are supposed to shove through a
q tip or a cleaner once a
year pipe cleaner
that happened to me my cert my
other big surgery when i was six
they had to put a no no
they had to put a camera in
there and that's what a fucking wyatt
yeah yeah glamour shots for these and
they were like this is roomy
yeah weaker than it looks on the
outside
but no so they they and they
and so they they sold it to
me like it's really simple you come
in it's outpatient you come in we
just make a little tiny incision in
your testicle and then you're home you
put ice on it the next day
you're fine wow and so i was
like yeah okay sure
so even talking about that in a
casual tone does not make it seem
okay to talk about ball stuff as
being really no idea like the sec
demi's like they're like you're madame next
day yeah i had a friend he
was like you had to probably shouldn't
be i had a friend who got
one who's trying to say like yeah
it's no big deal just yeah i
got it it was fine yeah that's
great i loved it yeah it was
grateful
nothing i'm gonna do it again but
so i i got there to do
it and i got on the table
and you're and i knew i wanted
to get up like all fours yeah
it was just like come on daddy
do it from behind balls first
could they put they they tell you
i mean i i knew i would
be out for it so i don't
know why i didn't think i would
be awake but you ain't you weren't
you weren't for no you're not out
for it oh and so it's like
they they they numb you i don't
like things like that slapping your face
to keep you awake no well oh
so they they numb you and then
and then at some
point he's your sort of names like
do you feel this do you feel
this i'm like no i mean you
can feel him pressure in him moving
around but i can't feel pain so
he's like ok this is the unpleasant
part which a doctor should never say
this is my unpleasant part before it
happens because then i started to faint
and i was like oh god no
am i
oh
those are my balls yeah this timing
his last words were munro i had
a doctor one time do this thing
i had to get something kind of
painful done and he was like he
was doing the thing and then it
hurt and then he goes ready and
i said yeah then he goes i'm
done i was like
like i thought the hurting part was
not it yet then because you said
are you ready and then it was
a psychological trick users yeah i was
like funny or something right this is
bad i think people should just do
what they're gonna do and checking everyone's
oh are you having any discomfort only
funny doctor ever was house well huck's
all other doctors shouldn't try what
about me you never say my hugh
laurie story really quick from when i
was doing holmes and watson and i
met him in the dressing or in
the trailer and he said someone said
like he'd been like waiting around to
land there like sorry to keep you
waiting all day and he was like
the weightings fine it's the work i
hate
very mature army yeah did you see
this video there's a video i'm not
done here but the balls by the
way no no none of you are
ah there was this video just saw
this video of a doctor giving a
baby ah a shot know and it's
so the dockers they drag baby right
right and so he like you you
have to watch it a bunch of
times
to see when the job happens wow
the baby never cries laughing the whole
time well that that it's amazing it
makes you kind of go well you
should never we should never
if stopping babies exact don't fill it
up like it's gonna be bad like
just go yes just do it just
and so so i started to sort
of like go out and they had
they and like run out and go
get smelling salts and cool up within
the ruling source that happens if you
faint like wouldn't be okay while all
the color out of my facing thing
to yes
they fall asleep oh okay so something
doesn't do anything it is bad for
the process no that's safe maybe don't
think anyone ever wants anyone to fate
like probably bad for anyone to fei
mean it just feels like if you
already laying down and they're doing something
to you they'll just wait for you
to get back up but it's like
i get knocked out but i get
up again and go to
right on my balls
so in any case i was i
got this the smelling salts and i
was fine so they have always like
smelling salts yeah like hospital operating rooms
old english made damon what was in
there oh yeah i don't know but
they like wave it under your nose
and i was after after like one
wave i was like okay fine they're
like no we gotta keep going lee
stop doing this sinus
like i get it i'm i smell
it and it stinks i don't like
it i'm wasting these so thorough
ah wells
throw these away these are bad salts
give me good service
so this all started because we said
he but his balls but yeah we
said that
yeah wow
yeah i want to say oh yeah
what fair i want to say that
the whole like hey you'll one day
you're out you'll be walking around after
one day was bullshit yeah because a
month later it took like a month
of being on the couch where i
was just like
it was bad it was horrible yeah
anyway but hey it all was worth
it yeah alright got him his ears
my name now i have three ball
this is what you do like you
just pretend there's a baby all the
time on podcasts like this dark servant
type situations you see serving my guy
yeah servant that show is really ridiculous
alice it was really scary to me
for a while then it became a
little ridiculous when you realize like oh
this isn't going anywhere yeah exactly
they're never gonna explain why that guy
got in the crib they didn't that's
the thing those really weird things i
didn't they didn't pay off no not
at all i thought it was a
really interesting story but it started out
scaring but it didn't just didn't it
literally went nowhere and there's gonna be
another season there is this there should
be a holy story there should be
maybe there's gonna be whole new doll
what are you talking about sermons oak
on an aged shaman oh it's just
shami lauren i would say rose who
i love i think she's like a
maze i once saw him coming off
a stage where i was about to
be interviewed and he was just being
interviewed nice i saw him and i
went oh hi like i knew him
because i thought i knew him because
he's been in all of his work
and he was right the twist is
we've never
meh
he was greeted me very warmly it
was like hi people i thought he
met you too yeah probably people never
know what's going on yeah you've gotta
give yourself more i feel like the
older i get the more like harsh
i'm being with my mental process i
was thinking this today of like you
know how like my parents are like
heart hold onto things and they're harsh
on themselves and
like my mom still brings up things
that she was that she's been carrying
around for fifty years of like you
know i remember when i scolded you
fifty years ago oh i didn't know
that stuff like that so i feel
like i was and i always go
mom you gotta list let stuff go
but then something popped in my head
the other like yesterday and it was
like i gotta do my advice
ice to my mom and just start
letting yeah oh my god it's such
a good thing to do last night
i was falling asleep and i was
like remembering this fight i had with
this neighbor i had and i was
like she was a bitch and then
i was going on forever and i
just wanted i was like kind of
reliving it and then i mean some
of the same things i wasn't feeling
bad i was feeling more like
i could send more stuff or like
i say did i let her have
it enough and then you know it's
like why i'm even thinking about this
listing my brain i just like going
in circles i have that over the
summer like one night i was lying
in bed and like some old like
ancient thing popped into my head and
i was like re litigating in my
mind i'm
oh what am i doing i know
i forgot all about this so weird
you're brainless wanting to tell me all
ones that you used to like go
to bed a lot of nights like
going through arguments in your head with
the people that you would just talk
to or something like that where you
were all i had written that into
a show yeah
drinking show where we're telling it to
me though that was like oh yeah
during the show i was
i dedicated the show to you all
he wrote this conversation they have with
you but yeah that was that was
a common thing that i used to
do is to i used to go
over these just like ruminate on shit
and just like go over like what
you shot anyway yeah if they say
this i'm going to say this yeah
i have i would plot it out
yeah yeah yeah when of course it
never happens that way yeah
it's stupid waste of time yeah i
mean it's do you do it about
things that you think might happen or
things that already did happen i used
to do it about things that i
thought might happen yeah like like if
i was if i was out with
a friend this thing and yes exactly
well what a piece of work is
man yeah it's really a waste of
insulate waste of life to waste of
i really feel like and i talked
about it a lot but i'm really
addicted to social media and i've been
thinking i really need to stop this
i would really like to spend my
my mind times doing something like my
mind literally like a moneybox
many bucks are just wasting away hugs
i'm in my
but moneybox is a funny way to
describe you get paid what we call
buddy
but i find myself just going even
if i was just sitting here at
that would be better than this like
well i know i know things would
be better than this and then reading
obviously would be better than that and
doing a task or a craft or
learning like i was learning piano for
like a couple of weeks lie
like oh later like i was supposed
to do like i was supposed to
do and tap dancing a yeah and
covert stroke when using covert asics yeah
covert we can doing it during covert
pianos are filthy and i was like
really enjoying it and then i always
i stopped i completely forgot everything i
learned now i just start over but
i'm like i just don't i
had to put the phone down and
go this is the time to do
something yeah yeah cool op and i
were talking about like okay so say
we do have a kid what has
to adjust in our lives yeah in
order and and you can think of
like whoa we're not going to be
able to to do as much work
or we're not gonna be able to
travel as much i said realistically honestly
if we just
it stopped reading twitter i know it's
enough time to take care of it
oh yeah so think about that with
like kids like i don't want to
be on my phone all the time
yeah with my kids in the future
like and then thinking about people i
follow who are always like storing their
their time with their kids
and i'm like stop like yeah i
don't know like there's some what if
you gave birth to a phone
oh they'll be really cool know what
it actually doesn't mean that point weirdly
i said i feel let me call
black mirror i want it i wanna
go back on something i said because
i feel like the people i follow
like like a celebrity or something who's
like always doing this with their kids
then i but i'm thinking about my
friends who do it with their kids
i like it because i get to
see the catalogue and i feel like
i actually know the kid
did because i we even though we
live for a part i'm like oh
i get to see them every day
and so there's something nice about that
there but people it's like you sir
it's like a you know when you
see it kind of situation where some
people do it it's like exactly like
pornography some people are
you know when you see it some
people will name is when the definition
of pornography from like this i can't
define it but i know it when
i see yeah like saying bill clinton
when something's upset huh you know what
i see and i see it every
day yeah see um that there's some
people that when they the way they
document their kids it's like this is
i
i this is sweet and it's wholesome
yeah whatever and then there's other people
where it's like this is just content
yes there is a difference yeah there's
a big difference and that's where it
feels bad and well but we like
making content with our dogs that's fine
and it's fun without you said daughtry
yeah yeah i said oh but you
know what i mean like yeah with
different address
putting them up in order to take
a picture in a dog in the
dog isn't thinking anything of that child
eventually would yeah true i trip out
on that the kids that are like
i follow i follow follow kids this
i think she's around town this little
this little asian baby um who is
so adorable
and like the the excuse me mama
or no no you know what i'm
talking about yes this this child is
pre verbal okay she is the the
herbal like in the usual suspects yeah
pre verbal kent
what a name what a name yes
ma'am variations character verbal what an actor
what a name
in life yes weird um the the
account is m y dot h i
n my ah hyeon a hin i
don't know how to say i do
not know how to say it aloud
okay this baby has a real person
she's a little toddler real personality she's
really funny her parents have given her
the way
aztec
but she's she's hilarious and it's like
this kid you could tell that the
parents are just fascinated by this child
like she's hilarious real there's just something
about her right and you can tell
like they are looking at her like
just shaking their heads like i can't
believe you know what a weirdo she
is i'm fall
knowing yeah it's absolutely worth your follow
absolutely wow
um we have to take what i
call a break oh really i do
i'm sorry guys but just were doing
so well i know we were really
going along at a quick clip there
hey really we're just real quick to
tell you guys i got tmc surgery
oh no yes they put they grabbed
part of a cubicle on my chest
oh
a big sippy gum yeah
it will be right back
welcome back to three um bag boy
wow we are about to play a
cheer oh something at your stupid ass
is ready get your stupid ass is
ready because we do something awesome and
we're not gonna stop now and don't
be dumb about it just enjoy
you such as this so stupid they
enjoyed the shit of sit back and
enjoy the cheer
um this is submitted by jonathan hi
jonathan is this the amazing jonathan no
just regular ah regular jonathan this is
a minute by the acceptable jonathan it's
called nick naming now here's how we
play someone is introducing a newer friend
to an old friend the old friend
has to
nickname to call the mutual friend and
the backstory has to be explained to
the new friend option to be explained
by the mutual friend alone or tagged
him with the old friend i think
if one person has to explain the
nickname that is the way it should
go so yeah the old friend gives
the nick
cname to the mutual friend the the
burden is on the mutual friend to
explain the nickname to the new friend
okay so the person introducing the nickname
has to explain it is that we
know the person introducing the nickname saddles
the person with the nickname when technical
asia okay got it okay so ah
why don't paul why don't you introduce
me to lauren and will test this
out
yes okay so we're we're at a
party what
hey stop double dipping the premises already
doing mystery was how wow what year
is it a man okay
oh it's so good to see hey
how did you see you mean i
been pretty good i mean ah you
know twenty twenty was a dumpster fire
someone said that one site that was
so funny and i thought i would
say did i i had that on
my bingo card that somebody was saying
that to me cause it goes funny
oh my gosh look
oh hey i can't put down both
of you in the same row we've
never met lauren hi this is lauren
this is scott hi hi to me
too i of course know him as
the intimidator oh wow yes that's how
you know him yeah i call me
intimidate okay why well they call me
when i say i mean paul calls
me the intimidator no one else calls
me that intimidate or um the intimidatory
yes of course ah because the first
time i ever met paul
he was down on the ground he
was he was scrubbing the floor at
the job that he used to have
which was um he used to work
at arby's and he would anytime anyone
would walk in he would say sir
this is an arby's is an explanation
of his nickname yeah yeah about yeah
yeah yeah and anyway he was down
there scrubbing on the floor
and i walked in and he said
sir this is an arby's i said
yes i know i'm here to order
arby's food and i was standing above
him i always say that when i
go into a facet of course of
course i've ever seen barrington i was
i was standing above him and i
was so right a bag of burger
king sang just whatever you can fit
in a bag sounds good right now
here's how much money i have give
me
a bag of food you mean whatever
size bag will buy a bag of
some burning
so standing above him and i tried
to step over him in order to
get to the counter and above over
i wonder if he'll ever go under
and we'll know because i ended up
tripping and stomping on paul's back how
answer to where i was like standing
with one foot on him and he
was helpless he was on his back
helpless
like like a little turtle on it's
one of my back and i was
on my yeah it really was confused
visual and um and ah he thought
that was very intimidating but that's not
why okay i'm called the intimidator that's
just backstory yeah oh clearly so cut
to smash cut to in fact oh
no i see someone i want to
talk to
oh
oh wow hey i liked her not
even i have to go to the
bathroom i see someone i want to
talk to really like her do you
think she likes me back know why
i think i think he'll sit there
and listen to my story was that
most of it or
it was yeah there's only one sentence
left
okay now my god yeah introduce me
to paul okay this is a different
party yes as a sock hop hey
daddy oh i don't wanna rock rock
rock rock all bard autoradio rock daddy
oh yeah what's up just listen
sing to the sokal music hey um
i want you to meet a good
friend of mine this is this is
lauren but i call her mommy oh
oh mama mio that's an interesting yeah
yeah where does that come from well
it's so interesting call by the way
hi nice to meet you i'm calling
him daddy oh yeah my name is
paul i'm laura it's not a nickname
it's
just what we call everyone these days
yeah scott i'm a father of my
last name is ogilvy
scott my last name is redenbacher by
the way okay i don't know if
that's important to anyone but i just
thought i was a germain so scott
like wakes up every day crying in
his crib and he's hired me to
change his diaper and sore
rt of
you play with him on the floor
like teach him out a rollover and
lift his head and stuff and so
he calls me mommy oh because he
that's what he pays me to be
so i'm actually surprised that he was
willing to share that information with you
given how how personal really is yeah
um he has a super super fetish
out being treated like a baby and
i think him calling you daddy oh
he uses the the sort of time
period as an excuse but well i'm
found out yes i want you to
be my daddy mr ogilvy oh i
have to go why to talk to
someone else i don't want to be
here anymore oh okay goodbye
i have to go why
wow hey why to go so bad
oh oh wait so who's left me
okay and it's always scott the answer
will always be me if the lord
god has gone already
learn introduces you to me what it
is yeah or no you and i
think even paul and okay got it
and what kind of party area it
is a gender reveal funerals are real
finally figured out what this grandpa send
yeah
um what a sombre but exciting coach
okay wow well yeah he's always so
secretive about yes he or she he
or she zack wearing baggy clothes never
could quite figure it out but this
is very excite me i'm sad that
it took this line and kind of
twisted that we're doing this via
we let this person go what is
i oh have you met scott yeah
i know both of you oh wait
yeah but you don't know each other
who is a mutual i'm introducing you
to yes oh okay oh you guys
are friends maybe you've just seen me
on tv that's probably what oh yeah
that's probably one tops he's the guy
who ran away
eighteen consecutive episode yes lauren and i
are old friends but you're you're a
different friend so yeah scott this is
my friend paul but paul i go
i know paul maura's big birds bet
bestie pinboards best ya they call me
so lori calls me big bird's best
lie
i mean well some sort of sniffle
up against reference know i'd be happy
to tell you
the reason that lauren calls ne here
scott a big birds don't go anywhere
i no i really want to go
to stay for a minute he's gonna
tell you alright the doors are locked
it's a locked door gender reveal fuel
to me i could just do laps
around the nope no okay just tell
him tell him what you wanted to
say here's why lauren calls me big
birds bestie
laura was born in albuquerque new mexico
and at the time that she was
where my brother was born and there
were strange laws in place they call
them blue laws which is on sundays
you could not do certain things one
thing you were not allowed to do
in albuquerque new mexico was two
to pretend you had seen tv shows
that you had not seen oh on
just one day a week or once
a year could do it any other
time but on sundays you had to
run if you hadn't seen a show
you to admit you hadn't seen that
show so would people wait until sundays
and try to catch people maybe if
you stop asking questions i will
yeah totally silent because i could just
jump around sorry wow
and tell you that your theory is
really um he wants to get his
point out before you respond yeah it's
all parts was more i mean it's
kinda how big birthday parties like where
people talk to each other guy even
each guy even comparable be if you
know a story where someone tells a
story and the other person lists and
the other person never gets to ever
i actually want to talk to somebody
else yeah i wanna talk to somebody
else you're both free to do that
okay bye bye
good game good game
as always a good game when we
ended up hearing
because never get to point out
something anyone got to speak
yeah did you say it i guess
oh okay well good shit really good
shit did were all done for another
episode night has fallen um the sun
has gone down i got a message
in my jerry portal oh are you
do you have to go check it
out i want to add a lot
in my during porno um
lawrence i love all for jury duty
i guess i'm jealous i don't like
jury duty i love the jury portal
though i love being judged really fun
to use the portal to portal lying
to save time i'll say janey i
can't do anything right now i'm entering
the portal guys next episode we're going
to talk about if we've ever done
jury duty no more chand
i bet none of us have ah
oh hey alright well we're gonna talk
about that next episode until then um
that's our promise that's hey will we
remember see you next week we are
definitely going to talk about whether or
not we've done three okay we'll see
alright by everyone but oh what we're
on instagram threesome
and ah we ah we post ah
reference photos for each week's episode or
why not and it's fun so follow
us go follow it yeah three m
usa twitter and instagram we love you
goodbye la vi i'm not gonna say
i love you no more i love
you and decided i'm not going to
throw that around casually anymore
a
uh