don't ask us to say
show me
ah can i sing a song yeah
please this is inspired by my travel
mug alright let's hear it for people
on the go there's wow wow food
market fast fast shopping night and day
neat so out if it's a really
really good fucking mug thank you now
it looks super eighties i love it
i think we should post so picture
but i'll take a picture now throw
it away i'm social we was so
good i want to throw one i
don't i don't get that take a
smiley picture with your mud dvd yeah
take this file a picture with your
body take a solid picture i guess
via a picture take a picture with
ya ma go but up we will
all go out to meet her with
her mug welfare nah we will all
go out to meet her with her
ma grandma we will all go out
to here yeah oh wow
nah but she'll be riding six white
mugs when chico's bus schmucks that was
the jingle for wawa know at the
two made it i was growing up
that's good and it's funny how jingles
yeah they have their their sound or
timers around an era yes that's why
you know but
gold can stay don't always do that
game where they like play the fucking
ah commercial and you're like yes what
year it was right okay that's fair
swearing by the production style alright having
a show they want well fuck
they play one day what came day
hey play the commercial and then you
hear it and you go nineteen eighty
four bit that seems as possible honestly
i'm aiming commercial and i'll try to
play okay okay name a commercial mcdonalds
whichever yeah well that's fucking classic one
or not know what year it was
i remember this game
you'll know it from know but that's
the fun of it you guys okay
here we go play you because you
can kind of tell like that sounds
like it's really crispy okay first we
have to get through this redfin
i'm gonna say this was twenty twenty
three mac with a savory filial fish
well until your fish chicken my goodness
that looks good ok then give us
give us oh wait you're making mcdonald's
menu that changes everything yes no this
is from this year brian co yes
by the idea of gambling that's why
you ever heard that he's doing fine
however i was gonna go away in
the past then i heard that music
i want that's current federal
no but see this is what happens
see if you have this if you're
in his position you get your ear
that you get offered a bunch of
stuff and it's so easy to do
why why would you not do it
you just get buildings buildings buildings we
give to your grandchildren yeah yes the
grandchildren grandchildren excuse who will inherit a
burning cinder
or in the sky yeah totally totally
totally so you love that dog and
you take this gift from my my
ah brother sister-in-law it's really nice i
cherish the way we're giving brothers sister-in-law
gifts now well yeah shit
just say thanks for being my brother-in-law
thank you for being my brother in
law i did you hear my little
hitch rose like do i commit were
like hey check same thing yeah
guys stop mid song i genuinely like
almost want that i don't drink coffee
but i could put some water you
can someone and start a go fund
me for lower to get this and
the nico from me was at twenty
one dollars higher twenty five yeah you
looked it up oh you look so
much
raw food how much sandwich because is
that a coffee i would say coffee
tumbler tumbler travel mug travel travel mug
okay what's the tumbler thermos yeah thermos
it's a thermal sixteen dollars on ebay
used i know thank you i don't
want away right from wawa right where
wallace
direct from the source yeah i don't
see it on their site huh maybe
they're not selling them anymore
wow limited edition were valuable yeah they
have a whole bunch of ones but
not that one but though i really
appreciated that they got me like the
retro know i love one because this
is what i grew up with and
that's really when you loved going into
wawa i still do and so that
will do bro is that what i
know you try to sleep like when
you were there i think although at
the time i was not drinking coffee
but that's definitely what their logo was
this was the yeah i went to
wawa a few times with you and
another time that i was there you
took us through one in where was
it i told philadelphia and you were
just like your cock of the walk
you're showing us around guys me i
know that back i don't think i
have this thing in my head where
i sometimes think philos
adelphia is a state
like i just it just sounds like
one it does it's it's almost more
famous than pennsylvania you know like how
much other stuff in pennsylvania thursday of
course like paper okay chinese is a
long rating is pretty low what's q
rating
it's like what people think of it
in a nutshell but yeah you're right
pittsburgh in penn or philadelphia or like
more famous than pennsylvania yeah i think
i think it should be pennsylvania philadelphia
it's not one of those places that
has a state identity you're right and
like new jersey as a state identity
yes exactly like pennsylvania if you go
like i'm from pennsylvania and i guess
i'd wonder if you are
amish yeah was there you know what
i have i wonder if i'm amish
i do wonder that honestly just wow
reveal the answer at the end of
this episode yeah i thought about it
i've wondered because of just how scared
you get when i turned on the
lights
yeah
scared hey ah tells me i'm a
witch i well i was okay yeah
i know what i have the editor
know with it's new england i'm like
no newline loser it's a region it's
not a state ah well that's because
of like new england patriots and stuff
like
because they're trying to like yeah they're
trying to like oh we're we're that
football team of like eight states like
utah midwest cougars is that what is
wait a minute i like midwest cougar
oh wow yeah it wasn't that yeah
okay so i was in chicago here
we go again she's yeah yeah jackie
i go doctor jackhammer humanities
these performance yes it was very nice
i made it back i did a
two hour signing afterwards and i met
a lot of people who say you
don't know sign language ah are you
one of those fakers he's so offensive
i've been faking it where i've been
thinking that i don't know it oh
that's interesting that's doubly hard it's hard
like trying to speak fake english not
easy zip zap csaba boo yeah didn't
sound like english but so yeah we're
english
it's just english with zeus our gingrich
newt gingrich
do you think newt gingrich was when
someone was trying to speak english bad
beer summary
we need new newt gingrich
i always think new gingrich's estate to
bees yeah yea newt gingrich
have you ever heard that song it's
an italian song where they're mimicking what
english sounds like yeah oh no yeah
what's wrong here i like i can
up like this but biomedical know ah
but the data i find is good
yeah okay so i was in chicago
and i was
being i was doing a signing and
a lot of metal really a lot
of really nice people and a lot
of people said like oh i love
comedy bang bang because of the book
but they were saying but i've a
threesome is my favorite podcasts oh and
although we met a piss pig after
our show a lot of a lot
of this oh my god i only
one person who said i don't like
being called a piss big i said
well you voted for it so
yeah like you said and he said
i did vote forward i don't know
why i don't like it so much
yeah i don't understand yeah you guys
voted for this thing but see sometimes
the thing you know even with like
the president for example you'll vote yeah
and the person you didn't vote well
a lot of people were voting for
piss pig to vote against the other
nickname right right i think that
one was yeah yeah yeah much worse
sweetie so um yeah yeah just so
it's sweet oh yeah um no i
we met a delightful piss pay after
our show coupled with a lot of
people want me to ah call them
a piss pig when i made the
book oh wow like ah i love
our pimping really cute i also met
ah an artist amy trummer who gave
what is this man
magic three of us some wow okay
so wait she made this based on
the title of one episode oh bar
where art thou it's miss mixing up
waiting to poo and oh brother where
art though outfits i think this is
amazing it's tremendous it's basically our heads
on george
clooney and who will frame that friends
george clooney britt so great if movies
just were build george clooney john turturro
yes and then like nelson tim blake
nelson yeah so our head row our
heads on their bodies but then wearing
hats i'm winning the fucking wearing winnie
the pooh
no i didn't know what it was
i was like never heard it said
like what if i insisted it's john
turturro i'm half telling you this turturro
oh she gave these to me and
said will you really take these home
with you and i want to prove
on mike that i would dang he
just gotta just worry yet they're in
our he is soon to be in
the trash can oh my
kidding oh way way i'm putting this
in my bed i have that you
sleep with yeah i found that song
you're gonna cuddle okay okay wait wait
here he talks ah yeah you guys
talk oh yeah i'm right over here
hurry yeah yeah i'm lauren we had
a fun time last night yes we
did we did a fun show
and the improv show at dynasty typewriter
every sunday yes you can go to
that the monologist was doug jones the
tall thin man who does all the
monsters he also i know him best
from hocus pocus of course billy bathgate
yeah thank you wow with the last
name too
um he was he was great and
his stories were really fun yeah his
name is not billy basket and i
know okay i thought it was
yeah yeah the code may say long
freezing cold ninety nine to zo either
code may say i'm freezing
i choose alright
isn't that almost haunting oh shit fake
english yeah haircut so this is italian
people doing things yeah okay
uh who's given a boost when the
same shoes open the same it'll maybe
get to come the boss gun
okay imagine the sims take some time
again to stay yet
is this the thick english yeah winston
do you understand it and remember the
last time you know this part right
here that's the banking bush the horns
yeah yeah that's what they that's what
they think we so much
now i did years ago at ah
ah oh my variety show i did
ah a phonetic version of this with
ah my renault real wow i had
i listened to it a million times
jotted down i wrote down what the
sounded like wow i used to have
that do that one when i was
in a band for likes covers we
would do sure you'd have to like
get one line jotted down rewind it
again make sure you audit right all
they remember doing that for girls on
film which is like so hard oh
now you just look it up yeah
yeah right yeah i think i'll kids
have it
so easy now thank you just look
up whatever lyrics they want you dropped
your dongle king your dongles out
you dropped this thing it's europe your
dongle yeah you dropped your dongle king
but a lot of people were saying
that they love three-day because of the
chaotic energy in it it makes them
feel like ah what their own head
feels like oh my god so yeah
i actually really like that i like
that i relate to that that that
gave me a chill yeah yeah it
should yeah
it is i mean this show is
pure chess pure chess absolutely shite your
chao chye love a little little charles
um you're like morning and monday yes
yeah people are still doing that sometimes
i love the smell of blank in
the morning i know it's so oh
i love the smell old it's for
maintains in the morning when did apocalypse
now come out seventy nine something like
that yeah so it's been now forty
four years we have to stop saying
gotta retire it but i'm the rafters
some people are still saying
where's the beef right well that's crazy
but i mean that doesn't bother me
so much okay you always say that
well because of clara pillar look i
love the lady as much as the
next guy keeps her alive i feel
like when we say it high you
have to think that us talking about
her all the time her ancestor ancestors
know her
descendants descendants or ancestors might be listening
the ancestors are all this oh my
gosh are they maybe they're all around
us there on the walls no heard
you have to love it right yeah
to have to love it i i
think we need shirts that say where's
the beef i think we do next
i think we do our next photo
shoot
shoot in shirts that say where's no
read em no no our where's the
picture things i read aware of this
oh it's better yeah whereas the three
numbers the piss pigs so we have
to try to five years the freedom
back says whereas the pittsburgh shirt said
where's the beef at yeah just to
be fat
yeah that comes right for you a
lot of people with ass be fat
whereas the be fat beef were the
baby it's like um be meats footwell
fat ace
e
learn you wearing a hat today i
am so ah and here's the outta
control it's out of control today what's
going on just you know i woke
up looked crazy i didn't have time
to deal and i put the hat
oh i want to say okay so
so i was in chicago speaking right
why i was late today because i
finally opened up
here at seven after wow and i
was in a few minutes you're a
few minutes after that but ah yeah
so i was so i zoomed into
chicago for just a day and all
it was just yeah it was just
as enemies hit the enemies i ran
around airport around the venue really clever
and then there's joe worry he has
the zoomy you just gotta let
it out so yesterday i had a
nice leisurely morning got up had you
know ordered room service breakfast and then
then went to the airport ah for
a twelve forty five flight civilized ah
left at eleven it was nice took
a taxi got to the airport and
t s a precheck all you know
one
in line it was so beautiful put
my phone down on the on the
scanner and the guy said are you
at the right airport oh that has
hey in chicago did not real i
mean it's been melee huh it's been
so long since i've traveled because we
always drive through there yet there's two
airports there i know well real quick
pop is that one time
i was taking my cows flying my
cat to l a um before i
moved officially and your cat told the
taxi driver the wrong thousand of i
was in the car with my dad
and had my cat and it's like
bag that was too small and it
was like that was kind of chaotic
already she was like losing fur by
the second just like freaking out and
like um and then
they were like almost to the airport
and go they don't have southwest at
o'hare it's a fucking midway and then
my dad's like oh i do now
because that's where i was southwest at
o'hare o'hare now oh they never used
to is always midway interesting yeah well
that was how i knew i was
wrong and then my um my dad
knows the city so well that we
actually got there and
you got there and hey well i
was like he goes i said oh
what do you think i should do
and the very nice cs age and
you said well it's about a forty
minute drivers had no i'm not gonna
make it he said well go back
down to southwest go back home go
back and see it change and see
if they can change it so i
basically turned into a ah monster fort
eighteen our ah honestly oh why was
that so crazy why couldn't you get
on another what happened i they just
didn't have anything everything had a super
line there was no chance he would
have made it to other know because
i was i went through security probably
a twelve o five
or something i am the end it
was a twelve forty yeah yeah so
yeah so i basically just like hung
out in two different airports denver and
um o'hare just like watching movies on
my ipad sure so so long that
my ass really hurt from sitting down
and you didn't get an ass massage
yeah back yeah
so anyway i got here really late
last night and wow and i knew
all of fourteen hours that's crazy yeah
it's insane it's actually mentally legitimately insane
it made me hate the fact that
i went there
well it does make it super annoying
we're trying to pop in and pop
out and suddenly you're doing this bullshit
yeah that's hard i've gone to the
wrong airline where ah whatever reason oh
if it's like sometimes if if somebody
else is doing the travel for like
you know festival gig whatever everyone's trial
it's two different airlines yeah right so
on the way back right i just
go to del right and it's like
no that's american and yeah then it's
you may be fuck it's humiliating you're
late as you milk shit is doing
that's the way i was worried about
i felt emasculated yeah like less of
a man yeah yeah one day i
think everyone knew when they
saw you watching your movies there like
that it makes you feel like a
little boy a little really goes a
little boy who's being punished yeah like
you don't deserve the responsibility of an
adult no because you fucked up your
cab ride and now i'm taking away
your skateboard yeah that's sucks
it sucks to make a mistake no
x-box for you no no no no
no no no sewer three years oh
no no no no no no that
no soup for you what is it
what is that no it's like this
thing anyway how do i how do
you describe lauren you describe it okay
so on friends they had this thing
there was this guy the naked guy
it was now
not him it was his neighbor makey
guide neighbor and he had this obsession
with soup but his he would have
this like dominate chicks come and tell
me couldn't have soup and rice slap
him and say no soup for you
oh like across the face or the
ass
but this was like primetime she would
put jump into like plastic baggies and
slap him with the plastic bag you've
sued yeah that actually sounds kinda nice
it does it sounds good it's hot
that sounds good have you ever been
to like the russian massages where they
slap you with like branches yeah i
have not oh my god that does
not appeal to me i was fine
have you ever been to the korean
spas and they like they get
scrubby delicous seal no basically it will
do they make you bark like a
seal they deal um no it's like
the place that i would go in
l a before the pandemic um
yeah it's like a ah like the
women are all the women who are
doing the massages are in like like
a bra and massage
um aaron bra and underwear yeah yeah
it's it is that like it's not
a bathing suit it's like a broad
underwear why because they are going to
get all wet they're like dumping anyone
scream scribbling down with with assaults and
they just scrape scrub the body and
then you come all this bathing suit
can yeah bathing suits are the bra
and underwear of this i don't know
but but it's not
i'm a terrorist and you're make you
happy like you know what i'm talking
about yeah i do it's easy to
see right oh i know yeah i've
heard about this like i've never gotten
underwear is more breathable so maybe it's
like they just change a bunch of
times a day if you're bathing suit
all day everyday and getting wet that's
not good for your vagina what do
you want for your fare
but just what's the best thing for
your vagina trash bag over your clothes
swimwear and crop top and shorts put
trash in daisy dukes yeah you're talking
yeah yeah that seems good and high
heels
we have to take a break okay
and we're back wow what a break
that was so much really good break
woo we erase ah when we ran
around we all got the zombies now
i'm tired there's one right though it's
a three-way tie we broke that ribbon
at the same time well yeah so
cool i was holding out a ribbon
with two hands it was actually kind
of tricky how she was doing because
we just ran right into it i
felt bad yeah yeah she we knocked
out over teeth i know she's dealing
with it now and i'm not too
worried you weren't either there's your problem
no and she seemed to find she
really you know she didn't wanna make
it our problem yeah they're the two
front teeth which are the easiest replace
from what i understand why
i think that is um you can
order them in bulk so the dentist
has a bunch of miniature got it
and they're just chick that's right yeah
the good thing about using chocolates for
teeth is that when your brothers paddy
just chew your teeth exactly yeah and
then you just replace them with is
cheap when i was a kid i
loved chocolates yeah i loved the way
they looked they were very tactile yeah
i loved the name of flavor i
like biting into on sir like they're
crispy
yeah crispy and then suddenly gummy i
yeah the word crispy crispy yes yeah
i love things that are crispy like
well let's run him down fried chicken
when i probably number one i was
level it's what i think of when
i hear the word crispy when i
was christmas or slang word crispy oh
well you would basically say like if
you
if like if you find someone you'd
be like oh yeah if you watch
like it was like yeah bird kind
of like before anyway chris bisbee yeah
we gotta we gotta start doing that
on this show wow is royal tell
me if it was local or no
universal yeah think it's universe okay well
maybe not do you really think it
was relegated nationwide
wide okay good point good good catch
i think i'm probably just earth but
yeah we'll see i don't think neil
armstrong ever started when he was on
the moon he might surprise me if
they if you wanted a crispy sandwich
when you get back in the ruck
mission control the music control do you
want a crispy side which up there
like crispy we're gonna send
another rocket up there with a crispy
sandwich to you and instead of saying
yes he said crispy
like it doesn't make sense that's right
he asked his acres yeah he asked
so maybe it's more like what wash
gives me what do you want for
do you want some sort of chicken
sandwich yeah but you i'd make it
chris i get sad when i think
about him still being up there do
i know because it's so it looks
over because we never brought him down
why didn't they yeah they didn't have
enough now so no it was truly
they forgot
he thought thank god i thought there
would be accusations from mentoring about this
they thought they brought him back and
when they looked back in the backseat
he wasn't there nobody was in there
no i mean nobody important are mine
i have been good for my business
people they didn't leave my name though
i don't know but yeah he wasn't
there and no nobody above the line
was
back right and two people forgotten they
didn't have as you said they didn't
have enough fuel to go back and
get him and so he said that
was that on me as paul said
as paul is playing you doing
one credit call me such a great
point that they didn't have enough fuel
lauren i did not say that i
didn't know and in this documentary they
were saying how long was this documentary
like three minutes about three minutes he's
been crying for the whole time moon
tears but the moon tears they come
out like gems yeah the name of
the line
they make little stars and that's actually
when you see the big dipper it's
it's it's yes yeah neil armstrong series
i didn't know his last name did
you
i knew it
yesterday i learned this is how you
can remember it because he had such
strong arm yeah he pulled himself up
to the moon okay neil strong arms
neil strong yeah there you go that's
how the popeye's real name that's also
your last name
oh my god i got these liberally
enlisted in the navy i got holly
these little when i was pregnant about
these vintage pants for a two year
old popeye and olive oil on them
she finally big enough yes why tie
i noticed what i found them in
the closet i pulled them out in
the the elastic was all crusty because
it was over us tya and so
i
at that address to the dry cleaners
to have them replace the elastic and
for weeks the woman i thought for
sure lost these little pants they're so
tiny and i kept being like i'm
popping into seat of my pants already
and she's like oh um i'll call
you i'll call you a clue and
she kept putting me off as long
as it take to do something like
that that's really i was i admit
that's the
kind of the question yeah and then
i had all three but i have
a theory of what i had also
given her a big blanket she's like
you pay when when i find the
what are not fine she's like pay
when the pants are ready i'm going
in i'm calling i'm checking out i'm
almost being like really annoying but i'm
kinda like where the just telling me
you don't have them just tell me
their lawyers i have to mourn this
loss because these are so cute yes
and then they appeared out of nowhere
they appeared everywhere all repaired no she
called me the next day she's calling
just fell from the sky entertain today
have the pants they're ready and then
i said great i went in she
do i wanna hear your theory because
i think i know what happened okay
okay you what did she did repair
the pants she didn't agree and they
looked so cute my theory
is that she didn't know what to
do because she thought the pants were
for you and she thought she's like
prowled never yeah get elastic big enough
she's yeah yeah how can she can
try to enhance got her foot yeah
and then then one day she happened
to see you
pushing hollywood stroll yeah and it all
made sense yeah the first time i
came in i didn't have holly the
second time i came and i did
have hall yes okay oh scholar yeah
um what's your theory my theory is
she thought they were brown and she
was saying they were brown like she
remembered them as being brown she sent
them off in a bag to somebody
else to do it she kept saying
look
for the brown pants they couldn't find
them i called the day before she
looked for the poppy but david ortiz
if the day before she called me
back i called her and said i'm
looking for those pants they're red they're
a little pants or red pants like
red red red then she next issue
oh i bet she's colorblind she thought
they were brown and popeye blood what
is the directly or a dog yeah
oh yeah and she licks them clean
but somehow drive if you want to
see the man well because they're dying
rather i didn't realize these republic pants
i didn't really cute they're very oh
do we get handed these down she
has so many ah you could borrow
em oh i want him back you
will have
to go through the same process that
lauren went through popeye pants in a
neat t-shirt yeah i know she's really
killing it that day wow she's already
wearing that when i got home from
the dry cleaner i said good let's
get these pants on i think it
emmys emmy feels enormous to me where
she's wearing one year old is she
wearing one year old thinks oh my
god i hope she's a big
fat baby she's so i don't mean
i don't mean fat necessarily just mean
she saw i mean she seems a
big she's yeah i mean she might
be i don't know do you think
charlie was in the ninety eighth percentile
for at least eight songs head she
really that mean again i'm ninety one
it's bigger than ninety eight percent of
other kids like out
of one hundred kids only two would
have a bigger head than home
or be taller or whatever right i
believe that's how i would explain percentile
wow i've never known what it meant
i guess i just yeah i guess
i've just come to that conclusion that's
why i think it means okay yeah
yeah because i mean is is in
the nineties on height and weight yeah
but eighties first for ahead which i
think is good because
been seeing a lot of like big-headed
babies out there yay what industry when
do we stop measuring things like that
but do i know what percentiles wherein
we shall measure each other's heads yeah
because at this point right get a
big protractor
i found out that i have kind
of a bigger head than i thought
because i bought this hat online and
then it was hat sizes one way
to do yeah it required a measurement
to pick out which size and i
was like yeah i have no idea
which one i mean i know what
my hat size is but i don't
know what percentile but i mean oh
that's a big head yeah it's technically
it's a large yeah because because you're
going to
if you are hats but i had
two small ahead was that too maybe
mine was mine was bigger than yours
i feel like i think so minus
seven and three eighths yeah i'm ah
oh i feel like she wants to
reach up to tie your hair off
like i was wearing a hat all
day yesterday in the airport and so
i like you pulled your head off
i went and looked at the
nicole i'm like oh it's about ah
seventy five behalf yeah where is my
where is my headwear is by having
glasses fuckin monkey came down from the
tree for forgot that was silly
but yeah i measured my head and
it was bigger than average i guess
we were not average it just meant
that i had to get the medium
large size as opposed to the small
medium why did you get this hat
what it was i really wanted this
i wanted it i coveted it for
about a year well it's ah it's
so it's like ah um what's the
word it's like a bucket hat made
of pilgrim hove
when um what's the word terry cloth
no no like bass gay jesus jesus
christ wrong but a cango right damn
straight yeah well the time it's not
a kindle i'm not samuel l jackson
know your angle
oh cool j where's the buckets i
mean all jackson wears the cap yeah
he doesn't wear the bucket anymore unless
unless he's doing know you're the one
who brought him i didn't picture myners
fucking go fuck it i picked your
name in a paper boy hat
who
samuel yeah that's i'm saying i know
he was don't fight he wears what
we used to call a jeff cap
why is it called that i don't
as a friend jeff you swam we
always call them that that was like
a universal yeah call jeff cups i
always called ah yeah they're officially called
jeff cap i think wily yeah because
i'm looking it up there's a brooklyn
style jeff cap
on sale ask finally jeff ask ask
her why this sleek six panel duck
bill shy google ah see the six
panel yeah i know it's it's a
there's a ton of just jeff yeah
just think these these types of caps
have so many wikipedia games mighty hap
wow officially called but i think i
might have known that but i feel
like we'd call it a paper boy
hat but is that also right well
there's newsboy news yeah newsboy using common
parlance that's what i mean
whatever is right is what i mean
newsboy caps skipper cap smart
ah gipper cap in wales is known
as a die cap
come on scotland it's abundant like flatland
you did it it's pretty cute right
of handicap in scottish and irish acts
in england well that's racist
yeah it is isn't it is yeah
paddy cap well maybe they're talking about
like patty cake
maybe
because it is it is that hat
is convenient to wear during yeah because
you don't have to hold it on
your head well i've heard yeah yeah
the old yeah i guess i were
you wearing two hats that are too
big for really because i'm holding them
onto yeah welcome from the wind comes
i'd either blow air they do yeah
yeah
well what are you gonna do what
are you going what what are you
gonna do i saw i don't know
if you saw this tick tock what
sound just went away what no not
at all we can hear you you
can't hear yourself um on going mutual
friend ah some mutuals to me and
maybe to as well this woman of
my mutuals was saying i
lost my hat in the wind and
it went so far into the sky
um and she's describing how like the
wind whipped it off her head it
was a big wide brimmed hat and
then she shows a picture of the
hat which is indeed a very wide
brimmed straw hat and then a video
of this fucking thing
thing is it is travelling it is
so far in the sky and she
zooms in and it just going higher
and higher and higher how did this
happen this is like dorothy nicer i
think it was the perfect like shape
yeah and and ah why don't they
make airplanes sad and wait why
don't they do that because they're playing
right now we're just sitting on the
ground they should be floating floating floating
high
oh well what are airplanes gonna get
better yeah and like what wouldn't you
feel like you're not doing they're not
updating the seats yeah well i feel
like a concert every time i go
on an airplane i'm like oh look
at these new up no no how
about this they're taking away tea but
we're talking about coach they're taking a
role
forgetting
they're taking a well i feel like
i'm so sick of this they want
you to put your plug your phone
in and put it in the little
holder i'm like i don't want to
drain my battery i want to watch
the movies you offer me i feel
like planes now other than southwest all
have tv screens they all have plugs
yeah they're they're all there's no that's
not this is
not true this is not universally true
if first-class is very different than coach
know i was on american airlines the
other day and i was and they
were like every single seed has ah
power and black options i was i've
been thinking about switching to delta as
my main that's my main yes my
main and a lot of people seem
to love the yeah yeah and join
us i think i should i think
i shared an adult is
we're not married is the best i
saw somebody and it's more anatomy in
new york ah we were having drinks
after a broadway play was it rudy
giuliani it was not rudy giuliani america's
mayor um but what you see i
saw leopold shot tom stoppard play oh
that's right oh wow i saw kimberly
akimbo by the way and lauren
you would like it and i think
you would like paul i told you
this already though so i i saw
a little um snippet of it on
the today show when they were why
i don't watch that every day but
yeah i happened to catch okay you
can know okay i looked at the
dates are like oh it's today yeah
you turned yeah yeah i knew when
it was on um but there's something
about perfer
naming a broadway song on any show
that makes it really yeah it was
just closing yeah but you want a
little you you want to be at
least fifty paces back yeah for everyone's
shimmy talented elite ideal way to watch
a broadway number removed from the show
is of course the macy's thanksgiving day
parade oh my god no austrian
or just reading thinking right yeah hundred
percent their lives thinking i love watching
that yeah and i love when it's
not quite right it's always so fun
that's great yeah they they had they
their lips thinking but they still have
to wear the costumes that they wear
in the show yeah no regardless of
the temperature yes yeah yeah yeah yeah
but i guess dancing around sort of
raises your body temperature so it low
lowers it actually does it read yeah
i never see that as new study
new studies dancing around study is like
temperature what are you going yeah
good have to say what i was
doing a parody of true story from
the real world credits
oh that's right story oh yeah yeah
some of those planes there's still some
old planes rattling around now there are
but i love when you have the
power you ever been on one where
they go this is the first flight
of this plane oh right guy was
so fucked i don't think i want
to have been on that it's it's
thrilling the maiden voyage yeah and you're
like they have so many new things
and you're just like oh my god
look at this
one of the imams where everyone okay
what flavor
for it the coffee flavor the video
games everywhere my god video games fucking
sick guy coke in the water fountains
i had the toilets full of piss
all i had okay are you the
plane experiences first of all on the
on the flight back i only do
this on the flight back from wherever
i am you okay we were just
in new york and flying back you
take your shoes off on the flight
there mon i keep my shoes on
the whole yeah right maybe i took
number up on a lot of them
because it was just too itchy
you're constantly scrape shoes yeah oh are
those wool shoes yeah yeah with moths
in them and no saw i um
i allow myself my treat which is
a giant bag of m and m's
peanut butter eminem's that's right not the
giant but i trash bag like this
share so wait i like this
out of like ritual yeah that it's
on the way back yeah yeah like
that yeah yeah and now you sort
of like that's my treat for doing
the trip yeah kind of yeah yeah
yeah i was a good boy it
all went down the airport yeah like
this nobody yelled at me but i'll
go way on the way to new
york ah some
buddy had i went to the restroom
and somebody had been fouled the seat
oh that happened me such amazing restaurant
yesterday where i go you like it
off the first plane i just know
i walk you to theirs to open
ones to open doors yeah both with
shit in them i'm just like guy
guys here don't just go one was
one was diarrhea and one was a
circular ball
come on
like maggiore lake was drawn those for
me what's wrong with you anyway i
feel like here's the anyone on who's
listening to this taken a fucking shit
and then walk right now just blocked
out on here yeah here's the issue
you don't try to sell yourself machine
oil it's gonna do a thing
nc it's gone i never walk out
i never think that stay in my
stay and i look babe and i
won't press the button if it's not
going well think there's self flushing toilets
because honestly sometimes it's no not on
airplanes on ah on in the airports
and i have when you like stand
up their self flushing so i think
what people don't even give it a
time people don't even look
behind no no i hit carlin people
are just so fucking gross sometimes like
people are just say like kitty carlisle
i'm thinking of this dennis miller joke
oh yeah that's work yeah that sounds
vaguely familiar like doggy style or something
she's low it's very sexy when she
looks behind her shoulder like kitty carlisle
and the gun smoke yeah oh i
thought it was like a ah like
an astronaut giving you i remember it
as like an astronaut giving you the
thumbs up like all systems go
maybe get you looked at it please
find that but so here's the thing
i want to know what's the mental
state i am waiting i'm waiting for
the ah for the light to go
off so i can use the bathroom
and i see somebody all i see
is dennis miller obituary he didn't die
no but somewhat near benghazi giller tell
me hey just want to let you
know i have to say
go mr biller someone who's saying that
they ah what just closed down buzzfeed
news that they should all publish they're
like death drafts for like trump and
listen to calls oh yeah like why
why does yeah yeah remember when deadline
hollywood published accidentally published yeah pence has
kobe yeah story yeah that was exciting
great and you know
no he did yeah he did how
did they identically write it because everyone
knew we had it i'm saying like
it's that's means that yeah yeah just
writing it okay so here's what i'm
besides they they do they do pre-planned
okay so i'm in the aisle waiting
for one of the bathrooms to open
up yeah one of the bathroom the
light goes off
this woman like furtively leaves the bow
know this is a bad sign so
it ought to be furtive when you're
the old casual guy if you are
if you're leaving a mess because about
it was still so
whistle the circus song so i go
in there and the sea is fouled
i'm sorry oh a lady went in
there and i went on twenty-two pee
pee all over the seat a phone
ra know if only this is on
the flight to new york that person
needs to be
like it's citizens
citizens arrest that is now to not
clean that up is so there are
air marshals onboard it's so great you
know there's only one to two bathrooms
yeah everyone you know that no one's
clone ellsbury yeah flight yeah there's not
like a guy that comes through amid
committed plate clean so did you
you leave the bathroom and say hear
ye hear ye this woman well that's
the thing i was like i got
i'm not i'm not taking this burden
on myself but i don't know i
you know i do my business and
then i leave so you're not touching
this when you say new business you
sat right down in it i i've
i just i just laid down just
put your
head down and take a little nap
yeah now wait so i likely on
my hands like please don't let anybody
be think it's you yes of course
so of course there's a woman's waiting
when i open my you have to
clean it that's why before you do
your thing you have to say to
the the flight attendant i'm sorry someone
just i'm not doing shit about this
no but here i wanted to say
to the woman like yeah i didn't
do it it wasn't oh because she
wasn't like waiting right there it was
like i opened the door nobody's are
great and then she like turned around
the corner and went in there i
was like there's a layer who is
a joke yeah so lately we think
that the woman before you is the
one who messed it up judge it
from the way she left yeah it
made me think that now was there
a pupil on the seat yes that's
so what did you think i was
saying
maybe period blood could it be there's
like jesus no
who poops on a seat
a monster like i'm like ah like
if you if you somebody who has
no statutory shine when funds right blood
can end up on the sea not
good not good but oh poo i'm
like you're just standing to shit then
at that point you're just hoping to
shoot yeah yeah yeah she was she's
worried that there's germs on the seeds
so she sang above
just drop us rain houses on this
shit i tell you about when i
was at comic-con and there's so few
bathrooms like public bathrooms there and so
it's like you know guys long line
and i was like oh god i
have to do a duty and so
you're waiting there for a stall you're
waiting for a stall to open up
oh and this guy comes out of
a stir
paul i'm waiting right there by he
gives me a look like i'm sorry
i i i clock it but i
go into the stall it is just
such a mess in it that i
do a complete one eighty and i
go ah right in front of him
as he's watching
yeah i dry heaved i was just
oh my god i know i fucking
flushed okay so people drink i wanna
drive of course yeah it's right now
so so this woman goes in and
then i'm like fuck man she's gonna
think that i did it and i
swear to god and she's going to
recognize she best week
ever give a mask on i didn't
have a mask that helps but she
can't use paul f tompkins he came
out yes just just like my face
she came out and i feel like
she immediately knew where i was sitting
she like looked right at me no
yeah that's this is terrible so you
you there's gotta be a better way
to do this you have to alert
i think i should have said like
hey maybe wait for the other one
this is what mercy before you
use that one know that it was
not my fault yeah yeah i like
had the wasn't me i know that
covers show you one hundred times in
your head what you try to go
like that wasn't me yeah yeah yeah
and i'm so mad at the person
who did it but the amount of
times that give us a description maybe
i could draw her i'll do an
artist rent well i only saw the
last picture drawing good what did running
away what
it looks like so is brown head
brown head fab member that drawing of
that last that someone drew is like
oh shit let's see oh my god
oh my god looks just like her
arrest her looks like or the beckman
good
oh my yeah this is the back
she did not have that everyone on
the menu but i want to know
i feel like women maybe do this
more i would guess because i i
ended up doing this lot all clean
pee off the seat that's not mine
yeah because it's so gross to me
yeah it's even as i'm and then
and then i'll make sure i clean
my own so
stuff and i'll come in even when
i'm not using the bathroom in an
airport i'll just tidy up
but i but i i think like
men can be just some thoughts well
i was thinking i've i've not cleaned
it but i have invited people in
there to assess the situation right like
i've gone into a stall and it's
messy and then i'll call somebody and
say what do you think what would
you do if you are me we
have to take a break okay
and we're back and it's time for
a little thing we call three cher's
and this one was submitted by area
man i guess he's probably from florida
um mirror mirror so my three year
idea is called mirror mirror two of
you play talking mirrors one
i can only tell the truth and
one can only tell lies the other
person is trying to figure out who
or what they are by asking the
mirrors questions the mirrors cannot answer with
a simple yes or so it doesn't
have to be a celebrity it could
be anything it could be well maybe
we should make it a celebrity let's
make it celebrities he asked it's ten
questions for each other somebody went to
school i just mean like a flower
yes
like an object chang oh okay like
twenty like an elephant yeah they ask
her gets ten questions for each and
oh wow we're holding flower oh i
like that almost like dumbo oh yeah
and i just finished reading no the
asker gets gets ten questions for each
mirror before they must decide who or
what they are and cannot ask the
same question multiple times the two
mirrors decide they didn't he of the
person this step has to happen first
so i should put it earlier but
oh well okay you could've just yeah
god nice jesus oh my god okay
the mirrors will yeah man if the
question asker guesses wrong the question asker
wins if they get started correctly and
which mirror is lying or telling the
truth so will god isn't that have
fun with it all
so start each question with murmur on
the wall no no no ca that
will take forever so we're so the
very first question will do that sure
so we'll be getting going for area
nancy yeah we'll do this three times
and i'll count up the points and
we'll see who wins at the end
how's that sense yeah you get a
point if you guess it right and
you get a point if
the other person gets it wrong yes
we all want everything you call them
points you get points no matter what
okay so paul you're going to be
the guesser and lauren and i are
going to decide you want to text
me or should i text you um
you're texting you text me his identity
yeah and then you text me whether
you're allowed or
okay
will you send it first yep
okay okay
got it got it
mirrors mirrors on the wall
a question i have for you that's
my call okay you mirror
hi b i a man or a
woman a woman you mirror be a
man you can't do that same question
twice otherwise then you know mirror hey
don't ask me ask i have to
switch off no no no mirror but
this is my
second question yeah no shit
vi alive or b i did you
be dead
miura yes when did i die you're
not dead
mirror yes
did i get married yes
mirror who am i married to
you are
look ben affleck
i've been f like no you're married
to ben affleck
i think you just gave up you
are ben affleck
mirror
who did i use to be married
to
you've only had one partner
okay this seems impossible
keep going
we'll see if it's impossible it might
be let's keep going
okay um i'll tell you if you
know who's lying
and you know who's telling the truth
it's easy yeah i know that keep
going and you might get my chair
figure out how to determine that right
maybe you could say maybe just showing
okay
i'm remembering the myth now okay okay
okay how does it go
if i ask the other mirror
if i ask the feeling this is
you're trying to game the system instead
of that's how this works he can
ask whatever yeah this is okay you
know this myth i wrote a myth
i don't know i don't know that
i think now i know all right
well keep asking some keep asking some
questions and you can work on the
myth as you oh no no just
keep going it's going
and gray is boring to me i'm
not bored that's good oh god yeah
mirror
am i holding a phone
no
there you go mother fuck was that
gaming the system yeah i it like
it is i don't mind it's what
ah what else i feel like these
questions should be celebrity based but anyway
going round we'll see what happens let's
just try to get through the first
round okay if you have a better
strategy of question asking i'm interested i'd
like to try maybe affordable alright
mirror or who am i married to
right now her name is jessica
her name is jessica shared last name
oh that's nice yeah
um what did i have for breakfast
it seems like you could ask me
questions about celebrities and it would help
narrow down knowing that i'm loving me
or what did the celebrity have for
breakfast i shit okay that's not true
okay
mera do i have any children i
believe you have to
mirror
am i a person
no
mirror
in my young or old um your
middle aged
but you'd say old yeah alright i
don't guess i don't know how old
he is
mirror what's your favorite movie of mine
top gun maverick
mirror what's your least favorite movie of
mine um
i don't know
i wouldn't be able to pick a
least because i love everything you do
equally
a mirror you can narrow down who
the person is yeah i know but
like ask a question about the person
by the way like well how you're
running out of quests how they're known
oh yeah how many is their limit
how many tent you're only supposed to
ask ten oh i must be you
must say okay yeah let's here's your
guess they asked me like a really
like basic question about this person that
kind of like narrow down like twenty
questions type question like
are you a tv or you know
yes am i movie star um you've
been in movies um it's not what
i asked you've starred in films you've
started not really movie
ah ah ah
am i jerry seinfeld you are you
might already know that we're just sorry
oh alright let's let's try it again
and let your guy guess i'll guess
keep track of the of the amount
of question well it also i feel
like we need to go back and
forth because yeah with the asking several
of me you're right just just saw
you take the little you plan
can um going to do it alright
so do you want to save the
person and i'll say who's lying or
not sure okay
and dead silence comes over the pot
as paul types out the person that
lorne is going to embody meanwhile i
am texting
which one of us is lying in
which one of us is telling the
truth
we already were ready
okay okay are you're starting with starting
with um paul hello mirror hey
am i a movie star yes oh
hello hello am i a woman or
man you are a woman came
um hello mirror hello em i um
do i tend to do ah no
ah let's see am i considered a
comedic or dramatic actor ie dramatic okay
um yeah um welcome
i'm back dr we know you have
many choices for mirrors you know i'm
so glad you chose me okay um
do i am i um alive or
dead you are dead okay um
and when did i pass
you have yet to die
okay
umm and ahh
do i what's my biggest film
gross or um culturally culturally
i guess culturally
jurassic park okay and my laura dern
no
laura dern i'm not allowed to ask
that i don't think you're allowed to
ask until the very end oh okay
yeah everyone seemed to know that rule
when i tried it huh
um okay yeah i'll let i'll let
you go back to okay i'll ask
different calls mayor for the different question
um ah question for that you said
i'm daddy so um and one of
us is lying no that's i think
i can
um if you do want knowledge more
you must ask me question fool
am i married
i don't go hey it's my dad
bruce dern huh
ah yes okay um
but that doesn't make sense because you
said i was dead
so not laura dern
okay um
okay so you're telling question for if
you must ask the question
okay um what's my biggest ah what's
ah what
have i done sequels to movies that
i've done yeah yes okay
um
ah tis tis tis tis am i
am i a man no okay as
that ten questions no that's five twenty
five piece yeah okay also think you
asked that already i suppose well but
i asked him twice and i also
she's trying to keep track yeah because
it's now knowing i'm lying yeah well
not made it clear um if you
want to get your kicks you have
any questions it's okay
um thank you i'm glad
am i my ah what's my bigot
what's my what's my role that people
must know me for e an interesting
question the how do i answer without
giving it completely away describe the role
the name of the role is bruce
did i stutter
it
okay
um i'm okay you don't know how
back to me okay yeah um yeah
do i have children
i don't know either why is this
person so mysterious um if you want
to get to heaven you must ask
him questions seven okay um ah do
kids today know who i am or
is it more like an older generation
be more familiar with this kids today
know of you yes
okay um
how old am i am i oh
no am i don't know okay how
old am i
a middle-aged okay
this is impossible i'm a man i'm
a movie star my dad's not bruce
dern knowing i'm lying yeah like yeah
i'm i'm trying i'm the way it
works is he will he will always
do one thing and i will always
do the guy got that i got
that also were mirrors oh okay
a um ah am i funny you're
asking me about my funny
ah i i would say you're very
known for being funny ah and your
roles do not have any light humor
in them
okay so it's the opposite i'm known
for i'm known for not being funny
but i play a lot of humorous
parts this mean fucking sense when you're
the one who fucking ass hey um
um
oh god
if your hotspot full of hate you
may ask any question eight i think
our hearts um am i involved in
political stuff yay
do i play a political role like
a character that's important you do okay
the fuck is bruce
um
this is question nine nine
okay
which because anything mirror is my turn
yeah question nine
if in fact you're feeling fine it's
because tonight
so are full of hate we've established
that and maybe she's feeling fine
ah oh well what's the last name
of my character bruce
almighty maybe look in the phone book
that's not honest you gotta be honest
the name is synonymous with items of
heraldry
bruce paper
let's heraldry the newspaper
what's heraldry
um bruce paper
you could ask me what the definition
of her what is the definition you're
telling the wrong one
well it's the definition of heraldry it's
not the system of which coats of
arms and other memorial bearings are devised
described and regulated
er colorful ceremony
what
bruce flag
i don't feel okay this is your
last question who am i you can't
ask that um ah how's paula tomkins
or scott oc i've never met me
i can only say one of them
has not okay that's not what's talking
about me
okay and last question ah why are
you such a fucking asshole i don't
know that was hard paul i see
from your side right when i see
it was really really hard um who
was ah it is mark ruffalo only
bruce banner the incredible never ever
or ever would have gotten that however
i don't think he's i don't know
if he's married i don't know if
he has kids he buys a boat
i think he probably has any probably
ah he probably has both we don't
know so much about his personal life
but he is political oh yeah most
face not funny buddy buddy had been
to he made funny yeah and as
the hulk he's yeah sorta funny yeah
the
thing is about this is that he's
married to sunrise kanye surname yeah he
pulled sunrise cognac he has three or
four kids three forty bucks huh he
loves yes no maybe to you know
talk he hates it through
do me okay i think the questionnaire
needs to be more along the lines
of like twenty questions or something like
parameters on it yeah feeling just like
any question yeah so like yes or
no you're saying no but but well
i mean we could switch to yes
or nose
i don't know
i just don't know i feel like
using the lying person to try to
narrow down stuff is just as important
as using the idea i know but
i like you know really confuse are
going to move as i think you
should try one i'll be true because
you'll see how confusing it is i
think we should make it only five
questions each just kinda let's just kinda
its yes slow through it alright yeah
here we go
it's fucking fly through you guys okay
so i'll text paul on name and
if i'm only getting five you can't
be totally obfuscating the answer right okay
well he has clear as my champion
so i'm gonna send you a name
name being sent immediately
name has been sand name received okay
status received
okay begin
begin
i'm going to lauren first okay hello
magic mirror hi
what do you want to ask me
am i a man nope
hello magic mirror ooh
am i a movie star
absolutely not
you said i can't yeah yeah gabe
drag just happened i am a mature
woman a woman okay
am i
married to a famous person yes you
are
am i in marvel movies
yes all of them
okay i know it was
there has been anyone who's been in
all of the
um ah stan lee much
not the latest ones
um
because what have you stanley
so i know i'm a movie star
who's married to a famous person i'm
a woman who's
am i married to ben affleck no
am i known for rom-coms
yes
am i known for action films um
you've done some that would be considered
but i wouldn't say that's the main
okay
um
am i a m i a dramatic
actress
never
okay this is my last one okay
have i been nominated for an oscar
yes
i think we can keep going this
is going faster with the way we're
doing it yeah ah oh and can
keep going okay um okay so this
is my fifth to you um
um how old am i
am i sorry am i am i
am i over fifty know you're a
spring chicken
us version is it is better
am i over seventy oh god
i mean you know i'm telling the
truth so let me just say let's
see
no no you're not okay so in-between
fifteen seventy some year it looks it
up there is poison in your no
no poison make up don't drink it
um
dramatic actor who has done but i
know meryl streep has not is not
married to a famous person
ah between fifty and seventy oh nominated
for oscars known for drama
oh man
ask another question yeah ah
have
were my movies popular most popular in
the nineties
oh absolutely
um where my movies most popular in
the twenty first century no
okay eighties then i would think ah
eighties dramatic actor fucking shit um have
i been nominated for an oscar more
than once oh yes so just once
i can give you a tip yeah
ask more about the movies because i
think okay the word you're using is
wrong
okay ah am i am i dramatic
actor yes but it's a very specific
you're known for a very specific genre
oh okay
is the genre that i'm known for
with my movies
um
ah is it ah ah animation absolutely
ah what is ah does it you
know what is the what is the
genre that i'm known for ah okay
ah
were my parents famous
no
did i just win an oscar this
is my jamie lee yeah i know
the success oh my gosh alright and
that's how we play
oh wait i didn't i didn't so
account of the points i think zero
and one yeah it was ah one
one zero and then one zero zero
primary i have three laurens one pause
one okay well it's over so it
doesn't matter yeah who cares well um
just because you have three losers
years clean up the game
oh okay oh wipe it all away
right now um listen if you would
like to send if you would like
to send us a three-tier yeah don't
just send it to y from usa
at gmail dot com why don't you
do that if you'd like to leave
us a voicemail the kind we're going
to listen to on the next episode
that was too cold us why don't
you call us at hag
eight hag claims a hag will claim
the eight bag will claim the a
you can follow us o ne say
enlisted if you want to hear ad
free versions of the show you can
listen on stitcher premium or cbp world
dot that's right
and hey we ah we all three
wrote some stuff for the cvb book
the comedy bang but yeah we'll look
great and a lot of people have
been getting signatures with the three yeah
so um you know someone brought one
to the show last night which is
something you can do if you're gonna
come to one of our shows we
assign a book that's right yeah yeah
why not um and listen ah
i don't this comes out when thursday
okay folks in los angeles i don't
know why this is happening but there's
still tickets left for my may fourteenth
show at lodge room it is variety
apia it's a great show we got
greatly probably because that's the season finale
succession and no and it's mother's day
and some others i thought it was
was why but then there's still four
more after that the seeds finale is
the twenty eighth not for more but
the season finale is twenty eight oh
how many episodes are they doing this
year i think it's like ten interviews
or eight or ten i can't remember
but i thought i looked when i
first looked it up i thought it
was the season finale oh and then
ah i looked it up if that
was the wisdom game with like slightly
different wording
it is the twenty eighth it was
maybe if you're hey stupid when is
the season yeah
quit fucking around nice to see top
of the plane with me so here's
what's going to happen we're gonna have
a great show with great guests and
then immediately afterwards we're going to screen
the that night's episode of succession so
you can have both in one place
and if you've never watched a show
like that in a group setting it's
actually kind of fun very we're not
going to be like
mr roasting here is we're just going
to watch it together and laugh together
it's a lot like watching a movie
where like you when you go see
a movie like fast and furious you're
not sitting there roasting it and shouting
at the screen and it's the lodge
room has like a big screen it's
gonna be fun it's imax their go
to well scott don't lie to them
on the mirror who always lies
go to paul f tompkins dot com
slash live and come on out to
that show it's gonna be a lot
of fun lauren um when does this
coming thursday wow so thursday i guess
what do i have going on you
know i just don't know um just
just do whatever you want okay see
dubai
uh