three
ah
oh ooh yeah well wow that's amazing
yeah i like that show wow wow
wow and shabab style
is one tommy's oh bob style
um hi everyone welcome back to freedom
the podcast with me scott aquaman and
no one else this mini podcast about
chain restaurants and scott talks about them
at length ah
i'm lauren lab guess i you still
have your homeboy sorry or reception she's
your teacher judiciary which should you choose
your hey i'm paul f tompkins okay
if you want to get that clean
so okay
name for a drop pony did our
show the other night and we love
kissing thompson guys first monday of every
month get it we're whittling down everyone
until finally it'll just be lauren just
by yourself yeah um but we were
discussing fast food and we realized we
have
it really talked about about here and
paul was like well it's because we're
not doughboys but i am curious what
your favorite fast food places oh okay
yeah we're allowed to talk about that
we're allowed to talk about it we're
not taste-testing them when you go with
em and em snow we only do
that with candy and yes we call
ourselves the doughboys but who cares the
dual gang private thing
um i think currently in and out
is where i go into currently for
burgers um but didn't now it could
change at any moment it really could
who knows what's happening um but you
know i don't know i've liked carl's
junior over the years but it's really
iffy like if you get a cold
burger
not you know so well this is
what i was saying that i have
been into in and out lately i've
just been treating myself and to some
but i don't consider it fast food
really because i think of it as
healthier slash more natural but i think
i'm making that up to me you
are feel what i owe
what i said to lauren was anything
that you can order from your car
is fast food and it's five dollars
total for the whole meal which doesn't
really bode well for how great quality
it is i guess you know it's
more expensive well if i got a
camera i just get a hamburger and
fries and it's like a little over
five dollars right right well with the
lines
ing as long as they are is
it really that fast that's a good
ass oh yeah you know i don't
eat fast food much anymore but when
i do have a craving for it
my last shiny more by
mr saturday i wait just a billy
crystal's parody that's right um i don't
i do what's going on when i
do get a craving for it i
think it's either mcdonald's or kentucky fried
chicken are my things i like the
chicken nuggets they've gotten better over time
because they made it with real because
they started will they
made with real chicken with real chicken
now and before it was pink glue
yeah was just chicken coup which i
would eat even if i knew that
comes out of a chicken's bottle yeah
when chickens lay eggs there's this this
pink goo that surrounds it and see
what just deep fry that yeah it's
like the chicken placenta anyway this is
a real question do eggs come out
of the butt hole
lol no chicken oh wait
the filmmakers oh chloe always slow boat
broad makeup i think that's what it
is but holy shit
um it's all a mystery to me
like yeah it's god's plan ah why
eggs are what they are
oh wait guys i'm so proud of
myself that i knew what a co
waco was right um the posterior orifice
that serves as the only opening for
the j digestive reproductive and oh near
near the tracks really so it's the
trait you get the trifecta and then
it's pee and eggs wow
wow that's why stems your aches have
a little bit of poop or pee
on them yeah i want to get
this leg
hey could i send these back i'm
so i don't i don't mean to
be a pain but these eggs are
covered with piss i actually got it
i think there's an egg in my
fridge right now that has feathers on
it really like a little and it's
making noise it's going ppp
well hope is the thing with feathers
wow yeah tattooed on your lower back
the course will target practice does anybody
get stuff on their middle back teams
got hurt when do you remember paul
may be more than lauren but when
president nixon well yes of course i
didn't do you remember when people started
getting tattoos yes ah in the nineties
and how just how i remember
seeing it now because i remember in
a script that my friend and i
wrote together there was like characters were
having a whole conversation about would you
date a woman with a tattoo this
is back in ninety three this was
you and your friend jerry seinfeld yes
of course and he was like i
don't know um but yeah it was
it's so strange how just commonplace
face it is now i guess in
thirty years anything is can become commonplace
but i it seemed to happen relatively
quickly leaving yeah i remember when tattoos
became like what right before i moved
to l a
no i'm gonna say like ah i
remember meeting a ah i had a
friend who had a bunch of tattoos
and at that time that was very
unusual for someone to be to have
multiple tattoos and this would have been
like the early nineties and what was
the perception of that person at that
time at that time it was like
gosh ah
are they going to want that for
the rest of their life i do
i do remember one of the people
in my church growing up had a
big he was in the navy or
he had been in the navy and
he had a big and hanker you
don't sail the seven seas sure he
had a big anchor tattoo on his
arm and that was like sort of
had scandic yeah he was famous
but it was sort of scandalous in
the church in a way of people
going like well obviously he's not supposed
to have that but he was in
the navy before he joined the church
and so i think there was interesting
for me it was like definitely at
that at that time in the early
i would say in the early nineties
it
it was sort of a ah almost
a subculture thing of like that's that's
a certain that's a certain ah you
know ah to say you know social
circle or whatever i can't think of
the term but that's that's i guess
cultures starting culture that yeah there's a
lot of tattoos you didn't see a
lot of
especially women with tattoos unless yeah it
was like in the punk scene or
whatever yeah they weren't normalized she and
she was a musician yeah so it
was like that was who had tattoos
you know it's normalized across fashion or
fashion photography yeah yeah yeah so it
was whenever you'd see like someone i
would work with at one of my
previous restaurants
we'd come in and have like a
bad tattoo or whatever you'd go like
god put your shirt on
we're in a restaurant not to mention
your pants um but it would just
be like god you're eighteen is that
really something like you know should you
be making that choice and now of
course it's like anyone can get a
tattoo and i feel like the thing
right now is like anyone gets can
get a tattoo anyone will get a
tattoo and they'll get um a lot
of people i
i know in my life have gotten
impulsive tattoos that they don't like and
then they cover with another tattoo so
it's just like there's kind of no
risk and feels like at this point
yeah i mean i don't think sending
it seems like a judgment risk like
people would judge you yeah nobody thinks
anything of it now yeah didn't like
starbucks employees back in the day had
to cover up their tattoos and stuff
while dis
miniland tattoos you're saying things like that
disneyland employees they just are now or
allowing them to uncover them real i
hate this whoa culture oh my god
that guy wanna see the pirates during
sexual assaults
you know who does the pirate um
lady pirate you know who does the
pirate you know who does the pirate
it's grey griffin she does the lady
oh my old college friend i was
added a couple of years ago and
she um i don't yeah i don't
know lady pirate at sea lounge i
mean you know maybe paris
are under-represented
do i know when do you remember
lady pirates not being a thing
early nineties
i'm at disneyland they when i worked
there they you had to keep your
hair you know a certain length and
above the ears and all this kinda
stuff and you couldn't you know show
any of your tattoos and you're seeing
your hat on there yeah yeah of
course a bird air air and air
air now and keep your animal head
on all the time even when you
just worked out
you could take off the bottom
but they they just last week when
they reopened they now are being more
inclusive for people of different hair styles
which culturally um you know people want
that's important yeah exactly so and the
tattoos they're letting that be expression and
all that kind of stuff so now
by
inclusive hair styles does that mean that
means black people right are allowed to
wear their hair the way they like
pretty much yeah but because i think
that's what but i mean that's just
i'm sure it also is like this
is not a professional hairdo it also
would have to mean i think people
who are wearing wraps and so i
don't know what their policy on on
roadshow we're
or to not allow that stuff when
the whole premise of like the place
is all these different worlds and different
cultures and different sex you know maybe
like it's all you got oh right
about it
i was thinking about it about disneyland
because when i worked there in eighty
seven or eighty eight um that that
seemed like the point where suddenly they
started being more inclusive across the board
like as a company you know that
you learn yeah
no it just seemed like they started
having like this is a bold step
forward for us we're now allowing dorks
to work here
ah
warren it's offending me that you thought
that was so funny
ah i didn't even have my money
i'd even say it but i did
that route
yeah there was like a side note
i don't know if you ever told
your bear bear story on the podcast
this is the first time i met
you is when you did ask and
you told oh yeah i mean okay
so i used to work at disneyland
this is not part of restaurant roundup
because i know that there's no known
use food at disneyland this is
not part of restaurant roundup this is
job roundup which honestly we haven't really
gotten into with you besides restaurants unless
you only worked at restaurants no no
i had a bunch um oh so
but i'll just talk about this one
i've heard a bunch so for disneyland's
um you know i grew up probably
three miles
away from it so i would go
to house i would go to it
every year ah you know i was
going to when i was a little
kid when they had e tickets and
all that kind of stuff like gods
and eat together electronic yeah it's like
juice
or any other juice and i love
six
no the e ticket i mean have
you heard ah oh wow that's an
e ticket experience that like cliche or
like well yeah you know and that's
what special yeah so so disneyland for
those of you who aren't steeped in
disneyland lore around nineteen eighty two or
eighty three or eighty four something eighty
five or eighty six u seven eighty
eight
nine would be too easy when you
when you bought a ticket for the
park you could go anywhere in the
park but before that you were when
you bought a ticket for the park
you are you are given a coupon
book okay and they had and the
coupon book had a certain allotment of
e tickets a certain allotment of
d tickets a certain allotment of a
b c d e right and e
tickets were a ticket you and everyone
apparently you don't
because you want an e ticket experience
every ride had a had a sign
that said what ticket would get you
on to that ride and the best
rides have the e tickets right so
you could get on like the eight
tickets were worthless you could get on
like the train that goes around the
whole park fuck right so but ever
anything good everything in fantasy land or
you know space mountain and all that
they were all ticket rides and and
you could buy extra books but you
couldn't just buy e tickets right so
you would if you went there several
times like i would go every single
year with my parents you just had
a stack of a tickets like sitting
in your collections that you would never
see
spend and then the ease you wouldn't
like take one day and ride the
train for twenty four hours well yeah
for twenty four hours yeah like your
bag again once you get on one
so you can ride as long as
you want that so it doesn't really
get rid of whatever yeah they let
you sit on the train all day
if you want yeah yeah because
there's three stops to and they don't
know when you got on or got
off so it's like literally you could
sit there and just go around the
train the entire time i feel like
there's only three stops i would begin
to know when that person do not
give one shit i think you've been
on longer than the three stops
um but so yeah i grew up
going to disneyland and and having the
ticket books and all that kind of
stuff and so so i was always
very fascinated with it so and i
always wanted to work there and i
would always sort of like look at
the how you know that i started
do that with every place i kind
of look at the design and look
at how you know i like go
oh
it must work this way like the
shift works this way like these people
are coming on now and these people
are like when you go to olive
garden like i think they come out
of that back room and i think
i don't know maybe it has come
to me that a hurdle
whenever they take the paper they go
back through that whole know but i
used to when there was a restaurant
called loves that we used to go
to in point apart i know the
diaper themed restaurant loves diabetes oh i
get it okay so and there was
a a commercial i don't know whether
it was local but it was a
chain where it was like when you're
in love
loves the whole world's delicious wow
hey candy yeah
and it was a bbq place the
whole world's delicious it was argued bbq
like god loves them
well it's like that kind of exceeding
like when your loves you're thinking god
everywhere else is so good and it
had a heart ah it's locally literally
was like a valentine's heart with yeah
cursive weil's disease and i said it's
a huge sign i feel like i
off suburban diana you know when you
stop in the middle of nowhere i
think
we used to love going there that
was like the special night that i
used to love we go to yes
and it would be great because like
i could get a half a chick
not have a full half a chicken
but an order of half chicken half
steak bbq you know like just like
i loved going to i love going
there but they had one of those
things up in the restaurant of the
the electronic sign or panel that had
all the numbers on it that when
the wind up to involve numbers in
the world so it would be like
one to thirty right of like your
ticket number your ticket exactly so like
suddenly it would light up and i
would just sit there while i was
eating and because you know it
it would take so long to get
the food and you would get there
really hungry and it would just take
forever when you feel like so fast
so i would i would try to
guess which number was ours and i
would be like taking a look at
the whenever like a number would light
up in our waitress would would hurry
back to the kitchen and it wouldn't
be ours i'd be like ok so
is that which she must have the
the numbers fifteen through twenty so if
any of those light up
that means our food is lighting up
anyway so i've always been fascinated with
like how places work you know um
so i really want to work at
disneyland just because i wanted to know
how it worked and there were all
these buzz kill not for me no
i i love that to me i'm
like i kinda don't want to know
like really know too much so i'm
like oh yeah comes the garbage
picker upper person and then you know
it takes away from this right because
there's a whole fantasy with disneyland which
advanced isn't that why you think it's
not real where they say that all
the garbage goes underneath and gets emptied
but then i've seen people up to
the garbage and i'm like well there's
all there's all these like the the
garbage goes
under the street so that the the
trash cans are never under there and
then they're always being removed under me
but i don't think that's true because
i've seen them be overflowing and i've
also seen people emptying them yeah exactly
so i don't also seems wildly impractical
even but i think it's a great
idea but there are these like legends
that you hear about and some of
them are true like the graveyard behind
the haunted mansion that no one can
see and and but there was always
the one to beg your pardon there's
like a little graveyard behind the haunted
mansion that's not real republic it's not
a real graveyard but it's like a
fake people are buried there yeah so
you know that's the one where you're
in line and you can see
the graves are like i died is
like the name of the person or
something i mean these are these are
ones i've never even seen them because
you can't see them unless you work
there or go on to a special
tour or they let you see them
but but it has like animators names
on it back there and people worked
on the ride and stares him an
interesting podcast about the ah
horrors and deaths at disneyland yeah and
it's really graham but um billy johnson
i listened to his episode and it
was really interesting so i don't know
how to find it besides searching that
but um but yeah there were there
are up there are certain things like
the basketball the underground basketball court and
stuff like that that you hear about
and um so anyway i really want
to work there
so i and i was in theater
i was a musical theater and and
through the toy sort of grapevine of
musical theatre people were like ok well
if you want to work at disneyland
in the parade or in the as
a character additions are coming up and
so and wait paul do you care
if you know how something works
i mean i guess it depends on
what the thing is i'm not i'm
not constantly trying to crack the care
of you didn't do you want to
understand how disneyland is functioning or you
just like happy to be there why
isn't there a third choice
yeah i mean yeah i don't i
don't need to know you know ya
wanna go to disneyland
no i've been divisional and many times
oh no it's love it it's never
my idea if it's somebody else's idea
i would i would but it's let's
go to disneyland i really wish we
could go i'm so sad that it's
all fucked up i've only made it
when i've gone i know but no
scary to go when it's not the
full like so a lot of people
are not going there it actually they're
only take
the reservations now and i was reading
that um a lot of the reservations
are going unclaimed because people will if
they're going to pay the bio they
want the full experience because there's no
paredes there right you know yeah that's
still fun i want to go when
it's good yeah so i went to
these auditions which were they combine it
into parade and character
oh and i quickly found out that
the parade people were a higher class
or they were viewed as a higher
class of people i should say so
um and only the best people got
accepted into the parade but then the
rest of you could get into characters
and it was loud i'm sorry i'm
sorry my best people what what did
you have to demonstrate to be one
of the best people
and it's basically a dance and movement
audition which is something that i'm not
like incredibly comfortable doing at least at
the time but i now you're very
free
but at the time i i'd gotten
into plays and stuff by basically like
doing dorky shit and not not looking
good doing it but like being funny
at it yeah right sold it but
you had to do a choreographed dance
and then you had to do a
freestyle movement kind of stuff and so
i went and did it and i
actually got a call back but they
said not
for parade for character so um so
i said ok and then they did
if we covered you from head to
toe
so they took my height and they
i eventually actually got the job and
it ended up being one of the
worst jobs i've ever had um checks
out it was like ah two very
calendars it's like ray counters is fun
because it's like everyone is your age
you're all just like you get drunk
eat out
the faster i get it i'm saying
hit on by tons of women it's
like ah lady you dress like a
banana yeah that was good but but
as a character you are yes you're
covered from head to foot and one
thing that i didn't realize is because
i'm six two and a half the
type staff in their characters
that i would play where all of
the super tall cumbersome uncomfortable so like
goofy goofy is okay because goofy is
not taller than what you are um
meaning the worst ones were like breyer
bear and little john from robin hood
because
they are in the eight feet variety
which means they're like two feet taller
much yeah there are too many taller
than you you know for the experience
you know but if you
but if you're a little kid like
six feet is tall and then you
look like an eight foot tall bears
better know you gotta be compared to
goofy yeah yeah to think about the
other people it's like you got i
who gives us like is there any
little kids get a warriors sugar you're
holding up the corner they're the same
size thinking of that that picture of
biden with the carters is like yeah
i keep staring at it i'm like
lesser things biden looks like breyer it's
so confusing it's wild that my sister
understand that after you're president you start
to show
shrink
have an obama i live in a
tiny hell obama is three feet tall
at this point i'm truly just so
confused like i i can't even zoom
didn't i was like i still don't
understand the perspective like they're not far
enough in front of them that it'll
be that it looks like a really
it's it's a wide angle lens thing
right if you if you're shooting with
a wide angle lens
depending on the body outside of the
details of the layoffs will appear bigger
yeah yeah it gets stretched yeah and
the carters didn't want to move their
chairs so that they would be in
front it just so funny to be
more chairs are here we'll just take
the picture
oh i don't yeah i don't want
to move my shares they can move
their chairs there they're a million years
old yeah they're a little feeder dangling
service should move there today even the
site even them in their chairs was
seemed proportionally weird yeah yeah there's a
lot going god i pray they're still
alive at the time this area is
wow what what do you have something
to say about it lord no i'm
saying there's nothing negative that's being said
it's just that they have big chairs
and they're small big chairs tiny bodies
nothing negative about that i hope i
hope they stay alive in the people
won't come after us for making fun
of these million-year-old people
should i continue at disneyland or no
yeah you should i just want to
shoot a story about what happened to
you and you are aware and you
go okay well anyway so berber ah
was the one that i ended up
having to do the most and it
was just such a drag because first
of all it's super hot i was
it was there i was there it
must have been the summer of eighty
eight
because i saw back in the summer
of eighty eight the one plus to
this is they were having a fifties
rock and roll aa festival that summer
over a video oculus which was looking
at the cool saddle shoes no no
they they had actual yes i was
just interested in saddle shoes
breyer bear had a the dovetail poodle
skirt and so no they had actual
musicians from ah from the like fifty
musicians doing sets there all day like
doing music sets so i got to
see roy orbison ah ro for yeah
that's right yeah which which was a
big hassle in and of itself
because you have to get his body
out of the park when you when
you ah lot when you sign out
for the day when you clock out
they give you fifteen minutes to leave
the park before suddenly you have told
this before yeah oh okay maybe i
just okay well then you know who
holds well on that one maybe i
just told the fifty's down anyway
fairbury was just a phone call depart
about roy orbison and that you only
have a certain amount of time you
got overheated and loss yeah so i
i is that a separate story no
no i mean they're all part of
the same story but it was it's
essentially it's super hot in it it's
eight feet tall and all you have
is a cinch like velcro strap to
strap it to your boss
body which means your waist is bruised
by the end of the day and
it's hitting the front and back of
your head constantly even giving you a
hey whoa whoa whoa i mean all
you you can just see out of
it's neck essentially right and and i
hear that they have them like with
fans nowadays and it's better but back
then it was just i'm sure it
was just
brutal so anytime i would be i
would look at my schedule and that's
the other thing they're not even given
you a full time schedule like you
you did and it would be like
fifteen hours that week or something and
you'd have to like go around and
ask people for their shifts and stuff
so but i would hate it when
i would see i was right i
would call in and hear that i
was rare bear on the schedule it
would just be like fuck cannot be
captain
hook today or whatever because you are
sometimes captain okay skeptic because i had
to i was picturing you and just
santa you know you're just wearing essentially
pirate clothes but they're just clothes so
it's yeah hot and all that kinda
stuff so it's this noise regular human
sized yes and he's fun like you
can play around um and i would
get compliments when i was captain
book by our handlers you would always
have handlers who are watching you and
i would always get compliments because they
would write up how you did out
there and i would always get compliments
of like men you are very funny
as captain hook today that was really
good they would always write it in
my class what were some of your
gags that you would do as captain
hook i remember i got there ah
the early shifts were
not my favorites like where you'd have
to go to the disneyland hotel and
do the breakfasts and stuff but but
one one early shift i got was
right when the park opened and i
remember you it was basically going out
there and entertaining the people who are
behind the rope the or the cordon
that they have set up that suddenly
at nine a
am they lift and everyone like runs
to go you know try to be
first on whatever ride to the there
yeah they're gonna get their tickets yeah
so you're you're sitting there basically entertaining
the crowd before they get in and
i remember that being really fun for
some reason i remember when they said
would you do the one thing
i remember is when
when they lifted the rope and people
started to run i did kind of
a like being overwhelmed by the people
fish swimming upstream kind of nothing funny
that i thought was funny yeah another
thing that was fun that we used
to do was when i was bro
bear and and my friend was rare
fox is we used to hide below
behind there was a certain place in
new orleans square over by haunted mansion
where you could end by pirates where
you could hide behind a corner and
essentially sex with each other and have
sex with each other no jump out
and scare tend to get caught having
sex
ooh i do yeah we do my
pants and you have to be completely
silent right yeah you can't you can't
talk so we would we would noises
for the effect for the audience to
understand my character i just wanted to
be clear for everyone we would jump
out from behind a corner and scare
someone and it would use the first
time it would
just be one person they go huh
and then laugh and then you you'd
go like shsh to them do the
shush sign and then they would watch
you scare another person and by the
end of it by the end of
like ten people a big crowd would
gather there watching you do the same
scare for people you know
that was really fun but the one
at one point my friend who played
breyer fox he said hey come out
here on this balcony i want to
show you something and i went out
on the balcony closed the door behind
me and there's no doorknob on the
door and essentially i was stuck up
there my entire shift waving at people
from the balcony and that's
and that was that i was funny
good actually it was it was preferable
to walking yeah yeah yeah yeah but
the one day that that lauren i
think that the story you're thinking of
is is we used to have essentially
the shifts were ah you do ten
minutes on ten minutes off fifteen minutes
on fifteen minutes off you would never
do more than thirty five minutes that's
not bad yeah
yeah so because it was just brutally
hot out there in california in the
summer in these costumes so thirty five
minutes was the longest you were supposed
to do and what you would usually
do is you'd be backstage and you'd
come out your entrance and exit and
entertain people by that entrance and exit
and then go back the way you
came when you're when your handler would
say okay that's thirty
five minutes but every once in a
while there were these shifts that they
called walk abouts or something where you
had to start at one entrance and
your shift was you would you walking
to another backstage area in a different
land so you would start on main
street and then walk and entertain people
as you were wide tried to catch
a few people that way um because
yeah fuse to disneyland i was very
dedicated to getting their autograph book signed
up they didn't really care that much
about it but when i was little
i really cared about that and i
still have my autograph book when i
was little yeah and so i was
like i want to get anybody we
see i'm getting at but they're they're
on a mission to get away from
you basically and i would be i
mean i'm a grown woman chasing them
going like
i got to talk to you like
you know i e yeah yeah yeah
she's like in a stroller like you
know a block away kind of like
carries of this habits um and you
could have just taken a pen and
signed it goofy know because it's about
how they do it individually each one
has their own signature um but yeah
so so those were only supposed to
take
you the thirty minutes or whatever to
get from one place to another um
and your handler wouldn't come with you
because they were just hanging out by
the entrance so the handler would greet
you when you got to the other
entrance but on this particular day in
july of nineteen eighty eight super fucking
hot it's like a hundred and something
degrees i'm
i'm sweating so bad yeah maybe about
one hundred three now probably do i
hear one of four
look kid about one hundred ten how
it felt inside but i got i
got lost in the park i couldn't
find where i was supposed to go
and i got lost and i was
out there for ninety minutes which is
so much longer than you are supposed
to do especially back then and i'm
just dripping sweat and kids are doing
what you were doing lauren which is
like tr
going to grab me so i don't
get away and because they want to
take pictures and i'm like blurry i
just like stopping and trying to wave
and take pictures really scary and i
i found myself and if you know
the geography of disneyland i found myself
out by it's a small world and
i was supposed to go to new
orleans square which is so reddit thread
who fucking knows over
anything isn't disneyland all these tools toggle
for the dismal fucking ton each shares
you who here's a reddit thread
wow you made me even though i'm
defending you
alright now you defend her paul ah
hey lately we're like oh
um anyway so i'm out in the
middle of it's a small world and
i've just basically given up i'm just
standing there in place while kids it's
kind of leader deaf i'm just looking
for an exit i can't find any
exit and suddenly someone grabs my hand
and says there you are rare bear
and i looked to my left and
it's a handler and they
i've been like on a mad search
looking for me for her that sounds
so fun further the last hour yeah
because i'd never reported back to where
i was like if i were them
i'd be like oh this is exciting
we have a good day happening over
here like this
you don't know if you're gonna be
like you're gonna catch you in your
head off drinking a beer because yeah
hey down and like those are some
things yeah price it doesn't happen more
often people just taking their head off
and go and fuck this and like
throwing it like kobe bryant's the hell
taking their like jeff jersey i yeah
you stole the two beers and went
down the slot right that's pretty great
where is he news
man i hope he's somewhere wonderful i
hope he eats two layers i love
that wherever you want much
i love him such a good guy
um yeah anyway so that was it
so i was i was one that
was probably when i was like fuck
this job i don't think i want
to come back to it which was
as easy as never calling in to
get your schedule ever i'm sure right
i i what's so funny to me
is that you're playing this character that's
from a cancelled movie
a like at that point they it
definitely at that point had been like
they locked that movie away yeah definitely
yeah even though they were still making
splash mountain and all that kind of
stuff yeah so what is the context
for kids when they see breyer bare
like nothing nothing with him you have
no context for that and i i
don't think it's like one of those
things where you just go oh yeah
he's
from one of those movies like you
just like kind of put them in
the robin hood sort of characters i
am i right um wait i have
an update on the jet blue guy
he lives between mexico and san diego
and he had a job at seaworld
as of tonight tears and nineteen oh
no mm okay and did we like
him still
i don't know why you would go
work at seaworld after that documentary came
out
maybe because of his prior work they
were like why are you
you can have two beers every shift
i also did not like my ways
oh yeah disneyland at the time would
would only let you bring two people
into the park per year um in
my opinion when you were when i
was working there i was like let
me come back here oh and and
by the way i would only be
able to come back twice a year
and just like as a guest i
was like living
in whenever i want a fuck you
should be able to be there every
day but the thing is like you
know what happened is that the employees
would start fraternizing like you go you
go around and you'd go see your
friend or you're out riding like i'm
not working doing her thing do it
hey i know you're a person in
there yeah you just roy
during the illusion for everyone else i
were on my way to mickey mouse
by the way i also worked at
knott's berry farm doing security during their
halloween haunt which is an entire lady
charity yes why do that excuse me
so this this touch the ghouls i
would have just
quit because this is the summer of
eighty or this is october of nineteen
eighty eight as well back in october
oh hey age so i would adjust
quit that i remember it was eighty
eight because i had just learned how
to get a good haircut and i
saw someone from my high school who
was like fuck
well so my dad my dad cut
my hair my entire life right because
oh okay yeah yeah because he didn't
want to spend money on haircuts and
instead so he bought clipping senses i
need pictures okay i barely have any
pictures of me by the way growing
because we didn't have like you know
phone cameras and so it was like
a big deal to put film in
the camera right so so i he
he and he was you know norman
forces guys so he gave me the
high and tight you know pretty much
for wow and then and then growing
up in the seventies and eighties the
bowl cut was the was yeah
he basically just put a bowl over
my head and cut around it and
shit a literal balka yeah and that
sucks and then i also was afraid
of barbers so if if he ever
did take me into a barber then
i would be very frightened that they
were gonna cut me and all this
kind of stuff so so i think
around maybe sixteen or so i
discovered there like a supercut to open
by my house and i was like
let me so let me see what
this is all about and i went
in and it was like oh but
i didn't know how how to describe
what i wanted right right but they
were like just judging by what you're
going with we know how to fix
this point but it still was not
good right so i spent all of
high school with basically precuts and you're
not great hair and then when i
turned eighteen and i went to college
my the guy who ended up being
my best friend cut hair and was
like oh like yeah why is your
hair so bad and it was like
i don't know what to ask for
and why is your hair so bad
you know what i have to say
um so i listened to
deep dive the new podcast from jessica
st clair and oh yeah diana feel
and i really loved it and and
i it's one thing that i've noticed
about their friend group which includes club
um but who else is in that
group like danielle schlosser casey wilson
or kindred one thing i really like
about that group is that it feels
like they're really honest with each other
like about stuff like that like where
it doesn't really matter but they'll say
like um jessica is telling a story
about some like really sentimental event they
had and then casey had like a
brain on top of her head and
she was like i i'm sorry i
can't do this with like that braid
on your head like
i slept with it i'm trying something
just like yeah it's not good like
and i think that's so funny and
i love that i may like that
kind of honesty i like that they
all trust each other enough to say
those things and it's not i appreciated
it because he was cool ah and
he had good hair and he was
like so why why
why is your hair the way it
is and i was like well i
don't know what to ask for so
he said well like is there a
picture or something that you like of
someone that you think has good hair
and i remember pulling out a picture
of of the band crowded house of
neil finn i was like can i
can you do something like this he's
like yes that's so easy you just
like it's shorter on the black music
like may mp the music and i
looked like erect sugar daddy i also
did not have a decent haircut until
i was about that age because my
growing up my aunt cut our hair
next door and she cut all of
our hair and so there's yeah you
know my school for frozen stuff like
that no charge which you really
no oh okay um and then i
went to like a bad barber like
just a local barber for a while
just like my bad lieutenant of barbers
yeah yeah yeah yeah no he suppose
yes yeah um and then i visited
my sister who lived in los angeles
in nineteen eighty
for wow and she took me to
a shortcut what sushi
sushi so that was very bad in
the los angeles news is that something
you had when you went there it
was not no i was just helped
to be cool like i think getting
your kind of vacation in a cool
city is such a good idea did
she teach you to believe what my
hair looked like afterwards i was like
oh my this is but see it
it was it was amazed it was
a revelation to me here's my here's
the thing i feel like it's easier
well it depends on who you are
in your whole vibe i'm paul i
ok well knowing your whole vibe is
but i think reserved judgement you'll be
able to maintain like you'd be able
to make it look the same or
get maintain the style yeah i
yeah it's in high school and they
look good when the person did it
and then i just would make no
effort to brush my hair put anything
in it i didn't know how to
blow dry it right or something and
so it just was like whatever all
the time and i feel like that's
part of the problem it's like i
could get a good haircut i had
the resources but i didn't care
or know how to maintain it yeah
but when your parents trying to help
you with that that i feel like
my parents basically gave up and never
never were like not never thought any
thing like that was important to me
even though it is important like your
yeah no my mom my mom shared
about all
she would be like why don't you
brush your hair that i'd be like
dough or whatever
oh my oh did teach me how
to do my makeup and stuff and
that was good and so i mean
i you know i'm sure i was
fine just i was more like casual
you know i didn't really care um
but i also see like these girls
now and i mean there are always
people like this like they're were always
like those girls who like had everything
put together and they looked like cool
but like it feels like
now it's like maybe because of social
media you have more pizza like to
look at and it's like youtube makeup
tips and yeah and you can watch
a video like how do i do
my hair how do i put on
makeup and like anyone has that too
available to them which is kind of
amazing know today that's what i'm better
things about the internet yeah but don't
you think that then all the
kids look so cool now that you're
like this seems wrong i'm not looking
at them so i have no idea
okay well it feels that way she's
got that kids all seem like really
put together and i'm like where are
the kids who like are dorks like
i guess they're not posting on social
media in that way it is always
weird to me and you see it
a lot in l a because you
you know
know people who are rich and they
the way they style their own kids
yeah it was like you see like
a little kid yeah that looks like
a fucking adult in like i was
like gel and like cool or so
clearly in a very expensive haircut and
like a super expensive looking clothes and
it's like this seems abnormal to me
i was
the one strange one thing i have
been doing recently is watching i've become
fascinated with instagram videos from like virtuoso
kids playing electric guitar or maisy and
doing like incredible metallica solos and stuff
like that and i was looking at
one yesterday with this like i couldn't
quite tell how old he was but
then
when there was a full body he
was like super short so i was
like is this kid like ten or
something like that but he had the
fucking coolest haircut and was wearing cool
clothes and shredding on the guitar and
i'm just like who taught him all
this i thought the six year old
girl in australia who's a skateboarder and
she's like amazing and she does like
fucking full-on moves like you know slipping
out and cut fine back into the
bowl or whatever the hell it's called
and she's amazing and i'm like what
that what is that about like how
do you yeah well yeah there's no
factories being prodigy is one thing but
the who who then on top of
it teaches them how to have cool
t-shirts
drugs cool and i mean she's six
and she's obviously her but maybe your
parents have to be really especially for
something like that where it's really risky
like doing skateboarding stuff like you have
to be really chill to like let
your kid fly in and out of
ah you know or or a terrible
parent
let's see i follow a toddler who
smears nutella order as you follow the
toddler too and i love her at
these so her knees ny he talked
about her before yeah she is like
she would her parents she she puts
food on her face a lot yeah
it's really funny it's really funny but
they her ma
mom gave her nutella and she was
just like she was eating it like
like that kind of thing where like
like winnie the pooh eating honey where
she's yeah her whole hey she eats
every meal yeah but then she just
started putting it on her face yeah
i love it i think it's so
cute but it's like the durable know
yeah i don't need everyone to be
a prodigy
yeah right i wish i was a
prodigy growing up geez
and i don't think i would yeah
i don't think i excelled at anything
participated i had to wait until i
was twenty
to be graded everything
okay to take a break we have
to take a break when we come
back though i'll tell you the surprising
conclusion to the knott's berry farms to
hurry oh wow here's what i was
surprised about that story over here i'm
always like brings you
how much more could there be alright
we'll be right back
and we're back and as promised here
is the exciting conclusion of the knott's
berry farm story um so i was
hired to do i was hired basically
i did the same thing where you
go in and and do a cattle
call kind of audition kind of thing
for ah for
knott's berry farm halloween haunt and you're
hoping to be a monster i have
to tell you something yeah there's a
video that is so funny and i've
talked about it on another show um
it's a it's i talked about mild
horses but it's a youtube video of
people auditioning to be scary at knott's
berry farm oh not scary farm whatever
and i think the halloween thing and
it's the
funniest thing ever it's like it's like
need to see that it's so loving
give them masks or anything or is
nil what they're like so walk up
to this axe on the floor and
just you know scream like
it's ah it's so good and some
people take like really seriously
it's it's just bizarre i love it
so much i don't know why i
didn't get the job to be a
monster unless i was too i mean
it seems like because my my best
friend got to be a monster so
it was very bizarre that unless unless
he got the job as a monster
i was like hey they're still looking
for people then by the time i
applied they were like we only need
security people at this point but
you probably just had that bear bear
energies yeah probably probably just to you
so that they were like you could
do security actually maybe they heard about
you from disneyland like this guy's gonna
get lost if you've got a mascot
yeah well so my friend he were
he was a monster and kingdom of
the dinosaurs which was an old ride
um at knott's berry farm and um
so he was watching what monster was
he at kingdom of the dinosaurs well
a kingdom of the dinosaur every ride
was obscured to and made halloween fide
so it wasn't kingdom of the dinosaurs
during halloween haunt but that was the
what why i don't know
like witch hats on the dinosaur
they had to share one
just pass it around um so he
was a monster in kingdom of the
dinosaurs and i was lying security in
front of kingdom of the dinosaurs where
i would basically like essentially i would
like lit in the hot people essentially
halloween haunt is just people trying to
zero guys any girls here oh yeah
i mean more lady
isn't there cyber honestly paul it is
not that far off from that but
it it it started as because everyone
just wants to cut the line constantly
and so it was lovely so you're
constantly just going like hey you know
when people coming up to you going
they behind me they were they they
just walked into the line and you
have to go over an arcs and
go like get out of here you
know
um so that's that's basically all i
did during halloween haunt but my friend
was working as a as a monster
inside the ride that i was working
so what he would do and he's
like this inkster he was this incredibly
good-looking guy right um well sure and
um so he would basically what would
happen is is
if a car would come through with
hot women who are our age he
would take off his mask to show
that he was handsome
jump in their car and then wash
chat them up whichever one he was
interested in and say hey let's go
out my friend scott is working as
us as a line security guard out
at the front of the ride so
go give give your number to him
and he'll pass it on to me
what that was his system i don't
know why i acquiesce to it because
i'd never benefited from it i the
one time that he ever asked me
if i wanted to go on a
double date i went to his apartment
and um the two girls arrived and
we sat down we talked for a
while and then he said ok let's
go when i stood up
and the girl who is supposed to
be on the day with me looked
at me and said oh you're coming
too so that was ah
oh wow she thought she was on
a double date with her friend and
this guy hoping to threesome with this
really good looking guy probably is my
friend arthur funds really
maybe she thought she would just win
out
so right yeah look at a dish
so so i would basically be fielding
um dates for him i do remember
he he had a vesper scooter he
had a cool like modx vesper scooter
and got some pretty cool i gotta
say he ah i'm jealous one time
he had a date wouldn't give him
my number
chicago no um he's a lawyer in
chicago but he had a cool wsba
scooter and one time that was tough
like the the girl that he asked
out lived an hour away by off
the four or five freeway and so
he needed me to drive him because
that was too dangerous to take the
scooter on so i drove him in
sat there while i he took the
girl into the
bedroom and i just watched i remember
watching the bangles walk like an egyptian
i mean i definitely had a couple
moments in my life for i was
just waiting for people to fuck
i feel like i can remember exactly
what happened but i just i know
that happened to me where i was
like i'm in a car and they're
over there doing something and i'd have
to wait for my friend to get
out or like yeah just so weird
i've been on i've been on in
situations like that where i'm like waiting
for my friend to close the deal
on yeah because there aren't things
you know it's not going to happen
you know what i mean and yeah
like this is what am i doing
here i the bird a friend on
a date once and this was when
we were adults but she was visiting
here and she met a guy online
and then i drove i think what
happened was he came to my show
show or something like they both did
that's how they like met up and
then i drove them to some like
second location and then picked her up
at the end
it was so random wow so yeah
sir things we do to have sex
i wanted her to have sex what
can i say well the final punchline
of the of the knott's berry farm
story is is that we were only
working there for that month right for
for all of october and your last
day was halloween and so
so my friend deny who my my
monster friend and i called in sick
on halloween when she was like the
guides insane after they've been doing that
for a whole month the guy answering
the phone was just like so pissed
and just like oh huh you're sick
you know like we're like oh yeah
i can't make it tonight yeah and
then we ended up going to the
park because like so
so does so kid like you know
name games like how we're not working
but i want to go hang out
yeah it's like you because we we've
found the entrance where if you dressed
in all black they assumed you were
a monster the employee entrance and they
would just not check anything and just
let you through you know what do
you mean you found that entrance was
wearing that for a job
yeah but you had but use you
you were supposed to show that you
were working there ron you know and
that one there was a specific entrance
where you could just walk in it
looked like you already had checked yes
anytime he went right through the park
you had dish but there was a
specific entrance where it was just if
you dressed all in black they assumed
you were a monster and so you
just walked right in and so we
just hung out there all night and
i
was just so i didn't want to
go by kingdom of the dinosaurs because
i didn't want my supervisor to see
me of course not but i mean
obviously yeah i think
there was a story um that josh
melina the actor told about he was
in a few good men on broadway
and when the big bang theory that's
right yes and ah ken marino was
his understudy in that play and so
the run was like you know
it's very successful show and ran for
a long time and so um josh
ah wanted to let i think it
was like coming to a close or
something and josh wanted to let can
get a chance to go on stage
that's nice so he told him i'll
call out sick and so you can
go on but then josh went to
the play to watch
him and fucking up busted by the
directing
because he wanted to see how he
did he like when in second act
of the play oh gee any like
i got got what are the directors
it was something like ah you feel
better like something like that ah oh
i better parenting dora maar au know
is leaders need to be made illegal
they have
i've been in some states but i
truly hate them i hate watching i
was thinking about them how i used
to be so mad in my old
apartment whenever a leaf blower would wake
me up and i would i would
just be banging the window like it
has to be illegal to do this
before ten a m ten am was
my cutoff at the time but it's
like yes it's because it's so bad
for the environment
it actually like produces so much gas
and then they just blow the dirt
around and then they halftime you just
see them put it into a pile
and don't do anything with it it's
like what is this why are you
moving piles of leaves from one area
to another what have we become dirt
don't hurt
just let it build up a little
bit actually um
i had a neighbor incident happen whoa
okay so we're talking by the way
with the reason i brought up my
neighbor incident before i never got to
i think was basically i i think
it was the result of you guys
shouting in my backyard for months anyway
go ahead you think that's why they
were mean to you yes you you
guys shout
yeah my backyard yeah i want to
put the blame but we would do
it once a week every once in
a while it wasn't like xy mud
but it's your fault okay whatever okay
what's your neighbors okay so um basically
because of the pandemic there you know
ah we don't drive that much or
fifty five
there's a car that we have that
we left on a street that this
is not doing think it's one cycle
in it's truly fine i haven't thought
about it much at all am
then the other day or this was
like a week ago now i was
walking to my car which is parked
in a different location and i pass
by that car and then i was
like oh there's a piece of paper
on it so i went over and
got the piece of paper and it
said hey bitch d dear asshole yeah
by the way this is a street
where there's no restrictions there's no reason
for this to be an issue there's
plenty of space it's although it is
illegal to leave your car parked in
one place for
i forgot what the period of time
is but well okay but i it
didn't seem like it's actually an issue
because right there's plenty of parking everywhere
why would we have moved data just
it doesn't we don't take it that
often or anything so whatever right but
um then there's the notes like please
move your car i need to clean
my front oh
let's see
and then it said um your car
has been here for one month and
then it had my license plate on
it as if i didn't know that
that's the thing yeah note on this
is the proof yeah and then and
then it said p s two were
like four twenty two is earth which
i think it means earth day earth
friendly do is keep keep clean and
i was like nothing i'm doing is
not clean this is not unclean this
is not tobacco car i mean it's
legally parked it's even better for the
earth and moving it i mean i
don't understand but so then i ok
so
but so i had noticed it on
for twenty and the note was left
on for eighteen so i moved the
car instantly and i was like i'll
literally never park there again whatever it's
fine
within a day she had and this
woman by the way is kind of
notorious already we're already having a lot
of back and forth about various things
that i'm like very confused by um
but she had cleaned the front with
there's like a small pile of leaves
where the car was i guess there's
really bothering her
she moved her car into the spot
and then put two green trash cans
to block anyone from parking behind her
oh lot of that i hate i
mean and i was just like the
pettiness is she just wanted her parking
spot back and she's using hey yeah
and i was like i don't hang
around hands yes um i'm sorry i'm
sorry
annoyed you so much to see a
car sitting there but there are other
cars that are also there all the
time like there's a car on my
street that has ivy growing out of
it but it's been there for
like i mean i'm very very very
long time so like you should leave
the same note on her car and
with her license plate number on my
license plate number um but anyway i
just kind of think it's amazing when
people get really because i've had a
nice interaction with her and then and
then i wasn't sure if she knew
it was my car and ah but
then we think that she does now
that it is yeah old people wrong
they all get crazy don't say now
i would love to raising cut-off oh
there is no crazy cut off sixty
five know like when does every person
become crazy like no one past the
age of what sixty seventy is saying
anymore it's like let's okay i don't
agree with that but i feel like
like i would never do the oh
another crazy thing happened here we go
so this is kind of shy this
is getting exciting so lords crazy things
this woman lives across the street from
me and i've
i met her briefly and she seemed
really nice she's like in her forties
i would say she seems like a
very pulled together person has a nice
house like i never really thought twice
better shame comes knocks on my door
with this being done with ou brand
i was i wasn't a big dog
was with her and i was in
the shower but mike had seen that
she was knocking on there but didn't
answer hey you're like you repeat that
i was singing yeah so mike saw
that she was at the door but
didn't answer it because he was like
i don't know what you want so
that was a coward yeah he's afraid
he can't even
he didn't he just was like whatever
i'm sure it's mike had crawled into
a kitchen cupboard it was somebody's at
the door or maybe he was busy
i don't know i'll give him some
sort of kind of law
okay so then i get another shower
and like we're hanging out and then
like a little bit later when did
you dress i i'm nude this whole
time and then she cum laude door
shower new y'all my favorite she comes
the door again with a dog and
so then he's like well don't answer
that i was like i'm good to
answer it and here's like a doughnut
i was like i was
we gotta know what it is now
she's coming here twice maybe there's something
serious or something i don't know and
so i go up and the problem
is with mass because that then suddenly
we're losing half of our like you
know ability to be a nice lady
you don't eat meat yeah yeah like
i'm like i'm trying to show that
i'm like a nice person you're surmising
like nobody's
business so but so in the meantime
i had to i wasn't nude but
i did have to put on a
robe and i had my pajamas on
and so then i i go and
get my role by mass by time
i get all that stuff she's gone
but there is a note on the
door that says it's your neighbor so
on so i would like to talk
to you please and then her phone
em but she heard me open the
door so she turns around
with her dog comes back
so then i was like is everything
okay because i'm like what does this
know like what's going on i mean
i can't even imagine what this is
about account yeah and she's like
hum well someone in the neighborhood um
called um animal control on me and
complained about my three dogs and i
said is it illegal to have three
dogs and she said i was like
i didn't do that i don't know
but i thought i was against illegal
hectares and she was like i don't
know but um i'm a dog trainer
and so i have diff
aren't dogs and somebody called and you're
going person that i haven't i don't
really know that well so i was
just seeing it and i was like
well i definitely didn't do that i
was like i don't care what you
do like
you could die right now
nah because i was trying to be
like i would never do that but
it's like what the mask on it
feels like i'm lying because i'm over
animated yeah to show the i don't
i would not do that i wouldn't
do it's like i wouldn't i would
make you like save it for the
razzies honey
i didn't win by the way my
size
she i she when i said she's
like very pulled together it's like i
have seen various dogs going out of
her house i've never even really noticed
that they were different dogs and i've
never thought about it because she it's
not like she seems like a hoarder
or something but now we're she's so
she went away but she didn't seem
to believe me there was definitely a
moment of her like kind of going
like well and i was like well
if we
let me know if you figure it
out like i truly was like i
don't know and then she left and
i was like she thinks i did
that and now i'm and i'm so
curious who did it and i'm like
but you either birthday lady or somebody
who like i think just doesn't have
some gotta be earthday lady right there's
always a one
one person who is constantly involved in
drama in the neighborhood yeah it was
the woman with half a brain in
my old condo she would she poured
bird seed into our porch and she
vandalized car that was me oh i
did the bird seed oh no why
would you oh no what did you
think it was her i've always heard
this whole time no i want you
guys to have a bunch of birds
oh no
did you mean she just poured half
of her brain onto the urge
no
murray's not a poor lady she like
intentionally vandalized our other neighbors car and
she got into like screaming that she
was insane but oh wow well yeah
that's what i mean like that's so
unfortunate what a shame it is to
lose one's mind sure of course but
well if anyway if one loses one's
mind i hope you would come out
on the
ah the spectrum of being happy all
the time instead of being that the
ideal isn't it i love that that
happens as often as you'd like and
for that i i will just say
one last thing about her is that
now that i'm aware that this is
a thing i'm trying to count the
dogs so i'm like okay every jimmy
currently with a dog i'm counting on
my dog
i just want to know and then
my other friend was like she probably
has nine dogs that are in there
at all times like because it's like
she framed it like why would they
call on my three dogs when yeah
so anytime anyone anytime anyone has a
framing it's always three times worse well
you know it's like she's setting it
up to go like there
is no reason it's only three it's
like new year like i parked there
for two weeks yeah you were parked
there six weeks yeah yeah i mean
yeah that's that's that's probably true because
i think i don't know how long
the car had been sitting there and
i don't care but i mean yeah
i'll literally never do that again i
don't i don't want to have these
sort of interactions you know my dad
used to get really
mad at me for parking um and
and this is something that he this
is another in a series of like
getting mad at me for something that
he never told me was a thing
like right right but but when i
started driving he would get mad if
i wouldn't if i would sort of
park where there was not a car
length behind me
up to the driveway because he's like
now only two cars can fit in
where three cars used to and he
was like really upset with me about
it and in getting really mad instead
of just going like oh hey by
the way this would be a polite
thing for yeah it's just like why
are you parking you're always parking this
way like i don't know i'd never
thought about it before like oh
oh yeah i guess that that is
like more of a polite thing to
do yeah but now i think of
every time i park anywhere sure well
we're yelling got results well um a
way to make a dog behave is
debated i think we talked about this
old arm expression on our group thread
is that an actual expression yeah yeah
um and i feel like it's not
an expression that seems to be just
like a belief system yeah
it doesn't like mean something else yeah
yeah yeah it's not a colloquialism it's
like well you know what they say
if you come into my house i'll
punch you in the fucking face real
e ticket ride with those dogs um
i think we mentioned this on the
group our groups judge the text thread
and
janie and i talked about it on
our podcast but i was the victim
of a prank call recent oh yes
i've heard this where a guy called
up ah called my cell phone ah
and ah se said he was a
neighbor
use a neighbor and ah he said
my wife saw you and your wife
walking walking your dog and the dog
shit on our in front of our
house and you don't have ah no
right and ah you next time just
clean it up and i said oh
your i think your wife is mistaken
because we don't have a dog and
the guy said look just clean it
up next time okay i said
we don't have a dog like this
guy i will send this guy masterfully
pushed a button in me by saying
the same thing over and over again
in a condescending way like he was
not calling me a liar but he
was just saying well just wait we
don't need to play these games just
to just clean up here so i
i'm going you
you know it's like it's like gaslighting
where i'm going i start to go
crazy yeah i have a dog i'm
telling you i don't have we don't
have a dog new guy just keeps
telling me to to clean it up
and it escalates to the point where
he's like he's he says like why
don't you come outside or something um
and
i'm screaming at this guy and so
i say fine i'll go outside and
i go outside ah thinking we're going
to talk to each other and the
guy is nowhere to be seen he's
like and i said where are you
where are you jerry you said you're
gonna come outside you're like homicidal i'm
not coming out there
and so i he keeps saying look
i just clean up after your dog
and i'm like wait i thought i
da yeah and then at this point
at one point the neighbor's dog start
barking and he goes oh you don't
have a dog was one of those
dogs that are barking and i said
that the neighbor's dogs and he says
oh well maybe that was it
ah i don't like you fucking idiot
sorry think well because how do we
yeah because act because he called back
and this to me is the is
the it's a very amateurish prank call
because if there were no peaks and
valleys to it really and the guy
had a perfect ending and then he
called back like the perfect ending was
oh maybe it was those yeah so
so he called back and i'm like
what what do you want man and
he's like listen my wife wants to
talk to your wife
you know and i said i'm not
gonna i'm not gonna put my wife
on the phone and he's he so
he keeps going on with the same
thing and i was like okay jerry
what do we look like you know
if you saw us on on video
what do we look like and ah
he says well you have a dumb
little moustache and you want to you
either your wife is pretty cute
um and i'm like well if you're
i mean now you're just insulting me
like what is the point of this
and go on my wife just let
legislators know it's my wife is pretty
cute because she's cute
um and i said but what did
he cute know she's wonderful know she's
gorgeous okay scott um but i i'm
in love with her she likes running
i can tell this guide as you
want to give it up so i'm
like letting it heal of course my
wife is beautiful yeah but he starts
with dumb little mustache yeah so um
i say what do you what do
you want and he goes ah lemme
my
wife wants to talk to your wife
and i said that's not going to
happen and then um he says oh
he says oh wait away my wife
said ah my wife said it was
your wife it was your wife who
was shitting on the lawn and i
was like then i realize that yes
i should have realized earlier but i
was like oh did you say oh
this is a prey i died i
just said oh okay i get it
now
and he said i said did you
did you get what you wanted and
he was yeah
ah so but i heard didn't you
say something to the effect of you
found out definitively yeah how does how
did you find this another i tweeted
about it and ah another comedian that
we know called me up this is
like somebody we don't talk on the
phone okay and he said did you
you did you get prank called by
this guy and i said yeah and
he said he did the same thing
he did the same thing to me
i'm not the same exact prank but
he the same guy called me um
and what i've been doing is i've
been calling him back all the time
to the point where he's begging me
to not call him anymore oh what
did you have his number did his
oh yeah yeah yeah but it was
a fake number it wasn't i think
it was a spoofed number yeah i
have no idea where there's like a
good number so yes yay yeah he
could be anywhere but like it was
very like when i think back onto
the signs were very clear that he
did not live in my neighborhood
and did not know like any time
i asked him what street do you
live on is like i'm not gonna
tell you right you know yeah it
was like they didn't like when i
look back all this the story falls
apart very quickly so what lesson did
you learn paul never pick up the
phone well here seek because he called
once and i didn't recognize the number
so i didn't take the call that
he immediately call
and and i was like oh somebody
is trying to get a hold of
me yeah something yeah yeah yeah and
it wasn't it was yeah so he
got me i hope you hope he
gets his jojoba enjoys and acknowledge jollies
wow i guess the idea is this
guy puts them up online and then
he takes them down once like a
lawyer says you better take that down
oh my god because it is illegal
we live in a state where it's
legal to record report
out of there yeah yeah that's why
crank anchors has to be in vegas
yes yes yes yeah um die i
told you my i mean it's better
than getting scammed i i told him
my mom was scammed recently on a
phone thing i think so yeah but
a a lot maybe she just haven't
well she
the guy has been calling her back
and keeps keeps doing so of me
for scamming you know i'm in love
with you
essentially she she clicked on one of
those websites that like your computer is
frozen and you have to call a
number you know yes i remember this
yeah and then she calls and she
gets she like
grants them access into her computer yeah
this kind of stuff and then she
pays them in order to anyway so
so the guy though has been now
calling her on the phone to try
to reengage because that's what they do
is if they find someone who's given
money once you know they may be
likely to give it twice
so she's just been like you know
declining these calls all the time it's
just so it's so such a bummer
for old people to like fall victim
to this kind of stuff yeah yeah
so mean it so as not to
do reality recap everyone i'm so sorry
but reality recap yeah gen shah from
real housewives
salt lake city was just arrested for
having a telemarketing scam system that she
was getting tons of money from people
old people yeah it's so bad have
you heard those tapes of the of
the like scam artists these be raised
here and they're very jerky
i just i laughed so hard that
that first jerky boys tape oh absolutely
that was one of the funnel my
god yeah i remember that yeah um
but yeah the the the like anytime
they bust one of these scammers and
then they play their own the tapes
of them back to them it's just
crazy how terrible they're like ye
yelling at these old people going give
me the fucking money you know like
at a certain point at a certain
point the civility drops and they need
to close the deal and they're just
like go to your beagle go to
your open up your bank website right
now and give me this fucking money
i'm gonna fuck you know and then
they plays in that work though yeah
like there and so they
play these tapes for these scammers that
they caught and they're just like scenario
lichens and yeah that's bad yeah i
shouldn't have done that yeah yeah i
did lose my temper there i i
wish i had been more measured when
i was talking to that old lady
about getting all of her money whatever
bank account and giving it to me
but are there things okay so it
like people have tried to scam me
even
recently and was saved for scam sky
for a second i'll go like is
this real and then literally all you
have to do is google like a
few words of it and then it'll
come up i'm like oh yeah this
is a fake thing yeah yeah but
are there when we get older are
there going to be things that we
don't understand that we're like
that's a good question because we i
mean we we are of age ah
with modern technology and knowing how people
exploit it and so like you know
if i get a i guess it's
like how convincing someone can be as
an actor because if you get a
robocall that
like your social security number is about
to expire you're like okay so this
is horse shit i know your social
security number doesn't expire you know your
auto warranty or whatever um but if
somebody's a good and i mean scams
really depend on
are you a good enough actor to
convince the person that what you're saying
is true right you know and like
that's why i think the robocalls are
you they can't get that many people
with those days they weren't like i've
read about him they work enough to
where it's worth it for them
right wow yeah well yeah essentially it's
free money i mean all you have
to do is set that thing up
there's very little effort involved right but
i wonder what could happen that would
i mean obviously the ones where they
send you a fake email from one
of your places to get your password
that like anyone our age fun yeah
sometimes like what could be something that
we would fall for
four
i don't know i mean maybe l
invented in the future where we're so
where it's yeah probably my kid just
more believable where it's like they know
the company that you actually are registered
with and they are they have some
more information or something yeah this is
yeah eighteen t and you have a
phone line with us and lovable but
you know or whatever and then it's
like true and so you're like oh
oh right okay um yeah i don't
know it's so scary though that that
you can just get old and not
know what's going on in the world
anymore and people can take advantage of
that i mean i do feel like
the generation before our generation is like
in the worst position for that because
technology like sped up so much and
they were not really taught all of
that stuff so yeah
that's way harder right i mean unless
there's a huge leap in the next
few years where we're unable to like
keep up with it which seems deep
fakes de fe that's a pretty good
one because you'll get face time from
your niece or whatever and it's not
your knees and that would be really
fucked i need all the money
and you know drama oh i'm in
jail stuck industry these give me the
money alright let's take a break when
we come back we'll do a three
jerk alright
we're back where i live too well
yes no i think organising to say
they were going to say we're gonna
say so yeah no no i mean
just say for three shot what did
you say nothing is further of course
this little bit is a perfect segue
a into the future that i chosen
so this why it is this
it's called listen to me and it's
submitted by angela viva gua one observer
attempts to see life water we talked
about her show yeah you said that
name yes she um she commented during
the she watched her show yeah okay
i got to passer one observer attempts
to listen to both other players who
are simultaneously telling their own
in stories stories last one minute then
the observer has thirty seconds to summarize
everything they were able to gather from
both stories everyone wins there are no
losers
oh i like that yeah it's good
then i wouldn't like you guys to
lose and for me to be the
winner but doesn't god that's not in
the spirit how dare you say such
a thing alright so ho a little
ho are you gonna listen to us
first lauren yeah i get my timer
ready give the old timer and say
what's happening who goes who's going with
you and i tell stories
the same time an i'm going to
summarize what you said okay and all
and i only have thirty seconds to
do that yeah you have one minute
and go i was walking down the
street just the other day and i
may cross house very very short pereira
seven feet tata will be very which
is short for i was aber lying
doing on
joiners say is and this this person
came back in damage over yield in
my rory said hey there's a treasure
chest in your ear with wheels i
was like no lagers in there and
sale you can find so sale is
going around the knee with ah xi
and mr sauce angelo of course and
cheaply like dug my ears
walker looks sad tiny sutures retreat and
i had which had the large glasses
of cold apparently lawyers doctors in a
sign romantic inbox where it was bigger
on the inside and i think i'm
the outsider hat and we were suddenly
rich and so we spent all day
like a montage where they just nah
it was like a shopping montage like
you tried
somewhere like you know wrapping the reading
box at me in lab in you
know yeah dora and we were all
just possessions and roller gave him all
i don't carry so
okay that was really hard
i have thirty seconds to tell you
what i heard okay so paul had
a halloween costume that was like something
over his head and then he also
had roller skates i made it really
hard to go upstairs so he had
like walked sideways up the stairs and
downs like do the trick or treating
and it was really
i'm comfortable and scott scott met a
tall short person who's seven feet tall
and then they had a ring box
and snapped at like julia roberts in
pretty well you missed the entire middle
yeah that's second
i wondering how people listening to this
will i mean you can focus on
one play you focus on the family
well that's the thing i was trying
to timely both and i often think
i'm good at doing that you don't
mean like in life where i'll be
like i'm hearing everything that's happening right
now and there's like no you're not
okay obviously i'm horrible at it i
listened to the two of you yeah
yes do i'm gonna keep time i
can i can probably do it it's
actually found that a little distracting when
i was talking when i was listening
right go ahead
dope i am so i was innerwear
screen i went on the counselors network
and our teacher nineteen when it was
monsieur de chico thousand and she was
a time when she was not a
nom and people want she was just
a rural person teaching brand new rides
and lots nine she brought little dad
was gonna bring this
original broadway cast oh jesus christ like
the kids screaming show reporting these ladies
are using them at first wary scary
haunted house the idea was that we
were gonna ever listening which something was
the core allow us to tell questions
scream as you know and the israel
of god is telling me the lan
as all this recording where i remember
the time
weight of area there was a very
jewish museum and she went to jail
but it was um during times ideas
i want to remove razor did she
specifically am using the thing like we
started like streets or maybe this was
a mountainous forty two song by som
turns out his main chillan prison to
this day she has but she slowly
slowly slowly cool and she's now show
yeah sure
okay
okay so here's what i think paul
you have my thing okay you have
thirty seconds paul you had a teacher
who was a nun named mrs pachinko
or something or maybe she wasn't a
nun i can't remember but she played
the jesus christ superstar cast album for
you in class and it was a
very moving experience you don't remember whether
it was song by song or whether
it was all played at the whole
time
lauren there was a period in the
nineties or something when people were making
new roller coasters all the time and
then so they switched them over to
being halloween themed roller coasters and someone
videotaped people's reactions to being on them
which was illegal now that's totally wrong
ah i mean i made it up
it was just a rambling story but
the the who it was was a
woman a teacher told the kids to
scream on the rollercoasters and they recorded
the screens they also recorded her telling
the kids to scream and then went
to jail for her whole life and
she's still in jail to the stand
she's slow xy yeah okay well i
was always close with you you were
pretty close i think you were probably
you heard jesus christ superstar you started
paying more attention to me um
but ah no i said well lauren
was going so slow and barely said
anything so i was able to really
concentrate on you
eating after every because i was making
it up again telling i do like
your nun named mrs pachinko but i
do think maybe this is a hint
because yeah telling a real story is
easier to follow i followed paul story
better than i thought sky yeah so
let's now you now scott and tell
real stories real story okay and you
have one
we have one minute oh look i
think of any real story well okay
well let me start over yeah please
start let me say you have to
think of real story
okay
i'm ready i'm not ready oh learn
to do it with me that's right
oh she went into her memory palace
i know
really why don't i know anything that
ever happened um ok okay go ahead
so when i was working for the
orange county rare winners hey at a
certain year where we dabbed noises and
yeah basically and i was really excited
to just house you would actually try
to like it into this page never
gotten to any plans then put them
no addition tag was gone i had
like
i would consider a really good guy
yeah there was this one seems sure
well who he was he's hard to
boy and he was really doing this
and bigot page everybody you know cats
are not there's something at all so
the kid comes over to our house
and rollers newspapers and i remember when
really fun to do but then i
remember it's never they never ended up
any attaching to cancel the base
show just a different but yeah remember
wrong i keep jokes why that happened
when they started the shooting way over
to the world so territory holding monster
october and but i was watching nothing
right because ultimately i still feel like
plate still feels like oh what did
i have to do something like that
memory of seeing the why was it
that they rolling up a paper
like that and those realising they've got
the word series happened to these children
having to do the show so it's
not just a random okay and laura
lauren audition for noises off but she
did not get it and they know
not doing the show at all for
some reason they did something because you
get eric and lauren did not understand
why some people got picked again and
again to be in
these shows and other people do not
ah scott was talking about the captain
of the newspaper delivery squad um you
would go over the captain's house roll
the newspapers together and reading in the
newspaper of people calling reggie jackson mister
october is when scott realized ah that
the world series happens at the same
time staff yeah i mean really yeah
hard for me really good maybe it
isn't easier when people are telling actually
yes we do to fake stories
two fake stories but both topos because
he was so good and he did
it so okay so much food it's
a real test so we'll do to
fake stories to paul and see how
good he actually is okay
and that'll be the deciding factor of
nothing okay okay and
oh i remember when i would make
me all tapping it's not a good
thing i went over to my friend's
house and i was just rolling newspapers
a while just nine is powering yeah
that and there was a story about
reggie jackson verifying and they were calling
interface images their heads under mad like
an aunt or like little monsters and
scenarios which anyway my religious
wrench and hit me in the back
of the head and hey me had
a dream why are you stare actually
this year you might go up there
answer marie my doing your well california
kid who i said okay fine i'll
do jumping it was did that he
literally jumping jacks early parents' house she
was probably probably not a better parent
company in michigan it's like jay finally
you worship a sweats me your name
i had yeah and a neighbor trying
to grab you and so he's already
wrapped his arms around that and i'm
literally no like a little outline they
woke up in the wind was like
his you know my house's yard and
our boat and then you took it
out really show him he tried to
fall off my chair and literally was
in jail to this day losing weight
mass number may speak and he says
oh you know what okay that was
a little tough because scott was way
out of the floor and you were
telling your same story with different yeah
i use a fake jewelry he paraphrases
store he wrote mr feb
didn't know that was real but then
he went out and he started she
was ordered to do jumping jacks and
so he was doing that lawrence started
out with a sort of dissertation about
nightmares that then eventually became a story
that i couldn't hear that well that
involved a neighbor and lauren saying it's
me it's me well you're forgetting about
the part where i wriggled free like
a little year
oh and he tried to take off
my head like a garter snake with
the show well i bet you maybe
that's too gruesome for me to recount
oh okay there was a friend who
had a nightmare who was so scared
that he went over to his neighbor's
parents' house instead of down we gotten
both them and the parents got arrested
and they're still in jail to this
day wow
well that was fun i enjoyed that
said everybody won every no love there
were no losers i think that one
goes in the in the in the
past three years will do that one
again in the pantheon guys we want
to thank you so much for listening
and guess what the giblets are available
it's her up we have
already know this you already know you
already know this but we we got
them sent to us just the other
day and we were so excited that
we all know what to say we
we all bought individual new pairs of
crocs and i'm just now we all
have a white crux so watch out
for the summer so those gibbins will
pop those gyms are going up so
yeah they they arrived i immediately put
m in jamie's crocs she was very
excited
good site buy it and they look
they look very funny and cute
go get them go get them good
picture and we'll see you next week
okay ah yeah
uh