three
food guy i dig it
i guess the history
by remake of the mix
oh hey oh okay guys the pupae
reback foot popeye reboots
hi everyone welcome to three duh um
size you need it's a chilly morning
and we're recording essentially anywhere outside my
backyard there is some construction going on
next door and isn't allowed in my
headphone knots not currently but it will
i know it's ironic they're constructing a
soundproof studio yea yea yea
i was telling paul before you got
here oh um i'm learning and i'm
scott ah we never know when they're
gonna show up yeah those days and
days oh my god my there's multiple
houses on my street being redone next
just be months with no action and
then suddenly it's like they're there all
day and night here's what i like
about that
is that i think it keeps construction
fresh yeah you never know it's gonna
have exactly you have to have surprise
it's especially construction as also mentioning the
shouting is new there there's shouting now
ally oh my god yesterday or not
couple days ago this used to work
silently there's one new guy you guys
like having makes fun he's shouting about
others idea yeah
ealing and a new guy but no
guys new guys just have a like
boy
yeah but ladder
ah a little bit louder now yes
exactly that's what i say to a
step ladder can i just say that
my neighbor's house is under construction and
then the other day there was this
person just going hello hello
over and over walking around their property
and i was peeking out the window
trying to see what was going on
and could they possibly win and they
laughed but i was like what do
they think is gonna how you saw
the person yelling hello idea but then
i and i was right next to
them they had sodomy i thought was
like an edgar allan poe situation where
someone was being built into the house
ah oh oh well what was a
purse
isn't built into that yeah hey let's
go on to d o to like
to harness about that now don't tell
heart is about a heart beating mean
that's what i thought me that's what
i know the casket momento de me
what i thought
here on the whole thing about a
body and a house these are all
parodied on the comedy bang bang halloween
and don't worry it was okay i
guess i'll check that out and learn
what is going on if you were
freaking out don't worry okay milbank tv
show has covered both tell-tale heart and
this one motel orc
the motel heart-to-heart
yeah casco matteo and i pray to
god i'm saying that that name correctly
a guy ah bricks another guy into
a wall in the cigar and the
will can't do anything about it well
i'm certainly can't
i mean yeah he could've fought he
couldn't push the bricks before they dried
look i haven't read the story so
i don't know but maybe he was
tied up yeah that would be helpful
but but the knight wagon all times
like please don't do this it's a
long project though to get to one
trapped inside a wall i think most
of our built already in there with
a little alex few months
it can take months if you mean
that according to that part of the
torture yeah exactly like oh man this
wall is like a lie the guy
takes breaks and the guy inside is
like come on
if you're gonna do it do it
do it i want to die already
know maybe watch you eat your sandwich
oh does he not does he die
in the in that story or does
he he just lives there oh what
about he just lives there he has
a little tv i feel like you
know like he's just like trapped in
there and he lives there i know
anything he does he think he's gonna
die do you think he's dead by
now
nine hundred years said ninety seventy one
it was his only futuristic story epic
and he was six years old and
it was seventy one yeah he's probably
like fifty seven at this point right
now or so hey
over six years okay for second game's
turning to me i thought that was
make me so much older o durning
fifty eight i think thirty eight
i really think so bye my dd
damn fair or it's um guys i
have an update here's my impression of
next door me yeah hey you
huh
sorry you have an update okay so
ah i think i told you i've
first of all i have a valentine's
update wow oh my i need to
hear if you do you have a
valid update i ain't valid update what
happened ah i i am lucky for
someone like if somebody's like if it
was online the hell
der i loud one jesus wow let's
look for someone what did you do
i asked cool op i was like
hey ah you don't care that i
didn't get you anything and she's like
no and ah she's like we're just
this is just for trips
take your hand off my knee i
don't think of you that way no
friends were on a friend trip home
as she said this is what the
trip is for so we could use
like well thank you thank you for
for setting it up i was like
do you mind if i record a
video of you saying that to lauren
and she said ok and then she
would know
because no i'm i'm with lowers you
shouldn't be on the record saying she
never wants to be around huh anyway
so case closed alright wow he says
you got through this one now how
about you paul nothing you didn't do
anything and acknowledging sammy mountains and in
fact yeah we do that we say
we kind of say it in a
jokey way okay know what i mean
mean but in a cute way um
but she she checked with me this
year she was like we you don't
mind we don't do anything right and
i was like no i hate it
wow so we were everyone just taking
the temperature we we did go to
a bakery ah the the day before
valentine's day and i got a bunch
of baked goods including some that had
ha
arts in em and stuff like that
account we put him out for the
whole family the next day yeah that's
very name to help and we yeah
my tv spencer was there lighting them
up in a line outside how some
of them had human shit in the
chi
oh my god yes so that was
that was i love it we renewed
our vows um on valentine's day huh
yeah i don't know if that's anything
we do it every week well that's
nice yeah wow just give me thursday
night
comparison overview guy that would get so
exhausted how reviewable yeah hey let's say
exactly
it's still just do a line through
once over these decent i feel like
it's a little low i do too
but i didn't want to say okay
you want me to turn you guys
he knows lowry said well we want
shower was too loud
um i also have one other update
okay she's us cry um scott county
here scott's updates we were
we were out of town ah in
and it was like ah we went
up to santa ynez and we did
like a wine tasting trip down so
beautiful by the way anywhere in los
angeles anywhere in california other than san
francisco i always said we went down
there right yeah i used to do
i follow writing i have no idea
anything that i say that we know
either we went down there now easier
we went up there oh okay said
a
correct i had to
because i always it's just a colloquial
like we went down to whatever right
when you grow up in southern sudan
was your when you grow up in
california just like we went down to
whatever so i used to say it
to like we went down to san
francisco and people would be like down
you went up that's very string oh
my god san diego's below us yes
yes so to me everything is either
san francisco or san
diego yeah right i always say i
would say i went up to sacramento
but i would never why would you
so what is there to do the
state capital yes yeah just to walk
by kevin governor yes
okay so what happened no she's a
senator um so we did one of
the wine tastings we were at as
we were leaving this is very nice
i thought gay didn't didn't say hello
to us at the beginning oh and
make us self-conscious here's a nice couple
nice couple who was one of the
tables next to us who
said hello there big fans of the
show and show how nice oh and
they said by the way we were
listening to it on the on the
way up here they said by the
way ah you are correct your streak
is good with the photon with a
pell toe so case closed wow another
castle close wow it's very kentucky back
to one
person that was really nice that was
really nice of them to be on
your side yes i like that i
my thing on the street are the
same i wish maybe i'd elucidated it
a little bit more sometimes easy dated
some incident me sometimes it's somebody is
literally the only motivating factor to get
me on yeah when we get you
know
what i mean and so to have
gone for a full year
inhabit in my mind of like okay
i'm really busy this week but the
weekend i'll get back on i'll continue
the streak and then to have the
internet down all weekend was just like
it's crushing to me i was like
oh shit of like oh no all
this work so anyway so i did
extra the following week when the when
the streak or wow and it was
back
reverse mr big
capital living mr spall you kept living
but this is hard
this is small ms small so i
was married when he called kerry hey
ms small
did she ever know he was called
bay or did he ever knows okay
well that's a good question you now
feel like this comes up all the
time you remember when jimbo at the
end of the was it the movie
no it wasn't where they showed his
end of the series because partner phone
and it said john was calling yes
i was like the end of the
series could he have a name that
wasn't just
john yeah like all this time like
larry write something something just kind of
legit to give to give him like
giacomo sigh infection the most like masculine
nam you could you know is like
infection yeah and also slang for a
patron even sex workers yeah true banshee
oilers beagle
john so many things are called john
a toil including a patron of sex
workers a dick is dick called john
now a johnson well i shorted
oh i'm sorry to hear that ah
you got me yeah the surgery
guess anyone wants to know mike really
liked his foot themed presents yeah what
was it it was like a trap
scraper box jib it's a baby quilt
tarantino collection
crocs gibbins and baby foot yeah i
told you about it baby was the
baby foot it takes away your oh
oh right right right right she has
he tried it no we're gonna do
it together oh ny always fun so
you bought yourself one yeah so this
is a present to yourself that presents
a couple's present that was romantic
got some mask
i'm not i'm not looking at the
sun because i i thought about it
i yeah i am conditioned now to
wince at me
you got scared because you don't wanna
talk i said it and it was
in the rhythm and i was like
he's gonna say that also i turned
my head because i suddenly the sun
started shining on my back i was
like wow do i get chilly today
it's very chilly so i'm actually kind
of okay with it but at the
same time i don't know i'm glad
that it's not blazing hot like it
was the day i know what's going
on california glad there
poor weather reporting climate change um so
um she got these masks and she
was like oh this one is good
jonah asks yeah yeah yeah my giant
heads
i got to be share for a
little bit okay um lucky i know
who fagor dorm back tom do you
want to see her live i want
to see cher live i'd be great
i think it would be what if
she doesn't exist and she's she's a
computer generated image feel pretty confident she's
not like
s one m zero any
simone ah but you know film um
simone and sheep i i'm not a
i'm not opposed to things like that
because i think it can be wishy
relaxing alec's facial facial masks got it
and it was like um sheet masks
where you play it on your face
it was like a no really more
gel you put on like a bologna
yellow and oscar meyer
thing was it was a package of
bellona blogging it had a first name
now have you seen those the guy
told us about it and they sold
out of them immediately yeah this guy
literally told this story okay lauren it's
for the listener homes i just wanna
make sure that i'm not trying to
erase age spots yes um but then
it was like and i've always it
was like
nah night or something we we were
we come back from always
i think it was after jackass and
we got home wow and i saw
jackass together or you talked about that
but we held hands during the scary
parts talk with josh testicles okay there
michael another penis um and i wanted
it sounded like very nice and she
said but then you gotta you gotta
wash your face first and i was
like i'm out that's
all i couldn't let because i was
i was all set another staff couch
and yeah it is really no i
had like les delay it onto my
face if you want but if i
have to get up and go to
the sink first no yeah yeah yeah
don't do it i get it na
da da da da noch die
eight sheet masks and wash my face
they feel so ah little i don't
like it i did one one time
and it was like okay it didn't
really i didn't get the i think
i built up the feeling in my
head of how like relaxing or whatever
it was going to be or how
good it was going to yeah and
it was just like this well-being home
feeling relaxed because
or slimy and i'd like to join
a sleek roofline face yeah while i
do that every day yeah i'm constantly
putting food on my wish is that
good for something or is it just
like it's too deep huff okay i
don't know that it's not just something
that is like fun to do and
there is a ball it's not just
for like romcom so you can take
a quirky bite out of it after
you
yeah a little chat what one comes
up when they're laying in a spot
and unlike the gobos i've never been
to but never even never oh my
god never seen this definitely happened a
million times
maybe it'll happen probably and it's stuck
in your head yeah but it's definitely
something that like you would do if
you're being funny did we we watched
marry me the romance launch this have
watched it the other night she asked
me to what i say oh janey
got me at the right time she
was like this is on tv right
now but if you have access
just do it wash your face first
i probably would i want to watch
it how was it i'm still watching
my life i love a class it
was good rom com it is it
is classic in many ways did you
hear as good from kula okay um
it definitely scratches that particular itch i'm
sure i would like it um it's
it's weird there's a lot of weird
stuff about it there's weird music in
it because she
plays a singer i was finding weird
she's famous in him yes oh she's
huge i don't really know what the
whole thing like more famous than jayla
yes that's a reference gallo in the
movies they're like oh she wishes she
was me
i find it strange in rom-coms when
they are ah like you know how
they can only greenlight movies when people
are a certain like star status yeah
and there are there are so few
of them left these days especially younger
people so they they greenlight these rom
coms with people who are in there
fifty s do they acknowledge like oh
well i've had three marriages already right
like why oh why is someone single
when they're fifty five years old day
they don't acknowledge age but they do
say they they they do allude they
referred to jails characters having been married
many times okay like she's a famous
person who's had all these
these romances that didn't work out okay
so same time it's had to be
desert yes that that is her story
actually so yeah it's just odd to
me like when they don't when they're
trying to pretend everyone is thirty yeah
you know what i mean and there's
sort of there's sort of this could
be anybody like somebody the character could
be any
the age honestly they don't do anything
specific to being at that stage of
life and i'm not saying that people
either to get married by thirty five
or whatever i'm just it's just like
you think it would come up in
their conversation even if like ok you're
fifty five why are you not married
why have you never been shown wilson
is i i believe his wife
he died and j lo has been
everyone's thrilled about in the movie grace
we are that hausfeld ah
we think someone pushed it paul don't
talk about our show eden i do
want to talk about it it was
so fun i haven't watched it yet
but you've watched it i watched bits
and pieces so i was just curious
how it looked in if they were
like switching between the cameras align it
looks really good um so we did
a show at dynasty typewriter for no
audience and was just live stream so
there's literally just like
little chuckles from the camera people were
you positive before by the way the
last would be ah yeah so we
really shows the big bang theory without
the laughs yeah yeah it was like
ten minutes of silence within yeah it
was tough to judge like what do
you think would get a big big
laugh and what would get a small
because we're improvising yeah right now so
sometimes we weren't on the same page
sometimes you like i thought that would
get you okay before people think that's
what we did we didn't do that
and i was like no one reacted
and when actually it was one of
the weirdest things because i think we've
been doing these shows on on zoom
or whatever for most of the pandemic
where we can see people responding in
the chat yes right yeah like you
know talking or whatever so we know
people are watching and they're there yeah
yeah
right there but that was the power
felt like nobody knew that that happened
yeah like it was the most it
took me back to like my early
days of improv where i'd perform for
literally five people at the playground theater
in chicago or something and be like
we that we would only cancel a
show if there were less than two
people so it was like the rules
were leading one
yeah or i think it was two
or less you know but you could
decide and sometimes you'd still do it
and like thinking it felt like that
because it was like it was so
pure i really felt like when i
put i got really depressed after whoa
when i got home i have like
a major comedown but i think i
meant that i was like really happy
during it oh okay i had a
great choice design of being happy as
well
you're super depressed no i haven't a
lot after the good shows yeah well
like get really sad after and just
feel like oh nothing matters oh that's
why you do this no it's like
nothing has been done is that or
something i don't know how to plan
for me i can't sleep when i
have shows like that yeah it's either
it's especially after like a big show
that i'll put together because there's so
much um ah like sort of submerged
anxiety about it and and like actually
having pulled it off and it's done
and now it's like i'm so excited
not just that i had a fun
time but that i don't have to
do it anymore yeah that i am
wired for
the whole light if i get wired
but then i'm just kind of spiraling
at the same time it's like no
but i don't it's sort of complaint
and you love it makes me sad
i know it's not even sad it's
ah i'm sad okay am i feeling
yeah i'm saying you never felt like
this on the bank big tour you
know ah
you're always gonna have a good team
care about that show knows righteously that
is not true i feel like i
truly have that sort of as after
wild horses i often we would all
kind of horses arms wild horses oh
and often have that oh um that
we would we'd be driving home and
then text each other like oh my
god i'm like ah
yeah it's also with that show we
share a lot of personal information and
then it's like you feel like you
like just shared over shared or something
and it feels crazy yeah i feel
like that every time we do one
of these episodes know got depressed for
five days
and and full workweek
anyway you can watch the show if
you want to it's own dynasty typewriters
website yeah video vault we the way
we did it was we we like
we use the stage we use the
the seats um we instantly wanted to
do it again and next time we're
going to have a camera that can
follow us anyways i'm so excited yeah
just gonna be really cool anywhere like
it's a drone like you can go
outside and go to your
houses yeah it's drawn so be really
far away and like because the amazon
warehouse
um yeah so like we can we
can go outside if we want and
and do see note concession stand or
go to the back room or something
yeah but it was really fun it
was it was a very it was
a unique experience a while because it
was a full show um and also
because there's no laughs we have to
just keep going how long did you
guys do three deck a little over
our i sort of felt like more
committed been to like well first i
haven't been on stage in two years
yeah but i felt very committed but
you know i think part of it
too is like we've been doing these
shows on zoom with filters like we
use snapchat filters yeah and then that's
silly there's a level of like kind
of just you are just goofing off
those shows
silly she's so fun but like this
was different where were like there's no
sign of whether it's going well there's
no reaction you can't get distracted for
a second yeah you have to just
keep going and i love that yeah
i it was really it was really
fun yeah if you wanna check it
out dynasty typewriter dot com paul f
tompkins dot com slash live you can
see link link huh your web
website that's my website there's there's a
link to the archive of our show
show with my website and you should
and also the the archive of variety
opium ivory wow i've never thought i
need to wash my face first you
don't need to but it enhances the
experience that's really why i put it
on right before i watch anything online
i washed my face
just make sure the sick cleanse yeah
i don't want to watch with a
dirty face there's this one video that
keeps popping up on my instagram that
i refuse to watch it takes too
long to get to the point and
then i keep missing it i'm like
no i wanna know what it is
but can't fast forward it what is
it it's a kid who's like going
to ask some girl to be his
valentine and he's like five and he's
lamps camp flowers wearing a suit
oh and he's at her door and
everyone keeps going like this the sauce
white and i just like can't bother
to click whose idea was it his
or that's what you got i wonder
it's the parents' yeah i think there's
a five-year-old twenty zero
walking around stiff as a board wants
to get married for insurance purposes
export business
um i ah i have this this
pet peeve now of people that put
first of all a lot of problems
disclaimer videos yeah lots of problems here
yeah this is also it's like instagram
videos tiktok let's break it down what
are the problem a lot of a
lot of pet
oh and baby videos don't need music
you don't yeah wow pats in the
baby's be the star if it ain't
guess what the music is not what
makes it good no and you know
what else is annoying that fucking robot
voice yeah type into me i was
going to ask my girlfriend to go
to the prom or whatever
yes i've i've just eat the corn
your own voiceover jack quarter on boys
just put the words on there well
yeah that's fine too but maybe it's
for um hearing impaired people for blind
people i'm giving you choosing what are
they getting out of the video oh
i guess i don't know i'm getting
enthusiastic assent like i know you guys
are talking about but i don't know
example so guys the world
my voice maybe you know tell me
your ot people ah people
his auto email responses out of touch
yeah yeah yeah i don't use out
of touch alone huh i don't get
anything for a week um but no
it's like this thing where you if
you put a caption on your video
you can have it lit read by
a robot because awesome this robot lady
oh wait she's a lady robot too
he thinks he's going to go to
church but his friends have a surprise
it's like so it's even worse than
that though it's like there's something about
the whale story when i did my
best there's something about the way that
it the voice sounds it's like prob
less nachos worse i know i'm doing
what i can paul you're doing horribly
ah do better you didn't you didn't
explain it anyone scott still doesn't know
what it's like
i'm lost when paul talks about it
i'm lost but yeah this dog hasn't
seen his owners since before the war
oh yeah just for the war
which war
the oldest dog in amelia
this dog is two hundred and eight
years old
you know those videos are like dogs
are crying on graves oh jesus you
know it's i've seen a couple it's
really it's really you're like well it's
like as soon as i know that's
what it is i will fucking flip
pass that yeah i know i don't
need that yeah when we went away
this weekend i forgot my keys or
something
and i was gone literally sixty seconds
and i went back in and ga
jumped on me like please don't ever
do that again yeah she's like i
think because you know all the signs
of like us with suitcases and yeah
guys like loving she's like what were
you you just packing up the car
when i see a i love videos
of of dogs being reunited with someone
or if the dog was ah found
after being lost or something and the
like a you know the dog sees
the kid and then they're reunited in
the dog is going crazy i love
the point where the dog has to
like go away for a little bit
and then go back like go run
around over here and then i'm gonna
come back and well georgia whenever whenever
she gets excited because like coop has
come
being home or something she like runs
around goes by the door and then
grabs a toy and and and choose
it really an er like grabs a
ball like okay yes good time it's
go time yeah that's the thing she
loves most okay here's my pet peeve
yep
people that put wait for it on
a video i don't want to wait
when it doesn't hurt onward when it
doesn't and i knew dawson's creek yeah
when the it doesn't need a wait
for it it's just like no this
is just a natural end of the
video the way that's not a wait
and wait for like should be reserved
for like a six minute video oh
no you think six is the cutoff
because i i
i've awakened to think like a minute
before the thing happening to see it
but then i go well why don't
you just edit the top of the
video no i'm saying like i don't
want to wait at any point i
don't care if it's very long i
don't i take a wait for it
is only for something where it's it's
you're watching the video games on
eventful yes yeah but you gotta you
gotta watch because there's a pay off
but people are using it for a
thing that just happens in a video
it's like that's not a way with
words it's like saying these actions are
leading to this that's the same as
writing a long fucking tweet and then
going that's it that's the tweet and
it's like yeah it is you wrote
a long tweet you hit that only
works if you're saying like viola davis
that's it that's the tweet like you
don't mean like it aims that no
people were doing that oh people will
do like a longer thing and then
say that's it that's the tweet and
i'm like yeah that's a long ass
was what we know that's the tweet
because it is the tweet stop it's
like the rent-free in your head thing
where people started using an incorrectly and
i got taken for a fool
ooh yeah i know i think i
mean i've talked about this acknowledge it
i think i think harris's humble brag
is all my cry all the time
right right yeah it's like people right
now say it in in tv shows
all the time yeah obviously thinking yes
oh yeah it's a hit it's like
it's like you know how like what
she
shows unfunny people like unfunny comedy writers
just use references to others things fat
people have said so they're like oh
humble brag humble brag much you know
and it's like no people are just
bragging yeah you're the falcon just screech
and die yeah what the fuck you
over your effects record
it can't be like ah look here's
my face on the cover of a
magazine hum humble brag it's like that
no you're just bragging yeah it's fine
just say bragg from now in fact
i think harris would be happy if
people never said it again yeah
i think i don't want to speak
for him i wouldn't know what if
he comes back from the grave just
to see if people are doing that
i would be happy with that i'd
be happy but wait how okay what
stage what what stage of reanimation would
a departed loved one have to be
in ready to be like i'm glad
this is happening on meeting so
age of decomposition of like are they
a zombie or they had to be
back to exactly like they wow that's
a lot to aria kidding
what would you what would you accept
i wouldn't want to see them if
this this isn't what what is so
weird about modern zombie fiction is that
people are killing zombies immediately and what
would really happen is at least half
the country would be like we can't
kill these zombies because they might let's
try and funny just try to find
a cure first because
cause like you know this is amazing
that especially nice you know what it
means so then that take it back
but then the other half of the
country would be like oh no our
responsibility to everyone else in the countries
too important and let's kill the zombies
ah so this is your home
huh snowflakes what okay what if you're
what if your friend or relative came
back they were exactly like they worked
if they had milky zombie eyes i
could accept that if they were exactly
how they were but i'd be kind
of scared that they were like not
really used and basically they weren't really
them what if they had like a
partially deque
imposed face which but then everything else
was fine the cheekbones both of them
now i'm saying like their faces slightly
rot like it was the forehead it
would be it doesn't smell or anything
it's just like they came back and
that halted the process it would have
to for you to like be cool
when
their whole life or like they can
only hang absolutely no they could do
they die again no
i don't care for anything that seems
to doe think it seems pretty very
good double jeopardy so you would look
at them and it would not look
good but they would start to create
plastic surgery to fix this no yeah
no that's that's that's the sammy oh
well they way they would come up
with this
they can't they will do it
invent hats yeah because so far we
didn't have him yet what does it
show they have like wear a ski
mask yeah that's creepy and then they
and their mind it's just their forehead
okay but if it was their cheekbones
they would invent a ski mask and
everyone would be cool that just like
everyone's cool with these face diapers everyone's
wearing ah
i'm not really like nah this is
your first hundred face diaper oh my
god what if that is someone's first
episode i don't understand that i'm bigger
boy the friends with whom
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back
and we're back hi hi guys i
have a story wow what happened to
me up in santa ynez i o
was injured oh wow what what's god
you kept this from us yes i
want to save it for saving for
the pod
did you get injured on purpose you
would have a story yeah okay i'm
like jackass
so what happened okay so we were
up there to do like just a
fun relaxing wine tasting trip through but
we also scheduled a horseback riding wine
tasting event site can i just ask
your new i've never done a wine
tasting yeah do you actually spit it
out or do you
you know in fact i thought that
was i mean you can like yeah
the sideways part of it if you're
like real snooty about it like but
it really is just an excuse to
go in and try six different types
of wines i guess that's what i
figured you get yeah like i kind
of went going like fuss is is
are half the people going to be
spitting know every single person there is
just like downing wine
we did it one time where we
went from you know you go from
vineyard you get a little bus you
go from vineyard to vineyard vineyard and
try all these wines and then it's
like it stopped being fun after a
while it's like i don't yeah do
this we can't taste wine anymore we
found that three was too many for
coola three shops three three different wine
tastes yes because you
have i think you have about so
you have six different wines and each
one usually and so it's probably two
mass and a half yeah so three
was like four and a half classes
of wine and shoot the afternoon it's
just yeah and she and so that
night she was just like i don't
feel so good so we're like okay
to to is two's the limit yeah
spitting it out outfields
like most decadent yeah rose thing in
the world yes and like who cares
about the flavor that launched like you're
trying to get drunk yeah and you're
just sitting there pretending you're like agreeing
with whatever you're saying fucking ah yes
this is a full-bodied this was after
tae after know i mean they're blah
the the full-bodied or the oh this
would pair with this like all that
is kinda cool but like the the
the hints at like when they list
six different yeah as i was doing
the thing where i was like i'm
getting notes of wine
i think you'll detect a flick of
juniper wow so we went to the
we we we the first one and
of of the day was this horseback
riding wine tasting where you you ride
horses won first one you ride horses
and then you do a wine tasting
afterwards that sounds really fun it was
fun and
we we rode horses six years or
so ago in costa rica and it
was really fun and and um so
cool up scheduled it and i was
like ok that'll be fun so we
get to the place and the instructors
are not instructors but the guides casually
throw out like and and
it's us in another couple
we're gonna race they just casually throughout
oh you don't have to does anyone
like want a helmet
and oh that definitely makes me want
one it well no really it actually
like sort of felt like peer pressure
because everyone turned it down including kula
because you wanted to like wear her
hat in pictures so that in the
picture yeah she wasn't wearing a hat
yeah no because it's too windy so
she's like why did i turn down
the helmet when the
i'm sorry anyway so so i amuse
like yeah everyone kind of looks at
me like palsy
yeah but i was like if you
fell off and you didn't have it
on it's just like what who cares
yeah who cares not on the horse
every day of my life yeah most
people who are on horses wear helmets
in their competitions and things yeah that's
true so i you're certainly doing that
well and they're offering it which just
makes it seem like there's a reason
they're offering as he has like they
have to for safety
this is the way they made it
feel like hey we're we don't give
a shit not required but they have
to bring it up yeah you have
to offer it so i was like
yes i do please give me yeah
and and i put it on and
my fasano never closed
so so they they're then they're like
pairing people up with horses and they're
like you know to cool up oh
you have a really really you have
a really nice horse um like very
gentle very you know whatever and everyone
gets like nice oh real sweetheart you
know all this kinda old paint and
he's like old helmet here
you get to ride the scary one
we call him tornado it was nacho
so they go okay you have nacho
um okay just be careful of nacho
because he likes to nip at the
other horses oh wow and he likes
to be like sort of the alpha
and he likes to lead and so
he's a natural friendly source think i
think that they should ride nacho yeah
well
well later i found out that the
one that our guide was was wearing
had like bucked three writers out of
her preview well nevermind then so did
you say guy was wearing the horse
he did i did i oh i
thought maybe that was a fancy word
for variety yeah yeah i don't know
why i said i wouldn't show my
ignorance i don't even know the second
session um so
so anyway so so i get nacho
and it's like i get up on
nacho and he seems fine and we're
we start the the ride everything's cool
and we're going along and yes he
is like trying to get at other
horses and i'm like pulling him back
but then he he does want to
be out in front and our our
guide is like oh
okay yeah why don't you just leave
i don't like that i actually like
this nacho very much but i don't
mind nacho but i don't think he
did like now i'm leaving like no
i wanna be part of the pack
on my horse i haven't written horses
a lot of make me nervous well
it's only three of us and the
guide is kind of like i usually
go off just zoo cool up in
the guy because the other the other
couple went a different way oh okay
i think he was proposing
to her because like you had a
driver and the driver was like they
had just met or something like that
and and the drivers like so you're
going to be when when his girlfriend
was in the restroom he's like so
you're gonna be and he's like ah
oh i just had sex on the
horse yes you're gonna be having sex
horse racing aha yes ah well it
was a breakup you're gonna be breaking
up with and he doesn't when you
come back it's just you and ah
but then we saw no evidence of
like her showing off her ring or
whatever so it may have been just
like the whole day was planned like
in later
that night he was gonna do huh
sure others time so tell the driver
he could have blown it seriously i
never trust a driver with a secret
like that yeah so rivers love to
talk so anyway it was just the
three of us in our guide was
kinda like well i'm i'm usually not
on the trail anyway i go off
to the side and you see you
guys can have an extract i've never
been here before
so she's like you you go ahead
and lead so we're going along and
i'm doing the whole thing of like
when you go up a hill you
lean forward when you go down the
hill you lean back and you know
all the all the rain you know
techniques and all that kind of stuff
and it's been six years since i
rode a horse but i was like
damn i'm like pick this back up
really good
i'm doing really good i started being
like i could do this like an
a film or something if if i
were offered so you're also sure if
i was like i was like imagining
matt damon and like true what is
true it true grit yeah true story
um true grid i was kinda like
yeah i'm like like like like i
could you know this is very natural
to me i'm like a man who
spanks a teenager so what happened intergrated
yeah it's very very high
thank you
um so i'm like in my head
i'm kind of going yeah i mean
like i could put this as a
special skill on a resume
updating your casting website leaning forward and
backward no words but i'm not controlling
know i was contrary i was like
you know and i was leading him
away joe was doing what not other
shit but joe no controls natural so
as i'm thinking this suddenly nacho goes
crazy cool and
like i don't know from my perspective
it seemed like nachos stumbled and freaked
out um the the guide's perspective was
like it looked like he got spooked
or something not just perspective nachi was
like ah
that explains a lot um but but
nacho basically like bucks and and tries
to throw me jesus and hey this
is terrified i hate this and i
love it well i love that happened
to him it's scary but yeah and
i don't know how but i hold
on like that he stops when we
missed yeah it's like he's not listening
but he's giving room for us to
do it he's pretend he's like pretending
like it's too long for a dramatic
pause
sell selling them before um but i
don't know how but i hold on
the the saddle gets like swung to
the sigh oh jesus i hold on
and saw and it stops and not
just stops and our guide is like
whoa you are wow are you all
right um i'm like yeah
i'm i'm shaken but i'm alright and
she's like wow you really held on
like a professional you're like matt damon
and true
ah um so anyway we finished the
ride and then we're walking to the
picnic table to get wine and i
stepped in a hole and twisted my
ankle huh huh oh my god
oh my god did you fall down
oh yes i felt it you felt
that go boo
you say you felt like a professional
she she wasn't watching i was like
are you okay she thought i was
having a heart attack or so because
i just i yeah sank to the
ground suddenly you seem like matt damon
and the way to fill a hole
since i live here and holes
wrinkle felt fine after three days you
have a lot of said the whole
time you had a bad ankle for
the last three days yeah the trip
oh yeah i mean it wasn't like
horrible but it's just like swell up
a little wasn't as bad as when
i got that mirza infection in france
well my guy i've told you you
have you never hear mercy i think
of you it was like
like the day or two days before
we left and i got that infection
and then by i was like limping
by the time we were leaving and
then i got home and had to
have it dug out woo yeah i
don't want to talk about that i
don't want to hear about i'm done
talking and they haven't dug out yeah
thank you like with what they
it was soooo it's like ah yeah
yeah like grapefruit spoon
that's making me sick
i still have like a little differently
has this podcast ever made anyone throw
up feel god i hope so probably
smaller are chewing sale only to the
imams but we do know their taste
tests we should but what should it
be yeah do something good fortunately bring
in some new eminem flavors we haven't
had but you know what they're also
gross
yeah exactly yeah you gotta ask the
mains yeah forget it anyways that was
the cats oh yeah that'd be kind
of fun there's a lot of different
cats there are um world market actually
has many different do they have the
macho macho yeah they have them i
don't know i figured out i don't
like ma i don't like much
huh i don't know that i've ever
i don't mind much ice cream now
it tastes a little like lipstick but
i think it's okay i don't like
my chop at all know maybe i'm
simply wearing green tea ice cream and
you might be thinking green tea i
love lipstick but to eat i don't
like montana on green tea i like
kind of taste a lot like trendy
things right man i had a much
ouch a coffee in new york and
it was so gross and we waited
so long for it and i just
like numbs it right now what does
matcha tastes like it was wine
um wish to get out yes like
i don't know i just don't like
it okay
alright maitland and it's one of those
things where i didn't have a good
macho thing why lie this is huge
my my brother was visiting recently we
went to this cool well he took
me to an art gallery that he
wanted to go to because he likes
to go see art when he's in
town oozes my brother and yeah so
we went to
manga space which is a cool art
gallery
um in west adams neighborhood and you
have no art where he lives now
he goes to see where he lives
as well whoa but he always knows
what show is going on in la
that i should go to or that
he wants to go to like so
so we went to see this art
and then across the street there was
this little cool little cafe up and
we went in there and then
he got these well i told him
to buy these donut holes that i
wanted and then he's like their stuff
inside when he brought him on him
to buy so you're buying valentine's presence
for yourself but give them to bike
yeah telling your brother to buy donut
holes from so hibs oh yeah yeah
but i was like get those and
he brought about things like their stuff
inside was fuck because
i hate when there's stuff inside of
pains i don't know really i really
don't like when they're to glue and
he's like a crim doughnut what about
what you mean any donuts not not
definitely not jelly why i don't like
fruit in pastry what about a gumdrop
tools what tools come what's in schools
n
always you want everything to be on
the top no i don't like when
there's i like chocolate and dessert totaling
what about gooey chocolate that's good ah
pan to chuckle yeah but anyways there
was like macia like cream or something
inside these and he was like it's
good and then i still ate one
and i actually really liked it so
i was pretty
surprised so it kind of went against
everything i ever thought wow i really
want to eat it because he said
it was good and i also don't
want to be a baby i feel
like i've tried to stop doing that
in my life yeah oh usually anything
yeah
um but i can have my opinion
on it but i'll use it i'm
usually but i'm usually like i'll try
anything that's got me totally to get
to that point yeah yes it took
me way too long i think but
i i definitely do that now but
i really liked it so maybe i
do like matcha fuck know they might
just didn't like that much coffee yeah
i haven't had it i think you
can
end up with a bad combination where
like macho shouldn't be in the thing
that your symmetric twitches are okay aren't
they ah but catchy cute cats i
mean yeah i've never had that but
i wouldn't want to have it because
i think i don't like it so
maybe i would maybe we should have
mit that's what we should try we
should do taste we should do the
macho kit kats just that no yes
many differently to try like five like
yeah
they have like orange we should start
start with the macho because i'm worried
that we're gonna love the other one
so much says oh hey you know
we have to do it the way
i want i know it was really
gross i had a pumpkin kit cat
that was someone i had for halloween
and it was disgust know and it
was like what i did not taste
like pumpkin because he's like ge
just like pumpkin because pumpkin and chocolate
tea there was no chocolate but that's
the thing it's no chocolate pumpkin doesn't
work in everything it was just pumpkin
flow so there's neighbor on the way
for i'm like that's not why i'm
here exactly yeah you're not going okay
it should be chocolate bottom or pumpkin
top way for middle
but i'm the ad and the chocolate
on the bottom pumpkin on top that's
my kid it's my classify um i
think it's cute that your brother knows
that you don't like ah things in
pastries yeah we also discovered that we
both don't eat the cross of sandwiches
we make at home
but you don't cut the crust off
no and he was talking about how
his son like wants the crust companies
like just eat into the sandwiches oh
yeah we both i made sandwiches and
then we both left it like that
and then that was pretty funny that
is funny um but yeah i'm alright
i the the the way i got
over my pick
keep eating because i ate terribly for
years was um it was a friend's
birthday in new york and we went
to this restaurant called he had he
had ah he lived in new york
and so you had like a night
for the people that came in from
out of town it was bloomberg mike
bloomberg
and we we went to this restaurant
called w d forty which sounds disgusting
what was like oily it was not
oily that's dvd fifty nine so many
before oh no dvd fifty oh okay
no of course they couldn't name it
after the oil oh i was why
it may now start
think that maybe w d forty isn't
a brand name but it is a
brand it is brandon okay um not
a formula does my four o nine
forty and it was um a at
the time molecular gastronomy was it was
a new yeah and so i hit
a restaurant in that three months once
and then i've never seen it right
yeah
no one no one does it yeah
yeah it's true um and so everywhere
everything was like dry ice and titles
i know it was not joy but
it was constructed and blah blah blah
and so is all these different things
including fish which i never ate and
balsamo um and i was like well
i just got to go along with
everybody yeah because i mean there's no
other option yeah
be like can i have the chicken
fingers yeah yeah and it was fucking
it was crazy but said it was
great it was like i didn't know
that's what happens we're going to be
and i enjoy i really enjoyed it
along my god one time i went
to yeah great yeah one time i
went to vegas to do a show
with ben schwartz and gallows airy it
was a corporate show for v
visa and who was an improv show
it was well very just the three
of you yes wow remember that show
you and i did were shown my
other weird alan yeah yeah i know
i was thinking the other day actually
huh everyone's a show everyone hated us
everyone hated us so much i'll very
nicely he was doing a big ah
whatever the video game
convention is or something i don't even
i don't even performing some mcos performing
ah and it was like three g
what does it for you three or
something oh that is what it is
yeah and um you know it's cool
that he was because usually it's like
metallica or someone like that yeah he
was booked but the end it was
live streamed in the the issue is
like in his previous
tours when he was changing costumes he
would play a lot of videos but
they're all like copyrighted video so he
was like hey do you want to
do you wanna do um the in-between
stuff it'll cut to you and you
can like host the broadcast ice and
we were in character and people were
well searcy was it was it was
gonna be me and paul scheer were
going to do it to oh our
placed him and um paul had to
drop paul was like paul had a
big idea of us playing julian's the
the assad brothers i guess
and i didn't i didn't not know
at the time i did not know
about the link between like video game
people and julian assange type people as
so i didn't i was just like
oh that's funny because wikileaks is in
the news sure okay so we got
wigs and and wiki that and wikileaks
t-shirts right
and be the the assange brothers because
it was video games or whatever so
paul dropped had to drop out like
the day before or something like that
and so he's like but i still
i bought the wigs and the t-shirt
so you can still have that i
was like okay trying to wrap my
mind around like i'm gonna be this
this that's not even my idea but
i was like ok i'll stick to
it
and then so i got one i
don't know why yeah looking back it
doesn't make sense it doesn't make any
sense but he was like happening game
was time was of the essence is
all set up a name and a
t-shirt i'm good to go but i
was like wendy poops or something yeah
you were winning piece because i was
like lawrence you want to do this
i was like this is the idea
where the assange twins
or something like i don't want to
do that because it was like i
don't know anything about that yeah yeah
yeah so so i was which is
what i should have done too but
i also did beep bebo
with the peeps brotherton said yeah so
anyway so so it gets set up
and i'm i'm like making cracks about
ah ah what was the other thing
i was doing i was doing like
stuff that i thought sandra se but
it was like hashtagging ah oh gamergate
that's what it was and because because
in my
my mind was like look gamergate is
stupid and anyone who's like obviously these
people who are watching this show and
ethics in gaming germany yeah but i
was like anyone watching the show agrees
with me right yeah so ah i
found out that video game people are
terrible and they were really mean
and they they they just were like
sending us the worst like kill yourself
messages and alison twitter al finished his
show and i felt so bad for
him because we were tracking in real-time
because we were doing like three minutes
here five minutes there and we would
have like euro five their five ten
minutes off and
and we were tracking real-time and i
was like lauren you may not want
to look at your twitter because we're
getting like really mean stuff like let
me guess they put your twitter handles
up on the screen yeah great yeah
yeah why would they do that and
so then al gets off he's like
how to go who you know so
like yeah had a great show and
i was like yours say i will
say i had never seen
number four five and he was fantastic
sure i was i love that part
and i just had to say like
al you're you're gonna you're gonna see
the reaction to it and not be
with it's um i think we're we
were funny to like us but ah
you're you're you're gonna get some weird
reactions from this and i apologize
fats and how well
it was a time that was yeah
it was it was like i that
was where i started like figuring out
that your video game culture could have
no relation to each other video game
coaches just like the card is so
straight but that video game people have
a very specific mindset that is not
that does not necessarily
align with my oh yeah exactly exactly
oh my god anyway so you went
to vegas went to vegas we did
this show for the people of visa
and people in the town of views
it's really fun and um and then
afterwards i think somebody from the company
took us out to dinner oh no
um so we went to like this
fancy
around their discovery i'm sure they did
not sort of scandal but i'm trying
to think of what the restaurants call
because i knew what it was but
i don't remember now it was years
ago anyways but it was one of
those places where everything was kind of
weird like all of the stuff on
the menu was like cutting it was
like it was like ducking cotton candy
or you like some fucking weird
hey but we ate by ate everything
we all did and were all like
yes it was like fancy and crazy
and everything was weird and i think
i can say this that and that
night we all had the worst diarrhea
ah
i think i can reveal that night
we adore diary over i i'm allowed
to reveal this now i was the
so i was up all night and
it was the worst then we got
to the airport where like oh fuck
were you think it was one it
must have been one ingredient or something
maybe or it was just how how
retail rich everything was because we have
so many things that were ah
odd and like really just yeah i
think i don't know that kind of
so you're saying because like i've never
seen you before my talk was like
duck and cat and cotton candy bitch
i'm gonna shit this ah um but
yeah it was pretty funny later anyway
we should go we should we should
tragedy plus time we should go to
like a weird dinner
are together and rewarding yeah weird dinner
yeah like fidelio like eyes wide shut
dinner yes we'd off of a human
body yes and then we fuck everyone
in front should be watched the tinder
swindler we we want weirdly enough ah
heard about it have not we watch
it in sandy
i enjoyed it um one thing that
came up though a bunch of times
is that these women had were given
caviar for the first time whatever that
was so amazing i'm like who is
excited to eat caviar isn't gross we
had ah okay here's what i'll say
we we bought a jar for christmas
i mean some people love it i
i mean i know that and and
we had we had it
ah you know with some other stuff
and it wasn't that good on christmas
day when it wasn't with certain things
but then the next day we have
the leftover caviar with um
ah the typical russian way on what
do they call them leanings and bellinis
and ah with with like
although regular okuda ma and it was
delicious oh for that so like i
think i like the traditional way yeah
you know who's a fan i believe
is josh flagg my favorite real estate
agent oh no we're hosting oh this
he loves caviar i think he's a
fan of caviar from what i remember
i wanna hang out with him right
now yeah what is it about him
that makes you when i um i'd
if you just like walked up the
driveway i think that would make a
lot of sense i'd just saw on
the show
i'm saying like rambo a machine gun
rambo miranda yeah remember miranda god randoms
us oh my god no i just
i just think he's he's fun he's
fun and they have the spin off
josh and jaw show me yes rally
recap yeah it wasn't as was joshua
josh johnson well because those two josh's
are ulta
lately my favorites to watch yes but
it was like it was more of
a personality show than real estate yeah
that's true but i don't mind that
but my favorite josh is probably joshua
from the bible well yes thank you
what did he do he fit the
battle of jericho always bringing it back
down to where we need to be
this isn't christian podcast we we need
to make this is so
someone's first we should have been saying
that at the top the whole time
yeah and i'm surprised we haven't mentioned
before now but yeah this is a
christian podcast yeah and we believe in
the bible we believe in that it
exists the bible it's real none of
it's teeth it's real no we don't
believe
it's a christian podcast where we don't
think the bible is we just believe
that we just knew that there is
such a thing as the ah yes
amazing
not getting involved in this age like
wow he's like he's like nah alright
we need to take a break we'll
be right back
e look at versace juan he's looking
up
nah helicopter back and it's time or
back or a three church i love
it everyone does as you know the
feature is the segment where we play
a game and we call it the
three cheshire that's right we don't call
it a game know it can we
do as we call it a three
three yeah
it comes from the idea that the
we will have features and two of
us took that to mean games yeah
this guy who are the two lauren
and myself it is what i think
it was i think you thought it
would be different segments yeah that's what
i was i was like let's do
a feature on the show for the
third thing of like we'll bring in
something to use and of course that
is a game
yeah
we call it feature to make it
branded it worked used to call anything
in your life something and brand it
yeah i mean like your toe you
could call it a flavour of his
good run on puig a podcast i
enjoy with jacqueline novak and kate berlant
um
jacqueline calls jacqueline has this activity she
calls big red and it makes me
laugh so much it's netflix and seamless
because both of them are red so
shameless it's like an order food ordering
oh so but she says i'm gonna
do big red tonight
it's funny i love that um ok
this game is called cursory rhyme router
this three chair is called cursory rhyme
and it's not what you're thinking actually
i don't know what it is um
i don't know what you're saying i
wouldn't presume to tell people when you
hear the tell me you hear the
word curse and you don't think immediately
oh i know what this is just
a fart
so bad yeah you are such a
curse word so this was submitted by
full pet i think it's how you
say the name but i probably said
it wrong and here's how it got
spell it p h u l space
p a t t could be petty
we don't know if it'd be but
politics but there's no accent or accent
agu
okay so one person picks a word
the person to their right recites the
first line of a poem which must
end with this word the next person
we're staying home or now because i
don't think the next person recites the
second line of the poem ending in
a word rhyming with the first word
o the first person now adds the
third line ending with another rhyming
words continues and different everyone is out
of writing oh i see notes so
we're gonna pick a word and then
we're gonna make a poem every single
line is gonna right yeah okay god
why is it called cursory i wonder
because you have to
cursory rhyme you have to rhyme you
must it's cursory i don't think that's
what cursory means can we google it
let's google ads i thought cursory meant
like casual like a cursory yeah like
like i have a i have a
facile knowledge of this oh it's actually
the opposite
hasty and therefore not thorough or detailed
nice great but also says perfunctory yeah
but perfunctory to me feels like you
have to propose no look wow i
know what you mean i know she
was a minimum effort of or reflection
like you have like you have to
do it but you're gonna do with
a lead me about perfunctory things like
i'm making it the wrong way
okay yeah great and then someone said
is cursory look at my dogs i
behold they're running okay they love to
be away from this house again me
daddy okay so really i would say
cursory ram probably isn't the best name
for this game well dang it might
be if we get hasty with it
we may pronounce your name
and it sucks well i think maybe
the best maybe it's the best thing
because it rhymes and that's what we're
doing okay let's find out nursery the
word we're gonna start with cursory you
can see is um juice juice oh
nice exactly bad it's the right so
okay okay so i'll sorry are you
start no i said okay you've provided
the word i'll take over from here
when i thirst at morning time no
i've already i'm like doing a full
poem instead of doing a line yeah
what does sorry to align to do
online yeah
at morning time i crave my juice
ah
the look on your face
at morning time i crave my juice
upon the carton i turned it loose
what i don't mind if it is
puce
as law so long as it makes
my bowels loose i said loose oh
sorry ah the abuse tim this is
hard okay i got a few more
and by the way i am a
moose a surprise twist wow um
i'll take a rope and fashion a
noose
and kill myself to see my god
zeus
what's this upon my thigh a bruce
that's good thanks
oh it could be two syllables good
yeah i'm thinking of one me too
um
this bruise i see it is chartreuse
i'll wrap it up in my papoose
and stuff at all in this train's
caboose
but why is
why is a v again
um
and then write it down which i
will peruse and send it off to
terry crews
ah
i do admire his fancy shoes
men l's sip a little bit of
booze huh
i only detective but i've got no
clues
but brian safety is my muse
softie yeah who's that i'm the softy
brothers yeah or you haven't seen this
video know of what's her name julia
fox ah oh my the the what's
her name from kanye yes the water
from k broke up keep going the
what's her name from kanye west
cam you knew she says they're out
she's just this clip of her talking
about being amused for i guess for
kanye it's like like when i was
brian sawfish booze for uncle john's ah
okay let's do a new poem ah
paul picks the words got starts with
that word yep
the word is
brown
upon my shorts a touch of brow
of course
regretted it
i didn't notice till i looked around
in this state can i go to
town
in this oh let's see yeah
like am i allowed just one of
the states where you're allowed to go
to town
because where i grew up you can
not sure which way either up or
down
but if i smell it i'll have
a frown
and to others be a cloud
i was gonna do clowns so that's
why i'm so so sorry
um
yeah ah um and then ah to
cover it up i'll wear a gown
that's what i was young yeah yeah
oh i'll give you the same amount
of time now and
a hat made of feathers down
in reviews down upon my hands type
just like a crow
other type of dough
okay whenever anything about ah yes those
phones no it's neither that's just a
different minas definition true shit um there's
a word for that right yeah i'm
sure there is different definition command
ok bird and how it's flowering oh
that's how i pronounced sure
it's a regional dialect and look at
my grass and how it's moun
because this guy a red blouse
yeah alright
um face
good
i placed this mask upon my face
but wait oh yeah
my face is wear a mask is
placed oh see your doctor seuss i
hope that
he's dead
any cancelled so many so many cartoons
that were offensive um
i'm sorry you said ah good face
you sit up on i say please
nice mask upon my face i hope
my zits it will erase
and once they do i'll run my
race
i hope i don't get sprayed with
mace and then sent off to outer
space
and the detective will crack the case
and the theme will be leather and
lace
nope did that one
this is very surprising we shall continue
and continue apace and present our goods
with the older grace whilst lying on
this lounge of chaise
i am so embarrassed i feel a
base
i want disappear without a trace
the people poop poop poop poop poop
i can't i can't remember what words
we've i know the longest we've gone
i know it's going so well we're
we're fucking doing it guys because to
me being too great right now
thank you teenager oh
this rocks
i think i'll
walk to their ways okay that's over
alright so ah good stuff guys this
episode we did we did um thank
you for sending in the three cheer
and if you'd like to send us
a three cheer write to us at
three mit three males remain calm i
wish me
you should get three males should be
free email at gmail dot com yes
but it's not it's freedom usa gmail
dot com let's try to get three
e-mail instantly yes um before somebody else
does um and josh thanks for you
it should definitely be three males three
mail gmail ah we are oh it's
so good we are three of them
usa ah
at ah twitter and instagram um what
do we have a new intern yet
no but i did fire satan and
he posted a video hired he posted
a video yeah she took it really
well i it's that's that's a that's
not real what that's like one of
his devilish sort of oh it's a
trick yeah it's saying everyone get pasted
hammer i forgot he's
the principle is nasties right yeah i
thought it was really really really gross
to do that but i just want
to forget that he's evil i know
i know let it be as about
yep yep great um if you want
to hear ad-free versions of this show
listen to the regular episodes or subscribe
to stitcher premium or cbp work
ll dot com that's right and listen
we love you and will love you
be back next week we may buy
bay birth
uh