fido
freedom
nina
oh boring i need to hear you
shout but dude dude dude oh there
we going looking at the phone all
of your spices ah lawrence too deadly
sins smoking pot oh ford smoking pot
smoking like though
mask how well do you think that
movie holds up if you are to
watch it right why today i watched
it like a year or two ago
i did you really find an airplane
airplane but
um and it was or maybe it
wasn't an airplane i watched something like
that and you watch the airplane on
a mask oh yeah um but i
thought it was pretty fun yeah i'm
trying to i don't even remember what
i thought about an at the time
i saw it in theaters i remember
it not being funny that's what that's
what i was like because i really
liked ace ventura and thought he
was really funny and then the mask
was like oh this is just kind
of lame and then i love dumb
and dumber even more i remember thinking
ace ventura was really funny and then
i'm i mean i went with a
friend of mine we fuckin die like
that movie then i watched it recently
showed us like but i showed it
to another friend like a year or
so later and this guy was like
you thought this was funny through the
hole
whole thing why remember i i was
dating this nice woman who's no longer
with us um and was she the
librarian at the school this nice woman
and she i wrote this script that
she she was like what what do
you find funny and i was like
oh like dumb and dumber it was
really funny this is around that time
and she was like ah yeah and
then she read my scripts it was
like ah and then she she she
worked at a she was sick she
were to to feel any
well i did have a tongue depressor
ah and she's like that's no tongue
depressor um but depressing
and it is small but i'm with
her this small and hard hillary
it was really really nice woman
so anyway associate she worked at a
film company and she put my scripts
even though she hated it she put
it into to read pile but a
nice lady she was very nice and
it got we got the only recommend
edible out of all-new out of all
the scripts and she was like man
i i thought this sucked but people
like it i guess wow and she
died and i was shocked down and
she died of laughter after she finished
the final page the only documented case
of a person dying from laughter usually
it's the best medicine but they don't
tell you
oh wow the humor in uniform yep
welcome to three threesome welcome to it
i'm paul i'm paul scott i'm hall
lauren yep yep hey yeah we do
it yeah yes yeah and you're listening
to the podcast where look if i
got to explain it to you you're
already behind oh man we gotta catch
we can't hold your hand and spoon
feed you our podcast
okay figure out what it's about and
how it works my listening my dear
yeah so check see if you can
discern the theme of our show every
episode as a theme that we decide
on previous to it like weeks before
weeks before and we talk about things
that relate to the theme but no
one is able to guess the theme
after the episode so you know it's
weird we've done it
over one hundred episodes now no one
has yet guessed a single theme no
yeah we've got and let's look at
some of the guesses from last week
oh look at this um charles from
lake charles oh interesting says humanity is
the theme it's like i mean it's
a little grandiose ones yeah theory from
lake superior we because the theme is
ch
chocolate chip cookies huh i mean they
came up you know that was no
one of my guests on the game
well one time you said that gum
inside of them oh right um this
one's from huron from lake huron yeah
well they say that we should make
the show more about something deeper it's
not even a guess it's just so
things cheaper something more intense something that
would really change the way the world
turns the topic should be colon
to wear a mask or not okay
we don't take we don't take your
questions by the way although here's one
from we'd be talking from lake ca
who says i suggest you guys all
go fuck yourself wow wait anyway rocca
getting this placid from lake placid says
i'm a big giant alligator but why
don't you make the theme me well
well don't do that fuck off although
we kind of did five episodes o'clock
yeah but nobody nobody allowed us did
one yesterday okay well this one's from
the erie from like gary yeah it's
a little spooky there's a drawing of
a ghost and it says the theme
of the show is people who were
born once once so non-christians worn once
i got my hands leaves out i
guess anyone is reincarnated
yeah i like the theme guys should
we do it are there people who
aren't reincarnated like do you only get
reincarnated if you believe in reincarnation yeah
you know what i mean like you
only go to heaven if you believe
in hell yeah i don't think that
makes sense i think if something really
is real it should just happen no
matter what you believe yeah i think
like heaven if heaven is real and
you don't believe in it i think
you should still go to heaven and
like a look around i think it's
okay if you get made fun of
a little bit yeah go look at
this guy likely living well believing yeah
how's do you believe in us now
and that can last for one full
earth year yeah which will be like
nothing in heaven it's oh yeah
a minute because honestly it's eternity that
you're there yeah yeah so it's like
you can you can take that for
a year you have to be if
you're not good natured about that if
you go to block you you gotta
have a thick skin ah so late
yeah well guys next week what oh
no we just started i wanna say
i wanna hang out in heaven with
you guys wow that would be so
cool there'd be so many people there
do you think do you think that
you would even say hi to me
i'd be a little busy i probably
wouldn't talk to you who would you
most want to see and why don't
we talk about dying so fucking much
because there any unanswered question it's on
my mind oh we just talk about
something silly like what do you do
ya wow right bill maher well who
would you who would you but there
there's gotta be people from history that
you'd be like this is the old
like if you could have dinner with
anyone can i can i say but
i kind of do want to talk
about wiener dogs no i think we
should but you know i don't think
that
a lot times those dinners i think
they'd be more awkward than people really
realised no i mean like everybody's would
we get any of your jokes or
your reference yeah it sounds horrible you'd
be like oh the tinder swindler right
a beanie boo fuckin have dinner with
abraham lincoln i want to have dinner
with like people i like from history
from my life from your personal history
sarah wiener dog so i want people
with my brother i sort of want
one guys i had one you did
really as a child you do so
a puppy we've never talked about it
no way out other it was at
some point the alice oh that sounds
familiar go ah stylus is what you're
thinking of yeah and did you get
it
that harass gallus i was not that
into alice i think because ah i
think back then this is the seventies
people didn't know what to do with
dogs really so it was like ah
so alice was like when did we
start to ever pull the car and
i didn't work i know alice was
in the back yard all day because
it's like well we don't want to
keep
letting out in and out to shit
so it's like just put her in
the back yard overs to do that
and they don't have a yard it's
just concrete yeah i don't know anyways
so sad i almost got run over
by yards it's okay i almost got
run over by a car on christmas
day the hell it's a shabby street
rice only bro ker lay egg she
still lit a dog that
that small and only broke her leg
was the car tiny well it was
christmas so it was it was it
might have been sway her legs the
size of being quite a bit of
slay
i think we need any remote control
car dolly wells if you know dolly
wells yeah she has the cutest little
wiener dog named morris and he's so
sweet i've got long hair now and
rome i want i kind of want
one a little i think they're very
cute but i also i don't want
one that's gonna go okay
well you're out looking yeah alright i'm
nicole parker my neighborhood listen co-host she
has a wiener dog named ah roxy
and roxy is blind just two marbles
in her head oh no um yes
so she's she's a she's a double
sammy davis junior
what a shit
he was blunt here i want to
figure that out yeah but i figured
it out you figured it out with
the pencil and a pad you figured
it out didn't take a pencil and
a pad i'm going to figure it
out
she shows your pad it's a drawing
of saying yes yeah i closed i
think i do enjoy seeing pictures of
that dog yeah and now i because
i will instagram of course is now
suggesting all sorts of doctrines to me
because i've shared like one photo that
i saw with nicole
lol right and then it's like alright
i know this guy loves wiener dogs
so now i've seen the same picture
of a couple of toxins with a
bunch of like baby chicks yeah it's
i've seen this picture one million times
why no i actually believe that when
there should be a feature that if
you have seen a meme or a
picture
yes already you should be like never
show me this again like i've i
don't want to see the same fuck
sometimes there should be a sambar reading
a meme yes and then i you
know oh my god ooh me and
then i'm i read i need to
be on my phone us the thing
that's awesome but i have a timer
on my instagram i can only use
it for a certain amount of time
yeah that's right and i remember my
passes
but right now don't know the password
i give you some picture and you're
like i don't have my time what
is it yeah just screencap it's um
it's better that way for me but
how does that happen but i want
to ask is how does the blind
dog get around does he memorize the
room or is she sexist and she
can smell
well let's write to hire the new
women yeah now wow
this first woman has broke the glass
ceiling dogs always known as man and
cats were women that's right yeah and
more recently a really long time now
recently we have our first female dog
but men are still remarks the first
male cat women are from venus well
you know are you from right hell
your anus is
that the title of your poverty law
by comic book is called men are
from mars women are from venus and
soccer is from yreka was you know
where you're from right and you have
to flip over and on the back
it says you're in your ass haha
the only coverage to be continued
do you know what to think because
we know people that have written books
now which is weird but um if
you ain't hire jamie dyer ire jane
eyre
highway of two cities st jane ayers
if you write a bow it's huh
if you are like a humorous book
now like whether it's a humorous memoir
or humorous guide to or whatever the
book has to have an impossibly long
title yeah to explain what you read
i do think the long titles are
too much sometimes it's stupid but they
make you do it yeah
yeah they make you do it it's
so weird here's why you should read
this nobody's book yeah why why don't
they just say that it's called well
i mean used to be you'd write
a book like fatherhood by bill cosby
for instance your favorite author
christ he can't help but if you
just named oscar a couple good but
you guys like what he did say
he's your favorite author ship ricky art
from the artist you've written tv star
is my favorite book of all time
but that sign language by jerry sign
okay so you don't need any of
that because you know who jerry seinfeld
is and you're like sign language oh
i get it he's gonna be making
jokes or whatever perfect father's day gift
right perfect it's got his picture on
the cover you're done here doe you
are psych john you are done shimei
obey him when i was in seventh
grade and that my my science teacher
was really like it was a funny
guy and i thought he was so
funny and i i gave him
it was a good line too he
was he was sort of like um
like like a goofy wasn't he wasn't
he was like a football player like
was he doing huh i'm still a
stepfather i'd like to fuck so science
teachers like
or oh ah no other it wasn't
it wasn't like i didn't have a
crush on him but i wanted him
to think i was funny and i
liked that he was yeah yeah so
might appear to that yeah so a
guy was reading sign language and this
isn't that great that was really funny
and i i lent it to him
but he kept it wanna give it
back
yeah i wasn't giving it to him
i was saying i thought this was
really i have by the way i
have some i've a friend of mine's
record album then he goes home to
his wife is like i've had a
rower crush on me yeah right and
i was like actually go to the
tree i just think you're funny i
also remember your name right now i've
had a friends record album for eight
years probably ah for the fridge
nz made a record no no it's
a woody allen record and i've well
why don't you put it in the
trash i've thought recently oh and watch
his friends should i try to give
this record back or is it in
bad taste now that he that he
shouldn't even own this yeah you have
to give it back with like such
a disdainful air like oh here's your
right i guess i ll
like i guess i understand why you
like this yeah but i've really messed
that up guys yeah want it to
be so good i loved it i
loved yeah and they made me so
happy i'm gonna tell myself no yeah
i'm a happy for the first time
i'm happy yeah nah nah hey ki
yes she's still alive right carol channing
oh i hope so really oh i
got to camp do you know where
are you familiar with the old alison
wonderland chosen i grew up watching no
leak yeah shooting up hey we're we're
gonna have what does it jam today
jam tomorrow does she finally died plainly
oh thank
my nine ninety nine twenty nineteen oh
wow jews around that long she died
in ninety seven but it is funny
and this the thing like i remember
todd glass talking about like when you
were a kid you'd see iran a
game show or something she's the oldest
woman to ever live it's like she
must be a thousand metals
oh like thirty nine yeah i know
yeah yeah she always seemed old we
owe issues in this were like that
for somebody i didn't know she was
in alison wonderland this v h s
tape that my godfather had copied from
the television to give it up to
your science teacher yeah he did that
to your science teacher and
i loved it it was really great
it was a fantastic adaptation who else
was in it and she sort of
has a mad hatter who's a star
studded call actually don't even know i
didn't know who anyone was i just
watched it sure yeah who played alice
i don't know we don't know and
yeah but you remember that it was
carol channing because i have looked up
that video in recent history is there
a meme
numbered the scene and i was like
oh i think that's who that is
and then i looked that up and
then it was i feel like i've
seen it because you shared it or
something i probably posted it or something
i thought it was pretty good and
i i felt like oh i'd love
to be like that when i miss
the years yeah here's where people could
get famous from just talking a certain
way
yeah who is you know harold shiny
yea or the guy going oh hey
hello there ah pat bertram yeah or
or joanne worley malaya it's joanne that's
ah
that's what my friend malaya and barbuda
who worked with god sacramento theatre company
and backstitch malaya it's joanne i remember
former malaysia roommate karen kilgour aref yes
telling a story about um
join warley was working with page somebody
famous broadway person i age skit ah
she would have been like the ingenue
at the time yeah yeah i think
i know who you're talking about and
this person page was i think ill
or something in her dressing room huh
and maybe this is a story from
oliva could um but joe hearing joe
ryan worley ed pages door going page
hey hey i love it it's so
funny i was trying to see something
because i sort of have a hunch
about some let me just see oh
hold on this is this is one
of our best shot segments on threesome
you know lauren scott orange got a
hunch yeah
friends got huh i was wrong oh
well she was wrong oh well but
yeah by the way lawrence on top
piano
the person you were talking about and
was possibly a voice in an original
disney animated film page page but it
wasn't hosting yeah oh oh i was
thinking of did you type search repaid
broadway page with that i didn't do
that please do it okay one second
please do it lauren were begging in
i also wa
know the listeners to do it too
yes everyone in the world let's just
any time we eagle something we want
you to google isn't the same time
yes no i don't think so no
m p three now because first name
page firstly it's hard to do that
because everyone it's just it's not filling
page janis paige i'm far far if
you hate for each
okay far it's on page four pawn
far downwind that's when the vulcans go
yeah i'm be happy this case davis
who was of course famously on hgtv
yeah she's also trading spaces she's a
broadway star she she did some show
wow i didn't realize that yeah really
i bet it was that person really
did that person
you're saying that she did some shows
yeah but i don't think i don't
i don't throw it away star and
i mean now native ah something page
maybe one hello dolly
oh maybe she was in it with
joanne worley well there you fucking go
huh interesting page page pay shall we
gotta get paige davis on the show
i know we've never had her broadway
highlights include bad bet in the first
national touring production of disney's between the
beast the title role in the national
tour of sweet charity and gloria on
the tony award-winning hit comedy boeing boeing
davis longest running associations with broadway chicago
having played roxie hart in multiple turns
on broadway and national international tour since
ninety seven i live in someone i
had no idea she was so ten
god yeah how amazing we got get
her on the show we got she's
the one guest yeah she's the one
guess we'll ever have paige davis we
know you're listing clearly any
anyone can get to paige davis please
please know what i always do i'm
trading spaces that was like one of
the funniest shows because they'd have like
that old guy who'd be like he'd
go over and designed to the on
the show if you're too young to
know what this is but texan guy
oh my god it was so funny
like you do
no no two neighbors would decorate each
other's rooms they'd switch switch houses it's
such a disaster and they would always
come out shit and they always say
like using sponge paint on the wall
they'd be like we did you're done
and sometimes you would like some designer
would be like i wanna put feathers
all over the wall or manure all
over the way it was always it
was it was it was always horrible
whole lot of second because it was
very da y
why and it's like it shouldn't be
die why this this motherfucker said a
minoan lie i'm lying about manure but
feathers yeah okay but thanks southern nevada
ordering guy would be like i'm going
to pay i'm going to tell a
woman she's a classroom nominee as a
template and make little egg people around
the border of the room and then
we're gonna put a fence around a
lot of the things we go or
no go people need i don't know
just the neighbors
we're supposed to be advocates for their
neighbors of what they wouldn't want so
a lot of times they go like
what are the colors you hate and
they go brown and they go okay
nothing but just make sure there's nothing
brown then the designer would come and
go like i'm doing the whole thing
brown it really would be in the
whole room would be like brown and
that's able to be like okay you're
doing the way they would conversation to
do it they'd be like no please
don't do this they do
i want bremen the designer would go
i'm still doing it sometimes they would
compromise now and then at the end
that people would come back and go
and cry and cry like it looked
so cheap yeah it was always so
bad like it was never done well
it was so funny there's another show
like this right or didn't have i
seen this well you ever think you
probably shame home makeover which is insane
with ah with the carpet tie from
heading to
the bus knocked out by the way
maybe it is that there was one
i saw where you could tell when
people didn't like it and it really
badly trailing by the way rock the
block is back anyway so fuck rally
recap great show yeah but back and
just start write a blog but page
rock the block is fantastic rock the
law to text christopher darden into text
art and because we both like
blocks are for wait for me oh
sure i'll rock the block is a
great show if you like homemakers they
take a call the second and middle
of nowhere and all the houses are
brand new construction and they give them
to all these designing given to designers
and they each do their own house
with their own with an aid and
greatest oh isn't there always a cul-de-sac
ah basis
really it's just a street of new
house every once in a while they'll
do it a street that goes all
the way through to an okay i'll
do that too but it's just each
designer does their own a team of
designers says their own house and they
obviously make different choices and then there's
a lonely process on each episode of
like working the kitchen today than one
person wins the kitchen competition you know
all this kind of stuff
tough and then at the end they
sell the homes my block ends in
a dead end is a dead end
street yeah so maybe you want to
run it's a lot like your career
i want my baby huh huh i
would like to laugh at that the
the houses are all new construction we're
going to relax yeah i met my
career
the houses are on new construction not
never before lived in and they can
make changes to the some of the
layout as well wait huh it's they're
not like it's like a house of
politics long enough that already exists or
you say sounds like a house of
horrors know like one of them is
like they make these out they are
all haunted didn't you notice in one
episode like er in one season the
houses were like on a highway they
were all just like you know
kind of far off but knife xy
with anyway i didn't like that yeah
anyway it's back i just want to
do it because i know you love
lakes but we love it i love
the program oh no so then all
these people have to move into this
new block people buy and they basically
are making little little little older streets
yeah it's just it's not
adorable when you put it that way
and i like it because i learned
about new designers too i like i
learned about leanne ford and she's really
good yeah she's really good remember i
love rushers i mean yeah she's still
around yeah she was young right she
was well she was young and then
she grew up and and had a
lot of drama around her life because
she was sixty and people like you
know me
does your yard to eddie cibrian who
no no he cheated on his wife
brandi glanville rowdy recap with leann rimes
and they now have a successful marriage
yeah randy has gone out sometimes the
cheating works out yeah so joy you
already say that for all
sometimes i work out i know i
know so many people are i have
known so many people i should say
in my life who who are the
kind of people that couldn't start a
relationship
couldn't make it end them for they
couldn't end a relationship well without starting
a new relationship so there's always an
overlap yeah because it's just trapdoor yeah
and it just continues over and over
and over again and then the people
that were
that we were helping them pete were
always stunned when it happened to them
yes yes it's like this person you
owe just from them they had the
times yes yeah like but now for
me it's like okay call it helping
them cheat while you have to fuck
me i'll help you cheat it's like
hey you need someone to help you
yeah okay you by yourself
hell hey this weekend i'll give you
pizza if you help me cheat
pizza baker alright let's take a break
look at the fun bottles of your
shoes scott we're back we're back yeah
it's like the surface of the moon
oh yeah but that if you were
if you were on the moon it
would be bad because the moon's like
this and then my shoes are like
this and opposites you know repel each
other well i was thinking you could
murder someone and probably get
away with o on the moon yeah
but that's very distinctive down here on
earth this is a great screenplay idea
murder on the moon the first ah
oo first daughter moon was first on
the me and it's an astronaut murder
someone on the moon and and people
don't have to be not future never
had before the boom
can it be doesn't have to be
an astronaut canopy like um a tourist
like ah a record producer oh yeah
like a slimy record producer someone wants
to record an album on the moon
yes like pink floyd wants to they're
like we sang about it can someone
younger ah by one year
sure
it's gotta be someone younger the bigfoot
by a year
i learn lauren yellow pink floyd is
pink floyd you love them yeah you
k wrote my college essay about pink
floyd well i heard you hell yeah
i've never got a band
what was it about what could a
pilot said it was so i don't
remember exactly what could it possibly have
been about but i was very into
pink floyd at that point when i
was early i was wanting i was
yeah you connecting it to something in
life and some blah blah you know
just some motion as a like was
it about the song hey yeah
yeah ding getting to go don't we
also we always my friends and i
think a handful of times did the
whole um think dark side of it
was that actually cool it was cool
yeah help but but but you've got
to start it over in the middle
right and you've got to be high
as ha da
the way that the other guy can
get that high anymore watch that shit
you can listen to these episodes along
with wizard of oz were watching wizard
of oz every single time oh yeah
and it thinks we don't look at
each other we look at the show
were just yeah look at those monkeys
i've never noticed them before oh we've
watched over one hundred and fifty this
hundred times i've never noticed these bugs
before thread oh monkeys are talented which
what you see them you can't stop
can't stop seeing them i was i
was like that with ah the show
peacemaker i don't know if either you
guys watch i haven't seen yet okay
every the the opening titles are great
and every time i watched them i
would notice someone new in them and
to the extent where like the very
final episode i was i saw steve
agee earlier than i had ever seen
him before in it and i told
that to cool up and i was
like eh they don't they're not changing
the credits are they in adding new
parts to it and she goes no
i go because this is the fur
first time that i noticed steve agee
before i could get the sentence out
she goes what you're fucking kidding me
you never saw steve agee i was
like because he has a whole big
dance part of it right why i
was like cool puppy got to stop
interrupting me i was like didn't see
steve agee until his big dance part
but you had never seen of it
because he was dancing off in the
background the worst is when
if somebody interrupts you with something like
that where you clearly were going to
say something else three like when your
voice goes wow like she said that's
different she said if you've never shot
use that you've never seen him in
life know in the in the credits
i was like in the credits you
are saying you've never seen him in
the credits know it was loud do
you say you're asking me the same
way cool to see so many differ
aren't place that he saw him i
said i don't ever steal your baby
until his big dance ah huh
anyway the credit so is wondering what
you're gearing up to
see your body was like tensei
laura moved your chair really tickled me
oh this way that's the way lauren's
gonna move learns gonna can i check
her body her since you brought your
own drum my god she's gonna move
the chair you're going off mike to
get glasses of water paul i bet
you wanted a glass of water this
time didn't you i did i forgot
to bring my bottle but tell my
boss tell
everyone why i didn't give you a
glass water because one time i showed
up here with my own bottle of
water and scott yeah i'd like ice
water for me and i dumped the
glass of water out to be funny
and now i'm being punished forever
yes you'll never have water so i
nailed it
i'll never give you water never
how's one does pool season start i
mean yesterday could have been was so
fucking high well you guys won't come
any fun sometime you should maybe we
should do one of these shows collie
and yes i can hear some water
stuff yes get her to the little
she's never been in a pool puno
she was born in july yes it's
too young
i'm too young when pool season ended
yeah and i wasn't trying to go
to any sort of beach or pool
yeah but it but now now i
feel like fun right
how's that water for you it's good
man you started cheated because you got
hers yeah and cheaters never prosper ooh
prosper now i've got some water oh
i um pumpkin milkshake
ah is that what the end of
there will be blood is about yeah
but i pooper your mil drank oh
my old buddy didio yeah too i
was thinking for la duda episode new
yeah i miss him yeah he's a
great guys think is there any possible
way he would remember me if i
met him somewhere
if you met him in character if
he was daniel plainview
if i were in micah mr prescott
like i mean don't you remember people
you've done things with scenes i you
know what though the older i get
yeah and the more things that i
do yeah it's harder to remember i
put holdings but don't worry it's happening
i've had people
i've had people now we've opened up
a new genre of joking with each
other i'm glad to hear um we're
both in this idler but i'm not
getting invited to the big slick to
be bad at softball presumably five years
ago when i teach ah there you
go yeah um i guys play softball
i've worked with people where they have
said we worked together on this thing
you know however many years ago
oh sometimes i'll remember sometimes it depends
on true but i guess i just
think of that movie as being so
important to his career that he would
have seen it like a lot of
times maybe that's not true i'd bet
he never saw it never yeah but
even if he's seen a lot of
times you could barely see me in
it i'm i'm like out-of-focus when you
can see me and then when i'm
when i have my lines i'm running
in silhouette i gotta
your scenes yeah they're very easy to
fuck it's one thing i gotta look
it up and very easy to find
i'm gonna do that oh that's fun
i shouldn't be in that movie it's
that's great that is never cool i
bet he's never seen it because i
i'm due a talkback after it once
and he seemed just mortified that he
had to talk about this but i
think that's him anyway right yeah
but i bet he's just like ah
i don't even want to talk about
this or watching or anything yeah and
i understand yeah maybe he thought it
was a different movie yeah because like
we're still talking about my left foot
i all these years later i remember
hearing that he thought when he made
a gangs of new york with scorsese
that
the original idea was this is gonna
be like kind of a comedy like
we're gonna go this is gonna be
like in bra crazy movie yes like
dumb and dumber said but then it
became like a like a serious oscar
bait drama kind of thing and that
it kind of ruined it for him
because he gave a different performance than
what he he was geared up to
give a different performance i think he's
i think he's
probably still get the same performance yeah
because yeah pretty big what he's doing
it's plenty big so i might have
been disappointed in the movie i see
i know you seem you guys you
tell us daniel day-lewis story i well
we go around the table when he
was an alvin and the chipmunks um
as simon's little brother was so funny
he's so good in it yeah he
he totally changed his body into a
cartoon so people don't that's what was
so cool because that was really method
acting he yeah this isn't true i
didn't do a voice for
wow
i was panicking for a second like
this read everything i know about daniel
day lewis law my old buddy oh
no do i bring this up to
him is who i ask about he
enjoyed working with alvin simon and theodore
is he really retired know that's what
given you asked in the game last
episode if um
if the person had been moving last
year i thought the answer for him
was no because i was like he's
yeah he's retired that's the thing i
would i panic too because i was
like did robert redford do one of
those marvel things within the last year
but i don't oh no yeah he
did the the final one but that
was two years ago right okay good
few cruyff um i'd liked i mean
i'd like to get to a point
where i could announce
some retiring
yeah you know you could do that
today if you want yes better than
people saying where's he been well cameron
diaz retired from acting which i thought
was pretty but no i was there
an announcement or digital shoot downstate the
time i retire i think like years
later she said oh no i you
haven't seen me because i retired oh
no i retired that's not going to
do yes yes sir this cancer wine
beer
snus now she has a child but
she wanted to focus on real cabernet
ideas
great it would be good um it's
called what is it called i don't
know i know i like somebody drinking
but it was on um somebody's already
promoting it on drew barrymore
you should have your own daytime talk
show lauren yeah i'd be really boring
nowadays so good at it you wouldn't
be good at it i don't think
so i would watch that i don't
think so well sherri shepherd just got
her own website how many episodes do
you think you could do before you
just lost all patients for up to
people like that i could do a
one hundred and fifty
it's a lot i think i could
do two weeks i could do i
could do like time talks well like
before actually internally got upset wouldn't be
that long but i could make it
last for a long oh before anyone
would know that i was even if
you weren't paid anything you'll know what
he buys it free because you love
it so i want to be paid
handsomely i wonder
or how long i could do any
kind of tv show before i didn't
want to do it anymore
i've heard some people say i go
wow that show must be so fun
you're doing eight seasons they go no
playing one character for eight years sucks
so bad yeah i mean i'll say
that but it's also like i think
it'll shut up section expands on the
character playing different or your characters and
like that's called it's just your own
person here and a great sich
duration for many years yeah i would
think yeah it would depend on the
individual project but i i feel like
because the the the longest i've ever
done anything was spontaneous nation where that
was a weekly thing yeah and i
did it for one hundred episodes yeah
right and like like the last the
last year was sort of like
i don't i feel like this it
feels same to me even though yeah
the content is different every time but
the structure of it was the same
to me and i yeah i got
tired of doing that same structure things
kind of run their course in that
er yeah telling us you don't want
to do this anymore know this but
this is a different thing because it's
not because just ca
every station right you know what if
we were like we don't want to
have conversations anymore
it's not my thing anymore no i
do know i don't talk anymore
over take it away from me i
think is i don't want to talk
no more no yeah has your baby
talk yet or no no but she's
babbling though she's babbling da da da
da da da da da da da
like she just screams yeah sundays ago
yeah
that makes me laugh so much it's
really what babies do that it's so
funny like what are they what do
they think they're saying that she looks
i yeah i know that i know
we've talked about this but is there
a competition between you and mike to
get it's getting a bit fierce i'm
really getting closer i feel the warriors
in the rupaul's drag race way yeah
it's fierce honey
and the words are getting closer to
being words um but not really like
she's definitely still but you could you
could say she has said data but
she has what about like i was
gonna say one of her first word
was mike mike i mean i'm trying
to focus on michael castle i do
think she knows who that we are
those
people because i'll say you know where
scott dunn and she looks over there
and then mama i looked sorry feel
stupid lie you looked around i look
like where does that leave
so try to teach her other words
my dad i shouldn't even astute yeah
what did you teach teacher words with
like we have some flash car and
some ass when when she's eating oh
just kissing over and over what she's
doing yes yeah you're eating yeah that's
a spoon spoon spoon do you do
the choo-choo i i do
don't um really didn't choo you but
she also does use the spoon herself
and boat she uses yeah so not
every time but i'll put some into
her mouth and she'll take the spoon
and then put it into does she
i wonder to me it's like why
when you're that young why you spoons
yeah do you not do not even
understand the concept of like why are
we even using the spoon the foods
right
there my mouse guys seem to see
that you can just it's like it's
a popsicle or something you know but
i posted a little thing on my
close friends today where she was covered
in um so good covered in baby
food because she was just i looked
at i was sitting on computer next
to the highchair and she was i
let her have the bowl with the
puree in it and then she was
just co
covered in it when i looked back
it was within thirty seconds i mean
it was like she was just eating
and then i looked over and she
just had it all what if we
still ate though yeah i would love
to you go to a restaurant on
your forehead i know so and that's
like a compliment to the code yeah
good way can we talk to the
chef i just wanna say food oh
my face is covered with your theirs
so this technique called baby led weaning
that i'm leaving like we're ready baby
baby baby baby led weaning so because
the baby you give them solids cut
to appropriate size that's a
and there's if anyone's curious about this
there's an instagram and a website called
solid starts on the website you can
just type in a food and it
tells you how to prepare it for
their age range so like she's likes
to what consistency yeah like yeah so
like so for example i want to
try giving i gave her a strawberry
yesterday and today and she i just
cut the top off and she just
held it and chomped it until
it was basically gone then i threw
it away when it got a little
awkward of size and i was not
sure about it okay but then with
the i'm gonna give her a banana
today says to cut it either half
lengthwise horse sideways horizontally and then she
could just have hold that and chew
on it and then like you made
me think of a banana split yeah
that oh won't work but so it's
a technique that supposedly helps with
them not being picky eaters because they
encounter a lot of textures and they
interact with the food as a whole
themselves so they're like familiar with what
it is as opposed i get were
curious too but as opposed to seeing
it as a puree you see role
object have you ever given her like
license to do it it seems fun
have you ever given her like wasabi
on a spoon as like um no
no but ah but there was one
time that i went to i went
to a bachelor party in vegas um
as the stripper with holly
no no no no no as it
was my improv team we went for
one guy's bachelor party yes and ah
we went to a sushi place and
we had done not mushrooms we had
done um we eat gummies okay yeah
but i had gotten pretty ripped off
a gummy and we went to the
sushi place and
it was one of those times we
were like this isn't fun like i'm
i'm feeling so weird and i talking
about this and then my friend dave
tony i think i can say this
or he he didn't understand just what
was that
he didn't understand like he'd see that
was hobby i don't know what he
did he he put it he added
lar he put those having so much
like an owner like he wasn't familiar
with how spicy own right and he
took a big bite and then he
was going crazy because it was so
spicy and i was like tweaking out
like i was like watching him do
this is like i couldn't stop laughing
but
it was like out that way no
but then i went to the bathroom
and i was like i need this
to end like it was just like
one of those
like the whole thing was just too
much happen to me a patton oswald's
bachelor party where i got so fucking
high before it ever started oh no
before we went to the first location
saving david cross talked me down oh
no i thought he was going to
be so judgmental and that was like
my headspace at the time everyone's judging
me and he was so nice he
was just like it's okay you're just
like dubai yeah okay yeah you're saying
that something he would be yeah wow
experiment yeah one time i was at
um this restaurant with my friends and
this is back when like i didn't
have any money and so as i
was like can i have something food
kind of some of your food and
someone had a couple of around to
different tables so when i had a
couple of socks
i'm similar to your food smeared all
over my forehead
someone had a cup of soup i
was like do you know if i
have some of this and they looked
at me weird and were like yeah
and i i took this cup of
soup and took a big swig out
of it and it's the reason they
looked at me so weird this just
before the mention of spoons i was
like it's dressing it was italian dress
king bay and yeah and this
they said it's dressing for years and
years oh my dress
said it's just like oh let's say
you imagine drinking dressing oh so oh
bo foul oh dresses dressy just like
spit up stuff the first time i
did i remember doing mushrooms once and
it was fun
one until it stopped being fun and
then when it wasn't fun anymore it
really wasn't fun but it was at
a um was it remember when ken
daley and c j had that big
house yeah yeah and with votes and
stuff yeah they had they had a
chinchilla and that was the first time
i ever saw ah the nintendo
oh sixty four with ah yes yeah
games and was like oh shit we
and so somebody had mushrooms we did
mush me and a few other people
did mushrooms i started jerry springer too
hot for tv tape
nice but i remember playing goldeneye yeah
on this big tv with ken and
bill odin kirk and some other person
and it started it just became very
funny like something changed in the music
and the music was sounded so stupid
that's what the
trigger was for me and i was
just laughing and couldn't stop having any
kin couldn't stop laughing and oh my
god laughing bill oettinger got so annoyed
was like i guess something's really funny
i don't know what it is but
apparently we can't stop laughing and it's
like i don't know what to tell
you valerie even funny i know last
laugh we did it was
a law so much more and it
was fun for a while and you
know so the the ones of us
who did it were talking to each
other and like having a good time
and then somebody said okay everybody it's
time to judge the pumpkin carving contest
and so
yes so there would be like all
day parties with oh my god yeah
yeah yeah yeah you would just go
there for a day that's fun it
was it was it was a very
specific time in one's life you know
and this is where it was like
when you're twenty five to thirty yeah
you see the same people all the
time all day every day yeah and
yeah so um we it was it
was
dark out we went to judge the
pumpkin carving contest and i remember it
was they had a pool and was
on the other side of the pool
and to go to get to the
pool i had to walk like past
this tree and this tree became just
a horrible forest like how do i
get through these dead branches in reality
this tree is
like as big as this yeah it's
like bronco round yeah and um then
we got there and we looked at
the pumpkin's and um there were like
eight of them maybe more maybe there
were twelve and so ah if you
the way we judged them was we
would go up to see jay and
she was on drugs too and you
had to say to her the nun
under that you were voting for and
so rather than do like one through
twelve and then writing hash marks next
to them or something she was just
writing the number whatever number somebody would
say to her so at one point
she she came up to me and
said look what i did and i
look at the piece of paper just
said all these random numbers and i
was like
i can't look at that
and they're driving me crazy it was
so it chilled me to my core
ah and then ah so whoever was
the winner they figured it with a
pencil about yeah and so had to
use that time and so then i
remember i think it was mark fight
and toby huss were like zwinky about
but they were pretending to be mad
that
their their pumpkins didn't get chosen and
they started smashing the pumpkin's oh nancy
said oh and it was that was
so horrible to me that's the last
thing that was like the end of
the trip was like this is that
bad it's not a member mark fights
house above the gas station of jerry's
garage and he had a slingshot
and water balloons and we used to
launch water balloons at all the people
standing outside the the ah the afford
theatre or the fonda i can't remember
which one they funded the fondo yeah
so all these people waiting to go
to a concert at the fonda we
would launch from from a block away
we would launch water balloons up until
then hit them what
and cops would cops came and like
interrogated us all i don't remember this
i remember throwing water balloons at people
they would people from the party would
go down into the big lots and
you would try to try to hit
them yeah yeah yeah yeah oh no
we were doing it to to randoms
i don't know if i was there
that i was like a drunk oh
wow
it was quite fun we had a
good time that's what i met everybody
yeah was that joe's jerry's jerry's garage
parties yeah we were all like fucking
broke and so these parties would just
have big beer nights yeah you would
have the cheapest beer and you'd be
just all ran to be like you'd
bring a six pack maybe of the
cheapest thing that you and you would
climb out onto the roof
oof yeah it was that was fun
it was really fun it was fun
good old days spoiled old days you
need somebody now asking you to climb
out on a roof they probably will
they probably will tomorrow
alright i don't think i think my
days of being invited to a party
where climbing onto a roof is a
thing or done i think oh i
think i don't want to climb onto
a roof yeah i think that's where
i am in my yeah let it
climb on this let's get on this
roof know that seems bad no come
on
let's take a break in the ground
take a break and we'll be back
with a three cheer and we're gonna
be on the roof
well here we are on the roof
and it's time to get a feature
yeah these cords are long these chords
are long bay chords don't really already
have a three no we didn't bet
on the we're coming back i'm sorry
why did i say that oh but
oh god okay okay let's keep going
you know why because
like where like there are times lauren
when we would do improv and i
would be playing some sassy lady character
yeah and i'd call you bitch and
you'd be like stop calling me a
bitch yeah and i was thinking this
is real i think no i missed
i missed it oh because it made
me think like you beside i don't
get offended by that no but it
made me think like a lauren doesn't
do this in life with her friends
like this is not a thing that
she does
is maybe ah call her a bitch
yeah no i don't really say that
but um but i don't care if
it's an improv oh so anything goes
at an improv know but i just
managed to stay but she can't do
it anything do ya characters kick your
ass
oh me i'm a pushover look out
for my characters
alright so it's time for a three-acre
and it looks like one of you
guys has got one no oh wow
lawrence doing personal business i think oh
okay um so paul is looking for
one right oh and i'm trying to
find my document here we go it's
a sacred sangre document you on the
other hand don't even try i
don't try because i said all of
this it's just loading loading loading so
loading loading okay this one so you
have no no no it just loaded
sun burst into my eye that's beautiful
it's like a poem yeah poem a
plane whatever yeah i haven't called letter
list okay this is a minute by
jack nicholson herrera pereira p r e
i r a to rera rera maybe
dom rera dom herrera at the count
of three all participants hold up a
random number of fingers
tally the fingers come up with the
corresponding letter of the alphabet so i
don't think we're we're like a certain
part of the alphabet obviously yeah yeah
well we can only do so many
well we yeah abc d e f
g h i j h to do
more than seven fingers you can do
ten we can but then we we'd
have to start the alphabet
over again yeah okay like if we
all did ten it would be if
we all did ten yeah what's the
what it's all to ten what are
you mushrooms no i'm saying chicago tea
reading the directions i don't follow you
can do more than eight so you
hold up if it why because if
we all do it around and we'd
run out of letters
i don't think you understand and i
don't think i understand that you have
to read it all right all participants
all participants oh just a bit about
the first about write down a list
of items list of artist you must
write down a list of items three
per category starting with that letter those
items are a movie or a tv
show a musician or band a food
places an
emissaries yeah it's categories pretty much but
with fingers
i use my fingers and scout so
i don't i prefer i tie my
hands behind my back that's how you
determine the letter of the alphabet okay
fine
but wait now we've gotta write stuff
yes yes every phone yeah okay alright
and then what happens when we take
it gets a point for each thing
they write that no one else writes
okay this is categories most of these
games were recycled games but that's okay
guy wordle is just a recycled lingo
right oh and lingo is mad about
it
yeah we always piss lng goes mad
lingo alright okay i think we got
it okay so open up so zayn
don't do an apology this time oh
i er i was in the middle
of one to say that ooh oh
wait apologizing for something that i did
yeah oh thank you i'm outsourcing my
elegies okay alright ready alright so three
to wait she nodded we gotta do
the fingers teacher hold on i'm game
and we'll countdown with three three-tier teacher
wonder okay somewhere just putting random brainer
to bring random amounts of finger yeah
ok three scherzer two future one sure
ten i did seven i did two
so nineteen the hardcastle so we go
a b c d e f g
h i j k l m n
o p q r s t yes
not t hey yeah yes yes okay
and what are the categories the categories
are
i'm but the doc again yep scroll
down to the circle
oh and we have to write down
you remember thinking i'm gonna remember now
he's starting with no it's s but
yeah so what are the categories movie
or tv show musician or band foo
all ice animal i gotta write these
down so movie yes how do you
spell that
maybe your sai chau chau musician or
band food place food place food place
and i wrote band again food place
no food i wrote ladies music is
bang is that wrong that's very wrong
and then what's the last category okay
okay i'm just scrolling
oh
where more of
movie or tv show musician or band
food place animal animal i wrote good
place okay i'm don't you okay and
how do we how i think it
should be as short as possible yeah
you're right fast as you can talk
to each other okay
ah i'm going to write my next
thing now
ah and ah okay i got it
i'm done i got here totally done
young i thought we're supposed to write
three things for each caviar no that's
impossible yeah if that's what it said
i just wrote one for each category
oh um okay well i can do
that but i don't care for the
reopening doc scrolling down your god a
list of items per category
now come on look into that yeah
now go oh oh okay let me
let me let me get my food
place hold on it's not a food
place places that my short film i'm
plugging it rude is one category places
one category oh shit i thought you
were saying a restaurant but saying why
place a place that's literally my short
film yeah
what a lovely planet you have affect
me okay ah
ah just checked me that's that is
the that's the log line for three-time
please respect me so he's just like
me okay i'll have one for each
one i can't do i got one
for each one o j yeah that's
where we're doing okay ship great okay
movie tv show okay jaws jaws john
yes
look
i had to reopen the dock so
we stuck in time
i forgot that one
we're just writing down to any movie
yeah because every time i would try
to i've tried to do everything and
then i kept getting yes
i have to go back
fucking dogs don't change a thing
ah don't change oh my god wow
what's your job i wrote down jaws
no change a thing will give you
half avoid for you to write yeah
okay stepford wives succession okay okay musician
musician
now you have to rise and go
for logos and it's silverchair as it
strokes i said youtube
ah okay food isaan soup is it
smashed potatoes i said oogie
plays i said salt lake city stratford
upon avon i almost said leningrad remember
that's not a place anymore and i
wrote st petersburg wow you guys again
and then analyze it snake i said
snake i say to whore
ah what do you think that game
was hell to think about when the
game was two hundred right or you
got about that letter to write whenever
you want by the time we got
to buy it was so but you
too that was so far long ago
in the past by the time i
was writing
categories and kept being interrupted oh my
fucking oh shit all right you're right
oh no now we gotta go out
on a high note but yeah that's
true yeah we're all the time anyway
alright alright everybody thank you for listening
we love you right to follow it
as freedom usa gmail dot com follow
us on instagram and twitter threesome usa
um and we will and if you
wanna listen ad-free ah you can either
keep listening here or you can go
to cbp world dot com or stitcher
premium we love you guys thank you
so much for listening and we'll be
back next talk
yeah
uh