three
oh
zo more than correct yourself up and
cheese eating
ooh podcast fo pause do we need
to measure lacivita it's kind of a
thing i love to eat how old
are you buddy i love to shit
like we want to look like winning
oh even better when it goes out
i respect my food and buy bottle
hey everybody i paul f tompkins i'm
scott arvin i'm
everything you say is going to be
like lauren fresenius like
sorry i'm thirsty your lauren lemonade looking
down here's what's cool okay went to
lemonade you take notes
please get ready leather jackets and you
will get your boxster bikes i went
lemonade which has been published in the
bathroom it doesn't exist everywhere and just
in the bathroom and a gentleman ordered
something and took too long and they
gave me a free lemonade oh and
a coupon for a another free lemonade
next time i go so oh cheapest
thing that they have on the menu
they gave you
one for free
would like three twenty nine are you
out of your mind
do you remember that commercial yeah john
are you out of your mind for
denny's right yeah probably
probably
what commercial wasn't it wasn't some like
many out of your mind yeah friday
night are you i'm ninety nine oh
out of your mind but friday night
are you out of your mind kevin
i'm out online every friday night it's
friday night look look look right out
of my heart all week doing this
bullshit hs yeah on friday it's your
real chance to
cuddly right and you call off the
record i talk off the record and
i say all the things that i
can't say here you completely talk on
background that's an understanding you drop all
of your friends who are all reporters
that's right all my friends are reporting
jenny's super slam because super slam family
nine what was your most most super
slime
what did it consist of a dulcie
bacon braised dougie and break-in dougie break
it unless you break in your house
to shit on the floor
five ninety nine
made the break get into a break
dance break dance break wow must be
eggs bacon of course
boil eggs bacon hash browns and pancakes
pancakes pancakes pancakes i used to survive
on the dollar fifty jack-in-the-box meal
a hamburger a taco fries and a
drink that's a great deal i mean
back in nineteen ninety ninety one show
i've heard you talk about this before
but not on this show not on
this show i like your thinking pen
down i love this baking
she might get him a paddle we
give them a special shirt yeah wouldn't
be like no but we please in
it so it's more aerodynamic city three
sided like a pyramid spanker
okay sorry three-sided paddle so it's like
a baseball bat but whittled down yeah
looks like a pyramid yeah like a
pyramid and you like a dreidel yeah
like a gradle thank you your adrenal
gradle gradle draino may face an eighty
on your butt
were you were you guys spanked as
children once were only ones yeah some
of the movie wants is about yeah
should you bendigo and your mom going
one second long it's a gift
throughly as a gift well what about
with the belt yeah i got it
with oh jesus you know i never
did i got my mother slapped me
across the face one toe but i
never got lucky bailed did you tell
her honor i will tell you i
took over while we had a duel
weird pistols at dawn it was very
weird but we did it and i'm
lying my mother isn't so spicy huh
you want asians she passed away years
later yeah from real slow hers her
sword wounds
um i my older brother used to
do a thing where he would torment
me by locking me out of the
house so that's so annoying it was
not fun because i would try it
was so frustrating and i would try
to get back in and i we
had a way to front door to
backdoor and sounds like my body
same love to enter the front of
your front door the mouth okay i
love to poop through the back with
back during your ears to my ears
it's bad so he would be able
to run back to lower earth right
into the microphone you'd be able to
run back and forth just constantly be
like okay i'm going to block the
door yeah in the back door and
would you fake do a fake out
like a quarterback fake out of item
i would try but i had more
i was outside tried more groundcover he
would just do a straight line this
short
distance between two point well we didn't
live in a shotgun mass i'm not
here to do ma
so here i am about my year
i was banging on the back door
window the back the window in the
back door to what end first for
to someone on let me enter for
someone else to try i can't remember
right i can't remember because maybe maybe
it's on my little brother was in
there and he could hear my right
or maybe if i just raised enough
of a racket it'll
right annoying it's like all right but
i broke the window off and then
when my mom got home and found
the window broken and ah sheriff who
broke the window before i could explain
what had happened she slapped me across
the face ooh and did you say
yes before she slapped you across the
face with my i think my brother
and me
immediately ratted me out okay yeah as
having done today just call you paul
or paul f tompkins called me
listen the name my francis disappointing yeah
yeah um yeah glee was they would
call you know when docker i don't
see fool i don't wanna say i'll
tell you off off the air to
off air what what they called me
well what
oh a little family nickname for me
oh really i was like i don't
want you knowing no one needs to
know look what if we guess it
can you say yes absolutely bitch
alright
what's a bitch
please stay
i heard it enough quite a bit
okay scott
this is giving me terrible flashbacks
flashback tompkins had a bed bug good
so she just tomkins she just straight
up open it was it open hand
yeah of course yeah that would be
a punch otherwise yeah right but was
it albain could go oh my god
back it was like
you cur you cry
yeah i did i was i was
i felt betrayed and angry it was
you know all that because you want
to die like you were in the
wrong and you were just trying to
redress a wrong that i was luck
i was this guy and just had
my own yeah yeah i didn't in
your home where your little my emily
slee family sleeps where i
play with my toys i wasn't trying
to break the window of course not
was or was it you know when
i was in it wasn't when i
was a kid i had to watch
oh so great it was a watch
that played space invaders what yeah yeah
yeah i was it must have been
nineteen eighty or nineteen eighty one because
i was in elementary school big watch
it was in our living room
and it's sometimes also played happy days
didn't tell the time
no it was it had just come
out it was so cool it was
like a digital watch that also played
space invaders it was like my prize
because you're holding your two thumbs like
you're you're like well what space you
could take it off you know space
invaders is a game i made here
it is a game that i do
listen to this what would it be
if not a game show
that's how it's done baby i know
you just like that oop you do
you are a little gun on the
bottom of the oh yeah then you
have to go on dude dude can
like partly right yeah the invaders like
start coming yeah yeah i played that
you played that yeah yeah i played
dad yeah okay so i had it
it was so great
ah and then i let my friend
wear it oh shit i know where
this is headed anytime i did that
it was about yeah so i saw
my friends like kids do you mind
if i wear during recess i just
want to like it so cool i
was like yeah sure and then we
were playing tag in the ah you
know on the on all the playground
equipment and i was up on the
sl
allied and he came running up the
slide to get me and my feet
were down towards him and just like
instinctively i like jerked my my foot
out and it kicked him in the
face oh
and he was hitting you just like
fuck you and took off the watch
and threw it against the playground equipment
and broke she's how old were you
guys ten wow and fuck yeah maybe
it wasn't a total flock you i
love fun goo go to fudge
this is bad but i once kicked
a boy in the balls for no
reason
yeah just like hey check out the
boy and assumes like clock i'm only
like fell to the ground i mean
it was like horrible but actually you
want to see what i don't know
why i don't know why it was
only homie joe just came over you
like yeah i don't know so i
think someone's always came over yet
like ah someone must have been like
go do that or so i don't
know maybe you've been told her at
someone else's fault well gotta be i
mean i obviously well i gotta be
i went along with it or i
just thought of doing it because i
saw it in something or something i
don't know maybe no idea little bit
by the mystery of balls well also
you'd been watching me funny home videos
a lot of true probably just gotta
be fun
ah but no one was taping you
yeah there were no side effects and
no scott music i don't remember getting
into
i'm sure i didn't i never really
put it together
skov using there's a whole sketch about
it on begging oh really yeah where
where the semester plays the saga yeah
i remember the america's funniest home videos
well it started out as like we
as as reggie had been had a
hidden camera on him for his entire
life and then every every video
oh descended into him being hit in
the balls with something in sky music
started playing and then it's segwit just
much like a bang bang sketch or
it starts as one thing becomes another
thing and then becomes a totally different
things segue into a skov video where
you hit yourself in the balls oh
lauren and roy hill's i'm not cared
so yeah
finally arma it's like my whole body
is hot
what effect jails what a they can
you kicked in the balls is it
ghost yeah that doesn't kicked my knee
oh what do you think he died
from being kicked in the balls thinking
he might have what if that was
the part of the story that learns
to tell us and like she kicked
him so hard in the balls his
testicle split open and just fell on
the ground and yeah blood he died
of blood
dated but i didn't finish my well
i can't wait around all day most
guys stick when their bows drop some
goods gonna happen oh you're back
so your knees fine still in pain
speaking of watches i did not know
how to tell time until i was
in seventh grade what and i was
given a watch for christmas that's unusual
for stressing out in class because ah
da and then did you test we
you to see like what o'clock said
on it
i don't think so because i don't
remember that ever happening but i remember
i've i've told this one spontaneous nation
because andy daly had the same thing
really that he was it took him
forever to learn how to tell time
i remember finding it really overwhelming when
you think about it you don't need
to anymore like the clock face it's
out of date at this point there's
no reason but everywhere else
as them no but it still i
mean miller rails are off do you
know what i mean will the only
thing that that it's necessary for is
for when someone's at your three you
know what i mean but what about
like like when you're playing ah shoot
em up games shoot em up game
so yes spaceship clock started like that
yeah but they're not like so
so necessary like yeah you know what
i mean get something else but then
it's like i have this clock as
an art piece then i look at
my phone i wanna know what time
it is yeah i remember getting into
it because i like watches a lot
i like time pieces a lot and
i remember a guy very smugly asking
me like why would anyone have a
watch anymore right yeah
fuck this guy you know you could
just look a train you just look
on your phone you can just look
at your phone and i said i
don't want to look at my phone
well do you know what time it
is right now and he said
no my phones in my pocket and
i looked at my wrist and i
said well i do it's telling you
to shut the fuck up but you
should have said yeah and that's what
i did say and he did and
he died from it jacques he just
looked me close so tight air went
in around i shut him down so
hard it sealed his mouth up yeah
it's like
like why why ever like why not
just sealed a close to your body
and have one thing of clothes god
except this is also what i know
yeah i said that to him too
yeah exactly the way i said oh
yeah but hesitating yeah i know it
was time yeah whoa you guys know
why no yeah duh why no two
two
yeah i know to do to me
understand simply understand i say oh she's
so fine day no no no
oh this was a free show joke
too good to leave pre show we
had to bring it onto two hots
for pre show to leave pre shades
too hot it's too hot for free
shows so do a lot for no
one to hear too good got to
share it oh lord did anyone did
you use to watch the too hot
for tv type stuff um no but
i renee
really know what you're talking very well
jerry springer was just one oh yeah
like ninety i did watch jerry ninety
five or ninety six i remember going
over to like ken daley's house and
watching the jerry springer will be like
a video yeah yeah had to order
mine yeah okay i never saw them
commercials it was like kind of at
the same time as like um girls
gone wild yeah yeah
yeah like where are we going to
get our porn the internet isn't invented
yet so i know i know i'll
just jerk off to girls lifting their
shirts over and over did the girls
go wild did that guy joe was
named joe something yeah did he just
segue into porn porn on online know
i know he had some legal troubles
oh yeah
yeah i believe and may be incarcerated
i can't recall chevron look it up
shelf and look it up strong stock
look it up sure then look it
ah chevron we recently had a communicate
with chevron yes and he included in
his response
it's a link to a google image
search of chevron which is apparently some
star wars expanded universe monster really you
don't say weird thing happened to the
guy yeah wow france joe francis yeah
oh joe francis ta middle name i
mean i'm not him in june
a jane ashley alexandra dupree alleged that
francis and his company found her without
permission but she dropped the suit after
francis released footage showing her consent she
dropped her bathing suit that is
hey two thousand and eight for women
sued girls gone wild for allegedly filming
them as minors francis roche francis presented
himself for the part of the child
year until the judge cited him for
contempt of court and fined him twenty
five hundred dollars for asking a plaintiff
during cross-examination if she was a prostitute
francis hired two lawyers that same just
good lawyer
are you a prostitute so you don't
care who sees you tis francis hired
two lawyers that same data represent him
for the duration of the cia oh
i can't afford another twenty five hundred
i think i better get two lawyers
francis ultimately pleaded no contest to child
abuse and noble contention charged yeah la
contender
and february twenty twelve nevada judge mark
denton awarded steve wynn seven point five
million dollars for defamatory statements made by
francis and september twenty twelve of jury
awards season has no tip one million
dollars in a slander case against joe
francis for claiming that win had threatened
to kill him over a gambling debt
francis witnesses
all denied hearing when make such threats
the jury added twenty million dollars in
punitive damages in november twenty twelve judge
joanne o'donnell reduce steve wynn's award by
twenty one million to nineteen million oh
donald research jury's award was speculative and
based on there just like francis and
that's it okay so he's not incarcerated
he's just still wr
rich and yes able to give away
twenty million dollars or so at the
drop of it remember when steve wynn
ah put a hole in a painting
when this when this is steve wynn
years ago he like fucking actually put
his elbow through like all right slick
yeah oh i remember that yeah and
he has a sharp enough down elbowed
but yeah or it was stretching as
a tight enough painting oh good razor
let me go the painting was taught
to his elbows so poignantly
you put razors in the sleeves like
peaky blinders yeah yeah yeah doi your
yoy yoy yoy see you doi we
need to go your yoy yeah rank
two more minutes no yeah boi yoi
nope gotta go to roy we'll be
right back
whereby yeah take a bite and i
still do it cover will cover for
you to take a bite and i
still will what is that what do
you got over there chocolate chip cookie
so learn to sell shopping good looking
disseminate throughout the yeah oh yeah
yes i'm i have a little bite
i'm i'll have a little bite you
might have a little bite yeah here
we go shoving you don't get a
oh shit i took too much
oh and i was a kid i
remember
my mom bought flintstones true oh you're
vegan yeah i ate the whole jar
oh no oh my god i used
to hide those in my underwear there
was no did you not catch a
cold for a full year i thought
you were going to stop an underwear
i've never had a cold
wow
i've never been to the doctor how
much vitamin c
my friend i
maybe i shouldn't tell the story because
it's not my story not because he
would mind because he's told it but
my family only told stories that are
anyone's story i like i don't know
we've told a lot of other people's
stories how we okay so my friend
i don't think that's true oh dear
my friend used to sell lsd i'm
listening
and he had he had lick he
didn't drop liquid form right and so
you would you would put it onto
something i believe is that how it
works you would like to do a
drop onto something so he was like
he wanted to sell he had like
thirty drops of lsd and he wanted
to sell it but he also drops
a lsd
du da to da thirty jobs in
dallas d i got saudis now but
he also wanted to get high so
he said conundrum so he said you
know what i'll do
wow i'll put i'll put the thirty
draw lasting dilemma i'll put the thirty
drops of lsd in my mouth and
then after like ah
half hour i'll spit it back in
why i'll spit it back out and
then i'll sell see the dumbest person
alive that's well works he then fell
asleep and swallowed it all
oh wow
is that thirteen like i have a
cup of coca-cola but my friend wants
it but i really want to taste
it so i'll drink the whole cup
and then spit it back in because
i'll get the flavor well that's sounding
works just driving anorexia right that's believe
me uh oh sorry for probably both
um but yeah so and then he
saw
saw he had hallucinations for years
i have to i have to go
back because this this makes so little
how old was this guy at the
time ah god i would ah maybe
twenty s wow what the fuck that
smokes that's also like my fear of
drugs like that is that i would
have some sort of break and then
be like now i have problem now
no i have prom oh i have
barolo i took too many dro i
held the lsd liquid in my mouth
and i swallowed it of course not
very good anymore
well he's the guy's a drug i
swallowed it up cause dan roof oh
that's a game actually that i was
going to tell you guys about what
is it okay when he's played at
this time okay we'll play it after
our next break okay tin roof it's
it's called tin roof rusted know but
it's similar to what calling something in
refreshments at fred schneider game it's an
oh okay
a grade i know the same is
exciting will play that after the break
ah lorne you ever do how many
drugs have you done i'm gonna talk
about that here shits because your mom
listens yeah well mrs lakin whole family
liz hi trish thank you for getting
that subscription stitcher premium i mean check
out john lifestyle retirement party
i saw feud on twitter
between you and john i was odd
i was at john's podcast i listen
to one of that app one of
the first episodes and um so he
had a long interview with ah karen
kilgour aref um and then he had
a smaller interview with me ah and
i was like i'm
as i'm listening to the episode i'm
realising oh maybe i'm not on this
one really because the time is like
slipping away yeah i was a germ
and ceo volume title yeah my name
was in there time keeps on slipping
slipping into the future and ah so
then we're so then finally oh i
am on this okay so we're talking
and then of
sudden like i'm speaking then there's a
very abrupt fade out and then he's
just talking about a completely different topic
and to what's happening i just faded
you but i do then i was
confused um i faded you out the
same way but but during the explanation
so people won't understand you
yes okay good
so there was an abrupt fade out
and then john just started talking about
something else yeah and no mention like
oh we're done with that guy and
also wasn't your full interview oh and
also like i mid sentence any fading
is like an that's enough yeah that's
enough for this jerk so i gave
him a hard time about it
on twitter and i didn't and i
was i was surprised by it but
i wasn't like furious but i wanted
to needle him about it because i
thought that would be fun for both
of us but i think it was
only fun for me i think so
i asked which took the fun out
of it yeah yeah i got you
yeah i had fun i like when
i watched something unfold on twitter it's
exciting what is exciting but in real
terms and
a r t yeah start the clock
and what am i doing space invaders
a real-time this is a good day
during real time to tunica she just
said real-time don't know but okay now
what am i doing doing space and
now you're doing space okay now what
i'm doing real-time due to space and
you're doing real time to slow down
the space of this doon doon doon
deny you're doing masha do
oops i did this
wait so it came back again because
andy daly tweeted to him that he
just listened to all of his ah
episodes and so it was like eleven
thirty at night and i should ignore
the bans and i was like crazy
for this is my kind of this
is where i live this is what
i like to do so i wrote
i
wrote to hit to andy and john
was included on the thread what did
you think of that abrupt fade-out and
then andy wrote back a joke john
did not respond so i don't know
i think yeah we need we need
a broker based but would it surprise
you to know he's here right now
ah he's got a podcast okay wow
i wouldn't express it stands up for
himself and he's fine
he's a grown ass maze a grown
ass man you don't gotta come you
don't gotta be scared he's and try
to appease you don't get to try
to appeal to grow nationally
we do we wait
what are you want on the way
home what do you think is the
cutoff for like when when is someone
a grown ass man is it truly
thirteen as they say in the jewish
tradition yeah i know what you don't
think so
is this strange like that that it's
so out of date yeah jews jews
are sure ya know so like you
have to be twenty nine to be
a grown ass man in this day
and age yeah not true for me
yeah that was a no i mean
i i don't think it should have
to be took me a long time
oh you don't even later yell for
me yeah for sure how lately lotta
guys
no because all these comedians idiots i
would say i always you know i
was a complete idiot for quite a
long time to get mature i would
say in my mid thirties when i
started to kind of realize that i
was not as grown up as i
thought i was but that i think
that trump everything but drive everything i
feel that wows hey why are you
lying
that every well you know that song
which um we start the fire by
the faces ah new law
oh yeah wish that i knew i
owed oh wait i was strong
ah yes yeah what about it i
just was listening to it and i
was like this is i love this
song and i was talking to mike
about how when he first listened to
it like blew his mind cause it
was like he was kid and i
was like oh my god like yeah
i don't i'm older now and i
get it you know like that kind
of thing how would how old was
a winnie a kid i mean like
yeah
just realising that you will know more
than you knew always will know you
are until you have some sort of
debilitating you know brain does it yeah
and you know less and less and
less until you're done yum but when
they are unexpected my visitors
the original there's a cool there's a
commercial that's about i don't even know
what it's for if it's for a
medicine or if it's for just awareness
but it's about dementia and so it's
this guy who's like seeing he's having
illumination when you're alone it's it's it's
like that but it's come to get
you what you know what
it can protect you he's narrating it
they they come unexpectedly my strange visitors
he does this weird he does this
weird horror movie rangers will come to
your house tonight wait have you seen
a quiet place yes i have seen
a quiet place this tamra
did you see the strangers yes i
saw the strangers that movie the strangers
will always come for you
yeah every question we ask you just
answer like yes i will always answer
like this when no later okay seventy
four due to like the peed on
yeah my brother is september six yes
um yeah no it's all about his
strange like mental like hallucinations having yes
he's having things
aren't there phantasms do you feel like
your birthday is the only real birthday
yeah of course what are you talking
about like you're the only person that
actually know like my date no that's
not how i feel but my when
i hear my birthday date i'm like
that's what a birth that's a birthday
that site
okay but that may three or so
you know you're like no it's yeah
i think when they're too close to
certain holidays i'm like you don't you
don't have a real birthday like i'm
like september six that's a birthday show
birth dad's birthday september twelfth shy never
ever forget ally too that's a bite
same damn number
day but yeah i think if i
hear someone's like oh i my birthday
is december twenty four i always like
mentally shake my head and go you
poor that's christmas eve to understand or
christmas baby and christmas but i knew
one
i'm growing up i don't know anymore
but i know carmel ice baby you
do i think it's a cool thing
that would have like for that to
happen to somebody as a parent to
school but then it's like you have
to every year try to separate those
two holidays it seems very difficult i
think it's better to be born on
christmas than christmas eve no because then
you can have a whole christmas eve
birthday day
a and then what does it yeah
what do they do because i don't
know like i think celebrating a birthday
now is we're so old that who
gives a shit i disagree
but when you're but when you're young
it's so important agent so employee here
in america it was traditionally growing up
like eighty yeah well yeah i think
that when you're young you think oh
shit yea i believe in america i
believe that i broke my day birthdays
a miracle will come to your house
room
your birthday everyone's growth is important i'm
sorry strange visitors come to me only
on my birthday i know it could
attack me mentally they tear down my
defenses until i am no longer able
to withstand i gotta find that commercial
no i don't chevy does chevy and
chevy
look up dementia commercial you know what
i've been yeah i've been watching commercials
lately for medication and trying to find
you like just trying to flip through
them like is anything going to work
you were doing it so many side
effects nobody ma go out close to
this one we're gonna watch the commercials
you're so weird the activity of microwave
yeah lorne syphilis and like growing they're
always doing like this can be your
life if you get if you use
this commercial urf use this medication there
always some activity like they're at a
county fair and they're laughing you know
sony outside they have me doing um
physical activity and you know the shoot
those things
like south africa it's doomsday yes because
janie janie has a lot of commercials
and and she goes on a lot
of commercial editions and there was one
for some fibromyalgia medicine where if you
see these if you see this this
commercial now there's multiple versions of this
commercial and they always do the same
thing where the the
it's always a woman yeah she has
to dig to indicate the chief swati
lamp was it a dog she's feeling
the pain of course chance to indicate
she's feeling the pain of fibromyalgia she
has to put her right hand sort
of on top lever left shoulder and
give us a subtle really subtle grimace
ah
and it's it's the same movement and
the same face for every single one
every single one of these yeah they're
very specific about it in the in
the audition more subtle marcel but she
was up for one of those where
it was going to shoot itself africa
nicole and shuster were watching teachers like
wait i think this is the one
that i auditioned for and then there
it's just like
it's it looks so usa there's no
way that that was the one that
said there's a million of these commercial
elsa don't get why things have to
shoot in random places like that when
it's like an indoor thing it's yeah
having the money somehow but it's the
crew's much money i live right south
africa triple that all the time like
i say like he wanted a crucial
mostly yeah i'll go up to
a commercial in miami i think for
oranges are saving my ass and it's
like why buying them why not get
just get a miami actor who put
up with miami miami
the bazillion reference oh that's where the
for the fourth season that no one
has seen okay i've seen it you
haven't done yet apparently i know using
this was eugene cordero oh you know
i because i don't know if it
made the i think it did make
the final cut though but he's asking
if someone wants to come with him
to miami and every take you'd say
miami in a different weird
oh yes i've seen this you will
you come with me to miami miami
oh mama mia mama mia he's funny
a he should be here but we'll
never have a guess why every number
but i don't know shaven just switch
places oh shit i was like seven
i stormed around the ship
sam laughed and shaven oh just made
a twist ending i was a twist
judge chevron did you find the commercial
wait remember this commercial it's on still
like every year they exist i do
exist he does this he made this
i hate it many to exist i
keep my gosh night this an i
can't
i hated it they're still running it
don't you hate that fucking guy is
awesome
eminem that oscar winning actor is an
o j k simmons i find that
took over for john goodman but i'm
like give it to somebody else now
to be at night jay casillas i
am going to reassurance commercials too yeah
i was vin diesel groot do you
know what i mean yeah it's like
let somebody else go groot yeah literally
don't even know
he says i am groot i am
groot he's gonna say it a different
graph few different ways i'm grit can
finish can finish i'm i'm group he
comes to me my groot comes to
me and says he is groot by
strange visitor um chevy divided although i
got this
what does this recording from your home
recorders from yourself or everyone will say
to me to bypass this is not
the one this is it racist terrifying
sitting doing it oh jesus christ am
i experiencing this or is this a
cliff boy grandpa chuck
become
every single night and give me instructions
starbucks
i don't like please kill all baby
soledad that was terrified i didn't want
that wait what was the loud de
la bo one day i just wanted
to say the green mam is voiced
by cree summer who's an amazing voice
actor oh and also regular on-screen actress
but she she
made me horny also on harvey street
kids she makes me horny the green
imminent makes me so horny i know
oh my god one
i can't tell it story you can't
tell what stories can you not tell
about you being horny about you taking
drugs yeah and this involves everything involves
you taking drugs and becoming horrid from
it i'm gonna send it to you
okay great we need to take a
break when we come back we'll hear
this terrifying
and will will also play ah something
regarding ah
i don't even remember what the original
reference was anymore any other m and
m's agreement adams okay we'll be right
back up in them grimm mc grim
ems you um
they appear out of nowhere as secret
visitors
you're next in place
covers nations and delusions these are the
unknown parts of living with parkinson's disease
parkinson's stories they tell but what stories
they touch only
oh dear the stanford wow
this is supposed to be specific so
gay man i take it down kick
it out oh this is right i
didn't know that it's also it so
specific the writer must be so proud
of this work i mean it's so
very specific that it's rings through let
me tell you something the guy i
you're acting the shit out of it
is the name so you gotta sandstone
salt thank you everybody in parkinson's and
my boy oh it's only terrifying yeah
yeah i didn't know that that was
i didn't know there was mental stuff
associated with parkinson's i didn't ah um
okay it's time to play yeah feature
gonna feel like i'm just looking time
for the feature okay yeah every game
for the p t for the v
this game is
um it's called hey fred schneider what
are you doing ah and attain the
voice of fred schneider from b fifty
twos and it's like you go like
suit kind of started clap hey fred
oh well i hear some people first
of all it's an improv game and
i've been in different cities doing this
game and people do it with different
rhythms really say that right now but
where i grew up we played like
this hey fred schneider what are you
doing and then you deal with your
voice joy chechens i'm firing day with
a big he went yeah you could
say words that actually mean okay so
you exam frying an egg with a
big way
ah
and what's the how do we you
just try to keep going how we
win you wow win
layers there i don't even know that
it's a good feature because i don't
know that there's a win and also
we might have to switch to one
of our features that someone suggests russian
writer what are you doing you come
to be night
let's just try it okay just a
second and we can we just say
just say random things yeah what's what
was fred schneider hey okay
okay fred schneider what are you doing
i get started okay granny alright hey
fred schneider why are you doing try
to get my cd bumped up to
first class hey fred schneider what are
you doing waiting for my silent friends
to come to me at ny hey
fred schneider what are you doing brushing
my
extensive away collection hey fred schneider what
are you doing throwing a watch against
playground equipment hey fred schneider why are
you doing going in walking all around
the mo schneider like are you doing
i'm begging a good for
a homeless man okay fred schneider wow
i feel like i have to sleep
so please shut up hey fred schneider
what are you doing watching dvd commentary
fight club hey fred schneider what are
you doing i'm sending fan mail to
judge
jody hey
are you doing it christmas time christmas
why not gay for snyder what are
you doing i'm at the genius bar
trying to get someone to talk to
me hey fred schneider what are you
doing i'm cleaning the stains out of
my underpants hey fred schneider what are
you doing
i am falling and i won't get
ah hey fred schneider what are you
doing trying to cover up a murder
i come in have a new fridge
know what are you doing drinking maple
syrup out of a pepsi can
oh hi you doing i'm climbing the
wall with a braided rope hey fred
schneider why are you doing looking under
cable cars or some gold okay schneider
what are you doing i'm in the
spider exhibit trying to get it so
i can power spiderman hey schneider
what are you doing hanging out with
thirty bus ride hello does the sweetest
the swedish rail are on comedy bang
bang based on that yeah you should
do fred chandra on comedy bang me
by the way this is my show
okay so here's a comedy bang bang
or this one this one oh you're
all my bad cells oh you want
to play another game okay okay well
we well pause for a second we
have a million suggestions secret visitors the
plots are unfolding okay i found one
okay so this ah this
from
this comes to us by the way
somewhere we we put out a call
for people to send us games to
play this comes to us from tom
lum l u m aka tom lum
person on twitter and he says
he says ah he suggests a a
feature called halo there too people have
a conversation but one person has to
increase their pitch each sentence the other
lower the losers whomever the third person
cannot understand first alright so thank you
so that's hello there so let's
play it so i'll be the judge
first of all and you guys still
are high and who's going low
i guess i'll go high i'll go
low when i go high oh yeah
so the optimist council obama game
let's call it shallow when they go
low we go high um do you
guys start on a on on the
same frequency or are neutral trail okay
just when you're talking you're just talking
yes okay but not at the same
time no certainly no conversation okay
so what are your plans for your
birthday to berbers while i was going
to go out to a restaurant with
friends it's a really good idea i
feel like um i know a few
good places like recommend i'd love to
hear those recommendations well i could tell
you about you started way too low
already
um there's a great place called sugar
fish not in the old theater it's
also shit because i don't think that
everyone of my party eats sushi will
there will be a problem because you
will do they will don't have any
other options nigger i think like a
land lubber plate
no
okay
lauren you've lost you lost and i
go high you go you go ahead
i'll go okay i know i was
exactly the same for the most of
that
do you like roller coasters okay so
that's oh wait you're sorry you started
high do you like roller coasters i
do yes that's great i like them
too no i don't actually online oh
you didn't even go higher
i'm going incrementally here because i was
so fucking really small increments
i left a smile land anchor of
it
i can't wait to play this okay
well you guys played twice in a
row so i don't not getting a
joke you okay it's your turn i
can if you don't like roller coasters
what amusement park rides do you like
i like to talk to the characters
so you're saying you just go up
to the characters start a conversation yeah
like like i'll get there i
for like like take a picture with
them
which is your favorite or both
ah maybe
ooh nah paul sorry you're out
they'll leave it going with you is
too hard unless you guys started entire
yeah ok you'll do it genius you
gave see the problem is is as
you can only go what if you
go high when the starting line but
yeah anyway that's exactly what i was
gonna say start the first point lost
or just hiding around firsthand and then
you just work the other way back
yeah
instead of starting neutral do you immune
me do it me yeah ok i'll
go the jody want to start all
i'm gonna start as high as i
can i'll start as low as i
can
okay and you're gonna be the judge
but you're so you're going hire yeah
and you're going lower alright
well i can understand you
that's one of the few states that
i know of no to cheating cheating
cheating is cheating just covering the thing
i was i was just like oh
maybe you should try it some time
it seems really neat
i have always wondered if it would
be a fun place
to take a cruise to i'm sure
it would be it would be very
cool to take a cruise there and
see the whales have you ever been
on a cruise no i haven't been
on a cruise actually yes i have
i went to hawaii on a cruise
and i hated it i've only been
on one cruise tom hahaha i've been
on tom cruise too it was the
best sex of my day
wait which day was this thursday
oh okay i had sex with him
on friday ha how funny thursday of
two thousand and two oh okay mine
was friday of two thousand and twelve
why did we both talk like it
was currently well i don't know why
we would do something like this or
who's plateaued
the problem is everything what is the
problem you can owe me you can
only make your voice so i mean
you only make it worse so higher
so low right but it's easier to
be indistinguishable if you get really high
yeah get really low because if you
run you get you you hit a
bottom where you can't make
yeah but i feel like i feel
like lauren went all the way down
way quicker than i'd want to raise
lowers so i guess it's not it's
not it's not know if if your
voices in this is indistinct indecipherable it's
just if when do you when do
you yeah when do you max out
so who has really fun no it's
not this
you saw any of this been fun
i think it's been fun for the
listeners i i is one guy mom
guy he's having a ball this guy's
getting his cheerio he's fucking bringing all
this work did you see the documentary
the evil genius so yeah like i
dad
the one point is that when she's
talking to when she's in jail and
she's saying he's getting his cheerios she's
i never heard that i might be
weird but i must say she's crazy
and you think she's crazy so you
buy the hype yeah i guess i
do think she was a genius by
the way i thought she would be
whose gene name sounds so
one's in jail and someone's barbara bush
this is a woman who like i
don't know china years ago so don't
know what this is but a basically
this man walked into a bank with
a bomb strapped around his neck and
he died his head blew up when
it finally went up so they found
this woman to be the cause and
there's a whole documentary meaning she strapped
it around his neck and blue
sue him up she said that the
bomb and she she's suicides plans or
she i guess she masterminded this plan
yeah i mean she's evil but i
think it's genius i think it's just
disturbing yeah i don't like yeah horrifying
no she's not a genius it's just
fucked up that anyone would think of
this i mean yeah it's inventive i
guess yes she's crazy
native you just created she has followed
through this evil creative intuitive vnus yeah
hey the games weren't the forest gumption
no we decided i'm glad that we
tried it for assumption as gumption absolutely
as a thing that's my main personality
trait like if his name had been
forrest gump get forest gumption what i'm
gonna do i'm being
try to bluff that ah yeah i've
seen forrest gump i've seen it i'm
first camp and now run as far
as these braces will carry me my
dear good woman here i'm forrest gump
i'm maiden um okay hello i'm forrest
gump very nice my forest that was
my life for
it was my forest
i don't want my cookie oh our
lord that was schakowsky um is it
time no it's nice on a shirt
know what is not assured what does
everything shirt might greet visitors which visitors
come to me
the blessed illuminati have come to give
me instructions which i will then parlay
into action the plots unfold what is
not a shirt in the choose your
own adventure of the mind i have
chosen anarchy
i receive you love a bit so
much for enjoying
i could do this all day god
is really having a great time
ah alright we should call it but
ah type of ted yes one ten
p
if you by the way if you
are sinking up ah you're trying to
listen to this at the exact time
of day that we get squatted it
that's when you need to know a
clock face because yes clocks and hospitals
i don't think they're i think look
i get all my oxy hospitals or
television can i just say they always
look
at a clog with a regular old
glock face something i think is funny
about what's happening right now is that
we're like petering out but we're about
to do a whole nother hour right
after yeah we're only good as if
we're going like round know what else
to say we're only peter i'm gonna
kick it back up with a whole
new we're only figuring out because we
because we ran out of steam on
the features the game
yeah but yeah the thing broke my
heart this is what i love about
threesome and because it's like the hanukkah
of podcasts with it seemed like we
only had barely enough energy for one
episode weight but the miracle is we're
going to have it for another pull
it out of ourselves kevin has an
idea that we should do the hi-low
game but just saying i like parties
not okay so
sentence all right let's try though not
like improv you and me alright here
we go okay should we should we
start on let's let's do that i
have started the same
the same point okay and he's and
okay okay i like chartier i like
party i like charter like i like
parties like birthdays like parties
guys
jesus we'll see you next time love
ya bye i love you
oh boo parties come to me they
told me to give me their simple
instructions parties i am malleable enough to
interpret them as they wish i like
parties
right but
a
this has been an year with production
executive produced by scott ackerman chris bannon
and colin anderson for more information and
content visit airwolf dot com