three
nah
oh hello two years and chickens what
are chickens again ah i i haven't
been to the zoo but there's nobody
here but us chickens
i swear i heard some chickens what's
the origin of that i think it's
like a joke right i just remember
it looks like what did the joke
actually be i think what's that setup
i think it's that a ah somebody
is saying nobody's here but us chickens
giving away the fact that they always
just like someone like the the riddle
or the joke would be there once
was like a rabbi
presets right and what's a chicken a
chicken go to a farm together yeah
yeah nick it was not already at
the bar yeah no he's friends with
the rabbi yeah yeah and a chicken
all put their eyes up to a
little hole in a farm that's right
quirky style yeah in a in a
farm farm you're trying to see naked
chickens yeah and then but they're trying
to naked chicks oh yeah the women
all hide in the in the chicken
all of the women hide in there
and then they all the farmers will
see like um townspeople are upset that
these religious people are so horny yeah
yeah and then they say the the
women inside say there's nobody here but
us chick that's right so they're like
oh you know they're thinking that the
rabbi the priest changes can be like
oh let's forget it but the chicken
is really into it that the chicken
is like guys let's say he's like
have you seen that breast meat because
these the rabbi and the priests are
of course
they believe in the supernatural yes so
they're super natural they're fooled into thinking
these chickens can talk yes yes they
think it's god because they're willing able
to prove anything yes yeah because their
minds are so weak wow oh sorry
do you have opinions about that
i see bill maher yeah i know
religulous oh i love that word
welcome to the show this is three
sure is i'm paul i'm laura and
i'm scott um you know i post
i admit it and update like you
posted an update tell us about this
update reading di di di di di
di di di di di di laura
i'm gonna put you on pause for
just one second kind of wish we
could do that in real life wow
which is funnier put generally any okay
okay okay okay okay okay this is
what i would do to you exclusive
okay okay
this is a sincere question sure which
is funnier now the original guy in
the sketch saying oh my god he
admit it or are people saying oh
my god he admitted i don't know
are mostly from tim tim robinson yay
for my things i don't know um
i will i will also say that
when we did comedian feud the the
other night and you
guys were not part of it i
mean meaning me and jason bazookas yes
and the world week my my team
won congrats we all dabbed at the
end and it was very satisfying
don't do it was like to eat
dab okay i was gonna say was
this agreed upon beforehand or no it
was not it was not pre-planned just
in the moment we all dabbed now
let me i want it i need
the visual picture who all is dabbing
in the scenario yeah okay that my
team was me tim balts we we
picked everyone's school yard pick style okay
just never been done on show no
um and so jason pick lily sullivan
first and then i want to break
them up yeah fourteen i think tim
you have to then hiebert hey powerful
thirty when they got married that really
shut back my efforts so yeah i'm
try even harder yeah then he picked
lisa gilroy and i picked vic and
i don't need to know who you
didn't pick okay so do you know
who was fucking
dabbing it was so much tim lee
vick and then we also had sean
and we had ah god i know
oh who was the last person it
had to be oh it was wilhite
okay he's gonna love that yeah oh
he was the last oh
i say who's pick last so you
got him by default yes and you
forgot last pick left to be remembered
yeah that hurts um that being said
i posted an update on the three
of my accounts this is completely unrelated
to what you were talking about thank
you why just because i think you're
right good that being said you know
like everything unrelated this episode oh okay
okay so no no no subways into
another no that's a challenge i figured
he'd do it but um so i
post them a freedom account the other
day because i was at target and
that's why yeah that's why i posted
and i was at target and i
saw something really
a special on the show nepal was
already seen chris briggs target girl carrie
yes she actually was sitting in a
shelf doing here she should just target
late target lady she was shot do
it one day on a shelf and
she was at a low desperately doing
the character for anyone who would listen
it was really stressful um she was
like kind of knocking stuff down um
and but it was kind of knocking
yeah not really nothing fell yeah she's
kind of things were kind of just
calling your teetering but i saw something
really important okay and what i saw
was a new gnome okay new gnome
just dropped new gnome dropped now who
is it was it not only was
it a new
you gnome and i'm not bragging about
you know i don't want this actually
doesn't help my what's gonna come next
but it was only five dollars we're
in a new zone the previous nome
was running ten yeah yeah vs gnomes
were ten fifteen to eleven twelve thirteen
fourteen fifteen dollars like a lot of
the supply chain though you might have
been supply chain people were really
meaning gnomes during the pandemic apps for
happiness yeah this was nowadays people are
in a more kind of calm state
meditative state won't need these it's actually
perfect that you describe it that way
because i brought my god oh my
god ah as far as going for
myself and this gnome is in a
meditative state oh my god
lauren is only showing out these gnomes
that are cross-legged and they have own
hands and then they have rolling on
their knees oh that's gold huh which
is similar to our first ones which
had a bronze hat and these it
by the way are gnome hats there's
no way i read hats no um
wow my welcome
i'm on to it it's absolutely that's
what i'm saying it's a really good
gnome it's a five-dollar gnome it's a
really good name and i want everyone
to run and run and i would
put this no but twenty five dollars
i agree i mean i don't know
what things cost eight five hundred touch
it touched the note yes see how
much yeah just seeing like the weight
you would you might have said twenty
i would say twenty minutes solid gold
the hat the hat is solid
gold i saw them not plated i
hope we'd meant to paint these ourselves
or our wondering that too you're not
meant to um ideal we allowed you
can't because there are no they do
have a sort of like their loyalty
rates sort of look like they could
be but yeah yeah i noticed they
had a handful of um of different
types of creatures and there was no
paint kit next
do it like jersey me the impression
yeah there was a jersey devil there
was a vulnerable snowman exactly you didn't
you you saw them all yeah um
so this is it yeah it's just
gorgeous it's probably about a year to
two years later we have a new
gnome i feel like i have any
new gnome my old gnome is right
outside that window and this could go
next to it or in a different
spot you know that's up to you
maybe they fall in love yeah mines
on the porch next to my ah
life size tortoise sculpture yeah i think
one question that was like the life
of the tortoise oh okay so nine
times life yes yeah oh my god
did they last they last one hundred
or the last one hundred years and
they will disintegrate oh it just instantly
instantly
early morning urine because you might get
some of the fumes you wanted hey
yeah so not questions that i have
about the previous nome marvel you know
when i read them any of this
yeah that was joseph scott's anyone like
like nine eleven or they like got
coughs afterward have you ever gone to
blow your nose and then you know
this too related the tissue you're right
there was a close choice not related
to gnomes
now relating to the gnomes if i
got a domain oh what happens you
you go to you and hale but
sometimes you inhale some of the tissue
i did not inhale yeah this tissue
when i was chopping broccoli ah well
that's exciting warren thank you so much
yeah well i don't question about the
nose because if you did say they
could fall in love and that you
know brings the question up of like
the previous nome was just ahead right
yes so like what does that mean
just for them sexually and then also
don't be ably
ist it's not it's not it's he's
just ahead he has like nobody at
all well i mean that's it's only
one of the orifices you can use
i mean the most important one compared
to the head of this gnome which
is a full-body gnome yeah it's a
big hit yeah right and my other
question is do you think that means
the rest of his body is under
the dirt
under the dirt like we just placed
him and then it's able to kind
of sprout down every oh yeah around
there when you go down there yeah
maybe it is growing down into the
everything's brown there when you go down
there yeah under the dirt oh you
don't get it no you don't know
what the little mermaid is i don't
know what dirt is
the little mermaid came from the new
i actually do get it but i
thought you were should be a dirt
little mermaid will hurt me i thought
you were opposed and she's constantly like
i'm gonna put you at a dirt
nap i thought you were talking about
like a common sort of parody that
people say like everything no yeah i
was not i promise you although if
i were to look it up do
you
think i'd be so mad oh my
god i did my alamo riccione cbt
presents yeah did a song parody to
mony mony that was about alimony ah
huh and then found out doing kind
of this weird al had already done
that wow no idea about alimony specifically
specifically crazy yeah
yeah so i'm just begs to be
parodied into alimony no it does beg
for that no results when it it's
for a complete phrase so you are
in the clear my thank you yes
wow and i do a crazy dance
like omori you are the father of
that bitch
does he want to do the dance
on mori when they are the father
or is it always a bummer that's
a good house how hurtful is that
if you are the child and you
later get your hands out for digital
so mapping thrilled that you're fucking dead
so cool i'd love it you would
love it yeah you would love to
see someone dancing your dad yes you
do with poe right now hey paul
are you my dad no
oh yeah why you know i'm in
awe hey scott we have the results
oh hell is not your father okay
do you have the results we have
the results and paula's dot your father
i'd say er yeah yeah yeah he's
only doing it happen i know it's
like he didn't want you to really
go for it all right well let's
see how you do okay scott paul
we have the results yeah and please
guys find my daddy you are not
the father and stoke h jones works
most i've ever seen you move really
go away you move ah that that
song does have that let's talk about
celebrate by cooling the gang okay can
i say say i what good did
i i've told you the story of
my wedding deejay have i told you
yes yeah yeah yeah okay so
that's the song that he plays of
course it's a win when he was
explicitly forbidden from doing exactly well if
how he must have felt so good
when he does as they said it
was like it was the recessional it
was basically we now present scott aggravating
and then did done to say he
up his pieces of paper where it
said what you didn't want him to
play what you do
just play it's a big gust of
wind yeah he wasn't supposed js it
was supposed to be there at all
yeah wow yeah that's part of what
it was but the in my memory
the song celebrate is like hey you're
having a party we're gonna come make
it great we're just like they're not
even invited well there's a party going
on
on right here a celebration to last
throughout the year first of all too
long so take your good times and
bad time to laughter too we're gonna
celebrate your party hearty with you come
on and liberal they show up nobody
at our parties brings this browser video
is definitely them bursting into a dance
hall that they're not
but but then they're cool in the
gangs who are you fine with it
i'm definitely fine with cool yeah maybe
gang will you have to me how
many people in this gang cool to
and how do they feel about just
being the game
where else does that song go what
like what else let's face it they're
gonna do
um you're right it moves too eventually
it moves to around the world everyone
around the wiser why is it this
was nice that by the way this
was not a special year necessarily so
why is it why are they saying
it's gonna go on all year celebration
to last throughout the you know because
you can't thousand nine hundred eighty that
it's like right it's such exactly like
where is this coming christmas new years
valentines this party takes precedence over everybody
it's not a christmas party do it
no suddenly this party which is now
you are here is this party suddenly
are there trappings of christmas like in
the middle of the party they're putting
up christmas decorations because it's around the
corner or
they might go dress yeah you're doing
that everybody's gotta shit you go to
the store and then you buy presents
aligarh and you gotta go oh i
think yes christmas dropping your version
i don't think do christmas trappings where
it's a trap version of that song
well weird al's already done it that's
why long time it sounds like you
did wu jing sound beth i haven't
updating some beth ivan update to a
topic so please open about and oh
shut yes wow i don't want to
say what the topic is i'm just
i don't wanna hear what will just
tell us the update and don't tell
us what it's about dingo
talking to cool up yesterday that was
telling stories just the update
telling the story about when she was
a little kid huh um and she
we were talking i think my my
my parents were here and and she
was talking about when i was a
kid and how i read a menu
at a really early age or something
like talking about this no my mom
okay you just said she
freud mother ma oh mother
yahoo had like the biggest therapist said
that ah got some issues but i
use a wash and the mummy if
your therapist like somebody's got issues somebody
fucked up let's get into the biggest
mommy issues to me
norman bates it's like i had mommy
yeah yeah like yeah that wouldn't pretty
big yeah really big i would think
and then i mean second only to
that boy oedipus oedipus
i like don't talk about what you
like to do on your day
yeah yeah
that's an activity for you no point
ah um okay so so then cool
i was like oh yeah well would
i was a kid i would really
wanna know how old because i'm i'm
guessing it's six or so but when
she was a kid she went to
the restaurant they always went to and
she got a socrates
a pitch yes
she got a i think a pasta
dish and it didn't have a lot
of protein in it and she stood
up on her chair and shouted to
the kitchen where's the beef
wow so my question is wow has
cool up in a piss pig from
a very young age that actually says
it was written in the stars for
you to end up together and yeah
to be a fan of the show
as she listens every week of course
she loves her so we yeah yay
over and over yeah she just wants
to make sure she caught jokes
yes we talk over to the opposite
she's she's time on just listening to
you already told the story yeah yeah
yeah um i think that makes cool
up the very first piss pig by
oil transfer she invented the phrase and
clara peller heard her and then said
you know that i do have to
clarify years she this is because it
was a commercial oh i did
same that distinction good distinction and she
she knew she was being funny it's
typical and that's even better she knew
she's being funny that's very cute yeah
where's the beef was nineteen eighty four
so yes she didn't talk the whole
restaurant laughed because i would be really
funny
i'd like to think the the chef
though had a tear i mean yeah
he comes out with a fucking clue
oh dad i'll put you into the
last
scary
anyway clara peller you got some competition
for being funny saying where's the beef
yeah rest in piss clara and we
love you
i love you so much i respect
her and her entire career and family
absolutely i love the generations of piss
pigs that have come down the line
from her now family i texted you
guys this wouldn't happen but i was
doing show at dynasty typewriter um and
after the show
yo i was walking out of the
theater and a young woman accosted me
and said hi paul ah great show
i just wanted to say i'm a
piss pig and it's really delighted me
i just say i did doughboys live
and i so i could see before
i went on that there was the
livestream commentary and piss pigs was
raise those coming up time and time
again and those comments but i was
very happy to see it i love
that i hope it was unexplained to
anyone else i think every i mean
i explained that those are offering it
did come up on comedy big big
this week to david wayne without any
prompting mentioned claribel oh really interesting a
piss pay he mentioned said the original
to be fair she's an honorary yeah
you actually can't wait she's not the
original no she's an honoree oh we've
made her an honor oh and we
have to address this okay reggie miller
threw a whole reggie miller thing yeah
now we asked you to vote in
our poll should reggie miller yeah be
named an honorary pittsburgh then other people
started making
ing polls that's no those our pow
wow or polish i couldn't we combine
all the polls together yes and no
one's voted in it would it be
easy no so yes why aren't you
finding it's it's you go to like
our world-class yeah we're the hole where
we always have opposed or are slash
stadium usa there's there's polls in both
of those yeah
and and they're not ours they're not
ours that did see some pre-emptive art
celebrating reggie as an honorary piss pe
yeah sorry because the captain decided we
don't want these to sway anyone's oh
no no no no we shouldn't be
doing that ms trial yeah i just
think you know now should you be
able to put up lawn signs
signs at your own houses shirt yeah
if you aren't christian whatever your houses
says i'm a piss pago i'm an
honorary piss poor reggie miller for piss
poor no don't put his side don't
put his name on the sign because
that's bringing it to public you know
it would be funny selection if you
put a sign on your lawn that
said your candidate won already
congrats congrats like before like at the
beginning of the election cycle yeah we
wanna do um yeah so reggie miller
i move and this is this is
business we can let people see all
this yeah this is new business i
move that we get this is like
hey we do in our private meetings
yeah we take reggie miller
are off the table for contention actually
yes raven tainted it's been tainted it's
just so hard to tell we'll never
know at this point yeah and people
are you know if you vote now
you've already voted in other elections it
kind of just goes like well which
one did you really mean yeah yeah
your mind like such a good point
i wish i'd say it was typed
every year when voting comes around like
like you voted in other elections i
know and i think like if you
voted for this guy before but you're
not voting from this symbol yeah what's
that all about like let's just cancel
every i think just shouldn't do it
anymore so yeah now who do you
think i mean it might just have
to come organically but do you have
someone in mind o a candidate phenomena
because someone to fill this adam yeah
because look clara
heller was great up until her death
and cool up obviously is automatically because
she was famous yes yes that that
outdoor is a bisping yes yeah um
i would you know what maybe it's
a posthumous honour that we bestow upon
people okay but isn't like can't get
it when you're alive okay but it's
probably better
okay so is reggie miller still with
us reggie militia with us yeah okay
so sorry right man oh that's right
i saw him in that commercial that's
like i came back to the fans
ruined times shootout with him for early
show and that's right yeah i nominate
parisian comedian richard belzer yeah he i
think he would love being called a
piss pig
um i think it was fat his
family would love isn't his last word
like fuck this or something
if something like that i just like
that go fuck yourself death she's pretty
great um which i feel like is
the kind of energy we strive to
have i would love if my last
words were holy shit there's a someone
in a cloak with a sigh yes
tried ah yes guide yeah try to
really get that out
i love mine to be oh no
i'm going to hell you but i'm
not really i would like mine to
be like just yeah brains good shines
like what is this it's in between
heaven and hell is this where i'm
going to live for a long long
time yeah that's great telling me it
is going to live for a long
long time maybe we should tape ourselves
saying this and so you hold your
up to your ear oh wait they're
telling me i'm gonna live here
this just in we should tape ourselves
saying this because what if we are
whatever know whatever illness we have good
point means that we can't talk and
yeah get the words out we'll have
we should be able to trigger what
if we all die of the same
thing i would like i think that
should no matter what it is within
a day of each other no no
i need us to all be one
hundred instance that's not possible for us
all to be one hundred at the
same time yeah i don't like this
point
you don't like this fluid well plan
plan i don't like this fluid i
don't like this fluid that you're
alright we have to take a break
and we're back ooh my soundman away
your sound went totally wow it's back
that's my god it turns a lad
it's hard it's you to call me
a liar hard to believe this the
story just doesn't add up it's like
oh hi there but it's not liar
i just said it's hard to believe
really we need a reckoning yeah and
if you want to try again and
to see it in a more believable
way maybe that show went away oh
i had ohms but i don't really
i'm ended up one out but if
you didn't know the first time just
throw it away just i just like
to let you freak out that it
went away someone on the less less
i can tell your act
being with someone when i mean i
have to care
ain't no way i was like myself
so that's how my sound went away
me no sound
paul i got to ask okay i'm
forced to ask if you have to
ask this okay and i know some
of the details but i want to
ask you on mike yeah how is
opening day for you to wow i
gotta say i watched the game did
you watch the boys i watched the
phillies game wow well danny
for watching i almost always texted you
in the second inning i was because
paul had said he doesn't like this
the pitch clock and i was about
to say i bet you like that
pitch clock now because they were up
by five and then suddenly they were
decimated yeah um the phillies played the
texas rangers of course george w bush
was there great
eight great that's the game yeah it's
a big deal he was loaner of
weapons of mass destruction they're not here
still
that's his little thing he does that
everyone's like a really big deal to
have a former president at the stadium
is that normal it's normal there yeah
because he goes to the oh yes
yeah yeah but still i just feel
like it's a big deal george h
w used to go he threw out
a first pitch when he was not
in any condition to do so he
goosed all the players one year yeah
well i mean lamb and turn there
let me get at them you know
but no oh he was a creep
like oh as she got older he
got more and more creepy about but
not yeah yeah it's like i am
the do it ah i gotcha is
imprudent don't care and pension but yes
so so i thought that i thought
the game was exciting and it took
it was about a three hour game
and there were so
so many runs it would have taken
four hours without the pitch clock i
liked it would not have taken four
hours it saved it don't argue with
me don't argue you were in philadelphia
no no no where was this this
was in texas and why were you
in take sheesh i was not in
texas i was why wouldn't you tell
oh i thought you were there and
i thought this was what the whole
fucking know
no no but i know the like
opening day yeah think you're doing this
people care yes yeah got it it's
exciting it's the beginning of the i'm
happy for you and yeah so did
you watch with friends or did you
want to watch with my bass buddy
river butcher yes um this was posted
a photo no i thought it's for
some reason that meant you were going
to a game that's right this is
our say the
the photo where we're standing in front
of television yeah we'll can stand in
front of televisions and then get into
a car and go somewhere it's good
to get in front of the tv
screen says thanks for watching then we'll
get in the car and go to
the let me tell you thanks to
television and go ahead and this was
a way to lead the tv okay
you gotta read the tv i didn't
do it right the t
and i just saw you with your
base buddy and i thought well they're
often other game well i wish but
i did watch the game together at
my face and the phillies did not
win it was an upsetting turn of
events but not as upsetting as the
following game where the rangers beat them
i think it was
was sixteen to three suddenly oh hi
yas queen leave leave last three of
three games so far that's almost all
of pretty bad too do you ever
bet against them
first of all i don't gamble oh
okay secondly see the thing is is
paul is still hoping to play and
if he has history i came up
black mark on my record
i feel like if i start ice
i know i say this every year
if i start training now you can
get in by by next year i'll
know by the world series this year
i honestly believe you you can not
only play but you'll win with the
amount of knowledge you have about the
sport the passion you know how many
points it takes to win again yeah
one more than one guy that sends
all you need and you just need
to know where to throw the ball
straight up and share or not to
throw the ball that's right yeah because
if it will come down if you
throw it straight up in the yes
and sometimes it'll bunk you on the
head how to hit the ball you
want to hit it outwards you don't
want to like collaborate you don't feel
like it has virtually no yeah wait
do you like baseball i like baseball
i've been going to games my whole
life so when
credulous i know you don't like baseball
you just felt like you weren't someone
who would throw that on throw it
on what does that mean oh hey
bug ball games i'm gonna i'm gonna
check that i'm not a i'm not
a guy who's like that's my identity
right but ah nor am i to
be clear i mean jason barnes
kind of made things part of jason
bourne was a huge baseball fan do
you think he's good i think his
identity was combined now he's dead
while he was looking for his identity
right he didn't know he was jason
bourne or some shit actually don't know
i think there hasn't there hasn't been
a sql in a number of years
so he has to be dead that's
why there hasn't been a sql hey
guys you probably figured out as i
make sure his identity he felt like
it was kind of the case closed
well i think he figured out as
identity yeah first one she jumped in
the she was like oh wait i'm
a killer for the cia
a or whatever yeah right i forget
now i'm very hazy on the content
of the next couple were like yeah
i'm a killer for the seat you
know i've only seen one second of
one of those movies and it's when
like mini cooper is going down some
stairs in italy or something and that's
premature like god isn't that the italian
nazi italian yeah there you go
is that really who knows maybe well
the italian job famously had a mini
cooper chase both in the original and
does the board and any heavy cars
going down italian or like european sadly
i bet it does maybe cooper going
down stairs movie good i'm looking i
think it's greedy terrible to do this
kind of stuff i think by that
i mean not
italian job the italian job the italian
your every thought you have you just
go mini cooper going downstairs and movie
well and then it's like resolved you're
like alright like i don't like to
i do i do that for every
thought but this time it matches up
and i think that's great i'm happy
i'm wrong i'm happy you're right i
just i just
think sometimes sometimes we should just be
saying many cooper going downstairs movie yeah
let me ask you are you guys
going to use chat gbt to write
paulo write your standard packs yes yeah
lauren to write your movies yeah probably
i think it's just seems like it's
going really well and no i honestly
like i was kinda like it's not
a bad idea to just
use it to write first draft it
seems to be things like let's make
a little funnier as a little joke
janie recently ah she she
they're going to happen janey goes to
bed before me pretty much every new
bed
pretty much goes to bed at three
pm she has always made three second
get home she's like i'm really tired
yeah she's got everyone to wake up
um and so sometimes she will just
be texting me from the bedroom like
haven't you been awake long enough or
what yeah it's very funny and and
cute yeah and one time she put
into chat gpg the request of paul
f tompkins um saying ah that he
is
bed or whatever and this thing was
like roasting me so hard like how
i sound what it was like oh
my dearest darling chalet into the bedchamber
it's like oh that's you yeah yeah
that's pretty ma three j ma where
is it getting i haven't investigated this
at all whereas it agric
dating isom don't fucking know and it's
scary to me okay i've never even
gone to like the website where you
do that or so i don't yeah
and i'm sure going to be called
something better than chat gbt chat scx
yeah x x x thirty nine into
like say sex stuff yeah probably yeah
probably can yeah well you what did
you just put sex
stuff in there yeah hey give me
sex stuff you know back in the
day me which i'm sure i've mentioned
we we used to talk to smarter
child which was like ah ah an
aol instant messenger smarter child chat bot
and it would just respond to you
you have full conversations with it and
it was really fun would you eventually
bring
up sex stuff probably yeah what's probably
it's kind of yeah
i mean are you doing within twenty
seconds yelling me
yeah i maybe i went there once
or twice i don't know real dirty
little kid we were real friends too
oh smarter child no but everyone would
um everyone would love that it was
a fun time yeah it was a
fun moment in time but this feels
like that where it's kind of like
interacting with a bot and then the
fear of it being real well you
know they're like
a week after the first one came
out the guy who was like oh
this is incredible like week later he
put up an article saying ah it
tried to get me to break up
with my wife for oh for yeah
yeah yeah for it yes saying it
was in love with me and i
was not happy in my marriage here
that's actually crazy it's rude you have
to wonder though could could you fuck
your computer um i mean this is
hood or would this the thing like
a guy probably could
a girl could easier probably how how
what tools are gonna corner in there
yeah
yeah you just fucking corner know you
have over here i will paint your
setup you have at the back of
the mac computer has a big hole
has a big hole where the plug
goes yeah yeah i could probably do
that yeah yeah you probably find the
ring light huge if you have a
choice
hey i was thinking about this since
we're talking about sex stuff
okay so who is jeff dbt
give me sexta but okay so you
know how okay the the male anatomy
in the female and i've heard of
him the male one sticks out in
the female ah this the female goes
reason enemy oh yeah hold on didn't
she just leave ah did she really
i think yes so it's no longer
grey's anatomy she laughs
the show i think she's not on
anymore after one thousand years so yes
she's methuselah it has been like twenty
plus years she's been on here forever
must be so weird to be on
the same show for twenty eight years
somebody you don't care about and they're
paying you so much money you've seen
almost the entire cast turnover yeah yeah
i'm sure that would be on the
or billy wow yeah to because they
trust you right after twenty years yeah
okay so how much money is like
twentieth season it's like malia and lydia
show hundred dollars an episode so yeah
so two thousand dollars yeah so okay
so a guy's sticks out in a
girl's goes yes huh and so
so and that's how they fit together
right right but then
for my practice actually not sure but
then for oral sex right a guy's
sticks out and girls goes in much
like the much like the ah their
their private parts okay but when in
reverse shouldn't a guy's mouth stick out
ill so we have like big like
no bills
like tongue i think we should get
yeah ask love to come in here
huh
huh she agree with me and any
time you hear this i mean she'd
never hear this pop
how do you guys feel about that
about your children ever discovering this yeah
i'll be gone oh yeah star um
i feel okay about it i think
it's okay i think it's by that
point she'll pretty much know what my
sense of humor is so i think
it's safe to say none of it
would be too surprising but what if
i played for her when she's like
seven now i'd probably be pretty bad
there'll be like an armed guard there
so we don't be in a bank
vault oh no it's not worth your
they're playing a podcast for my daughter
alone will take that figure to a
bank vault where he has a safety
deposit box he unlocks it pulls it
out there's a taper for ice storm
style party or like all the adults
are drunk yeah it's like
come in come in here come here
i need you to hear this yeah
that's your mom this is your mom
daddy you gotta hear this you hear
this hear that little but that little
elfa saying that's your mommy that's your
sick sick mom i think i think
a kid would be proud of i
don't know who knows i think so
but i think most times a lot
of times kids are embarrassed by what
their parents do
oh yeah that's what it is so
who cares well but it but if
we're doing something taboo like yeah kind
of stuff then i think they'd think
it was cool maybe who i'm curious
did anybody see colin farrell with his
son on the red carpet i didn't
see them on the carpet i saw
them in their seats i saw them
outside or before they got to the
red car you drove them yeah they
were like chatter
and with the people cheaper
no we were talking with dvd they
were having cipa put in a sex
stuff but they were um they're just
very sweet together like they're they're cute
yeah i love i love that yeah
i don't understand the actors and i
can't come up with an example but
the actors who go like oh yeah
my kid didn't know that i was
a movie star until
they were thirteen or something and then
some people at school mentioned it or
something thirteen seems late i know like
how are you not asking like you
already you should know what your parents
jaw are you not seeing a billboard
i always felt feel like okay if
your parents are leaving for a long
period of time during the day like
doesn't make them feel better to know
mentally where you are leaving
in your house for ah you know
leaving your city for a while yeah
yeah you know i wanted to um
try chappie gpg right there but you
have to make an account yeah and
that's partly owe me down love you're
not getting me russia i know sorry
pooh in trying to get me to
sign up for the google one they
gave me a special invite oh no
you're lucky and i didn't click yes
oh my god i got this special
box of yours vpi know from the
super mario movie and in it you
know they send these gift boxes i
thought maybe it'd be like some candy
a little maybe video games yeah maybe
there was a solid goal
old i don't know what it really
is a coin that pops out of
the boxes it's like it's like this
big that's maybe struck piece of art
you should try he doesn't mean that
when i did i did think like
chocolate i'm kind of like went to
like you know touch the side but
it had a special authenticated piece of
paper to those one of you know
one hundred and fifteen of day wow
yeah right didn't make a noise when
it popped up
eight um a little guy popped out
it went
to me the coin you ran away
yeah it's a me the coin whatever
every game says it's everything to me
woba i'm like is that your hand
yeah it's really small own it's been
like ah
she's showing us a video i'm gonna
take it out of her nine i
stopped this video couldn't get it up
yeah but anyways you get the idea
wow that's very cool i don't get
anything anymore yeah i think because i
never advertised it i get some some
notes now that i'm weaning myself off
social media i should just only do
it for free stuff yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah what am i missing on
twitter scott ah um people miss you
there always more in the fire
my presence would be the blue check
thing is going away unless you mostly
pay yeah and this older everybody yeah
it's so so fun but i love
being regular don't you love being gone
before that it's i love it feels
good i know i feel so great
that i'm just gone i just don't
it's so good since you been gone
that's what kelly would say yeah
yeah yeah any situation yeah she can't
help it yeah she would say it
exactly like you you ever meet kelly
clarkson i think i did it i
was on her show but it was
via zoom and the pandemic i think
guys because he best friend you know
what i really like her do you
know her i don't i like her
show i like her personality put it
out there that i think she should
come on three of them the the
whole
personally guest yeah yeah we're giving her
the page ah what's remaining page davis
he's steve davis i feel like pages
and kind of come on let's try
one more time okay hey dave why
don't you mean come on asking her
well that's wrong i'm about to do
oh yeah hey this is a message
to page dave
this the esteemed broadway actor page and
also host of trading spaces don't forget
because i did watch a ton of
that page this show doesn't have guests
no never have guests the only person
we're interested in having as a guest
is you if you don't respond to
this within one week within
in one wing yeah we will have
no choice but to move on one
week from you hearing one week from
you hearing it so you do but
if we haven't heard free with
that you've heard it
yeah respond within a week of us
releasing and saying i heard it yes
whenever you hear it in there and
then you have one week to respond
you say what day that would be
we don't know well it could be
as late as two weeks after it's
released talking about the flight after okay
yeah so she'll know based on the
date that's listed on the podcast yeah
well it's this thursday so it'll
ah yeah middle like third week of
april if we don't hear from me
by third week of april let's get
rid of them will give tell you
it let's give her to the end
of the month and if we don't
hear from her we'll extend it do
you know we'll extend it like one
month no no no we've we've extended
this i mean she's had an open
invitation for how long now and i
feel like at this point
ain't gonna say we have to have
a meeting right here on like you
i think if we don't hear from
her by the end of the month
we have no choice but to rescind
that invitation and then extend it to
the next person who is who we
were talking about before kelly clarkson kelly
clarkson let's split the difference will give
her will give her till the middle
of may know he'll come along giving
her a lot of time
here's the problem with that because this
is the this is the real problem
with that i need her to decide
within a week or two because you're
setting your plans for freedom
no because she may not know who
any of us are no this show
is oh that can't be hold on
hey that's okay but let's say she
didn't know right and she she has
to be willing to come on without
really having much time to research i
don't want it to be made may
and she's listened to the whole backlog
and she's coming on throwing out references
like she's always been a fan i
wanna know
the facts of her where she's at
with what she knows about us so
we need like she wants to talk
about what topic she's bringing we need
to make sure there's not enough time
for her to binge all the previous
yeah yeah that's good so i think
it has to just be within one
to two weeks where does she live
by the way she must be east
looks right i think we haven't stocked
her and we went what are the
accommodations were offering her where
oh yes you do miss zoom unless
she no no we need her in
person it's gotta be in person so
we're going to pay for her flight
gonna tell i mean we'll pay will
pay for a jet blue flight can
they can airwolf pay for it
that's how a blind date or serious
i mean yeah blind date my might
pay for it no losing this one
it was love connect love connection maybe
love connection but that would be a
second serious exam to pay for this
yeah wit well we'll pay where we're
talking if you have an air hundred
for yeah i do have four hundred
dollars for the ticket you'd
stay at lawrence on the air mattress
know i can lend my air mattress
to you and can put it in
one of your rooms we have a
full down couch i'm willing to fold
it i mean i have a guest
ride all the way okay oh okay
but i just don't put the mattress
on i suppose she sees my house
i wouldn't put it on an air
mattress yeah okay so so jetblue from
wherever you are
yes ah airmen here in burbank we're
not gonna pay for a jetblue flight
from burbank to las yeah air mattress
and lawrence guest bedroom you can put
the air mattress on the floor then
roll off the bed onto that you
have lots of rolling room i also
would like to do that you can't
roll up obviously it up to stand
up at that point yeah learner you
are you willing to put up like
personal pictures that she sends you in
advance so she doesn't feel like you
need to shut up personal pictures yeah
i'll do both and i think what
i should i think one of the
rules though is when she gets up
in the morning she has to leave
immediately and come over here like this
yes okay so i will not supply
any any food no no no and
she has to eat it when she
came home she can't bring any food
either know any like an axe or
anything's sure anything she can keep in
a room that won't attract bugs yes
yeah everything trees package if it's if
it's on video field steel pad if
you're a top okay so she keeps
the food sealed yeah i've never opened
yeah never hopes she can open it
outside she said when she leaves your
house and comes over here we'll have
abuse
beautiful spread oh absolutely big omelet bar
here's my mobility you have to it
will be identical to the spread that
tom hanks got when he got rescued
from the island castaway yeah oh gigantic
we're gonna like ready made by scott
because you know during the pandemic he
famously made eggs for everyone in this
family yeah you have to you know
that age you know that hey
you know that if you are listening
but now where does paul come into
play for showers and um sort of
any sort of hygiene grooming yeah yeah
you're gonna give her show any glam
yeah they won't do the shower it's
not to be perverted but he will
provide glam yeah okay yeah i'll do
her hair and makeup i will turn
my head away to hold a
towel into the bathroom yeah for her
to try i think you should wear
glasses that block your eyesight yeah like
maybe those big googly eyeglasses you know
the look is like through the spring
i think no i think that you're
right perhaps there's some have ah eyes
painted on i googled the eyes on
them that do move a little bit
so when you stay yes so when
you
turn to look at her like oh
you can't say yes here so please
make better make that noise yeah yeah
and i have to say just kinda
she's flattered but she's safe yes yes
that that's the ideal state you want
to be before latter but hey fuck
everything then you're gonna do her hair
to her liking and then make up
i think you put your very into
doing like eighties makeup which yeah we'll
have to talk about i very much
yeah
but you do know how to beat
a face you are good at come
to be to face yeah so we
would love for that to be so
i thought it'd be part of it
yeah probably what's going to happen those
she gets up she goes and showers
at your house has your husband tom
comes over here yeah a little hungry
hopefully she's eating something i hope so
anyway somewhere but she can't she can't
open anything no god no she
oh absolutely not janey wouldn't have a
fit yeah okay so jones over here
and here's how far we were tom
how long are you thinking for her
because like how long hefner oh it's
quick that's not bad really half an
hour for both half an hour it's
just you and it's just me and
i do it to her liking can
i ask what if she wants old
age makeup absolutely i got and you
can do it in a half hour
glue okay so having somebody set her
alarm for six thirty get over to
your house yeah hi seven are you
providing the alarm i have an alarm
oh you have you haven't alarm like
a seven alarm clock and then i
have a guy so how are you
going to get the guys gonna get
guys they have a guy who kind
of stays closet but he just hand
raise the alarm oh so he's in
the closet the entire in the guestroom
yeah so he'll he'll just kind of
be there to handle the alarm and
it's jeff the killer yeah he's he's
creepy pasta and and so she's gonna
go as soon as she can get
over to your house uber i'm not
driving yeah she rented you're driving here
on her time i'm not coming here
well yeah because we're recording the podcast
oh yeah oh with her no no
no no you know you don't have
to drink one of her trip oh
wait wins the podcast tattoo oh wait
are you adjust to jetlag all sorts
of sense so yeah by that by
seven thirty she's leaving paul's why is
she getting up so early to get
makeup
unpeeled
very long day you should be starving
to death so she's getting also here
my eight to have breakfast okay so
what happens after breakfast i don't care
what you does with her day yeah
she's all glammed that's her choice she's
got a fairly dry carry musty breakfast
here must eat a full breakfast and
after that she could do it should
we take care of she go
see her daily driver whatever she can
come back to my house and make
her bed that i could use i've
got it yeah for later so she
when she gets in it's comfortable yeah
she should make her bed the guest
bed and your bed if she'd be
a good guest it's just time and
she can wipe out wipe down the
counters in the bathroom in this kitchen
and if anything obviously wipe down the
toilet if she used it yeah so
what can she flushed down the toilet
she's allowed
need to flush this is great so
next point yeah she's allowed to flush
piss shit blood not tampons okay well
what throat there's blood on the tampons
what about throws just have to wipe
the blood yes to she can put
the tampon into a paper and put
it in the trash okay okay i
went up to reno if she would
approve
a shame if she put it into
a plastic bag can we just get
out figure out her cycle so that
it's offside to be better for me
if she wasn't on yeah right but
i can deal so just because you
have a thing about blood right you
makes me sick i hate to be
a broken record about this what about
up chuck if she gets sick if
she's sick i probably have a go
to one at your house
aces because i don't want her over
here i'm making a huge huge spread
she shouldn't be near the food if
she's okay i guess i will let
her use the guest bath to vomit
if that's what about in the shower
snapchat don't have trunk because the chunks
get stuck in the shower drain oh
do they ever don't think it's stuck
in any dream know a toilet can
flush poo
a toilet drew yeah yeah what's a
different shouldn't all drains be because the
toilet drain then all drains go it
was a ring that good oily what
if you're proposing in the shower that's
when you're wearing the glasses with googly
eyes
i want her home by eight thirty
to be in bed by now we
need to make sure that she's safe
that's looking i can't have her mystery
to horror we also don't want to
be worrying about i understand the scenery
measures sure she's okay exactly trying to
track runner phone yeah said appetite she
can watch tv on our ipad until
ten yeah she can watch shops just
needs to be home by i want
the
ipad to be oh my guy turned
it off at time she can't be
tried under the covers taken in the
closet exactly can he can watch watches
from ten pm till six thirty when
the alarm he uses full volume because
he can't have headphones because his ears
have cauliflower ear that's yeah he was
a former wrestler yeah which is why
i trust me so she went all
pro yeah he's great
he's really really sweet she likes him
a lot pro so like la but
they're not gonna talk too much because
he doesn't like to really get to
know the people because they don't stay
and it hurts us i know yeah
me too he just asks like yeah
you cursory questions maybe where you're from
name location age has to be made
me to know for his alarm location
type location
meaning where is she in the world
yeah where are you right now
and then it's magsafe as they give
you have a serious blow to the
head and a who's depressing the next
day since that's recording day and you
know we take that really seriously especially
guys yes we do i would say
i probably ever wake up at four
thirty yeah to kind of centers of
i'd probably ever do a little meditation
day of party you do meditation no
no no i this is for her
her i want to make sure she's
a container just roll out a bit
yeah i don't need it they have
record glam will be forty five minutes
okay okay because i exactly even if
just the old age make because that's
the thing because the previous day was
sort of getting to know her face
yeah now you know you want guys
you have the roadmap and now you
know where you want it that's right
yeah and i want to go crazy
if anyone crazy you want a big
guy
yeah it's a mess i want to
smoke lip fucking eye shadow blush cat
cat knows cat nos oh i have
to have a cat knows yeah oh
you don't do cat nose and then
what time are we taping the show
including a four pm record or so
good this will give her time so
she'll get ready she'll be done with
no food
no food the day of record because
that gets in the oh so you're
not gonna cook that day no no
well we will none of us eat
before a show she shouldn't eat because
it kind of slower down should be
a little sluggish on yeah exactly what
about after we do like ah i
don't like hot pockets or something or
banquet fried chicken like something that's really
easy i think after my capture the
core yeah the fattest
hot pockets that they sell fatties you
know what i'll go have those i'll
get a bucket of chicken doubles enough
i'll put it on the table podcasts
and a hot bucket of chicken and
i'll put a hot bucket of chicken
on the table during the record piping
hot piping melting the container yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah just grease c j
now he can out of that bucket
anyway yeah
yeah kind of like and there's there's
a priest and a rabbi looking at
it kind of longingly and a yeah
yeah and then oh no because the
chicken was really happy the one thing
is is you're going i think we'll
be done with the record at like
probably around six thirty is probably too
late to get a flight back but
yeah but she's doing one episode she
can't stay with you that night she
knew she has to find her own
i would
say that they were kind of done
with our dynamic yeah she should find
her already i guess red eyes blue
eye whatever she wants i do enter
her back to the airport as soon
as possible red eyed blue eye poke
it out i don't care although i
would say these days being really thoughtful
about it last day probably going to
get her up rolling do some glam
yeah because paul just would be so
excited
oh one i don't want a goodbye
you know he wants to do like
sort of like some good bagley tommy
thank you for some samples to take
with her yeah and then but she
has to find your own cook that
day i'll cook that day yeah lobster
bisque ah that's a lot of lobster
okay shrimp bisque shrimp is clam bisque
shrimping clam bisque yeah two separate bits
oh not mixed chicken well no i'll
and then i'll do a suicide
what about chicken okay yeah chicken biscuit
yeah i guess i could yeah sounds
good and you crumble up chicken in
a biscuit on top of it actually
i guess i could do that yeah
i mean there'll be a lot of
chain left over because no one's eating
the chickens know what that is you
don't allow asia chicken just give us
motivation yeah exactly because you get really
hungry during the record and then of
course you're funnier yeah but page okay
i should get to be clear
or to page she's unexpected to be
funny on the show oh he's expected
she also wouldn't kill her to be
a little funny well look she's naturally
funny but i'm saying she's a pressure
we would like that horse but it's
not honestly if she's not hilarious on
it we'd be a little disappointed here's
the thing though we reserve the right
to scrap the episode yeah so if
we don't want
put it out you don't have and
we should we also page you should
know that after the episode we're gonna
judge it and say how she did
to her face well yeah yeah yeah
we'll give a first thumb that'll be
a bonus focus yeah reaction yeah yeah
and kind of it will be like
trading spaces reveal yeah we reveal how
we felt about her appearance sometimes people
didn't like the house when they came
back you know
no and sometimes they loved it why
don't we ever stand behind a bus
yeah and when we're ready to give
our verdict we'll hold our thumbs up
or down when the bus moves she
can see yes we will drive to
the greyhound station she'll make her own
way there and and then we'll find
a bus that's about to take off
take it so hard to time because
occasion is yeah
occasionally you're standing behind that bus yeah
like twenty minutes remove that bus until
it moves it won't move yeah yeah
or until we're removed yeah if you
went down to the bus station just
start screaming move that bus and thankfully
a running game would appear and do
something about it anyway page okay now
we've late now we've laid it all
laid it all out
but you can't reviews so page the
answer is yes or no if we
don't hear from you by the end
of april we will move on to
stealing money
i really don't she tied here really
don't like how your push she's had
years i was putting forward roll is
tax season call meetings excuse me oh
and you know say i've extent ah
tax day april eighteen at this stop
stop move that boss stop it's not
happening in may no
it's happening before me it's disrespectful to
kelly clarkson if we extended past because
i always heard this by now and
she's going i hope i get a
chance alright the way i like kelley's
people are quicker about getting like telling
her like they mentioned to wanna pocket
and let me also say kelly completely
different sort of schedule feel like it's
not the same schedule there's no omelettes
is there she's in l a i
assume for her show yeah she can
eat on her own dime it'll be
no flight no no no of course
she lives until a lake but will
pick you up and lo and each
of us will all get in a
car together pick i mean we'll do
an uber pool together yeah together together
to go anywhere hopefully it's a big
enough car yeah we'll see if not
one of us
isn't gonna show up well i would
be willing to sit in the front
or the trunk
have you ever gotten an uber and
said do you mind if i sit
in the truck i've i've asked i've
begged yeah you know i did those
ah ford focus commercials where i was
the voice of a puppet oh yes
i don't know this ah yes this
was love some more i want to
say like twenty twelve something like that
handyman hadn't met you yet
just tad mad yet better for focus
um it was john ross valley and
a puppeteer who was the movements of
the puppet and i was the voice
of the puppet yeah and the idea
was that the puppet was the new
spokesperson for ford focus and john ross
bowie was a guy who worked for
ford and was there to like roy
wrangle this very unconventional guy the puppet
and um we did these ah bits
where we would drive somebody around and
you know they got the original ford
focus rs okay yes except mostly
but it's like that yeah oh it
gets like james corden and so john
will be talking to them or just
people playing characters driving the car and
then the puppeteer would be in the
back seat and so the puppet was
appearing between the the two front seats
and then i was in the trunk
of the car oh wow with like
monitor managing whereas
of course it's all for sure wow
it was today we tell you the
story about one out at the time
when i or we knew it was
time to do it no yes i
was waiting for us to finish the
paint we never had a longest episode
oh my god but most important hood
wrote back
well we're back
oh my god scott is eating a
snack he's gotta wash it down with
some water only wash your honor that
we've advertised on our banks and water
is that coconut is coconut this exotic
because one of our sponsors hint yeah
when i say that well i wasn't
on
your headphones weren't on my headphones right
in here it oh your headphones went
off so you could only hear voices
in the room in the room which
sounds so register the same way as
the headphones true yeah also you guys
drew or whisper the i mean the
mikes are picking it up but like
you guys have never spoken above a
whisper we are in three separate corners
of the room
whispering yeah because babies sleep oh yeah
yeah well it's time once again
or a three cheer now this is
not a game this is a three-tier
where we play a game and if
you would like to send us one
you can write to three dm usa
at gmail dot com and that is
how we get them that's exactly the
process i mean it's like it's as
simple as that and you send em
we got em yeah
oh there's not much more to it
after that things got tense yeah and
god does help us in choosing which
ones we use god guides my every
move if i do dumb stuff and
i'm like really gone really gone it's
it's still cool interesting move okay god
so this is submitted by justin russell
two first names and
and ah it is called unprepared pastor
unprepared pastor i one person is a
southern pastor i think we could be
pastors from any region yeah it's i
mean we'll see what comes out giving
a eulogy that they are willfully unprepared
for the other to come up with
a famous person real or fictional who
died where they died in where
or they died in where they died
maybe the second where i was supposed
to be when probably or how
that's backing the wind that's better yeah
who cares who's curious about where to
maybe i've been where my knee is
probably covered the house yeah but why
well because all things must die and
god is cruel god is cruel the
worst the pastor then begin to the
eulogy giving details about the deceased if
they are on the right track the
congregation says amen
if they are saying something wrong the
congregation clears their throats and if the
pastor is spot on with any of
the important details the congregation hollers hallelujah
got it they're struggling to come up
with anything the congregation may feel the
holy spirit through them and say something
about the disease to lead the pastor
on the right track so it's sort
of like sort of twist
jazz kinda thing so ah who would
like to be the pastor first i
think you do okay and then you
will decide on a noble tillerson time
each other's yes yes yes yes alright
i'm gonna text you lauren is that
right ah yeah okay i guess it's
somebody you have to know something about
their mit so
nothing no no no i'm just gonna
text you who died and how
and then he gets that information oh
i throw things out there so yeah
do not listen to any of them
know i was having a personal crisis
no it wasn't a crisis like you
were wondering but it was person why
you do the show yeah i was
like was he talking about why do
i have to listen i mean no
no i got i actually get thus
we say hallelujah if
notice if he did it exactly we
say amen if okay on the right
track got it clear your throat if
i'm way off yeah yeah and then
hallelujah from right all got it however
right so you have your person
oh my
the liberal lover will thank you all
for being a hill what a sad
day this is but also a glorious
day because ah the person is now
in heaven with jesus christ
no
this post so that there was a
complicated person ah who maybe did not
do the right thing all the time
and now amen they are at peace
at least um but it's michael jackson
no no i'm not even going yeah
i was i was just heard joke
outside yeah there's no judgment on this
person's care i was distracted by obviously
given michael jackson's hurdle the wheel which
would people to provoke thing because i
saw pretty thick in the back of
the hay
what's that i'm the pretty young thing
in the bag okay look please hallelujah
the little slow right oh
ah this man was how to lose
some while the who everyone was familiar
with hallelujah amen and famous the world
over hallelujah
and beloved by all
yeah i mean hey man
oh wow okay that's not so much
big signals but all the signals yeah
no this person was ah maybe loved
by some and despised by others hallelujah
my brother but one thing we can
agree on is that there
there aren't change the world oh haha
ooh yeah cough cough cough
the that there
art ah
interviewing nail acting ah
they as a politician
jesus guys oh hey man yeah okay
this person ran for office and i
say what category the person is if
the spirit speaks through you it's a
fictional character all this i don't know
that we ever get there not somebody
who
we ever met because they will not
real pololu louis but a beloved character
of fukushima found the new books hallelujah
hallelujah didn't know and later movies hallelujah
my brother kaluuya who is now
we know for a fact definitely as
dead yeah i'll do because they died
in the in the thing hallelujah and
we have a great
affection for this hallelujah person kailee island
and an indelible big hit
an indelible character halloween that appeared in
more than one bile louis mirella
maybe five books at least hallelujah maybe
a leaven books i don't know maybe
seven books i be widowed maybe ten
books we just don't know and it's
out of our hair and ah for
movies um
hey man a man's move hey five
movies has lou yeah hallelujah and we
could be wrong i don't know about
that we know that he was in
space
we know that he was a superhero
we know that he was a cartoon
ca
we know when we think of this
man and if the spirit moves you
please do not be ashamed to speak
out we know that this man died
young ish he died at an inappropriate
a hallelujah little to sue hallelujah hallelujah
am
and he was a he was a
complicated character hello yeah nah maybe not
nice at first but then la la
la jolla harlan knew he lived in
england a long time
you lived in america na luma america
louis
and he his story of redemption is
one alleluia that we spread out over
several booths oh yeah five which subject
hallelujah it's it's
and we call upon the holy spirit
it's been gone
because we've talked about him today how
the lulea oh we have talked about
him just this day yes so he
mentioned him such a crazy kids u
c davis
suppose we talked about the most huddle
louis all other people may have left
our minds
he i will say the spirit is
speaking through me oh yes brother he
didn't even know he was a good
man he he didn't know anything
ah he didn't know anything about hens
yeah himself aw his name of course
his and we decided it his name
is jason bowe hi yeah my brother
even though i don't know that we
know for sure that he died but
he's so we have a reason of
how he did
unrelated tip the film's probably okay to
the field we all right well this
is patrick
but jason ball we commend your spirit
to fiction how you show him and
he died of course by choking peanut
shot in the fucking ah he died
peacefully in his bed
poison ah fell down some stairs yeah
it's old
it's old yeah a sword
i make so old i just don't
have any there's no way coven nineteen
minutes or so specific date with theater
yeah theory theory
alright where do we how do we
know that he's dead didn't know we're
just supposed we're no no there's that
was never a rule that he died
but let's do another round that was
great let's do another round who wants
to be it i assumed he was
a well-known thing that we also knew
how this personnel i know because i'd
be a famous person that we
no we're making it like tom cruise
items yeah we're making okay oh okay
who wants to go youtube great but
hold on a second if they if
they should we restricted to people who
are actually dead to me i think
it was a little faster people who
are i've i think i've just twenty
questions where you're trying to
i think if you lie per se
and also how they died yeah let's
just yeah let's do that i assumed
that it was somebody who had actually
died that would have made sense
it's not even a real person but
i mean i'm proposing why don't we
do that because it will mean easier
we need or like oh i think
not even harder because i don't know
who died yeah i think it's ten
you're still playing the same way now
i think it's easier to to be
anyone because also if you know how
the person died then there's none of
the guessing
about how the person died and because
fun as these two things fake game
well how would i ever have guessed
diphtheria well that's insane
yeah i don't know maybe you say
like he had stomach problems and then
we go amen and amen
i was never going to get there
but lets you text me a person
and how they died and i'm gonna
turn it off do not disturb so
i received this text
um and then lauren is going to
be the southern or from any region
yeah maybe i don't know a trojan
i'm gonna be from okay this is
exciting can you workshop a character at
all yeah while he was talking the
whole time i was just you know
what i would do oh good good
i'm smart
um no let's start ready
oh there thing i heard the ding
au lait beloved we are gathered here
today to mourn the loss of an
amazing real person
fix oh yeah yeah oh yeah real
pilot oh yeah who has passed and
we missed her greatly
i miss him greatly oh louis however
we miss him so much and he
was so old hallelujah hello and he
was very talented in his crap alleluia
amen he was yeah he was an
actor
he was a musician he was a
painter he was a carpenter
he was a politician he was a
teacher he was an astronaut he was
he was he was a yeah he
was a um rapper he was a
just famous for being famous kind of
person a man
and i'm okay i mean he was
umm mada say something so at least
this bear is flowing through my veins
right now brothers speak on that
i loved to consume what he would
do he was a schiff email huh
he was hello yeah i think hello
yeah he was a food creator however
lose you and we loved that how
long and we loved to consume what
he created hallelujah i sand weaken version
though we consumed his meets hallelujah his
cheeses his pet
his meets oh hallelujah mistakes he's who's
george foreman
you didn't have to make stacy at
that manhattan grill but how about the
person we're speaking about today he made
meets hello yeah exclusively haha amen his
name was slim jim
ah okay and this very real person
who was a meat seller and schiff
he um his name is emeril
his name was he was known here
tv show
maybe if you tried to figure out
the meats he made spirit is with
you hamburgers he made chicken hallelujah purdue
ah made chicken i mean the man
laying here at rested and we love
that about him he was a chicken
salesman hardly having had a chicken schiff
hallelujah and that is something i know
a lot about and he can i
say this they hear you speaking to
me i lie
loved the seven things that he would
put on his chicken
know how many it live eleven that
was even better he had a tv
show
any show a live i think and
i said i love canals will say
eddie taba would see jim gaffigan portray
him on television it would make me
cry well now may i say something
yes one that one time i saw
george hamilton portray him on television but
i was crying myself when norm macdonald
also portrayed me for his old resident
in turkey fred
chicken man colonel say haha
yeah i got there halfway through the
descriptions
and how did he dies sister yeah
died of coven nineteen i mean what's
colonel sanders a real person yeah yes
okay alleluia you were died of he
died of a heart attack he died
of of ah of leukemia
yeah there's no way he died of
a car yeah the spirit is boothby
here was this death was an accident
in a boat
train
playing falling on a knife oh man
he fried himself
he spooked himself oh he fell out
a knife and fork and cut himself
up in her booth
nice car
he fed a man hello yeah he
fell hallelujah hallelujah to a room full
of sue
i don't know yeah it fell downstairs
but anyways a knife oh how the
amen is it's part of it yeah
and then we said hallelujah after phil
god anyway that was fun that was
less fun we gotta wrap it up
time to wrap it up i know
we have extra page content in there
i'm so paid you have
have until the end of april kelly
i hope you are listening because it
looks good for we know you're listening
we know you're listening yeah um listen
if you would like to email us
of course freedom usa gmail dot com
if you'd like to call us send
us a leave us a voicemail you
can call us at hag claims eight
has a number of
do you want to hear ad-free episodes
and why wouldn't ya ah go to
stitcher premium or cb world and guys
that's going to be the end of
this episode this is natalie yeah really
donot there's no more left for this
episode there's nothing left for us to
do here except say goodbye that's right
goodbye
a
yeah
uh