three
a na ho wow brave
the brave welcome to ethereum lisa this
is laura and over here is up
i'm paul hi scott we got everyone
right yeah yeah um martin's wearing like
a very like ninety s ah being
rounded do
i did too did it to backdate
it all started dancing see why is
it a nineties beanie because it's so
good flowers i think it's cute thanks
i like your nineties are back beam
um whatever why am i being castigated
for saying you're wearing a beanie your
nose chopping your dick off
i am wearing a beanie and it's
because i didn't want to wash my
hair today really i wear beanies in
the house now you know sometimes knew
more about chile ebenezer scrooge style yeah
every year scrooge hates me but he's
just greenish hey wow it's me i
need your scrooge huh joe ah i'm
a pretty new guy
or the nutrition are going to work
out
you're gonna what are the lines many
genders are there no prisons are there
workhouse your chrome achieve a lot of
chapel
a bit of pork there's more greens
and gravy about cheese or gravy than
of grave match okay then we got
bit if it was because you just
to beef and i just view therefore
rotation
i was in that show and so
i would have to hear the horse
awesomely yeah oh shit all day christmas
christmas carol and that show can i
say that i watched a muppet christmas
carol for the first time over the
holidays now you know you didn't watch
what you've been missing out to the
jamie and i did watch
ch along ah yeah i kind of
because it's beloved i knew it was
like after my time you know what
you mean like for yeah for people
younger it of course would have so
much more sentimental although it has sentimental
attachments because when i was in the
show it came out and yes i
watched it in sacramento wow
enjoy these doing better than us did
you watch it at the century twenty
one on fifth century twenty one yeah
and i bought a house the next
day i remember people saying ah for
years how ah you know deadly serious
michael caine's performances in that movie and
so are the memes are still bound
yeah i didn't know what tax
he's funny i mean he's not he's
not kidding well he's watching he's not
winking he's not winking he's not camping
it up but it's not like oh
my god this is intense but i
think he is quoted as saying that
he and i don't know if it's
a real quote that he would like
i'm going to do a muppet movie
i'm going to do it deadly sue
fine going to do yeah our guide
that the muppet movie
a yeah um he was good but
it was good he was fine i
thought it was very touching i remember
sitting there and going like is someone
chopping onions or am i cries it
got justin
shopping onions within my wife just opened
the leg so much chopping broccoli
bracco hey who did you be teaching
ah chicken maker loud yeah oh dear
like give you a imagine can you
imagine so pitching that and can you
imagine such a thing can you imagine
someday you touch my monkey
right lateral touchdown nike would like to
touch my monkey would you like to
touch do you think mike myers is
pissed at that would you like would
you wanna build a snowman song because
like that's clear that's clearly would you
like to touch yes really there's no
way around it yeah it's the same
case just said why music yeah change
so it's a toy
total fucking ripoff why these words these
were his words words and then suddenly
everyone is making money hand over fist
and he's sitting there in the poorhouse
from that song that song saved frozen
because people were not interested but that
things suddenly it's like do you wanna
build a snowman and people are like
oh hey i'm turning around on rose
yeah yes some bang
hangers i recently watched that film for
the second time i saw it when
it came out initially on um dvd
or whatever rental but um i did
watch it with holly and it is
a lot of great songs you don't
really think about how does she feel
about the wickedly talented adult design she
loves her yeah it's funny me
hello no
oh i'm in trouble please come to
me please come to me please copy
li talented adele dizzee just one of
the best moments in tv history now
she's sang for kristin bell in the
movie ah christian but who plays elsa
know she's facing um anna interesting oh
yes she thinks beautiful yeah i didn't
know that she sang kristen bell
shifting bow grist and ah very good
yeah she's saying i did not realize
that yes she i did not know
that she sang a nora show to
the central park okay before she was
kicked off
um what happened oh yeah oh yeah
no but i thought the show got
canceled but is it i think it
i think the guard cancel i don't
know but i never heard about it
again oh i think it's the one
isn't that i think salama got canceled
i don't know what they want they
just keep making episodes they're like okay
well just just put
you are a network and someone was
just like hey i made a bunch
of episodes yeah and you can have
them for free yeah i know on
three seasons but i mean i guess
they're worried that they couldn't get advertising
for them is that the thing but
if you if you just offering them
a tv show yeah i put em
on they've already done thirty nine episodes
as i try that with netflix the
thanksgiving time
yeah ah but yeah who does adele
does seem sing for or is she
just she's she also really i guess
she's playing the role of l and
plays the world and plays the role
okay that's a yes because she's a
real broad baby what kind of not
really doing that anymore where someone sings
and someone does the the old ah
natalie wood yeah we'll even deal lie
lion king actually apparently i'd learned that
j p t was the voice and
then they had another oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah mighty king like
no king was before
you should sing in a cartoon i
should i remember zero of that movie
except hakuna matata that's all i remember
well then i saw the whole feel
the love of course that from surrealism
you remember the sexy ca you fear
longo to na sixteen when they feel
the love
i get nala and simba get out
are they getting you love that's what
is happening sun's going down rolling around
in the fucking tumbleweeds of africa to
all his barbed penis is coming out
yeah scraping everything on july and soapbox
i don't know if they should i'm
gonna come in and i'm actually kind
of scared to see what alliance pina
this looks like now all right let's
look at a little yeah it's so
weird that that's how evolution works that
it's like okay for an hour for
us to propagate our species we have
to have sex okay and he looks
so
keys is real that's what's on my
balls all these not gonna lie this
did not know that that's what it's
never seen it never went first one
like that first was just like a
person write like this one this one's
where i'm i'm like that's gotta be
more of what we're talking about that's
what we're talking like has spines on
it spy
fines yeah the first picture that comes
up is basically just a dude's penis
put onto photoshop but why can't it
just be nice why does it have
barks and spine i know i would
just have a really nice about it
so everyone can see not the problem
with pandas too is that the why
what are their penises do there apparently
there are europeans doing this
these are monsters and like they're really
wide like like oh i mean i
think it's uncomfortable for both of them
for both sexes they're like ah apologies
that this has got to go down
yeah here it goes and that's why
they're there there's so few of them
in addition to hear it so here's
what we're gonna get into weirdest animal
penis just that's okay yeah what do
we got labeled one of the weirdest
penises of the animal kingdom by sunday
magazine by the penis awards i don't
have to say this animal is a
penis awards have like a razzies too
i don't know how to say this
e cea mai chan around her at
chicana a kid no kid never heard
of that i know how to say
it from the they might be giants
song oh how did the song ah
what's the fucking name of the sun
they list all these geniuses and species
is it one of their like on
the top of apollo eight team knows
oh so the people say we're not
really sure why it looks so weird
but we do know that they only
used their penis for mating not urine
urine not in the pool of their
own urine oh and there's fifty heads
on it and looks fuckin discusses it
a kitna it looks like a big
it looks like a big deli meat
that just got
ah it's honestly sick
it's honestly really it's honestly sick and
that i was horny enough okay so
tap it the list basically says whale
duck alligator these are all getting really
weird we've got the kitna we have
a slow whale mammal is the name
of the song oh man oh man
a whale can only fuck another whale
right like if it
tried to fuck it off and it
would be morally yes
but it would be bad for the
doll why why would mating be painful
for an animal cats it says meeting
as painful like why would why would
anyone who's yeah yeah yeah it's just
more proof there is not a god
because when you want the cats to
have pleasure but there are so many
cats they don't it doesn't stop them
they have the horny impulse they have
the horse
and care about the female cat cats
it's like
so they're like okay the female cats
they don't like this i gotta grow
some bars to just trapper there yeah
like she wants it but then when
it starts she doesn't want it because
it sucks it sucks so i got
a fuckin i got trapper trapper keeper
and i guess they mean
that's right we have to be forever
keeper after that if that's still the
way it's like oh and those always
made those silver pieces move is basically
yes same as and thus similar to
the way that in such that the
cat penis does move in frequently inside
and such like
ah their names are called they raise
a paw the bat the cat dolphin
and dog colaba erin hogg the fox
the ox giraffe and true kid nikkei
rabiu i did it
i'd love to
yeah holy shit okay they might be
giants it's like that's too weird write
a song about something just normal why
don't they write a song about a
boy meeting a girl and falling in
love but yeah it goes tesla bending
was not about eli musk
in ten though we're on about tesla
elon musk god it's got elon musk
you better stop it elon musk you
better stop right now you on ma
see a better topic you about to
it yeah badass not know you know
people with tesla's and do they feel
like they wish they didn't have one
i know a lot people at tesla's
but they want i'm going to ask
them that question i want somebody who
has one and
and became kind of bummed yeah like
love the car but then what did
feel like it was kind of taint
everyone was trying to get me to
to re why mcnulty moulana retiree was
trying to get me to whoever yeah
we have forty eight hours sold to
this yeah everyone's trying to get me
to order when i was like no
i don't like the
the guy and they're like you'll love
it you'll love it and you know
my correspond you know and yet it's
just if i don't want to think
about a specific negative thing every time
i get my car yeah
that's where i stand i don't want
to own a car that was created
by a dork
that's but dorks probably did create a
lot of the cars well they're no
they're nerds okay they're nerves yeah door
there is report nerd ferrari and nerdy
semitic nerd
but tesla made by dorks for dorks
well a dork i'm not going to
buy one door i'm gonna throw them
on we shouldn't throw them onto the
test
yeah but they're dorks though of course
they are if you work for tesla
let us know where you would like
tesla drift you work for the deaf
l'automobile company you baba dork a tesla
drove straight into a pool in pasadena
really speakers did they mean to ah
it seems that they act what are
the gasless pronouns
it's a them and went through a
fence of some sort and straight into
a pool and there were children in
the car no but i just noted
children in the pool why haven't you
noticed yeah adult swim that is true
that would actually probably er um i
have notice dies nice of you to
acknowledge that they do say it is
too
tesla when there's a news story about
a car i'm like finding you on
there oh yeah and pointing that out
it's like that's true even if it's
kind of irrelevant that's true yeah it
feels like the news is a little
bit like bias and slash crash jerry
stone because the person was driving in
the yeah yeah i do hope they
get self-driving cars under control that's scary
right you want it i want it
i think it would be great i
was i think have i talked about
this i was talking to my mom
about it because i think any sort
of new technology in older person is
like fearful of and she was like
no i would love it because she
doesn't wanna drive she just wanna drive
and she's like if i could get
into a car and just punch in
where it should go and then know
that it's
safely going to take me there it
would be so it feels like every
car has to be doing that then
that's how i feel about it either
everybody has it or nobody has yeah
i don't think there should just be
a car with nobody in the driver's
seat driving behind me and cutting out
there shouldn't be five cars out there
yeah i think they can do this
yeah i love driving them i don't
i don't mind driving
i do enjoy driving and like it
yeah i have i like it a
lot i think i would feel sick
sitting in the passenger seat of the
car just took me around there's something
they make you move over have you
ever almost hit a a friend of
yours who
i make me think you have yes
oh specific have i ever almost hit
a friend of mine like in a
car like yeah oh erection where you
almost hit a friend to no i
haven't have you i don't think i
have i was making a right on
a light ah and ah the pedestrian
like you know start crossing the street
eat and i didn't notice and i
stopped right away and the pedestrian looked
at me kind of anger it was
curled tarts yeah i was like hey
he looked at me and he shook
his figure looks to campaign ah and
then later i was like wonder if
he recognizes me yeah hey
and we laughed about it but it's
you think you would have done that
with finger wag if he did random
noise for news
yeah funny yeah i guess it'll just
be with the crowd i was happy
that he had like a sense of
humor about it yeah well yeah imagine
if he'd got mad i always wanted
a four way stop in my neighborhood
and i thought i had gotten there
before this other car right that was
coming the opposite direction
and i was about to turn and
then this this person was like furious
like i just went an inch into
the into the intersection to turn and
i saw this big flurry of ah
motion behind the windshield and then i
looked
and it was was somebody that i
knew and who knew me and then
like changed like their demeanor completely changed
like oh accidents happen but i will
never forget that the true your yes
yeah so we should always treat everyone
who are strangers like they're free
and can you imagine also i think
op's know can you imagine if your
treat your acquaintances like strange exactly yeah
if you almost got hit and you're
going with that method of thinking and
you're like hey can you not you're
my friend like it's like that would
be a really weird your brain doesn't
do that yeah you're not defending yourself
by going like hey stranger but here's
the thing you didn't mean
knew that we weren't in danger there
was no danger in the situation shirts
we were so far away from each
other it was just it was that
person's turn right and i thought it
was my turn and this the so
the the rage was so disproportional
yeah that's where i was like wow
you have angrily yeah i do think
that nothing even happened i used to
when we've talked about road rage and
i used to think i think i
used to have like more i'd be
quicker to just be like fuck you
i don't do that anymore no you
gotta take a break even like an
even think a year ago or two
years ago or something there was
i was driving back from your place
we were recording and i um we're
not having an affair i would never
come here this is for work
but this guy got very aggressive with
me and like was like i didn't
give him the finger or anything but
he was he like almost like i
think i may be pulled in front
of him but didn't realize i wasn't
doing anything on purpose but he got
very upset and then he was like
fucking with me like driving like clothes
coming and it's also just happen to
me on the freeway not that long
ago where this truck like i was
trying to get over
i wasn't even trying to do anything
i just was trying to switch lanes
and slowly waiting for my turn and
then this guy just was like not
leaving space and being me yeah and
then like actually scaring me like you're
really really short stopping in front of
me to make me you read the
stories of other people whose shortstop in
front of you and then it causes
like these pileups yeah it's very dangerous
it's murder
hey man it's really scaling dealer the
i just couldn't wait to get off
the freeway the idea of being so
mad that somebody did a minor thing
that's the thing that you are gonna
like you have to like get up
next to them so they can see
your face like teach them a lesson
or whatever you think about it rosemary
delicious i know we're trying to go
get road rage jason it's all about
politeness which is like to be that
angry about people being impolite yeah like
because you're not that angry if someone
like you meet kind of doesn't shake
your hand or well i think my
roadway maybe about somebody like doing something
dangerous like they cut me off i'm
like fuck you it's not like yeah
but a lot of times that's like
it was my turn yeah i don't
think i ever had rage like that
i'm like hello i get to go
but i've had people that have been
i've never gotten this way people mad
at me just for like an accident
where it's like oh i thought i
could go and i can't go right
i didn't see you there when i
was trying to change lane into the
people are like furious i know i
know let's know
you always got larry remember if something
like that happens like conduct the last
accident i was in in the parking
lot at the ah the grocery store
yeah down the street um what whoa
so this was in fried green tomatoes
yeah i always snap to you is
yeah which i guess was oh no
i didn't then let me guess you
owe me you told
her you are older and had more
insurance i thought fried green tomatoes feel
like noise just now and i sort
of think that if everybody does it
today it's the exact same things it
is the same thing i've never seen
either just i just got sandy very
green tomatoes i don't know i saw
steel magnolias for the first time oh
but i'll never see it i liked
it i was i was making a
left into a
parking space and then right as i
pulled in the person on the um
the right the spot in the right
hand swung her door open and i
yeah hit her the edge of her
door like straight on with my car
anyway that's a very easy thing to
happen because i feel like people aren't
always looking myself
another phone and she's had her open
her heart out looking um seem to
think it was her or was my
fault and was treating it like it
was my fault and that feels like
it's both people know it's let's say
hurtful family and the investigation it's also
just bad timing yeah
essential obsession but it's but but any
door stealing hurtful throwing your door open
you're gonna have control of what just
outside you have to look because like
if you're driving down the street and
someone in a parked car throws their
door open and you run into it
it's their fault yeah that makes sense
so it was her fault but she
was treating it like it was my
fault and he was very weird i
just felt weird about it like in
my
head just going like you know this
is your fault you your best lady
but people are kind of trained to
immediately not take blame because the law
is well very true that's why i
started wondering is is like are you
is this just you jockeying for your
insurance because you know your insurance always
has never take responsibility never fallen but
she was but never falling
responsibility is like super fucked up it's
like if you clearly did something it's
okay to be like i did that
well the first big car accident i
got into where i totalled my wife's
car when i was learning to drive
yeah um i had my license for
like four weeks or something and i
blew through a stop sign that i
just didn't do the same
wide intersection and this car t-boned me
and then we are we're getting out
of our cars and then she the
other driver was like did anybody see
what happened and i said that was
my fault you don't have you don't
need witness let's see this same thing
happened to me where i was in
high school and i went through a
stop sign and there was a big
bush
blocking the other stop sign with the
car coming demand and
i hit the back of this car
and it's imprudent i had just recently
got like learned to drive yeah really
and this sounds like there are spun
around and it was so crazy i
went back i hit the dying door
like yeah and it's like a movie
stunt yeah i mean this was an
old couple and they were like a
block from houma oh and they got
out there too
oily fine but the wife had spilled
fruit salad all over the husband ah
was the fourth of july was the
third one an old people thing to
happen i know and that put the
stone issue that gave me a hug
and it was so nice i was
so upset but wait what happened was
my teacher was at a barbecue right
in front of in the house that
i crashed in front of and he
saw me
me and so he came out and
was talking to me and then his
dad who's a lawyer came out and
he was like don't say anything and
it was like this whole and i
was and that's where it kind of
got in my head that like yeah
that's like an important thing but i
think it's different it's different to be
like well we don't know what happened
we'll let the investigators work it out
yeah as opposed to being like well
when you did that you are at
fault that's what she was trying to
yeah
oh yeah yeah and she was english
and it's just bugged me yeah she
was like oh so you so when
you did that you did this you
know and like your insurance you mental
y'all yeah you join to have a
laugh oh yeah is it all your
problem into bite but the worst part
of it was then we both were
going in and so then we had
to shop and can you just walk
kevin running into her in the aisles
and you had to fall in love
mike yeah i love her however man
or if zurich
i'm awe
wow we're back for back ah hay
is for horses straws cheaper grasses free
buy a farm you get all three
wow are you supposed to say that
when somebody says hey that's too much
i read it in a spiderman comic
and it is stuck in my head
oh that guy getting paid by the
word
hey as far as what grand jury
yes it straws cheap progressives for you
by farming you get all three it
doesn't scan his for horse no no
you don't start with that you just
don't know just start with straws cheaper
someone goes hey straw cheaper grasses free
buy a farm and you get a
throw can you imagine oh don't say
that because you know you
not being cut off immediately you imagine
yeah do yeah hey man you're trying
that shit what are you trying to
rob a bank and you just want
some peace and quiet yeah i'm trying
to get your attention and then this
web head comes down it was spider-man
who said it yes it's his typical
like making light of the situation like
this is bad enough already i'm trying
to rob a bank
can i'm being interrupted people have wet
their pants out of fear in this
bank and now this guy and his
fucking pajamas is making jokes it's a
great quest just doesn't make sense it's
a great it's a great question
ah it's a great question it's just
a big question somebody had to ask
it um they did alright now i'm
on never let you guys or hide
in your comic book room and shiver
in fear
talking to you o talking to you
paul i thought that was yeah that
was a question for the rod is
a question for scott as i stare
into his comic book room i know
it's you just bigger than my entire
house
ah i remember a neighbor of mine
where we booed i had a bookshelf
like that with like comics and binders
and stuff finder and i was fascinated
by it it was a collector and
he really took care of a shit
wow and where is he now dead
yeah i know i have a lot
of these vary with comics i'm realizing
i have a lot of friends
who collect comic books isn't that interesting
i have a lot of friends who
collect comic books yeah um you what
do you collect other than stupid clock
condoms cat clock clock condoms
hey i like to collect miniatures i
collect so my sonny angel dolls i
collect gnomes for my yard i collect
you know um actually do have a
lot of collections come to think of
it and let me ask you this
if a gnome was real yeah like
this like from the gnome book like
the classic drawing yeah home if that
was
hundred in kind yeah yeah yeah it's
it's it but if that wandered into
your garden like you're you're washing the
dishes whatever you look out the window
i would see i would scream yeah
run i would ah would speak english
or a language i could translate i
guess it would i don't know i
don't know what they speak i would
like if it did speak english and
i could talk to it
i would try to strike up a
friendship and i would allow it to
live and my my property but i
would want my god guys i'm getting
a call
is erica i don't know who it
is hello
no no no
thank you that was actually a person
getting the wrong number probably i go
by sonja sometimes i think that the
way they try to call the dance
yeah oh your only chance do you
only talk to your fans what's what
do you only talk to your fans
although i only talk to my fans
oh wow look the fence you love
your favorite paul i've always said
oh almost as fans a new chat
oh no i keep my clothes on
okay
i just call it self yeah yeah
that's why don't we just separate overcome
i would just sign up and see
what he's doing on there let's just
sign up now
we can share an account if you
wanna go ahead and be better because
i don't really want to pay i
just want to know if he's actually
making my only social media president's only
fans and that's where you can find
all my updates you know
i do think there's people when they
when you are like someone you follow
and they make an only fans and
hugo i want to just see it
i don't want i don't want to
know what you're fucking doing in their
friends just just send your show me
show me your boobs yeah text me
what you're doing sure your tits just
show your tits please is like what
denise richards has her only fans on
like what's happening on there i'm gonna
pay to see but i'm like what's
happening didn't she start it because this
is what i heard because of her
daughter because of her daughters her daughter
started in charlie sheen got really upset
yeah and denise richards is like don't
shame hers but yeah but i'd pose
for playboy then she started one i
think because everyone was making so much
money yeah would we make money we
should we do a three-day
are we finished together or no charlie
sheen no no she's married to another
man who was with her when she's
on real housewives oh yeah by the
way new season of many great things
happening someday including real housewives of new
york which i can't wait for and
then of course i did have a
dinner with a producer overall housewives franchise
and i was just you pinch yourself
join
no but have i mentioned oh yeah
two people i know were asked to
be on it and i think that's
fascinating yes you should i wish i
would never want to cast yeah it's
like i wouldn't say would hate my
wishes but hey i wouldn't fit allen
would hate you the audience but hey
i wouldn't true it would be no
you know what the audience would love
me because i was the creator the
crew would love me
for sure yeah the audience would love
me because i would be saying things
to these women that they need to
hear reality recap yeah um kathryn dennis
fired from the only reality show we
want another arm yeah and like carl
southern com it's it's it's debater davis
across a spin off
off
all the famous cars are in it
yeah very carmax carmilla ah um ah
and like a cup a couple days
after the announcement that she was fired
she started an only fans that's all
it took she was like you must
for three of them people must be
making bank
on the only fans if we serve
for three minutes it's just like extreme
close-ups of skin and you don't know
when to guess what hard it is
or who it's from although we could
take because of our feet i wouldn't
mind that if it's only feats
we could we could take pictures of
our feet and be like have at
it yeah we did and only van
only for feet and all three of
us did it yeah problem in feet
too while you're there will be no
solo lauren nobody we all know everyone
would be going for my v hours
now we don't know i would want
to take a bigger percentage know we
would we would make sure our fee
a-frame with you yes so you never
know whose feet they're enjoying
we disable comments
so we each know it's like when
a firing squad
okay well if somebody has a blank
yeah so everyone has a blanket only
one percent of the bullet
wait what does this way how does
that work is it not that is
it not only one person has a
blank so they so everyone everyone has
a posible that was i had the
blank i see i thought it was
everyone had a blank they went always
so everyone said twenty people are shooting
at one person why
probably to length know is is my
response was depicted what's a good six
five i think ten attend i think
ten to shoot one person yeah because
the way you because one guy is
blank you want you know it takes
nine bullets to shoot to kill someone
what if you miss three people miss
if your slim guy doesn't shoot them
in the toe wave that way if
you miss you should not lie form
your irish clive i'm or more but
ten sounds good to me twenty s
l size or more twenty is more
than five but how about a thousand
okay we got as a black there'd
be a firing squad so big it
couldn't shoot god
this is so scary what happened during
firing squad execution the inmate what happened
with option yeah totally placed over his
head a small aim quaintly placed over
his heart to a chair and execution
i've never seen the type of officer
though i've seen i've seen enough i've
seen blindfolded i've seen like hey here's
a cigarette after the shots a doctor
will examine the inmate i don't think
that's necessary
that like pulled down his pants or
yeah i'm dead why do you have
to assume his ass has to be
in the navy he's just tapping his
knee come on it's got to replace
no reflexes he's gone
hold a mirror up to it also
it doesn't have a face anymore that
was another clue i know but they
they one person has a blank so
that they all sort of like have
plausible deniability where they're like i maybe
maybe i don't but i don't sit
here and i love you're a member
of a firing squad yeah you're guilty
i love shit like that where it's
like you're so close to not doing
this at all
all yeah like your understanding dad why
don't they get like they should do
it in the army to where like
one soldier is picked and has ah
ah he dies every time but he's
out there he died knowing it was
that's like when they pardoned turkey it's
like whoa whoa whoa it's so funny
it's like that's not no yeah it's
not like i hurting human beings by
the way are eating a turkey is
extremely kind and let's and bless let's
put the turkey into other holidays christmas
santa's a turkey well i do think
valentine's day doesn't have enough turkeys and
i think birthdays i agree with that
but i wouldn't want to make sense
of scots sanders the turkey easter bunnies
turkey or you just raise a turkey
to ferries to turkey great pumpkin is
turkey great pumpkin filter no more witches
and goblins it's turkey just no more
witches no markup but we are white
turkeys to prominence of that
bravo bravo hammer or he's a turkey
he's a turkey suddenly read your where's
your bridgeton where richardson is a turkey
where did your grimace sweatshirt go it's
on the chair are you scared to
be grimace why i'm scared people are
gonna call me grimace does it need
to be cooler in here or what
oh eddie well we've had the windows
oh but i like you know i
just had my hood
me off i'm fine alright we don't
need to analyze his body temperature oh
let me let me go let me
get a few analyze his body temperature
at the third analyze this analyze this
analyze yeah his body temperature analyze this
analyze that noise with football maybe
analyze stress cheaper
chiba chiba for me i just thought
i got free clip on instagram from
the movie fear to recall it with
more marky mark and reese weapons and
was still be seen on the roller
coaster there is a scene they do
on the show i don't even finger
blaster laura wow
yeah she's a ghost she rockets into
the air there's a scene where he's
coming out now the roller coaster catches
coming into this i mean their house
to try to kill her basically and
her family this happened to me okay
i don't think i've ever talked about
this have i you've shared a lot
of stories that don't sound isn't you
told the story a thousand times that
someone will you and your house yeah
no okay so i went i i
had i had ah my my parents
gave me tickets to the phantom of
the opera when i was nineteen years
old for christmas right beautiful it's a
beautiful show
maybe i was dating i was like
it's a beautiful it's a beautiful show
it's a beautiful beautiful beautiful oh you're
one of those people the interview after
the show for the commercial yeah to
it to people it's
people would quote me forever if i
said it like that it's really beautiful
show i've told you about the lady
outside of the king and i a
they had a commercial for when it
was running in philadelphia with ewell brynner
who did it forever that is one
of the one of my favorite musical
he was like sixty years old doing
still doing the king and i the
i party's guy by the way it
was in the king and i with
him of ca
source and so and so there as
well shit virtual support the commercial ends
you know the man on the street
interviews it ends with a quick like
a supercut of old ladies saying fantastic
philadelphia accents which is the one and
then a lady at the end saying
wonderful
okay so sounds like that's burning my
brain forever
fantastic fantastic wonderful oh my god i
love that i love it that's really
amazing thank you thank you and so
someone tried to kill you oh so
i found the opera tickets and this
was i think i'd had a girlfriend
the year before i'm sure you know
let's fuckin phantom
tried to kill ya but you know
wow here you go trying to drop
a chandelier on me god has to
mention having a girlfriend so much that
he said i had a girlfriend the
year before who doesn't know this this
is what this ties into the story
girl from the year before and i
had a girlfriend the year after but
this was a year where i was
not singing oh the one year in
a monogamous relationship you're saying but i
was single so i
i and andy was at a time
where i was not seeing anyone i
didn't i wasn't dating anyone wow so
like seeing you weren't dating a norman
not you your single just single with
no like no strain your info isn't
and so yeah they were in voluntarily
celibate there's no way there's a way
around you are mad yeah but so
i just details love musicals didn't
really have anyone to to go with
so there was someone who was in
awe it was college drama that i
barely knew and i was like hey
would you want to go and she
said yeah and it was a date
and she said yeah but it was
still a few months off and so
she's like
task yeah and again they're a little
early but i think but i think
both of us were like hadn't really
ever thought about but we were like
yeah we could be attracted to each
other whenever yeah oh yeah but but
she was like well well like
like wow myself into that there's maybe
three musical tickets where this is maybe
three weeks off because i think i'm
gonna be weird for it to be
two months a months is like hey
in two months do you wanna go
a date with me but it was
still it was enough time where where
she was like well well why don't
we like get to know each other
first like come over yeah let's have
a date before we sit in silence
next to each other for four hours
yeah
so i went over to her house
in this this she lived with her
parents and this i remember i remember
her mother go asking me she was
a milf know her mother asking me
what my favorite movie was and me
saying earnestly i said back to the
future
and she was like no but what's
your favorite like real move like serious
movie and i was like the godfather
into it oh okay like impressed and
like as deep coat like i was
like that came out four years ah
uh
but i remember we rented dominick and
eugene what's that a tom halse movie
oh who's that he was nominee davis
was just kinda ah that when i'm
gone what else can tell you heard
about my days okay tom holtz tom
holtz yes he's also in ah um
parent parenthood parenthood yes yeah i'm paranoid
yeah oh i like
that phantom sun was blue um but
but i so so i remember we
round up some post is a german
serial killer who became known as hight
amanda know spelled it wrong hobbyists yeah
avi obviously dear i cut on my
thumb oh gross um so you go
the stranger
or given a hand up to a
spiky de jesus
it's like a light says let's get
to know each other i want my
mother to condescend to you yes come
on over but so they go they
go upstairs and we're in the i
remember it was like a den that
had
yeah it wasn't even it was like
sort of like french doors but it
didn't seem like real doors necessarily um
but we we and i remember we
didn't even start the movie we just
kind of started making out right and
email yeah yeah and so then suddenly
there's like this and this is what
i think of
when i think of the movie fear
because there's just like this bipap papa
on the door loud la papa papa
this is what inspired that because i
have actually have a story about that
specific moment yeah because it's in the
trailer i've never seen it and there's
so there's a scene where he goes
he's yelling with these people they got
yeah and so the
the dad is going to quickly like
the that the killer is typing in
the code it's opening and right he
sounds because he says something calmly he's
like i gonna come in there and
i'm gonna kill all you something something
something whatever he says i'm gonna come
in and then you'll he gonna come
in and actually ad libbed improvise so
let me in the fucking house
really scary within the instagram post said
that the director the the editor cut
that and put it into the the
gag rule because it wasn't in the
script and the director was so upset
when he saw that wasn't home he
had it put in the film i'm
like that is a key that was
an amazing ad-lib and was very scary
it changes the whole scene right and
it's so good and it's like that
sort
of ninety s like obsession with the
fish-eye yeah yeah it was the fish-eye
yeah i've never seen the movie but
i just remember that anytime i fish
in the screaming yeah anytime i think
of that i think about when this
happened yeah it was basically like her
ex-boyfriends oh basically like who was an
army guy huh um but basically it
was greenplum
guys yeah he was tiny small soldiers
army man
no but he he filled a bag
of his buddies came over i think
he was watching the house or something
and saw this fool that i was
there and started to try to break
the door down to like fuck me
up or something know for our country
for our country and they called the
police and the police came and i
had to give a statement to the
police and all that and i was
just like re
really freaked out by wow um and
then the phantom must have been like
the next week or something like that
because we still went together but that
was the last time we ever had
a date i don't think we ever
like maybe we like kissed goodbye at
the end of phantom and we never
spoke and so she clearly got back
together with him yeah okay yeah he
was amazing but yeah
somebody once see only time this ever
happened what's your store oh you told
your story it was the behind the
scenes yeah just thought i was interesting
that he improvised that line you know
and they were gonna put in the
gag rule i'm like somebody funny it's
actually really scary and also that though
if it wasn't the gag rule if
it was in the get-go if you
made this show me yeah exactly addition
we know what is in the movie
and what is not
and this certainly is somebody opens a
door at the wrong time they're like
oh i didn't i wasn't supposed to
do that yet haha yeah oh yeah
you're right yeah you're right it's really
wanna work alright we have to take
break okay
and we're back and lauren has a
three cheer for ah okay like a
good girl i've done my homework and
open to the document um this picture
was submitted by nathan duffy and this
is a really fun night fee i
know nathan d v d yes she
does all my artwork yeah
i know from you via you've done
artwork that i believe i've been in
possibly a possible human host possible the
name is kate winslet in titanic style
here is a yes of course he
said here is a little three check
for your consideration it's like the literal
it's called it's threesome trivia three via
so everybody
attached pdf there are fifteen questions about
our beloved hosts five questions per host
all of the questions are based on
conversations heard during the previous season of
three-day oh no the host will come
from reading your own questions allowed the
other two can write their answers down
are buzzing with their name or whatever
they decide works best the point is
let's see who has
earned the most about their fellow hosts
okay you will notice i didn't include
any answers with the questions this prevents
me from having to send a separate
pdf free chosen and eliminates the possibility
anyone accidentally or intentionally seeing the answers
in advance we get it you're lazy
you know i think very smart and
thought this out since the questions are
all based on personal stories that the
host of total podcasts multiple times okay
then that's a day yeah hey should
know the answers to their own
questions okay okay so you're just to
read these do you want me to
read it yeah i guess i could
just read them all it doesn't you
don't have to read your own and
we all we all are answering your
answering as well yeah weights and i
need a piece of paper or something
okay you want this and i'll you
know i phone ok okay where do
you get all that paper if your
southwest journal i don't know where even
got this notebook it's like my work
so and so
so random so yeah it's so random
okay these are the scot questions oh
they're divided by each person oh so
you won't answer these but you should
write down what the real answer is
oh okay okay got it the first
question the first concerts got attended was
for what band oh god i'd have
listened to you
ah i laughed but i was really
ah
ah um shit
okay um so numb number them no
it's number one ok two scott has
had his hair permed once in his
life why did he get that perm
hilarious
um
it was like a little this is
your life right for me to thinking
about my permed head three scott and
the writers on the cdb television show
were forbidden from writing any sketches that
featured what animal was just thinking about
this because she wrote to me today
what i don't remember any of this
i do
okay for scott once visited a store
in santa monica called beads and things
what were the things oh shit i
love this oh my life is so
interesting five the first time the crock
fairy visited scott she left him a
gibbins that looked like what
oh yeah
saying they're good but i i think
i remember this
how do i get this wrong so
tweet give the answers on that one
and see how our point yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay so one we have
to paul and i will each say
so what concert was it i said
george michael
i did not have an answer so
i'm going to say um itzhak perlman
zamzam the answer is oil go boingo
wow i thought your cycles basically the
same thing in my mind you do
not come looking like i think okay
scott his hair why i sit for
a play i know that it was
for a play was for a musical
called
oklahoma where he played the role of
curly oh i i mean paul is
definitely right i wonder if you get
it but that does count right oh
okay because it's right there oh thank
you i guess it counts play it
was i mean it's ok let's say
animal okay shut up what's the animal
that you tell me what you get
i said cow
i believe it was snake snakes yes
so i was afraid she was fried
just have to be snake the head
of the network was afraid to snail
right kind of and could find really
okay that we were it so it's
okay that we repeat them because i
don't remember what yeah scott once visited
a store with beads and things what
were the things i said records i'm
so mad i couldn't
remember because it's something crazy i just
put down umbrellas pool tables oh man
even crazier that i could and then
the crack fairy left one in the
shape of i said fries i said
baby yoda groggy oh you suck i
did promise yeah okay so keep track
of what i got caught which was
basically i got three out of five
you got
three okay so so we're keen remember
that because we're all going to tally
up our points at the end okay
so i'm writing just write down what
you got okay yeah my questions now
everybody okay these are lauren's question questions
about lauren mean get ready to write
and you can't see it yep the
first concert lauren attended whisper what badge
is she it's harder than you think
um
what dumb shit does she
and when you're ready let me know
okay oh this is so funny make
you feel special like your life is
interesting way
okay ready in nineteen ninety seven lauren
and her friends bought tickets to the
mr bean movie bean in order to
sneak into what r rated ma show
yet ah what what year ninety seven
ninety seven
remember this i like this game idea
really fine but it's really fun yeah
i can't imagine our listener but it's
a great game because you know you
everyone knows we were told yeah probation
not like you're just having to know
some of what your friend you were
told oh my god a movie and
ninety seven i don't know you have
to just guess okay writing i know
it's not this
this but i'll just write down okay
while in college lauren and her roommate
were informed via a note on their
door that they had one what prestigious
dormitory award
ah i kind of remember you talking
about this but i don't remember the
areas
ah thanks for listening
ah
okay you're writing yeah when lauren and
her friend tried to go swimming in
the shower what did they use to
cover the drain right
oh oh right um okay
i remember you doing this yeah but
i don't remember what used to cover
the i mean years are very specific
well mine were too okay what was
the first movie lorne watched with her
daughter oh
um oh man
okay ah what is that called
let me know when your you gotta
put some down
okay okay you guys ready yeah i
did i did not do what i
didn't do well either thank you the
first concert warren attended was for what
band i said it was dave matthews
you are under the bridge when they
poured that shit
okay i said i did not know
what to put so i just put
in sink and was surprised that the
phone auto corrected it immediately wow
yes wow good yeah was um dispatch
desmond don't even go around shy yeah
yeah
okay and what well what movie do
we buy tickets for to sneak we
bought when we are sorry we bought
tickets for being sneaky yeah i know
this is not ninety seven by said
pulp fiction because it slack r rated
movie that yeah i have no idea
when this movie came out or if
it's already by but legends of the
fall it was scream sri to you
okay well in college my we were
informed on our door that we won
what prestigious dormitory award i said cleanest
room that's what i said too that's
the right answer wow all right okay
when lauren and her friend try to
go swimming in the shower what they
use to cover the drain said duck
tape i said towels phone book phone
book
that's good
that's really good and then what was
the first movie that i watched and
kanto i said marijuana it wasn't cut
whoa i got to i can't believe
i got to think okay great why
do not feel comforted about any of
great job everyone now and wow so
so paul has four total you're doing
really well with all four total yeah
so so four is
what we have to beat yeah so
educate how many do you have you
have had one i've two so i
have to get two to tie and
three to when i have to get
all five right basically okay um no
well if you get forum right the
first concert paul attended was for what
band oh shit so from the same
episode of
um okay what would it have been
trying to think of like what it
could have been
ah alright
i'm just going to do this okay
nathan if you want to go back
to other episodes and do this yeah
yeah i really do it's hilarious paul's
first serious girlfriend laurie worked in a
toy shop with what honey oh god
damn i wish i could remember it
oh god oh god it's like i
know the other punny yeah
i think he guys had trouble remembering
it within that episode i know
okay i gotta i gotta do well
on these last three okay three is
according to paul's fifth grade music teacher
a song can be a rock and
roll song and listen to what instrument
yep thank you
and this by the way i'm benefiting
from this being constantly talked about yeah
we're almost became a character man now
fair in the car i am glad
to be reminded of paul was the
president of a four member club headquartered
in his childhood basement what was the
name of the club my god that's
really hard that's that's honestly unfair i
don't think
remember that um
okay okay five and final question when
paul played jigar in a production of
aerosol what offensive phrase that he used
to insult the character of julie
ah it was in the script ah
shit it was what i was in
that show i think i i have
a guess and it's not right but
i think it's close like but if
it's not close it's funny i remember
now okay everybody ready all right yeah
first concert i said divo this high
the jim croce
oh gee i don't know this long
dead by the time i was
it was squeeze oh that does sound
familiar yeah in philly right and okay
well it's a choice shops funny name
i said wine me up i said
toys not in the belfry
the last wound up i was co
you are so close close i was
close hatch account and about no wind
up cigar okay according to the music
teacher a song cannot be rock'n'roll unless
it includes one instrument saxophone i said
drums it was saxophone that's insane yeah
exactly that's what made it a story
funny so anytime a song with saxophone
came on in the
car usually an r and b so
we would say hey rocket girls rock
and roll counts okay paul was the
president of four member club headquartered in
his childhood basement was the name of
the club i said cool kids club
it's not what i said the world's
biggest it's all shit i wrote k
k k o i realised i shouldn't
oh okay
world's biggest dumb shits shangrila to shangrila
to why don't i remember this that's
like yeah honestly i wish i did
now i will um okay and then
what did you say to julie in
the play i said you called her
an old whore i said whore too
but i don't think that's i know
i think it was i if memory
serves was
wobbly hipped slipped ah slow we would
accounted slip damn ok i got one
i got one so i totally owe
total like i got three wow you've
always are aware and you know it's
all the best wow that was a
great game nathan thank you so much
really thank you that was really good
that was really fun yeah absolutely
loved to play that again i would
totally play wow well that's gonna do
it for this episode and just a
reminder um we don't like calling you
this but we want to thank all
of our three piss yeah yeah i
actually have never said it i don't
think that's probably a lie i mean
i can if you guys wanted to
be
called the the audience overwhelmingly yes yes
i think about democracy from somebody who
said they wanted to be called little
ducky pigs oh okay i've saw that
too that's one person yeah i like
the the issue is is everyone voted
on the chance was this right i'm
honest reddit vote i forget where it
has
opened i think i think they went
to actually they went to the polls
okay i think on election day they
say we're also going to hold a
separate flash it was made sense just
because everyone's just doing good just to
get it out of the way yeah
anyway but thank you to all of
you and if you wanna hear ad-free
episodes of threesome you can go to
stitcher premium
m or cvb world dot com and
you can follow us at three m
usa and you can call us at
haha in poo or whatever that number
is like one old bag wag or
when old bag wag ho wobbly hips
slightly wobbly but imho just yell out
wobbly hip slut and we'll hear
it will come you will be there
in five minutes tops ah you can
call us add gaga jag opt again
jack opt so stupid um call it
a gag allah ho seventy eight
and um yeah yeah anyway we love
you we love you thanks so much
for listening thank you so much and
i was so fun we'll see you
next week bye bye
uh