three
sponsored by carl junior
three yeah
play me out with a goddamn deaf
dedication
oh hey everyone welcome to the aid
of where that were that we are
excited boys we are awesome we are
good pressure okay it us it us
the pretzel gang where were the mental
thing i don't remember but we are
we did say we were that's just
like germany weird
the prison gang and were like america
except more legs won't just kick our
legs we are the pretzel gay just
kick our legs we twist and twenty
tristan twist we twist and twist our
legs
me i read slugging watching me with
her leggy people we love to eat
people are salty people were for some
people the most okay we don't love
d people do we yes we do
we do only see people your people
wow hi everyone i'm lauren no stop
singing i honestly think i'll jokes alternate
side i think this confusing for the
listener right all jokes aside i think
it hurts aren't barrell he's probably because
if you if someone doesn't know and
the hear you then they think lauren
has all the horrible opinions and stories
that you exactly
and they get suddenly scott with the
higher feminine voice all the credit for
all of the good story yes and
then when people are saying who's the
third one they are so confused about
who's lauren is they forget about me
and they just turn it off yeah
i'm too confused they turn it off
before i get to my great stuff
alright i'm sorry i'm paul
the scot oh my oh my god
it's like oh my god here's the
thing it takes me a good
thirty to forty five minutes to really
get going on these episodes right yeah
and i feel like people you're gonna
make people turn off before i come
into my own right yeah maybe they
should just skip to forty five minutes
from now do it alright let's do
it why don't we just cut out
every time yeah sure yeah let's cut
yeah
hi everyone hi everyone welcome back to
the show let's going on with you
guys like what is a story of
sight of some great news when i
why i signed up for a brushy
one strings kickstarter when
nothing i've been looking at you
come on why are you lying why
lie you lie why do you i
love you little abuse
genova reveal you shudder
and paul yeah it's going with you
well in reality within earth where real
things happen within reality i'll tell you
what i'll tell you what i'll tell
you what ah today started and i
you got that right i was just
like at home
doing stuff around the house have a
big audition tomorrow oh really gonna prepare
for do you want to do any
of it right now and i sure
don't wanna hear about but i haven't
had an audition this good in a
while huh and we had lauren i
had a conversation recently about auditioning auditioning
is a weird thing yeah and it's
it's you know one
of the most important things about visioning
is you have to feel confident going
in and if the character feels confident
oh scott
true if the characters insecure you should
go in feeling like you have no
shame about yourself yeah you yeah really
absolutely yeah and so i was like
great i'm going to study this requires
an accent and i was like great
i never get to do stuff like
this i just want to have a
good audition what kind of accent chinese
yup yeah it's called real racist our
edge yeah it's called racist garbage racist
hour
um and i'm getting someone to put
my eyes back i'm like um to
make more you can just wear eyeliner
like zach grafton gardens oh right wait
when he was in the chinese right
he was a waiter at a chinese
restaurant mail it was weird i thought
i watched that movie but maybe i
didn't i feel like i see
me put these headphones on you and
we'll see i remember them oh mandy
nah
a bow ne to com i remember
i remember about that movie i remember
them yelling into a hole i remember
i remember that one scene that made
me so i was very cringey about
it natalie portman doing like some weird
body jiggle and saying everyone's from i
like to do something that's never been
done before wow
oh and like okay you're quirky i
don't want keep talking me i feel
bad chat i felt bad for well
so she had to do it she
thought okay i can do some things
around the house i have a lot
on my plate right now and i'm
doing very badly managing all of it
there we go that's how you pass
me that's how you feel that is
how i feel and also that is
what i know for yeah
okay so does this happen to you
often ah yeah it hasn't been this
bad in a while right where ah
yeah what do you think is causing
it is is it it's time management
or is it just you have too
much going on i think it's too
many things going on at the same
time yeah and ah there are certain
things that should take precedence that i
i am pushing offer and i'm and
i'm leaving other people hanging as a
result of it and it's bad okay
anyway you know i feel like when
i'm traveling away we gotta talk about
this someone made this clip for us
let's hear yes i saw that this
was from someone made this clip for
us they took this ah the single
channel icing moment
i'll teacher like and she yeah she
puts headphones on let's let's let's let
the audience hear conundrum things you should
maybe listen while yeah yeah okay
please be
became football
the book
oh don't buckle back down
when boo boo
the bong on a mama huh
so the cocaine wrong
it's good i like it
you gotta watch it because they're both
just smiling back and forth without tongue
like really sweetly and it's changing his
life this line in the movie was
a shin song yeah yeah slang de
de de de de de um but
when you just grew away wait so
let me just finish yeah oh yeah
some dicking around at home doing various
things around the house that also need
to be done yeah and feeling in
general
just kind of overwhelmed but i'm saying
i can do this up to a
point and then i'm gonna work i
have nothing else to do for the
rest of the day but to work
on this audition which is at noon
tomorrow oh no and then suddenly you
get a text from i honest to
god was like settling in like alright
here we go and that i get
the next room for it saying hey
uh
you're supposed to be supposed to be
here
wow i do two episodes yea oh
that's so tear we can work on
now let's just do it workshop it
now i think recommendation thanks you in
search stress me out when you know
it's because it's like that the whole
thing is that you have to feel
you know it yeah before you go
in exactly yeah and a lot of
times i know it as i'm sitting
in i give my
self like thirty minutes in the car
when i arrive at the base and
i will just read it a million
times so yeah like i really know
what it is but it's much better
if i'm able to get up and
do it at home my feeling is
that i want to be if i
can if i'm completely off book then
i can take whatever note is given
to me yeah no without because i
don't have to
wow so so like if they make
if they make me do a tiny
adjustment or something then it's like or
even if it's like you know sometimes
major issue there's there's a made up
word or name in the script or
it's like i don't know how to
pronounce this i'm going to ask beforehand
but in the meantime i have to
memorize this right you know and so
i might be memorizing this word wrong
yeah right and so i want to
be
able to if they tell me like
oh actually it's pronounced this way that
that's not gonna fucking completely yeah throw
me off you know yeah so and
then i have a show tonight of
course oh what show work to improv
oh go i was gonna say like
when we go on tour or wanting
him i'm like anytime i'm traveling or
out of town for work i immediately
become horrible at emailing and handling when
we choose yes like yeah i just
i'm used to doing this on my
computer not on my phone i get
much more on the computer but i
also just feel like i know i
can reply on my phone i could
sit yeah just look at this i'm
on my phone all day but you're
online it's like you're travelling yeah but
that's the rules don't apply you are
in so many cases you are trapped
i'm in a place for a certain
number of hours where it's like i
could rip through all these emails yeah
and get it done but you you
also feel like you're in a weird
stasis yeah the stress like my job
right now is just to travel yeah
and it's just to like do the
show and not get stressed out before
the show yeah when yeah yeah i
get stressed out during the show what
time is your
addition to twelve noon i think you'll
be great i think i'm gonna be
great you're gonna be how many pages
is it it's um it's not that
many pages but it is most informational
the dialogue is mostly me yeah and
there's there's some weird action in it
as well um it's like one of
those things where it's like meanings
awful glances and you know you're gonna
be looking at a chair yeah you
know yeah you told you to write
to the person who's reading with you
or do you i talk write to
the person who's reading to me and
if i have to make up another
person because yeah yeah and the scene
i'm talking to multiple people it's always
weird okay thanks so when you're talking
to multiple people this is what happens
usually there's one person most often bored
disinterested
person who reads the things very flatly
ah but but so you're trying to
act to the one person where where
the person actually is but then if
you have to talk to another person
you change your eyeline because they're filming
you yeah but then that person still
talking yes and they're sort of like
you know looking at like why aren't
you looking at me no they're not
it's their first day scott listen you
know i don't like to divulge hollywood
secrets on here in the first place
right because i don't think that's that's
it hurts us but also i i
hate even more spreading hollywood lies and
that's a hollywood la hollywood lie that
is going to bring down the system
and it's going to tragically ruin everything
that is hell said a fragile whatever
yeah they're already trying to take our
violent movies away from us they are
and our guns they are no always
have a good oh good too hey
we can't take our violent movies away
no oh video games either i'm just
saying instead of netflix screaming don't take
our violin movie
like what what have we went out
and protest netflix we had cited say
give us a show yeah we're an
arc or strategy we're fun please really
miss my movie you were funny our
movie by the way comes out in
a week yeah you are moving
your sorry our urine all did he
want zach knows profile yeah news broken
on this show you know the ryan
goal
we were at new orleans and i
knew that you're in it on this
very show well it's got a lot
of tension and they are always fighting
physically fistfight we've this final it's true
that we fist fight a lot but
it's not always about between two ferns
know but it does come up off
and sometimes it's about this really skinny
woman that we're both in
love with yeah me
me
well ho i think your guys do
that is fan art awaiting back
i was just fighting over this release
getting woman that you bought all of
us as popeye popeye characters i am
definitely i would like to if you
were obviously popeye i gotta be obviously
ugly popeye vocal your vocally pop i
haven't got the build
that's a very sweet face oh damn
bumpy roast the baby you been pie
roasted you and bye bye rosa hay
roasted spinach ag gag gag gag yeah
guy guy guy guy guy guy guy
guy guy always thought it was so
silly how joey on full house would
always do impressions of popeye
lie like he only he was a
comedian and yeah like popeye and like
but that was his actual act yes
it was way real dave cooley's oh
yeah yeah yeah they ride home
google dotcom cool look are telling us
to google or yourself jovan she doesn't
to the ether but we know it's
about chevron oh okay yeah no they
incorporated like his regular standup act into
the show so that he could be
comfortable oh there isn't just flash bad
but i don't play that too oh
it's to reason was this twenty twelve
on there you don't think he's still
don't fucking pop
okay win over kota go go to
kodak kodak hodor hodor hodor hodor go
to tokyo middle video ho ho door
or grammarly grammarly does more than catch
errors grammarly you can finally get free
one needs that joey glad
stone voice comic is my nonpaying job
to cheer people up
hi michelle it's me kermit the frog
or you don't want to cry do
yeah when you pause it for one
second he does not sound like kermit
the frog that is in the least
still worse kermit the frog impression remember
and if you do that on stage
with anyone care it was oh it
wasn't really like i this was the
eighties but would they be like liz
this way for a lot of people
you really like where they'd be like
popeye
i'm like a dubois pi if you
could replicate a voice like that you
would see people lose their shit well
the comedy club especially zachary eighties it's
like someone's being ah you know energetic
you know someone's being extroverted yeah well
dumb play the clip
hi it's me peewee herman huh do
you want to go to my playoffs
huh also not good
ooh yay
who's that lady sprinkler oh my god
it's so many dudes did this shit
yeah
that was
very common to see
but he got on tv to do
it oh shy girl shit time i'm
entering all right thank you and i
was gone i wanna switch a little
bit more cosby cause oh guys me
almost cut that off this was from
last year mo small child like virgin
ah
back in the house you're gonna have
a big view mo jo il
no can you get not really here
kenny zum wow or incredibly sarcastic miss
chow wow i didn't know that cosby
did that juicy jello jello pudding i'm
choosy ball jell-o boring oh wow oh
cosby didn't look bill cosby on not
a fan
and but let me let me just
set the record straight he did commercials
for pudding not for jello
yea wow oh wow he meant to
say j a i l ah hi
there i'm kermit the frog hello
cover to fraud so peewee herman
oh my gosh do you do wait
you do peter o'toole we talked about
that recently we done very recently very
so recently what do you do any
other impressions why use a lot of
them question how many being long ding
dong come on ding dong follows but
i mean i mean like shaker ones
yes he
or did junior on stage ah doing
the stage now i didn't really yeah
i didn't really make sense that was
like that yeah that was like that
you would do that if that was
your thing yeah yeah but it was
not uncommon you didn't want to be
put in the ghetto of impression comic
knows that they put themselves there but
it was
it was that if you didn't if
you did a lot of voices you
were avoid you were definitely of a
guy who did voices or a girl
yeah but yeah but there was not
uncommon for comedians like to ah just
like regular old damn comedian to do
one impression yeah yeah you know and
say this is my impression of this
person yeah i know just say that
doing that thing yeah
yea it isn't my immersion of this
person of this person doing a weird
thing that was very common like is
my impression of this major celebrity and
then doing a weird thing like yes
cutting himself on an envelope and tripping
down the stairs yeah these are all
the like tropes like these are still
around like people are still downing people
still do it
yeah
what about you lauren what impressions do
you do let's hear right you do
any impressions i don't really when you
were little did you do impressions oh
yes but i think i've talked about
my share impression and her lou which
is pretty funny coming out of a
kid i'm was it did go well
hello
oh i'm sure i'm not sure i'm
doing my tongue thing i'm trying to
see i don't know read ny aid
i will i like to imitate people
but i wouldn't say i do impressions
that people but it was more out
of cruelty
well like yeah look at you i
like to mimic and mock people but
if i do impressions like if i'm
watching tv like i like to try
to voice yes okay let me pretend
i'm on tv and see i mean
pretend i'm on tv and see what
happened the news today was interrupted by
other news when the space shuttle was
interrupted by an asteroid
lloyd hey um scott
we're going to stop the news really
quick what's up you're doing really bad
at what the news at the news
yeah excuse me excuse me we're doing
the news next door were you interrupting
us of course it was with other
knew what we're gonna do news you
does tried to tell him i tried
to tell him well i try
try harder
i shouldn't be mad at you sir
are you guys going out is there
something going on between you why would
you hurt going out we just have
sex oh a modern woman a we're
sex buddy not s e x s
e c k s yes we silent
era shoe eruption car and caravan this
did you say c k louis sega
we were having such a good time
he started doing ladies dream this louis
c k impression of louis c k
and his alleged sexual varieties petit and
he invested that he wrote about in
the new york times yes it's oh
my gosh or not you've got popeye
of course we know well there's of
course whoa taza yellow
hi boys i'm larry
yeah haha boy marty that was a
big gotta get back to the future
on the eighties larry david eighties comedy
scene that was a huge impression that
every you've got to curb your enthusiasm
larry
pretty pretty pretty good
here's my larry david pressure let's hear
it i'm making this all up on
the spot
i was getting a permit the fraud
good my name is pi huh um
the pop imam lauren were you always
extroverted though mr papa gave you all
the clues are you always like a
big showboat funny in class but i
also was waiting i'm sure yeah we're
like funny dances
slips i think actually there's actually there
is a video of my peasant child
whose fifteenth century friend i know i
did quips like the toothbrush is very
current ah yeah yeah wait there's a
video of my impressions that were on
vine if you google lorin lab kiss
vine impressions i think
you can see my really good impression
with one recent this was something i
was into doing a few years ago
someone upload them altogether and twenty fifteen
my c nice smell what the rock
is
the math somebody's were you watching the
mask on the plane yes i am
did i catch you watching the mask
on the play i like looked over
and i looked over on the plane
to ah wherever we went i keep
oscar right well i really i see
my long walk to my left and
what should my wondering i see
but richard jenny the platypus man himself
or a p yeah and and i
was like what fucking movies this and
it looks it looks really bad i
haven't seen the mask since i haven't
seen a day out same yeah why
would you and i always quote it
but then i thought well what even
is the story there and then i
put it
on because it was on the airplane
and i'm you had to look for
it you had to like well i
like to look through the classics okay
classes yeah oh and classics it was
really enjoyable i didn't finish it but
didn't finish didn't finish and finish couldn't
finish but it ah it's very warner
brothers have like it's like all
looney tunes and stuff i definitely remember
that i was a kid when it
came out so probably just was like
that's what movies are yeah um but
so very what movies are curious someone
always rushes he is hilarious in the
mask he is very funny did anyone
stop him no they tried they
so he just contains well i stopped
watching o u's yeah we're the somebody
he said somebody starving you so high
am that somebody cameron diaz amazing it's
all ah pretty fun and he is
disturbing looking i mean it's really silly
but he's great so fucking funny yeah
you know yeah he's hilarious well yeah
hey you're not on trial you're like
mean you're you're like the jim carrey
of the modern day though that's all
i want and my as this tim
bitty step me
ah seventy be dumb to stop high
bison bp you stubby
wait let's hear more impressions okay man
down to rapping though that was justin
timberlake think it's a boy man
hi my name is mariah carey i
have two twin boys one's a girl
and i have a husband named nick
my name is trick i'm an alien
from another planet
i'm michael lewinsky like the presidents of
the question
oh tom oh i won't go off
on their mouse whistles
hi i'm sarah jessica parker i love
my shoes
shin very expensive colors expensive colorants ah
yes the wickedly funny adele design i
like this
but i'm a better dater
voice hey what is going on here
get back to class zak's leader lisa
turtle was that mr belding
you have this
to go
so my name is bob simpson oh
shit i just liked how long is
this video it's okay d'arnaud oh my
god there's so much left yeah oh
it was my fun thing that i
was doing on vine that's fun alright
fine yeah i like that someone compiled
them so i can always have them
yeah like that who did it
oh some weirdo and see who said
it that's so nice to bike and
shitty oh you cheeky bridge and then
some people in the comments think they're
real in that i suck and other
people get it you don't say no
man there's just a lot of
dumb people out there yeah it's really
really annoying to engage with them when
people who are like the weather like
willfully
jews do not know yeah willfully obtrudes
overlay after if you had if you
knew i who knows if you ever
tried out for us no i don't
know yes but okay so what what
did you have to do an impression
i did do a few impressions but
i honestly can't remember i you cannot
remember
mr belding i did maggie smith lets
your mac no no i'm not i
truly don't eat like i i created
the rue de more that i created
them for the edition because they flew
oh no this was a tape for
the flight they they flew me out
twice woe failed okay um no it's
fine i'm spy bring it up
no it's fine it was cool to
get to go to ru you library
i truly did not you think that
you would ever tried out for us
oh you love well on the spot
watching them was my dream my whole
life and so it was really cool
to get to go and i tried
out on the stage for my second
ride on the site did you say
love for new identity
said go
the first one i flew out for
was ah at the pit theater and
they had a bunch lauren was in
the audience i could see him through
a little peephole behind the state did
you say alright that hire someone with
my own name
yeah good wacker with my name's ever
seen his name written down so yeah
no he doesn't know what it is
um and then i came out again
for the tesla kate mckinnon got it
that year oh well yeah she was
great you know no you couldn't both
be on the show were they saying
they knew they were going to be
ordering more white guys yeah
i tried out for digit tryout for
i auditioned for mad tv oh yeah
brand-new think i passed on it but
i did not do characters and so
i had to make up some yeah
yeah i tried out for the dana
carvey show and did the same thing
oh i tried out molly it's really
hard to make that shit up in
the last like no
no that's why you gotta like have
have years of that under your belt
before you're ever ready to like that's
why nowadays i'm just like oh no
i don't do that and it was
like it was like a pre read
it was just me and the casting
director and i sat in her office
across from her who she's up on
her desk i sat across from her
i would ask her about these fucking
these guys to meet up
nice stir ah uncomfortably it was horrible
it you feel like you are funny
at all or like oh oh no
did not allow yeah it was it
was bad from the moment i started
yeah yeah mo when i started yeah
and i kept doing it i should
have just said like you know what
somebody saying yeah don't really do this
yeah yeah yeah i feel like i
do have room
on your show for somebody who doesn't
really do this yeah i think i've
gotten better at not trying to do
things that i say you're not good
at that i'm like i don't want
to put myself in this situation yeah
i have a friend where i'm gonna
leave really vague because whatever it's just
not my story but it's not that
big of a deal but he recently
was offered a part on a show-me
crew and it required him to do
a like sporty aq
activity that he's never done oh yeah
and you told the story in podcast
i'm new i told you in the
car ah podcast of life yeah kid
tell the difference anyway the same in
the car and here oh that's yeah
that's anyway please start doing incredible oh
yeah do much cheaper save room room
he was panicking every cent
because he had to pay to to
do this thing and he is now
he never did it before and then
and he said that he couldn't he
said he could do it because he
was like oh yeah and then we
were kind of teaching him and then
he has this thing he can do
well that you could teach him skating
oh okay and then he roller or
ice rollers roller blading and
meetings hard too did manage to figure
it out and do it but like
your today he did confess to the
people he did on the day because
he shot multiple days where he didn't
have to do it and they want
to be liked and and it will
heal and he they already knew him
and knew they wanted to turn out
a bunch of senior gentleman but he
knew that the other part was coming
later and so we had a couple
weeks to like try and they they
he told
when they helped him get lessons they
talked about oh that always bad though
i don't think so i don't know
i think it was more like a
ah let's just try to fix this
yeah but i think as actors it's
so easy to like want to just
say yep i could do whatever yeah
whatever yeah sure yeah good question so
many things that make me uncomfortable yeah
i'll be the star of mtv yeah
yeah yeah definitely yeah i'll do every
yeah everybody i were seeing that ad
in the paper wanted star tv show
and i said well sounds like yeah
quincy jones requires star quincy oh my
gosh alright let's take a break
drop the mic
hey welcome back mike everything on ne
shipping is always free way
yeah drop them like dick to bump
and dump bogdanor for the fucking banner
free shipping shipping
oh seven reminded us of the wayfair
theme thank you to the person who
sent that to us apparently shevlin met
him the other night and who knows
who knows who was more impressed the
first one medford medford man medford boy
who who was the wayfair person impressed
that he
met shaven or with chevron impressed he
met the way for your person we
don't know we oh we will never
know um welcome back to three-time though
welcome back for three mo go back
to three of them though i'm paul
f tompkins still i don't know where
we'll still laura ren no it's not
no you're not one
i'm good with mine i'm not doing
today
um what do you do some were
we talking on this note about you
not having your management that water eating
the things you can do to fix
this i don't like this tone i
mean like i get into situations i
think we all do i would like
to know what your tactics are for
like turning it around honestly i tried
to
um
the the biggest
the hardest part and the biggest hurdle
is
to understand that there will be that
this will affect you later the things
that you agree to now are going
to affect you later and that stacking
up so many things is going to
be can be detrimental um but the
problem is it's like it's hard to
know when to say
say when when there's things like we're
going on tour and i'm writing the
script and an audition comes up whatever
then there's all these other things the
florida like i was supposed to do
the um the zillionaires improv show we
do it every month and i didn't
do it because we were flying the
next day and i was like my
tank was empty yeah it's just like
i gotta go
at early yeah you have to be
able to do it yeah yeah and
honestly i'm now thinking about calling in
sick to the show tonight yeah because
most most everybody will be there and
your priority needs to be for needs
to be yeah you're few miles yeah
yeah it's hard because i feel like
i often want to say yes to
everything the dress
the truss but but and then i
feel like i've gotten a little better
in the last couple of years at
saying no just to random even things
like i think sound fun like a
podcast silence movie on or something yeah
yeah but then i'm like you know
i think it'd probably be better if
i just had that day to even
do nothing
yeah like if there was a chance
that i could and i probably won't
end up being what happened absolutely but
i would like the opportunity to leave
the window for some time in my
week where it's not like every day
i'm running running running running like twenty
things but it's hard to do because
you're pushing yourself and you like you're
the you're the motivator behind your own
career yeah and
so it's hard to say no we
and hard to know when to draw
the line when you don't have a
when you don't have a main thing
yeah if you're know your job yeah
yeah your job is made up of
a lot of little out of it
yeah yeah then it's it becomes harder
to to conceive of and manage the
time because if it's like i know
i'm going to be at this place
every day from this time to this
time or whatever like
the the ah the junkyard the junkyard
i know that's it's gonna plan it's
gonna be me and that dog occasionally
those kids that made up instruments out
of garbage maybe leroy brown will come
by my homeboy okay he's really bad
even the dog is like i'm scared
of what's strong
but yeah no you must like that
song because you're from chicago bad bad
leroy brown huh i always i'm i'm
interested i didn't know he was laura
know i love jim croce from the
south side of chicago the baddest part
of town was from expo is it
well of course
the bad boy i when i'm bad
by comedy mike and i'm mike i
was like this guy exemplifies a lot
of the personnel traits oh bad bad
leroy brown yes i'm always interested in
the songs that you know because when
we were driving the other day you
started singing along to an old survivor
song
which i believe is like nineteen oh
yeah for eye yeah yeah yeah and
i was like don't know that i
know one survivor song eye of the
tiger of course of course but um
and i was like oh yeah i
used to roller skate when i was
you know like twelve to the song
or whatever but i was but then
i was kinda like i wonder why
laura knows it i know where i
heard that song for the first time
where i was in a car i
i feel i love lyrics i love
to know all the lyrics to song
lyrics person to yeah and and does
it happen pretty easily by filling full
metal de jesus if you ever heard
one ah you get i didn't get
popped by rosie rosie perez sweet
happy rock oh that sounds delicious
right now ea canceled the show tonight
we're making dps cancel
guys you do hear sweet beast from
popeye cancelled
wow another one bites the dust um
i don't know when we cancel i
feel like um i can learn lyrics
really quickly if i hear a song
on the radio the second time i
hear it all basically know although i
feel like a pickup lyrics pretty quickly
yeah i loved yeah and i'm always
amazed by i love me like who
i am and how i am but
i'm always surprised by people who will
be like i don't
ever know what a song's lyrics are
oh yeah what are you hearing yeah
hear it yeah you just hear them
now yeah yeah it's like what it
sounds wonderful around me i'm yeah slaton
around so first you had a big
sue so loud wow
rattle down think i know that talking
because i was in a car with
my friends who were a bit older
than me and i was in i
was probably twenty and they were like
twenty eight or something and that song
february to new years eve romance friendship
ship and i don't know if they
put that song on or for just
on the radio but i'd never heard
it and i really liked it and
then i went home and downloaded it
and then i just always like limewire
at that time i believe it was
our stern huh i might have been
um i don't think it would be
either at the time of this what
years this this would be
two thousand six or maybe iphones could
have be might have been an i-tunes
gumroad gumroad it was that one of
them miss that so then what appealed
well road is like a sort of
australian craigslist kind of oh service cool
what what did the lyrical why did
the lyrics appeal to you um i
just thought it was a fun song
it was honest this i'm high viber
eye on you yeah what can we
play yeah you know like a rickroll
harasses no plus no chevron's already doing
it don't try to trick me all
right alright
david thoreau emily does
grammarly grammarly fucking grandma everyone to put
it off my ass grammarly
it's just fun feels great oh i
know this yes okay and this video
there's a woman looking out the window
and there's a bunch of stars
i miss i miss songs like this
yeah it's great camp people put out
songs like this anymore well here's one
the alderson soon
what about um every day of my
life who does that song the search
is over that was a very important
song to me in high school what
is that one the searches of coaches
over you with me oh wow like
i know that seven survivors i thought
so i thought the voice what is
certain let's hear the searches your grammarly
ad
i didn't do it
another window where i know oh my
story the video directors in the eighties
had one idea listen man we're survivor
and you can do whatever you want
it's just video but it must start
with a window a fake window
this song made me think of this
girl that i loved so ma wow
but she was never to be except
sometimes ah that's around but she had
a boyfriend i worked out well that's
pretty good it's better than nothing you
know what i mean look
going back looking back looking back you
got somewhere she likes to shop somewhere
i have hsieh the boyfriend but she
can't control it okay so well when
i was fifteen i was in love
with this girl who was sixteen oh
shit
november december lupski mike sold
oh no wow
so she was she was in drama
with me and i just and and
she lived sorta over by me remember
where i used to leave the apple
yeah she lived over but she looked
over there he is the ball of
the apple in the bag i'm like
that then the neighbor yelled or you
got very very ah
upset about with yeah it was weird
it's weird but that's why we're i'm
telling the story because we tell weird
story oh that's a good point please
proceed prophecy pre pre pre preis say
freeze i beg of you so
i just want to get a ruling
on this okay okay because like this
this is very similar to to your
story but so she i know that
she knew i was really endure yeah
but only she can tell because you
had all those hearts coming out of
your eyes yeah but only viewed me
as a friend but i think fringe
that hurts
so when you get put in the
friend zone oh good friends don't hurt
you in cells don't like that and
cells don't lie that says oh hey
hate being in the friend zone it's
the last place called the unseld
whoa so those moral is don't put
anyone in the friends huh yeah everybody
already have so shy they have pressured
monogamy nobody puts baby in the corner
somebody puts instill in the friends of
love and telephone zone
shoots up a school so the fritz
i'm in
instead hey it's come back it up
as a kid he said tang and
i'm dropping in the friend zone so
it's icy out here
hi i'm in so
okay will be the redzone please mummy
preis so i want a ruling on
this because i felt like i was
getting mixed messages so um pretty much
like me pretty much went the entire
school year right where she wanted me
to walk her home good time
ah it's and we would talk and
we would laugh and very fun we
were in theater together and plays and
stuff and i remember two times signs
something it it felt like it escalated
once was time one time was when
we were doing the show aladdin and
ah we were in the wings and
both about to go on
and she like kissed me on the
cheek and said good luck or something
like that never that had never happened
before and then another time was it
opening night know it was just like
it was not a special it was
just a like it may have made
run mid run exactly that's what was
so susp
ashes about it and then the other
time was i went to her house
and we were i remember she loved
the movie white nights and she would
or she loved dancing gregory was sort
of threads mikhail baryshnikov so um and
i think i got her the white
knight's soundtrack for christmas but anyway drink
say you say me violent or richie
yes and also featuring agh
against all odds by phil really cullins
no not i guess no that was
for the movie against all odds and
a separate lives with ah you have
no raw ask me oh i feel
you know these online i don't think
i do owe you a song it's
a good financial habit it's white knights
m i g h t k k
n he looked at white can age
yeah several lives steam from white nights
though the time of day oh maybe
it does look and nobody is right
yeah i don't know because i'm sorry
it said in rush i said in
russia so it's baryshnikov and gregory hines
and gregory hines is like amazing tap
dancing in in years niqab
like i saw many times i saw
with her in the theater you easy
that carrie's boyfriend yeah second date sure
i think i got on blu ray
recently just came out okay so then
the other time i'm sitting in her
i'm sitting in her room and we're
talking wait go back now you got
it on blu-ray it just came out
yeah you don't
no do you just get like a
ton of blue rice and junior columbia
house record yeah i get it it's
sent to columbia house then i go
pick it up from them
you do order a ton of blueberries
all the time whenever something comes out
sometimes yeah but so so much fulfilling
so often that you're not sure you
have it or i know it's coming
i just can't remember if i ordered
it or not you want to i
may have it's a lot like the
brushy one string situation where a lie
becomes tricky
i either did or i didn't okay
who cares we'll get back to the
story so you're in her room your
room and i remember the doors internal
life that's certainly did my math did
you chicken in the corner and i
remember she had a marilyn monroe poster
and that was where i was kind
of fixing your gaze no
speaking of fix my gaze i adjusted
my balls those other games like kathy
griffin where my gaze so here my
pants
so so and but i remember the
marilyn monroe poster because i started realising
the sort of cliche of of ah
girls of that time like all all
having a marilyn monroe poster up like
she was the ideal of glamour whatever
okay so then she she reached over
to me and she
she like put something in my jacket
pocket and i was like what was
that microfilm
she was a spy and it was
a dead drop
the falcon and the snowman situation um
no she puts she she it was
weird because she like came over to
me got really close and then put
something in my jacket pocket and i
said what was that she goes oh
just a piece of trash and i
went oh okay are you fifteen right
now she's yeah
is that what you're asking you look
like yeah you look bad fifteen been
on for fifteen yard fifteen k race
your fifteen keep going because this is
basically a question mark in your life
you're wondering yeah like me
me or yes so i so i'm
walking home then and i reach into
my pocket and i take it out
and it's her school picture she loved
you and she wrote like a hard
on the back
talking about what i've been talking to
by which you wrote a heart and
then also the words i'll never say
yeah she's never gonna fuck you dude
what did it say a hard nose
or a hardener name or whatever she
ooh i don't she had a crush
on you i think maybe the cheek
it went in and out maybe you
think he's waiting for you to make
a move
awww maybe baby you're so aloof that
she was like alone knew all this
then you were like i can't tell
now and i'm an adult
ah
yeah thirty five years from now i
still won't understand what's going on but
i swear to god she knew that
i was into her and and was
not giving it to me money too
afraid i don't know and she petrified
and then she yeah at first um
at first and then she became a
cheerleader the next year and was popular
and that was the end of that
anyway
how do you know i found a
clip speaking of i was go to
the cliff
i just need to put a clip
um ah after we did the raise
my tv show in philadelphia i found
another clip because of my captain noah
search and it's this high school this
philadelphia high school see quote choral group
singing i will survive fools
it was all food oh no oh
oh no waves in here it kept
thinking i would never live without you
by my heart a very interesting arrangement
oh well we see for fucking foils
oh
it's in chamonix longhorn
chamonix longhorn yes look it up shaven
chamonix longhorn okay kevin can i send
you the ah the link and you're
not gonna make fun of me right
send him that record
shit i'm not gonna rock rush watch
johnson at the request send him scott
scotty mccreery maybe looked northern during then
lie down low miller organum doors and
turn them lights even lower
wow the sql
maybe who continued to keep those doors
law he wrote a follow-up to that
cover okay listen to this lodge
ah now there's for the listener there's
a million kids on the stage and
the guys are wearing red jackets and
trousers and oh dear this is the
whitest thing to ever have they're just
seeing it as fast as they can
there's no detectable harmonies or anything it's
all in unison yeah this is like
a banana amsa all their faces are
dead
all the women are wearing vests blue
vest and white blouses the gentleman wearing
skirt red blazers with roughly tuxedo shirts
and black ties this is a mess
and it goes drumset there it goes
on forever it goes on forever and
this woman is one of the people
as bobbing her knee like as if
she's always sharing
one single person everyone else is stiff
as a board light as a feather
she's the one person who's into it
but these hairstyle i remember all these
airstrikes to get that update or owning
they all look like girls i went
to high school with yeah
do i yeah that is the new
remedy longhorn high school concert choir nineteen
eighty one were you in the wire
at all
i was in my i was in
my church choir in grade school and
then of course i did the shows
in high school
that's a good example of a thing
we'd seen and then there was one
time i was in a special choir
ah of students there are only a
cupid doing it and you're shaking your
head i can shake my head she's
about to shake her i damn well
please
she ah i was i was one
of the students selected from my school
to join in a massive choir made
up of different students from all the
catholic schools in the diocese because ah
we were celebrating these silver jubilee or
maybe the diamond jubilee whatever
of john cardinal krol who is the
archbishop of philadelphia related to nicole's dad
yeah yeah jewels girl yeah the private
investigator ah that's right they made their
money from arms sales
you just okay we
that's what she said so there's this
big choir check all these of all
these different high schools coming together and
we sang we sang some religious song
that i can't remember but i also
remember we say hey
carrier lays on down the row that
a lot of mister mister but we
also saying in addition to some religious
songs we also saying the philadelphia tourism
jingle what is that philadelphia get to
know us which was sung by padding
the bill like having a lebaron was
like eighteen eighty six yes she's very
much so do you still remember phil
adelphia get to know was see what
people believe in the power of each
other can do ooh ooh
here it is it sounds totally different
i get the best oh phew oh
my and marianne have perfect pitch
people rowing on the schuylkill river that
looks so fun ben franklin prisoner later
all girls are getting idol ooh this
is how we hear this visit we
like no you can't be near children
in yeah even if it could feel
your weird costume don't be near a
child while i was running up the
when i took the museum of art
when i took my nephew around when
we had when we would see a
movie and everything i was like getting
kind of paranoid that because my nephew
was like you know part asian yeah
you're very clearly not related you clearly
kidnapped him is what you think people
will think oh did he jump cooler
but no
no i started thinking though that no
people like a moderate especially in law
like people just assume oh that must
be his dad yeah yeah right yeah
you must be married to a year
you are really like right right when
i thought i was creepy i walked
around saying like this is obviously my
nephew everyone you didn't put a piece
of trash in his pocket wiggling
a little school photo
oh it's his own some trigger some
trash and he's like why don't you
think i'm trash uncle uncle oh my
god that feels like the wrong clip
however it was interesting and i haven't
done any of those things in philadelphia
yeah what oh you all you've done
is go to a hotel yeah really
oh and i went to a theater
you didn't get together a rowing crew
and go to a rocky steps and
glad liberty bell i didn't go to
anything but sweet green i've been to
the liberty bell so fanatic love em
there is this hats on crooked but
it's okay that's thanks still i don't
like silly can you play kevin want
to see if it's the chorus
look out
ah two women running people doing double
dash now an old man doing a
soft shoe next to a kid
a the power of job
can do
ah the hooters hooters amazing philadelphia's own
the only band after the beatles had
the same haircut
is that the only band from philadelphia
the hooters know they're allowed there was
a lot of affiliate there's miss patti
labelle herself there
huh
off
if i ever show you
talking about your hobby we actually we
were talking with most random clips of
her telling me about choir and suddenly
we get to bill bay and suddenly
it's bill cosby what is happening is
up everywhere she haunts alright we have
to take a break
all romance for sama macho
i used to listen to the song
and think about her yeah house nancy
reagan yep and the fact that i
wasn't doing it yeah you were saying
no that's
i think i confused personally
they're just do it
ah you know in theory i cannot
say just do it here's my answer
to your drug problem just do it
oh that was several lives that was
felt that was the best part of
separate laughing no i didn't become in
on the chorus really slow i love
the bridge oh so typical love leads
to isolation but you build that wall
but you build that wall
wow that happen okay
diminishing returns yeah let me started a
little high and one of our policies
that was diminishing diminishing returns yeah yeah
i think it was oh my gosh
it's time for reacher what do we
got this game is called disney court
the suggestion comes to us from at
robert yoon to hosts gives you a
a this is like
his third three zero yeah i think
it might be two hosts give testimony
to explain their crimes and plead for
mercy as a disney character decides whether
or not to free them from the
jail we've decided to modify and have
everyone be a disney character yeah yeah
everyone in the world but do we
look in the mirror
but do we have to do an
impression of the disney character or we
can do it like the other game
and are we guessing who we all
are i think it's deal as choice
no i don't think would to guess
i think it's dealer's choice and let's
begin okay yeah paul and i will
be um paul will be the bailiff
scott will be the judge and i
will be the criminal right in this
round
yeah just picks her account this is
very important oh good question yes shit
it's a crossing of verses here we
go what you think all disney movies
are in the same universe and all
picks are mobile they say all pixar
movies are in the same unit well
they look the same they keep them
separated at disneyland springs
separated no
hey do you know that theory oh
that's a great song do you know
that theory that all the pixar movies
are in like the same yeah just
having him now sober jali is like
you know monsters incorporated yeah okay what
about cars though outlier they say no
they say that's in there too like
in ah but it's like in the
future when all
it's like after wally
all the humans cars takes place after
wally i think i don't know you
said this woo okay anyway this but
i should i shouldn't i should know
i'm judge buzz lightyear wow that worked
out your honor we have in the
next case to review to infinity and
beyond you mean ah
that's a little joke over you by
the way they live i am living
candlestick my name is oh yeah he's
so perfect for me because i am
beast
oh hello beast i'm so grateful to
see you lumiere all rise away your
suppose you're not my favorite guy i
wonder if i should recuse myself from
oh no no we are friendly ultimately
yeah this guy this guy he cursed
me to be a candlestick it was
able thing a lady kirsty soul just
hate that my thing my
crimes i've done something awful judge what
don't you know a little bit of
my well i'm i'm reading the docket
and you had a very interesting crime
alright sorry i just want to say
yeah i know thank you all right
the honourable buzz lightyear presiding court is
now in session explained to me this
is this is
very odd what you did explain to
me exactly in your own words and
don't look at him explain to me
what you did in my own words
i so rarely get to use them
for who could ever listen to a
business will you talk to all the
time ah you just visit marilyn exactly
oh um well okay what i did
was bad but i'll use my own
words me go piggy make
baby go paycheck okay maybe he should
use someone else's words use it properly
which what did that is that what
weird to say meego piggy meego what's
meego biggie what's make baby with p
make you meet a baby make baby
made a baby with a pig not
be solely because asprey ama beast right
i'm not human in when i am
be by the way you are a
human because this is post your movie
but look at me you hey yeah
you're slightly hairier
or than your name is not harry
by the way you're slightly hairier than
others but you don't still consider yourself
to be a beast do you yes
i do okay because i know my
tendencies and my nature so are you
trying to get out of jail i
want to go home home to bell
you're off to a terrible start i'm
still
with bell but i cheated on her
with it
and explain that in your own words
again meat animal horny go bye-bye go
come come in toby
how do your order because look your
honor should i clear the line you're
right you're right you're yeah but later
call me your honor please god my
year because i
because i love my wife i sometimes
have beastly urges and i had to
go out as you love your wife
or in spite of the fact that
you love your wife whatever english make
go-go this please
i don't know about this i was
locked away a long time until my
book reading wife joined me in my
castle book no frank sinatra she please
have famous non book readers as we
all know he's helped me get home
to my wife and you get home
p i love love go anyway
alright your honour with you please yeah
let's get a regular but you may
approach the bailiff yeah this is fun
we've got through her gonna let this
guy him i mean of course yeah
this guy back onto the street know
i mean he's gonna fuck more pigs
yeah that's what he thinks what's the
baby we got to ask about the
baby do we yeah it is
there's a baby mister bass yes it
is born it's only take six weeks
for pig babies and is it's half
human and half pig which half is
which we send in the twenty three
and me and it got way more
pig than beast okay it's it looks
like a wild beast
how much ah iberian peninsula in sub-saharan
africa two percent but sounds about right
alright i believe i have a ruling
okay you are going to jail to
infinity and beyond
my last one thing i know was
like most late mc lol yes alias
and seen wow that was fun that
was really wow i want to be
the judge and i want to be
oh i'm going to reveal myself as
in characterization oh okay um ok yoda
i know did so
and by the way this disney disney
now owns all of star wars star
wars no okay let's just keep it
cartoons how about i'm the star wars
the victor harbor from alias
they own abc yeah you're right okay
i think that's fair game
okay um i forgot who i was
gonna be keep going
order order order in the court hey
i'm supposed to say that i'm peter
pan oh peter arise order in the
court the judges over here and and
they want to say who they are
aw da co guide o the ariel
is
now in session that's right slapping fins
slap the bass and she's also obviously
and i love you man fan okay
and um i see it on our
docket we have a very interesting guest
today yeah it's me the tramp um
you are so hot in that movie
and it conf
fused me as well you know look
i'm a very lucky man waving hot
dog we had a case in here
recently about bestiality this isn't reality i'm
a mermaid and anyways
i'm the judge bailiff i can throw
you out of here in any second
oh i'd like to see you try
high
mermaid rose did beat her bad na
ho i'm back because i can fly
i can fly i can fly i
can fly i can fly we know
you see it everyday okay now it
says here that you committed a crime
that most people would look down upon
yeah look um i didn't pay for
that ah
spaghetti dinner and a dine and dash
huh well i didn't know as a
dine and dash because i'm a dog
and i thought you think human rules
don't apply to you
no they don't i'm a dog okay
i thought these two human beings are
so invested in my relationship right i
assumed the meal was free why wouldn't
it be around around here in the
transcript that the owner of the restaurant
came out to the back alley and
put what mister
our tramp here thought was the tracks
he's dutch mister the tramp here just
the trump budget for the tramp thought
that it was spare food that was
going to be thrown out and then
he received a bill on his way
out and they give me food i
figure this stuff they don't want anymore
that's usually how i get food right
i have made my to see john
already
i have a decision to let you
know
so that's it for me we're done
no she hasn't said her decision yet
the ramp up alright i'm ramping up
okay the other cases go on for
quite a while do you want to
go along well enough hey the tramp
i'll take you back i don't have
my decision and i bet you'll be
pretty unhappy that i've done that yeah
i have a mean streak it can
come out
out every once in awhile if i
am the evil one or from actually
myself like judge ursula well i might
be i didn't know you were that
tramp the tramp trump thank you calm
down your honor conte no i won't
calm down typical typical what oh
a mistrial you thought you wanted to
nav the child go on all get
mirza le dragon well if i had
my nice little way i would have
let you off few poor unfortunate saw
on hodge and it's so you just
said there'll be more like questions and
stuff that's no
why didn't you pay
so it's a bail situation telling laden
pay well why didn't i pay for
the restaurant again i i i'm just
ah you know i'm just a dog
i don't and you don't have a
wallet
if you're gonna take a lady out
on another excursion you think you're not
going you're under oath do you have
a wallet
i guess i have a wallet what
kind but i don't know what it
is because i'm a dog did you
steal it from my humans pocket with
your mouth i think that it was
it looked like it was a like
it was he was purposely putting it
in his pocket in such a way
did you think it was a joy
to drop on the
no i didn't know i'm gonna go
on with my sentence he added okay
he's got an attitude yes he added
it was coming out his pocket such
a way that i was like this
guy probably wanted to fall out of
his pocket because his worn anymore i
will just gently grip it with my
teeth grip and ran to help him
out grip and rice still with the
broad that you took to the telling
in place you mean judge yourself lady
i asked you a question late in
a rod that you know her name
is lady lady and i are still
together okay and i but we're not
like why didn't she point out exclusive
you know what i mean why didn't
she pay i'm sorry am i asking
too many
questions judge ursula
i'm going to make you into a
teeny tiny little booger in a jar
and take everything good about you and
take it as my own now there's
not much left there to take peter
are you talking you're talking to me
your your name peter pam the tramp
i'm peter yeah it's a struggle what
would you like to exchange
nj um for a beautiful skill um
oh maybe my feet
you know anyone know the skill is
i don't care yeah babe you should
have great head but you've just got
rid of your fucking money yeah either
way we done yeah i can fly
goodbye i can find me on here
right this skill i gave him was
to give good luck jim
yeah yeah how about to receive that's
not a skill see a funny way
i do it is skill to receive
what
peter
i was special skill i'm great at
receiving blow jobs a graded oral six
receiving it
your honor why didn't she pay she
it was a date maybe i'm old
fashioned but when two people go to
a restaurant one of them should pay
should they not well people sure but
what about dog what did i say
oh yeah he caught me in a
court trap
you're on but here's the question tramp
you can talk kacha the tra
ah i can watch world but there's
but no one knows if we don't
talk around people so they don't know
if i can talk
yes they sing to us as if
we understand english made yes they put
food on plates and give it to
us instead of a little table my
decision oh shit oh no you're going
to jail to infinity and beyond oh
yeah but why because he didn't pay
and everyone thinks you're real by ah
i think so yeah oh seem all
right now i'm the yeah you judge
i'm the i'm the bailiff and you
are the criminal scott okay okay okay
oh okay okay okay
whose name do i know all these
things i used the workers here yes
what did you see who do you
have a crush on
someone had a crush on me and
my rare fox had a crush on
good old breyer bear ooh that's a
conflict of interest truly why there's supposed
to be the bitterest of enemies yeah
and he would pop up in the
weirdest places a guy had a career
i felt like he was director yeah
to where i felt like he was
like but only when you are in
the costume
it would be like pop up right
next to me at disneyland i'd be
like what do you do it here
okay like there's um i'm going to
be
roger rabbit oh no wow i prayed
this day would never come to imprison
me
and
ah death rattle okay
um
oh i'm the bailiff i'm the old
hag from snow-white before you know that
mcqueen
and i will george goofy oh mister
goofy
throw your goofy you fuckin weirdo i
fucked up lee oh no you sure
did
balan what's the charge
this little ravage has done something so
dastardly so bastard lee so costarred lee
custard that
i can't bring myself to sing it
lest i turn into even more of
a hug for having uttered those words
say it i gotta hear all about
this well your honor
it is not a pleasure to listen
to you owe solicitation what solicitation our
crime yes you are out there tried
to be a sex worker no i
was trying to solicit one oh i
get it you're
so goofy movie you ooh let me
explain what happened you know jessica jessica
rabbit beautiful wife why does that make
you mad have you seen my nose
why did you try proactiv it doesn't
get rid of warts why would you
try compound wu that's a feat it
works on noses to upfit and goofy
finding yourself of that why would a
weird thrift
well jessica was gone for the evening
anybody want an apple yeah sure yeah
me i want yeah i wouldn't do
it oh huh
save me i'm dying why did this
help he got to x's for eyes
oh boy this is gonna be bad
news for me i'll gonna get disbarred
just because someone died in your court
while i watched it happen the may
live game
are you excuse me i was his
lawyer and your emails this is highly
irregular uncle remus okay okay you smell
different yeah we had to do some
changes with all right uncle remus your
clyde will be tried posthumously really because
ooh yeah times when this happen
and the charges are immediately dismissed on
indefinitely court oh okay well loosen what
do you got
your client is charged on woodcutters solicitation
he had a story that we never
got to hear what i could understand
and i reviewed his case
his wife jessica rabbit was cheated on
him with ah christopher lloyd the famous
actor not judge do but christopher law
she came into contact with him while
they were filming the movie so she's
real she's real he was a guy
pretending to be a good thing but
she's real and ah well you know
one thing led to another and he
found himself on the other end of
the adultery stick and um
what who did roger rabbit my clients
dead client oooooh so um he went
out there and he saw a beautiful
woman on the street and he asked
to go home with her he said
please so he saw a pretty lady
and he didn't know what to do
he didn't know what to say yeah
ooh yeah yes and he said please
he was very courteous to her and
then after their encounter she expected a
tip of some sort and ah
and unfortunately yeah he did not know
that it was not a consensual encounter
that it was instead that she was
a prostitute a sex worker sorry so
she just wanted to tip well you
know what my money paid you know
what they mean when they say a
tip meaning like no i don't know
i guess this lawyer has been with
a few
new sex worker is this true it
will look like every night you with
this beautiful woman walking right oh sure
let me later yeah oh oh boy
how's that working out for you all
right i'm ready to make my ruling
please i find roger rabbit and his
lawyer both to be good guilty you
just want to say that because it
feeds into the whole guha i mean
i kissed it not gucci and that's
okay
i'll give you that edge i love
you to infinity and beyond your going
to jail if i play today at
the oh hey fun time fun fun
time time i was three fun time
that a true reacher that was a
known neck can
not be the stigler straight-up creature we
gotta tell everyone about our shows that
we're doing we've got to do it
yeah we haven't alive threesome coming up
ah come out and see us in
toronto on september nineteenth at our old
stomping grounds the queen elizabeth theatre it
is literally two weeks from today so
come out you can be there see
us
for just relapse come out come out
wherever you over you happen to be
and then watch girl
i'm not in this movie but you
are both in this movie watch the
between two ferns movie it's coming out
in ah in just ah two weeks
just to leave just two weeks you
can wait two weeks can't you owe
weeks mo trailer just came out this
week please watch it once and share
with your friends wisely
e
i buy
uh