three
now they're doing karate
we must be cobra kai
oh yes welcome to three years what
happened we're talking about the show this
is
which i watch every week i've never
seen and now they're covering corona never
coming corona scots and i thought you
were gonna say she's lawrence you guys
now you're doing corona corona and scots
and i thought another to karate and
then we started very briefly riffing on
the idea that i guess somehow the
producers of this are thinking
king cobra kai because he most popular
show on we gotta start doing karate
on the show i would love it
if every character on that had some
justification getting into goo that's how you
figure out that's how they all know
each other i don't know how they
like their family or whatever but they
definitely omitted to dojo or so they
definitely are family but i like the
the first episode of this is us
blew my mind not to be dramatic
but idea at the end of it
i went ah oh my god well
i say technically i still want to
see it's i don't want any spoilers
okay technically i was still so is
the best one oh and it's it
just gets worse and worse and worse
i watch it backwards i just mean
because there's a good twist
and you're like wow but there's a
good there's too much like my three
last night okay and of course mandy
moore plays a sixty five year old
or older what yeah oh my god
are you serious i don't know yeah
because i always think about time travel
you know tell me anything about time
travel it's just a story of slide
back and forth yeah exactly don't tell
all my love this was a few
years ago after after some super bowl
couple of years ago they hyped up
like the season premiere of this zone
yeah it was happening after it yeah
yeah and so it got they really
hyped it up and so they got
all these people that has never hired
show something yeah yeah okay they got
all these people that never seen that
show to watch it
and just i've never seen the show
but watching people's reactions to it online
like what is it like putting them
through a super bowl makes no sense
everyone's like oh and then you're like
watching this row usually like they would
have a football star like guest star
on the show you need something stupid
it on hey it's wide receiver i
don't know if you're very sensitive about
your weight
i just pick on me to know
look brighter
i played in the superbowl
and maybe winning the ha two ways
yeah when you guys doing guess what
i want and we only made one
and maybe i lost but at least
he doesn't want to jinx it so
he refuses to shoot that one when
you watch the super bowl do you
go wrong oh huh whoa i feel
super raw
rah rah and you have my superbowl
party that was the last party whenever
to and my dad was there and
we were just talking about yeah hi
oh hello to your dad and i
wanted to talk to kula because he
wrote his miami across laos and he
rode his bike across loud yeah and
she has a bike now do you
think he's her dad
and my oh my god something to
tell you fascinating cool third dad reveal
means are die rather
um that would be a great conversation
they should have it on mike on
these very mikes oh wow how bout
it i mean what if it's a
new show about ah and it's called
i rode my bike across and we
just talked to people they'll go there
my dad across anything that allows a
highwire hello i like the name of
the show is i rode my bike
across yes so women and then ah
alright
you've if you've written your bike across
any anything the grand canyon a squirrel
it's own right
by the way welcome to freedom i'm
scott q i'm paul i'm lauren and
ah this is us this truly is
us it can't be anyone else you
know never would be anyone you think
we have more of a claim to
the phrase this is us than the
show seriously we've been doing the show
so
since they started but well after they
started but our catchphrase is way fewer
episodes is we be three oh let
me write me that's right i thank
you i did forget that yeah we
got it right okay we be three
also the pretzel gang the ah crocodile
grew them three them boys where we
also have our individual identities oh what's
that which i wrote down
oh shit can i on your underwear
and while you look for that yeah
sure i was thinking of this in
the way here because i have this
gator adhere and it's blue and i
don't love that it's second time you've
said blue on the show what else
is able blew me away
harry re this is ice keeping track
of the different ways i say
it's my thing
i'm open to big what happens soon
like a very mild army job
i've one weird kid
talk about that um but like everyone
else has stopped i know but it's
still doing whatever it is month later
so um so it has blue one
and my question is if we didn't
put in any any die to these
things they'd be like brown and that's
why we
any okay so like weekly or ones
you think they put clear dion know
so maybe they're clear but why don't
we go maybe blue and it's like
well what why do i need it
to be blue can't you just i'd
rather be clear well it's isn't more
enticing so yeah like it's it's it's
something more than water doing something where
like there are fu
foods in nature that are blue that
it's supposed to remind you of like
blueberries or reminds me of zero whole
fruit you know what i mean i
think it's an old thing it's supposed
to be like it probably share yeah
oh glacier freeze thy get work i
nailed it i burn even though ice
is clear it's reflecting the ocean so
that's why it's blue the ice is
reflecting the ocean in your freezer
i mean in name
ice isn't blue way but the you're
talking about like glue no no no
okay now the water is water right
ocean is clear as well yeah and
it's reflecting the sky that's what it
is so yeah oh yeah sky famously
blue yeah it gets it no what
is it he said blue oh i
thought it was a reference sky
famously blue that you were saying it's
sad when you see a picture of
a polar bear float okay are you
sampling ice cap oral and it's just
about to go die
and it's like hey photographer rings that
kumiko a room in your budget should
give him the fish or something it's
what about teacher manuf fish well teach
a polar to asia polar that's what
a great show for amy poehler yeah
teaching jabari she pretty he said
oh no she picks one subject she
has nothing she has no knowledge of
like physics or i don't know i'm
not presuming that amy poehler doesn't know
anything about physics there's no way to
assure she knows a lot about at
all women do now when did we
start all of us collectively as a
country caring that nick offerman makes things
out of
would ah
every suddenly was like you know he
woodworker i guess i should feel like
that was like ten years ago yeah
i mean it was when parks and
rec started another thing on parks and
rec know i think it was a
thing of they made it because it
got popularized because like suddenly it was
like hey here's this actor who's very
funny on the show i mean it's
cool and and it
hard being written about like here's a
weird quirk i mean like what weird
quirk do you have that that people
should write about i fart in my
pillow before i go to bed
every night
it's always weird
they say it's unusual when you do
i'm to say
only six nights not since harrison ford
have we cared this much about an
actor who can make a bookshelf this
he also make book shows a commenter
was not like jesus himself is christ
knew that yeah he he would ah
would destroy yeah he would do it
for directors and it's weird when you
see i know we've talked about this
but when you see someone like him
pop up like he's in
serpico as a cop with maybe one
line really yeah maybe one line or
maybe he's just standing in a hallway
slime someone has one less thing to
do that's harrison ford i think if
why are you ignoring him yeah he's
he's a major stuff and the guy
from star wars gonna be you should
say hi harrison ford we should decide
who movie stars are going to be
and then make
sure they never do roles like that
so it's not distracting in well i
just watched diehard for the first time
nigh yeah is this for ah one
of your for my patreon i did
a watch along if anyone wants and
you are like the guy from known
lighting why i was confused because i
was like what did he do before
this like he's what happened you know
and then we kind of
went into the character bruce willis re
so well is because a bruno of
course he was a bartender is but
for them was like jesus christ our
lord himself was just like random little
parts like man who walks into the
bar like literally his eye mtv is
that yeah a lot of experience because
he walked in one every night and
then go to he was on a
show for sixty episodes right before diehard
moonlighting
i don't think so is that a
show yeah yeah i thought it was
something else so it's all regardless i
thought oh that makes sense huh
because i was like how do you
become like such a huge star lie
wow you're just being man who walked
into the bar one time well he
didn't he got on moonlighting on the
already pretty early in his career absolutely
and that made him a massive star
yeah i'm going to scroll all the
way but more in this show was
huge moonlighting was you shy it was
like loss
just basically holy shit
did you just watch an episode we
lost i just paused the show and
you it for forty seven that part
where it was like last um but
but yeah he was a huge part
of the cultural conversation and then he
became a movie star with comedies like
blind date and stuff but diehard was
the first time he had ever done
an action thing and people were like
really this comedy guy
shimla
so people weren't on board well so
they also unexplained something because one of
the trivia facts about the movie was
that they didn't put they took his
picture off the post because they thought
people wouldn't want to see him because
yeah people just knew him as like
the smirking kind of like funny guy
that's so weird who was who would
like do rapid fire dialogue on moonlighting
and that's why they put the the
original po
oscar was alexander godunov
sitting on top of that nugget to
me tower almost like it'd like i've
been shoved up his butt
oh yeah video oh oh my god
i love that
yeah the man writes this is real
this is real it's not real
i mean yes there is a video
that is real a man falls down
the stairs his recorder flute rolls off
the um console table and into his
asshole where it then makes the sound
of a tube
a beautiful beautiful videos wonderful sentiment it's
that laura dorothy yes of course dave
ferguson repeated it
alright so it came to me then
our friend paul john examined it like
this pewter film frame by frame and
he made his own
you only said that to me
wow i would love to see a
movie like j f k where john
is like in a court room pointing
to frames
it's like why are you doing this
why we have no question i'm not
a judge
i told you about what happened during
j f k right when i watched
that there was a screaming kid in
the movie for the first minutes three
hours and forty five minutes or something
and just running up and down the
aisle screaming hours for the first three
hours no that's a new dog three
hours know and if i let me
look up the right side that's also
it's extremely long
oh midway around doing that in the
movie here you walk out to the
front and you go you gotta get
this kid out of here you can't
fuck yeah yeah like sisters get stitches
i don't care give me some stitches
get this thing out how many stitches
gonna be but i was three hours
twenty six minutes too long so the
for the three i would start screaming
running down the aisle so for the
first
every hour i was just trying to
further verse three hour i was in
the back the second to last row
and they'll run and these people were
in the front row and and scram
baby note okay it was a family
i'm sorry why are they doing this
it was a mom and her four
kids don't go to the to learn
about history we have to see the
most boring movie for you guys and
and
ruined house last time i was back
when kevin costner was like you had
to go see every kevin costner film
because it was an essential you know
what i mean yes in joe biden's
america maybe ah but um no cost
to put that hamster up his ass
i'm just mixing it up
but so she so so it was
a woman her screaming baby and then
heard like ah two or three other
screaming kids were running up and down
the aisles but the baby the baby
was crying throughout this is so the
edge of chaos yes it's so amazing
it was insanity j f k but
that ten she was way at the
front
and i was in the back and
i was like whatever i'll deal with
it but annoyed everyone annoyed she finally
like ah after three hours right right
in the final act half hour before
it ends she spanks her kids and
goes come on we're getting out of
here in the baby's crying and she
she trudges up the aisle
how to take them out and everyone
applauds and unfortunately the old woman right
behind me in the back row applauds
right as she passes her oh no
and she and the woman i've i
know i've told this story by apologized
anyone who started but lauren maybe hasn't
i don't think so um has the
the one yes the woman turns to
the old woman goes
you dare make fun of me when
my kid has an attack of the
ships and then open hand while absurd
in the face
and the woman's going ah henry go
get her and her yoga her husband
like crazy doesn't know what to do
so row two runs out and i'm
laughing so fucking hard and um so
then a half hour goes by the
movie finally ends and i walk outside
and the police are there and
though the woman i think is in
restraint so yeah it's just like squall
it an arab wow amazing amazing time
at the movies horrible incidents the movie
in the cell then the balcony is
closed this same theater by the way
where i went to go see a
different movie i can't remember what it
was juice probably which can with the
scot i know you
no he is sousa six um and
ah fuck is that ah different screen
though maybe it wasn't sim sorry different
screen but we're we're sitting there
and there's this guy was green there's
now i can picture it there's this
guy behind us who's like rocking back
in forth in a seat and kind
of muttering to himself this is during
the previews mister jerk off came to
town
any and i say to my friend
hey do you want to or no
my friend says to me because i
don't notice it he goes hey do
you want to move and i go
i like these seats are we're we're
cool here he goes ah there's a
guy behind us who's acting weird and
he's like started going i didn't mention
it
oh and rocketing back now so you
can't even stay at that planet my
parses didn't kill him and he's kicking
the back of my friends seed which
i didn't know because i didn't feel
it so i would have been like
oh sure let's move these kicking your
seat but this guy's just being a
weirdo it's the it's the trailer for
a certain movie that demi moore and
woody harrelson are in and and robert
redford
ird and i've no idea and decent
proposal but let's see so so finally
robert redford says to demi moore in
the trailer
or he says to woody harrelson can
i sleep with your wife for one
million dollars and the guy stands up
in his seat and shouts an indecent
proposal
and it's it's wow so he just
i want to see that movie is
that good ah yeah but ah adrian
lyne
wow and this is right as we
have stood up to move and we're
like crouching and he shouts it like
basically in our faces more like ah
franklin was it doug benson ah shouting
that yeah i would have thought that
was funny if it had been absolutely
do you think this guy that's all
all he would but like anything he
says the only thing he says and
then he did he leave after that
i wonder if it was a guy
like like us who was just being
funny but he was low now and
he was like that if he was
with his friends it would have been
like haha alright he's making this shaking
and kicking the seat and stuff adds
another ally think he was titillated by
the whole
how indecent that proposal was i mean
how sounds like he was also condemning
it that's true on a scale of
decent to indecent whoa what do you
think of that proposal see more and
i think it's okay would you would
you do it first of all if
someone for a million bones and the
guys who robert redford in the nineties
he is the one offering yeah he's
he's offering yeah
he's i'm married twenty harold you're married
to nick offerman i'm married to nick
offerman but robert redford can make one
million dollars out of what do i
need for a million dollars you're married
you're married to your husband currently but
robert redford comes up to you currently
know your current husband your current situation
but currently robert renault not currently nineties
robert read
eifert not ninety years old he's a
golden box she's ninety years old he's
gotta look kind of old in the
early nine yeah if if copper red
looks good i will pay you a
million dollars to have during q i'd
go okay
and he doesn't want me to watch
the good i don't think micromolar ok
alright you don't think my going to
watch a million dollars i want the
money on the table
well january did an episode of the
big ones podcast about that it's a
podcast where they discuss like moral dilemmas
um but it's a comedy podcast it's
a mandela and i'm really maria blue
sushi and so yeah i'm trying did
that and i was taught yeah yeah
yeah yeah episode was great i really
enjoyed it
it was fun guys went off on
a tangent about donuts that was really
enjoyable as do nice um but we
did so the subject was the the
indecent proposal and what would you do
and everything in janie and i almost
got in an argument because show she
was seeing it from the i almost
got into an argument
she was sort of seeing it from
the standpoint of who cares about the
husband this is her decision oh i
well her body her choice yeah yeah
yeah and i was like yeah yeah
but but mentally we were married couple
i think shares the thing about the
about the proposal and it isn't
decent absolutely truly isn't it's indecent proposal
but it's not something a decent person
would ever propose to another do so
for you and your husband get on
the same page ngo won't get this
million dollars and then we're gonna pay
off whereby a house or do whatever
you know whatever you want to do
together with the money and they work
this is what they did a movie
then well
let's forget this ever okay that's what
they do in the movie okay so
she doesn't know i do want to
watch a roll around in the money
there in vegas they like put it
out on the bed this is where
the trope of like rolling around in
the money sort of conservative from that
i can't think of it like another
example of it on film before then
i have told him saying dan
then i don't think they invented like
people would talk about data did it
for sure but i don't think anyone
ever in life no nil capture on
film no yeah it's a lot like
porn because it's too hard to get
people to how to capture people doing
it right you know what it is
in documentary you're trying to do it
the money's not as much as you
think it is like it doesn't really
cover you well that's why would you
like it needs to
and you pay us in woods was
his ah the most famous writers right
i did this like this you have
one condition sketch duo were in the
u a long time ago um and
we wanted to take a picture where
we were sitting at you i'm christina
last longer
yeah we did on snapchat ah we
we wanted to take a picture of
my friend day in a tub covered
in candy like all over us so
we bought like what we thought was
a ton of candy and it was
like like covered like nothing like the
bonnet like the just yeah we've we've
put a blanket on ourselves put the
candy
yeah but it still wasn't enough and
then someone just photoshopped it of course
because what we should've done the entire
oh yeah you should have been naked
in the tub together yeah just photoshop
candy on top of it was it
a funny picture we happy with it
it turned out good yeah who's our
postcard you know to come see us
at the playground theater the playground fear
ah i wish i could have seen
one of those
if i ah if i could go
back in time that's the one thing
i would do that's so sad i
heard you'd be disappointed what else are
you in chicago when i'm there um
ah back in what years is mrs
b two thousand and six
you should go ah during i mean
if you want to do the stuff
i did go say hi to barack
obama go to like quit smoking horrible
bars with a bunch of improvisers
no thanks so well in any case
learn what i was gonna say as
they roll around in the money and
they're all happy but as you can
expect that's only halfway through the film
it's gonna get emotional then woody harrelson
can't take it and so he he
they fight all the time about it
because he thinks that she was too
flip about
you know doing it and she doesn't
love him enough
and then he's an architect so he
goes any e starts signs a building
that's like i hit my wife it's
like it's not gaza
i call it i hate my wife
closet
but they break up and he goes
and he he gives a lecture about
how every brick and leisure he every
brick can be an amazing building and
it sure it's just a break now
but it could be a part of
an amazing thing and students are like
well you're fucking blow in my mind
i like that i forgot to build
you made the material yes and then
i forgot what happens after that but
um but but yeah alright but they
aren't what's amazing about that movie and
i can't remember if i've seen it
or not is that the the way
they get into such dire straits is
there's so stupid there
to stupid people they blow all their
money um you know with their businesses
blow so many times on the show
ca all three of us i said
it was like losing blue
and then they're like okay here's our
plan
go to vegas and gamble know who
we're gonna win we're gonna win yes
it doesn't make any sense yeah idea
of gambling that money is the dumbest
don't ever go to vegas unless you
have money to lose that's the thing
i am
i go my i'll give myself a
budget for gambling yeah right exactly and
you're fine losing it's done and that's
just my play money and it's fun
because i will bet so low that
i'll make it last hours exactly exactly
having a good time the challenge all
but you're not betting the same thing
each hand or when i play roulette
which is just a random ass game
and it's like oh is it some
of the worst odds in vegas and
yeah but i had to look shit
i always thought there's the worst thing
is i always get to a point
where i've i'm up like a lot
i when i somehow i'm down gone
i once went to vegas tonight it
i was doing i was doing the
whole like
ah bet the swingers thing
what happens there
i remember one part of that movie
and it's something about an answering machine
i suspect that's the best part of
the movie yeah for sure it's a
good movie um but i was doing
the thing where you bet on red
each time you just double your bet
ah every time or different advice
oh absolutely your friend my snipes
ah but i was like you know
how i met him when i was
the fifty six passenger wow you know
how hard it is to to for
for it to be read like more
than eight times in a row or
something you know so that's what you're
basically betting on is like you you
bet five dollars and then if it
doesn't come up red you bet ten
and then you bet twenty
any then you bet forty at any
bet eighty one hundred and sixty etc
and then finally like it'll end up
black and you win the original five
here why i know like gamble okay
math oh lots of mad fun but
you know but the problems by like
yeah because you just go but there's
things on her like shit
yep and i just put it yeah
and i just put it on different
numbers that mean something to me right
and then eventually it's gonna work out
sixty nine six na and thirty five
thirty four
then if it was very for do
it all and say what is michigan
one is missionary tuesday night
xeno because it's number two v three
is diarrhea unrelated ah
that i had heard i think the
sixty nine thing was based on like
positions of the kama sutra or whatever
then this is when i was a
kid and then finally someone explained to
me no it's because the nine in
the six are like opposites of each
other which is what you're because like
the the ball of the six is
is not since all of this as
a nine is the boobs
ooh zip v that these numbers maybe
i do like that but i was
gonna say about the roulette thing the
problem is is i did end up
getting to a point where it was
red or it was black ten times
in a row or something and then
you're just betting these insane sounds like
my friend wesley knew what he was
talking yeah yeah that's horrible you're betting
these insane amounts
just trying to get your original five
dual five back and then it if
it ever winds up on zero that's
the other thing and it's just loud
double green but technically if you had
a lot of money you could just
win five dollars at a time but
it was like this isn't even fun
anymore i'm just trying to win five
dollars at a time and scares i
want to win thousands yeah i want
to have a big bucket of chips
ps to walk around everybody sees me
go allies the mera chips i might
have said this controversial at some point
we talked about gambling but when stephanie
and taig got married umm we all
every all the guests we stayed at
this casino hotel which ones you want
to give him a shout out maybe
they'll give us all the the three
of us free rooms no i don't
remember what it was called but it
cause it was like i love to
get married guys with youtube drip but
wasn't vegas we would have a horrible
time
we whatever you don't want i want
to do ah tell your story then
i saw all i wanna say is
it was it was in mrs sippy
my ss isis itp iser wet anyway
some like that yeah mississippi because she's
from is yeah take it from yeah
that's why it was there when mrs
that's why he's we stayed at this
random hotel because i go up
close ha co-op hey alright is lawrence
dad your dad
and um the funniest thing was that
every like all of us comedians all
play l gambling together and screaming for
each other and oh wow that's fun
it was there as a hanford and
um a lot of fun people it
was at the craps table um suzi
barrett it was always was fun always
all different colors so we all got
nicknames for our chip color and then
we were like you know just going
crazy and i remember my cancers were
brown i went to vegas with him
and i taught like all the birthday
boys how to play blackjack and my
god can you imagine being a fly
on the wall o trying to educate
them about anything okay idiot you know
what one is right
missionary now i want with all the
bang bang writers ah ah for like
a trip in between one of our
seasons or whatever but i remember i
remember i was like ah okay this
is how you play blackjack and then
within like ten minutes i think i
had one like seven hundred dollars or
whatever all of them yeah
yeah and they're like whoa and then
ah i said ok i'm going to
bed and then i hear that you
played it all night for the next
seven hours
that's fun
are you going to say if we
went to vegas we would be high
no i've never seen a like one
of those big show other fun to
do oh i would like to do
that i would like to go to
vegas and see like cirque du soleil
a or like so young i'd see
that shit sure yeah we saw ms
dear i think was our first mean
cool up was our first ah like
cirque du soleil show we ever saw
it was
really good there and say ten and
then we took a we took a
cab this is early in our dating
relationship when she was fifteen we took
a cab there and you explained our
cabs where
we pay him
he's forced to drive us um but
then i saw i didn't the cab
ride wasn't all that long i didn't
think and i saw i could see
our hotel in the distance i was
like let's just walk back and she's
in heels i didn't think about oh
my god the war and yes oh
my god we're walking at one of
these birds squirrels there is um and
so
the walk turned out to be like
an hour and she was gone fucking
madman by and by the so vegas
so many of these stories by the
thirty five minute mark it was kinda
like you want when listing another cab
or whatever you know is like look
where i was like okay we only
a half hour i'll see it it's
still tiny
yeah oh my god that's the worst
ever though that is a very vegas
thing too i feel like in vegas
like the goal is to be as
fucked up but functional as you can
be that's like the only way to
have a good time but i went
there for like a bachelor party um
that was like coed a couple of
years ago
grid of educational five years ago but
um i feel like no matter how
much weed i smoked i was never
stoned enough for what was required of
the to be in vain order to
enjoy yourself because i just think vegas
is really disgusting yeah it's it's i've
i have a hard time
getting that idea out of my head
yeah um right that's why i feel
like the shows would be more please
shit on me it's fun to see
the show it's just like if you
please don't shit on me we went
during that trip we went to see
ya read penn and teller i've definitely
told you this story i don't win
when right which one doesn't talk with
eller
tell her oh awesome points did they
tell her disappear and he was literally
high like he was talking like that
pen was oh that's right you so
you said this on whatever less so
how did we get back to this
gallery hey guys baby usually michael jackson's
their touchstone know you have a mini
pen not having a void you know
what i'm not gonna complain if it's
very sweet switch if it switches the
same job by those glasses he was
trying to sell also my cousin got
married in vegas
um a million years ago while i
was like just in my early twenties
and it was that was really fun
because right she had elvis at our
wedding right you know the whole thing
yeah i'd talked about on the show
about the wedding i went to with
the guy getting married to someone for
a green card and we had to
take a bunch of picture yes yes
yes that's the only wedding i've ever
been to vegas but it is
it's like i know someone who did
that oh someone we all know yeah
they have talked about it in the
podcast but i don't know if i
want to um yeah you don't want
to wait up in case it's yet
i don't know but they did that
briefly umm this man needed um a
green card and man offered to pay
her to get meh
married and she needed money so wait
who's the person we know the woman
has a man the woman oh i
go law she's still up there can
you can you imagine collapsing thing she
smudging up their um but anyway very
fascinating and then they never like live
together anything it was never like right
they never console
made the marriage they never had to
like have a relationship really but did
enough to make a sex tape but
then it's approved to cover a couple
years to check this out i didn't
want to do this but here's our
sex tape know i went to one
vegas wedding um which was dave foley's
wedding to crissy guerrero oh because he
was in he was in a bad
marriage for a really long time couldn't
get a divorce right foot finally she
wouldn't have got his former wife would
not grant the divorce wow and ah
they're too nice o'leary canada that's horrible
so like oh you just work it
out and you imagine someone saying no
you know ah yea we're there we're
living in different countries it was wild
oh my god
and so finally um he was able
to get divorced and they immediately scheduled
a wedding in vegas and so it
was like a last minute thing and
a bunch of us went yeah it
was really it was really fun just
to go on a bus or did
everyone make lu lu ou flu that's
the best because you're just in and
you're out that's right nan years
go by years goober they get divorced
in vegas and yeah they were baby
we all had to go back watch
them sign the papers then more years
go by unesco they get back together
whoa in vegas yes all of these
things happened in vegas
what happens in vegas cause it's stashing
kutcher
i went to a friend of mine's
bachelor party in vegas where we took
the party bus and um you know
big group of guys and and it
was it was one of the o
g one of these things where was
like you know hey we're gonna do
the typical vegas bachelor party sort of
steaks cigars strippers and we're gonna mm
murder a hooker so me and my
friends we're rooming together and they say
hey we're we're ah we you know
we we went to a couple of
strip clubs and was boring or whatever
and so they go hey we're gonna
hire these strippers to come to one
of our rooms and put on a
show for us like
two strippers putting on a show for
us i'm immediately uncomfortable yeah i'm immediately
so
ah so we go okay well let
us know and then we never heard
anything about it and we go i
guess it didn't happen we went to
sleep were the two people they forgot
to tell forgot
out of our name knew you would
be like fifty or sixty anyway god
they forgot to call us and so
the next day the one good thing
that came out of it was the
next day they went around collecting for
the stripper show and were like you
didn't mean never called us so we're
not paying and that's good but what
this show like a vaudeville thing
yeah i'm diana today
nah main alright we have to take
break we'll be right back
we're back and we are the peacemaker
the patch worker and the midnight ogre
master nicotine which one am i you're
the midnight coker i am either am
i the peacemaker you're the patch maker
oh you're the peacemaker because you look
like george clooney in the nineties that's
right
that's why i'm the peacemaker what do
we talk about george clooney saying he
uses a flow be to cut his
own hair we talked about this but
i mean look hey we got a
why not we should because we've told
the same other two stories everyone can
stop emailing us i just finally i
just don't get to do it believe
that i saw that too and i
also don't believe that but anyways it
isn't
does you have it close to the
head like his when he first started
doing e r and he had the
scenes for the kaiser know the kaiser
permanente's a role that kaiser with kaiser
rolls um i just don't buy it
at all what else is a fly
when i'm fuckin trillion billionaire because it's
covert you're not gonna he wasn't saying
during co he was
saying he always has always been doing
that well don't tell me what a
floppy does well i didn't really know
about what flip does fluffy tell he
told told me but it's a it's
a tool that you like come through
here and it cuts it and actually
now there's this new tool you need
or you guys neither of you have
seen this commercial no no
seen here with the nescafe ones with
no shade vito he does here were
the two in the commercial that's it
that's part of why it's even weirder
it's like he's all like advertising this
it's an old product right i mean
it's vit yeah like so yeah so
he's he i thought he was kidding
with the woman didn't get it that's
how i felt nah it goes yeah
i do it and then i just
thought even in his lie
like self-effacing way where he talks about
how bad he wasn't batman even though
like he's not the problem in batman
the movies the problems about another things
yeah but he you know um but
he loves praying so here's the thing
i feel like we're being praying okay
now but i i kind of i'm
curious about a flowy because mike really
needed a haircut and we cannot get
one
and i feel like i might there's
this new product i saw this commercial
for those like something tremor whatever turbo
trim or some fuckin shit and it's
like it's like the same picture about
trim send us a turbo trim so
we can test it yeah and it's
thirty dollars from crocs we're all people
who have been talking about crocs are
the sales of crocs are
up during the pandemic because of us
thank you for telling the game the
crocs we gave this talk so um
we're the crocodile crew and you don't
send us free crocs rocks can't mean
i don't even have crocs right now
least you could do some superior medicinal
crop i don't have crocs yet it's
insanity okay so turbo tax or something
like that turbotax yeah
and and it looks like it starring
what actually do the job but i
don't know it's kind of like a
safe way to kind of buzz your
hair without going short it's like a
vacuum thing so it is that qm
so it pulls it out of it's
root it's pulled yet pulls it out
of it's roots it's too powerful it's
it's a jet edge and
what no but vacuum technology what would
it be for re one the hair
so that it only cuts like trim
zil interesting yes super weird i i've
been cutting my own hair i've given
myself now two haircuts since the pandemic
and i'm due for third as you
say i just gave myself one you'll
not do well but a lot
of product and because it did not
resent my well trimmed my ends greeks
have like all these split ends and
it's all gross but let's use on
but i i a cutlass its way
makes hair so long ago but began
to pandemic like day two and i
did such a horrible job and it
looked like such shit like the back
wasn't that bad really honestly yeah the
was why couldn't you cut his hair
easy because when you did at it
because what i did and i i
kind of knew immediately what i did
wrong instead of like cutting like
up into the hair i kind of
like crosby's weird lines
i looked so fucking ugly and then
i then we had someone come to
our porch and cut our hair in
july and so i was like super
long scissors and yeah we had masks
and we were outside right and she's
she was fantastic but it's pretty expensive
and then i was like no i
just paid all this money for us
have haircuts we're not even gay
going anywhere yeah and then he hasn't
had one since july july that was
when i did my first of december
january um that's a long time that's
a really long time to not have
a haircut well how's he look though
do you like it well he's had
longish hair so at some points it's
all it's not horrible but it's like
it's just that
ing like you want to shape it
as you're going if you're gonna throw
it out and i like his hair
shorter personally my hair styling is always
like you have the ability to have
long hair why not have ability if
you had long hair i believe that
would be a problem your hair continues
to grow i can't imagine what have
you put you have the details yeah
whoa you a different person
my hair with i will say in
the red hot chili peppers photos that
we were in that for for one
episode of red chili peppers that is
the longest my hair has been for
thirty years so you can industry thank
you but that was we took those
like the day before i cut it
in july when i saw you guys
i cut my hair for our special
cause trip but um wow
but i knew he would be sitting
in a car so how do you
do it do you put a mirror
and the mirror in the bathroom back
please don't please don't speak something please
don't speak doors locked you abbey you
gotta dig into a resin rubber like
glass tables do you have any idea
what we're seeing right now no god
damn you
you're person here i know a lot
of what you guys talk about no
i'm not saying yes it's a fault
of yours i'm saying you need idea
because you know actually somebody dies
comment that somebody mentioned um that they
thought this was like a weird comment
i i i made a reference you
guys didn't get yeah and they thought
i didn't get that i even made
it
wow exception one what do you think
i'm just saying full lyrics to a
song and no one gets it and
i i don't know that i'm saying
i said it's a rare condition in
this day and age okay which goes
awesome right no tv songs like this
day newt now i read any good
news
family matters a bow page love and
tradition of the brand is ah some
people don't know even harder to file
keepers full house but it does something
kremlin oh wow crossover was family matters
with the theme songs and actually mix
them up on it yes but i
said that no one reacted i didn't
care i didn't go butts from
i'm that i don't it was just
whatever exactly and somebody's like didn't even
know she said it it's interesting that
everyone goes all the time it's like
who cares everyone has like a cultural
blind spot of imam of um whatever
like children's shows were on from the
age of when they were like eighteen
shouldn't know until they have kids you
don't even know what i mean
like whether i have i'm sure there's
a million things i don't know but
if you wanna hear blossom sure i
do okay
piano goes like this
dude i don't know about the future
that's anybody's guess a notary's a login
node impressed fire up your data paper
i gave you oh yes ababa
what does this have to lose my
opinion nation the sun is going to
show alesha and miami alec yeah i
know yeah yeah but like who is
she in the show she's the daughter
she's the main shit ah her dad
who's single dad because the models pen
and paper have to do with her
story ah it's just as fun
one son and she just dances so
tasting the the theme she's like it's
all white background and and her dad's
playing piano and then she's like dancing
around and like doing all these little
and her outfit changes old time and
she's like
sounds awesome and that's terrifying now call
me cat is blossom grownup and she
once called cat nah i'm just kidding
but that's my wow my dog's new
show oh i see yeah
did you see blossom blossoming dog day
afternoon ma'am bala baluk may m obama
level my mg ya fiala tata
dodge she's just an extra in the
courtroom it's interesting
i don't believe you but
she was in beaches as a child
so i don't believe she'd be an
extra beaches get stitches she
ah you believe the young that midler
is that greg yeah oh that's cool
that's another movie i've never seen there
aren't like nice movie there there there
are a bunch of movies i've never
seen because i they came out and
i was like oh that's too commercial
i turned my nose up at them
and sure man cool guy so andy
ah are you keep talking i'm gonna
move some television show eight is enough
yes i am and now there was
that was a spinoff wasn't it because
the coach was actually on growing pains
no just okay now it
okay now eight is enough who's that
oh i like dick van patten you
know look at this guy with betty
buckley are you familiar with grant good
eve broadway star many booklets right i'm
familiar with willie ames well yes i
am because he was on charles and
char yeah yeah
only show before the item rich okay
this show doesn't really bring the girl
to me it isn't enough to fill
a house with our lives it's beautiful
song always spend days lug bride and
shiny new da times and i always
love shows like so many
kid i talk during loss wow
you could have i wouldn't dream of
it i wanted to yeah it was
crazy begging for you to say whether
she was pleading with her eyes oh
damn urine is feeling herself i'm gonna
let her run with it myself i'm
feeling myself so
um go ahead feel good
well it is all it is enough
with duh i'm not going to sing
this song in pieces the dumb ross
onto the pool in your suits and
die sobbing oh look he walks in
submerges never guys
i don't know what i would do
and so what i would do i
think i would run into the pool
and try to get you that's what
i hope you will
it is enough as one of those
shows that backend this like brady bunch
don't know what i would do where
baptize i'm not i don't know that
i could save you know you can
it'd be too late i make my
mind even from what he's like him
doing it to himself yeah like if
he was more
you do seriously if he was like
i want to die now just wanted
to suits and then like bow attached
you know weights to himself really just
kind of please stop me at the
waist
well since are heavy i don't know
whether i could get you or not
so you go into the workout room
you grab a twenty five pound weight
hold on each arm and you slowly
just hold the yeah yeah these guys
like oh let's drop this happens is
your head is down in the pool
but your feet are flowing to the
top for your whole rice the weight
so it's key
keeping you down he he drops them
two issues here i got it i
have an elegant solution here i give
an elegant so it was kind of
floating like mario and water elegant balloons
i put the i get down in
there right down in there and i
put the bar of the weight on
the back of my neck that'll kill
ya so that i'm my
head is like down there and then
it's awkward i can't get the weight
off okay but you don't want to
but i don't want to exactly well
no point i use a finger i'm
the nicest guy i can't lift that
weight at that point so at that
point i'm just going screaming the thing
about the weights is the will to
survive always sue
supersedes the desire not to so that's
why you have to do the weights
you know but you can't just hold
the weight so you have to like
make them and like where you can't
get them off when that child crying
masha that's what i'm saying that's why
i put on the back nine yeah
it's it's grim
but i think it's funnier if you
don't have any weights at all you
just decide to walk into the pool
like that too and then for some
reason the pool keeps getting deeper and
deeper and you're just walking there's like
a whole set of stairs we can't
see just
knees below oh hades i get on
there and see for seventy oh well
my god i see the town rising
such a good show that was a
real fun show hades town i was
sobbing i loved it i loved i
loved it so much we got i
was there i saw that show like
oh fuck you i saw that show
in new york ah
when i was there to do some
shows in brooklyn when she's there to
do a certain television show as well
or no that was when i read
i've been to new york more than
once
wow you're so metropole yeah wow i
miss traveling oh my fucking guy i
kind of do i really do you
know what i bob zeiger came on
ah the shuffle the other night and
it made me nostalgic for the tour
yeah i miss going everywhere yeah to
um see you
went to see hades town and i
was with um ah tawny newsome eugene
cordero janet varney we saw the show
we saw hades town and then we
were on our way to the to
the bell house in brooklyn to do
our show and we were in uber
and got a car accident wow we've
talked about a taxi ploughed
into us it was the weirdest thing
um don't you think when you're in
a taxi you're safe and that nothing
can happen to you examine your paying
for it see we're we're setting it
up so i've to tell the same
story i told
e which is that my gym teacher
has got you hit to tell one
story you've told him i'll talk about
tyler and didn't have a spell on
and they stop short and she slammed
her face into the partition cheese and
lost teeth is that what the fiance
song partition is about ah yes it's
about my gym teacher or the only
thing that's wrong with rotation
i thought it was alright so like
that when lauren went to vegas she
saw penn and teller oh my god
and he couldn't even tell her doesn't
talk but penn couldn't talk either and
his voice was like yeah maybe it
was honestly i know i know i'm
like i'm kidding by retiring telling the
story no honestly we're all kidding but
he was like
oh
have you ever been so sick that
you
have you ever been really sick where
you like should we cancel this show
and then and then yes like in
my opinion should he have cancelled but
like i wanna miss a lot of
i would have been disappointed and honestly
i was thrilled to watch when i
saw okay the way he was trying
to talk through it was hilarious
hi so it was wonderful
but so many were there willing so
wishy and said he would have been
bad when were you so sick that
you should have cancelled the show but
you went ahead
oh standup gigs there were standup gigs
where i was under the weather and
you know because you're the only person
you know like there yeah there have
been improv shows with things we've dropped
out of or or standup lineups that
yeah because like i can't do that
tonight but um but yeah there is
i've never been able i don't think
i have i don't think i've ever
been able to say
wow i am too sick to even
go do that show i have to
i have to make a call to
somebody to say refund people's money or
whatever right i don't think so i've
been there i first of all i
should have cancelled the first comedy bang
bang tour after i broke my foot
yeah doing according to my orthopedist but
um
he was like they gave you a
walking boot and you've been walking around
across the country on it like you're
you're crazy because you santa johnny appleseed
i couldn't believe in amy shakes parliamentary
how she went on tour while she
had hyper veces sharada or whatever it
is shoes which is morning sickness essentially
but she was she was pregnant she
was vomiting
profusely the entire pregnancy trying to do
these shows she went on tour across
the country but what one of my
bang bang shows in san diego i
was so sick that we had to
call like a hotel doctor to to
come give me a shot and all
this kind of stuff and i still
went up that night did a show
it's very nice because that's a desperate
need inside
you to connect no no the whole
like the whole
refunding peoples to know it sounds too
hard too much and i know you
could and i could call my agent
go hey i can't make it to
the it just sounds like such a
bummer for all involved i agree but
there were several times on tour paul
where where like you weren't responding to
texts or phone calls we thought you
died maybe three times oh and where
i was like
honestly we had was we have the
hotel call you and then like because
we couldn't get through to you i
remember because i had that one time
my brilliant plan backfired yes one yeah
but i think there were three three
separate times where i was like oh
no i was like i don't know
what i'm going to do i was
i was calculating know who can i
call to fly
fly out to replace him that's psychotic
different different thoughts different thoughts i was
so worried i was like some things
wrong but then the third time i
thought okay now we just sleep now
this is just a thing but yeah
there were a couple of times i
realised i was causing such a panic
i apologize it was a slow panic
that was
is like
the the longer is possibly be what
i think because i always think everyone
died basically instantly anyway like yeah as
soon as you don't see them anymore
yeah well like that person's dead okay
something horrible happens right
sorry your dad like if i if
i'm waiting for someone in their late
or you know whatever anything you know
anytime coop comes downstairs maybe fifteen minutes
later than she's she usually does i'm
like oh for christ's sake i hope
it's not happening jam dead all the
time she thinks i'm dead all the
time
that's terrible i always see my coming
back i don't go said latino i
i really do the thing i've fucked
because i can't say my wife like
this
you can't say anything partner but i
think mike said she'll show up with
so shiny
yeah i'm talking about the same you're
talking about okay
i can only say something times that
i think my my lot right
but it's terrifying when someone's sleeping really
late or something and then you're like
but jamie's also if people don't respond
to her text within thirty seconds she's
like why is this person writing me
back so like like
wow what they're doing but i will
have that about with a text like
they hate me they're mad at me
they hate that i texted that i
will say a problem there but how
much time do you let elapse hours
like i mean i think like if
it gets three hours and i go
i'll remember oh that person never wrote
me back and then i'll think this
is minutes
janie ah a popular text of janie
says are you getting these texts i
will say that i think we've you
know we've been we've been one room
apart for a year we've had so
much like unexpected tragedy in our lives
that now our brains are sort of
like oh shit is this happening and
yeah like my
my parents like the other day i
got a text from my sister saying
like are you guys in china and
i said what why and she says
well ah mom thinks you're in china
because ah she hasn't talked to you
in so long and she heard you
are going to china so she assumed
you are going you're in china not
real
spawning i said well i talked to
her two days ago and we've never
said we're going to china but other
than that yeah
china it's so random especially right now
yeah very weird china's more random than
ever go into china to run random
hospital do right alright we have to
take a break we'll be right back
bay
alright we're back and it's time for
three chair and this one has been
submitted by made this for l m
a m i don't know who l
mam is but thank you for making
that for her or him this is
called mission statements or it might be
like super computers right might be
chair ah it's not a chair
ah okay they call this game mission
statements someone is given a word and
makes a company name from those letters
example cats equals creating actual turmoil and
the other to ask them questions regarding
the business and decide if they'll invest
in the company i like this who
wants to go
first paul you like it so as
you like it be immortal learn and
you get it lauren do you want
to get follower yes probably a short
one to start probably supergirl fraudulence
oh don't get your raw
um your word is
poem
thank you hi welcome and thank you
for a welcome oh we're coming to
see you i'm sorry i thought this
was our office i know i had
myself designed to look exactly like yours
and i blindfolded emily are on the
way here so we didn't know for
ios yeah thanks i stopped playing lol
why did you tell me this was
a great surprise i mean this is
just an investor
i mean isn't it interesting how public
sector off it going to be a
surprise party oh no are you planning
a surprise party for me because you
know today's my birthday ah happy birthday
look i've made you a cake that
looks just like okc at home
this looks exactly like my bacon so
took pictures of your home cakes you
see ten nine tenths scales sorry right
don't have all the ingredients sale already
had solana or medians
use less of everything okay i get
it you already had a kick it
out so you had all the ingredients
you should make you a better one
i'm sorry
no sheila please stay he already had
a kick at home it he's begging
for a surprise party you have everything
you need happy birthday gail now look
dale
yes it's right here on the cake
happy birthday dale oh my name's dale
oh my god dale twins i saw
your name was gayle why did you
put dale so did you make this
with your ironing the cake oh i'd
see the comment here happy birthday comma
well okay still make sense if it's
a happy coma dale and it was
for jail well
yeah okay i have a calm happy
accident alright well i'm a little disappointed
that i've just been taken to a
replica of our office for my big
surprise oh i'm sorry i didn't you're
not a little impressed i mean just
be very clear dale and i are
not in a relationship and his expectations
of me are far and beyond what
they should be i think
co-workers cube each other because ship you
especially though if a coworker comes up
to another coworker and says i have
a great surprise for you i'm going
to blindfold you and take you to
a surprise location on their birthday you
don't even know it's gonna happen here
this dale wants to tell us about
something very interesting now i'm like sherlock
holmes though i've already seen that he
has investor investor portfolios there on his
desk i know in
st pipe yeah and the weird hat
with the flaps i think that makes
sense it's cold yeah we're using it
here why is dale sheila i'd like
to welcome you to a very exciting
investment opportunity okay i have a company
that is going to change the world
irl oh okay see what am i
holding up here what does this part
of my hand the fingers the novum
the mid the task it's hard to
hold a fat skin
i have to say it's hard to
hold a part of your hand you
usually have to hold up the whole
thing i'm doing my best year dale
that you like you can't hold up
you know your thumb well i guess
you could hold up your thumb like
fonzie and not hold up the other
parts of it but
what am i trying to say daddy
didn't invent holding up a thumb by
the way um the par with only
five guys gladiator
fonzie thing was rolling around in money
he loved it he thought it was
end when ron howard first filmed that
he sometimes filmed the episode the part
of my hand with all the criss
crossing lines to tell my future oh
the pipe bomb now
this poem that i'm going to introduce
you to is not flatlining part of
the hand no it is an acronym
that stands for parrots always laughing maniacally
parrots always laughing maniacally a may this
sounds like an incredible
i mean well first of all i
always think parents are too quiet i've
always said that it's like yeah you
can talk about stuff but you know
i don't know your emotions i don't
know if you're happy i don't know
if you're sad what's here's the thing
about paris is that they don't speak
when you want them to they're withholding
yes frigid bitch
but when a parrot does laugh it
feels terrible you feel mocked by a
member of the animal kingdom laughing at
us parents are always laughing at us
okay not near us this is what
i am proposing a service
where you would send a let's say
fifty dozen parrots oh okay so we're
talking six five tires twelve is as
citizen then the then you carry the
zero and and six hundred you did
the math and then we dispatched them
to the world's leaders fifty dozen at
a time
okay there they go now so every
world leader gets one parrot of peace
know every world leader gets fifty dozen
parents they get five hundred six hundred
parrots a p five hundred six hundred
yeah sappy nice i love that shit
your business a broadway show you're pitching
will evey
actually will be of course okay they
fly leaders york twice wow the first
time for a job and the second
time was for leisure oh okay what
did you do in the leisure time
by abilities literally saw every broadway show
that has ever been as eh
ever been made one all of time
incredible do you want to hear like
that yeah why don't you list them
okay
porgy and bess
the earliest probation is just an order
of your seeing them this is an
order of my recollection oh fair enough
sure gets so you didn't remember anything
else of hamilton
mean girls
billy elliot five years a eilish
our ratio should make every town you
build it
kinky boots
annie
get your gun or joe oklahoma oh
dare i continue my jam i don't
like version of oklahoma did you see
the one in where they serve everybody
around
i i have to say once i
went to new york with some friends
and i said hey should we go
see that oklahoma and the whole chile
aspect of it seemed to turn them
off yes i said what that friend
was talking about
you really want to go see a
broadway show and be farting the entire
time and the audience they'll entire audiences
farting and everyone to see chile to
get in although that was the price
of admission although i did go see
sweeney todd where they made meat pies
and it was wonderful short
you know
do you have a food that goes
along with your pitch
well it's a good question do you
wanna hear that at first you wanna
hear the full pitch or do you
want to hear my we didn't hear
the full pitch no no i somehow
didn't get to it huh weird i
wonder how
alright go ahead
rent
are you still talking about the shows
are you reminding really we have two
girls
i think she's still talking about the
shows that she saw or she might
be talking about girls that she's dreaming
go on oh
the parrot's perch directly outside the residence
of each world leader and they begin
laughing laughing maniacally the world leaders have
no choice but to take it personally
because it sounds personal whoa i love
this this is so good i love
that you have to talk to each
wait so this is like a military
weapon you're pitching us and why are
you pitching us because you know we're
realtors it's not a military weapon it
i've got a condo in studio city
that would be perfect yeah i'd love
to get to know that show
is that like how to succeed in
business without really just nineteen sixty seventy
s all those titles are so looking
off broadway and you know it didn't
survive past ten the idea is that
preview since all the world leaders is
suffering the exact same fate the world
has no choice but to unite in
peace i love this idea love it
know what the okay the reason i
pitch it to to realtors is
realtors need to have a good name
again after the capital insurrection ah thank
you because of that one who said
she was a real shit out on
the plane she said it so many
times right if you really want to
be around so you think that if
you lay right sold this to us
then we could take it all the
way up to the top through the
chain of the pentagon to
realtors who are well pro usr you
you engage me to do this and
you get the credit oh i love
them all i get is free tickets
to broadway show which one do you
want to see all of them that
have ever been created so i've got
to pay for all of these or
get my hands on free tickets somehow
but we would get credit that's up
to you
it sounds like a good deal dell
credit for something yes yale other day
that's priceless
mean dale yes whose other dale weight
i'm relegated to other day oh sorry
john your other dale
other jail i think that i paid
doesn't say happy birthday other dale i
don't think oh it says happy birthday
comma day that's right i'm dale alright
yeah i'll do it
i'll do things i hate to see
you fight thank you thank you but
i think you should make a o
yeah
because this was a million dollars to
fund
an indecent proposals oh all right ansi
yea i think that does should we
do more of it or that may
be it for this episode it feels
like a lot it feels like a
lot all right that's off this episode
ah feels like that's it for this
episode we will see you next time
play that again maybe
we yeah
oh la la la la la right
crocs send us send us crocks sinnoh
scratch alright said his crocs alright by
x
uh