three
oh oh you're bad yeah i'm a
bad boy i'm the bad boy of
freedom hi everyone we're somebody you think
you you're healing freedom
give us free
we're in st paul we're still in
the hotel room that we recorded the
last episode in and i'm literally in
the sixty seconds in between us recording
these episodes the little wicked child started
shouting again ah kam paul screams shah
yeah
yeah i was scared i would be
if i was a little kid and
you came up to me and said
shut up i live in europe to
inspire fear that lasts forever in her
in your captain's hat yeah i look
official yeah i do look like a
urine yeah so for all she knows
she's no shirt he wears it's a
little girl yeah thanks to show anything
yeah that sounds
like a little girl it's in what
way
screaming about dolls and yeah she's like
i have a little guys
my petticoats
well we're here in st louis sorry
currency no we're in st paul but
yeah minnesota the weather is bleak it
looks cloudy and grain every school place
that we've been to on this tour
has been incredibly hot and the theaters
in an uncomfortably hush but this is
not hot but this but this is
the one
sunset and it'll be hot in chicago
when we go there tomorrow oh but
this is the one place where it's
for some reason gloomy yeah and the
weather last night was not frightful it
was ah light full life last night
was it was fucking nightfall yes and
we're hearing kevin ryan's hotel room at
and chevron over here is ah looking
at us
laying a kimbo on their beds yeah
yeah it must be weird for them
hey you're gonna be sixty five in
chicago tomorrow it is yeah or you're
going to have to agree to like
do something after we leave okay so
i can just like everyone on this
okay thank you
start farting let me ask you
let me ask you a question hotel
people wow yeah
do you like to get the room
serviced every day if if i'm here
for two days i don't bother many
there's three venues i will go like
a week without getting the room a
few days at a time i'll get
new towels maybe look i go a
week at my house without getting distressed
so it's not that weird i like
to i like to
just not have them bother yeah you
know
because i don't care do leave tips
yes always works you must mean to
i mean i didn't know that that
was even a thing until cool up
who used to have the job of
of servicing rooms that was late that
was a late relation for me too
yeah i didn't know that then i
felt kind of bad and sometimes i
forget i also think and it's been
a long education of like
who gets tipped and who doesn't you
know and it's always a question of
like do we tip them i think
all tips should be abolished yeah because
it's refusal or you should tip every
single person in your life for everything
you but you you'd think all teams
should be abolished in favour of people
getting paid more or just you want
to get rid of the tips no
no everyone i want everyone to have
nothing everyone should get paid what they're
worth
earth or there should never be a
question about it where just like we
tip ryan after he records us we
tip kevin for you know like every
single like we we hung out last
year she tip us for being on
your show that's why i mean we
tell me we left over for him
last night we hung out and we
all had dinner we should all tip
each other did you get all steamed
up
i did not hear you shout i
didn't
anyway well to a native i like
to hybridize with stuff like that and
i've like at points i've wanted to
do something regarding that like write something
or a tip guide yeah something like
that because a manifesto i go maybe
funny sort of but also factual thing
i i've been
cause i think it's something i would
really like to have but it would
require me to do a lot of
research because i still get confused all
the time about whether i should or
not in certain situations like if you
have a company car like if you're
given a ah a business who sets
up a car for you yes and
they take you to the airport do
you tip them i often do because
i feel rude not tipping them but
then i've been told you don't have
to because the company tips them know
the company yeah but it depends who
tells you that you don't have to
tip them because one time i remember
one time being told like you don't
tip the owner at a bar if
the owners behind the bar and he's
serving drinks if he's the owner he's
getting on the profits you don't tip
him how would you know well that's
the thing
i asked well yeah but you would
know if you if you go there
a lot go there a lot right
and so i asked ah a friend
of mine who was a part owner
in a bar and i said i
heard that you don't tip the owner
and this guy said i think you
tip based on the service no matter
who it is but people have different
belief
leafs about that them and and they
do but here's the thing people's beliefs
are always anything contrary is always a
justification to not tips not tip yeah
oh so he was saying you don't
have to tip because this guy thought
he shouldn't have to tip because if
the owners making all the money but
he presented it as if it was
a known piece of etiquette right
right and i was a gullible idiot
and i fucking swallow that shit up
like babies food yeah and then i've
felt like a real fool well and
then was like nail salons oh definitely
tip but when i read a whole
article about how they really need the
tips because they get paid especially in
new york there was a whole expo
say about it but they get paid
so little that it's like offensive and
that's my that's my whole point is
is like we should be paying people
more like the the people who service
the rooms we don't know how they
do how you know like we didn't
know how they do we don't we
don't know if they're doing well because
we're gone we're not paying the hotel
anymore so it's not based on soon
but it's if you it is if
you've used
em for like a week and yeah
but come in like cody come in
the bank of the upset oh yeah
i mean like charles j these people
more do you tip every time they
come in the room or do you
tip at the end because that only
one person gets it and it might
be a different person hopefully they pull
it but i mean this is what
i'm saying about tips are an imperfect
system where like and then there's
the thing where i've had terrible service
at both of the restaurants we've been
to on this trip but we go
and i can't i can't i feel
like i still have to tip twenty
five percent yeah everywhere i go buy
me up for me says nice service
for to give a bad tip something
would have to be extraordinarily bad like
where this person
this person actively is trying to ruin
my day well i didn't do this
in complaint corner last episode but can
i tell you about the last let's
reopen the complaint quarter play the jingle
and i'm playing to do so she
was so nice i have to say
she was so nice i'm not going
to say what hotel it was but
ah i ordered breakfast and she was
very bright and cheery
sorry but i had a complicated order
and she didn't write it down
and the whole time i'm saying it
i'm like you should be writing this
down she came back for clarification because
she forgot half of it i clarified
it and then the the food was
wrong
yeah you like to order your standard
order is you want a bowl of
oatmeal with a little moat cut in
the centres sure and then you want
coffee inside that and they're avoiding the
coffee yes floating on the coffee you
want like just a little bit of
scrambled egg and a shape of a
boat yeah and then the flag should
be a toothpick with an orange wedge
on the sun then she wants i
islanders naive that looks like a fork
but is really a nice yes and
the spoon that looks like a noisy
anyone can remember this and then you
want the plate to have written an
icing my king here you know by
king here you go
so what part did she fuck up
oh milton have a moat be ingredient
the ingredients and the thing that i
was asking ah shh yeah yeah you
know like all the specifics she just
like gave me whatever like it wasn't
like she got the thing i ordered
wrong but like all of the ingredients
you order what you want i know
this is so mysterious it was harder
to youth elixir he was okay
okay so but like me it was
like a little elixir it was an
egg scramble and i said i wanted
egg whites right and i wanted let
me see if i could ok you
tell me and then i'm gonna see
if i remember everything here's here's wow
can i get the egg scramble with
egg whites spinach mushrooms bacon sausage and
cheese
and then she said
well you could get it with everything
do you want the tomatoes and do
you want the the the other vegetable
i forgot what it was i was
like no i just want the mushrooms
and the spinach so you want egg
white scramble with mushrooms and spinach tomatoes
potatoes
honestly think about this i already lost
what you said and i will see
what else is happening is that i
don't know you and so i'm thinking
twenty other things about you about the
choice you have to write time i'm
like i'm on the phone imagining you
nude i'm like this guy's wow because
you're nervous yeah it's public speech
king
so what i got was not egg
whites she by the way kane brown's
oh here's my shell here's a flax
egg the playing field when it comes
to cheese and and i said could
i have feta instead of the listed
cheese right it's fitting yeah let's get
swiss cheddar whenever it was
i said is it possible to get
feta so she walked away and then
like a minute later came back and
said it was swiss cheese right and
i said no you know it was
feta and she went oh yeah of
course and the food and then it
came with regular egg yolks
yeah please talk to me if i
were a server i would thrive on
writing it down i would i would
love writing it down you get your
little paper you get your little pen
you have no questions you don't talk
about reporter you are able to tell
the person exactly what it is no
one i never think it's cool that
you're not writing it down even if
it all turns out perfect i'm like
i think we've told i'm str
yes i think we have i don't
know it's a weird pressure thing that
restaurants put on people it's stupid it
doesn't make any sense for restaurant restaurants
want people to remember it i don't
think restaurants do ever so i think
paul did tell us there are some
restaurants where like the look is like
oh write that shit down yeah like
you know i don't think it's ever
the servers idea like why would it
be you know
i think this place was just she
didn't she wasn't carrying it was this
here someplace else this was in kansas
city in kansas city so i think
it was just shoot i think so
every experience i've ever had with it
is a server's lazy doesn't have their
book and is like i'll just remember
it um i've never been in see
you come in man sky with my
complicated or will also you know i
feel like it's one of those places
where people just order whatever you know
like i'll have this thing they don't
moderate yeah and they don't expect someone
to come in and like one egg
whites are oh i have the kansas
city stevedore you're like i'm from l
a and i want a egg whites
spinach mushrooms no tomato from kansas city
give me the casey
e bladder buster and then i went
to my place i was like hi
i'm from la and i want avocado
toast some millennial and they're always like
ships i was like this is like
an ass way the lady was staring
at you you think it's because she
recognized know i think she was like
suggest watching a local oddball yeah what
jimmy
she was watching me
and then i think you'll like that
i always feel like someone's watching me
somebody thank you rockwell but i yeah
hopefully oh be alive some matters me
yes yeah michael node yes that was
close yes and i didn't even realize
i was michael jackson
yeah he was so mad it was
so exciting when that song came out
i was so excited when i heard
that i was started because i was
like
you want him you keep defending him
my life who i have to fight
with i remember staying up all night
on somebody's watching me eve the songs
coming up tomorrow it's coming up tomorrow
valley he probably is thinking about me
too i hung up my knees rockwell
thinking about i'm scott i'm
i'm fourteen i'm thinking about michael jackson
and he's somewhere thinking about me highway
chappelle i'm serious it is disgusting and
i do not like him anymore okay
oh you can like his know his
actions
ah you don't like it but you
do have to love what he did
oh my god
did we talk about that the nick
cave essay that he wrote about morrissey
yeah but moore's yeah no i mean
he's eating care by the way he's
waiting oh do we talk about it
out here yeah we did talk about
it you can say it again well
just just the fact that he feels
you know because morrissey's like gone into
the alt right and he's yeah we
can still enjoy morrissey's music because once
you
release it i don't feel a song
belongs to you and to the artist
anymore belongs to the world and it's
so tight wrapped up in your experiences
and your memories i thought morrissey said
that no no miss remember the magazine
was simply about yeah i used old
cancel me he's like i don't want
to become so i can so
i wanna live forever even though i'm
old roy but anyway and apap is
a fraud don't come to me
nick cave also wrote a really incredible
essay about grief which you should look
oh yeah that was tense yeah well
but i think the game is a
cool dude i really love his writing
yeah like his songs i have all
of his records and i like him
but he's not like a super favorite
of mine but yeah and here's the
essays he writes yeah i don't even
know yeah he's very very
ah you know emotional and um touching
stuff that he's written because his his
son passed away oh that's horrible um
we'll see but but people write hills
sometimes respond to them oh my son
was young and that what happened i
don't remember do you guys all want
to close your eyes while we do
this
yeah pauses i like just laying in
a bed right
i don't turn my turn on that
lamp it truly is like yeah and
we're just like oh at a certain
point one of us will stop talking
and then there will be silence for
ten minutes so what do you guys
watch on netflix
i've been watching black mirror on the
on the airplanes because i've been trying
to download ah flea bag from amazon
prime and episode one certainly downloaded and
i watched ah
but episode two anytime i click the
download button just spins and spins forever
i don't know what to do the
way i didn't tell you a story
this is really anything so story time
so a couple a few years ago
i went on a bachelor party
i want to like a bachelor party
trip to vegas with with a coed
group and the way it shook out
with the rooms for some reason me
and this other guy were sharing a
room we had two beds and he's
married and it was true as truly
where the orange zones leptonic you put
yourself in the friends i put into
on the friends of
and so we didn't care like we're
like whatever we'll just share a room
like we've known each other a long
time yeah and when we were falling
asleep it was the funniest thing because
we talking and then we were like
we both have like partner like we
started laughing so hard because he's like
my wife like i why am i
talking to you in this room and
not my
why like what is happening this is
so weird we are adults like why
didn't we just get separate really think
it's true like we're being cheap or
something like everyone was sharing a room
and so it just worked out but
like we were cracking up because it
was so random and weird and it
just doesn't happen in life online but
is very straight on the next like
next leg of the tour
we should all be in one room
oh no that was wild horses' board
a point now where we all want
our own room like we did it
for a while because it's like fun
and then we're like alright alright funds
over right but chevron over here in
ryan over somewhere yeah i guess he's
taking a shit while recording the episode
that's probably your fault that they're in
a room together
oh look in the mirror on that
one you got me begged for it
is their responsibility to book their own
trap oh well then yeah that saves
you money i mean it's so it's
totally reasonable it's so maybe they love
it here it's not even about the
money haven't you guys stay up talking
as you fall asleep you do it's
not your hopes and dreams
seems i haven't shared a room with
somebody that was not janie in a
very long yeah it's it's very funny
when you're doing that and you're like
what i'm happening last time i did
it last time i was way too
old for it it was at south
by southwest and i very i didn't
without thinking ice kind of was like
someone was saying that they didn't
have a lot of money and that
you know ah south by southwest was
only gonna pay for the flight and
not a hotel and i was like
oh yeah we'll just you know i
have a room i'm gonna i'm sure
i have an extra bed in my
room if you ever need a place
to crash whatever turned into crashing the
entire time with me and i was
just like lacquer this is not a
relaxing trip for me
during adult should know that you can't
just crash on someone's name if your
room is paid for by somebody else
it's still like that's what you got
i'd just be alone i just remembered
the last time that i shared a
hotel was ah
it was this was a long time
ago and a long long time ago
bob ohio's ohio
why hey buddy hey would you mind
do you mind crashing in my room
with me it was good to you
step out i wanna take me and
bob and david cross they were doing
standout at the punchline and they asked
me to show them were sharing a
bed no no they asked me to
open for them they got separate rooms
but they i did
not have room for some reason i
can't remember why this happened because i
had money to get my own room
i don't write i don't remember what
the circus why did this happen but
i but bob so bob was in
the bed and i was in like
a trundle bed with me you're in
trouble it whites
no old rio oh is in my
thirties yeah yeah it was weird it
was so funny it's like i've i
feel like i've been in a handful
of those situations all to save a
few hundred bucks that i feel like
in the moment it's so awkward that
it would just be better i don't
know i think it was that the
the the haute the
the club was putting them up but
they weren't paying to put me up
right right and so bob offered that
so i would still make money you
know instead of just wouldn't like lose
money on a hotel room you know
right so what weird things happen what
they do
well just being involved it was not
there ah but i remember bob asked
me who my favorite comedian was and
i can remember who i said but
i i remember c k i'd fifteen
you know it looks like even night
yet once everyone likes them um bill
cosby
but i said whoever looked up but
that's that's also like a question that
always paralyzed me because it always makes
me think i'm supposed to mention somebody
your daughter like that's working at the
time or whatever i don't know i
always feel like you know i give
a dumb answer that right so i
said whoever it was i don't know
kevin meaney i have no fucking idea
and then bob says not right my
favorite woody allen
i remember having that feeling of like
oh i said the wrong thing i
said my my answer was dumb and
his was the smart answer that's a
comedian yeah he did stand it he
did stand up but you know and
i'm playing for such a brief time
he had he has like three albums
editing
yeah i guess i'll go downloading those
put some money and just wait to
hear you scarlett johanson listening together so
we're like the remote to bed like
the mo i just you know psychoanalysis
it's it's so it's it's what we
do
we've made love they'd love the and
michael jackson tools with every episode we
did every episode of this podcast forever
we always do somehow lead us into
it though you had snapped trail or
near the pied piper
no um the pad did you have
a lot of sleepovers when you're a
kid oh yeah you loved it righ
all the time what is so thrilling
about it so fun you could talk
all night yeah i would have sleepovers
with all my different close friends but
then all like my best friend and
i
i have talked about natalie from like
age five to now i mean we
have scores now but like in our
twenties we did but like it's just
fun and when we travel together and
share a bed i don't care it's
like it's like gary dicker with your
old friend fuckin travel together share bed
who gives a fuck had sleepovers were
so
great we'd like get in the bed
and like talk about everything and like
then have pancakes in the morning
i remember
i remember having a sleepover at my
best friend's house when ah we are
in what like seventh grade eighth grade
so i'm like yeah it was seventh
grade
ooh there
wow you're phrasing ah
and i remember that his mom my
friend eric's mom who is this cool
lady hurney was sybil and she was
this was a great period because she
was divorced she remarried this fucking creep
who is such an awful awful creep
but i remember him
like my my friend and i one
time i put over his house and
we were like brushing our teeth were
like make a noise in the bathroom
and he came up from his bedroom
and slap to my friend on the
side of the head oh my furious
we were making noise like with no
warning you know and it was just
like well we're we're fucking kids have
a sleepover like this is what happens
i imagine slap
hoping someone else's kid it was crazy
i was shocked cause i can imagine
someone know his kid show he slept
his stepson oh that's shitty you know
what i mean he did not raise
this kid like yeah new in this
yeah in this relationship that's scary yeah
and so then she divorced that guy
and then he left the house and
so then there was
this great period where you know they
had that house and he and the
creepy guy wasn't there and it was
fucking great that she was getting alum
and then his mom his mom started
dating this cool guy um who was
ah just like the polar opposite just
like the best guy and it was
great to hang out with and um
that
like towards the end of of our
you know time being friends grade school
friends um but there was a few
of us there's like a handful of
boys like five boys and we're having
a sleepover probably for his birthday or
something like that and i remember we
were looking at like an album
cover of some female singer and it
was like a really hot cover like
very sexy cover pat benatar and we
were all of it i mean maybe
i know the cover and yeah we
got and she caught us looking at
it and like making like she caught
me making some little comet or some
megs of lewd face or something like
that which was very out of character
for me um was something like bajo
a c milan zito
oh and they saw the guys all
saw that she was standing behind me
before i saw and it was like
this you know i was very embarrassed
but she was very sweet about it
but then she was kind of like
she was like hey what about this
album of this melissa manchester album you
know and it's like this other scenario
yeah la it was like i forgot
about that and then years later it
was like she was like you know
it was just trying to facilitate something
i don't know she was like yeah
i'll i'll help you
you i'll help you do hs out
you know like i'll i'll when embarrassing
which she was you know what i
mean she's gonna be like z-axis fine
like another also transfer right oh yeah
absolutely one hundred percent like i don't
think i knew i don't think i
realized that a crush on her but
she was really cool now
that's interesting you had i you had
a crush on the mom but i
don't think i realised it like well
think about it now i think that
i did yeah it was a compatible
launcher up on facebook know look it
up scotty look i'm ah okay i'm
her name i've had this memory was
sybil was the last man
memory in my samples it was sybil
pebble or i'm on one bed there
on the other i guess i'm ignoring
you i've had this memory in my
mind she's talking of a of a
basement he's in therapy right now
we're the therapists
okay one i've i've always wondered what
the circumstances of this were but i
remember being younger agents ah there it
was yesterday and i was with my
brother and i was in a basement
somewhere of a house i don't know
and my and we were
i think there were other kids and
the other kids were like well our
our dad has playboys in this basement
oh shit and so we looked at
these playboys for awhile so that's one
memory and then trying to figure out
like what was once so then the
other the other memories in there the
other memory was that i was in
there in in in this house in
the like foil where they kept a
tv
yeah and i was watching the movie
scavenger hunts sure and my parents were
like we have to go we have
to go and it was like fifteen
minutes before the end i was like
it's almost ending and they were like
we don't care let's go and i
would like search the tv guide for
years after that trying to find this
movie oot like a replay of this
movie so i can see the
end right zone let me just say
i didn't do that let me just
say that i got a blu ray
of scavenger on recently and i watched
the end oh closure what how was
it how many times was this it's
fine but i hear snyder this ah
so it turns out that it turns
out and this this is when i
was twelve because i just found out
where
or i was because i was talking
to my mom when i was around
spacecraft would you think it was ironic
that you were on a hunt to
find the ending to scavenger ah so
i was twelve years old so that
would be thirty
sorry
but i found out where it was
because i was talking to my mom
about being on tour and we were
just in the in the east at
in rhode island and everything i was
like we went through rhode island didn't
we and my mom said on our
trip when i was twelve and she
said yes and then she said i
said and but did we ever go
to virginia she goes no we didn't
oh
she goes wait a minute no we
did go to virginia because it's for
lovers because our relatives live there and
we went to dinner she goes maybe
you don't remember this but we went
to dinner there and they they got
really drunk and kept fucking up the
dinner and wouldn't like kept forgetting to
turn the
oven on and everything any went three
hours and you guys kept like coming
upstairs going like we're really hungry whereas
whoa and your relatives are just trashed
and i suddenly put together that that's
the house and i was like oh
my i remember how and so i've
always wondered like where the fuck was
that that i was in this basement
yes i figured it out i wonder
where i was when i was in
the basement there was this girl that
i was friends with in high school
it was like a newish friend to
me and ah it was always fun
because her house her parents had recently
gotten divorced or her monitors and endorse
from her stepdad umm al
and
the house was like really big but
there wasn't really any furniture in it
and the dab takes cool i look
back at it and i think because
i always thought it was fun to
go next we would like have all
this room to make up dances and
stuff
like like and we're always over there
like and that's where i learned about
raman and i loved ramen noodles and
because they always had a ton of
it and there was um like a
big yoga like whose places are what
each other mature and just their cupboards
faces what i'm saying like i look
back and i realized oh she was
like going through a very hard
time with dad like a lot of
the furniture she didn't have much support
got to shout rom and because the
kids all the time pay for the
morgue yes and like i truly like
was like we could do whatever you
want here this is so awesome and
things looking back i feel like whoa
that was crazy that like i my
vision my understanding of it was
so skewed yeah obviously but i mean
that's so cool that like obviously probably
the mom was worried about what impact
does is going gonna have on the
kids you know and and instead it's
like kids have just naturally optimistic way
of looking yeah the thing we were
having a lot of fun and they
were she had little siblings who were
like way younger from like the mom
second marriage and we always babysat them
and play with i mean i loved
going
over there was always great should go
no well um okay we have to
take a break we'll be right back
we're back where backward where bow same
poem and it's back having our slumber
party episode we're all on the bed
the lights are off lauren has her
hoodie turn the hello it all the
way around huh
she looks like ah elliott or e
t or a combination yeah and yeah
closing yeah really dark in here super
dark in here it's getting dark in
here so let's take all your clothes
keep on yeah i don't want to
be stumble around nude in this room
with you guys knew that's right it's
my your back
wait is naked not a choice naked
is not a choice nude means you
had more decided to really yes naked
is just they were stripped from you
naked means look i don't know how
you got that way but it was
not your idea i don't know i
don't think that's true i don't think
yesterday
it is true i think it is
true i do think a streaker is
nude streakers nude for sure not my
kids oh everyone is naked someone has
forcibly removed the i think naked is
i think news or zayed i think
insane i think nude is always naked
butt naked is not always nude wow
wow so you like nude i love
it
would you ever go to a nudist
colonies no never ever i think nude
is a hilarious word would you ever
go to like something like a spy
where you have to walk around naked
and i'm talking about this like that
yeah you know i mean i've been
to places like that but i keep
a towel on or a robe or
whatever i don't i don't i was
look
the idea of you guys doing that
is funny yeah hey guys going there
occasionally like cool apple tell me about
please talk about this because like yeah
when you run into somebody who knows
we tell you ah so weird yeah
no it's less weird for women i
know that's probably not true i feel
better and because you're less horny know
i know
i actually don't even know what i
mean i'm just thinking my own perspective
it's probably equally it might be less
weird for guys because i feel like
guys are more naked around each other
and like locker rooms and like i
do think it's weird unless i just
have that idea for like movies or
some in it and i how i
have this in locker rooms and stuff
there's always people yeah i think it's
weird that like we force trois
five year old boys to be naked
you do with each other we don't
do that scott the two of you
i'm like wait what when was it
forced like you had jammed yeah jimmy
yes i think yeah they tell you
they tell you on your first day
in gym class they're like look you
guys are going to have to be
naked with each other because you're going
to be sweating and you have to
shower after
say yes and you guys are just
gonna have to get used to it
and don't be a pussy and you
know he didn't have showers until high
school as far as i recall so
did you not just in your sweat
like and then smell bad from what
i can remember now we were my
clothes back on i was like whatever
i think it's really weird because like
some have puke
cvs some don't some are more developed
everyone's just like take a picture you're
right yeah everyone hear what you're pondering
some some twelve year mission tubes
ah i'm lying on the bed when
you're opposed like mike above my mouth
as if i'm going your memoirs and
i just think she's twelve year old
boys him pieces some jsoc don't that
was some new sedie indian pew as
well
this could only dream of having the
boobs that's a book you look at
them and you wonder when did they
come in and do they know tis
and are they loud to them or
were these yellow band live my whole
body how did my race pew i
am twelve
yeah become a human but i am
now older me doing radziwill died when
i was like to be with i
remember the twelve year old boys remember
that p me from this day wow
lulz is a tangled with the gym
shorts barely discern
funded from their bodies but yes it's
supposed to be like teaching you skills
that you have to deal with in
your adult life i think we've established
they don't do that but no you're
not you don't constantly have to be
naked with every person you know fuck
no man so then why bother
private showers it is easier to be
naked with people that you are not
going to see every single day of
your life yeah it is just there
to make kids have to be naked
by each other like i think it's
weird i think it's like almost child's
asking for bullying yeah i think it's
challenging for
i remember being uncomfortable with having to
change by the lockers and in my
locker room as a kid it was
weird it's weird for girls to yeah
okay i'm just saying it's too much
pressure it's too much pressure to be
fabulous i think every i think in
in junior eyes and high schools ever
there should be
ie one private locker changing room and
shower for every child yeah yeah i
agree it's really not that much to
ask if you consider it like stalls
with a module gonna say bathroom look
free college we should do this first
yes exactly however i feel like you
only hear kids complaining about this as
well talk to there too
too shy too shy shy ah they're
too fucked up from the experience it
scars them for life when i took
a cross country train trip um there
was a shower on the train because
the three day trip right and but
it's not you don't like a shower
in your little compartment know when i
took
my cross country train trip when i
was twenty three yeah i assumed it
was like the forties and fifties yeah
like scene where you have your own
room yeah right so what was it
yours it's like an airplane you're sitting
there what i had right next to
so can you pay more and have
a bed yeah i had a private
compartment
but you had one it's essentially the
private compartment is like a little it's
like a little room with two chairs
in it in the sliding door that
you can close and then you push
the chairs together to make the bed
that's wack attack it's like a job
that's not enough room or comfort it's
very dangerous really suck but it's better
than what i
had to do which is basically sleep
upright in a in an airplane seat
next to an old woman who constantly
wants to talk to me and you
normally prefer to sleep upright in your
coffin
it was a break in the dirt
of your homeland
um i ah the last day of
the trip i did not realize i
had not booked the same fare class
and so i had to go to
share and it was actually better than
the bed oh really yeah it really
was well because you're not given the
idea that you might get comfortable like
there's some part of the chair was
comfortable enough
roof like a bed suck we went
to australia i was in the back
row of the plane i believe you
are in first class got thank you
very much makes it clear that i
wanted everyone to know i was in
the back row of the plane by
the bathroom and next to a man
who was in the seat next to
me and i was just two seats
on the side of the plane i
was
on and i curled into a i
took a pill to knock myself out
i curled into a ball it was
like a melatonin by the way i
don't think i don't know what pill
you might be thinking i do and
then i see curled up as tight
as i possibly could and i got
up maybe two times in twenty hours
yeah and it was fine you're able
to do that though that's true i
i really to do that
i cannot sleep on a plane unless
i'm flat
flat on my ass
i sleep i could sleep and any
plane situation but it's uncomfortable i'm not
happy about it i'd rather be flat
but i can't sleep that's why i'm
saying you can't even fall asleep i
can honestly like ah in um in
thailand i was like as tired as
oriental sit in your socks are so
fluffy that they look like
ah go ahead take a bite ah
your socks are so fluffier look like
marshmallow you new semi nude these are
semi nude socks not naked they were
not stripped from me let me see
if i can find a difference between
new to naked okay um
nude definition sensual when i was on
that train did i tell you about
that train trip how the old woman
i did oh sure about the old
world so the old woman next to
me i i brought a book i
remember it was a cary grant biography
i was read out that'll keep you
engaged for learning biographies from like old
movie stars at the time huh um
and ah i had ah my headphones
and i guess i wonder if it
was it was it was probably a
disk man okay at
and i sit down i have a
couple of pleasant you know exchanges with
the woman that i'm going to be
next to for three days i cary
grant is yeah i wound up here
nah about his biography nothing about what
i was interested in reading in are
like oh that looks like a good
book nothing about that right wow so
so i just have a few pleasantries
that i exchange of like oh where
are you going where you know all
that kind of stuff and then i
thought okay we're done right i put
on the disc man i start reading
my book while i'm listening to music
five five seconds later tap tap tap
something must be wrong right did you
get to the sideway does lsd
what about the part where he did
the black and white fin sizes almost
his entire career oh just get to
that part tap tap tap i'm thinking
either something's wrong or she wants to
ask me about the book or something
and it's just more i take off
my headphones just she's like so in
milwaukee are you going she just wants
small talk literally the rudest thing i've
ever heard and i just was like
i said ah yeah sure yeah
posting a pic i put the headphones
back on it tap tap tap she
still taps me she just wants to
have a conversation she wanted to have
a conversation the entire three days i
was on that train but very intermittently
and change your seat no couldn't change
the seat and so i ended up
just doing things like they would announced
that there was a movie in the
movie car which
it was just like an empty train
car with a dead television show we
didn't talk about the movie so i
went in and watch dennis the menace
for no reason was there a smoking
car no we talked about this in
line at pepys so the people we
talked about the lineup at bay yes
so everyone who told her when should
not have gone there you know what
i want to complain about that so
we went
the pepys pizza and whatever corktown rebecca
up by the complain cornerback open katana
playing or being young okay this is
in providence no new haven haven new
every first of all multiple people told
me to go to ebay to the
point that i put it on my
calendar ie that puppies i didn't know
the fuck that was but i was
like don't forget that because you're gonna
be wondering where to go just eat
puppies just so i put on my
calendar we though we all were going
to puppies we get in line it's
a whole fucking thing we eat there
it's good we leave everyone i posted
about it then we start getting all
these comments and messages with people sending
links to articles about pepin being a
trump supporter saying i was like you
are the reason i am there
there you think i want to go
to pepys you all told me go
to pepys now you tell me puppies
cancel baden swiss you need to get
the fuck out of my thisis classic
and treatment it hey you should go
to this restaurant and then after you're
the restaurant you went to the wrong
restaurant shit has understandably isn't i don't
know what yeah i'm here for a
day okay you ready for dictionary stuff
yes
thanks to chevron for sending me this
technically speaking naked implies that a person
is having wrote this yeah he just
jotted this down for me technically speaking
naked implies where did this come from
ken kevin read it come from it
comes from mental floss no he case
isn't no no
no shook his head no ticket if
if kevin starts reading stuff that i'm
leaving yeah holy shit i gotta go
taking the happen you could take going
but yeah technically speaking naked implies that
versus unprotected or vulnerable it also describes
something that is unadorned or without embellishment
as in the oft mentioned naked truth
nude on the other hand
and means one thing and clothed think
of it this way if you doff
your duds that means close to pose
while descending a staircase for a two-day
think of it that way
i think there's more to the sentence
i know but i mean think of
it this way if you doff your
duds like i'm ah dammit i'm already
enough not enough way back i think
though i see where this is going
and i think that you mean you
can be naked while having taken off
your own clothes meaning yes you think
you let me fucking finish it wow
heavy
it's two went to the trouble to
look up a mental floss dot com
if kenny looks a bit like family
to me then i went to the
trouble to tap on the text and
then i started reading and now the
train has left the station and i
wu near the old lady trying to
bug wow think of it this way
if you off your duds
to pose while just sending a staircase
for a tasteful painting done by a
respected artist than your nude if a
bunch of pappa razzi suddenly burst in
through the studio door and take your
picture without permission you are suddenly naked
wow so there was a little truth
to what i said there is a
little bit of his anxious yes
the ten a lot the distinction little
bit of like it and take starring
brett gelman was like and you can
take off your own clothes and still
be naked that's the one difference to
me yes yes but it does imply
vulnerability and capability not maybe not your
choice to be seen that way right
which makes it hotter oh yeah man
oh yeah
yeah the only reason our brothers conversation
is because it's hot
you're all about the hot conversation i
love hot conversation by that i mean
sexual and sensual sorry well and sent
you whoa speaking of both of those
things we have to take a break
okay
and we're back in time for reacher
time three-tier da game is called actor
switch three actors are given a situation
and a character from the audience
they start
so see you next week at some
point during the sex which shoe call
out switch the three actors now have
just switch characters that means they have
to really listen to each other and
be aware of who the other characters
are
another character at any moment and remind
students the aim is shit
a complete cohesive scene and the other
one's situation so students the aim is
to keep striving for a complete police
have seen no matter what the situation
now paul yeah hi scott as at
me and me yes we are going
to play the game now and we
have to rotate ah going clock
wise so i will take over scott's
character when and paul mine and scott
paul's it wouldn't be wait yeah yes
right i'll take over paul's paul you
take over lawrence lauren takes over mine
yes love it yeah love verses with
a suggestion who's giving us a sector
the audience stupid kevin
kevin for his suggestions water park i
heard waterpark i heard waterpark
ah could we get a season one
of the four seasons winter winter waterpark
boy that's gonna give us a lot
to work with okay winter water park
guys you ready yeah yeah i'll start
hey folks ah you're kind of late
in the season we're ah we're gonna
close down after today's your name my
name is ronald raw an old nhl
just ronald oh honey don't don't be
so rude to this man i asked
him what his name was is shut
up or you said raw and i'll
see you are an asshole
fuck ups folks trying to talk to
their kids listen to this man my
husband down a fucking water slide that
has no water on it so he
rips into a million treads and dies
at the end you're mad oh would
you talk to me like that baby
to not kill him my baby i
love you baby
no come near me i love you
i love you switch
i love you i love it i
love you no no no you're me
now yeah what would you think i
was doing i was telling him to
fuck off oh so my character would
think kissing oh fuck off hey guys
do you mind not doing this in
front of me wrong old so you
do pronounce it that way i fell
down
yeah you guys i'm ronald it's me
i'm him you're me what okay yeah
okay students listen carefully okay i hate
my wife fucking slot
do you guys do you guys want
to go on some riots like i'm
not supposed to do this but i
can turn the taps on um why
did you let people in if you
weren't going is the right kind of
freeze or am i going to get
my knee is scraped up with bees
can't believe mushy please stop doing your
rats
well i mean i live here in
the car do whatever apps go to
hell you go to hell who i
love when you talk like that you
know
tell me guys guys guys tell me
you get off again look i can
i can't win i'm just going to
turn on the taps here and we'll
we'll start this wage
yeah turn to the chaps because my
taps are already turned off oh god
you're disgusting i hate you i'm gonna
learn are no habs is peaceful but
you're dangling drop the dough we have
a problem we have a problem asked
me what was wrong around pipes are
frozen i need somebody to heat them
up ooh you know can eat him
up as my wife here
she's hot as shit well what if
i took off all my clothes with
yeah whoa what's up with your body
i nude but why was now i
feel naked do you have a breast
in your belly button yes i got
an implant you don't think that's hot
hey i it's been likes it i
guess i can only speak on that
i don't want to get ranting say
your own name right my husband is
is as you can see a little
person yeah can't reach the breasts that
are
just dynamite classic in bed together i
love breasts that i don't have to
work for i feel so he wants
to suck on this tear up i
wanna ass on that t
look are we gonna get on this
ride oh come on dickhead
switch
ah you gotta talk to me that
way and i'm going to have to
ask you to leave the park unique
rally done we're not leaving we have
to position slide today or we get
in trouble yeah alright well i guess
the water seems to be coming up
through thank you i'm so our mummy
and daddy said we had to wait
you're related yeah are you brothers
yeah and you're mary and were thirteen
years old i always tell him to
get off me
look i i think maybe you should
go someplace cells you're the one who
let us in here wrong anal okay
okay and seeing
that was arguably the best the worst
things
alright let's get a new let's do
a little more diane we need a
suggestion anything at all please
right sir horace a forest are you
just saying your favorite cure songs yeah
and give us a season and it
was a time of day time of
day mid afternoon mid and give us
a season and give us a season
moderate afternoon forest autumn boy believe daddy
william please pick more berries do we
have to go home we can't stay
out here forever money let it was
very you cuddle hers she's she's going
to be spoiled because she is so
she's a berry lovers that the worst
thing to be we have somebody got
to berries
in the house yeah well you know
she hates eating them but she loves
picking them well i love eating them
but i hate picking them you'd think
it would be good to be a
match made in heaven i know but
i said you're cranky about yeah on
the bright side of things go ahead
honey oh isn't this got stung by
something in the space oh what is
it what does it stupid idiot
honey what is it oh you stupid
kid i can't still be the kid
for wait who who are you i
thought i thought i'm always when we
start i always go oh i should
be the kid and i'm oh i
don't like i'd say nice happy what
is that news about yeah
darling please let me put something on
it hurts oh my god look at
this this i've never seen what is
it of night was taken out of
your finger wow
your entire fingertip has been chewed to
the bonus so fast oh my god
this is like a man flesh-eating termite
will i be this way forever there's
no way to reattach it so i
believe you will be this way forever
year horribly scarred no honey there must
be a way let's find the tip
probably inside the just
oh lee
where did she go oh oh no
oh no i'm falling down a deep
dark hole oh
fucking idiots mommy what do you want
wait what thank god my family is
with me you're supposed to be the
kid your the way
ma abby
no i'm the husband i felt better
whole let her fall she needs this
we already fell she's never anything bad
i fell to you brute but i
let it back i kid don't you
care i know i'd be a bob
did not help and you brewed why
did i ever met anyone have a
match no match
ouch no honey dinosaur face oh woe
was dear
my ass on your face yes you
haven't heard those match no
old-fashioned it would be anyone have a
lookalike so that's the idea
i'd ever hey my lies hole and
my family and dad do something no
you're the one who has a jetpack
you could fly don't have to do
and he's like nah dude on your
phone
you horrible brute so it's thank you
leave it my god my pants i
think too that my mommy die dying
on my phone's running out of battery
ah no one to watch one last
final youtube video for i die pie
pewdiepie
a little better than ever heated gaming
moment
he's funny and seen saying well that's
another one in the books another one
but it's the books the one there
yeah i've done it another way by
anyone
zappos yay
a no one buys the butter
oh bow bow bounce another one bites
books bow bow couch and know my
dad's duty belt am i never good
to go
remember that the bad batch have you
know bow to bow it's real and
another back
every day yeah and the one we'd
open and no one got nowhere my
movie if you don't know what i'm
look you know i want up i
want my watch when i'm in my
room wow now i'm debbie
dan bau beach i'm on i want
by smashing man or brown magic horse
and now i'm back to this random
wow
wow i bet that
dick cello josh yeah yeah yeah freeze
and da da lat debbie yeah evening
gown oh alright thanks for listening everyone
to see sorry about
oh and i apologize for nothing i
actually think you're welcome for all that
yeah i actually think you're watching to
see me banking yeah oh yeah oh
oh yeah sure what our next episode
is going to be whether it's going
to be on tour or whether it's
going to be back in the studio
but we'll see you whenever it happens
yeah man we love doing
the show for you guys and we
love hearing that you love it and
we love you we love you we
love you bye bye bye
a