three
what's the name of our show i'll
tell you
no i didn't hear you because i
wasn't listening ye were shouting
wow you are shouting the word that
you wondered why that's so we know
is it do you think people would
buy that as a single just that
to the saddle and three m's we
just did that song by michael irvin
yes starting over and then a little
bit of the conversation after it so
i'll do this point now it's almost
guess maybe i think it was the
number one single it is almost crispy
it's also hanukkah
and it's also it's christmas of this
year that's right because beer which i'm
so excited about because that means that
feels both with my family oh yes
i'm very excited who
i've been hearing a lot about you
in the night i'd actually really awesome
decoy
i'm very excited for honeycomb because it's
very fun with my my family
i doubt that's the way you talk
a lot huh
i am not to jewish but he's
paul talk i do i have a
menorah i put it out when it
when it's a when it's a christmas
huh that's nice yeah yeah huh okay
um that scott by the way you
know my so my um sister-in-law's jewish
my nephews are jewish and i always
want to buy them fun menorahs because
i see so many
a lot of orleans seminars the social
phone fun fun fun fun weird old
menorah
let's call it high but yeah but
like how many menorahs that you have
so i don't buy them ah but
i did buy them during the pandemic
about them ah blue hanukkah tree christmas
foods nye and some hanukkah ornaments so
i was like you need some pandemic
fun you know did you feel like
buying that tree did you feel like
i know this will be received well
or
or is this like wow just got
there they would they celebrate christmas with
my sunshine they just don't always put
up a tree sometimes they do yeah
um but i thought this way you
would be more excited to put it
up because it's kind of both yes
and um they like i asked before
i sent that's a very large gift
to someone making sure they want that
yes
i passed the gnome it was a
no passing zone you pass down you
swallowed it and finally passed
that thing goes in easier than it
goes out i tell ya i will
say that no the gnome you hid
in my bushes yeah what about it
passed it the other day and saw
it passed it yeah huh and you
thought nanny thought thought of you and
i thought oh what a nice thing
to do oh that was fun for
me to to thank you yeah i
was so
nice minds on our front porch oh
mine's a minute my yard too and
it's really fun really actually up to
i have the big and a little
how can i get us to
you just gave us a little loose
can try think i gave you the
little one okay and but you have
to if i see the big ones
they changed the model so if i
in the target garden section there is
lawrence home free there was talks about
it on previous episode reek she's a
fucking freak for know i love i
have a lot of little gnome houses
in my yard she likes me the
pointy headed freak there's a website that's
called its point you're just my ferry
home or something their heads are pointing
are gnomes heads pointing oh that's
coneheads because they take off the hat
and they rub their parental units fran
we are from france have you ever
seen david the gnome who david the
gnome is like an old well it's
like a nineties cartoon that i think
is probably a german tune or so
mad i don't know it has the
look of bonjour man but i don't
know if it is and it's um
a nick
the nickelodeon and they the theme songs
really fun well done david the gnome
for world is a vampire doo doo
doo doo you gotta hear the theme
song weight title screen of original david
l nomo opening it's it's originally from
amy oil spanish
see i didn't know that oh interesting
okay it's narrated by tofino martinez well
like the american version is what are
we talking about just voiced over adopt
over something really great cartoon was from
nineteen fifteen twenty seven you guys are
both on your phones it was followed
by doing my better informing the pub
i don't know what we're taught
talking about davidson no mother fucker what
don't you fucking it you are making
me mad
hey now it's freezing in here right
so i was able to like david
letterman but keep it
yo soy david l jamo
greetings my friends in my magical kingdom
this is why you when i point
out and i go where i like
oh round you i don't grant wishes
that somebody else
a
stay
florida's so how are your chance
what's more loves it
let's just get to get a little
bit see can we see where it
goes and this is where it breaks
down
i'm david no i'm here to say
i like to wear a hat and
be gay birds tuck and fish that
sing
where's the tony okay and unusual there
are birds that can talk vicious say
now you've got my attention this is
a show yeah i'm really behind it's
almost over
a guy oh what's a kingdom i
don't like that yeah oh it right
down with the monarchy yes exactly yeah
i gonna watch the megan markle documentary
no i'm not either i'm sure i
well she has a documentary she and
harry made their own
doc is it like true stories are
finally telling suits and then she meets
him it's like i we just watched
the most recent season of the crown
i've seen random episodes of that which
i enjoy and name it's in the
diana years now where they get the
divorce part i was most excited about
but i know that well then you
should watch it
i've seen dubai's yes stop is like
one of the last scenes where kevin
costner calls her and says will you
be in the bodyguard too and she
says yes and the night before she
dies well is that true yes famously
i met her famously i did not
know this story that's fucking and say
oh anyway
oh wait she's still she's still alive
at the end of the season and
also war she's about to me dodi
fayad sappho my duty butter i'll never
die with but there
right so yes even so your a
bad man say i just those things
that are set in the past where
we all know the end state type
of yeah when they do like really
fuckin dumb foreshadowing oh i see yeah
that's what it means one thing that's
funny is elizabeth debakey plays diana in
this season's elizabeth take you she's a
extreme
the tall actress oh yeah from marines
ago so yeah there's have them shoot
seasons of diana number two yes yeah
when i saw some of the first
dance there was the first eye and
she was so or they were so
good so non binary actor who did
such a great job and then elizabeth
dubinsky is she's good but she's like
her being
i'm so tall she plays diana oh
her bedside hero and the tall person
just wait but it's kind of distracting
when you're playing somebody that you know
is not that she was tall she
was not she did not tower over
prince charles oh okay did wish you
so okay like they don't have him
on a box or anything why shade
is just his tall frame with her
head how
how tall was princess are you thinking
that because you met her when you
were a child i was yeah honestly
i was just thinking than amendment
five eight hold on let's find out
my son five ten five ten ten
wow but the biggies like six three
isn't she i think she's over six
fotolia yeah i'm not sure what lies
you're either well you know i know
but you gotta look her up and
then how to's prince charles that's the
other thing he's four foot don't you
love when you see his feet and
hands
i love it so much i've never
seen his feet i saw the feet
the other day why are they the
same as the hand we were hooking
like the feet she browses around she
checks on her store she goes monsieur
you know always told me what they
say is i have never lifted a
thing in my life i've only walked
once i've never done it it's like
princess status of like his hands are
so soft it's so soft and plump
if you're talking about your own wiki
feeds mail tree my wiki feed is
like
like i've never lifted everything that i
like i think my life she is
six three oh nice she's six significantly
taller than five ten yes and she
never even taller than everyone else on
screen yeah but she's an actress she
give us your email honey we're not
the disparaging news diana wear hats too
like i'm sure like if there's a
hot seat in there like wow we
can't do
i think just weddings and shit you
gotta put her in flats the whole
time you got a pair of flats
and she's still like a giant test
but um there's something about it that
makes her very bird-like in the wig
and everything she's kind of like yeah
i think she's trying to makers of
a little bit smaller sometimes oh like
hey i know i'm not supposed to
be so yeah
why did i fuckin bring that up
ah the crown so there's scenes where
their scenes where oh i had a
point this one
ah aka three to something that never
happens on the show it happens so
rarely that it is cause for celebration
um say wow great job boy huh
celebrate she you know she tells she
sort of covertly does an autobiography with
ah what's his name andrew morton um
from morton's steakhouse yeah exactly cool he's
not important are you tired of writing
steak menu you write about me
yeah it's crazy she had the foresight
to do this nobody sees this coming
so but then she does an interview
later with the bbc and they and
i as i was thinking it that
i have i think queen elizabeth say
it on-screen like how many times she's
going to tell her story finally tell
her story she's done it like again
and again and again yeah and feel
i feel like the same with prince
harry and meghan markle it's like finally
this re
tell our side of the story again
oh wow all we have is your
backs exactly i saw i like your
the other side for once yeah no
one knows the full story only we
know the full story and i guess
now we're all going to know
and then we know it um i
know we could guess it yeah i
mean i'm they suck okay i'm interested
i say to them that the royal
family yeah
i mean it was this incredibly archaic
outdated institution made up of inbred people
suck i don't understand and no and
morsi i apologize to people who who
love it for reasons that i can't
comprehend but what what is there to
like about is it's just ceremonial right
right you know i put there enjoyed
the words family tradition as
a common tradition of tradition and joy
i guess but i've i've taken a
tourist tradition and every time that i
should have been so lucky to travel
like i enjoy your show going by
and seeing the things in traditional jewels
and and all that tapes i find
it very interesting to some extent but
i i also think it's actually more
interesting in some
ways now with it being so modern
and there being an l people making
away from it it's like it's changing
like i think when you go when
you look at the museum stuff and
you see all the old jewels it's
like it feels so long ago it's
actually not i think that's part of
what's interesting with the crown yeah is
that you go wait that was like
the fifties yeah you know it's like
it's not long ago like that's kind
of weird it's times like this
that we're talking about are like yeah
yeah it's like i sort of put
them in a category like they're not
the same age as people i really
know don't think there exists in this
other world yeah that's that's my grandma's
you hundred years earlier than the time
the threshold right yeah but it's like
no slayer happening they're still doing a
could go to target they just don't
i'm gonna be so cool to see
charles the great leveller but will you
go to target for sure like every
choice excuse me king chart that's true
he's the king now we thought we
thought it would never happen do you
know i referred to princess diana's lady
die almost all the time when i
when i think of her i forget
that she's pretty because it was lady
di for such a long time and
when i was growing up and then
i heard a winch person on a
tv show refer to her as lady
and i felt like oh i'm not
the only one what's the difference um
well before she was four she was
princess she was lady die so she
became princess when whenever she married o
just married charles
she laid all the title well the
first one is no the first time
she gave him a blow job because
prince became latest kate has been married
and not been so i was just
i'm just doing them making the right
family tree in my head so she
was made chair she was engaged she
was lady di that's what i'm wondering
like how do you get the right
all of lady yeah yeah
so not a ton of course lord
die but no one talks about it
i think that's a lot of men
from my generation who are from mars
we know huh
huh who don't really know anything about
them like why was there nobody should
go but i feel like i was
raised to know about them i feel
like we're raised to meet her i
was i remember i'm old enough to
have ah
someday your daughter is going to be
baby die i was young grilled for
your parents were like this is going
to be your resume strictly say you're
going to peak early but um i
got the grade when i was i
remember the the royal wedding happening when
i was a kid yeah me too
yeah yeah it was a huge deal
or how much she was just right
or i've seen video you may have
just seen videos take place
i was i was like young took
place know that i'm sure i didn't
know that yes here we watched it
in the middle of the day yeah
i don't know what time it was
there i want to see what you're
like one am like a marijuana yeah
well she passed away that we could
watch it she passed away in ninety
six or seven yeah
ninety seven seven ninety seven hour journey
january i was at the no because
i actually won so was before i
was born but they so i must
have just seen five million k
these times are rubbish because i've seen
it she looks pointedly at age
earlier but i'm like i wasn't i
clearly in lawrence and that's before i
was born she looked right at me
and she put her thumb in her
mouth like me and she said goo
oh my ghoul oh and the guy
i was with guy
was at the rustic on hill hurst
and sitting in the in the back
when we all rescue yale restaurant and
they had a tv there how did
you get there and was your route
let's see i probably ah
went from cyrus island cherokee probably went
to franklin and then turned i guess
left on hillary's love knows not bad
hold on a second
yeah left on hill hurst yeah that's
top left but david's right within the
places on the rise across the street
yeah um but i remember a guy
jumped up when the news came on
this fucking guy jumped out of a
seat what oh my god no and
he dropped to his knees oh like
clutching his head
ed i thought it was that she
got married no no
i was just about to fly over
there no i remember watching the news
and really devastating yeah i had just
met her this guy was like why
is it always the good ones wasn't
this because i i i know i
was in san louis obispo playing in
a a ah amateur football game that
we would play the fuck are you
talking about between ah
amateur football game yes thank you so
much
bro and we're not here to see
the otherwise it the cnet's edition
this machine that ah peters kicking it
off
the fuck
oh ah oh sure we gotta take
a break scott was playing shut the
fuck up we gotta take break i'll
tell this when we on the other
side yeah in the meantime shut the
fuck up
we're about okay so i was playing
the week the week after the final
game of the playoffs and prior to
the super bowl okay we weren't dying
out so slowly play
it was hey this isn't bad
yeah
we would play out we would play
a game called the dog bowl named
after my friend dug up in san
luis obispo jag where it was the
shorter the short hairs vs long years
there's what did you say in short
hairs vs the long you had enough
friends with long hair yeah because in
san louis obispo everyone's like they're a
certain type of person has long
aaron is kind of a layabout yeah
and then there's a certain type of
person who has a job and i'll
check corporate guy so was the short
hairs vs the longer bone yeah to
be clear i hate them all yeah
so we so if they were dogs
i'd like it the shores vs the
lawyers i just remember it happening then
so was it the sunday or was
et saturday night i don't remember the
day of the week and i apologize
for that
well scott loves to remember the day
and the location of the film i
remember it was nighttime it was so
much night to saturday night yeah you
are not day drinking oh yes because
i remember it i must not have
heard it on the saturday night i
must have like woken up and did
the news reach the doug bowl
so it came out of the field
but i believe we died in the
early hours of the thirty first of
august nineteen ninety seven so much the
middle of the night hey real quick
um my middle of the night in
france in the made love nah friends
okay so let's do a paris tunnel
right yeah it's time did we learn
about it in the us yes
okay what while you're looking for that
here's some other celebrity heights because this
is people also search for these okay
claire photo five for crazy riddler foil
i've said things i'm trying to picture
these people just saying you're going to
john david washington five nine dominic west
six feet from ah the affair time
is it
paris tom hollander five five
alicia vikander if i say so it's
one am right now so it would
have been so associate she died at
four fifty three am so it's three
hours later um foremost for it was
eight pm here okay so it must
have been yeah must have been saturday
night there we go think so i
have an airtight i could be that's
where i was and you were not
in france i was right right
chicken okay ma zooming if you recognize
this name palm clem clement tif oh
yeah from a guardian ago oh five
seven oh cool
what does what does palm play she's
mantis she has a big part in
the christmas special i haven't seen that
i don't remember mantis i'm sure we
all first-time of these the princess diana
beanie baby making it a topic of
that generate very true very true and
it was were those made before she
passed away or were they made a
were
in memoriam because they had the were
made to replace her
one of them don't worry guys some
friends we got this handled she will
not you will not have the void
of her in your life we're gonna
make this baby baby it's gonna do
everything you need and you can retire
what were you buy this thing and
you're set for life well if you
have one it does all the same
things that you had when she was
live and that you didn't speak to
her
oh shoot yeah yeah exactly yeah
why did they make more babies of
dead people are eating babies still worth
it you know and i've j rye
they really aren't no yeah i mean
everyone thought they were going to like
send their kids to college with yeah
well my mom tells all summer wine
at the time and i remember being
a little upset but she got a
few hundred bucks for a few of
them i was like you know looking
back she was right i don't know
slander
gone yeah she did she went on
a bender she loves getting high but
i have all my beanie babies here
in la now so if you guys
want to see him sometime i'd love
to i have all my nf tees
here oh good as well imo my
entities here remember when we've been told
he's a lot yeah that's like a
moment with friends fun yeah like should
we do them should we not do
them
yeah yeah are we roared
what other are like the one company
went out of business it was a
big scandal write the essay fdx yeah
they're all like three-letter companies like w
t f guys right now and if
she no fucking token
yeah i don't know no fucking are
they still like it's all going to
collapse isn't it dumb shit no ah
well there are a lot of crypto
bros who get very angry if you
say yeah looking horse racing they will
defend you on but hey i think
there's a whole community actively participating in
that but i do think it became
less talked about why did we kind
of all i just don't think anyone
like
tks him anymore okay yeah i don't
like em yeah there was a time
you really liked oh like some summer
when on twitter you could replace your
circular profile picture with just a profile
on toggle
know what yeah i didn't i didn't
know how to mangano oh lord i'm
so proud of you lawrence halfway shiny
sunnies now no
if i wanted to you could you
could go to the bathroom oh i've
just start over
my hands hey know i was surprised
i did not get new well i
heard my hands are cold i think
it's what i'm experienced okay do you
want to turn up the heat dear
no okay
hey very good huh
some look good but you know don't
do do do do do do do
do like it i loved that record
so like oh um i liked robert
palmer yeah i used to listen to
robert palmer i liked that song doctor
doctor gimme the news yeah that's a
good one i like um
i liked his ah the smash as
well
house but but ah the remake of
banging gong i thought was very good
that was also from power station that
was our station yeah that that album's
great and actually was what he based
his hit the sound that he bases
his songs on after that because of
the success of that album they had
such a positive experience yeah it will
use the tony thompson zeph the drummer
from chic he used him one of
the thompson twins no no anyway um
did you know they weren't twins ident
there were three of them yeah give
you a badge i saw a picture
of them and i was like am
i allowed to see this picture because
the secret's out
when you first saw boy george
what did you think i mean i
was i was a kid i was
i guess a t thirteen ager yeah
and of course you know i thought
he's like this guy is the craziest
thing i've ever seen yeah i find
you're like i like it i thought
it was normal and everyone acting like
it was crazy was weird
scott that's how far advanced ai he
was he was a weird oh
he's good friends with one the real
housewives which was that's not surprising the
diary tuesday that's right didn't he didn't
he sing it one yeah yeah i
don't know how i know that she's
like boy you're just going to sing
at my party your excellency la chal
just going to sing it by pre-match
doing it right would you do a
real housewife show ah with just the
three of us yeah
but you know what i do know
i do know multiple people who are
asked to be real housewives do you
really i do know yeah yeah and
um well yeah you can i mean
you know of taste i'll tell you
later but
they both said no but i'm like
this i was begging them to do
it because i was like so when
you said multiple people was two two
that's multiples i mean it is just
trying to keep it does it does
but can you believe i knew more
than one no no i can't can
you believe anyone at all i can't
oh and i only i know any
of them i know neither of them
are one
you would think of as typical that
type but but this year they're kind
of shaking it up like new york
is about to have like jenna lyons
who's like the um she used to
do online she wants to say she
was like the head of j crew
and all they're like huge re-branding when
they became like really like gold glitter
fun action i don't know if well
it happened and
whether you know it or not it's
history and she's super cool but she's
like she seems too cool you know
it's like we had a whole new
generation coming in of interesting p because
you want someone who's bit of a
hot mess and why i think we'll
find out that some of them are
oh boy i can't wait let's do
anything being funded yeah we don't and
you don't have to call it real
house
ivs you can switch pans by the
way if that one's running hey include
you that you don't have to call
a real housewives but just call it
like the three friends and it's camera
the cameras follow us the three friend
wives i don't think we would make
a good reality show i think when
doj navy horrible
i think we would be forced to
sort of fight with each other we'd
be like yeah we will share many
measuring five olea scripted yes of course
already on mike we're playing it up
a little bit yeah we talk exactly
like this one we're hanging out
it's so open so we have to
do well let's do our um our
intro our little intro lines like when
they hiring oh yeah they have interline
i'm not some blood i just get
down with whatever yeah like okay just
go with whatever i had to find
it i am a slut
so and you start stuff because you
know the storm very well
um so it's like the music like
like okay i out the three friend
wives of los angeles put him opportunity
anyone by wow and then the title
comes up zoran is this lauren cool
up and janie are in the show
no less
yeah here's the three friend and as
always three friend was yeah so we
see lauren okay like she turned around
into frame you know and that game
comes up i don't just talk dirty
i play dirty to win and out
bolted out i want watch out scott
oh ah these guys hang out with
me as sort of a favor
okay this little thing it could be
a little sassy right oh
let's talk to you again without a
bunch of guys i bought wow scott
i'm old and i'm tired all the
time oh no actually i was a
little better but i think we can
beat it
yeah yeah let's do one more scrap
i bought but wow scott i have
some impending medical problems that i'm really
worried oh ours ah ok calling if
there's a sort of play on words
or something that's that's always fun that's
kind of why i used dirty two
different ways yeah yeah that's exactly right
my new year's okay but bob bob
oh no not ready huh
but blah blah blah but happened to
prop adapter but i got up and
up and up and up okay guys
be very busy
since wow
i tip my hat to you but
i won't tip a waiter wow i'm
like the villain yea yeah yeah that's
good waiters so the topic today's wow
scott i will tip a waiter but
i won't i won't wait for know
anyone know you can't refer to the
other one you have to do to
be stand alone
well you hey you of your hat
thing and she's got her dirty fucking
mouth and nothing you have that dvd
collection say wow i did it and
i'm done wow scott
i have a lot of dvds but
dvds doesn't stand for dozen video okay
dicks let me try and think wow
i'm i'm workshopping twenty bucks get dumb
wow lori didn't have it i spend
my days wiping asses but i spend
my nights taking may
kicking ass
ah something who's both ali and maria
you excess like oh yeah she's only
got one hell is this swiss banker
right now by the time i'm on
the show i have like eight kids
i'm like i'm like well that's true
this room covered have seven more coming
i have i could be my covering
kids and i'm like cool i'm just
like look i
i know i look like a crazy
mom during the day but when i
go out at night i dress like
a slut and fight like a whore
i wouldn't want to do that i
wouldn't want to fight with you guys
so come on i'd flip a table
in your general direction
i'm five glad that mushy python reality
tv could definatly come together
that's that's great i don't even know
what i'm quoting i fart in your
general okay
oh i shouldn't make these one biology
but that's okay you can you can
if you want it's fun to make
one pile yeah it's fun to make
piles how how many times you wipe
holly said i'm interested how many times
a day well you know as they
get older you don't change their diaper
as frequently so you're in a stage
right now where you're doing it every
couple hours at least probably right for
yeah once again i want to say
a sniffed into the microphone and we
will cut that up okay um i
probably change like four neighbors a day
for all of them hollies
i don't have to speak on the
other day person changes
um so that's three so it's like
that's every yeah every six six you
know but it doesn't make sense because
it's not during the night so like
okay let's see one in the morning
then i do one before naptime then
i do want after nap time then
i do one before we you know
change it before the beth and i
do and maybe
and maybe there's one in the middle
and then i do one before bed
or put it on but then let
him call and contexts i'm just putting
on will say four or five for
five okay you have it you have
a ten month head start on me
so i need to know like what
do i need to know in this
next ten months oh yeah i've said
i have a fourteen health i have
a fourteen month old that's true okay
so what do i need
it's just ah fourteen months ah you
don't need to know any of it
now you just need to know what's
happening right now really i honestly think
that's true like you just i feel
like for me it was more it's
so overwhelming to like think too far
ahead it's like okay what's the next
thing she's gonna do like show you
know in a couple months she'll start
rolling over and stuff and then you
have to change up
now she sleeps because that'll change that
it's like don't worry about that yet
because you don't do it yet you
know it's just shiny things like who
gives a shit at this point well
it's just like you are at this
point i feel like i'm doing really
well because it's like right and you'll
continue to because you'll just change slowly
each new thing that happens and you
don't have to get overwhelmed by all
of the things that are going to
happen we sent you a picture of
my daughter the other day you correctly
identified she was wearing holly ali's old
pants oh hi anyway i realised i
never have to buy clothes ever again
because you'll just constantly give me this
gets old quick because i and i
will get you a lot i was
actually going for then either it made
me kind of feel like i should
buy some clothes
for holly now would be great so
that i can get eventually yeah that
really nice um
great scheme i was like i wonder
how people feel about this and i
think it depends on how much storage
you have in your house but like
i was holding onto so much stuff
and then i started to feel really
overwhelmed and i was like wait because
even if i have another child i
can't keep everything she outgrew because then
she continues to grow for years it's
like exactly goes on forever so i
started
just getting rid of things which felt
really good but at the time when
i'm packing them away i was like
oh these are so sentimental and then
i opened it i was like oh
i don't really care about this but
it was nice for you to go
holly's band oh no the pair i
gave club over all the things i
gave up were things that i thought
were really cute and special i want
to donate a lot things that were
kind of just like i want to
see a picture of holly and them
as well i know i was looking
i have to find it um
i think i'd like the trauma
they have a little butterfly sisterhood of
the traveling butterfly but panties one and
those were also a hand me down
from i believe jonathan silverman's child oh
wow many seen a lot of bites
yeah the the pants the single guy
residual yeah isn't that nice yes well
that's great i gave me like a
really nice bag of hammy downs space
you're working too
on good girls yeah um and i
think he's so great and ah some
of that stuff ended up in emeralds
because well we're i mean already emerald
grown out of her first stuff so
we are passing it on like crazy
we go why did anyone make any
new clothes well that's also the hard
thing with remaining extensive
baby so where are we all just
trading clothes yes we do it so
fast but then when i get a
hammy down of something that's like a
nice brand because also like coop and
i have a mutual friend who has
hammy downs coming our way multiple time
right where the stuff is good and
i'm like this a friend of yours
who continues to grow yeah baby the
baby has nice brands and we blast
oh very united huh
recipient i know the personality the intercept
some of these because i'm like someone
i need him first and then emerald
is part of the friend group that
says your hair looks fucked up no
would you i would tell you yeah
we got the ah the aquaman family
christmas card oh good no it's so
cute so i just made mine the
other day
looking forward to it i pray i'm
on the list you are you'll get
one we find yeah we i don't
think we've made one in a few
years because the coven years oh yeah
what are we doing wants to do
that wants to sit like we're gonna
sit around with who wants to have
their fucking picture take on showers shitting
around it this way why i didn't
take photos i just put compiled
some that i liked on your the
one of emerald yawning was so cute
that was the only photo that was
good because we got a we got
her in it we got our two
no three dogs and cool up sister
and there was literally one picture where
everyone is looking at the ah there's
at least one dog yeah
you know who took the photo ah
a friend of ours okay
you don't have to worry about any
time or its ah a friend who's
the one the lady who takes the
pictures of the babies in and getting
getty sample centers or the deep dive
art i don't know her work enough
to comp last name call have you
ever sent a christmas card like that
like with foe
oh no i haven't and late january
think about it every year and then
you should never do it you should
do the wheel of time right now
yeah this is having sales here's what
look it'll do this i'm not i'm
not a place where i want to
be photographed right now i'll tell you
that you have a nice picture of
you guys from this year because that's
really absolutely not here's here's here's what
you do
yeah you got some duck tape you
put it over cheney's mouth and then
you hold up a sign this is
peace on earth
oh my god this is a classic
physics class that i'm that would be
funny everyone
no it is it is like a
classic funny yeah no no people film
that when i say classic i mean
like basic people there there are lots
of people who do that every year
and like i saw someone posting about
it the other day like well it's
that time of year again where this
this type of person you know so
if you're not fun
funny and you're making that it's actually
it's so misogynistic i can't take it
awesome absolutely horrible but you did it
it's funny kind i don't think so
you don't want that you're out there
no no no not funny enough from
no no i agree i did i
don't think it's actually good but i
do think the irony may i understand
layers that i can then yeah i
understand yeah
yeah but i think what we what
we need to do is we need
to do a picture around christmas time
for the next christmas yeah so we
do a picture go now you're gonna
automatically look worse next year than feel
right now that's absolutely true so take
it yeah i know even though
i'm told read about how you look
because mixture you'll look even shinier that's
so true scott and you'll go look
at it no don't say hey look
back and say that's what i thought
i looked shiny that is every picture
i think it's a horrible truth about
life
i do have some pictures where i'm
like i look good on the phone
no i you should everything from six
years ago i'm like great man why
would why did i feel bad i
think you're very handsome i think you
look nice thank you very much but
it's true we have to take a
break i was gonna remember i was
signing notes a break yeah oh to
match
oh well oh no
it's too late we gotta take a
break we'll be back
damn we're back and sorry i turned
to eyes startled too loud i've been
going up and down and it's not
freedom rocks turn it down man
these pretzels are making a dar say
it is time for the three cheer
if you'd like to send us a
three-tier idea please do please write to
us at three am usa gmail dot
com don't be insulted when we don't
like them no and look it can
be anything that when they're kind of
a game that personally is more fun
to
me sometimes end up just being kind
of fodder for doing little seasons is
mad aware of the gmail okay good
good good i just realised i was
like is anyone even looking at them
what if there's thousands
i mean how when do we get
like we're wanting gone
okay once again i've been ignored well
soon you'll see um so we dan
we're gonna play a little game this
is a game this class huh what
does this whole data ben what's she
up to whereas dido she was not
backing up mam at the rock hall
of fame i'll tell you that much
it was
ed sheeran singing that way that's why
y'all do as well but i think
i might enjoy that cover what about
fido dido she hears he bid yeah
it's going to bring up fido dido
but you didn't know if it was
right time i thought maybe too soon
i read the room and i decided
no no no we're not doing that
today we're gonna play a classic freedom
three cheer
called celebrity hunt and this this is
where um we all yell hunt and
then we go in a circle and
one person will name a celebrity then
we yell hunt than the next person
has him be right has to name
a celebrity that begins with the last
letter
of the name that was previously said
do you get it guy do i
got it and we all and and
when what they say the name and
then we go oh god and then
the next person does it yeah and
if you take too long
you're fucking out you're out and then
you have to keep going because yeah
we do need to have some competition
we need to healthy although yeah but
this is weird yeah it's good for
the shows and yeah okay if we
if we are constantly jockey for position
i think it's good for the show
i think so totally between feel like
you're winning threesome by the way because
that is like ninety percent of the
oshie i always think i'm winning so
that's interesting i always think i'm losing
oh only somebody's right
ah here we go it's you winning
this is how we play this week
if this lebron and shall i start
yeah we'll logo me scott lauren network
yeah right clockwise and three to one
huh it's true we tell igy for
huh
han's rita ora huds annie leibovitz hards
ziggy marley guys yoda
and alan arkin was ah midnight midnight
nah that sanders or elizabeth meter lender
who is the guy and ah groundhog
day right yeah see dad yeah ned
ryerson the kid ryerson there is no
deadly meter lecter okay he goes yeah
where did you okay so wait who
okay so let's start over so okay
sir i'll stop doing this
or do i just joined it and
i'm still gonna be okay so i
you start do i just do it
i'll just do it huh dead baby
huh and yvonne orji hods how do
you spell that ah there's neither yeah
okay huh gods um india r e
hons
ah elizabeth
huh sam shepherd huh jan keaton hot
ned ryerson
natalie portman hodge ned he's really into
dough
okay now i go as long as
i can or i know yes yeah
okay again huh and
elizabeth olsen hards neil patrick harris huh
just seventy allen ha so the l
word um um um emily blunt hods
trisha yearwood huh
da marie jones floods susan susan sontag
susan susan susan about susan susan ivan
susan
alright let's try to get on alright
let's try to be okay should we
go the other way yeah sure okay
who starts ah me me lauren starts
three two one huh helen hunt hogs
were going the other way so oh
no that's no that's star search areas
ah
ah tammy wynette huh and edward james
almost hunch is that within us yeah
um um sharon stone hot elizabeth olsen
huh so that doesn't matter did you
say that yeah or i thought he
said it's not the same round so
i think it's okay okay
oh hey
okay it's not the same i guess
just not saying
ah naomi judd huh and deepest magoo
ah tipples buku
ah alright yo man shot okay hot
so goes me and do i just
do anyone or i guess does anyone
do you do oh yeah if you
want okay otto preminger robert downey junior
hons roberts
ah nothing but you and dave roberts
seems robert downey sr oh i was
name is i want your turn just
alone you yeah oh shit okay will
give me the hunt i will yeah
what was the last one robert downey
jr naja ah ee ah
richard roundtree huh um elizabeth debakey huh
and iggy azalea haha albert soooo knobs
huh
who who loves wow
nah
we were going close fleeting oh my
man
i never saw it
oh hon susan sarandon huh huh didn't
have that in your head is also
even funny
mcnulty huh
ah edward herman huh hods fucking n
again ah natalie portman huh
nicholas cage huh
mackenzie knees
e he e calls up
yeah what about the guy who said
you created that einstein harsh dying and
said nice no matter
alright well that's how you play celebrity
tags textbook and it's fun and the
best part is getting deal hunt yes
yeah i wish we could do that
on our own without distributor to your
name o he just yell on it
should be like we hope and healing
it together right around where the rules
a little different and we just have
to say someone where the word hunters
in there
name ok okay and helena is excluded
no we give you a first okay
again kick daddy and go hard helen
hunt huh jason hunt hot robert hunter
junior hans bonnie hunt todd hunter s
thompson
hodge charles m hunch hans hunter ah
her parish ah and hunter biden too
but it's not a term i've a
ruhi ah brunt ho bauma ah
diane hunting huh
sean fluffier hods queen elizabeth hunt huh
lauren hunter
ah
ha ha you entered some h u
interesting intercept
we're out of the way dad we're
we're out of it okay listen thanks
everybody we love you for listening you
can follow only for listening you don't
love you for if you do crime
you don't love you for that it's
conditional um and if you want to
follow us on socials it's three dm
usa you can ride with three musa
gmail dot com you can call us
at a number
which is in our instagram bio and
if you want to come see my
show january fourteenth ed dynasty typewriter go
to taper dot com and come see
it's your show so fine my shows
don't but you can watch it online
ah go to vimeo my vimeo page
has ah past varieties on demand um
so much fun and you will enjoy
ten pollen i've been doing the comedy
bang bang best us together this week
and next week so listen to though
there you go it's a lot of
fun and if you want here at
free episodes of this you can go
to stitcher premium or comedy bang bang
world and then if you wanna hear
old episodes from out behind the paywall
on tuesdays we're doing three visiting on
the two's that's
right three visiting on the two so
you'll have ah an old episode pop
up in your fee that you can
listen to without ads and or no
with ads but from behind the mind
and that's it and ah you know
we're we got one more episode until
the end of twenty twenty two what
what day is this when this comes
out this is the twenty second i
believe just oh my god
christmas is coming around and the geese
are getting fat please put opinion the
old man's hatch she haven't got a
penny a hay penny will do yeah
i've got a hey ben even god
last year
two gentlemen god bless you if you
haven't got to hate then even god
bless zoo goodbye goodbye my name
uh