three
seventy five awards
six seven five four that was fun
that was so fun
can i tell you something i had
a great time doing yeah oh boy
here we go numbers go in any
order you want it doesn't fucking matter
do you remember the drummer and hang
up the phone you don't you don't
know lauren but paul do you remember
the drummer this is paul by the
way he's one of the three members
they want to shut up without a
gift for our lord jesus
yes i do and they easter sunday
yep on easter sunday would you show
up
so you showed up without a gift
for lord jesus the drummer who showed
up a little gift for lord jesus
on your christmas say oh wait we
know we've returned on easter oh back
again really oh yeah the little drummer
boy came back on easter okay that's
the story as a man he's a
man now yeah you say maybe you
must be thirty three so a little
i was like thirty eight
like forty would you be surprised i
thought you're talking about a real drummer
and something that really happened on easter
i wouldn't because you're stupid master manipulator
i am dumb um no the drummer
on joanie loves chachi do you remember
him
what in the band oh it sticks
sticks sticks was joining like weight on
joining the shot no i remember the
holidays oh oh maybe stay oh wow
you're talking about the man stick suddenly
like your narrow he's in sticks so
it wasn't general chachi the drummer instincts
ah that would be amazing my name
is joanie loves chachi and i'll be
playing the drums for you today i
like that name of that show joanie
loves chachi we always play on an
earlier show called it called bridget loves
bernie i didn't i didn't know that
yes yes yes yes and that was
a show that i think the look
of it was
as it was a ah a regular
old white girl loves the jew oh
nah earth how did that happen i
think that was the hook like she
was either protestant or catholic weird and
she was dating a jewish guy so
you know we are any weird premises
for dvd tv shows i went down
the rabbit hole
all of like i was you know
i've stayed kind of away from the
info about it like i know it
as a cultural reference but amos and
andy i was like boy i was
like i got i gotta figure out
exactly what happened with this like one
day i was just like enough being
in the dark about the ins and
the outs is there any way for
deemed what is no i wasn't that
but but i was an andy yeah
i don't think i know what that
is
it was a it was a radio
program ah whereupon the actors ah who
were and and i believe the writers
who are white ah portrayed ah people
who were black oh and ah when
i found actually interesting about the story
is that by the time it became
a tv show people were like
like thought it wasn't right and they
said blackface on tv they started with
blackface on tv and then they realised
that wasn't going to fly and so
then they cast the cast black actors
in it and then people were upset
that it wasn't the voices that they'd
come to know and love on the
radio and so the whole thing just
kind of fell apart so that the
voices are insane too it's like it's
a craig
easy caricature it's horrible right but i
was i was glad i just assumed
that it was on for years and
it was popular and everyone loved it
but i was i was interested to
learn that by the time it came
on tv people were like the this
should not be happening that's curtly and
so it was not so that was
the part of the story that i
thought it had a happy ending as
it was cancelled and now
now you know the rest of the
story yeah hey yay yeah we need
you to come back i'm here okay
i'm here i just didn't know what
you're talking about but now i'm ready
for the next thing so whatever happens
next i am so excited to talk
about that okay well let's update our
references from joanie loves chachi and amos
six the drummer on happy days figured
into a couple episodes there maybe it
is jolene jaci judge judy dempsey joked
joining those chachi was a spinoff from
happy days which was a spinoff of
and i thought you know what i
think like american style right well something
yes and then that was a spinoff
of it was
although it was similar to another show
wasn't i don't know sad week's great
sad week i'm looking at joanie loves
chachi if i can see sticks was
the drummer as a switch and pitcher
right there yeah we exactly week sad
weeks thirty fourth week sad week
ks
i'll tell i'll tell you who hell
sad weeks i'll tell you who won
having a horrible week with you rico
master was one of the characters see
ah bingo pierce mario master ellie and
a net mssql oh i didn't realize
they were all related this is journal
of chacha yeah so no name sticks
was that chinese last name i told
you six percent happy day you know
chachi arcola chachi arcola
of course i wondered if six went
over with a master rallies or what
i guess they must all been related
on the show they were part of
the band or whatever i just i'm
just saying the drummer would count it
off like this you know how you're
used to a drummer going one two
three four it was always funny he
went one two three four like really
bored that is pretty fun hey at
the time there was only so much
comedy that or the maid
so to you that was very funny
was hadn't seen a lot of stuff
there were only fifty shows ever
and i love lucy started them all
yeah only been fifty tv show we
could only watch lucy and the chocolates
so many times they stopped numbering them
like it used to be like yeah
number one where please don't i love
lucy a sixtieth tv show
so you remember when they stopped doing
that and must have been really exciting
for you guys which i do i
missed it the first time it wasn't
there yeah i was like wow this
is number eighty three would have been
number eighty three come on keep counting
it's fine count now it's like this
netflix shows number a million and two
are so many shows or boiling i'll
never get it all
content in the world that's what's so
cool my owing mo yoi your believe
like flushing life after love here yes
i leave that for ms such a
great song otherwise a great race well
have you heard the adam lambert cover
from the mark twain pending oh gorgeous
i bet it's where you justice was
let's say the already tabs know i
think i don't even play no if
he had done oh no i don't
think i was ready to test my
name's kevin bring it up that would've
been amazed are you doing just sitting
there reading your email schiff adam lambert
at the kennedys adam lambert believe it's
sadly incredibly dunny around
running a restaurant performance and then you
got cher watching it and being moved
to tears she cries a single tear
falls out of her stone face stone
solid
it was hearing aids health romo to
throw him out no residual dramatic he
does take one out at some point
we're talking about of course it's in
your monitors which we know doesn't actually
have notoriously give people a hard time
yeah even know that technology has yet
to be perfected
a oh my god i want to
saw so he slows it down
he doesn't loan flubs it's not just
that like he really acted really it
gives the song so much more meaning
do you come to the audience they're
already crying yeah just george washington from
hamilton think
see some way
really na sra
matsui they are jasmine safest joy all
around him there on hamilton's and stars
born
yeah it goes can i get that
hearing it out of there that he
pulls out a big year horses
move on and you're done with it
you don't like wow i'm taking the
listener know they like it bring it
bring it down a little bit more
over it until the very end because
the very end is just to the
bitter end d fucking goes for it
do you it makes me want to
see queen just this performance even though
he'll be singing queen songs
i would love to see bo is
one of the best people to ever
come out of american idol yeah yes
he's obviously i always like to him
yeah i always liked him umm what
will check from riba singing la riba
was also honored the same to share
she invited the whole cast of rba
at least one of them my wife
and i watch it
shares like i think i'm feeling something
i love share so much me too
i love her love her so i
love her twitter we watched a clip
of her with ah then chastity bono
on the sonny and cher show and
they it's like this was the days
of tv where like no one there
were no rules like
yes yeah then she brings chastity out
who's wearing an identical outfit to share
and they just do this extended thing
where they have a conversation and then
share says you wanna host the show
and so they they pretend like like
she's gonna come out and and do
the same show open the share just
this is like it's not playing you
off it's giving you the courage going
on this story that's not what happened
look at url the shares in tears
everyone needs to go watch those she
looks better now than she did that
how many views does have this has
two million eight hundred and eighty four
thousand so judging by everyone who's listening
we contribute of you at least a
hundred more by the time the senators
lin manuel
share share gasps
oh my ca it made me really
think about it do you believe in
it i don't even know anymore i
don't have
after love life is over they call
me cynical so they brought us chastity
and they did the thing where it's
like hey do you want to host
the show yeah and it's fucking adorable
it's it's unbelievable it's like they they
if something you don't really see that
much like they clearly they have like
a regular mom and child relationship right
they're very sweet together it's it's i
have three great moments that was that
we just watch right the chastity bono
thing and her ah her but on
that ship yeah those times i think
that um what a career he pushed
it off
listen to shares covers of abba songs
because they're pretty fun from recently yeah
or just to do a home she
didn't album but i think it was
related to the movie oh okay i
don't know because i didn't see that
what what was she knew take a
chance she does she yeah she might
but she's a vu she does um
she is weight homeland what
is the one that but she goes
she goes it goes she goes through
chicago's channel show song it's just we
have seen you twice in short term
as the name of the game that's
the song that's my favorite one she
went to checks it all mean yeah
sure sure oh shit a whole album
called dance
in queen she does dancing clean gimme
gimme gimme name of the game eso
es waterloo mamma mia chicky chicky chicky
deep what's chiquita chicken
kita is dando the winner takes it
on one of us for no damn
solid line solid album those are all
i have the songs and the name
of the game doesn't have a star
next to my apple music as if
people aren't loving that one the most
well let me tell you what it's
a great song okay judge by what
other people like oh you know that
makes me think of is the
the
the footage of um george michael doing
ah some things in the bathroom
did he get a dribble possessed
oh that's richard cooper yeah and rod
stewart oh i know but you know
i've told you they did for real
but there was there was a local
there was a local newscaster in philadelphia
that that rumor started about as well
it's smaller after the richard moscow flooding
come on it's so funny to like
go off
off on some local newscaster yeah started
town rumor yeah everyone's like hey that
random person that we see on the
news specifically does this thing yeah that's
funny he went jets johnny like richard
gear he was inoperable the durable strange
have you said dallas
ellis rains also did that i'd be
like yeah getting bit i get it
yeah yeah guinea pig yeah so what
video of george michael are you talking
about weight foot but is it safe
this guy moved out to l a
oh and then the rumour followed him
out to l a and no jo
like in los angeles there's no way
but see people hamilton how were you
an adult when that removing anyone
believed it no i was a i
was in high school because it feels
like only kids would be saying that
like it wouldn't actually affect anything because
you guys do you think hey you
to the government a news guy at
double-a possess
good newsman fifty triple
um but okay george michael george michael
singing somebody to love the queen oh
yeah this was ed wembley like rehearsal
footage oh it's oh that's right i
did see that it's the most joyous
isn't ah david bowie's watching well also
didn't ah discourse jesus christ is there
there's also a spirit yes there's everywhere
there's
video of david bowie singing under pressure
with any linux wow yeah that's the
really cool stuff where like some mine
sucks no no well my guys find
the way you described it it was
bad the other one that he's seen
is good i put my couldn't hear
know that it's it's really cool because
david bowie is like wondering if this
is going to be okay you can
sense it
a little uneasy okay it's a little
unease about like if she's gonna be
able to sing it or not and
she comes out and suddenly like blows
him away and he gets this big
smile and yes oh i got to
see it yeah let's check a little
bit of this out that is ah
not what i'm telling you came out
peter sutera is that something video
i mean that's that's the actual that's
not the rehearsal she's just like ah
harley keno yes yeah this is the
rehearsal footage okay this is it turn
it up bro
this guy just freedom rock this is
so fun
for us yeah
i wouldn't have done that but i'd
be worried right there you wouldn't have
done this
zoo boy looks great she's yeah very
striking lucy it's really sad
so right now she's kind of singing
like lower in a register and he's
like yeah sure anyone can do that
and she's just doing a backup
what is this
good friends screaming
six
uh i'm worried about her right now
right because it's almost it's rehearsal she's
going out she's a little show and
again i want to cancel this one
cancels yeah who is that who's that
guy was just doing that i don't
know what that is
there's an idea
oh she's so good
uh there's the kid from jurassic park
what he plays him in the movie
suits people on the streets
this was another smiling at each other
one way
is it a good good while you're
singing over it
yeah blame me
he's smoking while these things that's gonna
come back to my mo and stuff
smooth he does look pretty happy
oh look he's sober like good-looking really
great eyes like he's giving her like
york and george michael's in the background
he's just fucking like it
here comes
uh he's twirling around
she dressed like a newsy
since like eleven easy
oh that's somebody's thing right
whether newsy could deliver the paper boy
go on strike
hello you got me back very user
like oh yeah you doing good
george michael
it's sad he said to
good people here glad they got to
watch each other rehearse for the
and here's somebody love sounds great yes
the georgia medical aid song is really
trapped i own time i guess i
will say i was always a george
ma
i was always in george michael fan
and were you a george michael stan
i stand like we're at a point
where you don't have to say stan
to ever know you know who is
standing and everything eminem okay fine that's
the original stamp is a little bit
you you don't stand everyone i did
use a threatening letter to you save
your standing for very specific people okay
yeah i agree hey lauren i agree
i'm generally a fan of things yeah
automatic yeah airplay password replay passcode is
eight one nine seven guys guys get
over here one nine seven you can
do it if you could be over
in the next ten minutes get rid
of it kevin get rid of it
renovate kevin god ron and why did
you get rid of her
play passcode it's a security breach so
you don't get on my damn security
breach security page nine bitch so what
are you doing jennifer maybe you gotta
show this is a weird episode reach
into my aha or restyled sho yeah
well let's talk about stuff that's not
videos
it's okay right how about this is
good ah i've had guys see that
mean you gotta crash about the cars
you got a question i'm gonna have
on by the time i made my
bedtime my mouth open by the time
i'm thinking okay um if you had
to work ah
at a specific so we never got
to the answer on this last one
if you were sponsored by a company
what company would you be sponsored by
and you had to where i can
jacket the senate and but they paid
like your whole mortgage like but your
clothes had to say wow yeah anybody
i know but everywhere everywhere you went
a breitbart yeah that local area close
ah would you how much money would
it take for you to
add breitbart i because you just couldn't
no matter what well i don't have
any moral ten million dollars no for
ten million dollars you think money changes
moral
your post questions like this went nowhere
you think oh what how much well
would you do this i training acts
certain people would start to justify the
behavior but you also said somebody could
buy your birthday for a thousand dollars
yes please i don't need it but
your birthday i want to ask you
a question too based on a previous
episode alright
me lauren bradley receipt
if i would just give you twenty
bucks for no reason yeah yeah would
you give me twenty bucks for no
reason sure you really yeah if it
was like kinda twenty bucks you just
go here and i would note episode
you wouldn't even have to say like
i needed yeah of course
i would do that to yeah i
would give it to you but i'd
really wonder why you want it because
in normal human interaction you would say
hey do you have twenty dollars that
i can have because this thing you
wouldn't just say i want two dollars
yeah i want to kind of clarify
because i i when we talked about
it it was very telling
you you i think you thought there
was some big message there that i
wouldn't just give you twenty dollars yeah
i would give a homeless person twenty
dollars before i would give you twenty
dollars why because i know you have
twenty dollars no i don't i need
twenty dollars if you weren't like i
want i just want to make clear
my point is not that i am
so stingy that would never give anyone
twenty dollars
i give money away to charities and
people shot but it's where you don't
want to give you twenty bucks right
you told me but if you really
want it so bad can i give
both of you twenty dollars okay but
then would just shut the fuck up
if you give us about twenty s
and then we give it to each
other
i don't want your money this is
what i want i want you i
want you guys to give each other
twenty know it actually i don't wanna
i don't wanna i don't wanna tweet
comfortable i want guys it makes me
uncomfortable i want twenty from lawrence while
i'm saying
i don't think i want it not
i want it to be her twenty
dollars i say twenty she years from
i'm willing to fund this show i
wanted to be money that she is
learning to understand what you think is
being shown by me not wanting to
give it to you but i will
give it to a homeless person yeah
it's really what does it show you
what does it tell you just tells
me a lot about your personnel jazz
about how you were raised and to
value the dollar or you value a
dollar more than me more than friendship
you don't need it you have amo
no i don't mean it
you know i don't eat thai dollar
because talk about your money all the
dignified yeah you're constantly saying you robin
and i'm i'm spending money on something
else guys guess what it is this
time i'm spending twenty dollars on it
okay so like what brand would you
be able to wear all of your
body were shah that's newbie
ah of course ah i feel that
i still need to go back to
this this is a weird question because
it's like what brand would you what's
not real it's completely failed but that's
why it's a bad question is like
well i pad good question i pick
cartier i pick like the most
luxury you ever wear shirts and see
that everywhere you know right oh holy
that is lame here's what mine is
everyone make fun of you here's mine
is tasty cake that is the local
baked goods company in philadelphia so you're
actually trying to get them some good
advertising in addition i love them i
don't if it works for them great
but
yeah they're paying my fucking mortgage absolutely
i'll wear it tasty cake sure i
only like to farm i lie and
do i like the product what what
do they taste like they taste like
sweet things get some pie sugar it
up yeah yeah you just gotta sugary
would you like driscoll's fruit
scholes roots what's risk every day some
strawberry brand or something and people will
be calling you like fruity yeah and
they
jody berry shortcake a pineapple head oh
no don't do pineapple wow this is
a real twilight zone and came back
twice to me as well because you
didn't just say people calling pineapple that's
true i would read everything
scott come on i want everyone to
know i'm i'm a jenner i don't
read i truly don't understand the question
i think the other he is held
on no there's no because he's clenching
is weird okay i just think it's
strange that if i were to come
up to you and say oh d
twenty dollars that you would ask me
what for you but for you i'd
say
why
if kevin said hey do you have
twenty dollars that's weird i'd actually probably
give it to him without as many
questions as with you with me you
i just went for i don't have
twenty dollars i don't think he's going
to spend on that here's the thing
he needs that i'm telling you i'm
telling you a cation this is why
you think it's weird because i'm telling
you i don't need it i just
want twenty dollars that is
why it's weird but why is that
strange that was don't you want twenty
dollar no because i would rather have
my own money that i've worked hard
for work hard for please i work
hard she worked hard for and i
mean or you think you work harder
than me come on no man carrying
this work equally that's such a joke
but anyway is all i'm saying is
if somebody who needs money and is
in need what i'm saying i don't
need the money it's why i want
the money paul
this is almost a pointless argument thank
this but here's my point about your
i'm gonna give you a hundred dollars
for your birthday you are yeah okay
great so here's the thing you'll never
celebrate your birthday ever again and i'm
owning the date wait a minute i
thought i was accepting a thousand for
this yeah you've got one hundred talked
yourself
elf down if you honestly if you
give me a thousand dollars
just because i wanted i'll give you
something in return like i'm buying something
from you no i'm saying what are
you gonna give me i'll i'll give
you something how about this i'll give
you this going i'll give you a
thousand dollars and you never celebrate your
birthday again i know if anyone's specific
birthday to you say shut up ah
shut up florence now
alright like we have to take
effect
we're back we're back we've used to
debo reach lauren you said you had
a question no i just i was
actually fully kidding i'd love for someone
else to ask a wash okay i
have a quest oh what's your question
i
i made a tweet recently regulations characters
was me i made a tweet hundred
and forty three
i said it was a joke tree
but it's also kind of it was
also kind of serious right that you're
straddling the line between drama is what
i do this is why the art
of what i'm doing that's right that's
why i'm different um i said like
most people i keep a running list
in my head
head of people that i don't know
if they like me or despise me
right and then laura and i started
talking about it on text and i
actually wrote out my list wasn't involved
in this no you're you're on my
list yeah you didn't ask about lauren
du no no no but i did
i did follow up and say who
are you talking about yeah and then
i was
i actually wrote them down and i
was gonna do mine but then i
feared it would be too long because
i ah i always think that somebody
hates me or something everywhere i go
well i was great mine was gonna
be too long and then i realized
well there's some people that i don't
i don't know but i don't care
about so much there's there's people on
the list that i showed you that
i don't necessarily
like them but i don't know what
you don't and i live in them
not like i think that's usually the
basis like if you really investigate you
go maybe i have a problem or
something and that's why i think this
person doesn't love never come to that
conclusion it's the same thing it's like
when you like the faults you see
in other people or problems with yourself
or something it's like you're going like
this person is like me because i'm
putting out the energy of i don't
like them or writing yeah but i
but i'm like a friendly guy and
i don't see i don't think i
put that energy out to these people
friendly as casper the ghost himself yeah
and i'm dead
wow so nice so i say send
my list to lauren and then she
and it was weird to see that
it was i'll show you the list
it was like of course you cannot
say any names out loud right but
everyone assumes that i'm on the list
i'm not on the list because you're
gonna show me the list people anytime
yacht because we do so many shows
together anytime you tweet something like that
no anytime you tweet something like people
joke around like oh yeah
ocm is on the list or whatever
that's i think i saw that's all
hollywood hand people don't understand they want
to eat my hair and so wicked
man let me see this here simply
don't understand her in sweaters was with
him and so i sent this list
to lauren and there were a couple
of people that she responded about like
saying yeah i get that person to
and or um
oh that guy is just like he's
on some sort of spectrum or something
but then there are other people you
did not say anything about and i
was like it's true they don't like
oh i need more than i just
like have no opinions i don't know
what your actions are that's what i
yeah well yeah i'm one of at
least one of these is insane insane
yeah there's one guy i can take
off for sure because what wow
oh it was full because
because he's the best man at my
wedding let me highlight the one that
i think is is insanity okay let
me see alright that's the one that
i just i know that's not insanity
i just don't understand that well okay
we'll have to because because this person
is extremely hard to read shane the
one that i said he is actually
cut my cum off the
way to a lot of people because
yeah it seems like that doesn't really
outwardly show a lot of affection that
was that came up in the hawaii
trip we talked about this person who
is by the way a person that
i do like a lot um and
i was relieved that other other people
had the same feeling and essentially saying
nobody knows you nobody knows for sure
yeah and i was like ok i
feel better
now that it's not just me yeah
i feel like i get that a
lot where people go like i don't
know if he likes me or doesn't
like me i don't i just don't
think about you
jan fifteen
intense i'll think about you at all
so let me tell you well done
think about everyone really every night as
you sit down for your player i
think about every single person and i
think positive thoughts about them it's such
a weird thing to be on the
earth for what feels like well an
eternity you're well when you're you're you're
all
you're ever have ever felt right and
you are you're always like they might
be dialed yeah exactly my giants don't
eat this pot cookie older than you've
ever been and now you're getting older
now you're even but that the the
shift that stays the insecurities that stay
with you that you think all be
done with that by the time i'm
that age certainly
i'm realising that life is short and
why would i bother caring about such
a thing you don't care as much
but you do you do think about
these so you can't control your thoughts
but it's not like i'm definitely not
lying awake at night like what can
i do to make sure you gotta
sleep like a normal person yeah yeah
my move them getting bed you i
slip
nine and i wake up during the
day do you have a list where
you think that people you could name
a few people where you think i
can't tell say like me or not
i don't listen people i know don't
like me
yeah they made it clear yeah and
then as far as like people who
i don't know i don't know yeah
i'm not sure maybe you don't spend
as much time considering such thing i
well i feel like i'm looking at
myself
laura looked over viso slowly and meaningfully
anyways it's like yanks say to pharaoh
oh i will say that when you
are work when you're not the boss
and you're working with people there's lots
of me there's a learner the boss
i mean i know there they might
be giants song um when you're when
you're like because i had my own
show
for a while when you're the boss
of something it's like just one unending
fight with people yet to get to
get what you need yeah from the
show or the project whatever you're doing
is just like you're constantly being told
we can't do this we can't do
this we can't do this and you're
saying like but we need to do
this we need to do this so
like all that stuff kind of goes
out the window at
a certain point where you're just like
we have a business relationship and i
don't care if you like me or
don't like me yeah it's like purely
about getting the the end result done
and yes we all want to be
pleasant to each other but we're here
for a purpose never going from never
being a boss to suddenly being a
boss which you which can happen in
the right way yeah line of work
is is a really strange thing and
and the it you know it's hard
to be um ah
i don't know it's it's difficult to
walk the line of getting things done
if you're not and not be a
crazy asshole you know anyway because you
don't want to you don't want to
have the bad news of saying to
somebody this isn't right or this needs
to be different or whatever it just
feels like you're being difficult it feels
if you're saying i'm still horror
everything about the way that's the horrible
thing about being doing like sort of
what we do when you are suddenly
you know either directing something or or
in charge of your own show you
just feel like you're being difficult all
the time because you want because you
want to achieve good greatness or whatever
and i'm not saying that you like
like i flip out and yell at
people because that's not good you know
to be but i'm just saying like
i have a constant feeling like i
am difficult to people because i'm saying
like because i'm saying like hey can
we do this better can we can
we yeah it's just to drag it
becomes a drag on like i feel
like i get home at the end
of the day i'm just like oh
god i
just want to be like feel normal
and have like a normal interaction with
someone where i'm not you when the
reality is like when you have been
an employee of someone in a creative
endeavor and they've asked you for changes
you're not thinking oh my god this
guy is insane why is he never
shuts up you know it's like no
this part of the job i get
it you know it's all
so because you're dealing with your someone
has an idea in their head that
they are trying to make a real
thing yeah right and so that requires
a certain amount of translating and it's
not going to be right out of
the box the first time i also
want to process if it has something
to do with the very nature of
art where people are bringing you know
no like if you're if you're working
at a job where i don't know
where you have to have numbers or
something that the numbers are there the
data is there it's it's i need
those numbers we have to have them
but when it's art it's like someone's
coming to you with their vision and
you're saying oh but actually i would
rather be this and you feel like
you're disappointing them because they came to
you yeah lauren you seem like you're
zoning out or looking at the tv
what's going oh well i did glance
at the stop watch behind your head
um but i wasn't well you're talking
praying for
time to speed up guys why
eternity i'm gonna do that all the
time i was interested um was is
the operative i don't really think i've
ever really been a boss i i
you were sort of in charge of
your characters episode yeah yeah i definitely
definitely but like there were a lot
of other people certainly enjoyed the special
thanks
which i understand if people understood and
like working together on all of those
too like i got to like yeah
dictate certain elements of it and choose
a lot of things but then you
know like other things i wasn't in
control like it wasn't the director so
then like that immediately changes a bit
of the perspective because there's another person
who's deciding how things so
so then but like i directed a
short film in the fall yes so
one was really send it to me
and i still have never don't watch
that one because i'm getting a new
ex really watching so um your laziness
oh yes my watch the old lazy
oh yeah well there's a new one
it's gonna be much better i hope
so because there's okay i well you
do next you not
me but it was hammy so jovial
i'm wear my goggles because of how
he's dressed yeah it does a lot
for topic battens fire ah i just
i did feel there was a different
sense of pressure being the director of
the day we did all one day
but that do you feel like that
pressure is pushing down on you
yeah pressure can be um any linux
and hear about like but not great
at first kind of phone in for
a little bit ah i liked it
a lot i liked being able to
control elements that i normally as an
actor don't get to control but i
also was realising just how much work
goes onto that sidewalks just
like every single question is directed towards
me and then yeah everyone needs information
and you're the only person with the
information and you can spend the entire
day answering questions or you can make
the thing right you know what i
mean and hope that you know some
of it gets delegated and yeah just
like people can work themselves yeah i
was thinking
well that i had a crew of
people who were like really independent like
they were able to come up with
their own thoughts and ideas too like
moving forward so that it wasn't just
me going yuck here's what has to
happen but um it just gave me
a newfound um appreciation for the role
of director well i hope you get
to do more of it because from
what
i've heard about this short it's fantastic
well have not watched it so so
i see you being supportive now it's
nice um i would like to direct
more though and um mostly but i
thought it was really fun did you
wear jodhpurs know did you ever really
i was in it as well which
is another element that's a little different
i'd say thinking about multiple things how
do i look how do i look
how i feel do i look fit
into i look pretty boys wonderful thing
do you look good i can't i've
never been able to tell
have you ever directed
no no any interest in it no
i don't for that reason well you're
one of america's great entertainers you should
be directed niles you know anything like
the thing so but i'm also director
proof
did you read that thing that when
it was it was like the morgan
freeman yeah the guys even kevin kline
kevin claims janeiro or in some movies
some movie together and they told vegas
it was called oh right that's so
clever and they did it and entertainment
weekly second live let's talk about the
title for a second oh that was
not a play on athens last and
older
not like this is called and your
city old vegas oh vegas yeah it
doesn't rhyme with la so it's not
the opposite of life it's not even
in the universe of law yes or
is it last vegas or you think
it's the last thing that i think
it was last pick oh vegas
so paul little my siri that old
vegas is a terrible title yeah no
one even used it
no one even used it
much is given to those good old
me
this last vegas
you're really working yourself up about it
to happen other things like that though
was sure there have been other things
but not this thing i know i
want to try to save this
so they're in entertainment weekly be interviewed
like the one bit of press they're
doing they're doing an interview together and
they're talking about i forget if he's
just kevin kline morgan freeman okay was
it the director of this particular project
or was it was actors project yeah
okay well no both yeah yeah so
they're talking about this director and they
say he was fine he didn't tell
me what to do so that was
good yeah
and then they start they start saying
like oh god all i allow a
director to tell me is faster or
slower yeah one time like last guy
came up to me and try to
give me a direction on how on
how i should be feeling in my
students face whatever like i already know
how i'm feeling yeah yeah that just
tell me faster slower ah i was
more
kevin kline which is so insane because
in the exchanges that i've had with
people it's always about like what are
you thinking and why would you say
this right you know to be freeman
though i feel like if somebody were
like he can just talk and it
sounds like there's meaning behind it yeah
like oh he does mean like faster
slower like he's maybe i'm gonna say
everything exactly you know
saying yeah i'm gonna say it exactly
like morgan freeman joanna morgan freeman study
there happens in thirty seconds or happens
to me morgan freeman what do you
like what do you want to do
like the thirty second person you'll like
them both you'll like the minute morgan
what's wrong with this picture
two at a time when to play
with succour
i had an experience recently where i
was doing something where i was direct
being directed in a character that i
had done for many years oh yeah
and by new person i never met
before and did not know was going
to be directing me oh okay so
i had to adjust on the fly
lie of like the the thing i
try to like there was a time
when i would have been very insulted
by that and very upset and like
would have felt like i'm supposed to
say something i should say something this
person and i'm gonna let it really
annoy me and it was annoying but
i was like i will i'm just
going to do that the professional thing
and i'm gonna take the direction and
do it but i
i should i should have a talk
with the person who hired me for
this to say it what's the deal
here no one told me that this
was going to small zoo with this
guy it was jerry seinfeld it was
jerry he loves to direct characters to
dreamy imodium there's anything wrong with that
hey there's not
oh wow well you know you know
careers are going to be long and
laura and i think that yours is
gonna have wonderful twists turns so to
peaks and valleys oh so now go
down to the steps you want wanna
just like keep going up up up
yeah i'd like to who wants valley
so you want to you want person
at the top of your poster you
want to have a bunch of i'm
i know that life is a roller
coaster and i will go up and
down oh wow wouldn't you rather just
just go up and i some things
keep happening but episodes at a certain
point won't you have have got like
you know you look like someone who's
been nominated for an oscar even wins
an oscar undoubtedly their next thing is
not going to be as good right
but like there's so few tom hanks
who went back to back but don't
you think like what the shit hunger
x is one as they're going up
up up and they know they'll never
ever be able to top
what they just did that's when you
pivot and you do another hobby another
hobby meeting a different job no like
something else that's challenging must be very
rewarding i just feel like it must
be very difficult to have achieved that
kind of success of like winning an
oscar for something and then and your
relative
lovely young and you're like whoa no
those thirty whatever oscar then they never
do anything yeah yeah i've thirty years
left and and i'm never gonna win
it's never gonna get as good as
this you know tatum o'neal yes but
yes machine little feather that's a quality
problem
wow you really got em all their
sheds a different i don't know if
the last one that's didn't she accept
the award from our lumberyard oh yeah
yes
i can't do everything i can't know
everything is hollywood history before you on
interested in anything that happened pre like
what's your kind eleven
what's the point really you don't want
to know what led right i'm not
interested in history i don't think that
there's any area that i'm keeping my
focus on and that uninteresting i just
zone out about certain things don't write
well i mean maybe you're just not
interested in the oscar ceremony or whatever
like i read like a
board shows there i read a book
i had a great book where it
was just like you know talks about
every single year and what happened and
all the trivia and all icons yeah
i'm not that interested i had i
had a really great book that told
the story some may say the greatest
story ever told the bible yeah wow
do you know this book yeah i've
heard of that book i started a
hotel
it's for free
it was for free
thank you santa conditioner people take people
up here can i get a fresh
bible
what one of every hotel you went
to you call down to ask for
my i'm feeling brand-new for i forgot
to tobacco what could you bring me
a bible bible and every hotel i
mean there's no no certain shows like
the the marriott chain they do really
yeah hotel i just sit in that
i don't think as a chain had
it it's such a strange point of
view of that well if you're
staying in a hotel you must be
at one of the low points of
your life you could be that's how
there's the temptations you've strayed from home
yes temptations arise we see it it's
like here's a general book a lot
of people like like somebody like michael
crighton they're just like the bible know
no fear that the the religions
actually put them in there the hotels
don't the the religion oh the hotels
do because the maria chains on by
mitt romney's family oh i didn't know
they put bibles in every i don't
like why don't they put book of
mormon in there too on the nose
so much troops religious texts you could
be throwing in there and be it'd
be much more interesting to open your
table and see a
koran but but what is the point
of view behind it because i always
assumed it was not forgotten i was
assumed it was like let's let's get
these people when they're at their low
point it's not just like hey if
you're bored check this out i think
it does come from a tradition of
that of where we used to be
back in the fifties or whatever yeah
we're at a hotel if you're traveling
if you're traveling subject to it's like
like say maybe don't shoot junior ever
get shit faced drunk man it feels
so fifty is to like think that
like that's so like a black and
white sad rainy movie at a motel
where the guys sam raimi sam raimi
movies i think something like gotcha for
the model down i feel terrible directed
spot the third
amy brother and i do sad movies
my point i get your point i
got your point like a scene from
it's a wonderful life exactly yeah that's
what i mean is like it's not
really a packable now especially when you
go to a really nice hotel i
can google the bible anytime i want
yeah google how many hits does that
have how many unique kits does the
bible have got to be in the
thousands probably alright look
let's take a break
or back i have a feature that
i've selected from my past this is
exciting a and we kind of talked
about playing mash and on my radar
colonel potter i always turned the channel
when that show came i know that's
that's your generation because it's animation um
it's too brown it's definitely dusty it's
a dusty show i don't believe there's
humor there um so here's how the
game works it's called mash it's gonna
tell your future it's a fortune telling
game what i need
who wants to first mean you're going
to take around and here's how it
works i have labeled at the top
i've written m a s h which
sands mansion apartment shack house yeah which
is wrong cause i put houses category
because i was thinking okay there's a
mansion apartments lupus jack quite a difference
between the shack shack is even worse
and it's s h a q
you live with him and that's okay
so category just the general come over
all the time same with general saves
i'm dying
so then the categories are spouse pet
vehicle job salary and so i need
paul to name four things in each
category x ah that he would want
and then i'm gonna add in one
of my own that's a random one
to throw it off okay so far
and it's always a bummer one might
as well be okay yeah ok it
will be fun so oh
marcus welby let's get three celebrity that'll
be your turn wait your turn that'll
be three celebrity chance for celebrity houses
and you would want to marry celebrity
crushes shit do they have to be
current do we have to reveal from
your past to reveal our actual crushes
or the embarrassing
or just name beautiful people are i
mean were you can name anybody can
even be funny ones that you don't
want orange or that you do but
would be unexpected like elon like she's
not gonna marry how do you know
just give up she's not going to
marry you dude
i'm going to say um
the first person that comes to mind
is sydney babbitt knutson
back she was on borgen a great
show every word you said is fake
since z babbitt was that a new
show so can you d s yan
know it's an old show it was
a danish show okay about the government
and it's a fuckin great show here
how about this i'm gonna go jump
each category seem to think of all
the people at once so give me
a pet that you would like to
have meaning
a specific name of a pet or
just a title and ronnie
ronnie from jersey shore st bernard okay
give me a vehicle it could be
a wagon it could be it could
be a train it can be anything
but you drive this thing you drive
this thing i say a train okay
now that you mentioned it give me
a job
ah conductor of course no job that
i would like to have archaeologist
sexy archaeologist
okay maybe a salary amount that you
would like to be paid yearly yearly
okay yearly a million dollars
okay give me another spouse option for
your sake
ah rosamund pike okay give me another
pet um a falcon give me a
vehicle
oh um
a a vesper
okay give me a job
spy okay give me a salary
half a million dollars oh pretty good
options i'm giving you some good opposite
oh we're going again okay here we
go is it's not more than three
is it just give me one more
one i put one in myself right
but for me yeah yeah i need
to throw it off maybe one point
oh i know so it's not just
all good stuff yeah
damn daniel ah damn daniel
and today with white bands
so ah um
cush jumbo what this one is jumbo
she's on the good fight okay pet
sitter dave out loud as wild um
as wild i hope should i have
hoshi have a good four twenty
hat um what i got st bernard
i got falcon and one that i
made up i'm gonna and one that
you made up i'm gonna say
a savannah cat okay and then a
vehicle
motorcycle sidecar okay and a job um
right y'all just spy
novelist okay and a salary
one thousand dollars here now tell me
when to stop
is that okay when i was drawing
dashes on paper one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
okay so talk amongst yourselves i do
matt hi paul how are you scott
was the number i just i'm good
twelve eleven eleven okay
scott why are you afraid to reveal
your celebrity crushes because you might work
with them or something yeah i don't
want them to know i'm horny for
them who are you not horny for
millet start their work with them anytime
i'm horny for everyone i've ever worked
with denzel washington hey don't get offended
if i'm horny don't get offended if
that's paraphrasing a little bit
ah the way have i told you
the word i i used to not
like the word horny i used you
used to make me cringe and i
think it's very it's very funny really
it's kind of cute yeah well we've
passed this sort of you know austin
powers point where it was like annoying
during that yeah yeah now because people
go mahoney
and they would say it like him
not like that but like ram
i think it's when people talk about
hoarseness in a very um dispassionate way
i find that very files i hate
it when people actually are horny
i hate being horny yeah i hate
that too but i think sickens me
i hate it when people are horny
i like anytime i feel like someone's
horny it's like like when other people
are hunting i don't like when i'm
horny right so you like it when
someone's horny for you know well no
i don't like that i like to
being horny for other people and things
so you like them being generous
really horny away from you at st
george near me but i don't want
an act me and if you don't
want here's a real question have you
ever been in the room while someone
is having sex scott not you is
a real gotcha question
and and and you're pimping me because
there's something we've talked about off my
wow i will come you know i
even today know i'm a peeper oh
here is your future you are going
to your future your future future you're
going to live in a house yeah
ny ordinary to cush jumbo yeah i
don't know who that is but congrats
you're gonna have a cig
vanna cat yeah you're gonna drive a
train
everywhere you're going to work as a
subway bagger which means that you work
at subway but you just put the
sandwiches in the bags
they don't trust you the response is
that for real job i'm no but
i mean and then your salary is
five hundred k wow for subway okay
let's see i've been there a long
time got i'll do yours next yeah
do my twenty nine okay so we
need a spouses pets vehicles job salaries
some new spouse
i'll give you three spouses okay ah
mary holland erin whitehead yeah nah and
somebody is now an interesting okay um
and then pets pets yeah um i
i'm gonna say give me a a
give me an iguana in there and
give me an iguana give me an
iguana in there and give me another
boston terrier that's the one i really
like and then one more and then
give me
a god i can't imagine how your
rabbit grow so rabbit okay vehicle vehicle
give me an elantra
how about ah one of those jay
leno old timey cars
and then give me a hoverboard
okay
um job yeah jobs jobs jobs jobs
jobs ah ceo of apple speaking of
jobs
scott jobs
jim cash
and rob hirsch
um movie star
um one more and ah i also
would love to be like a programmer
okay and then um salary salary i'm
gonna say one hundred million dollars one
hundred and one million dollars in one
hundred and two million ok
okay and now tell me when to
stop
stop okay and you talk amongst yourselves
oh we get to talk amongst yourselves
again i i guess when we started
this game i forgot that i was
going to have to we're going to
talk about talk about we're hormones yeah
i know
so your who is cush because jumbos
on the jersey of the good fights
on cbs all access oh what am
i going to start watching cbs all
access well i mean this shows i
like this show friend of mine recommended
it to me sure i got cbs
all access for star trek discovery so
i wanted to see isn't it now
on amazon now i don't
oh if it's on amazon now isn't
that now on amazon now but i
don't know if the new episodes are
on no the the first season so
when i started watching it wasn't yeah
i know so you've got the picard
thing coming up in the toilet cards
come in and i come over and
watch twilight zone know because you put
it what do you mean i poop
poop poop outta you pappu does ceos
all access what
i said what am i gonna subscribe
but you can yeah well see that's
the thing i'm a cbs all access
subscriber but you're too good for it
don't hoard your cbs the horn and
any time i will got your oh
wait hold on oh wait more talk
ah so anyway keep on da gosh
you are going to live in a
shack know your spouse is stephanie allen
no
i felt michael jackson i'm both here
list i never thought it ah your
pet is a dragon's tail i made
that up and it's basically just like
the back half of a dragon dragons
but yeah i got terrible ones so
yeah cool is a grave on wheels
this is what you get for being
a smart ass your job oh my
god you really dig it a lot
of bad ones your job is gym
sweat wiper jesus what is helping your
salary is one hundred million dollars oh
i'll take it all away for you
mr modi gonna say since you always
think that enough money can buy happiness
i'm probably happy and that's ok
stephanie is a good woman we'll be
happy together in your shoutout your dragons
ass driving your brave on wheels your
job as a sweat wiper and shit
rave on wheels sure actually that was
something you said i forgot oh yeah
don't forget you add in one of
your own for each when you can
put them in different orders just so
it kind of like miss mixes it
do you mean a hearse what do
you
talking like i mean like i don't
know i drew but i drew a
grave on my paper
i thought that's really brave on wheels
at first i thought he's a grave
on wheels like that it was a
thing like you're writing a tombstone on
wheels plans under storerooms okay so what
are my things give me so much
um spouse domhnall gleeson oh he's cool
yeah um jerry
amy pippin was god because f real
yeah she's got to put it at
norton
jeremy and then you can add in
somebody already did okay
and then my pets um i want
a teacup kitten cup kit i want
regular kid elena mountie poo
i want a lab or doodle
you have one calendar you want one
oh you have you have a labradoodle
okay and then make up every cool
than my vehicle alone you're making mine
up yeah i did my vehicle i
would like a range rover oh and
ah cool stretch limo and ah
stretch hum are you driving it are
you a chauffeur driven whoa but in
the rainbow right drive it
oh
and then you make it up and
then what did you put the made
up one on every on the same
line no i mix it up you
make smoke so i'm also mixing in
some variety yeah yeah say except for
me no you just happen to get
all the bad ones i'm not kidding
i wasn't even paying attention to what
you were getting i just circling it
was fun though
um and that really good half game
job job um um tv show runner
um famous stand-up comedian wow are you
coming up with these ah um i'm
just looking at the people in the
room now look at kev
even
professional um um
professional um ah basketball player whoa in
the wwe nba yeah hope you guys
got realistic goals i would never expect
to them yet and then um you
get one and then salary
thirty five k
um um a million dollars um one
billion dollars whoa that would be fucking
cool tip oh and then you made
up one yeah okay and then you
draw a little dashes until i tell
you to stop stop
he just speeds it up if there
are less dash so it's i read
the second line no no no what
you do is more of a math
to it you go one two or
you know how many dashes are on
the how many and on two okay
so you are one to cross the
second one one two oh it's crossing
circling and then you keep going into
there's only one in each category and
you circle that one on the new
whoa this is craig
crazy i know this is fucking nuts
what's i know right crazy i'm i'm
really excited my future i feel pretty
hopeful a lot of good opportunity feels
weird to play this game now that
our futures are sort of set you
know can happen i know i know
you could still get one hundred million
dollars and live in
shack with stephanie
what would have to happen in order
for that to happen i feel like
ah first of all er so you
have to both get divorced or something
worse yes even say right and then
okay you're writing yeah oh you already
have him i think like what is
the what is the conversation that's definitely
i would need to have in order
to let you know with a friend
you both go look i just need
to figure this out i gotta live
somewhere i had you know i don't
wanna be alone right ah you're established
let's just do maybe they die or
you know maybe something happened to them
at the same time or love with
each other yeah and then you were
like why don't we just do this
just really stick it in your face
it's okay alright you ready yeah your
spouse is of course michael jackson wait
what yeah where do we live where
do they live oh the man we
didn't do that i'll go right m
a s h the topic a little
bit but we didn't you never saw
south the a o m a s
h is mansion apartment show
south bay cross also age crossbow crossbow
pass the mansion i live in a
marriage okay it's my pastor with your
liver like darling he's a lot of
space to go off and do his
own thing i respect yes yes his
needs i don't know what's happening your
best life your new michael jackson live
with a teacup kitten oh you drive
around an array
range rover this is good to your
job as a tv show runner oh
my god you make annually one dollar
i need money i have my eyes
on michael jack money yeah sure i
volunteer enjoy it i really wait what
was mother one that's it that's it
i wonder if you would be happy
um i think i want i really
happy in my situation i don't know
about you i definitely wouldn't because i
would i think michael jackson is a
vile person
i just think it's disgust you want
to know the native ones you missed
out on yeah oh yeah you guys
wanna know your your pit was not
a roach
i got all my shitty was no
your car was not a bird scooter
ah your job
pp lady
and that's it that was the vp
leading got a dollar a year um
yours so you think marry michael jackson
you didn't get to have a giraffe
on a leash oh you didn't get
to um drive a trike you didn't
get or you did get to be
the subway bagger and you didn't get
the salary of three dollars
your set you got everything bad i've
seen except for the salary yeah what
was this that's actually perfect for you
you could've gotten zero dollars a year
oh man imagine if i had all
that stuff is that even a salary
like could you agree to that you
would have to you'd have to read
a one thing to pay you zero
dollars a year i think three dollars
a year and you will be taxed
on here
well that was a lot of fun
it was fun it was fun i
remember playing that when i was a
kid and just dreaming about being in
a mansion or something like that and
then designing the mansion and saying like
oh it's going to have a trampoline
like slide and scott are you going
to tell us who your horns are
off mike i told you i'm on
yahoo i'm horny for i told mine
come on you're it's not embarrassing
it's great oh no it's a little
embarrassing minor grade
yeah no minor great i'm not embarrassed
in mind of who you're horny with
i'm not i'm not embarrassed of who
i'm warning with yeah honey with them
by the way they have no stake
in the data but there there are
learning with rosamund pike they're feeling warning
right now but they don't know why
that's the power of my audience
alright guys that was fun time lita
fun we're gonna i mean you know
we're going to do another episode next
week but as you know as far
as our taping we're not seeing lauren
for quite a bit of time so
let's say goodbye to my guys nah
nah nah nah nah nah hey
a good ah nah nah nah nah
nah nah hey goodbye
nah we hope nah we come back
but if you don't yeah we hope
you do if you don't who do
you want us to replace us damn
bryan safi
yeah i can see that i'd be
on absolutely shit energy why don't we
just do the next episode should start
with
oh we should do one while she's
gone no okay you can alright we'll
see you next time bye
ugh