three
oh um is the name of the
show and welcome to it my name
is lauren lab guess my name's paul
f tompkins y'all know me still the
same oh gee oh yeah
u c o g p u that
song because i'm scott ackerman hello freaking
sulked
it's freaking socks
hey guys dad freaking socks who's got
a topic who's good i got a
topic i got a topic to topic
i wanna bring this up oh shit
okay well we're reporting on zoom we're
recording huns and now i'm not i've
not looked at instagram cool up is
mentioned something to me
now that you're commenting on posts or
something i don't know ah i don't
know i don't know
so we're recording on zoom because of
the heat
we were in my backyard for many
of these episodes throughout this pandemic i
receive about one all but when i
received my first noise complaint from a
neighbor the other day and was it
wait was it the neighbors that play
the music's allow no it was not
the day they play the music way
loud they play what did you do
during an ep
isolde we've heard them playing their music
super loud yes we have listened to
this i was aghast i was by
the pool i was swimming and i
turned on the music this is a
sunday at noon
a sunday at noon to receive a
noise complaint from annoying my children sleep
i have never never heard the like
and he he peered over the fence
and he whistled at me and noxious
whistle oh and he was like hey
you you wanna turn that music down
and i was i couldn't believe what
i was hearing
hey god i couldn't believe it wack
i could not believe what i was
seeing that is our research and so
i think my face betrayed just how
dumbstruck i was what was happening and
he was like did you hear me
oh can you imagine honestly sunday and
will it is rose
and deal i want to know what
social security i know what these what
the status is here what's his mother's
maiden name
is his first pet's name um now
to be to be fair we this
was maybe the third day in the
row that we had music on and
were swimming but still on a sunday
the weekend i just think we're trying
to listen to a song called i
hate my neighbor if it's
middle of the day on a sunday
it's like who gives a shit there's
not much you can do i mean
and like i say our other neighbors
son that they're right next door to
as well blast blast blast it did
the house that's blasting when we've recorded
is pretty far away yeah there there
directly next door to them but
but i'm even further but this guy
was like really into it so i
haven't this is my first noise complaint
i've received in years and hours this
year i want i want i want
some details he's probably i'm guessing between
three and eighty nine wow and that's
a guess as it gets okay so
i'm not so
he could be to be could be
nine my question is more around your
age ah probably not he's probably younger
it's just very fucking ballsy bowles screams
very aggressive it's bolted to peek over
offense to whistle at some to whistle
at someone and then to do it
aggressively yeah
and then read the wolf whistle and
then rather than say could you turn
that down to say you want to
turn that down yeah like it like
he's your dad or sansa yeah no
i don't fuck off and then and
then when i when i did it
any i still hadn't given him a
verbal yes he was like did you
hear me and i said yes okay
a yes sir sorry sir really bothers
me i remember there was one hundred
times i'm sorry laura what have you
just sunk under the water
he slowly dropped it i do have
to say i'm talking to the gardener
tomorrow and up go the trees because
this cannot happen again yay yeah nineteen
countries were planting sturdy machines and sort
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i
remember my first department in la i
was hammering into the wall to hang
up a fucking litter
all piece of art
trying to have some tiny comfort in
my miserable existence
and i think my girls i feel
like i probably hit the hammer four
times and dom not hard to do
don't like banging back from the other
side oh and then i did it
again because it wasn't done like and
he did it again and then i
i look
looked through the peephole and he had
opened his door to like in r
and r i mean yeah our walls
connected in our doors were next each
other i was so scared oh yeah
yeah you don't know yeah and what
was this at noon on a sunday
and it was the middle of the
day i'm like i'm on sunday though
and i don't know if it was
a sunday because he certainly wasn't working
from home let's be clear
i was like it was like you
you have to allow people to make
a dot of noise before you get
mad like i had barely done any
somebody doctor in an apartment building you're
gonna hear shit i mean like i
don't remember ever complaining that's the thing
if you you always buy whatever place
you buy or you rent whatever place
you rent and you have to take
it
to account like okay well there's going
to be i happen to live next
door to people i'm gonna hear some
stuff sometimes you know we live in
a society do you have any joker
or oh that's what that's right this
mean i don't know what that is
thank you society i um um oh
wait i have a story oh okay
thank you tata i was in i
was in new york i was perform
aiming at the bell house after the
show someone gave me some ah fan
art and it was a portrait of
myself like paint like it was it
was you know on a canvas and
it's like a little a little painting
and so i was staying at the
type that lorne would put up on
a wall i might yeah a little
tiny piece of art i might hammer
her it up into the wall yeah
and i was staying at my friend
john hodgkins ah he has an office
um that has a sofa bed so
i was staying there um and i
was you know coming home very late
and i was ff
for sure drunk um i'd drink after
the show and you know it's new
york so it's like i'm getting in
it like you know three four am
something like that sure i'll still legal
and aboveboard yes and i think this
will be funny
i will
i will hang this painting in john's
office and ah rather than like take
an existing thing down from the wall
and put this in it's place i
found a new case hammer and the
nail
because he had he had a lot
of stuff that he had yet to
hang on the walls and so he
had like the hanging tools out right
and i was like this will be
funny and so i ah bang bang
bang because the hammer however the snail
then there is a a response bang
bang bang from the person that i
had
i very definitely woken up in the
middle of the night who was on
the other side of the wall um
and i felt bad about that at
the time and then the next day
i felt bad that i'd put a
whole johnson on and did you hang
it up yeah of course i did
and didn't like it um i think
he i think he was very good
natured about and he thought
it was funny he conceded that it
was funny i he never betrayed that
he was upset that i fuckin put
all
oof it was a good spot though
you can hang something there very easily
yeah had one should keep it what's
so what are the worst like neighbors
with adjoining walls that you've ever had
i can remember one one we had
i was living with a girlfriend and
she
unfortunately gave this older woman who lived
underneath us her phone number which is
a big mistake because the old lady
very nicely was like oh hey what's
your phone number in case i ever
need to get a hold of you
to like you know some guys yeah
and it turned into a like if
we eh
ever we're just talking at ten thirty
at night we would get a call
and she'd be like what do you
guys do when there are vampires oh
my god you gotta block that
this is before color ideally no idea
yeah it was
so so there's that but then i
was in a condo with with cool
up and i had heard a conga
line with cousin in did that the
dead dad zipped up the attack that
does anybody find out who knew did
you do do do condo with cu
lao di di di di doo doo
bibi bibi and we had a hopeful
boy
years later probable law are you billy
crystal's jazz girl boo boo boo i
do think you could do it um
but we had an upstairs neighbor who
was like eighty and it was a
dream because she turned she had to
turn her tv up so loud to
hear it but i don't give a
shit because then i'm like oh i
can turn on my tv i can
turn my music whatever and
she could never hear anything we were
doing it was i could say hey
you old lady
the top of my lungs well i
i was thinking about um i mean
i've definitely had a lot of bad
neighbors and i'm sure i told the
story of when i thought with my
neighbor about the trash can yes um
that was pretty intense but did you
get a trading card from him too
or it was a woman and oh
someone with a trash can was a
woman there's egg on my face and
you did it i was just remembering
this story from i don't know if
i've ever told you this so when
i was living in chicago in an
apartment um i had to harness me
to pay me and i was it
was a third floor um apartment cope
walk up and we always were coming
going and so we left our apartment
door unlocked all the time not that
there are two doors to get into
the building and then we would just
leave our door open because we always
were there when people come and go
and people coming over whatever and there
was only one other apartment on the
floor so it felt like no real
risk
and one day i was not there
but
my friend my one roommate had a
guy friend who was visiting and he
was sleeping in her room in the
bed she was at work and my
other friend was um not home i
think it was just that guy was
just there but we left the door
unlocked and that's not that's it we
all did that so whatever he's people
broke into the apartment building walked right
into our apartment and took
my roommate's laptop and mine was right
next to it they didn't take mine
i think they were running out out
by then and then they the guy
woke up and he like heard the
music kind of yelling but he was
like really small guy like there was
a kind of know you know it
was just like a crazy sort of
moment he was gonna do something and
then he chased after them a little
bit but they ran back down they
ran through the whole apart
and down the back stairs and ran
away and then that night they came
back later whoa because it was mocked
or yeah they tried again so we
we were scared it was stupid we
were scared after that happened so we
had a bunch of friends over and
we were all sitting in and they
started jostling the back door and then
two
guys ran out after them and tried
to get them and um they just
gotta shake hard but they also stole
our um bbq gas tank or whatever
wow and we're sitting on the front
stoop with it like just waiting for
their ride and someone had seen that
yeah
it's crazy wow i had people ah
well i think i told you about
when someone stole like five hundred dvds
out of my condo and no i
don't get no oh yeah i just
i was gone live in a blockbuster
why did you have five hundred eighty
how did you have now i don't
know but wow so how's the same
ca
rondo i'm curious i don't know i
have thousands i don't know you haven't
been back to make sure you do
this to me the number s too
but you have
ah which to legally blind but i
think that's the best but you have
legally blind and you have what else
made zone so i was gone for
one hour getting lunch when i walked
away are you mad that i'm asking
you this because i just don't know
i don't i mean
i literally don't know i couldn't even
estimate okay fine fine five hundred i
don't know okay so you replaced all
five hundred sure huh i like to
keep it at five
okay so it was gone for one
hour and when i walked back into
my place i sat down with my
my lunch that i gotten and i
looked at at at the time like
my entertainment system had shelving around it
and that's where they all were i
looked there and they were empty it
was like my god what what has
happened in and so cool up i
told cool up about it because she
came home and she went to my
neighbor ah the crazy one who i
think i mentioned who had half of
her brain removed who would just walk
into my place sometimes go huh where
you half my brain is gone do
you want to hit have you seen
it
i learned and so cool op goes
to her place and says um hey
someone stole like five hundred dvds out
of our place and the woman says
well they're not at my place do
you want to look in here they're
not here you can look if you
want
oh
so we think it's her
ah wow it remains an open case
i don't even think she would ever
even sell them or whatever we went
to amoeba and said hey if anyone
brings these in you know they're they're
hot
but um did i ever tell you
about i think she just threw him
away because she's had them part of
his one red shoe he had a
he had a brain and a brain
injury that injury or injury and he
would walk around downtown evanston um assess
what does the word for singing you
know tell talking about
something like i wanna say the word
is not espousing what is the word
like espousing yes that what i mean
yeah them will keep going and let's
see
talking shit talking about how people need
to wear a helmet when they ride
their bike because he had this accident
oh yeah
he had a helmet that he he
would wear what he would just walk
around and he would come up to
me and my friends and i always
would go shopping when i was in
like fifth grade we can't be sure
babies um with by two friends and
he would say three musketeers who'd yelled
us from down the street three musketeers
three musketeers that he'd started and we'd
go like oh no and like
we have taught us got real good
guys get two yours
and then he would come up to
us and be like were you carrying
swords yeah and we had our stupid
feathers in our cabs and he would
always
he would always go on and on
about how you have to wear a
helmet but you could never get away
and we were like ten so you
didn't really really know how to you
know and he would just ah tell
you that you have to wear a
helmet because he think he would tell
his whole accident everything that happened was
kinda living he said and he would
just walk around and tell people about
that oh that's sad that's very soon
but he probably helped a lot of
people
i mean i never forgot helmet awareness
probably was not you know that widespread
back then right and i didn't want
to wear one because i thought it
wasn't cool yeah i mean that's the
prob do you know i didn't like
wearing a bike i did not like
wearing a bike helmet for the longest
i still don't like it but i
didn't wear a bike helmet for the
longest time um until
bill and i may have told you
this before until janie and i's relationship
got serious and then i realized oh
someone else cares yeah to protect your
head hey yeah if my if my
head is cracked open on the sidewalk
oh my god i started wearing a
helmet i know i i never i
and i never looked back after that
i always wear a helmet
what does you tell the story about
you driving not driving riding your bike
on the sidewalk was it do you
remember the story i think about it
someday yes yes i if i think
i know that when you're talking about
i was riding my bike ah near
i think i'm on my way to
u c b or something like it
was nelson's eye
i imagine it in front of nelson's
its nose before i got to gelson
okay but it is on that same
street i was riding on ah franklin
and i was riding past the swords
moving back from the microphone like she
will just go on interrupting i'm not
interrupting
she's just in awe of the story
like a pall on a bike i
got to sit back for this one
i'm just letting it be told very
briefly to my goddamn life
do you think the musketeers do you
think they were bummed out by their
dumb hats or do you think they
were proud of them the actual people
yes huh i think they are proud
of them that seems probably very probably
in fashion at the time so things
like check these out and and it
was very like eye catching and it
was it was elaborate on fathering them
yeah
and they're and they're super memorable yeah
yeah we're like geisler it's like scott's
leather cap yeah
maybe i'll bring back the musketeer hat
it's it is weird when things that
would be super come back into fashion
like platform shoes i did except so
much yeah like everything nineties is back
but like what about eighteen nineties yeah
oh wow so i'm running my bike
and i
i all of a sudden this
person
jump steps out in front of me
from an apartment building with their dog
who is not release oh and i
skid like a slam on my brakes
my kid and i keep going and
ah this person yells at me it's
illegal to ride your bike on the
sidewalk
and i fucking stopped and turned around
i said it's illegal to have your
dog off the leash nice and then
she said oh wait are you pull
off tom
ah and i said yes and she
said i'm a big fan and i
said well thank you very much my
nice shares oh my god it was
great because we were both wrong
that's so crazy the other day when
we were we will guess it was
a few weeks ago we were recording
at scott's and then i drove home
and this dog i was going to
turn left know that was going to
turn left um and there was a
green arrow left and it took me
w one second to hit the gas
like one second you know what i
mean like right yeah and they say
a new york minute and the guy
behind me
like ne and then i immediately gave
him the finger because i i have
reflexes you know yeah and then and
then i was like damn
ex because i'm a human because i'm
fast i mean it's just like i'm
going you fucking asshole yeah my god
and like i turn and then he's
on my ass and then he he's
coming up behind me going oh shit
and then he pulls up next to
me at a stoplight and and and
there's plenty of room for him to
go forward but he stops next
my car and he stared at me
who isn't a big truck and he
he just was like i didn't i
didn't even glance at him he was
a jago pickup truck not the best
trucker i just i just stared straight
ahead kind of like smiling
it's the best thing you could do
i mean and you know easy wearing
out easy yes staring at me and
then he eventually drove off and then
i just had to kind of like
hide behind other cars until he was
like really far away and then i
kept going because i was like at
a certain point i might get you
know my ass beat yeah we will
we once when i worked at the
los angeles times sewing tell em
marketing selling the paper over the phone
it's gonna say um some real market
journalist seems a little nose at the
times
gangs in the sheriff's department
um i was seventeen i was still
in high school so my friends it
was a very good year we would
we would all drive to my door
ignored we would always drive to my
friend's houses they live in tea and
we would drive to my friend's house
and then you would drive to the
law it was yeah wow oh yeah
what did you say
i couldn't hear you
oh yeah
we were a carpool in other words
much like the recent carpool karaoke series
which has delighted america and beyond
ronin ceo james corden was before the
late show yeah what's your question okay
did you know who he was before
you yeah i did from the ah
the tv show gavin and stacey which
i highly recommend into the thought i
thought it was really i didn't know
who he was and i was like
oh cool they kind of picked someone
i don't know who they are but
i guess it was fame but it
wasn't cool
yeah i guess just because i didn't
know who he was doesn't mean he
was like you know an up and
comer right it's nice to personalize like
that oh it's cool to pick someone
that i don't know who it is
so we we used to carpool to
the la times and my friend um
was driving my friend this is my
friend who wanted the rocky horror picture
show's okay wow that guy he's still
your friend we this was before the
rocky horror show right yard it was
honestly rude so he was it was
his turn to drive that day so
we get
into his car and he cut someone
off and the guy beeps really loud
and the dumb and he flips him
off out the window the guy follows
us for a half an hour all
the way to the los angeles times
and then like pulls into the parking
lot where we work and gets out
and confronts my friend
and my friend backed off so hard
he's like oh no i was taking
out a cigarette and just it was
the cigarette was a cigarette that you
saw
these are flesh colored cigarettes
they're very special important it's like oh
no no i was merely ended it
wears out a cigarette and the guy's
like oh yeah well you better watch
yourself pal
and then drove i drove away i
mean this is the thing i feel
like i throw the finger out pretty
pretty readily but i i know it's
bad so i really i don't want
to do it it's just so easy
people are so fucking annoying i know
people who do really dangerous there's been
you're like they could get more didn't
know i've i've had like guns pulled
on me and shit while driving in
the oh yeah yeah really was
but yeah like like a dude just
i remember i was downtown and a
guy and i know like fucking restaurant
stories we had to sit through just
to get to the gun stories because
that is part of my like my
freak out daydream after i do it
is oh they're gonna put next to
me and put a gun up yeah
yeah that's happened to me where a
guy like just tapped on the window
with a gun in like
it showed it and i was like
i just like ran through the red
light and got jesus like this was
an attempted carjacking no well no it
was someone that i cut off in
traffic or whatever and they were trying
to say and they wanted to jack
your car know as a reprisal he
just wanted to show you he has
again has a gun and could you
know like don't do anything or
whatever but yeah don't ever coach like
good there's fucking crazy people out there
so you gotta keep cool on the
road and it's hard too because i
haven't had a bear i've barely driven
in a whole year but five minutes
on the road i was like going
fuck you screaming go
but i mean for the most part
i think i i used to have
way worse road rage and i feel
like now i'm i'll just kind of
casually flip people off but beyond that
i like take it pretty slow and
like let people in and like i'm
not i really don't i think that's
the problem with road rages like you're
you are so polite and you let
people in and to see someone who's
nah
not polite yeah it enrages you yeah
it does therapists i
i had a guy once um can
i be your therapist i really do
want to take a lot of secrets
like how much do you pay your
therapist radio because really for i'll do
it for half and know how much
i pay because i feel people go
nuts and sign you will get to
know people are free it's not working
yeah you're getting ripped off your nuts
um i once had a guy i
was coming up to a yellow light
and it fell on the line to
me and i didn't want to like
accelerate to go through it so you
see stopped so stopped like ripe and
nadia know you can't be mad at
someone for that week we probably could
have both may
made it through this yellow if we
if we split up but you're being
was like well i'm not gonna you
know i'm i'm not in a rush
you know so i slept so as
i slowed down it turned red and
then the guy behind me guy behind
me like threw up his hands in
like ah why like yeah like i
was being ridiculous so i just did
it back to
in the car i don't like mocking
him like ooh
and then what do you do he
didn't do it i then i didn't
look i cause i can't ever look
again i looked for i assess i
felt like assess the situation like now
this guy's like me he's going to
do anything yeah to i was one
stone up their hands please
do you know that intersection on it
on um griffith park i know every
intersection los angeles go okay yeah me
i used to live in challenging on
griffith park ripe for the five griffith
park and i'm gonna look it up
whatever side not written before riverside before
you get to riverside but um i'm
gonna look it up na ho um
but
but ah it's ah it's griffith park
blvd and ah most viewers else feels
okay so firstly in greenwood there's a
red light that it says no turn
on red light no right turn on
red light and it's one of the
only ones in los angeles so much
church bells going off yeah
yeah that's my i haven't church this
guy comes over on offense on a
sunday um that is my i have
a wind chime outside my wildflower wind
chime wonderful i love dramas well that's
replacing the bird sounds from my backyard
your wind chime right
chimes you know it's a specific thing
you gotta get just the right one
you gotta love wins and yeah very
true i got i got this is
like a ah it's a sort of
nautical one so it's like a ship's
bell sounds kind of like um yeah
i really it's very i get why
like as i'm getting old
ldr
it's very tempting to buy a bunch
of shit like that for your house
and i get how it happens now
too like there's a house in your
neighborhood where there's people have like just
plants and shit all over the place
like i understand it now and the
temptation is you have to resist you
must present yeah edit
and you must edit you might actually
on a hunt for some good garden
gnomes hunt
so okay so i met this red
light and i'm with cool op and
miles want to get into what constitutes
a good garden gnome but go ahead
yeah but i only found one so
far and we're at where the where
we're at the we're the first how
do you say this year were the
first digitas people yes the first indigenous
people know were the first
people at this life and so there's
no one in front of this the
light yes so but it's big giant
sign that says no no red turn
no turn on red guy behind us
starts laying on his horn trying to
get us to go and we are
pointing at the sign we're like reaching
out our fingers and pointing at the
sign
and guys still laying on it finally
he gets out and comes over and
goes hey mother fucker you better get
the fuck out of my way we're
like we can't turn it's illegal he's
like if you better get the fuck
out of my way because i've a
gun and i'm gonna shoot you dead
right now if you don't get the
fuck out of my way and his
girlfriend is there and we're like whoa
will do
a shooter no one way she goes
yeah p says shit yeah
wow that's crazy were you really scared
so we just like my my friend
just terrified pulled over to the right
a little bit and the guy just
like screeched around him and went through
the red light and what you could
have done anyway if you want to
do yeah i mean i'm just saying
yeah we had this happen recently where
there was this um
like a weird shit it's a weird
lie yeah like he says shit that
you blew a bubble she was wearing
like a crop top too and she
was kinda overweight and it was just
assumed
there's this light where it's like the
oncoming traffic um has a red on
trough even though the the oncoming traffic
from the other side like it's like
you know just a two way thing
basically from my side it's green and
from their side it's red and i
don't i can't yeah is it hot
hollywood and ah no okay good but
but so my point is that i
i'm going to turn left on my
green or might make an i are
gonna turn left and we pull into
the intersection and this woman is good
trying to turn as well but she
doesn't do anything and we're going go
coo coo
so shit and then i have gone
and then like minutes you know or
seconds into it we realized oh no
she has a red light because she's
going wow you're just screaming at her
to go we actually had the right
of way and it was um just
do did you say sorry or you're
like us
i'm just getting the cigarette out i
hate when if i'm making a left-turn
somewhere and i'm in i'm in i'm
the the lead car right yeah and
you're in pole position that's what i'm
a politician and if i can see
something that's coming up and i stopped
for it like there's another car coming
ups exactly in the fucking
person behind me as i go go
go and it's like do you why
would i just stop why would i
go and then just stop for no
reason in the middle of fucking street
i definitely had a ramp and like
i've gotten mad lets person not going
and then i realized there's like a
little old lady cross industry yeah yes
little lady who is crossing the street
little lady
lily lily oil cream that person run
them over oh shoo it out there
on the road because it's like we're
all trying our best words of wisdom
scottie we all got a cool it
out there on the road and written
when you think about it like yes
i used to be really mad on
the road when i was getting to
a job that would
if i was ever clocking in late
they would you know like fire me
or whatever your pit or fire you
dock my pay whatever but now really
who gives a shit if we're ever
late to anywhere we ever go to
you know like the percentage of people
out there on the road or are
really needs are late who need to
get there or even yeah i figured
delay it's like you
yeah everyone's late but basically you know
what i mean where like it's just
yeah just seconds is going to matter
i know you know i mean you
know everyone's late to everything out here
let's get into the gnomes oh yeah
okay make should we take let's take
a break and we'll get into the
o teaser yeah it's come back no
talk long
you won't want to stop listening we'll
be right back
and we're back so no talk so
i'm on the hunt reviews freedom highway
to get it
i like to have a few gnomes
okay sure ideally as we as i've
mentioned multiple times i thought trolls world
tour was like the funniest movie i
was like wow this has become my
loves running high i would like to
have a couple gnomes that are not
i know that's not what a troll
is but i don't want you
yes as close as you can get
okay yeah i also thought the gnomes
trailer was pretty funny um okay what
about knowing your juliet yeah was that
another one yeah yeah it wasn't but
i thought that was funny too okay
so
if i know me if i know
if i know y'all know me still
sanji oh my god so i want
to hunt for new names but you
know it's really hard to find because
there's a lot of very quote unquote
funny gnomes oh are they doing that's
gilding the lily it's a ha cli
there and they're really over the top
i mean there's like a gnome on
a cell phone yeah oh no i'm
on a surfboard and there's a gnome
like mooning you and it's like oh
on yes a gnome would do that
if they were real i mean they
were real they do it all the
time but it is funny but do
i want to see it every day
no no so obviously every other areas
i found you need a terp for
this rooms please put every
other day i got one gnome so
far i'm i'm taking it slow i
don't want to just buy whatever i
see now how big is this gnome
this one is small it's all it's
little but it's only ahead little for
a gnome but big for a penis
ah it's ah wait it's only a
heady seven inches tall you've got judging
by
savage dick and
it's um i know my seven inch
dicks that's existed seventy five so you
know it's all like a smurfs or
three applesauce yeah a nomad is the
seven inch dick like it's like it's
exactly an inches it's just you have
to say dick so um the its
i'm target and it was only ten
dollars and the alumnos early price which
i want to say a lot of
gnomes are coming in at thirty to
sixty dollars i'm just going it's it's
so gnome i don't know how i
feel about this why why was this
just why is it just so damn
is that why it's only ten dollars
in aesthetic
yeah didn't spring for the body so
do you have a saw here it's
a white ceramic gnome face and it's
like all white with like a beard
and then it has a bronze cone
hat that is really ninety percent of
it huh and i think it's very
funny now that's funny because it's just
charming it's charming oh here
i'll try to find you a picture
i want to see a picture yeah
yeah i wanna see picture of this
gnome before i decide if it's funny
okay
target gnome hold on are half way
there got it right now okay no
no that was an exciting movie
will smith oh no can't make will
patton it's really a nose and cared
and a hat
haha a minute is it even a
humanoid thing season painted her and it
looks like a little hamster or something
with a hat on
harry do you know what a gnome
is oops
a lot of smaller looks send this
to paul because he's got to play
past thirty days a week
does it have eyes no that's what's
funny why does funny i don't understand
you got ripped off and you're too
proud to admit guys it's literally seven
inches long
whoa
ah now i like the fact that
you're so diluted that you like it
i think you think you're really fucking
matters i like it because i like
it because it's like you don't really
know what it is and then if
you if you look a little yeah
don't i still don't oh my fucking
i mean yeah it's a that's a
weird way why are you so zed
well i mean i liked that you're
not just getting regular old gnomes and
putting them out on your lawn like
a weirdo but this one rep i
would say this is representation it's more
abstract when you say it's abstract it's
adaption that's and that's what i find
humorous about it and i think too
slow because it's because it's it is
funny it is god you're not fucking
cracking
at this comparison here's what i'm gonna
do i'm gonna put it on the
cool i'm gonna put a scenario to
texas to our tex chain of other
people and see if anyone clicks on
and says haha no one's sick like
it's ah haha just from me linking
to it well that's what i mean
is is like a lot of times
on this text chain people will send
pictures and
everyone go haha that's funny or a
headline or something like that if anyone
could tell me this right now yeah
yeah you say so funny just from
looking at it lauren you maintain this
is hilarious i'd like to see how
normal people re if it gets one
haha and you can't tell mike to
do it
ah then we'll say it's funny but
if if more likely than not people
will do the question mark and this
is exciting
quest
i mean i'm embarrassed i just texted
okay she's done it she's we'll see
by the end of the show we'll
see if anyone oh wait you do
oh i didn't do it paul yeah
instantly ruined the expert huh i'll remove
my haha okay remove your ha ha
thank you okay so the has gone
we'll see if any of the other
people to play with haha and while
laura tracking this throughout yeah wasn't haha
tracker
lauren has said react honestly
ah
and then she says she's trying to
ruin this she says this is a
three-time test enough qualifiers but just want
to see if it i use but
see i could be against it they
don't know where i stand true that's
true i think we're gonna get lots
of real just saying like why what
is it now instead of just a
true just like how would people really
wonder
boy don't write anything to that because
it's because it's not funny but it's
not funny in that way it's funny
in a way where you if you
picture in your yard you kind of
go that's funny well it's not you
just sending us this picture will let
me but now how is it displayed
in your yard you just sit it
on the grass well that's do i'm
gonna i'm i'm
not sure yeah we've received something from
janie okay judy says my review is
just you ah so what i'm looking
for
ah okay we've got some more oh
lorin just as l o l it
looks like three different things things all
lewd it is
she's very dirty my wife okay
again maybe that's maybe that's funny i
mean that's not why why like looks
like an upside down of vanilla ice
cream cone with a chocolate or caramel
sort i want to put it kind
of dress i want to blend it
into some foliage okay it's not a
main piece it's a sort of decide
you're you're looking around and you come
across it and it's like oh there's
no oh well i'm gonna get some
more traditional gnomes as well but i
what what drew you to gnomes over
one other controls world i want some
funny um long stuff i think it's
fun
you want to have a lone bellow
magical i want magical not funny necessarily
but i want the feeling of whimsical
imsi yes ah do yoon and whimsy
do you do you want other people
to see this or is this just
for you know it's just it's for
me and if you know someone comes
over and they look around sure i
i'm i'm i'm happy
you know i like wonder like him
over do they normally look around yeah
you know what i like um little
fairy houses when people build those into
the trees when they put like a
door on this tree and oh and
do you remember my god that was
my role very the viral fairy whoa
i love so much and i would
like to have one of those on
a tree like i would like to
things like that i think that's so
q to miserable did pippi longstocking have
a tree like ah ah a hiding
space in a tree what am i
lacking common into your world what i
don't want that that's what it is
i feel like there there was a
book i read as a kid with
a female protagonist who
i had a secret hiding place in
the nod of a tree although am
i thinking of to kill a mockingbird
i think that's what you're thinking of
okay i wanted i read your logs
to be like talking about a singer
in the back of my head
that makes sense what what i was
saying or what she was saying because
talking at the same time yeah it
was great i could tune out completely
i put anger through my hair and
i made the wired braids yes that's
the way to do it it's not
changing i've there i feel like pippi
longstocking had a thing with a tree
e but i don't know what it
was like a secret headquarters in a
tree and there also by the way
there was a book series i read
about people investing about kids investigating crimes
and they had a secret layer underneath
a junkyard that was considered hide out
that fascinated me and i i tried
to replicate it once when my dad
dug up a tree in our front
yard and we did a secret fort
underneath in the big hole in the
ground with like a plank of wood
and put dirt over it and then
surprise people who would come by by
jumping out of it so i've always
if you know what those books are
please let ah the freedom usa instagram
now can i ask something
yeah what is the way i give
my permission yes
thank you what is something you guys
have bought recently and it doesn't have
to be as you know suppl rising
as my fuckin kinsey groceries
yeah this is an episode of add
to cart slash groceries
but it's good you think you'll ever
go on add to cart i've never
been invited so no probably not so
what have you bought
ah well i mean i pad you've
been getting forever you don't count yeah
i know let's see i pre-ordered ah
prince's new record
new record
i gonna need more info on how
that came about his his new record
or how did you if you heard
some news about prints recently that we
haven't heard he he shelved an album
ah um and ah is put and
and so you know his somebody else
said
we could make money off of this
yeah well the heirs to say he
didn't want out there no he ah
there's discussion about this he apparently knew
when he died all this stuff would
come out and he's fine with it
and then other people think well no
he didn't want any of it to
come out but his state feels that
he wanted all of this to come
out and so they're they're putting it
out but but as he put this
in
in writing anywhere
i know he had no will he
had no winner that's a big problem
that's why we all can lay claim
to anything of his yes
that's why we get all of his
records for free now how did attend
know my friend hey by the way
jessica says oh so jessica's weight in
she says i don't mind it thank
you but she doesn't think it's funny
that's what we're testing so far no
one has said huh
i'm not worried so prince
they're they're putting out this unreleased record
but the the reason i i preordered
it is because if you buy the
super deluxe version it includes a blu
ray or dvd i'm not sure of
paul and i went to see him
from those shows not the specific show
that wow but that that series he
did twenty one nights
here in l a and yeah and
this was one i did not see
in person so um who was the
special guest tonight we were there was
it i mean normally it was like
she li or the time or sometimes
no but there was i feel like
there was always like an extraneous celebrity
who would show up and get on
stage for two centers dance during the
yeah sometimes it was going to
funny sometimes it was i don't remember
i think kim kardashian was there once
yeah yeah dance and then everybody who
got friends was like or whatever yeah
but it's like everyone would make her
endure you to not shimmy say like
get the fuck off my stage if
you're not gonna dance or something like
that yeah yeah i bet she can't
dance or that people will make fun
of her i think that if she
ev
ever was even stand up that ass
would just pull her down to the
ground oh my god okay so janey
said like i said looks like three
different things to me with a lat
crying laughing emoji which could imply she
finds it funny no she finds herself
funny
can you okay let's weigh in and
say janey why are you laughing
what does this emoji mean
um i keep the prince didn't have
a will show she says that rolled
in pubic hairs first and now she's
she's landed a job now i gotta
return it jessica yeah because jessica said
it looks like an ice-cream cone the
fell on the ground to me that's
janie added her filth tim just says
upside down cream cone check and is
that free
code hey you guys wanna go for
cream cones should i ask do any
of you find it funny
you're attaining the experiment janey says because
it looks like a vibrator she says
it's so sonically she is laughing because
she thinks it looks like a vibrator
so does that count that does i
think it's funny she was laughing because
she thinks you look like a vibrator
she's laughing because she pointed out that
it looks like yes i think she's
like i think she's laughing at her
own observation i don't think she's laughing
at the thing itself don't think it's
funny that it looks like a vibrator
i agree
i think it's tragic
i can't wait to display this i'm
gonna get ten it'll look like bowling
pins
tell john says i've expelled similar items
that's that's about right right yeah that's
yeah that's the tenor of his tits
nora just ignoring it nor do you
think she saw the phone
we've been we've done this text thread
for literal years now and there's one
person that just never ever ever died
and it's gotta be annoying because it's
a lot of texts oh yeah i
mean i will wake up and there
will be a hundred texts i silenced
that chain but i check it debate
check and you silence a chain this
is yeah you put an outbreak but
the change alert yeah and then you
check when i always check and it
just isn't fast one
a particular chain yeah holy shit swam
out around that shit okay this is
wow this is maybe franny haircut and
everyone thinks looks like shit
what did she supposed to look like
i mean it's i mean little i
think she looks good thanks hi frannie
my friend hey fran he's got a
haircut
my dog groomer was i called them
a month ago and i said can
i make an appointment for a dog
grooming and i said our next mobility
bay one and i said i'll go
somewhere else course it didn't find new
girls but i did mean i found
like a bunch of reviews for horrible
places that were like oh ones
a million one serve user like that
people post a picture of their dog
and it was like so fucked up
looking that you're like oh fuck did
this happen i have to wear did
you i want to sound so bad
the place please and then um then
i googled because i was like what
about like petco i can't just walk
into a pet co and do it
and then i googled that and
the first thing that came up was
about dogs that died at petco after
getting oh no are like petsmart petco
i think it's pet co after getting
groomed and dying those eight dogs die
after getting groomed at petco river like
jaw not going there but by the
way they're sponsoring us this week so
you can sleep anyway
how about pepe bleep bleep out pet
bib yeah hippo people people people people
sue bee baby se da baby boo
boo boo boo baby bb boo boo
booboo i do that that that that
big scar you're part of that show
right that where we did the the
dramatic readings of the one star reviews
of that gym
whoa i don't know it was wrong
time ago you cb tom lennon and
that myra i think put it together
somebody else who did not perform but
helped to put it together it was
there was some gym in l a
that had just hundreds of once refuse
and this place like you read the
reviews this place sounds disgusting and anyone
going into it we did a shows
like an hour long show where people
one by one got up and did
dramatic readings of these one star reviews
it was a really funny show wow
i gotta watch this oh no you
did already i thought you were any
wow i gotta watch i did i
did the night of one hundred and
forty tweets or whatever yes maybe you're
thinking of um it wasn't but thanks
oh no i mean when you think
of me being at oh i appreciate
it okay um if you're imagining me
in on stage was probably that night
of one hundred and twenty i'm imagining
you and you're wearing a suit of
armor no but with a football helmet
i'm like uncomfortable my chair
why get up dance around what's up
with your bomb in my lab david
bowie taught me it was cool to
be uncomfortable in your chair really yeah
alright
what did you buy recently oh no
you talked about your gnome how about
that's why i asked
i don't fucking know you know
whereas it isn't in here yeah she
just did like a doubletaker he's like
i don't know and then saw it
and went boy i remember oh bobby
that getting up and walking away probably
to retrieve the item
are you talking to me are you
talking to you
let this hat wo which is dirty
that's ah did not already have it
looks like a civil war hat it
is it's it from the union navy
it's a replica of ah reproduction of
a union navy hat that i came
across you know like it just got
stuck in my feed somehow right and
this is from thing
instagram ad knows from an instagram mattos
i was shopping for something else and
then this popped up some other kind
of hat or whatever and then for
some reason i got very paranoid
that it was a confederate right that
it was the on the wrong side
because i saw i saw an officer's
hat that had the same insignia and
i was like oh shit what the
fuck did i do right and so
i look i was like in bed
scrolling and searching and trying to find
like and then i finally
like fortune in bed
and then i finally was able to
confirm that it was the correct side
ah yeah you stamped it out that's
lucky paul do you think the stovepipe
will ever come back i hope so
i'd wear one i saw him a
young man smoking out of a um
but what kind of pipe is this
where it's like
ah like a mirror sham pipe like
sherlock holmes yes yeah i guess i'm
just strat stone i was like wait
you're really doi i'm talking about the
hell knows abraham lincoln the tall tall
top hat what did you call it
stovepipe that's what it's called because it
looks like a ah you know
no the old fashioned stove that had
the piano my piano yeah i've heard
heard of it and it's like can
you imagine like the first person where
one of those hats and you're like
this looks good and then you get
out in the world and was like
hey it's like yeah you were in
a stovepipe on your head you're like
you gotta think though that like a
brooklyn hipster must have tried it once
and then sometimes i live in a
bramley you know creepy oh my god
don't you think do you know i
had one and i wore it the
last time i remember wearing it was
to jimmy paros podcast thumb when he
was still doing it at what stage
nothing stuff by party jimmy pesto flipper
it's very hard to say and um
so i wore it because it was
around christmas time and so i wore
this you know sort of dickensian christmas
outfit to show yeah i remember this
and ah and then i never saw
it again and i don't know what
happened to it and my sneaking suspicion
is you sat on it and became
a normal hat
yeah became normal and i can look
right at it flat pancake black hat
i think i ate it i think
points zero upon it and i was
like this thing because bird but it's
still good
um we had we we had after
not thought no because we've been here
for a bit so we had a
bunch of shit that just accumulated in
the garage and we finally broke down
and called one eight hundred got junk
to just call the shit away and
i think that that hat got taken
away oh they assumed it was zhang
just goes missing like i have my
sunglasses are missing their prescription i can't
find them i'm missing two of my
favorite pairs of sunglasses and i had
them on a trip and then i
packed my stuff and came home and
i'm like where the fuck are they
i have all my sunglasses all of
them that i've ever had okay i
hate when i don't get over that
stuff for years i feel
like when someone goes yelling i'm like
i think about that hat all the
time it was really good at do
you know when i called one eight
hundred junk ah probably three years ago
they asked if they could haul you
away
they recognized me over the phone and
i was so glad that i was
being nice all over the phone to
people that aren't big nice well no
i mean nice phase
no it's happened like five times where
the people like i'm being super nice
on the phone and people go wait
is this these got aggravated and i'm
like oh good i'm being nice ah
i know what what is a situation
in which you're mean well you know
if you're ever talking to a like
customer service place and you're
frustrated like i remember there was a
bank that wouldn't let me rabbit rabbit
she's like come on i haven't gone
right when you're home this is scott
aquaman
alright let's take a break
alright and we're back and it's time
for three cheshire and this is one
we played before because all the ones
you've been sending us are no good
this is called half-life and this is
where we are going to improvise a
scene for two minutes and then we
will improvise the same scene for one
minute then we'll improvise the same scene
for thirty seconds then we'll improvise the
same scene for fifteen seconds and then
eight seconds then four then two
then one and we'll see how it
goes alright well so was you guys
ready yes i have yeah timer it's
gotta be ready i'm ready yeah you
know i'm ready i'm always ready i
was born ready here we go this
is the two minute scene here we
go and start welcome to my shop
i'm so expand dong ding dong what's
up please i'm so glad
to have some customers in here because
i just got a new selection of
wind chimes and gnomes do you have
a wind charm that is a gnome
or a gnome that is a wind
chime i actually have one of each
i spent over here on the shelf
you can go look at that well
good because this is a robbery oh
no oh oh but i don't want
money
just want all gnomes that are wind
chimes and i don't want anyone chimes
that are gnomes thank god because i
have thousands of dollars in my pocket
high thousands in this cash register and
now i'm starting to change my my
no no yes yeah you said you
said yeah mama gentleman thief i gotta
stick to my word okay alright one
no one seed oh by the way
i'm a gentleman what don't you get
okay i'm sorry well no my winters
but i just know i want gnomes
to shut up yeah i don't have
any gnomes i'm say wow
you had that covered look i don't
i just wandered into the store i
don't i don't have any gnomes i
don't have any wind chimes can i
go no i'd rather you didn't get
go till the crime is complete now
i promised me and call the cops
yeah no kidding because i'm gonna shoot
you now do you really want guilty
of gotta see this i kind of
do want to be guilty murder it's
been on my bucket list oh really
when danny shoot me i dare you
to shoot me i want to go
to the top of the grand canyon
and looked down at the bottom i
want to fly on a plane ah
i've flown on a plane how did
you get here were on a deserted
island i took a boat stupid
yeah i said i gotta get to
that deserted island would jibe store that
also sells gnomes you took a boat
here yeah did someone else drive it
or did you drive it i drove
it i'm a boat driver and a
gentleman thief
two minutes ever felt so long when
talking about i think we realised this
the last time we played this game
now give me those gnomes that are
wind chimes and know when jobs that
are gnomes that's the time we did
it we did it okay alright can
we remember all of that our desks
sure we can
alright here we go this is the
one minute version here we go and
start hello and welcome to my shop
i'm so happy to have some customers
here i have a huge collection of
wind chimes and gnomes
please take a look thanks ding dong
ding dong was a plays sunni gnomes
that are wind chimes or wind chimes
that are gnomes i do i have
both they're right over here on this
shelf well this is robbery oh no
oh no oh no yes i want
what do you want i don't want
money i'm just gonna rob you of
all your whinge gnomes that are we
when jibes i do not want when
james i don't know thank god because
i have thousands of dollars in my
thousands in the cash register oh i'm
thinking about money no you said though
you said i did state that and
i am a gentleman thief yeah because
that way you're wearing a tuxedo or
on the shelf how did you get
here by the way this deserted island
i took a boat that i steered
myself
because i'm a boat steerer
interesting well you submit it's two minutes
never felt so long it's on two
minutes let's be one we said that
in the last scene
now give me those okay done
alright that was the one minute version
can we do it in thirty seconds
yeah yeah i think so and we
do it can we do it here
we go and go welcome to my
shop this is where i sold gnomes
and windchimes texting dong let's plays yeah
do you have any wind germs at
her gnomes gnomes there when gems i
have both the right and the chill
for her
well this is a robbery oh no
that's right give me all your gnomes
that are wind jobs and no wind
gyms that are gnome oh thank god
because i have thousands of dollars in
my pocket and i have thousands the
cash register how did you get this
deserted island now i want that money
but i'm a gentleman oh and every
dictator i get about dessert you start
a boat o two minutes never felt
so long now
a few minutes it's one minute
alright fifteen seconds here we go and
start welcome to my shops where i
sell gnomes and wind chimes was a
place that's i was eighteen give me
everything i'm a robber oh not money
just so much money how did you
get your kids zero and took a
boat oh my god
two minutes never felt so lucky to
shoot my bucket list seconds and done
all right and now we go to
seven seconds that luke perry special here
we go and go welcome to my
shops where i send them sandy huh
no so plays robbery owe thousands of
dollars montauk oh
right now we go to three seconds
here we go and start names when
checking jimmy please oh good it's alright
and hell one second
and da da da da da
oh you did it right did we
sure did alright i asked and a
half a blast and a half thanks
so much for listening remember to get
our giblets i love y'all so much
three ammunition store you gotta get em
and you can send us three years
three dm usa at gmail dot com
tom yeah i would say a helpful
guide for three cheers is no games
that end with and whoever is the
funniest wins
and also games that can be played
with just audio yeah yeah you don't
have to make up a game if
you can think of car games things
like that you know yeah games that
make me look good
yeah good luck
um but ah thanks so much for
listening we'll be back next week don't
you worry about little old us cry
don't worry bad thing
a guy we'll see ya bye bye
uh