free
ah no welcome to the show where
we talk about whenever we want my
name is laura schaeffer x where all
seven year olds not we get to
talk about whatever we want what did
you say scott i'm like chuck except
for what we agreed we weren't going
to tell you okay that's right yeah
talk about
don't talk about that ever but but
but everything else is on the everything
else no everything else except that one
subject that we all we are not
never discussed going to talk about that
we don't talk about machine thing or
two ashamed it's mortifying you would not
that differently allowed us if you knew
about it that embarrassing thing that happened
when we went on that trip together
there were never going to talk about
it yeah we will never talk about
it's almost morally wrong um but here's
the great thing we talked about what
everyone no one can get mad at
us or yellows yeah well that's what's
great because there are no guests i
never will be and it's just the
three of them and everyone no one
to storm off getting angry with us
because they were on the show and
it wasn't what they expected hey exam
less bell to answer one less egg
to fry wow and that was a
clip from the hit song one less
egg to fry
love song clips
um i just play song clips on
the radio you are leading your the
whole thing you're just have to get
any seconds it's like i get it
yeah just did the best part but
the data that's all you need you
guys only listen to classical right yep
only don't do that da da da
da didn't come overnight i may have
told you this but when i worked
at two
our video i found out that the
ah of all the branches of tower
the different things that they sold the
place where there was the most theft
was the classical section where we had
a classical annex next because every store
said it's like public domain will know
all those dvds and cds are made
out of go
old oh that makes yes because the
classical ritual i just saw an instagram
a video that ben lee posted of
yes singing christmas coloring machine whatever maybe
please come home close parentheses and it
was so fun when what was that
close parentheses yeah put clothes on parentheses
and see what happens
spin is sort of like a little
like logician mark yes exact clothes pins
are my quotation marks okay let's go
over all the laundry items and what
they're like and punctuation okay so we
have ah like a big billowy shirt
on a clothesline oh no now that's
close okay so we're talking about laundry
items roderick
i i a tide pod is like
a period sure yeah just detergent is
like an ellipsis robin because there's little
grains of it and they dot dot
dot and like a dryer sheet is
like a hyphen yeah washing machine is
exclamation point dry no hold on washing
machine is questionmark dry
after his excommunication point because it emphatically
answers what the question yes dryer brings
armani imo gently they are dry
yes that was from amy man would
do a christmas show every year um
for many years i think this is
one of the this past year is
one of the only years that she
hasn't done it since maybe two thousand
and seven something like that
because of covered kami na the commonality
from war and we listening to like
comment and i can't stop laughing it's
a fun way to shake things up
after four or five today so right
yeah thirteen because i because i called
kevin
i know there's a commission if a
coven has given you an until dysfunction
just kind of do that oh shit
kevin oh god um yeah and and
ah
it was those shows were always so
much fun i was ah part of
almost everyone um and i really miss
that a lot i really missed it
this year because it's it's a fun
time always and she in recent years
she and ted leo have been doing
it together um and it's a real
good time to really look to it
it made me really nostalgic for like
eighty different
things at once yelled to net video
absolutely yeah for baby without a mustache
ceilings i miss when you didn't have
a mustache i miss being in ceilinged
rooms with others i miss christmas
in this lamps i miss lamp samus
and why do you just watch a
pixar movie there's one of the beginning
uv time why would why would she
miss lamps i don't know he he
made the point and then he's said
that he set up his own joke
that it was like i didn't have
a joke before i said it scott
he was like i got a good
game show lamp
ps scott during cava did you put
all your lamps out of your house
threw them all away i caused it
so it was wanting for living in
darkness every time i've been to the
doctor they turn on that light to
look at your boho yep
whoa there there there paul that's what
that's what this is come on paul
stop bashing my head in shame that's
what this show show is okay i
may not know a whole lot a
second that is not what this show
is that is maybe an aspect of
this show but that is not the
thrust
the thrust is fun that's true excepting
is fun
it's
don't spread your videos
have you ever wished you had a
penis like even once
which
oh i wish i were better right
now wished it um i mean i
definitely got my hands and knees and
prayed and and knees can i get
on all fours to pray and no
one will ever break me of that
habit
sticking my little bud up in the
air dear god i'm like a dog
i wish give me a penis for
a day one day is to know
what it's like what have you prayed
to god and then all of a
sudden your divorce saying your wish is
granted oh that would be shocking right
i mean you know freaky freaky friday
type situations i think we're getting into
it we don't talk about it enough
that
there is something about the body that
is too it's almost too much to
get around that lighting that's a child
being like for example the original freaky
friday a child being in a mother's
body and then suddenly you're like i'm
this body you could just like they
don't buy i think they don't react
to their anything besides their face
whenever they do freaky friday yeah well
in the more recent in the free
karate re remake i believe yes there
was a lot of reaction to the
body which is fun for the parents
i guess and use it for the
children yeah it's pretty weird yeah it's
weird when it's the kid going like
what my body does this
yeah there'd be like but yeah tits
now my tits are all the way
up here instead of all the way
down there
this is what the show is actually
right what if we if we were
to freaky friday each other
who would you want to be in
oh i guess none of you because
after that cause that's pretty disgusting
if you had to pick one of
us dirty want to be in awe
okay ignoring okay so this is this
is the conversation they have whenever they
weren't waiting for visas ignore the body
ignore their bodies for the day as
this person yeah and i'm like who's
lifestyle and and whose spouse do you
want to hook up with and all
that goes well now you made it
weird paul
oh my god whose spouse do you
want to essentially rape
it's not it's it's not right but
they don't know you're somebody else inside
just false pretenses what are you or
you're gonna say okay look ah i
guess what i mean
cool outfit so paul scott's body um
but let's have sex i've always wanted
to do this as scott so like
you guys obviously i know you would
want to switch with me and then
be able to fuck mike
i want to switch with you and
turn mike down for sex
just to see the look on his
face i here's the thing about freaky
friday thing is that yes it would
be interesting to be in someone else's
body but i would hate for someone
else to be my body yeah but
you know other things only one way
freaky friday one way free what happens
you just lifeless husk
with no soul alright i gotta go
in the closet nature oh that's right
yeah something i did
not breathing
like what it is like you pass
out at a party somebody drew all
over you
i guess i wouldn't want to freaky
friday with any of you i have
a freaky friday oh yeah i guess
the fantasy that a fantasy of being
someone that you will admire oh no
just like you know i don't know
being an athlete or what i got
but you don't get the abilities because
your brain doesn't work the same way
so if like you freaky friday with
like a famous
football player you're not going to be
good at football but what about if
you if it was like a weightlifter
and you're like whoa i mean there
was walk around preening and lifting things
just covering myself with oil
which is ever enter a weightlifting bodybuilding
competition yeah of course
so are you tolerant right now men
from real housewives reality recap yeah who
um got very fit and started doing
bodybuilding and it was like so it
was real housewives oh see tamra i
don't know why that's so gross to
me it's pretty royal well it fits
and it's the it's a type of
swimsuit they put on and how they
walk out and pose and it's a
yeah just some soil as opposed to
with the elbows up and down yeah
yeah yeah i i find it kind
of funny and i know that people
take things seriously but the dreams in
which i'm dying oh man sorry ah
that um it's just like you do
all this work on your body and
then the the end game is you
walk out on stage and you pose
and deutch opposes and then people applaud
and i guess you win maybe yeah
people wanna fuck you more well like
arnold schwarzenegger got like you know
much of movie roles from it that's
true and it's very terry crews those
biggest muscles his was the bodybuilder terry
wasn't a choice first player but i
mean it's the same like you're doing
the same stuff like like he could
have been a bodybuilder behold on it
he could have been but he wasn't
scott that's a crucial distinction you did
not well not seen him in a
speedo tiny
speedo lifting up his elbow
you really want to see that because
like my that and he i would
freaky friday with him because i bet
he has a lot of fun yeah
it was the most fun like i
could accept anyone like access to things
i think is the reason freaky friday
i want freaky friday was like taylor
swift because it would be like not
a day
day where she goes to an event
or something now when she's just hanging
out in the woods with her boyfriends
no but i wouldn't i was actually
thinking i wanna be in her house
and like you know really cool so
maybe she goes from her house takes
a private helicopter to the grammys performs
yes i do like a really bad
song
and everyone's like that's so okay but
i'm gonna do interviews after and say
really weird things you ever seen your
ability wouldn't you yeah but i'd have
to know all the songs maybe i
wouldn't know all because i knew how
a lot you don't want your teleprompters
come on you'd ever voice but i
don't think you would have the confidence
to use the voice cast singing or
i play guitars well the guitar part
just yeah definitely singing is ninety eight
percent confidence
and two percent skill maybe and one
percent the hot leaving the president freaky
friday with the president be really interesting
because then you could see all the
ufo shit and you could figure out
who you could determine policy yeah hey
be in joe biden's baby like hey
remind me who killed j f k
again like we tell you this every
day
a
wait said even so your freaky friday
with somebody who has early dementia we
we tell you this every time assuming
he gets freaky friday every day but
scott yeah once once you leave yourself
open sewage is that am conspiracy theory
that someone else killed j f k
what yes it's one of the most
famous ones people time warren
oh lions
i mean that it's not that guy
yeah you've never hold mike and there's
so many high theories about you know
this
o j f k it's right there
in the title and i wanna let
say yeah hold on wait i'm just
gonna google this oh it's it's it's
probably i mean it might be the
first conspiracy like major conspiracy okay i'll
talk to me let's just say i've
never heard of this just for the
sake of
the conversation but everyone at home just
chill out it's it's sometimes people feel
that i don't know if this isn't
maybe i do and i forget who
even gives a shit and who cares
you even give a shit i don't
want to get caught up in conspiracy
theories one way or another by um
i went to the i went to
the place where he was killed when
i was in dallas and went into
the building where they showed where
it was yeah because the museum is
built a plaza he was not killed
in the depository well killed in the
car but i'm saying you got the
museum is built so that you can
go through and then see the actual
point where the person was standing where
they shot the gun who would you
say the person is
um lee harvey oswald yeah there you
go do some tab as well
awesome
and he was too or something
i don't know when he was killed
umm so i'm dead
i was gonna come down and i'm
saying
god i feel like it's like an
idiot but i'm saying like oh i
went to that museum and i stood
there and i'm saying so then they
think they figured out where he's shot
from all these different things and they're
saying it wasn't him who's who's hussein
this people seriously about everything so so
kevin costner the movie kind of goes
through all the the reasons that they
don't think it was him because of
like the angles of the bullets
stone match and all this kind of
stuff so everyone thinks that like there
were what there is at least another
shooter in the bushes essentially you know
that a frames early harvey oswald you
know he was a patsy who sort
of took the fall because he was
just like some dumb shit you know
and then he was killed shortly thereafter
by jack ruby who die
died of cancer and ah it's it's
all there's a lot of stuff that
if you look at it does seem
extremely fishy but the the outcomes razor
explanation just is the clearest one it's
like yeah one guy killed you you
think by now someone who knew would
have come out and said like oh
by the way because people can just
just can't keep
a secret like that it does seem
impossible they couldn't even keep watergate secret
for that long you know what i
mean even the judas in the black
messiah dude like came out on sixty
minutes was like oh yeah yeah i
i worked with ah who was at
the fbi or the cia began to
watch fbi but but yeah like even
he couldn't keep his mouth shut and
it ruined his life yeah wow he
killed himself
lf later that week yeah because of
it it just seems impossible that somebody
that they could keep a secret for
that long however i don't it it
doesn't seem entirely out of the realm
of possibility it's enough that nuts to
fill that makes us there was a
conspiracy yeah so that there was another
person and or whatever and that they
framed somebody but like if they could
i'm roger rabbit i mean kimi for
him anyway because he's so savvy
no honey bunny rabbit if so what
is the theory that the the that
you're saying part of the conspiracy thing
is that the president knows who really
did it or that kind of thing
like people well they they let the
president in on like all of these
secrets when they become president and that's
pretty exciting that is one that people
think
you know oh yeah that's probably something
that the cia knows about or whatever
and it's ufos and who killed j
f k seemed to be the two
major ones paul can you think of
any other one oh moon landing that's
my moonlight oh yeah that's my favorite
one that didn't really happen yes which
is just like what is that yeah
the the hardest thing went all
we talked about hello okay okay go
on there again in which is the
part that i find weird i'm like
well then if it's so easy easy
and we've already did it we are
we've already did in the sixties vardy
didn't really do it again that's when
people start going we're going back to
the moon it's like who gives a
shit did we see that there wasn't
anything up there
i think there is an ah there
is ah an a notion to to
make a base on the moon that
would then be a way for us
to get to mars easier i i
really don't want to go to mars
yeah you better get used to it
because that's where we're all going yeah
i mean we'll in twenty twenty four
yeah we'll go there in a couple
of years i mean yeah i don't
know if i would go to mars
maybe if i was an old man
you know what i mean if i
was like a widower and i had
nothing left going on i'm retired and
talk about this every six episode we
honest so
we honestly we haven't explored this angle
before right now it did around the
moon seemed fresh it does yeah i
would go to the moon but i
would only go to mars i think
if it was like because you're not
coming back from that trip in our
lifetimes i don't think anyone likes to
take together like three weeks right here's
what i would like something like we
lifted up by some i think
you said it was like we say
the same things we're so stupid
yeah if um if paul paul if
you went to the moon let's say
you were like ninety nine yeah and
janie had passed to it umm you
know that three days three days early
yeah okay she's so she's ninety days
early
she's she also got to live a
very long time she's in these as
well
then you go to the moon and
it would be like comedian perlis tamkins
gu i don't know why the new
orders are comedian he's he's great yeah
he's the last person who remembers me
ah those to the moon and then
you're you're on the moon and you're
like i guess i'll do a podcast
from here and then you do
would be so awesome boot on garry
moon from mars it's like freaking coal
dude do battle it's cold as hell
yeah
what did you ask me a question
or no you just presented a scenario
eight i see so ten days after
my wife does i am going to
march into buck
hell yeah
ninety nine out of hours of doing
podcasts and airwolf um supports you yeah
emotionally
rocketship says here while you're off branding
and you hear well yeah you got
for christmas
we buy pennzoil five hundred years before
still couldn't get you any ads but
we will provide a rocket ship to
take you to mars
and then you get up there and
they're like we actually did get one
ad and then yeah like it's internal
that's it it's internal it's one of
those
i'm i'm glad i did
ah mars you're like fuck
you just take off your helmet
yeah cause lazy doing scam guys and
she's she's seventy five
talking about future scams she's been doing
it for oh hey scabs
this robot tricks so many people
alright let's take a break
and we're back we're back we're backed
everyone i know i am yeah oh
yeah i think we're all back i
think we've all grown up a little
bit in that time yeah yeah i'm
paul what is your favorite aerosmith song
is it
banking on bobo what the hell is
that and why like the harmonica unc
and i'm bo yeah that's fifty cents
for real innuendo i want agree like
everything's there are no little bit and
nuendo ish if you really think about
it i gotta say dream on it's
it's oh
so rock anthem
i wish i could sing it i
know but only steven tyler can get
up there and only one was that
little voice of his oh the toxic
twins they've done it again liv tyler
showed her home on architectural digest there's
this great show that i really enjoy
i think it's on hulu called open
door or something like that reality recap
yeah
yeah it's not almost not necessarily reality
i mean it's it's true but it's
my it's home tours and hers was
a really great highly recommend just like
when you like waters it it was
just really milliard to me new york
times wasn't veronese was it funny no
nothing's funny about this program no serious
her her her home had some
whimsy to it she had like um
sky laning a pink skylight
you're not allowed to have that she
did what what was pink about it
was it like hey the glass was
tinted glass was tinted itself or was
it a floor it's like pink looking
oh it wasn't the mechanism of the
skylight was painted think
anyway fun show
that kind of thing so i've known
scott quite so my video you've given
one was mm edta led you gay
so well i don't have to tell
you the whole thing yeah it was
a good episode i'm not saying it's
a story i want to tell i've
been told my stories are long boring
and pointless wow told you yeah guy
who would say somewhat me
i do feel lorin like you've mentioned
her before on some reality show or
some something where she was deal with
lee taylor being herself and you liked
her and like her and i and
i'm actually in that episode she goes
and looks through some old boxes of
lord of the rings memorabilia that she
was given at the time that they
shot maybe course you know
don't care about your burns at all
hours in the incinerator because they gave
her like a giant sword or some
shit um that by the way is
my favorite bit to do when someone
gives you a gift is to meet
its say thank you and immediately throw
it in the trash when when does
this happen in your micah this is
so thoughtful thank you so
put it in
i mean that's probably did talk about
her excuse me probably to talk about
it before because i also find her
kind of mall nobody find kind of
interesting because she there's that whole story
which i'm sure i have wrong where
like she didn't know steven tyler was
her dad until yeah older photo todd
rundgren shelling a poster of him on
her wall
yeah that's weird and the poster said
abby a day
i
it's like popeye maybe yes please sorta
does that at the end of ah
yes what he's very much like popeye
yeah here's the popeye of singers so
they're ever my sing scott were you
really close to being cast on full
house as the dave cooley a part
where you can do all your impression
that probably when i was fifteen or
fourteen
would have been my favorite like dream
job or something yeah because i like
i would look at like robin williams
i was in a church play i
remember donkey
where it was like there was this
christian sketch group that i remember would
play knott's berry farm during during the
christian band times that i would go
there and see certain white christian bands
like like ah striking see talk and
discharge around a you know are not
around
any other steve taylor striper harman i
actually i did see amy grant there
and michael w smith i believe i
saw both of them but um so
there's this christian sketch group who would
do like basically like leave it to
beaver parodies and stuff like that who
the but have a christian message at
the end you know and so i
remember we put on one of em
at the church
sj ah and i was cast in
it and i was like imitating a
tv switching channels and i was doing
all the programs kind of stuff you
know it's like yeah and the funny
thing was i wasn't like sticking to
the script i was like throwing in
some hot it's something i wasn't around
but that's the thing i wasn't improvising
like i
it was doing the same thing all
the time but i was just kind
of like it was more like i
was doing punch up but i thought
it was improv so i remember and
this is so mortifying but i remember
when i when the directors of it
said hey we're gonna do another show
the year later i was kind of
like i knew i was the big
hit of the shows i was wow
so sort of like
um could i improv in this one
and they were like yeah sure like
they didn't give a shit like when
no one noticed you change ah how
fucking stupid
that was no that was like when
i was in children's theater like my
first like this was like in my
town there was just like anyone could
audition so for many school or whatever
and i was in was it like
a community theater yeah yeah ready for
kids so i was in um like
cars for kids yeah
one eight six zen guys is kay
here is guys yeah paul smash it's
literally the worst thing i've ever heard
um but i was in the beauty
and the beast show and i didn't
get any part that i didn't get
caught wasn't a licensed one or was
it like
knock wise because it i think it
had the songs from the disney movie
but that would be the tipoff yeah
i mean i i was tens i'm
trying to remember what happened in it
but i was cast as mother wolf
which was an add on part there
was like a little wolf family over
they do show other whoa i was
theirs mother will
follow up from the baby well but
we were like come out of this
little interstitials and like the whole a
little thing about that show is beast
is the weird one
i literally held a mixing bowl i
came on stage held mixing mothers they
go wolf and then i would like
improvise things but i also think it
probably wasn't improvised because that just sounds
gonna be a total train wreck and
now that i think about it where
you like repeating jokes you knew worked
yes it's probably the same thing where
i was like we got to improvise
but it was like you
doing like the hanukkah song
i just came out and had like
little funny things as like levity i
mean but i can imagine what it
really would be would be like the
long silence as i walk out and
then like we say something where does
the spotlight finds us and then like
we leave and everyone's like he or
whatever right and it feels amazing because
like we crushed we crushed i mean
and and expe
stations are low in like ah those
situations from from an audience standpoint so
for stone crushing really yeah thank you
think there's i pay money to see
the show
i you get me into the church
you mean i like oddly yeah ties
if my nephew comes with the show
included the show included thinking this super
savvy grid go show included
if i if my nephews did a
play i would love to go watch
i would love to watch a little
children's play i went to go see
ah mt and morgan walsh's kid be
in a play once it was really
fun like cool off i went to
go see them in a little shop
of horrors and it was so funny
because they had multiple kids playing the
same part yeah so like
to most knicks would come out and
say their lines simultaneously so it's yeah
it's insane it's so why why like
that why not like i know why
not switch them off yeah performance know
even basic scene by scene or something
it was so funny silly simultaneously talking
like just have all the kids playing
the part dress the same and then
they just come in and out no
explanation it's just like whenever they go
off stage a new kid comes on
it's super confusing so this was just
yeah it was just that more kids
could get the chance to yeah yeah
because because there were no there was
no pretense about the show being good
yeah that was what i loved about
it it was like look these are
these are five to six year olds
i'm not gonna be a good show
really little we just want to get
them out there to have the experience
and like you know have all the
adults taking pictures and something that's being
able have a story to tell later
when they're on a date
i like the idea of having someone
you said in sync with because then
if you forget what the line is
here they all forget you forgot yeah
i don't think a single person remembered
any of the lines was so what
if there was someone on stage on
a broadway play the same way there
is with children's theatre like like the
teacher is there like trying to give
people q
since i mean i know they they
they say all the time such a
cliche that that's the actor's nightmare whatever
i literally have that nightmare like once
in a while and it's sort of
like scary thing ever yeah it is
like you're like i have no clue
i was in like hamilton and dream
i had and i was like i
don't know what's going on i don't
know who i am i know there's
an expectation i know i know
always fucked up and forgotten a memorize
the lines over the like previous three
months yeah i've always liked procrastinated on
it and then one day it's like
hey by the way you gotta go
on tonight it's like fuck i know
yeah well anyway lot is sorry sorry
what i get a lot as i've
memorized the wrong thing oh and then
they say okay we're doing this and
i'm
saying ivo were doing the other one
they're like nope
when i would do that community theater
stuff i was always really really nervous
about forgetting my lines and i that
was so stressful like the memorizing was
the hardest part and then as you
get older it's like because i always
think like broadway seems so intimidating half
just because of the memorization and i'd
be like nervous that i would mess
it up but like i do feel
like you're
brain gets into a rhythm with memorization
and oh yeah i'm so much easier
it's always so funny when someone comes
out and jumps ahead in the script
because this would happen at a high
school not the like pro shows that
i did but like in high school
sometimes like pages and pages would be
skipped like like fifth
eighteen pages someone comes on and does
something from fifteen and then and then
it's like everyone backstage is going oh
no he's skipped fifteen pages what do
we do and then it's it's like
somehow trying to maneuver them into getting
back on track of the pre because
you know something needs to happen in
those fifteen pages to make the whole
thing right so funny so let me
be like yeah we get to go
denny's even earlier
but i always kind of feel like
if something gets skipped in a show
that means that it's not important you
know what i mean like anytime i
was doing comedy and i would forget
a bit in in part of a
bit i was doing i was always
like oh that's the part that should
have been cut out yeah yeah i
remember it then it's it's although i
have done that on stage where i've
tried to do an old bit
and forgotten i did it on tv
once i do i do a tv
spot and this australian when i was
doing an australian ah i was doing
the melbourne festival and i got this
tv spot and i had i had
like a small it was a very
small amount of time for the sep
so i was like ok i'm gonna
do an old bit because all those
old bits are shorter
and i thought i could just do
it from memory and i forgot a
co rusal part of the bit and
no one was laughing like i just
completely i just completely like edited that
out of my mind and went on
and i skipped like i cannot tell
i cannot stress enough if you go
back what made the bit good
was this piece of information that i
by the way i'm talking about a
ghost well yeah i feel like with
any sort of standup thing like that
you need every word of it even
if you think yeah parts not that
yeah to it's like it just makes
the rhythm right and yeah although if
you're i don't know i feel like
sometimes when i was doing standup if
if you're in the moma
ain't enough and you skip a bit
as long as you're communicating what you
need to say it's like oh i
didn't need that stuff yeah well sometimes
your mind edits that way naturally like
when you're trying out material it kind
of automatically goes to the parts that
work better yeah and then you kind
of look back and you realize oh
yeah i didn't need to be throwing
that in there sometimes you'll have you'll
go back and go like oh
oh shit i forgot that was a
really funny part and then you go
it was just dragging the pace down
so who's trying to base town it
was a real page tracker yeah i'm
like lee pace who's next i didn't
see his picture he posted some sort
of like the picture was like for
some reason everyone's obsession recently it's always
easy pick stoned out of his mind
right he's
wearing yeah but he also gets like
long hair he has long hair the
background is is incredibly vibrant right he's
jiving i'm sorry vibrant thank you i
accept your apology i'm not keen i
don't accept you say by lauren well
with me or with you
he was reviving with vibrant but yeah
everyone was like a little pulse rock
some ah the to bang him yeah
i did i did seth meyer so
with him and i said hi before
the show and he's like oh you
wanna take my trash show first of
all he's like credit we didn't know
who you
we're at all yeah no no no
it was take my drag yeah that's
how i felt he should have acted
to me and instead he was like
i'm so nervous and i was like
what what's i mean no no no
not to me just to do the
show oh do the show lord he
doesn't give a shit about me but
he was like so whew
germany's just like i'm so nervous i'm
like you're late you're gonna be fine
when no matter what happens yeah brow
i mean it just feels like it's
so much easier on non comedians to
do a show like that because you
there's no expectation for you to say
or do anything funny you just have
to that's also that's also like they're
not used to being funny in the
situation so
so they feel a big expectation of
like oh shit what if no one
laughs at anything i say right right
yeah it's true right i feel like
anytime i've done something like that i
have like an out-of-body experience like i
feel like i'm not like so weird
yeah i've i've done such a bad
job anytime i've done panel on a
talk show i hate doing panel
yeah it's the worst beason because you
just feel like no they don't they
don't know who i am they're they're
like bummed out it's not a cooler
guest oh see for me i feel
like my feeling is i not a
standup so when i do these things
i'm like i don't like having a
pre-written joke i say i don't like
them interface pri right then i feel
like i get
so steamrolled by the people who did
pre-run so then it's like it's just
not me not my favorite way to
be funny the only thing that i
ever liked that happened was on that
seth meyers i had gone through three
pre interviews where i talked about my
stories and i was like i don't
even like these stories or whatever but
then when i got out there seth
was like so you host your the
whoa
most of your show and i said
yeah this is weird shouldn't we like
you i should be interviewing you and
he's like right let's switch and then
like we switched so much more fun
it was so fun and he was
so into it and so so like
cool about it and everything it made
like it made the interview so much
more fun that we started on just
like an improv note yeah my experiencing
sounds good
i think i think having good experience
paulo i'm happy for you sure you
tell the same story over and over
again is really like brutal yeah yeah
you get used to it
yeah i mean that on this show
no this show it helps to forget
that you've told the story before ah
yeah like say things about mark so
much better if we just like you
just say so if you said like
twenty hours ago as like episodes ago
you know as opposed to like someone
called you and asked you i'm happy
to repeat all my same stories on
here and i also am happy to
receive my spankings
you can't say fairer than that
is that a phrase yeah yeah yeah
of course it is yeah they say
j f k they don't
he stated if you can't say fairer
than that that was once said to
me um in the country of his
origin england when i was working in
that kelsey grammer show um and we're
living in haunted kelsey grammer trash kelsey
grammar presents the sketch show lauren don't
act like you didn't
watch every episode that aired well i'm
i think it was like how many
aaron i think six aired yeah around
thirteen episodes i don't really i'm sure
we've talked about this but i'm gonna
google this you may have come up
before y'all could just tell you um
well i mean that's part of trying
to make it so he doesn't have
to repeat himself well since it was
an adaptation of a british show that
already existed we were doing like the
their scripts
stuff i'm looking at you we had
to ah there were the guy who
is the producer of the show who
was the you know he was the
showrunner he was the director but he
was the showrunner he kept encouraging us
to do the exact line readings from
the original sketches and he would kind
of like try to direct you into
the end of that
it like force you into that and
it was frustrating because you know it
was me and and ah a couple
of few other americans marilyn rice called
kaitlin olson malcolm barrett um you know
we all auditioned in everything and at
the the additions were a lot of
fun and then when we finally got
there to do the show it was
sort of like we're just become
the parrots pop and it was really
frustrating and slicker you could have gotten
anybody to do this if this is
what you wanted right why did you
bother having why did you bother auditioning
comedy people so after a few weeks
of shooting i was getting so frustrated
because i was just being given these
line readings over and over again and
finally the the producer at one point
said it's funnier that way you know
about this one sketch he said it's
funnier that way and i said you
can tell me that it's faster you
can tell me that you like it
better you can tell me that it's
gonna play better on screen but you
cannot tell me that it's funnier and
he said he said you know what
you're right
that that's that's true and he walked
away and then this ah this grip
turned to me and said well you
can't say fairer than that night wow
i was like yeah
just one time he kind of agreed
that it was great if he wheeled
in a birthday cake that said you're
fired on it
it actually would have been great
everyone saying happy birthday mistakes but you
can give cakes yes are you able
to show off your legs the way
and your butt
my legs and butter my kids tasty
things um they the way they do
ah craft service ah in in london
was they would put out these little
like throughout the day there would they
would bring out little you know like
trays of things and just kind of
put them all over the set did
you experience this all over
what because like they never took love
like on the set where you're filming
but then like aroused like so it's
like an easter income my experiences like
that we didn't take lunch then you
have like little food coming out all
day so everyone's kind of like always
feeling no love lunch was walking lunch
or whatever it's called wow well we
were we were filling in a place
where they had a canteen so we
yeah and get lunch i really like
the the the comedy aside and the
the practice the way the comedy was
directed aside that was a great experience
and i love being over there and
feeling like i was working in a
different culture and that's fine it was
really cool but i love that they
would have there so they would put
little first it would put out live
will savory things so you would like
turn around you walk upset you turn
around they're like sitting on a ledge
would be like a little dish with
you know some savory thing and edge
so you're really hung up on where
it is no i'm just fascinated with
like like i wanna get it from
the person because who knows how long
it's been on that ledge you know
what i mean who knows if like
it was flies but that's also what
kind of snap eating i know but
like any even snacks like just like
i want i want to get em
from the person like steel know anyway
but
wait what do you wanna go they're
all like deviled eggs and stuff i
just don't trust anything that looked a
little jar of manny's with his own
you know what i mean like if
i just happen upon oh my god
here's a snack sitting here that's been
unattended right every minute but day-night but
the food crafty has unintended largely you
know what i mean like the the
craft the craft authors usually crushed surface
every player asking out the grilled cheeses
and stuff well these people are doing
that except i'm not putting it in
your little hands sweethearts what i don't
like about it because anyone could like
fart on it or anything what the
fuck is wrong with you
do you realize how many enemies you'd
made on sex oh yeah like constantly
party oh my word have to be
on guard at all times i would
love to work on comedy bang bang
tv show and just walk around and
fart on your food yeah you missed
your chance and i sadly sorry that
we got cancelled sorry oh man
how many episodes did you do lauren
do you remember this tv show yeah
i think three three
sounds right somewhere around there yeah mate
did you do vol you probably did
let me get eight twelve twelve it
really did at least five because you
did i mean there are certain people
who did one per season like andy
samberg and matt besser and i think
but you probably you probably did to
season didn't you so maybe i did
yeah maybe yeah well i mean there's
an easy way to find this out
out by candle holder i am google
you do
how many did i do
five
i'm gonna watch what i i want
to enter other food falls palm well
no nobody stopping you well for me
iranian ah what ah what if like
you tie the to church in watching
brother verb falls was part of it
um you did fourteen episodes of county
baby
ng wow is that the record and
they blend together to be five is
it a record who's someone who's not
a regular yeah i e me what
have you said it was he he
did more than you
the amazing i mean like not me
not reggie there's a way to look
this up i mdp and now one
of the characters in the skits well
i don't know if that counts i
don't know what i just read that
you did fourteen i didn't see what
you know they all were my was
always featured karen i didn't have time
to watch them all while we were
talking here
ear or during the pandemic that's true
actually watching real housewives from beginning further
v getting yes of orange county i
guess we didn't new york seasons one
through like seven because my can never
seen it and wanted to watch it
and then i was like this is
my dream and is mike into it
now yes he was sort of noise
into it but not fully with the
you know with history
not mike hanford my camphor did more
than you paul
as that feel he did nineteen episodes
a fee-free he played what character was
planet this is what i'm saying well
then you did the most of even
bandleaders so in your mind in your
mind on comedy bang bang what they
did with skits
yeah skips it's very reductive little routines
i will say we got there the
someone listed their favorite sketch shows of
the last thirty years and we weren't
even mentioned how many fucking sketches have
their most kelsey grammer percents this issue
mitchell tone was great they said it
wasn't funny
so they did mention it
oh bleakly they said you know the
one show that was not funny at
all i just assume just so you
know that one's not on this list
so don't worry please read it
alright we have to take a break
bike
hey we're back we're back well yeah
to three dom webapp webapp loves it
up it was up why no so
i learned that that day that commercial
campaign came out of a short film
really
yes those same guys really commercial yeah
that short film what is command short
and then budweiser said how about we
give you a truckload of money and
you do your idea is now ours
and they said yes budweiser yes yes
budweiser how much money i think it
was like one hundred dollars each whoa
shit
the commercials are very memorable yeah they
are although you know what bud had
a campaign during the last super bowl
that i think required you to remember
all of their previous campaigns well let's
list them was up was ah i
love my iser remember that guy the
frogs of course
the frogs you have joe zuzu
did he do bud commercials the clydesdales
the clydesdales declared you got the where's
the beef lady okay scott
i feel like you're making a mockery
of this of us listing but both
cars are listing the budweiser campaigns you're
making a mockery of the woman who
said she goes she goes like where's
the beef and then she lifts her
skirt and then there's budweiser hanging under
yeah hanging under like christmas
there's a neil campbell one that was
on during the super bowl why did
yeah that was one of it that
was one of his big breaks what
did he do that's why i hired
him on comedy baby you're like i
say you're really funny shubra commercial i
think you'd be really good and my
shoe i remember was something about someone
getting hit in the head with a
cat
can that's all i recall sounds hilarious
he was very deadpan as i recall
it so i don't laugh at things
like that i don't like it when
people are injured i would love it
if something fell on your head right
now but it would be funny yeah
you should have like a trap like
a fake book or something hanging above
your plate i book you can just
slap on the slime
to myself all these like oh look
so fucking cool hanging but then you
do like reverse so you like push
up into it and then you expect
everyone to think it just felt oh
you tilt the camera and you're like
oh ah
i mean people would be concerned right
if i was doing that have you
decent
i think i just i do a
wellness check ah hey just like it
has he deals with the pandemic don't
see my cups over here
oh it's for three years yeah oh
that's right oh my heavens i almost
forgot we were having so much fun
oh my heavens and now that fun
stops this is a a game called
increasingly verbose and in is submitted by
prize check p r i s e
c h e c k maybe play
on price check
oh the object of the game is
to complicate a simple sentence until the
sentence can be complicated no further player
one provides the simple sentence players two
and three will then take turns complicating
the sentence slightly so here's an example
do you like jazz is the sample
quit is the sample question then
if somebody has to say has to
enhance it like say do you particularly
enjoy jazz music and then the next
person has to maybe say i would
like to inquire about your opinion of
the improvised form of music known as
jazz and so on and so on
great and then i guess the the
winner is whoever can keep going the
launch there's no winner and we just
have fun no there has to be
more has to be a winner and
and yeah i think it's a person
and it has to be made a
longest and it's oh i was once
playing a card game with my niece
i think we were just playing war
and i accidentally won i was out
trying to
and then she said let's let's play
again but this time make it so
i win oh and i didn't woe
to provide a good lesson
okay we really like starts i ll
be happy to dispense the simple oak
sentence and will go clockwise on the
zoom meaning lower than me see and
that's me that's counter-clockwise we have learned
we should have dragged ourselves into the
same position which way okay so who
who so lauren drag yourself into the
position where your clockwise from paul i
mean i'll just go after paul no
no you will drag yourself young lady
um okay
okay here we go i think it's
raining
i believe the sky has some precipitation
i in fact do believe
that the sky above us has an
unusual amount of precipitation
laura that's me oh i thought was
you paul
no i mean you never get to
go i think it goes between two
people alright i'm alright um i mean
i get to go if you guys
are going to be dicks about it
in my estimation i want upside dry
and now i'm odu covered in wet
due to the fact that the rain
is coming down from the sky precipitating
from the class just changing the entire
sentence
it was a game like we don't
have to say the story to be
a stickler for severe sentence the first
engine was i think it's raining
but i feel like we need to
build on what the previous person does
we should rather than well that that
was specified but i do think that
you have to retain the original words
i'm not look look i'll shoot again
we're not price check here let's try
to get maybe price check should have
said why
but his intention his or hers intention
let's troll yes i think the idea
is that you want to ah still
keep the words in the original sentence
the yeah although there was in the
example the latin the most elaborate one
did not have some of the original
words it didn't yeah so i think
it didn't build upon the pre
obvious one though yes it did i
think you you want to retain the
central idea okay you know you're you're
trying to communicate the same thing with
as many words as possible okay okay
we'll try it again you want a
new sentence yeah i want a nuisance
i woke up too late
you see lauren you my myself
um oh well some sources i'm i'm
i'm supposed to to keep in i
woke up too late as part of
the sentence no i guess you're just
supposed to like cheney cheney and a
little more word keep this keep the
sentence structure yeah ok again start small
so we can build okay
um i
i see
i my scared um
i i woke up later than i
intended
i found out that i had awakened
much later than i had attended
much later than i had intended due
to my alarm clock not
alarming
i found out upon reflection that i
had awakened much later than i had
intended mainly due to my alarm clock
not being set and not alarming
i found out that i had awakened
much later than i had intended due
to the fact that my alarm clock
was not set nor did it alarm
causing me great distress as i wrote
arrived late what i was supposed to
be there for i found out much
later much to my chagrin that i
had awakened much mm
much too late much later than i
had intended in fact mainly due to
the fact that i had not set
my alarm and it had not alarmed
and i didn't wind up at the
place i forget what you said is
the place where i had intended to
go and it fucking sucked
well once you leave my piece of
shit luck i woke up later than
in china due to the fact that
my alarm clock was not set nor
did it alarm because i did not
set it and so i was getting
i think we're gonna stop there because
scott did include the the phrase i
forgot what you said yeah so i
think that's a good indication that it's
time to move on let's try let's
try it again i'm gonna maybe a
sentence or do you wanna move on
to a different game no no no
i'm let's do this together yeah yeah
okay the sentence is
my cows it sorry i'm i also
think you're not supposed to necessarily add
onto the story i think you just
need to express the same phrase right
with as many words as possible okay
my car won't start
me yeah good
my car the one i drive every
day won't start
unfortunately i found out my car when
i drive every day won't start
my car automobile if you will seems
to be under the impression that it
is not supposed to start today
unfortunately this little thing over here that
i like to call a car you
know the one i drive every day
you get it it's under the impression
that it is maybe not supposed to
turn the engine over today aka starts
i firmly believe that of all the
misfortunes that could befall a poor benighted
souls such as myself falling downstairs eating
an apple with a worm in it
ah the rain on my wedding day
sure the absolute worst the unspeakable if
you will
has just occurred today
my car won't start
we the american people understand one thing
about ourselves we like to wake up
every morning work hard
put our children through school hope that
they better us in some way when
they grow up and unfortunately that's not
going to happen to me because i
cannot arrive at my place of employment
today because my car well it won't
start
these are the times that try men's
souls
when wishing to leave one's home too
fly free explore strange new worlds seek
out new life and new civilizations to
boldly go and no one has gone
before why that requires some form of
conveyance and the formic fans i have
a car well it done did me
dirty this morning by
by not doing what it is supposed
to do i e starting but in
fact doing the exact opposite of what
i desired it to do which was
to not start
i think paul wins if you want
to try to go longer
alright that was long that was long
i was long that was long i
was small and more yes give all
the intense
i read a book today
i read the pages of a printed
book today
in my thirst for knowledge i will
admit
i opened up a book and read
it just today in my never-ending quest
to know more about the world around
me and those who have come before
i opened up the creased pages of
a printed book today and read the
words written thusly
you know my mother always used to
say that i was born with the
curiosity of a thousand cats and i
think this tale will bear her out
just today i saw a book and
said i gotta know what's inside that
son of a bitch and so i
opened it and page by page i
can see
assume the information within until finally there
were no more pages that was just
today
i started the day having read no
books and already the day i would
like to have read a book so
for that being said i
are you on the bachelor that ah
i pulled a book from the shelves
of my home and i opened the
book and read each word until it
formed sentences and paragraphs paragraphs into chapters
chapters into a full story which i
then
heartily consumed and now have the knowledge
of within my brain
to thine own self be true a
wise man once said and i agree
with that wise man because if i
can admit anything about myself it's that
i like to read books and coincidentally
just today
i read and i don't want i
don't want to stress this too heavily
but this happened within the confines of
a twenty four hour period
close parentheses
i read a book
this is going to be tough lauren
can you do if and when we
saw somebody justin bieber beat paul of
this game because this is how he
does stand up
i once saw a poster that read
reading is fundamental and the de mental
part was crossed out leaving just the
word
haha next story knowing that
i just say it
try it for myself i
took what is known as a book
teaches you
this page has been together by thread
on the spine glued into a hardcover
and printed with the title on the
front so all who see it must
know what is inside
i opened page one and began to
read and my eyes could not stop
going from left to right
the words written by this man who
came before me right
right this piece of fine literature and
as i closed it at the very
end i thought i have simply read
a book
well no today
oh very good i think it's a
tie wow yeah i a really strong
but i also think a lot of
a lot of that was ah we
were getting outside of the one sentence
structure maybe getting into short story if
i would have started webster's to find
the book yes yes oh i was
about to do st paul tells us
ah alright well that's it for another
episode of this silly ass show called
threesome we believe it we need it
we thank you for listening ah don't
forget we got merch guys if you're
in the mood for some merch it's
out there including shoe charms thanks hey
seriously
i pray those shoe terms have been
restocked by this point oh i hope
so by this point i hope it's
their error airing at this point it
is if they're talk by the by
the time people are hearing this i
hope it's because they've sold out a
second time i mean to me yes
really need that so yeah you can
get ah shoe charms for your crocs
or any shoe with holes of
yeah you'd get in any hole if
you if you've got old ashram button
you know take parachutes you already have
and punch some holes in it yeah
with a hole punch the hole punches
was for that's when you bought it
also makes you crash every day that's
right um also we got t-shirts and
we got if you buy something that
you don't use every day
a throw it out because you don't
need okay you can just rent two
on the day that you use it
don't use every day just throw it
out so yes so if you skip
one day of using a thing into
the draft naive to trust and you
just rented
i need to read rice today sure
all right all right all right child
ryle right
see you guys next week thanks for
listening ah d
a
uh