ah
is that good or bad
oh no to your voice where i
do a little moan at the end
oh is it good it's good for
me and it could be a moan
of pleasure could be mode of pain
because there's this whole razor teaches us
there's such a fine line wow because
he likes those pins in his face
she's painted his face i know those
pains in your face don't you govenor
you're acting a roy pinhead make you
got pins in your head in it
a day in it welcome to welcome
ah three i've never done this before
my name's scott i'm scared yeah yeah
shower scare scary this welcome to threesome
i'm paul f tom i'm lauren f
lapsed and i'm scots proper scott proper
plot puffer wow wow oh my shoe
the show oh it was like me
i need your mouth into a coup
here
or what you are so don't ever
say oh yeah the words coming out
of his mouth i'm confused do you
understand the words that are coming out
many of them mature is one of
makes ringtones why why i don't know
but i hear it all the freakin
time i also maybe made you say
because i was thinking many amateur why
were you i'm the guy you don't
just
oh did you yeah if you're just
focused on her oh we're doing three
am okay now remember he's the problem
it's him
um so he loves many the mature
he does is it a ringtone for
specific person that isn't a meme in
need a mucho or is it everyone
who ringtones it took a text tone
into ring to i don't even know
who it's just loves it yeah i
mean you should sound like someone forum
i certainly hear but
ubc do you think he's texting himself
so you can hear it he definitely
doesn't wanna listen to the song you
do he doesn't have a spy or
use that do you use that um
approach of texting yourself things i don't
do that i don't like for like
a picture i want to have but
i've never do it for like remember
to do this i don't do it
for that i
sorted using the reminders app really there's
a reminder yes yeah a lot yeah
yeah well it's actually actually very actually
is it very early it comes with
the iphone and it's actually what's a
sanctioned like iphone app it's sanctioned it's
been blessing curious because it's a great
bother yes on nobody's listening right elizabeth
lane's podcast
husband andy o'shea listen psycho candy and
i love it it's like a kidney
and he was taught to do list
app that is supposed to be really
great for help he has a d
d and so supposed to help keep
you on track with certain things knew
the second you think of something you
put it in the i don't know
why the app is better than just
making a list but it will maybe
it has reminders you got a jackass
why because i
i make a list and then i
don't look at it yeah wow i
don't know i did it just last
night what would you would you put
your list i made a checklist of
things that i have i had a
show last night with um amy mann
and ted leo congrats thank you congratulations
paul that's so amazing you great paul
yeah thank you so that's all you
wanted to say yeah
yeah goodbye finally this is a sign
of prefect oh this happened to i
made a checklist of things that i
needed to bring with me ah for
the show and then guess what i
didn't look at that list and i
got in the car yeah and i
was about to pull away and i
was like i remembered one of the
things i i was i got cocky
and i was like i remembered all
the i got all yes yeah
you can't you can't do that no
one but it's like what's the why
did i make that list if i
wasn't going to look at it for
exactly that reasons like right before you
leave out look at that list so
this used to be so important when
you like all the years life that
we were this is putting on like
shows the hbo workspace and all that
comes yeah making the list of every
prop you have and every single thing
and he was so important i remember
a particular performance where someone i was
performing with did not bring a huge
thing on the list and he was
just like well this is why we
make the lags um drive us is
why we make it drag them to
fill
so the memes are no more oh
i knew we'd get to it we
have to mention it because we didn't
know that obviously when we were recording
that hadn't happened yet they haven't warp
was having a meeting debating while we
were having our i don't write minnesota
during that this is all fake by
the way i think this is for
the super bowl
it's not real scott don't say that
i'm so sorry we were like whoa
hey isn't it am i dumb is
it fake you're dumb
i legit thought it was real which
part mean it was real that they
got rid of the characters oh no
this is all a super bowl lead
up to super fun or so wait
hold on no and i'm pleased audience
know that i do have brain cells
and i do use them regularly but
when i'm scrolling about other things when
i'm currency instagram i just kind of
i take it you know and just
like i let it wash over me
and i just move on why would
you think about it for more than
didn't minutes i was like oh they're
done with the mascots yeah my wish
but they said they were having my
rudolph be their person and then to
me that people i think people would
be like happy because people were so
upset about the mascots so now you're
saying that they are going to have
all of them
come out in the at the wheel
and i'm gonna do a dance to
liana who wants
that's what i am saying janet jackson
will be reinstated oh you saw that
and you am eating super bowl ever
oh wow want to point to pronounce
awareness emeritus yeah the super bowl is
not on my radar but also i
also am not looking for pranks right
now i'm not looking out for well
it's tricked by a company that's it
happened at the exact same time that
they key
killed mr i howie but to say
the peanut thing i remember i didn't
i knew people were saying it was
this is michael yeah the one i
bought i was like okay he's actually
dead he went to his funeral yeah
i thought was you mourned oh and
i cried like i put good cloths
over the mirrors i wrapped my garments
i i like ah i just i
think the super bowl sunday by the
wow and by this the super bowl
is this sunday so we'll find out
so i'm glad that we're talking about
this being released or as we're supporting
release okay oh that's good do you
think the super bowls this sunday well
you know i don't fucking know no
one actually started watching basketball
oh i've never go i thought they
would talk about it they're never gonna
let i'm missing though by not rolling
policy sport twitter because i think if
i was on twitter i would have
seen everyone but the lion here the
super bowl you stupid and i would
understood
and you know no i just think
i think this was like oh people
are talking about the memes thing we
have this big campaign with maya rudolph
coming up let's make a big thing
out of it um and instead it's
like this weird backlash where people are
taking series we will see because i'm
seeing a lotta articles about it's weird
that people are invested but i guess
they are like when you
don't care about a thing yeah it's
impossible to believe that somebody does something
stupid yes i find it weird okay
here's something i've been noticing turn me
up at my headphones actually don't i
just turn myself up yeah you have
to do it yourself it's right next
to you
um but what i find what i
find very strange is like that there
are fans of things like scooby-doo who
are so protective of it that they
hate like versions of it like a
new velma vs exact cool op sun
like there's so much hate for apps
on it yes she doesn't she's working
she might as well spit and squeeze
face that's awesome what's it called of
the elbow oh great and it's just
like it's not the official scooby-doo movie
or anything like you know how used
to when the superman movie came out
i was like oh yeah hope it's
good i hope it's good and that
turns out to be good yeah but
it's just another random like scooby doo
show of of eight million scooby-doo yeah
licensed properties that will be
out there yeah eventually you know like
why get so upset about look i
defended the imams last week and i
stand by that i hope that it
comes hoping you would
help the company you're going to show
up and i hope they all do
dance i think they will do this
and i hope it's toronto i really
hope it what if what if it
comes out and no they're never mentioned
again in my rudolph like eats them
at the beginning of the commercials like
they're dead now and then i just
bored for the actually that's funny and
i think i think it's alert when
i read that they were going to
replace them i felt
bad for the people who had just
gotten those jobs as the mascots but
i liked the idea
amber ruffin
see another introduce the character and then
a week later they're like we can't
do it yeah everybody's mad yeah and
then we have to appease these pen
then i thought who are filled with
a yeah but i thought my doing
like a candy commercial is actually really
refreshing and there's something sort of throwback
yeah so just holding a bag of
my name is something shows up the
commercial for yet it is refreshing i
like i like the m and a
a candy commercial where someone just holds
the bag and they're like yum and
then they eat it and then they
eat it yeah that's all we need
why are we spending millions of dollars
on these super bowl commercials yeah
or are they saying yuck whatever they
feel yeah sure honest yes johansson honest
not to my taste but don't y'all
anybody's you can tell ya anybody yum
oh god only yuk yuks and only
yum yums yeah so somebody says i
think this is gross you have to
say i think it's gross that you
think that oh you to make them
feel bad yeah that's do i actually
have
thank you
that makes you a sick individual look
i don't know we just helped hype
up the commercial and i know i
know sorry we're talking about mgm's again
we've already done the taste test i
didn't leave their commercials on this book
we had a symbiotic early beta shell
and help m and m's grow their
power i just thought it was a
topical thing and i guess it's not
dope
do other candy companies make mgm's they
just call them something different yes yes
absolutely are not as good by the
way why should they be as good
okay you know what should wait do
you know what is really good wow
but they're expensive but they're they're a
sort of caviar healthier note vote yeah
it's like a healthier alternative to an
eminem i guess
unreal oh yeah i've always seen me
make peanut chocolate covered peanut whatever with
a shell it's essentially a peanut menachem
and it's really fucking good although i
do think the whole ten hours of
like um virginia it's made from all
plants i don't know i don't i
don't know why it's
better it's just better ingredients are like
less dies or i don't know what
the fucks natural guys yeah i follow
this account on instagram called the food
babe
and she's always like food babe so
hot she's it's just him saying that
oh hey it's like the daniel craig
grazie toby weekend yeah exactly yeah he's
always posting in the commercials roman ems
daniel craig dennis miller oh dennis miller
yeah oh yeah and one eight hundred
collect and what did i remember when
he called monday night football yeah yeah
yeah making a lot of show
owing saying to me i hope he's
okay i think he's doing grid gets
protect him at it yeah um anyhow
um this account tells you like all
the bad things what you should eat
instead i mean sometimes it's kind of
like okay okay and other times you're
like oh that's good to know okay
so i had pizza last night what
should i've had it's not a salad
it's really yeah it's not like that
it's more like
like this if everything they just go
salad if you're buying a apple this
granola you should know that it has
these ingredients that are actually really synthetic
and bad you should buy this brand
because it's all natural or whatever and
so i'm like you know taking a
lot of that in right now it
is true you cannot take
a you know you can't take at
face value of a package that says
this is all natural and healthy and
shit which is so crazy that i
could literally say all naturalists absolutely yeah
it's like yes um but i remember
i used to think that trader joe's
was somehow help helping i see i
thought that too i think so because
it's
looks like the way it looks because
it looks yeah farmers market or something
granola e about area i thought that
for a long time and then eventually
i was like this has more calories
than everything else i can't just eat
these peanut butter cups yeah which i
like for staving off cancer taste mers
should be healthier because you bite your
toe i'm so sorry the dark chocolate
peanut pie happens in my cabinet
right now so good yeah yeah and
the brownies that they sell like the
package brownies really delicious yeah oh of
course i mentioned them in my famous
werner herzog review of trader joe's parking
like ah which ah lately i've been
getting a lot of people ah on
instagram tagging me with other people doing
werner herzog impression
yeah and i want you to know
i'm not interested
real werner herzog tag me all you
want yeah big werner herzog i'm doing
my own it's funny yeah you don't
want to be influenced by them yeah
that's what i'm worried yeah they're so
much funny or you don't want to
steal don't want to feel john salley
yeah i actually am hearing an echo
on myself i always hearing that on
you i hear you guys fine turn
every turn all the
headphones down other than yours that was
easy that was bad that's that's probably
the um what is the special recycling
then you have here ah these were
trashed now ah cool op god this
is it's so this is your trash
now it's so-called the yellow side say
i can't have it is for trash
half of it is for recycling it's
so fucking cool
wait yellow means trash what does yellow
i gotta learn going over to investigators
have a recycling thing on by the
way put the ah put put this
down this is what's picked up at
the plastic recycle plastic recycling recycled paper
and paper recycling oh wait so it's
both recycling oh here's it's not what
i want sorry you
edu you ah do it to the
left to do it to the left
do it to the right that's the
way you block out the light did
that fix your problem by the way
the funny okay thank you honey
well wait yeah we have just received
word oh that now we have to
start composting our food way i saw
this on cigarette them let's look in
the grey shirt super bowl thing so
this is
this is the thing that would be
that would get me yeah if they
got me with compost oh really
it's about bud light yeah they'll be
good we got we got a compost
or for it for this express purpose
but it's the cars making kind of
a lot of work it's a lot
of work but here's here's my my
issue with it is that the recycling
they already admitted that they the danger
would always i know i know yeah
so what are we so yeah why
are we
data first well the composting thinking is
actually very important because no no i
think composting is important i'm saying why
are we what is the lie why
are we lying why are we saying
recycling is not real oh it's not
really going there i've always like one
of my making this f and we're
still doing it of course yeah plus
i don't have time in my trash
for all the recycling so i need
the session basically it's just two touchdowns
yeah
just giving you a task sorting out
for fine but it's it it also
with the gases right now that all
i'm posting is a house's composting will
help a lot but it's you also
have to teach everyone how to do
it you can't just say no by
the way you pose here's here i
should not say composting although some people
in my neighbourhood have started doing that
we have to put it in a
separate bin we have to pay
put it now in the green bin
which is where like the mannings yeah
eaves and shit and so but then
that means that you have to get
another little trash can in your house
yeah to put eggshells and you know
it also is an existing injury yeah
i think it's carrying flies this stuff
they have stone like they have said
that they're gonna start giving people
these specials are good if you want
anyone to do it i have a
friend who has a big com poster
in her yard and like huge like
a big old my car thinking it
kind of like roll it's like it's
as big as a table for the
listener lauren pallotta tape measure and she
just ran around the room yeah it's
like this big that's big yeah and
she like you know has a little
worms in there and all this activity
going on and they yeah they do
stuff to it they put worms in
there yeah yeah why it helps it
like become dirt worms help look i
don't know i think you know i'm
gonna be able to plant whole grain
make things dirt that's what they've always
done that's what they always shit dirt
so
whatever they eat even if it's like
the two bikes don't really kickass yeah
because it's nice it's like diamond i
just hated was a big line to
shit in it i just like the
one in school wasn't that big day
but i do a worm i don't
remember i remember doing that we talked
we talked about where was i taking
the frog i don't remember the one
i did the worm in the frog
you just did rog you did well
i love the frog
and baby pig you did a baby
pig you know i cannot discuss can
i say in a way where the
roar of the wurm the frog and
the baby yeah we are who ate
obviously are the worm
i'm the pig yeah you're a little
europe his pig you're a frog because
you're kind of like you wear a
suit yeah yeah you're like michigan jarrod
i'm ah okay because i'm like i
have a great personality but people still
want to kill me they think you're
filthy but you're actually very good
the little curly dick
stop hey guys curly dick and curly
tail yeah tail is curly can you
believe too much crowded laying around when
he moved yeah i was all curly
knows god was just like he was
so pleased with himself this guy's like
that yeah check this shit you imagine
god going through all those details like
if you believe that
god created everything yeah like all right
got to design this pig
i mean he got it right so
that's what would happen if you started
just drawing random stuff but wouldn't if
your supreme being i just i hope
are at some point i would make
our listeners i would make all these
things work with fewer parts yeah like
you just don't need as many things
in the world know you know anything
like they're always like oh the bees
do this blood should just flow it
shouldn't be your mate a heart for
it let let these lippies do the
pollen shit and all that but like
take take away the stinging
like i know it is you know
how much does it help do you
do you know what i mean yeah
hell like oh it helps the poets
well i hate them some would say
like okay well all the bees if
they can't sting they're the people trying
to get them then they will die
out so it's a natural yes it's
already been happening so yeah so given
so so what give them to stakeholders
and suddenly the summer know what do
you do this summer stung by a
bee this summer does oh i know
what you did this summer because you
might be yeah yeah what robert you
did mention i was actually it was
splash mountain where the where he gets
stuck in the yeah and then they've
spaced will be there like hey this
is go
going away let's have some fun we
put in real water when i was
opening robots and a real fox where
did you get stung dear i've already
told that i'm not telling it again
of the okay you're not telling it
again i got stung on my hand
and it was in downtown disney waiting
to go back to the park for
night is why i tell you don't
go down there i know you set
it down daydreams
very bad bad things happen down yeah
i tell you i got stung by
a bee when i was searching for
my friend's dog yes yeah yeah i'm
a hero and so amaze either two
good things at one and i sacrificial
i didn't stop either like i went
ah and i cradled it and i
massage it but i kept calling out
that name to see
oh my hand is healing oh yeah
pretty guys right isn't it crazy how
the skin just comes back together and
like heels and it's just because because
miraculous like she went yeah yeah like
it's weird having stitches and like looking
at them and being like you're keeping
it together yeah sometimes i trip out
on and i'm disgusted by the seal
that you're
mouth makes your lips coming together yeah
it's airtight that it's just like sometimes
you can't think about that kind of
stuff yeah sometimes you can't but sometimes
you do say those sometimes your brain
just wants to be nested i have
yeah oh hey oh we maybe we
take a break okay and we finally
have something interesting to talk
oh it's one of paul's prompts paul's
prompts oh my god okay let's say
bregman let's take a break when we
come back paul's prompts an astounding new
segment on three of them this is
big because i've never seen paul's eyes
light up like this i bet anyway
guys know
sure what's up but you were just
right didn't see it
i like your mouth we'll be right
back
and we're back okay alright paul's type
of job you paul's prompts yeah and
here's the jingle
if you're not late you're on time
i say if you have a friend
then that's the way to be happy
in your life it's paul's prompts i
love that really saw some something would
run with prompts but nothing does unfortunately
prompts
pump see clumps clean i mean drops
ghazal yeah examples
okay pause prompts there what is this
how do we play or it's not
a game yeah it's just you talking
okay it's me and you like good
day it's this is me saying something
that will prompt conversation hey i love
hey he'll tear it though
there is an intersection that i have
to go through almost every day intersectional
it's a very broad intersection and it's
unpleasant because it's like it's too wide
and you feel like there can be
there's the potential for an axis four
way stop it's too wide you you
preferred to be a little more
narrow to get in there
okay so ah pretty much oh you
know it's the it's the rule of
okay you get here before me didn't
you go wait is the issue here
more than more than four way stop
or it's just too it's it's too
wide it's four-way stop but but how
many lanes just single lanes
a single lane yeah yeah yeah but
it but the cars are so far
away you can't tell who got it
and how to know you can but
it's like it's so wide that some
people might be it's just like people
are not sure who goes when okay
it seems hey so one time i'm
at this
this four way stop and it's my
turn i know that it's like you
know what you and i start going
into the intersection in this woman coming
from the ah perpendicular yeah either the
left or the right of you
she's coming through she starts coming to
and then she honks at me right
and i stop and then she goes
through and she's like cursing at me
through the window yeah and i dry
wishy like like the curse and thinner
or anything no she couldn't touch my
face okay
and so lucky i drive on and
i'm like that sucked and when i
get to my destination i have a
text from my friend todd cooper yeah
who says
by the way you were right oh
and lady that lady was wrong he
saw you you had to write whoa
he saw and it was first it
was very valid oh nice guy but
now i'd never think of that every
time i go through that intersect you
think of the texture you think of
the i think of golden i think
the whole you think of every test
and so your question i think of
everything everywhere all at once yeah i
just watched that do you have a
is there is there a location that
you that you have to frequently be
at that prompts a memory you know
time you get it happened so much
wait let me think i have to
think of one but i do feel
like my brain does that a lot
yeah why yeah
i think that every time or you
know what i think i once you
become conscious of it then it's cemented
you know whatever sometimes what i'll think
of is what podcast i was listening
to when i was in this area
like i will remember part of a
podcast connected to i was driving here
and i was listening to that and
then that was what they said is
right here right and it's like that's
not anything it's completely worthless
um i don't know do you have
one on top of your head i
mean i've had some and i know
i've talked about it on the show
already so i've had stuff like that
things like this go into carl's junior
and remembering the time that i someone
was offering me like all the leftover
fries that were in the
in the fryer because they were closing
and i thought he was trying to
say like hey would you rather have
these fries to replace your fries i
was like yeah these are actually kind
of cold and he was trying to
be nice and i said these are
called and so anytime i go into
cross like about okay but that's also
like um random girls remembering any crows
during mis step that you made
i have like those like haunt me
differently i think this is yes this
is remembering something good this year i
didn't knock you were someone curse it
doesn't matter that there that it happened
at all i thought i was doing
good and answering your question but now
you've told me i was bad i
think you're great i'm just following them
to trust i know why am i
in
trouble i don't understand i'm following the
prompt and i'm trying to parcel out
what the prompt is asking and i
feel like you're off base so i'm
wrong okay alright well noted by the
segment was a flop well no either
a segment why do i try oh
no no no no no no no
no i'll never have a segment on
this whenever i hear pulse prompts again
i think of
this you're never going to hurt it
the only time it's ever gonna are
you trying to forget this stuff though
are you trying to i don't care
because you go through this intersection a
lot i'm worried that you're gonna constantly
be rethinking of this one memory and
it's going to suddenly overwrite some of
your memories that you should be remembering
till all my memories are just yes
every time i remember places another member
is i'm worried about this it'll eventually
i don't know what my birthday is
i don't know meh whatever thing i
was at this intersection was very wide
ah i don't know i mean like
oh you know why else it kind
of i realised why
it also that intersection freaks me out
because i was at it was a
similar intersection where i had a horrific
car accident where i totaled my wife's
car because i did not see a
stop sign i blew through stop signs
so you so you're you told one
story where you're in the right but
you're really also stop at la
nah let's stop signs to make up
for that so true
it's so true how many stop signs
are worth a car so they make
these stop signs octagonal octagonal octagonal octagonal
is this where the podcast has gone
and it's so easy you will notice
these things paul sure we get back
you'll be like wait that sign is
not square i gotta look at this
thing right and yet you just were
like oh octagon who gives a shit
and you just went right through it
is that subspace relays the story yes
stop sign that it's more what lauren
is saying what you're saying although i'm
not just coming your theory that it
was obscured in
some way they also make them read
so you can be like well that's
not a white sign or a yellow
sign this is a red one i
wanted to paint the wrong shade of
red you'd be like wow no that's
not real it's a little french club
was maroon i don't know that i
would take a lighter copper like blood
red bull in a way
you think blood looks like copper lead
tastes like copper tastes like like cup
but but it's brown it certainly blood
is brown not really red that's when
it dries really true
you gotta admit it's a beautiful color
when it's coming out of you oh
it's beautiful rich and i are merely
my hand it was always so flying
nah you're getting blah oprah just gives
everybody yeah so you you just did
not see the stop sign what were
you going to say it i think
i was reading a book but a
book of my left
i remember once i said to go
love she's like oh this is when
iphones were just coming out and she
was like there a lot of studies
that there are a lot of accidents
caused by people looking at their iphones
and i was like it's just the
same as reading the newspaper on your
way to work it's just like why
you shouldn't be doing that either are
you doing that occasionally like if you
had to go
go to ah like santa monica and
you're stuck in literal like votes before
four or five one one entertain there's
no movement you will stay there for
forty five minutes just barely moving so
everybody hurts so yeah i think that's
when people used to people like putting
their makeup on and doing all sorts
of dangerous changing their clothes danger
it's assigning jennifer beals takes her bra
off thunder's switch that's what got her
the audition etc got her the role
she's rather do that at a restaurant
okay we have this written into a
script
no she did it in the audition
in so adrian lyne cast her in
the thing and she put it into
the thing she did it in her
audition yes she was just like kind
of bold move i wouldn't think to
do you should do it in your
next audition yeah you're broad i'll just
show to the camera she likes thinking
like what should i maybe i should
take my bra no i think she
what's the scene that were happening and
no no this this was like just
in a meeting i think it wasn't
even like that's actually her reading order
she she was just like talking to
to him and just like was changing
and kind of did that and he
was like it was a different time
gotta put this in my moods also
this was her first big thing yeah
nothing like to be an unknown
can be true and you're you're like
i'm gonna go for it i i
don't think of it i don't think
it was i was actually just so
you're mischaracterizing it she was not a
plan know i'm doing that on purpose
oh why though it's it amuses me
to do so
i like to think of jennifer beals
with a whiteboard before this meeting wanting
this thing yeah she's practicing to call
raleigh i love her she i'm all
caught up and oh really generation q
and i'm not but you love her
is it was great we had a
lot of bet in this season and
a nice finale ending that was a
good story for her do you know
what i want to rewatch
and the theater when it came out
and i it's not a good movie
from what i recall the bride oh
the bride of frankenstein yeah i've heard
of that and sting plays doctor frankenstein
oh i was just hearing that he's
a good actor where i'm smart less
why because they're talking about bano his
bottom was on the show and they
were like bano
he probably be good actor like stings
a good actor meeting other singers who
backed okay actor for sting i think
that's probably where the bar is he
was great on ah studio sixty of
course
no he's like finding quadrophenia because i
don't know anything about it but then
suddenly he's like hugely famous and he's
just sting i don't know what's going
on your wrist paul ah having a
quick one off the wrist um my
wife and i are engaged in the
hunt for some important document that october
and i think she may have fun
found them oh yeah joe biden leaves
something in your garage my friend hunter
let me guess is it the mariehamn
of irony looking for um the title
to my old car oh because you
need to give it away give it
away give it away now i know
that was the kind of thing like
sometimes you you just go where did
i have the four site to put
this summer
more logical and i recently had that
experience where i was like hey the
thing i'm looking for is in a
folder labeled that thing and i was
like that was amazing and i actually
need to go in my file cabinet
and do that with it all again
because it's been a year since i've
really organized we do have a big
binder that's all like just important documents
yeah ever now that you're going for
if when
your house is on fire as a
win by the way because i know
shit i have going to be setting
it on fire until later this oh
yes why would you do that will
you tell me when it's like saying
she's been in here
i don't watch them i want to
watch it on but then i wasn't
in the mood to just like not
paying attention absolutely is one of those
you have yeah moody but it's it's
great it's really great he alone ah
but ah he loves many of them
so i ah i are talking about
mike i didn't hear yeah like
no so it's enough if we were
a stand that said he likes know
i heard blow level look like expansion
mature were you talking about mike because
i just wanted to say that as
well you're just guessing if i was
talking oh i'm not really lead to
you oh my guy talked about this
off mike but mike loves always that
wasn't on the notion on the show
no it was on the show
show was on the yes are you
sure i think it was this show
sucks yeah oh i know wow i
hit my hand oh good so far
why are we doing this oh but
here's the okay so here we say
it wondered in that that i'm binder
of important documents okay but i'd
already taken it out and put it
with the rest of the old car
stuff but that's dangerous it is dangerous
because then i misplaced it yeah oh
wait so you took it out you
took it out of the important place
she'll sure be hair it to prepare
to go to your line or all
of the things that you're gonna need
here's yes exactly and then you misplaced
it and there any smaller folder
her and then misplaced the smaller folder
but luckily danger zone my baby came
through yeah you know i do think
like there's something about do we do
do you feel like you misplaced in
the house do you think you've got
move to play something else okay because
i find i have like a system
in my mind for like my bills
and things like i'll get mail and
i'm like i'm gonna put this right
here and until but yeah michael
put it in a different pile and
i'm like yes that's the power i
forget about everything i don't yeah i
don't like i have to go on
a hunt for my pills huh tons
and i put it on my pills
high for my bills high mermaid titles
hot i don't like like putting something
of mine somewhere and then having cool
up move it some oh so where'd
you know what you know what to
tell myself somewhere else hello yeah so
like i put it in the same
place every day because i cause i'll
wake up in the morning i'll have
my
coffee and i'll have to take all
my pills yeah who are they like
exam your bake on too and it's
not like cool ups i'll take my
poor i could ask her do what
i do do my podcast ah a
little
gleb still sleeping so it's not like
i can ask her hey where are
my pills so i'm so like i
open the cabinet door and they're not
there and i have to go fuck
now i have no one from the
cabinet that's you know they're there they're
in a different place in the cabinet
or so how big is this cabinet
medicine courageous no no no in our
ah
ah kitchen a kitchen you mean a
couple in the cupboard so the cabinet
i call a cabinet yeah
anyway okay so so we put somewhere
else and then you're like i don't
know my pose by nine i won't
wow
i enter werewolf build
it feels for now isn't that great
yeah yeah nobody should be wearable fitting
no that's really nice it's not critical
but it is treatable but no yeah
you'll have to take in you have
to take nine a day if you
want to be a werewolf you still
can be ruled it is your choice
to see your dog
and if your doctor is werewolf then
you can go see my mother-in-law by
the way will flip my mother-in-law had
a car accident on our way to
visit us lie on our way to
the airport was totaled the car this
is a couple months ago oh god
total total the car
and i i heard her on the
phone talking to the insurance person i
guess and they're like well can you
send us the title of of the
car and she was like it's in
the car and i audibly this is
all one speaker i audibly heard the
person say well you're not suppose
used to do ah that's really tough
that's a tough one though because ah
i feel like
you need someone to tell you that
yeah it's not a given about this
type of thing because it's giving registration
don't you think somebody always does though
probably i mean i was told at
some point i know but i'm saying
yeah i don't know who told me
or why i know that yeah but
like there's to be an official guidelines
to be like license registration slash i
think in your mind you can also
kind of
oh title is registered yeah i don't
know like there's an beneficial guy and
he doesn't see my car things go
together in the car yeah anytime you
buy a car there should be a
guy there and this is his only
job yeah and he says hey by
the way dear don't put that title
in the person who sells you the
car so congratulations and they ring a
bell in their deaths and then this
gentleman comes out and he looks impose
oozing but but yeah he's dressed really
far as anybody's yeah like it's friendly
it's like a friendly nutrition lord grantham
and yeah and he comes out and
he says just a reminder don't keep
the title in the call yeah and
then smoke bomb and he's cause you're
gonna run now he's still got he's
still there after the smoke we just
ootd over yeah and he says who
was that like come on i know
it's companion oh you just took off
his bow tie
who's that i was just thinking about
magic trigger saw on instagram oh my
god magic trick make noise and a
magic trick also um just lucky you
didn't know the word but just justin
willman who is a magician oh sure
magic magic magic drinker yeah like his
show he um posted this trick and
i was so it was the kind
of thing where
just went i just have no idea
how i need it of course there
were cameras and someone could say well
that person is in on it and
it was awesome i don't think so
um i choose to spend my time
here that that's how all the david
blaine specials were done like we're floating
off he's floating off the sidewalk you
know you've received that oh yeah where
it's like
fake the camera looks down and he's
like floating and and everyone around him
in on the sidewalks are gone whoa
but they're all actors are paid they're
not only i think are they actor
you could be an actor you can
be paid but you got people
they're either their life kids they're either
actors or they have to film it
so many times because so many people
can see how he's doing it that
the few times where he's doing it
with the exact right angle where knowing
i see that he's actually standing on
the ground right um they go whoa
and they're like oh thank god we
got one
i've wasted so much time yeah i
mean i'm sure a lot of stuff
is phases which i just you know
i assume i mean sometimes bags aren't
real magic know i know i don't
think that but i do think some
tricks are being performed in real time
and my person doesn't understand how it
happened but i also think like the
david copperfield making the statue of liberty
disappear is bad because it's like
like hey we're gonna do this and
he has a crowd right and then
it's a simple camera trick right they
do and the way it was i
saw it explained is basically like the
cameras pointed at the statue of liberty
they put a curtain down yeah they
move the camera like slightly clockwise to
a part where the statue of liberty
is
not they raised the curtain and the
statue of liberty isn't there but the
whole crowd is going whoa but they're
just the wires yeah they're liars the
crowd can see the statue of liberty
is right over there where that where
it's always seems like a waste of
time do you know i did that
the pretty much the same thing at
the end of my last comedy special
but i the statue of liberty disappear
i did that from nobody cared somebody
said dave cup fiore did that and
i was like oh yeah didn't we
didn't hear that because somebody told me
yesterday i ah i ended the special
by um ah the idea was i
was going to throw a smoke bomb
down on the floor and then disappear
and so it was it was
all done in post but i had
to coach my addi mr grantham much
like lord grantham i coach the audience
to say like oh pretend i've just
said yes so here's what's gonna happen
i'm gonna jump back i'm gonna go
like this because i didn't actually have
a smoke bomb right um and then
i'm gonna walk off so that the
camera can get
and yeah and so i need you
to ah you know your your clapping
is the end of the show and
then i do that and then you
have to be like slots like stunned
yeah and then take a beat and
then give me like huge applause and
did everyone just applaud right away no
they did they actually did it perfectly
thought i can't believe you got an
audience to actually
early but they were your family up
there study they did i think we
did it one time they did it
they nailed it it was great but
your whole audience was like oscar-winning actors
oh yeah oh let's i yeah full
disclosure my old buddy d day was
there
who's daniel daniel c o o like
de de de de de pretty much
said every day that de de de
de de de de da de di
do you want to talk about your
and then he retired from acting because
of that trick was involved him putting
so that he had a woman look
at a deck of cards she chose
one in her mind you know the
the card
yeah he put the whole duck in
between her two hands very tightly and
put the whole tech in her hands
yeah and then he reached in and
like grabbed the card and it was
the proper card right and she was
like wow and then he shit wasn't
that i'm pro and then he goes
yeah it's pretty crazy because there's not
even any carter and then in her
hand
just a brick of glass
so i was like that's amazing
however you're doing that is amazing i
don't like i don't know at all
how that's possible that someone wouldn't feel
their hands too and a lot of
tricks involve that yeah with someone holding
something and then it is something else
and i'm like how how did they
not feel tiny shift in their hands
timelines tiny mimes as well yeah mice
and mimes it's sort of cool
that that majority minds tiny minds oh
yes well they throw the cards into
tiny tiny minds i just met their
barrel were stupid yeah but i think
it's cool how magicians like refuse to
share their secrets do i think it's
cool things rude i it's kind of
cool because it's like if i could
just know right now i don't think
i'd be that happy as a person
you're right
no but i'm a happy person because
i don't have and so i think
that they're keeping me like not that
i do like that idea like that
and that was penn and teller's whole
stick but yeah that magician not telling
the masked magician the mathemagician yeah my
souls my oh yeah i must have
told my penn and teller story before
oh what that i went to vegas
and saw them that's great
yeah and which one talks yeah penn
jillette he lost his voice oh yes
yes yes you did tell me it
was one of the funniest things ever
because what did he sound just like
huh he was like which is really
higher can you help out here be
like he'd be like his voice would
go really high that he'd like sorry
sir
and then he tried to get it
back and then hey yeah yeah that
point is canceled the show it was
wild but i was on gummies and
i was having yeah it was a
great show i don't remember it i'll
actually forgot they did magic because i
was so focused on wow
what a great act he comes out
with a crazy voice yeah i can't
talk you it doesn't help me get
help at all which is like kind
of amazing sorry yeah
we'll be right back
and we're back and it's time for
three cheshire and this was submitted by
elliott masten and matt our producer says
he thinks this one's good yes matt
producer says he gives it a seal
of approval so if you don't like
it approval take it up with
matt yes if you don't like this
reacher we want you to tweet at
matt apodaca yes and say what were
you thinking your three churidar is off
my friend no don't say anything negative
to matt he doesn't need that in
his language say nice things to him
yeah yeah and try to sing to
us try to say a negative thing
in a nice way
look if you can't say anything says
at least nice things to madam producer
and just write just tweet him and
say like i think you're doing a
good job or you're yeah at least
it's nice
like the back half can be a
slam get it
as long as it's nice up every
day wanting to back up all right
well this one is called musical chair
actor yeah and i know you know
thing
fill the snipes like almost had fans
their listeners don't go reapers listeners is
moreira
yeah um we're being very sassy today
everybody alright so what this is the
game mostly it's what we start within
an improvised scene where we're all improvising
okay i'm yeah i guess we're not
playing ourselves we can be whoever true
i don't want to play myself
oh to be a charter right duh
so we do one or two minutes
how long do you think we do
this you think one yes okay one
minute to last couple minutes feels like
an eternity when we're doing a game
and then we switch roles and try
to do it as accurately as possible
to the previous time oh so you
really had to listen to each other
then we switch roles it's up again
it's gonna be really
tough and try to do it as
accurately as possible then we switch back
to our original roles and try to
do it and try to remember everything
that we said right okay this is
gonna be impossible okay i said ok
okay i don't know i would say
buckwheat wilkin pinup
woke up and nub and none around
places alright here we go and start
yes hello am i in the right
place i think so this is the
filthy alcoholics meeting yes hi so i'm
sorry you look too clean oh i'm
very dirty inside did you take a
bath before you got here no beth
was given to me oh i see
okay dios man servants know some people
tackled me and made
we take a bath oh okay that
makes sense well next time just try
to come in a little a little
more dirty if you could we'll do
alright alright everyone we're going to have
to have our seats now we're gonna
have our seats now yes everyone grab
your seat alright and if everyone could
please take a code i was in
charge
they seemed like i was joining your
that's i'm am i just the doorman
i thought you were just the first
program to have to speak to the
therapist about that afterwards um my name
is mike just a doorman to you
my name is my name is yeah
not gonna tell you because this is
filthy alcoholics anonymous so um oh what
an ominous phenomenon dude dude
due to an ominous
yeah well no can you imagine if
that was two minutes eleven so jesus
christ alright we're going clockwise meaning this
way paul
yeah so or i'm gonna play lauren
okay okay oh you play me yes
here we go okay
hello am i in the right place
yes filthy alcoholics meeting oh yes that's
what i'm looking for you look a
little too clean oh yeah i was
filth here before
did you take a bath or something
about those given to me oh you
have man servants or um something like
that okay well could you try to
come a little dirtier next time i'll
work on that please thank you alright
everyone have your seats oh excuse me
everyone take take we're gonna have seats
now have you have your seats now
and we and you i'm not
in charge of this meaning you're and
you're in charge of this meaning i
thought i was oh wait no homo
yeah i'm in i'm in charge you
just are just the doorman you know
you're just the first person that that
everyone sees when they walk in well
we'll we'll talk about this in therapy
later anyway
everyone know you're the first person i
saw that's what i say
anyway ah let's get started okay with
ah it ran out but it didn't
ah well even even get to your
whole name what was it the what
was it remember ominous oh right right
right okay alright let's switch again okay
hi i'm paul oh yeah i'm scott
yes i didn't go off
okay here we go that's what i
said about my career
hi am i in the right place
oh ah you're looking for the filthy
alcoholics anonymous meeting yes so good oh
yes oh you do look a little
clean oh i'm sorry i should be
dirtier i clean i had a bath
early oh you had i was given
a bath oh okay do you have
a bunch to man servants know people
tackled me and then put me in
the bath yeah that sounds right
yeah um alright well yeah next time
if you could just be a little
dirtier and we'll do okay okay everybody
please take a seat take your seats
we're gonna take our seats now ah
yeah okay i will hey take a
cookie
we're going to start the meeting okay
um i thought i was in charge
here so this is a little weird
doesn't didn't it seem like i was
in charge oh i think that you
maybe you're just the first person i
saw when i walk in okay well
we could talk about that in therapy
all right so this is filthy alcoholics
anonymous phenomenon
like mom today what did you say
obama this obama imam and nod to
data and i'm not and it didn't
go off again get a better phone
you get more in oh my god
coming for the phone i've never heard
you so vitriolic i'm really full of
maybe i'm not pressing start okay well
that would be
problem i swear i am but i
just expired it okay here we go
we have to do it one more
time as ourselves and don't get back
on your phone when you look at
your phone look at my phone because
i'm looking at it because the timers
i'm trying man i look at my
phone you look at your own phone
when i look at my phone here
we go get my own phone okay
it's definitely going guys
mainly replace oh the filthy alcoholics meeting
ah yes you look a little too
clean to be here oh well i
have had a bath oh you had
a bath while the bath was given
to me oh you have manservant or
something yeah it's pretty dirty some people
tackled me and they put me in
a bath of that makes sense well
next time try to come a little
that's our thing absolutely right everybody we're
gonna have we're gonna have our seats
now we're gonna have our seats now
yes we are please have your seat
alright we are going to start the
meet i thought i was in charge
everyone take a cookie didn't seem like
i was in charge yeah you were
just the first person i saw i'm
in charge so i don't know why
thought i was in trouble thought that
but that was wrong so we have
to talk about that in therapy later
but
um for one could just um oh
um and leading the meeting and of
course my name is my name is
my name is my name is an
ominous because it is an ominous meaning
and so i will not be sharing
my name and and an ominous do
dude you need to know now yeah
perfect perfect wow
wow and that's how you play
we should play one one yeah we
say well i was trying to say
wow usable chair actor sure okay let's
do it again and this time let's
do big characters okay some movies silly
or like switch it'll be so silly
here we go crazy when everything is
be something different
hello everyone
hello eat today oh you're late i
know i'm late but i'm sorry i
had ah a huge thundercloud erupted right
above me okay so you're both bradley's
parents right yeah of course ridley very
i've read lee's whether i read lee's
other mother that's great a level lies
bean couple too
we're not a couple oh you broke
up yeah we are a couple of
lesbians obviously but we've got a couple
of ebola okay that's bad we hate
each other it was good dude i
think that's actually coming out in bradley's
behavior it certainly is really oh it
certainly is really
if we go to bradley woods and
you see why we broke up she
sounds like an idiot she is talking
about me like a bud here right
everyone because we wish you weren't here
we both wow i never see anyone
walk in on a pogo stick but
that isn't how it was autumn
right so wait i'm playing lord no
i've no idea so your plague be
okay okay thing i was paying less
attention yeah alright here we go harder
than doing the the broad character makes
you less it really does alright okay
we go where scott yeah okay okay
ooh is this the right play it
certainly is
all right everyone thanks for coming to
the meeting
i carry a big thundercloud was also
you're late you're always late ah yeah
big magic wow okay well now you're
here alright ah yeah we got to
talk about brad yeah i'm trying to
get struggling you know or whatever you
are we have to talk about bradley
behavior
you are you're the you're his eyes
mother yes and i'm his mother too
oh so i love lesbian couples are
actually not lesbian couple we broke good
we are lesbians though a couple of
lesbian oh but yeah good you're not
together i think
oh yeah you're not together
yeah guys what are you wasting away
but having a lot of fights oh
yes and i think that's coming out
and badly behaved yeah it's really hard
ah alright here we go ready and
i'm sorry i'm late is this my
place oh yeah
how did you sound yeah wow yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah you were here
yeah i'm glad you made it you're
like oh there was like thunder cloud
over my head oh okay well just
following you around or something yeah that's
making me late to everything okay yeah
riley's parents yeah ah i'm bradley's mother
and i'm
mother oh you're a lesbian couple oh
why not a lesbian couple we broke
up yeah we yeah we actually hate
each other now yeah we find a
lot so you're just a couple of
lesbians yeah we hate each other
well that's coming out and bradley's behavior
oh it certainly is is it
ah you forgot it certainly is is
it
ah i imagine bradley is really taking
now we're back to the original oh
my dear rachel yep here we go
forgot hello everyone are late oh i'm
sorry a big thundercloud with following me
around it just erupted right above me
okay we need to talk about bradley's
behavior and maybe principle obviously
we owe you both his parents yes
i've rarely mother i'd readily saw the
mother oh i love a lesbian couple
oh look good on a co know
we're a couple of lesbians okay robocup
yeah we hate each other yeah well
actually that's coming out and bradley's behavior
it certainly is is it you can
see why we broke up
yeah you're really stupid
i forgot who bradley was i never
seen one coming on a pogo stick
yes i'm on top of a pogo
stick do duty but other data do
a nominal doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
to toto to wo e seconds love
ah
ah okay ooh and that's how you
play musical chair wow we really shouldn't
thank really to the person who submitted
that thank you elliot matt yeah and
you oh yeah thank we love you
eliot i want to thank you having
the number one
injury lawyer in los angeles yes we
see your bus ads everywhere i'm really
massive and i fight for you if
you would like to follow us on
social media you can do so at
three am usa send three cheers and
emails to streatham usa at gmail dot
com and please leave us a voicemail
at four two four two five two
four six seven eight or
easier to remember heg claims eight
um accurately with the most because it
sounds like the headline claims eight yeah
e i am witchcraft explosion that actually
is the easiest one has claimed eight
yeah because haha im imho was like
not it was also too many letters
and your channel yeah yeah yeah um
if you
i wanna hear ad-free episodes you can
do it at stitcher premium and the
show of the show and cdb world
dot com and remember on tuesdays where
three visiting on the tube that's right
yeah putting out our old episodes in
this very feed and you can hear
all of look you're going to be
with mori anyway so why not listen
to a podcast
further yeah it sounds great thank you
we'd love to hear you listen we'd
love to hear you liz love to
hear you all we love to watch
hulu so get out of here go
whoa alright we love you bye bye
bye
uh