three
hello hello oh
like a pixar character
welcome to three dam my name is
lauren lithgow my name is paul f
tompkins scott are we officially freedom now
yeah yeah we got one whole episode
debating the name which we already knew
as threesome we keep referring to it
as that i guess it's like in
the calendar is there another three-time on
podcast dot com
podcast stuck that's what it should be
podcast dot com hi everyone welcome to
the show can you imagine imagine a
million every single person whoever will know
or show kiss cam we guys start
that week yes guarantees
um laura oh let's explain what the
show is because i think this point
at this point episode eight we should
let people know if they're just visiting
there starting with this episode okay
i'm paul this is laura and this
is scott we're friends haha we we
we we worked together a lot and
we hang out together a lot enough
information for you out there well in
case it's not here's a little more
okay outwit we outplay outlast out with
it how is it that was the
fourth signal thing
on survivors yeah with it oh is
it you have to tell a secret
every single person has to tell their
deepest darkest secrets like before they're handed
a check for which is an embarrassing
secret oh okay yeah like one time
i wet my pants in my car
and he did and that sounds that
sounds true you know what i probably
have i've thought about it but you've
thought
good idea listen bathroom really bad i'm
just like what am i going to
do i think on a trip to
vegas there was you know that big
stretch of desert where there's nothing there
was you know you just pull off
like who gives a shit yeah but
but i but i think they're easier
for us scott than it is for
laura through cho i remember um when
i was in girl scout camp why
went there one time to
two minutes later girl scout camp view
the original demo now just came out
anyway go ahead while i was in
girl scouts and we went differently camping
for one weekend in cabins i don't
know what the situation was but i
um sounds like a normal cap situation
to go i'd rather go to girl
skull lamp
me too and okay outside for some
reason that's what is making me feel
like i don't remember all the details
about this like when i was eight
but was outhouse like outside or oh
no i was peeing overall like a
log oh and i i remember i
plant a frog over my jumped up
and had no sentence of like the
angles right oh that was like ten
ten and i'd never done that before
was that the first time you figured
out like where your pee goes yeah
it was like no i'm gonna inspect
my vagina
like my dental mirror out
no i was like oh no and
thanks been telling me what i smelled
like pee for the rest did you
like hide them hide them under the
bed i don't remember that but i
would say started because i was just
thinking the slow day i speaking up
hiding things i had gotten that same
year when i was in fifth grade
i got like all of these books
about angels out of the library because
i was very
curious about them sure and i believed
in them and then the book started
to scare me so much that i
hid all the books in my closet
oh and like didn't return them for
a long time then i was really
worried about the fees it was turned
into like a whole thing so you
were scared of of the possibility of
angel i like you gloss over that
you believed in them i was very
curious about them because i believe in
them and
i had such a belief in them
i want to learn more than i
learned too much i felt so scared
what did you do you remember what
it was that you learned that i
just felt like it was too real
like it was almost like ghosts or
something like it just felt really really
scary that was weird there was a
weird period in this country where people
talked about angels
well that show like that show books
about them touched by ne yeah yeah
it was like doctor angel would have
yeah doctor angel medicine angel today
angels really are the angel medicine angel
angels really are the ghosts of the
sky but there was highway to hell
they said that where there was an
angel yeah with michael michael landon oh
and there was michael the movie about
an angel oh yeah yeah he was
like a slob angel yeah he was
nasty did he go up against the
snob angel
yeah slot vs gamer yeah
get your real the snobby his angel
um so yeah it just it just
was something where it's like oh shit
they're real and they're all around there
watching me but i would hide things
often like that i didn't want to
deal with right i had like a
sandwich that i didn't eat and then
i put it in my closet and
then it was and smell green dust
by the time like it had just
been like so much
golden wow it was just like you
you didn't want a ticket to the
kitchen i like telling them that i
didn't eat it in my lunch or
something and so i just because i
was your height you're hiding the process
of eating it yeah i understand did
you forget about it yeah and then
i found it and then i was
like oh no baggie yeah but it
was just the most disgusting what were
their worms and stuff it was just
a
peanut butter sandwich sos really just like
covered in loss oh wow being in
the closet idiots and i also thought
that my ah dead great grandfather was
in there a lot of times in
the closet yeah i remember that's why
you put the sandwich in there it
was all just all scary things i
this old man i like would be
in bed and just
if my door was open a crack
i just like i could see him
in there because he only did i
mean oh jeez you saw his dead
body yeah did you kill him yeah
ah yeah i know i was like
four when he died and so then
i was the first flick funeral that
i remember to and then so i
remember seeing his body and then and
my family took photos you know like
that was a thing i don't they
took is that is that proper degree
that used to be common practice those
sooner all to send to our greek
relatives okay um which is very weird
interesting stand by the greenback doi smile
is this i i met somebody recently
who was a friend of a friend
we were at we were all at
dinner
together and the person had to tell
the waiter i am deathly allergic to
olives which i'd never heard before popeye
got divorced during the break one of
those like don't even do it right
huh don't even bring her yeah sure
yeah the conversations to your famous impression
but she's so she's like she can
eat olive oil but you can't she
can't touch the outside of an olive
or as such she was ordering
um a glass of wine and she
said could you please tell the assurance
sneaking a bite by the way she
she she apologized she said i'm i'm
sorry for what i'm about to say
because i know it's very annoying but
could you please ask the bartender to
wash his hands before pouring the wine
if he's handled any olives right and
um yeah she said ah i'd never
heard of this and she said yeah
once i'm i went to degrees
nice and i went into a restaurant
and i told them i'm allergic just
can't go to great yeah the person
said what the person why did you
come here huh why didn't you go
you wouldn't be able to do anything
like everything would have been touched by
that at some point every every shite
olive it's drenched in olive juice
juice wow
yum dr oliver that isn't all of
doctor olive
dr oz
i like dr oz speaking of which
your first lunch pail wizard of oz
i have remember that from last episode
i had a marvel superheroes lunchbox did
you yeah
like going to lower the super ooh
are the superheroes on the fantastic four
of course all four of em all
for oh they all they got them
altogether oh wow you care if i'm
going to pose for this lunchbox that's
like when i saw busta rhymes and
he brought out the entire flip mode
squad i couldn't believe did you carry
your lunchbox in your hand and wear
a backpack or did you
put it in your bag i feel
like i honestly don't remember i think
i cared because i think i was
proud of it i don't think that
i haven't it was like a little
suitcase yeah you didn't have a backpack
yeah it was almost like you're a
businessman yeah briefcase or do you have
a book strap no i don't i
think i think we kept everything at
school oh i don't think we had
homework until
will ah this is pre giving kids
homework when they're seven so i didn't
have homework till junior high i think
which is why which is why my
grades my grades were great through elementary
school and the minute there was homework
i started getting work until junior high
i don't think so i remember i
still like it was always homework yeah
know that
we we would do stuff like you'd
get a project or something you had
to do at home occasionally but it
wasn't like every single night you had
to or maybe had to read a
book or whatever i hate projects i
hate project i grew up in them
so
the idea just looking out of the
window watching me as a whole group
oh lordy mahoney shut up ah the
worst part about a project i ran
out of lyrics i knew by the
way that you have i was trying
to help you that you ah have
to help you like the
for sites like joanne out your schedule
so that you do a little bit
at a time i would always be
doing it all i would do it
all weekend before of course it was
hell horse yeah there's you know when
there were like six weeks yes but
does it does any adult ever do
anything with that kind of foresight that's
the thing why are they where are
they even giving kids stuff to do
month
in advance it should be like it
shouldn't be like this is a real
world you get something to do that
you have to do all weekend and
cram for it but it should also
just be you they give you an
assignment like hey the end project is
this thing so this week you've prove
to me that you did this part
of the project right and that would
actually train the bram in to to
do stuff like that yeah yeah
you're right i had a i had
a muppet show lunchbox and i remember
there was a thing where if you
were a guy and you had a
female on a lunchbox people would make
fun of you and say you were
in love with that person and i
had muppets and there was there was
one side had miss piggy on and
everyone
was like you love miss piggy you
want to kiss her you wanna marry
me did you
i did i loved your sucking i'm
hoping i run into her isn't it
strange to think that there's someone who
is sexually attracted to that puppet yeah
yeah i mean they're adults so absolutely
you think that they are then attracted
to frank oz as well like yeah
the voice i bet they i bet
they have to think about it but
do you think they're also attracted to
yoga
huh yeah they're definitely attracted unit and
grover sure i mean yeah there are
people with buffing that ish both finger
he directed it
i don't get it franco's directed bo
finger lauren okay now i get it
thank you
yeah no i mean i guess they're
like puppet fuckers out there yeah for
sure yes there was those furries we
worked on a show with puppet show
did you ever hook up with anyone
not that anyone saw
when everyone else would go to lunch
what if what if you want to
get a little hot dog i'd say
one hundred just like a minute what
if you were attracted to puppets but
it couldn't be if your own hand
was in the puppet it had to
be someone else's hand puppet i'd be
very difficult that's a very hard line
specialized prostitution where it's like i need
somebody who's really need a prostitute and
diary and you couldn't bring your own
own puppet either like you have to
bring your you have to bring a
puppet yeah you say you say to
the the sex work sex worker provides
the puppy yeah like i'm sorry it
doesn't work if i bring a puppet
gene used to it i also need
to see the puppet in advance to
see if it's gonna be that i
am attracted to yeah yeah la yeah
let's totally shop it
to pee no puppet you're the puppet
boston to zip up but nope i
think you're seeing what they look like
i like i'm going to be very
careful about how i answer this ah
um from what i understand no
like you meet them outside in new
i think i think there's a lot
of like you are told the person
looks a certain way or you see
a picture and then they show up
and it's a totally different person oh
you think there's a lot of that
yeah yeah yeah i guess it depends
on how much money you are paying
and i think that if you are
if if it's like la weekly the
less you pay the better you get
and really because they're hungrier for
but i mean it's like if you're
if you're paying a lot of money
like high-end call girls or whatever i
don't know you would probably be able
to order very specifically this is what
i want and you'd be happy with
i had a i had a friend
and i'm sure they have like pictures
online and yeah now it's probably more
yeah me saying all this ri
minds me i had a friend who
is interested in purchasing the services of
a sex worker a friend and then
i okay here's the thing and then
i had another friend who worked at
that on the side as a sex
worker as a sex worker and so
i might i was like oh to
my friend i was
like oh let me ask my friend
how how these transactions normally occur and
as i was talking to my friend
i realized she just thought that i
was asking for ice huh you know
huh but i purely was a middleman
look them up no no not them
up oh you just got the information
you just wanted to know like how
does anyone ever even do this yeah
so
i was so i asked her i
was like how does someone do this
and she gave me the whole step
by step which i've been passed on
my friend will really enjoy this
glass it's getting harder right yeah
it seems i will say it seems
like a nightmare to me like just
someone you don't know but that's what
some people like i know what you
mean i was watching some like documentary
thing about um was the bunny ranch
where it's like all the like and
then these this there was like one
story of this they following this one
guy who
was very socially awkward and like just
didn't have any thing in his life
like that could sunni intimacy yeah right
and so he had this relationship with
this woman at the bunny ranch and
then he would see her like once
you're satisfied all his money because it's
really expensive and then they would spend
the whole weekend just like fucking i
guess and then like doing activities and
stuff and just hanging
out and he just wanted to hang
out with like outside of the ranch
um probably just in the room i'm
guessing but then like it was he
talked on camera news because it's the
best time of my year and like
it was just yeah no i don't
i go back and forth like i
don't know whether it should be illegal
or not
i think people are if the woman
wants to do it then it's fine
isn't it weird that you that the
they the women are mainly arrested for
it and yeah but sometimes there i
mean there are a lot of people
doing it against their will yeah exactly
yeah where it becomes complicated because you
don't know
no if it were legal there would
probably be less of that yeah yeah
you know that's well that that's the
why you legalize anything is to regulate
it i guess yeah but i also
feel like it prostitution is not as
a thing that i don't think that
i would ever use but makes perfect
sense to me you know yeah it's
like
it sounds good to me
prostitution it sounds good to me
it's the new campaign
just like regular people there's a catholic
housewives prostitution it sounds good to me
do you think the commercials would get
better for it
did you see boats like this call
leo's calls which is like so come
on we can make better commercials
there are so many bad commercials still
being made for like just local companies
were like how did everyone say yes
was good or that person should be
the one on camera do you want
to find kind of i this it
makes me weirdly happy is how the
end of like infomercials is
is still the same it has remained
unchanged like that blue screen yeah with
that without the white and yellow yeah
oh and a little box yeah it's
it's remain the same forever and there's
something really comforting to me yeah yeah
you think like it would have evolved
where people would just start using comic
sans yes something but somebody's like no
this works this works it's it's suitably
yeah well i bet i bet what
happened is and this happens in sketch
comedy a lot you put up something
that's slightly different and you're like no
it has to be the normal thing
yeah otherwise people aren't going to get
it yeah yeah yeah i mean like
people people need to recognize it so
quickly that you need to do this
it's gotta be
oil blue screen yeah the the numbers
and yellow yeah all the other types
in white and then there's like yeah
i'm sort of hazy glowing box around
the item that were showing i bet
the editors have like tried other things
like this looks better right and you
go no you don't recognize it as
a thing you should call you're scared
you're fired you're fired no puppet you're
the puppet no puppet no puppet
no puppet you're the puppet oh la
raza or lorin tell us about chicago
what do you want to know you
love it you know what i just
found out that i'm really excited about
what is that lean away went to
my high school really and only two
shoes were at school the same
debt she created the shy which is
a new show on showtime so she's
on she's she did the the very
famous master of none episode about coming
out giving oh let's not talk about
that well she's about her and she's
amazing better um she's just really talented
by what i've been like admiring her
and like i listened her on a
couple podcasts and just kind of following
her and she younger or older than
you she's two years older than me
okay and i was so would you
have been in school at the same
time i know and i my friend
told me that and i was like
that's amazing and she's on um npr
fresh air talking about moving to evanston
from the south side and how it
was like saved by the bell to
her when you get to the high
school rishi y
listen to the episode she wanted the
drama people that you mentioned were really
good at it no i didn't i
don't think she was in theater because
i didn't know her and i pretty
much what new although yeah but um
i could get in these like oh
watch them i guess um i could
be wrong but i don't think so
but um i just thought that was
so cool my school has a lot
of
amazing people that came out of it
so i feel like that was a
really good one to the end do
you do you mind just has me
oh well good for you to love
attention do you hope that like you'll
be known as ah as a recognized
alumna alumnus you know i already am
recognized as you did we talk about
this how did they invite you
they invite you back to do a
show or yes and i and there
is a wikipedia of notable alumni um
and i look at it my school
every so often looking for and see
who's been added i think but yahoo
also went my high school who i
just learned what i was looking at
it audrey niffenegger who wrote the tie
time traveler's wife which is a book
i love there's a lot of people
at m is this time it was
at a movie with dom gleeson movies
not good okay but the book is
amazing okay but also because i liked
the book so much maybe i didn't
like the movie i don't know if
people who didn't see breathe the book
like the movie
my crush though who's your crown now
guy is he really yeah even in
celerity slash i never seen that you've
weighed any of them know you've never
seen a single star wars but i
think i saw the one with the
with the e walks when i was
little
and you're just paul
never seen a star wars movie i
heard you've never seen star wars bosh
never she never see stars you know
she shows you just not interested i
just don't want to see that yeah
okay so you
you're not interested in in sports not
real i could go to a sport
you're not interested in star wars want
to see that what do you what
do you what are you into so
much more out there like what like
like mamma mia ashore i've watched that
i watched like every live musical ah
yeah but that's just like something i
do at home for fun
one when like they were coming on
we were talking about the things that
you do for fun what are you
watching movies joue foam the things you
know talking about watching a star and
go to the sierra
by now
featured prominently on three wishes here's the
things to buy huh here's the thing
i am listed in the notable alumni
for my high school's wikipedia but my
name is spelled wrong wow does it
link to your actual page and no
it does that's been going and well
mine is annoying because it says i'm
most known for being
are you there chelsea which i don't
think is that huh so that's not
at all what no one knows what
he wants to say podcast super stow
but i'm yet to use any show
that people are aware of what it
is maybe our idea of a crash
ah maybe wants to go change that
why change it everyone's awesome i'm alerted
to someone sends us to me that
someone in congress or something keeps changing
the comedy bang bang wikipedia yeah someone
that's crazy angry yes yeah because yeah
any time they there's a member there's
some member of congress or somebody who
works in a congressional office who's updating
the comedy bang bang because
because why says who did it like
because i think when you yeah because
it like says i think anywhere it's
from any time congress if somebody bad
governments yeah well we're yeah yeah let's
shout out to whomever donald trump needs
rand paul probably steve king from iowa
we all listed three people we ate
ah the dude below would you guys
ever get into politics no no no
i feel like i've said i've said
so many but that's that i mean
unfortunate matter anymore this is a bad
thing to bring up but al franken
and all he had to do was
basically just say like i was a
comedian i said some things
things that were offensive that i found
funny at the time i i'm a
serious person now i don't i don't
stand by those comments i don't know
if you did something like that i
don't know true because now we're in
the social through so many look i
was a comedian i grab people's asses
ah i thought it was hilarious and
it was everyone liked it everyone liked
it i think
they don't talk about we are in
a weird time where like so many
celebrities are becoming these people that like
everyone has a known past yeah yeah
so that i think you could get
over i mean when i was at
the white house they were saying when
i was there they were sent bowling
i really did i
i'm the fucking i'm the only person
here who hasn't been in the white
i a strike i had my first
points i i didn't want to go
i saw i didn't go the first
bowl the first ball i bowled was
a strike and i was like well
i can't get better than that so
i just didn't continue that's cool um
but no they were saying that they
they were gonna invite they they were
having an event with you
two people and there was a certain
bano youtube oh my dear boy they
you got to go because your vlog
all your haul videos
hey guy
unboxing video ah i just got a
new barkbox for my dog
we're just gonna pack it here okay
so this is ah this week
so they were having an event for
youtube stars and they they mentioned a
certain youtube star that they couldn't invite
because judy pie because because of a
video they had done um and i
and i said to them so um
how does that work do you have
to watch like do you read about
certain videos they've done or
or they say anyone who who comes
here to meet the president we have
to watch every single video they've made
or listen to every single thing they've
ever done no way this job coop
used to have yeah they've lost of
time yeah and because they have to
make everything we say they have to
make sure that it's they're not putting
the president
someone who's going to have controversy or
whatever and i was like can i
ask you a question why am i
here and they said well the president
really wants to hear we just don't
bother with it
ah like thank god because i started
to get kind of freaked out about
it as i was getting there that
i would be turned away but really
strict rules because i was there for
comedy festival a bunch of people went
to go bowling and um and a
woman was turned away because she had
a
dui from like fifteen years before why
i'm the epidaurus yeah because i had
to go through a security check once
you get in the road to get
into the place um that was my
fear was like at the door they
would be like oh by the way
we just found yeah whatever it was
i saw that i was like geez
i had no idea they were yeah
yeah first of all why do you
care because that yeah doesn't really matter
what does it yeah what does it
have to do with anything i'm not
saying you guys are great know but
like yeah but you're not driving the
area of yeah i don't know you're
not like getting behind the wheel of
a car in the white house bowling
alley
it was a special day at the
y
i am going to drive cars and
bull okay hey you should watch if
you haven't is that david letterman interview
with obama and i haven't yeah yeah
yeah wanna see it was it really
um but that is my ultimate fear
that sort of like when i was
going to vancouver that time oh yeah
just turned away at the the actual
border i guess something i
i get so nervous about that shit
and i have nothing there's nothing do
you know what i mean yeah like
there's no but i still i just
like well order book crossing a border
makes me so nervous i had i
had a warrant for my i would
occasionally have warrants for my arrest out
there for years asia it'll be give
reasons to be afraid for not for
not paying a ticket right basically
it's really extreme and it turns into
like you don't pay it for so
long it turns into i mean why
have us pay it well i have
all the look you couldn't gamble at
vegas no no no this is this
is after all that i have these
theories about like you know how jew
accesses you know you don't support the
man giving no acs
excessive tickets and stuff are all designed
to keep poor people poor right sure
and it just compounds as as you
don't have enough money to pay them
it just compounds and they they they
can just basically like just keep you
down anyway so i had these i
have these tickets for a long time
that were just hanging over my head
for years and
they would go away at seven year
at the seven year mark they they
wow they go away but i would
just be ups just really nervous about
being pulled over for years at a
time yeah because if they pull you
over and it pops up your you
go to jail right now and say
and so for for five years stretches
some
times i would have these things hanging
over my head and then something would
happen where i would would get a
ticket for something else and they go
you have a warren you need to
pay this and then i would have
the money or whatever so anyway so
going to other countries or whatever i
remember i once went with andy dick
to vancouver he was gonna know boy
he was gonna romantic getaway huh he
was he was gonna do a qa
body death ray show that we had
booked up there and so i was
on the same flight and we were
we went through the airport we got
all of our luggage all this kind
of stuff and as we're walking out
someone taps him on the children says
oh right this way and we never
saw him again yeah i remember that
you were there you were there yeah
but hey knew who he was
was i don't understand they took him
into another room and kept him there
for three hours but so because they
knew who that was and whitley knew
it was coming because of who that
they they pulled him up that's the
thing i could never understand this flag
yeah why don't let not allow you
to buy to buy the ticket because
they would drag yeah yeah get there
to the border jangly yeah um do
you know what
you were doing scott was gambling why
by gambling was tickets yeah that's like
the action that would stress me out
so much to have that going on
yeah i would just i pay tickets
like the day i get them right
so well nowadays yeah yeah but at
the time when you when you're struggling
for me well yeah but i'm struggling
to load it every
every every ten dollars counts towards you
no no no i'd totally get it
but i would feel terrible heels over
good yeah i would remember once i
was pulled over with with cool op
i think and and ah it was
within a six year period or something
and i got pulled over on the
highway and i was like ah
i think i've gone to jail now
i say no well that's like a
little jail now
alright we need to take a break
we'll be right back
welcome back to three dom it's official
three-day that's a we are three duh
three duh entertaining about to say yeah
um you know my rest story right
if i told you guys know when
my girls this was you see
he this just going this is in
philly i was like philadelphia ny freedom
nineteen or ten na up
so are to have a conversation at
the three of us because any sentence
makes us think of a song
or to some other kind of interruption
sweet three people with the same disorder
really is trying to get through a
store sorry sort of good for broadcast
bad for i was either like nineteen
or twenty and um i used to
i had to take the um the
subway to get to work in philly
i didn't know i guess i didn't
know that philly had subways as we're
very modern i like some ways i
do i love this above i love
every day actually do like both
i went for a while i was
on a diet where i eat subway
sandwiches almost remember that and it was
and it like jared fucking pedophile and
i was i had some similar things
go out diet
yeah yeah but it it did make
me lose weight and scandal first of
all i love a scandal i hate
that he did it but i get
excited when there's some crazy ass thing
happening why guess it's it's the i
know what you mean is to one
lightness i can't believe we're living
watch the weirdness of the details yeah
this the subway sandwich guy that will
go and say even just like the
tonya harding thing like yeah thinking about
that my wheelchair gonna love when something
and we'll get we'll get to your
story and it's like a bug but
yeah i was obsessed with the o
j trial yeah oh year and a
half i watched that everybody now i
have been watching it but i read
i made the can
section the other day of all the
trump stuff of like being impeached and
all this kind of stuff of like
oh it's the same thing for me
is the o j trial where i'm
upset it's the opposite for me really
happy i honestly i dread every day
i've gotten into the habit now of
like what is what is it going
i know but for me it's the
same like new details i'm so excited
but it's gonna have the same outcome
you'll see like i'm obsessive only refreshing
twitter but not in an excited way
yeah i know it's like what's happening
what's happening what's happening now yeah yeah
anyway what's your subways i was i
was i was nightjar twenty i was
working retail and i was headed home
on the subway at that store yeah
amber nash hudson the bill
it's in the hats in the belfry
what if it was bats in the
belfry and it sold hats neurons like
you know you could've made it huh
oh i couldn't afford that be i
was going to afford i was standing
on the platform waiting for the train
i'm like jerry seinfeld when this back
when i smoked and i was smoking
a cigarette and i'd seen people smoke
on the subway before and so actual
car yeah well yeah i'd seen people
smoke on this before probably in the
late eighties
yeah okay and so i i just
lit up the cigarette and the train
came and i was like well i've
seen people do this before what's the
big deal it's it's so it's like
one thirty in the morning you know
right and um i said kind of
cool and you look like i was
dennis lee or airy cool i looked
like denis leary andrew dice clay i
had
had an attitude people thought i was
a rascal and so i get on
the subway with the cigarette and i
go one stop the doors open and
a cop says you and like gestures
for me to get off it was
the cigarette still in your hand yeah
yeah yeah okay so i or did
they know that you were doing it
and he was waiting for you
that couldn't be possible right oh okay
he was just already training just happy
doing an illegal thing
it's oh it's like get off i
don't know they have a sensor and
they're like someone's smoking a cigarette get
to the sky it was just a
horrible coincidence of wrong place wrong time
you think people get away with it
but you didn't know i thought it
was time somebody who's like so ladies
hardly entering the train and so this
cop tells me to get off and
he says put out the cigarette please
yeah off twenty
two positions in a one night stay
oh he sang the entirety of get
off
he did a little dance he did
a little dance now i don't own
ribs victoria so
so i got off and i'm thinking
oh great i'm gonna have to wait
for the next fuckin train and he
said he'd take you down to the
station
yeah he said he says step over
here put your hands against the wall
and he starts frisky it's not just
a ticket no he's he he he's
like do you have any needles in
your pockets anything i have to be
aware of any drugs on humans like
no-no and the whole time i'm like
this really happening he fucking handcuffed me
behind my back and takes me up
the escalator and i'm just like no
i'm like what's going on yeah and
i said let's go is this like
a yeah is this real arrest is
this real
zeus daga real rez mister officer
now it is like a sickness
and i said is this like a
real arrest and he said well it's
like it's like a parking ticket and
i said they usually put people in
handcuffs for bargain tickets and then you
just stared at me and then i'd
stopped asking question oh so i'm using
his power yeah yeah like discussing to
do this handcuff yeah yeah it's it's
like what the fuck do you wait
but did you go to the stage
can they put you behind bars took
me yes that's insane they they took
my fucking belt and shoe laces and
they put me in a hoe face
your shoe i was would you commit
suicide a lesbian of yeah i wouldn't
i mean it's all i mean that
was a good call i ah ah
yeah i was scared i was
like what is happening you know you
have to share it with the cellmate
know i was in this little cubicle
cell by myself and there was ours
or just bars yeah okay and then
and then like a little bench just
made just make it doors
are we better are we fucking around
with bars for well now i can
see out there it's nice share coming
in
bars are good but there were guys
there were guys in cell next to
me who were ironically they they asked
me for its garrett and please don't
bring that up yeah and oh they're
so there was a guy there were
guys on either side of good you
have smoked in the jail no just
so why were they
i forget they asked me for wanting
to barter i was i was the
middleman like they asked me to pass
something down to the guy next to
them oh and i think it was
and i couldn't reach them it was
fucking it was ridiculous how long i
was there for probably like an hour
must we sing this song how long
now we have to make really can't
do it
to yourself ah if everything you say
reminds you of a smuggler you cannot
say sorry you got it got it
that seems fair and yeah it's totally
fair so um i was there for
about an hour and then they let
me go um lead mind of that
post
oh old man river
wait she's saying lo oh i know
that's a low song
so there was a there was i
was did you get a court date
okay i did i did go to
court and this is insane the day
of my court appointment there was like
this like this massive snowstorm and philly
and i woke up and i was
like i'm never gonna make it there
in time and i went back to
sleep then they
they sent a postcard to my house
that said you have this new date
and you have to show up to
wish you were here yeah at that
point i was still living with my
parents just make sure the judge my
mom got the poster like what is
this and i said that must be
some mistake and i i later that
does that ever work it did i
totally lied i said let me find
what this is and i totally lied
and said this is what happened and
they got me confused with somebody else
and when our man yeah and
ok so then um i tried to
go to that court date and i
couldn't find the place and i was
like fuck of a thomas guide and
stuff and you know
wow you're wearing me saying i kind
of blocked out which is i was
arrested in jail for four years i
was i had a few cogs cocks
spas i told you about another episode
and i had to go to the
friendly police officer yes oh that's right
i had to go to traffic school
bee beep um what to do like
many
hours of it and it was horrible
but i didn't come away with i
think it was one would know i
do it yeah sounds yummy carby i
um no i think i had to
go for like two full days of
so like driving school weekend and it
was really boring and often and that
one word oh well i had to
go to court first i guess that
was part of
i like punishment but i kind of
garage we usually part of the punchline
i'm saying the school was part of
it okay so they sentenced you to
like ok well we'll get it down
to just traffic yeah but i was
i remember i was so scared i
went to call ya dad i totally
forgot i remember i went to court
once for one of those tickets that
i had and i ah i thought
it was just a
go by thing in the in a
clerk would do something you know like
stamp it or you pay it or
whatever and they're like okay just go
sit there in the courthouse and then
the judge is gonna call you up
i was like wait i'm literally going
before a judge right now on tv
my tv randy very scary um yeah
and so and and then the and
then they were
they had so many people they were
trying to say like looked speeded along
you're gonna make the judge mad if
you don't just say guilty yeah just
take just say guilty to anything yeah
they're like telling everyone just say guilty
otherwise you're gonna make the judge mad
because we have way too many people
so just say guilty and so every
single person pretty much would get up
there and just say guilty and then
the judge would cut you a break
if you say we're all the same
kind of and prophecy right yeah yes
so so they would cut you a
ne would save you several hundred dollars
i remember i think the i said
guilty and it was like a so
i think that warrants at the time
were like seven hundred and fifty dollars
or something like that and they they
got it down to one hundred norway
never and i was afraid one hundred
two hundred
was afraid they were gonna make me
pace seven hundred bucks yeah i didn't
have or whatever but no but but
i was just shaking there and then
one person didn't say guilty or not
guilty and the judge was like
you are usually sure you do this
because like yes i'm not guilty so
i want to say not guilty and
they had to set up a court
date and all this kind of stuff
but it just reminded me of just
how much the system is designed to
make you just like well i had
there last time i never knew how
much the monetary value of my infraction
and i never made
add it to the courthouse so they
issued a bench warrant for my arrest
and i i sweated that for a
little while and it's so weird because
on the one hand i'm terrified of
all this stuff but i think the
thing i was terrified to actually go
in the first place which led to
just compile yeah we're oh i know
now you're really in trouble we don't
know what's gonna happen
yeah causes almost paralysis fairly unknown note
that that had when i was younger
that was a big it was a
big thing for me it's always been
my whole life of just if you
don't know what a situation is like
it's tough to go into it yeah
whereas now i think you could read
enough online about certain situations like this
that you would go okay i think
i know what's gonna happen when i
get it but even like eve
and like driving to a place that
i don't yeah oh for oh yeah
and or something like that hey the
first time i go to a place
and i don't know the the route
yeah i'm like i have so much
anxiety about getting there in time not
getting lost whatever and then the second
time it's like oh this was a
five-minute drive you know yeah it is
but the first time it seems like
an epic journey those people who can
just
just go do something or talk to
someone they don't know or you know
anything like that or just confounding to
me yeah and i don't know why
that is i don't know i know
why isn't it about i feel the
same way and what is it about
and i don't remember ever being brought
up that way of like these don't
talk to someone you don't know or
like please be afraid are you thinking
of i'll take this one scott i
have
my cousins on both sides are very
outgoing people sides very very good cousins
both good says thirteen years family from
both sides
so they have that thing of you
could be at a bar with them
and see them up at the bar
talking to someone and you would think
oh they ran into an old friend
of theirs oh and it's a person
like it's a person they've never met
before i hate that like i it's
great i don't know i love it
another
girl
little i love it in other people
i admire the trait but i when
someone approaches me in a familiar way
yeah it depending on my mood it
really bothers right if i'm in the
mood i can like has anyone ever
approached you in a friendly way and
acted like a friend when they're really
just like someone who knows like a
fan or whatever that's what um women
like hey lauren hey
and then oh yeah your life they
say name yeah yeah we know ty
how's it going hey that bothers me
because it's just so familiar it's just
not fair because it sets up the
interaction you don't know what you're getting
yourself into yeah exactly um but i
think every single conversation anyone ever has
they should state their full name and
their staff their business yes i was
traveling with my
a dog over the holidays and that
was an invitation for a lot of
people to talk to me that i
did not sign up dogs are but
i was in them i was in
a good mood because i was excited
to go home and i don't know
i just wasn't a good mood for
both how did out of the dog
travel i don't do really well walking
about it on a previous episode i
don't think we did but she did
a really good job she was i
mean she was like
skittish in the airport but like once
i put her in the bag she
didn't leave me
skittish cat skittish so that was the
song you posted but
i think from that fucking video game
that that computer game oh yeah yeah
yeah and you posted something that fit
into the the crow yeah in the
bathroom yeah and then i had to
go look that song um i put
was you think one of my favorites
too good it was fun but i
was
just trying to understand the tweet it
sounds like got it um it was
a fun journey has found but my
dog did a good job but there
were people who would just like really
get into with me and then they
would be like oh and you're on
the this show and then said i'm
talking them for like twenty minutes and
security liners me where i'm like but
i was in a good mood so
it was good i don't mean
to sound like that it's just that
feeling of like normally i keep to
myself and i just go through things
so then i was like well my
dog really is everyone's top and then
people want to show me their dog
and so i ran into kevin on
the way home we are on the
same flight and weird he sit next
to me silently right now gross and
this is almost like you're on an
airplane yeah you witness this though i
had my dog and then this mm
man was like ah like really into
the dog and talking to me about
the dog a lot and then she
was like oh our dog is kind
of like that and you know whatever
just like oh our dog is part
chihuahua which my dog is but they
didn't look anything like and then he
came back with like photos and videos
of his dog after like he went
sit down for all things like walk
back to me like here's my video
of my dog
i'm like and it just i can't
not who's rolling over into videos of
your dog yes right after the fact
videos yeah oh would care at all
ever doctor in invitation to talk the
first dog i got i didn't realise
it i didn't really know that because
like i don't really
interact with other people in my neighborhood
with her so it's not really like
a thing that i've witnessed your address
i feel bad now because i've talked
to people about their dogs no i
think i think okay i guess so
it didn't really bother me which was
the interesting thing it was just like
i don't get honestly i shouldn't go
on that yeah we'll talk to people
about my dog that i would be
aghast at ever having a conversation with
like a black race come on
well then there was this man then
there was a man who did bother
me there was wearing okay and i
was sitting on i was sitting on
the floor like it was going to
be boarding times wayne owe anyone there
were no seats and so i just
sat on the floor with her and
then this man comes i mean he's
like talking about the dog and he's
like oh wow she going to be
she been on a flight before you
know all these ques
kitchens and i was like no but
i was training i was really cutting
it off because he seemed a little
weird and then he was like he
walked kind of was meandering around me
kind of like then like popping closer
circling kind of just like like i
suppose you're looking at other things and
then kind of talk to me again
and then kind of looking away and
kinda like and then he he goes
and i was kind of getting more
and more shut down because i'm just
saying i don't care about this
the nonverbal cue yeah so should i
give my number bookies and then he
came back to me with his phone
and it was just a wallpaper of
a picture of a woman and it
said i i just showing you this
by the way i'm not hitting on
you this is ah he didn't even
say like this is my wife he
didn't explain this zero
i'm not i'm not hitting on you
and i was like i don't it
wasn't what i was thinking but that's
fine and whatever i'm clarifying like i
just don't like talking to fucking weirdos
but yeah who have weird pictures and
when i landed in chicago i i
i ended up standing right next to
his there's a bag by itself of
course i should
i have stood by it but i
liked it and then it was his
bag if you see something standbys he
was underground talking to more people then
i realized oh maybe he just really
is this annoying right like someone was
pulling their kid on like a little
like scooter toy and he's like is
that yours or did you run that
from i'm like oh god you wanted
every detail about every person's life just
leave them alone
oh my buttons on the shady wasn't
really hitting on me he's just annoying
yeah speaking of planes can you or
did you ever fly on a plane
when people did smoke on them yes
i still think like crazy yeah yeah
yeah wellington slightly elites and samurai movies
made illegal oh i wanna say mid
nineteen nineties yeah i guess i won't
address i'm the first
time i went to um to london
my sister lived there at the time
and i flew on a plane and
sat in the smoking section and smoke
cigarettes like like a curtain could keep
fucking with smoke so nasty disgusting nasty
nice nice sitting outside at a russian
master
i'm just doing impressions of unit i
it's good it's good
i always sitting outside at a restaurant
recently and these men were standing there
smoking right next to the restaurant and
my friend i'd tell them to move
because i was so great yeah well
it's supposed to be what ten feet
away or something yeah and they were
just right there and i was like
don't you see we're all sitting here
and that just comes right where i'm
eating and yeah when i see someone
dress smoking while they're driving in there
they just sit in there and they
have
a cigarette and they they blow the
smoke out of the side of their
mouth as you're driving it it it
is crazy to me i can't i
am sure you smoke out there i
you know i'm sorry i'm told i'm
you know completely shocked the people will
let me take this because i used
to smoke if you smoke there stop
doing it yeah i'm just terrible it's
i'm so shocked razzie anyone would start
now
yeah that's what really gets me i
can't believe it's still around yeah can't
believe it's still it seems very arguing
it would just become really unpopular and
people would be like no that's not
a thing that anyone does well you
cannot lay it kind of is poor
people to like look down i it's
you see it so infrequently now in
l a fucking actors smoke i guess
you're right but when i lived it
stress when i lived in the midwest
it seemed like everyone did they all
did it in basements wow my whole
childhood like a lot of my relatives
smoking site and yeah my grandparents and
you know older generations ah if you
do it stop it paul what's the
book that you recommend people read the
easy way to stop smoking by allen
carr i read that book and have
not had a cigarette since wow that's
amazing that the book was their trick
it was part of a book being
the way people stuck on the bible
stop me from killing people suffering from
everything bad i want to do like
we need to take a break we'll
be back yeah we'll be back
hey welcome back hey welcome back a
wep a welcome hey welcome back hey
welcome back mon oh no oh no
oh no dodgy oh no dodgy territory
dodgy territory as the da da da
da da terra del rey
there's another toronto um welcome back ah
we're going in and now's the time
of the show that time of the
show where we play where we have
feature feature paul welcome to feature what
do you got paul i have featured
today um this is a little game
called there's a little game called pro
and now here it's fun tell us
all about mary who married you know
mister belvedere sounds l o j antutu
seven talking talking about mr belvedere sure
i feel like that's something doug benson
did so i want to make sense
that makes sense right away that brings
that up a lot mr belvin
we're sitting on his own ball ooh
ooh he did that impression but maybe
that's why you did that impression yes
yes don't know anyway
ooh press conference is a game where
two of us will choose a celebrity
so a famous person and the other
person will unbeknownst to them be that
celebrity and they have to guess who
they are from the questions that the
other two of us will ask and
are we trying to lead them into
guessing or do we want to
keep it from them as long as
possible i think we want to keep
it from them as long as possible
okay wow so also asking true question
asking questions you would ask of this
person yeah oh okay okay so who's
up first so we we have some
celebrities written down i'll tell you what
i'll be i'll i'll i'll be first
up you'll be first i okay so
so let us not look okay we
have chef kevin over here ah will
you show yeah very quickly yeah i
was playing a game online on an
xbox you play game i was playing
are you playing yea that's
an inside joke for us playing video
game and ah and there's an online
components i'm playing in strangers right and
i am flying a spaceship and i
get killed and it says you were
killed by chef kevin twenty seven and
is it this dude is not oh
okay some
other weirdo mothers she named himself after
our own chef kevin twenty seven he
was the first guy we are using
naming an online game with people who
knew you were you know know you
have an alias and what is her
name what does your code name i
will never really have in twenty nine
yeah
okay so kevin will you give ah
will you show the name of the
first one to lauren and i and
don't show us the others because we
will then know the answers to all
the others got it so good okay
you're just about to show every single
name to both of us can you
dig
i knew that you could
don't show the back of that paper
to me either don't show okay with
a banker or a burden me okay
yeah okay alright
must just ruin yeah okay you wanna
ask the first question yeah
yeah i mean so yes i have
time for question order i've time for
a few questions oh he's not a
reporter yeah yeah look in here yes
no i know her go go ahead
stretch um
i want to know
you want to know who's just asked
the question if you're a real reporter
okay
is it true you have look guy
this huh you guys go first okay
you're sitting on the game um i'll
come back you later excuse me yes
a person of non-specific gender that's right
are you a puppet
well no puppet
i'm no puppet
perhaps you're the puppet
maybe maybe ah no i am not
i'm a real person okay alright okay
excuse me yes gotta go yeah is
your suit really yours or is it
made for someone else
that's a bizarre question as far as
i'm concerned well i mean i'm trying
to be you just asked me if
i was a puppet and you think
that's a bizarre question
these ah these are my clothes and
ah ah what were you asking what
they made for someone else yeah i
are you asking my wearing someone else's
clothes they just look a little large
well um you know i recently had
an illness so i've i've said you
didn't die it's too bad i didn't
die question over here yeah sure idly
from the sacramento bee oh bud vase
jerry seinfeld was interested in buying our
paper i don't know if you heard
that rumor no
um why did you leave your shirts
on the floor of your bedroom
because in the present the united states
and i do whatever we guy were
you see the buffet thing i was
like there's no way donald trump right
out of the gate
i haven't done sorry ah within the
only name you wrote down yeah the
knows no one even person in the
world for okay good i e neck
so throughly so i threw me off
yeah okay them the money got it
i got it okay
hello everyone hello hello such questions questions
questions
um i hope this isn't a delicate
subject but you don't have a very
localized form of alopecia do you
no i just ah don't want to
have hair there interesting okay good question
over here question over here who do
you think the next person will be
to e got oh wow um i
think it's going to be cool join
your club
ooh well i you know i think
it'll be oprah um man who will
join my club yeah well that was
the question you just answered it thank
you my question i'll get a princess
you got your answer your question yeah
my question um
did you consider
other
ah ejaculate tory phrases yeah did you
did you did you did you know
that one seemed to be just the
exact i was good for you yeah
okay okay question over here question here
was it disappointing for you to have
to star in that movie with that
dinosaur
no you know he was playing a
good brand
um i am i know god okay
keep going you're going oh god
shah going over your question yeah
do you take showers or do you
still take those baths of milk
i'll never stop taking the bag beds
of milk am i question here questionnaire
your question here what does steven spielberg
like
m e t ah
no you're not what a weird answer
to my question you gotta e got
um he got it e guy got
it you got um wait who the
fuck am i quiz question like are
you just looking back now many years
later
were you maybe a little upset that
your boyfriend put on blackface yeah
i loved when he did that i
have a quick question over here i
teach over here yeah your breakout film
what was it do you think do
you think that people got confused by
the title and thought that it might
be ah a sql the prince's breakout
film
the color purple
starring whoopi goldberg yes that's right knee
yeah yeah you go goldberg yea go
back to all these questions
hey what did you mean by the
l because she's no eyebrow driver okay
and then it bloats the blackface thing
what's the matter dancer dancing at the
friars club when they were they were
coming work couple ten dancer whoopi goldberg
yeah he got over the friar's club
in blackface why yeah because it's hilarious
that's so weird she really bathe in
milk
she sent a picture to spike lee
of herself in a in a milk
bath oh okay there is ah i'm
looking for right now there's a there
was a really funny ted danson joke
when we did it between two ferns
alive between two friends to dance about
the blackface thing oh god why did
i always forget about that blackface thing
it's so funny i love him so
i'm looking for it right now hold
on hold on hold i don't think
we i don't think we used it
but as it was ah really funny
i'm looking forward i'm looking forward i
have all the jokes here ah what's
the weirdest place you ever made whoopee
goldberg
ah um gosh where is it okay
does it do you guys have one
for me oh yeah oh yeah haven't
watched either heaven what the flawed he
gave it he gave it to sam
so okay so close your eyes count
me again sure close your eyes i'm
i'm looking at this because okay okay
i got it
okay okay yeah i'm still looking for
this but i'm looking still looking oh
here's one you did a blackface routine
at the roast of your then girlfriend
whoopi goldberg how ashamed are you that
you once dated one guy older
okay did you but you didn't do
your ask him did he i can't
remember which ones we actually passed because
we didn't tape it so it was
very fun though all right i took
one over here ya go sir
i thought you had a question i
do sorry i'm sorry i have a
terrible stammer oh i understand when you
were younger did you ever visit your
father at work
ah quite often it was a big
thrill for me to visit my father
at work yes i enjoyed it and
all of those sundays
over here yes over here over here
um do you wish that your sketchy
career where it was more successful or
are you happy with the way things
went i think ah life happens the
way it happens and i'm obviously a
success now um so the fact that
i was in sketches early on that
didn't quite pop is fine to me
now because it
wouldn't have led me to where i
am right now made i am robert
downey junior yeah nah why would you
say that what a weird thing me
yes over here when did you first
started when did you ever start yes
go ahead let him stammer
same guy the same guy call the
same guy all right what is only
two people this press conference was just
surprised very unsuccessful despair that you're giving
a press conference you don't need to
ah when did you first notice that
there was a problem with your eyes
yeah well definitely when i looked in
the mirror and ah they didn't work
ah or or i saw the problem
with them so it's gotten more serious
ah my daredevil by the way
his base over here do you fear
cutting your hair does it excite you
do i fear it and my adrian
brody's roster character no
um do i fear cutting my hair
no i don't so it's very exciting
to me i always enjoy it it's
one of my great great pleasures of
my life went away baby yes i'm
calling a baby baby snuck into a
room would you say that you have
more friends now than you used to
to have more friends now than i
used to have more friends yeah it
may be the same exact number no
i think i'm more
our um
my hank williams junior with all my
rowdy friends um
hold on oh look i got nothing
but time i obviously staged a press
conference for two pp you feel frustrated
by the tabloids obsession with you ah
i obviously it's not it's not something
i love but ah you know it's
ah it's part of life now it's
out of my life hey hey over
here yes how important to you is
your greek heritage
you know what ah without it i
wouldn't be who i am today i
mean my mother and father had sex
and that causes heritage so i wouldn't
exist it wouldn't exist so i um
and being greek and being who i
am ah a greek former sketch actor
and i don't remember any other details
other than i have friends and maybe
more friends all my friend in your
eye problem and my eye problem and
you also i think you must have
really chronically dry skin considering how much
lotion you use
are you worried that people will see
pictures of you before your plastic surgery
plastics do you feel that you have
to drink only one brand of water
am i i'm obviously jennifer aniston yeah
yeah oh that's how you play prescott
for ah wow that was fun that
was fun i enjoy that what's wrong
with her items i just dry dry
i don't think she does that was
courtney cox oh sorry she has a
drive agenda remember this no
what the friends writers there was like
somebody who was like a writer's assistant
or something yeah who had a lawsuit
revealed had a lawsuit against saying that
that she didn't like the types of
conversations they had in the writers' room
yeah that they were too sexual or
something could who said that though writer's
assistant suits the show and because they
said courtney cox's vagina no i was
that
he did say something about her vagina
being filled with twigs oh right but
yeah like dead leaves or somebody like
because she were making fun of the
actor yeah because she was trying to
get pregnant and couldn't get pregnant oh
my god yeah it was like the
stuff that came out was legitimately horrible
oh no but then there was this
all just guys you're like we need
to do stuff like that
part of the creative process everyone's like
with all this me to stuff to
be like oh yeah so i can't
floor this a flirty business fuck off
florida business on slitter prison rules oh
wow oh this was a food issue
those sir this is a florida business
there was a thing of like writers'
rooms or the the chill
til that falls over comedy writer rooms
like am i allowed to say that
joke oh god yeah well anyways well
anyway well and i was fine press
conference was fun right talking about news
for months and months ago years in
fact years i hope no isn't over
fabulous comes
davidson i do i'm sure you do
alright well thanks thanks for listening we're
at a time we'll see it next
time we love you bye bye
uh this has been an era with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and collin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com