three
oh cheese cheeseburger cheeseburger cheeseburger cheeseburger
welcome to the show welcome to the
show we are bad yeah how many
people do you think we're listening to
this for the first time immediately turned
it off well they're talking about jesus
you just they start every episode by
yelling cheeseburger that's not bad though cheeseburger
cheeseburger cheeseburger is is not banksy hard
for cheeseburger
or it really does actually was the
last time you guys had a cheeseburger
well i don't like cheeseburgers okay oh
laura and cheese please wait do you
like hamburgers by the way welcome to
the show is scott ackerman across me
i have easy cheesy lauren lucas bay
right next to lauren is me paul
f tompkins he'll take the cheese please
row me is the cheese
himself
da me fuckin guy yeah dang yo
um i don't i like hamburgers yeah
i like to taste that meat in
your mouth yeah huh um let me
know um can an episode go by
without us like sexually harassing on-air know
let the record show
hey geri there have been some instances
in previous episodes where have i put
paul do you really need to pull
up the plata files i had you
pull okay let's be okay here we
go let's play that file for
and play lower let me get at
them tips
see
that you regret it now like wow
that everybody's getting their come up in
hell
so do you like here
if you if you go with what
a human ever kiss me or mac-n-cheese
do you think like yeah eighty wait
a minute are you from another planet
he's with this guy
he gets about humans know but i
mean like say say they fell in
love because mary mckee
say they throw him in again
mayor machines' supposing love with a human
yeah but wouldn't it be something to
overcome like she's like okay why i'm
in love with this personality but here
we go let's see what shape of
water i don't know what that is
and i don't know what anyone's tweets
her okay lawrence move dammit lauren let's
everyone's very understated waterway
whenever you're listening to this i don't
care the shape of water is about
this fish man and this lishman how
fish ball in love
local news anchor it's been have you
ever heard of ah hellboy that familiar
yeah i've heard of it this is
one of the characters from that graphic
novel it's just i don't think it
is actually okay i don't believe this
is a hellboy yeah um it's not
a spinoff maybe it's prequel motherfucker know
i know it's not shutting the hellboy
universe are you sure yeah yes are
you sure
yes our percent this is actor doug
jones playing an entirely different fishman yes
can i just why are you so
angry this is absurd and outrageous it's
not i am fishman yes i was
watching justice league the other night oh
my well i thought aqua mannose montage
so you would never realize that aquaman
is a re
real thing right no i thought you
thought it was a super hero character
that a clean yea would play
i mean it's not so i tweeted
that and then people went mad it's
not that hard to believe because it's
ridiculous yeah and it's like oh he
like it so i guess in their
mind he's getting to play batman
like it's as good as or no
meaning in the entourage universe if it
were a fictional yeah creation yes it's
like playing batman yeah yeah but didn't
they make a bunch of jokes about
how it wasn't as good as bad
manners yeah i feel like they made
fun of it but it was still
a big deal i mean they were
really good out make love that show
ah yeah well i was kind of
gay
but i did watch every episode and
banned the movie and eliza yeah me
too i was i saw the movie
like friday morning at ten am i
don't know this last friday don't say
you use use on the first available
screening i to in the center of
a dome the first two things that
movie are so eight dumb i
can't believe it it's like all tits
yeah paul would like it i guess
yeah play day it's here the tape
oh but i love tits still why
why guys stop playing these ah sorry
but we recorded him ah why did
you cut them out of the previous
episodes if you're just gonna play them
here you know what i saw today
a online um it was a comment
about you guys oh no don't tell
us no it was good oh it's
okay i wouldn't tell you a bad
one oh really yeah not it's just
something he would do i'm a nasty
one um nobody said i love i
wish i had a friend ship like
scott
and paul where they can just talk
for hours about anything on mike yeah
it's about the best job that's how
many things the best of us right
all you need is the pressure of
of having to an audience right yeah
but i thought wow i really horned
in on that what do you mean
no and i'm happy like i got
in the friendship train now we we
vacation together what do you mean i
know i know we understand just about
anything we want yes here's what's wonderful
it was one
powerful who are you telling show everyone
oh okay and everyone listening if you're
dying right now listen we got a
silence in the world right now what
if there was like a literal world
moment of silence because using gender fully
use what chuck never went i was
working in london for their um jolly
old london
for their veterans day you know what
do they call it an armistice stay
or something like that i can't recall
yeah where they have the hours on
the puppy show and so they have
they have a national moment of silence
oh they do and so we were
honest the same time
no you can decide what you want
to do it yeah i do want
every other minute just for different stuff
yeah usually if i'm in a conversation
yeah i take them over to say
oh yeah every couple of seconds i'll
do like eight hours of silence every
night or what nine eleven yeah
i started to get drowsy and i'm
like never forget
i'm in
but they they had um they had
a tv on sets so we could
watch like d ah i guess in
front of buckingham palace or whatever they
they were like cutting to all these
different locations and so the moment of
silence happened and it was dead silent
like all good thing because that would
never happen would never have
yeah i can never get that to
ya there would be someone like going
by the camera go oh yeah yeah
about potentially ruining it yeah exactly i
fell asleep right outside buckingham palace this
lash is trying to meet the prince
yeah i just fell i just fell
in any megan markle stole your man
what was going on we were on
tour right and i yes and you'd
had so
some wine i had why i don't
know martino as those martinis with my
canford and then ah i was i
don't know why i was walking around
or something that i just fell asleep
right in front standing up you had
turned to
people tried to make ah i was
wearing that big fuzzy hat you know
i think your time to kill before
my time to kill yes and you
fell asleep on the street now i
felt i fell asleep like ah on
the on the like the back statue
throne of ai yeah that's pretty chilled
it was pretty chilly me i don't
i could relax that hard and i
just remembered that today for some reason
i don't know why i think i've
ever fallen asleep outside oh really i
can comic-con one year i was so
hung over from a saturday night party
that cool op went into comecon and
i just i i was on the
the bus to get
they're like the shuttle just about to
throw up on the shuttle and then
i just fell asleep on the grass
in front of company for an hours
hours
and then i woke up i felt
great why sure
oh my guy oh jesus it's happening
again i don't think i've ever slept
outside besides camp you've never slept outside
it's usual stamping well outside yeah glamping
i wasn't a turret i was in
hotels in tandem with
joe what's the best timid what's the
best impression you've ever done bill cosby
we just heard just now
um huh that's a hard did you
ever did you ever grow up going
like oh wow i do a pretty
good i'm always made me do share
when i was little okay is it
were you doing someone else doing sharing
huh
oh for me
yeah pretty good and i my brother
already always what i did no impressions
no chicco hey i finally that was
very funny ah nice i really do
doubt that we are a little when
i was little i remember doing like
groucho marx
wow roadshow really as he talked where
forever
yeah that's pretty much it yeah the
most ridiculous thing i ever say the
sugar boy now one hundred and eighty
yeah um but i i remember my
homes when they talk like a stupid
idiot
yeah see that's the key to impressions
for five talks like a stupid idiot
on his office yeah i'm always impressed
when someone can do an impression of
someone who talks like a normal person
you know what i mean yeah yeah
and then you're like oh my god
yeah like realised that person has quirks
like there i think there are some
people where i'm like they don't really
have anything weird about that yeah well
you remember when peter
did the alan alda impression oh my
god so but bill window later yeah
they both do great ones you're like
oh i guess i never i just
thought he talked like a normal regular
guy or or how could you even
imitate that and then yeah that's crazy
you gotta seize on imperfections and exaggerate
them yes and break someone down yep
that's what
we're here to do that is what
we're here to do with this show
let me ask you this when you
were when you were a kid and
were you i'm assuming you were like
you like to goof around stuff like
um goof off is what i call
it would you get it jerk off
would you get shy now
sexually harassing me
yeah yes mommy yeah you made a
weird yeah i'm starting this um where
would you get shy if you were
asked to do it on command yeah
i do think i don't i didn't
like that yeah but i was asking
my mom when i was home for
the holidays like what would i be
doing it when i was little like
right now at like at the
holidays or whatever interesting sliding door style
if i were a lot if i'd
stayed lit
i was like what i like because
i have nephew like that movie little
where he makes a wish can i
always be a little and you just
see like decades go by and all
of his friends growing up but he's
gone gets older
that's right he's like my business will
never grow he looks like he's eight
years old but he has alzheimer's ah
sorry guys
i'm not saying because um i have
little nephews and they were running around
and i was like they're they're a
little boys in there it's hard to
like get into like projects or something
you don't mean like when i was
little i remember enjoying doing crafts my
mom and like sitting down and doing
something but i feel like that's kind
of a girlie love to do crafts
with your mom you're welcome to it
anytime
huh i met your mom how i
met your mom yeah i would love
to do crafts with them oh hey
call her up ma'am she loves fucking
jacob rajan shit um and i she
said that i would come down and
perform like put on a little show
put on shows yeah and so i
didn't i remember doing that that much
but i was being watched
what showed what would you do which
he little performances we didn't really get
into it but three sisters will like
i have one hole i'd like to
home movies myself included have a camera
and one of them i know i've
been wanting to go get the you
have to home movies because you didn't
have a camera my aunt had a
camera so it was she was around
we would film but we only have
a couple movies
um and i would there's a video
of me like singing in a rock
and paper tube to achy breaky heart
oh
you know what tube a vacuum rapper
wrapping everything oh got it um so
that kind of thing like the long
tube yeah yeah so yes yeah like
an aerosmith yeah because you just tyler
almost like they were like kerchiefs tied
to it
amazing i because we i was a
kid before you know home you know
there were like that's so you
yeah there was like you know super
eight or whatever yeah yeah yeah yeah
and so because i'm the fifth out
of six children there's hardly any picture
oh yeah they're deliberately tommy gatto yeah
yeah yeah yeah there's it really it
stopped after my my because i had
three sisters then my older brother than
me then
a little
cv mentioned three sisters in the beginning
to bring it around yep it's like
chekhov's
so um because my brother my older
brother was the first boy there was
like and he was blond hair and
asshole in photos lots of like this
boy photos yeah like he'd be in
a forest on a tree stump right
yeah just like don junior well there
was yeah oh yeah i guess it
is like that but so there was
the novelty of him
him and then like okay that's another
power on our doug yeah yeah yeah
it's too bad yeah sorry yeah sorry
we did you perform when you were
a little around the house i was
painfully shy but somehow i wanted to
be a puppeteer
and so yeah yeah okay yeah i
and i want it to be one
too you could have developed really yeah
did she make puppets shouldn't make them
but we have a ton you would
buy puppets she would buy up yeah
do still she still has a ton
of all my mom was a preschool
teacher until recently oh okay yeah what
at what point does she get rid
of the
puppets probably never because i have these
nephews now love them and oh okay
so she put on shows for them
and stuff like that they did a
puppet show oh wow yeah right that's
great grandma oh wow um and my
dad made me a puppet ah where
where ah using the little tiny ah
ah baseball hat that you would get
when you would get a sunday oh
yeah yeah so i got one of
those and then i also got one
of the tiny bats at a dodger
game i think and so he and
and then he took my ah little
league shirt and he stuffed it and
made a puppet out of this who
was holding like a baseball bat it
was his puppet it was just a
i'm what like
yeah on both sides of the room
i somehow stretched like stretch armstrong and
i
you made your costumes um no it
was it was really relatively big with
like big arm like i would put
my arm and it was like muppet
style i'd put my arm and one
of the arms right and my other
arm as in the butt up the
bud around the corner um yeah so
i just made my my friend edit
word and i would do puppet shows
for scissorhands yeah that sounds dangerous to
show the other hand you lose all
your best props
well yeah i mean my mom tells
a story about how i did it
a church play i was very shy
and i did a church play and
and i said my line or something
and i got a laugh and she
says that my eyes went wide and
i looked at the crowd and she
was like man i knew that that's
what you want it well pride is
a sin
yeah for you to do that in
church is disgusting funny though how you
just told that story like am then
i knew because you probably heard that
a thousand times and you're like there
are those stories that i'm like okay
we know i did that when i
was like oh right duh i know
i've grown up since then i'm always
interested in the stories that i've never
heard thy know like bust out a
story one day i i'll be like
i've now
ever heard you tell anything like that
like some story about how we were
at a ah some sort of game
on the bleachers and i sat on
my mom's lap when i was four
and my dad yelled at her saying
that she was calling me and i
was never allowed to sit on her
lap again like i was like i
need eye opening shortly and my mom
and my mom told that and was
saying
that like our i thought and i
saw i felt so guilty that i
had been coddling you like shit for
who so your mom was one who
told you the store ie well they
yeah it came i think they were
both telling her so i don't know
very very that's was your dad telling
you with pride from it i screamed
at your mother in front of every
probably we did just have a conversation
station where my dad was telling a
story my mom just like kept interjecting
say nope that did not happen that
happens huh no you're telling the exact
wrong story now you're getting none of
the details make you wonder about like
everyone and like what's actually true i
feel like if your mom or your
dad was thinking that the that was
going that was exactly how it happened
i feel like i would trust
my ah wife's telling the stories way
more than i would trust my memory
like if she were to tell a
story ago yeah you remember i don't
i this the opposite for me because
i have a very good memory and
say that memory is ah because of
emotion so i'm a very emotional guy
wow i'm crying right now oh yeah
you always are just tear streaming no
one knows
out of your friends okay you know
can you mark that
what is your episode favorite parts
oh yes it's tough to go she's
off lauren if you can choose for
like one day yeah right now good
i tested
trying to know if you get on
mcgee's if you could if like one
if if you had the option in
a big style wish to jack huh
style and if that was the option
or if i could have anything if
you have anything in the world
ooh ah ooh oh god oh god
tell you oh we should take a
break sure yeah alright probably say let's
take a break when we come back
we're going to have more advice talking
more paul coughing he's gonna get over
whatever he's been nursing for
weeks ah yes lee weeks um we
will be right back
welcome back welcome back welcome back we're
here and we're not leaving no no
we're not going anywhere not going anywhere
now now not yet to healing you
ah man go away
yeah this manner yeah huh
share away yeah more more no i
want to see cher live i'd love
that i love her twitter does she
perform yeah she just did let's go
dates and i'm like yourself i would
love i want to understand she puts
on an amazing show i've never seen
during big hollywood shows i think she
like reads letters from the audience
letters to the editor
she's sent there's like a big hat
at the entrance to the theater isn't
a lie you yeah this is a
lie okay you let's play two truths
and a lie we know this one's
the law okay so the seven tell
us two truths about it shares a
lie
there is an entrance to the theater
there is one of wait what if
that were the lie what if that
were the low end entrance you're just
find yourself there no windows and no
doors of course there's always my way
when was listening i went there last
year with my neff ah nephew yes
same answer what was the word almost
going to be i get confused with
familial relationships especially with a ah constantly
changing one i forgot what do you
mean
well with with kit know with kula
ah having new relatives oh okay that
even because he's growing up i was
like silly happy well yeah every year
it's like what are you now are
you today don't have uncle scott
um i got confused i was making
fun of the trump family on twitter
and i forgot the baron was saying
that baron and don junior are brothers
oh that's what i was referring to
also i was referring to don junior
as baron's uncle and then someone said
to me
so their brothers and i laughed and
laughed of teddy you seen the latest
picture of barron he's like all legs
no ooh he's like he's like the
first giraffe all the way up to
his but he's like that leg lamb
christmas story ah tattoo and it's on
a person um but with the garden
she was wearing there's some piggish
you imagine barron trump wearing garters yeah
imagine rain does amazing yet american barron
trump and rocky horror picture show he
looks honestly love it before so it's
very small and his legs a very
long he's almost as tall as the
debt what if not to i mean
obviously he's a child and we should
be talking about simply can't leave him
out rolling huh
yeah it's ap when he were eighteen
if he were starring in hedwig in
the i may branch yeah so much
fun when you're legally allowed to star
in that musical yes i would pay
i would pay so much to see
it especially how much did you pay
especially if he were to do a
monologue at the end of it
personal personal model silly makeup and every
single makeup yes like i went back
i want to thank everyone for coming
i would i would i don't know
i would pay to ask me three
questions about living at the white house
i would pay i pay a couple
of grams i say i'd pay like
four thousand dollars right probably probably somewhere
around there not not if they were
like especially if you were cut off
i think i would be
crying loud
what sounds great then i'd be hilarious
to be the funniest thing i could
ever witness like i think i would
do would be so i'd have to
pay up for especially if you are
cut off from the family fortune because
he was like an outcast he really
brought an easy i would be like
here he wouldn't get the money would
be paying for the theatre oh what
if he were
exactly the same in hedwig and the
angry inch as he is now we're
just like him just trying to please
our talking
what kind of meme monthly delivery guys
oh yeah and everyone's doing the show
around him
it's just all time it sounds like
going to see like a little kids
in a play ever seen little kids
playing i saw oh hey you told
that story oh i told her i
told her that just ah well when
i saw the little shop of horrors
play with five year olds playing it
we i don't know if you've told
the story on here i think oh
god told that well i i
thought i saw these five year old
kids wanting a little shop of horrors
and it's so funny because i in
my mind i would be like well
they won't they won't be good they'll
but they'll be going for it and
so many of them are just like
rotary blah blah blah blah saying the
things and then there were two moshe
knicks and they spoke at the same
time which nick's mushing his character yeah
oh mishnah
shop owner say munchkin then i was
a little person and like i just
feel like i went on a call
but they cast two little kids wait
wait wait what were you picturing in
your mind well i just was really
confused but then i was like maybe
he means like a russian thing or
say i just like was had no
why why wouldn't you just assume it's
a character from the show they were
too much knicks it just seemed like
it was a say
slur oh really and that's the kind
of person you think i am yeah
actually
so these two kids because they had
more kids than they had parts so
they has two kids and they instead
of just like swapping scenes they just
said just talk at the same time
so they spoke manderson that's not the
story that you're gonna tell what storage
isn't it was good that little boy
who'd like did something no no not
that story oh boy we've told them
this several video to putin oh yes
oh no i don't want to get
outta outta put not on this show
who catch one of our previous episodes
of a show we've done
yeah una burden
ah wait i wanna say what this
reality show i'm watching i'm only okay
alright
it's on netflix i actually i hesitate
to even share this with the world
because shares oh yeah robin not sure
there is i am enjoying it so
much myself that i feel almost you
don't want anyone else to like start
having kitschy fun with it yeah it's
mine but it's not mine it's a
japanese reality show called
terrace house how so it takes place
in japan however it's landed on this
something
and it's amazing and it's this how
it's basically like real real world meets
big brother but there's no challenges and
no like forced drama so there's three
boys and three girls and they all
are like um people who are perfect
for fucking yeah i know incidents it
does work out but se does
it does put there but it's so
fascinating because they're all people who have
individual goals in their lives like they
have different careers that there's like a
guy i want to be in a
house that's your goal yep
asleep and i'm fucking hemphill i've only
slept outside except for camping but they're
like there's like a hatmaker like an
architect and like different people they'll have
makers she's great really the different somebody
has to make the heads she's a
designer
and then when you're ready to leave
when you feel like you've reached a
goal of your or you're just done
with the relationships there you just leave
and they put a new person of
that gender and wit so whenever you
want to leave with me on whatever
schedule was somebody i would never like
those months yeah i would never work
out in america as much of them
wanna be there no no no time
so much of it would never happen
this way it's something else you say
that made me think oh and the
moment of silence because like there's so
much about the culture that allows the
show to work this way but like
in america unlike real-world they have sex
on the first five minutes like someone
will be fucking this does not happen
they have like courtship and then like
maybe the like there was one couple
that got together and like you learn
later that they do have sex building
out
like a conversation that she had like
about it or something and like they
don't actually show all the drama always
just like you'll see a conversation where
like earlier you said something really rude
to me and you won't have seen
that and so it's like it's it's
so good and then ensure they're just
the cameras don't work sometimes they might
not film everything but still like it's
because i'm haven't figured that out yet
if there's always a camera
they're not but then there's these interstitials
with these comedians these japanese like celebrities
oh and they make fun of the
show and they make fun of all
the people and it's so i'm gonna
choke so funny it's like you're choking
because it's so funny yeah i can't
believe it no when i think when
i watch though it's so fascinating because
it feels like us hanging out like
how we would make fun
none of them like it really opened
my eyes up so much like culturally
like i i've been to tokyo and
i loved it there so much but
you can't communicate at a certain point
obviously i don't speak the language and
to hear them like joking the exact
same way that we joke i was
like this is so cool it's just
awesome i think you would really enjoy
it what's the name of the show
terrace house t e r r terence
house
hi i'm terence house welcome to another
episode of theresa but also if you
don't like it then fuck off
i want to check your terms lie
i love it laura do you remember
we were talking about the people's couch
yeah we were going to do a
show we're gonna do at night at
lcb where we watch the people's couch
on homicide
ouch i it's not already more he
moscow is like people at their apartment
watching a different series of different girls
who go watching bravo shows and commenting
on them so you seeing it's basically
just their commentary you stick a little
clip and then make fun of it
or something yeah and then we were
gonna do a show where we come
into on that that's almost like you're
trapped in the closet commentary yes
that's right that's right alright kelly did
um ah you know the fast track
to the closet and he did a
of a visual commentary where he was
watching unity it was his back and
he was watching a tv screen then
he would turn over the shoulder and
he sat in awe like icy share
it was the weirdest thing he's sitting
like in three-quarter pro
file with it with a screen you
know in front of him and he's
watching trapped in the closet and then
he would um he would just pretty
much say who'd watch this one was
happening yeah and then he would just
turn over a shoulder to the camera
hygiene while he just look at the
camera yeah so when i oh and
i saw paul do this live he
put that on the screen
and sat with his back to the
audience and then turned around and spoke
overall funny i love that it is
interesting like culturally other countries with people
who don't want to constantly be on
tv or just how much i remember
i was watching ah in probably the
early two thousands i was watching this
nineteen sick
sixty s episode of the dating game
and just how different the united states
is now ah this episode of the
dating game the the woman it was
three bachelors and a woman and the
woman said to okay bachelor number three
sing a song that you make up
for me and that's a number three
said um i don't think i would
be able to do
and no thank you and she said
okay and then they moved on and
i was like oh yeah of course
back then how demeaning to be on
television came now yeah well anyway ah
all these things that had not been
invented yet all the tropes of television
and not been invented yet
and there was still some ah you
know like sheen of civility to everything
yeah well you you had to go
back to your neighborhood and friends and
family and they would yeah make fun
of you if you did something like
that i'm not going to sing songs
and nowadays it would be like i
saw you on television but i think
that is also what's kind of fascinating
thing about this show is that i
would assume
culturally they would not want to be
a part of something like that like
just out of like what i know
what the culture but then to see
how they handle it and how the
comedians like roast them and exactly i
mean the joe i mean when i
say like it i find that to
the most fascinating thing because their their
culture meaning like the sense of humour
that they show
share is so exactly what we do
that it was like really eye opening
when i felt like oh i feel
like i have these judgments about other
cultures or things that i think senses
of humor or they don't always lend
yeah one yeah remember when big brother
first came out here in the states
they included all this stuff that they
would put on the ah
i believe it was a swedish show
first and they they made all these
like jokes that they would make on
the swedish version that did not fly
with americans because you know we we
had had it was all this kind
of ironic stuff of like look we're
just going to show you the chicken
coop for a whole minute yes like
yeah we we've had lettermen for twenty
five years you know old iran
just on big brother yeah the first
season they did it exactly like they
did the original swedish show and it
was not very good and then they
changed it to make an american job
but you know american idol ah is
kind of the same thing when it
was pop idol in the u k
they have the evil competed to be
the next popeye
oh my dull it was so dull
boring papa
okay okay but they they had two
comedians and compression you were waiting to
share i paul knows that i did
pop one of my favorite i thought
of that story the other day it's
wait what oh i'm a talent please
yeah yeah
okay so when i was thirteen i
lived here in california and i started
listening to kiss fm right top forty
radio yeah and they had a ah
they had a district eon from i
believe six to ten was his slot
and his name is bruce vidal and
ah
i thought he was so cool you
just sounded say his voice was very
very cool i remember like years later
i saw a picture of him and
he was like giants like oh gosh
um not no judgments on that but
just now was not the mental image
that i expected um and he would
do this thing called the boogie line
and where at about seven forty five
he would say the boogie line is
now open and you would call the
radio station and you would like tell
jokes on the air and and and
then out of around eight twenty or
something his team would edit them all
together and it would be like random
montage of people calling in until july
so when i was thirteen i was
like i'm gonna call the boogie line
and i'm gonna get on this i'm
gonna get on the radio did you
call a bunch so i we they
still had the taste in your mouth
measure from the church show so i
mom could see it in your eyes
so i did an impression coddling that
oh sad life
so i didn't impression popeye because he
was my favourite cartoon character when we
didn't have a tell i mean who
was better no yes i was no
i was very i was very very
into the early like popeye comics dropping
williams i was very excited about that
movie when it came out yeah of
course i was very into the early
cartoons
in the early comic strips um did
you know that the that the jeep
was invented by the the word jeep
was reply popeye
what do you mean so they named
the vehicle named after that character yeah
i don't know wait it's a character's
name yeah yeah so jean the jeep
yeah crazy so ah so i did
sort of an impression of popeye and
so i called up for the first
time and i was like okay i
really wanna make this good excuse me
so i had um i
i'd taped a bunch of sound effects
i think off the tv or something
which was all like bio oil like
a toilet flushing and stuff like taken
work though yeah yeah and so i'd
taped all these and and like a
chatterbox laughing like haha and stuff like
that so i called up i called
up the
umana as popeye oh my god it
was like roosevelt was like blueline and
i was like hello it's popeye and
then i would then i told a
joke right i told some joke with
all the joe i know okay i
will i actually don't know any of
the jokes ah there is one i
do know yeah
but ah that will come later in
the story so and then i would
tell a joke and then i would
press play on my tape recorder which
would then play the sound effects and
then he would and then he hung
up would it be one sound effect
per know it was like a string
of up until until the intelligent grassroots
boy yea
yeah boy so and then you know
he would just he would never say
goodbye or anything he would just hang
it you know so the first time
i called in they put me on
the air and i was like holy
shit i got the i got the
taste of it so i would call
regularly for months for like three months
or something like that and he would
put me on all the time right
and so
so then i called back one day
and i was like hello it's popeye
um i gave ah blue toe ah
toilet seat with an inscription on it
it said aim high cook a good
gig and then i press the the
button and bajo like toilet flush
shh and then i'm like listening for
the hangup and i don't hear it
and then i press stop on the
tape recorder and i hear bruce fidel
say popeye and i don't know how
to respond because i've never spoken him
in this manner before and i didn't
know if i should respond in character
or whatever so i just said
yes
t thirteen and he says we want
to give you the special hotline so
you can call in and not have
to get the busy signal anymore i
got pop and i'm like okay yeah
and he gave you the special day
he gave me the special hotline and
i said thank you thank you
and hung up and then i think
i called the hotline once and it
just lost the luster to me or
something plus i also i was in
teachings is always better than the kill
i was in junior high and i
remember saying to like some people i
think i started eighth grade or something
i said to so i said to
like a cool person i was like
hey you ever listened to kiss fm
ah bruce vidal at night and like
yeah sure i was like
do you ever listen to the buoy
line i think so yeah i'm popeye
okay ah and they're like who gives
a shit
are these separate thoughts yeah everyone's a
begun i'm popeye are you okay
yeah for me
so yeah that's my popeye story
i love it i don't know what
made me think of it yeah yes
so funny i don't know why we
were talking about that i don't either
ah terrence terrence house terrace had terrorist
wow like sense of humour being different
and then something yeah yeah anyways yeah
anyway why don't we take a break
okay let's come back when we come
back someone
we'll have brought a feature for us
to do
alright we'll be right back
hey we're back and oh frightening everyone
frightening listeners hey boo it's frightening we're
back um welcome back laurens on her
phone and wrapping it up wrapping it
up um sins
um welcome back so this is the
part in our third segment one of
us brings something to do what's right
and a little fun thing for us
to do and it looks like it's
up to me this time so ah
lauren you've probably played this but i
brought some some plays here oh and
we're gonna do that
that game where one person reads actual
lines from a play and then the
other two ah improv that's fun around
it well i have done the show
grabbed water at usb have you ever
snitching i've never seen it no they
do that so you have an actor
ah one character's lines of a scene
and then improvise knows nothing about it
it's something that i saw when i
was
does ah eighteen or something i saw
this improv group that my friends were
in i saw them do it and
it's like the hardest i've ever laughed
this we're setting ourselves a terrible ah
but ah i i've never i've never
seen it with three people but i
assume that two people can do it
while one person reads lines right yeah
okay good man
right now so i so i brought
three plays three different plays and so
i'll read the lines first and you
guys can how's how's this usually start
learn well it usually is the person's
memorized oh
oh who gives a shit or on
the podcast scott we're gonna do this
writer we gonna facet that's how it
starts now but i guess you just
you start yeah tell her tell us
if we need to like be um
wait we'll work with three people yeah
because i'll just say lines then you
guys played other people i don't know
let's just try it let's try it
ah this is not going to work
less well maybe it should be maybe
should be two people and then we'll
do two different people alright let's just
see how it works it's just if
someone wants to join it okay and
um this is biloxi blues by neil
simon i'm gonna play epstein um and
here we go okay
the army has it's logic i have
my own okay well are you going
to come outside because everyone's waiting for
you and we we really don't want
to start unless everyone's there since i'm
not guilty of a crime i reserve
the privilege to keep my own motives
a matter of confidentiality
you keep saying you're not guilty but
you you know what everyone out there
thinks you are okay i'm not trying
to beat you sergeant i'm trying to
work with you it doesn't feel that
way it feels like you're actually trying
to fuck with me i don't think
it's necessary to dehumanize a man to
get him to perform you can get
better results raising our spirits than lowering
our dignity this is you can't turn
it around on me because i know
that you did know yes
saw you take it i didn't want
anyone to see that okay that was
a personal diary think inventing a crime
that didn't exist to enforce your theories
of discipline is neanderthal in it's conception
i didn't invent anything something actually happened
out there and you know what it
was okay egyptian kings made their slaves
obedient eventually they lost their slaves and
their can just i didn't go to
college because we can pull this shit
on me ok i don't care what
you know about egypt it
should be an interesting contest sergeant let's
get out there and i'm gonna spit
farther than you and that's the plan
okay and whoever doesn't doesn't spit far
enough is gonna be sleeping under the
fucking trenches after i crush your testicles
you can replace them with their gone
already
and see ah husband all right here
yeah here's yours okay
you'll do it with paula with a
sample yes okay and you have the
play angels in america perestroika tony kushner
and let me find ah
it's not a real good one find
a real good one okay
so lauren is going to be doing
the lines from angels in america perestroika
perestroika and paul will be improvising around
huh
okay excuse me right rings around okay
yes thank you
oh this is gonna be so much
worse than i'd imagined
oh right
whoa you got actually no thank you
really convinced him
oh this is going to be so
much worse than i had imagined well
your imagination is nothing compared to mine
when i'm imagining is off the charts
horrible fuck you you little shit bag
hey just because you're jealous of my
imaginary skills doesn't mean that you can
talk to me that way don't see
any bruises
well not every bruise is visible because
some are emotional like you inflicted on
me you are one noble guy inside
don't flatter yourself louis so it's your
tea party talk
okay first of all thank you for
coming to the tea party secondly thank
you for saying the thing about nobility
i don't get how i'm just noble
inside i feel like that's just what
nobility is i don't know if you're
saying i don't look noble which is
an insult i guess but anyway talk
i'm getting to it let me pour
you some tea
makeup
okay
this is a tea party this is
not we agreed that we were just
going to come like just fresh out
of the shower we weren't going to
doll ourselves up it was gonna be
a casual tea party for some friends
oh huh
but
okay here it comes
so i can't do anything without you
assuming i have an ulterior motive yes
i invited you over to have a
no makeup tea party
and yes i do have an ulterior
motive which is
i want you to go in on
a business with me it isn't yes
it is what i'm telling you it
is it is we're going to open
up a frozen yogurt franchise the two
of us you were saying something about
being reasonable yeah this is entirely reasonable
this is this is i'm telling you
this a license to print money people
love fro-yo
you want to come back why
okay i don't know if you're paying
attention i'm saying i'm moving back to
this town
to first of all host these regular
tea parties no makeup tea parties but
also to open up a frozen yogurt
franchise with you my best friend oh
no you didn't oh yes i did
yes i did i've already said sida
lease you're seeing someone else
okay
i am seeing
other realtors because you are yes i
want to open multiple franchises threshold of
revelation now ask me how i know
he's a mormon alright
how do you know he's a more
wow yeah you you want me to
ask you is he a mormon yes
how is he urban fuck you i'm
a prophet was
a
ah very good and that was fun
i was fun now paul you have
another you have a different play i
do well now i have two places
to play so i have the caretaker
and the dumbwaiter two plays by harold
pinter starring webster or
didn't make it over done in a
dumb later
really oh i guess so yeah but
wait why would that because he was
small yeah but still hasn't done later
so the set of the twentieth century
yeah we had a dumbwaiter attention when
i worked there my friend actually their
parents to her parents design their house
they built in a dumbwaiter from the
garage to the upstairs kitchen so you
could lo
food groceries of course i'm interested i
have a dumbwaiter in my house too
i'm just saying we all have dumbwaiter
and i was a waiter who's done
oh shit it isn't really emasculating name
for thing that's cool yeah well yeah
it makes you not want to put
one into your house yeah i'm waiter
what it means is it's a mute
twitter it's a waiter that cannot speak
like a perfect waiter it's me
it's able to say cannot stand waiter
humor by the way
we had like adaptations yeah guess you
just like that too much we a
server no i just mean humour that
servers do because yeah i'm just doing
oh oh i'm sorry i thought you
were saying i didn't like your jokes
yeah now i'm saying no like we
didn't see your play and like get
yes you hate it huh
yeah i did i did a standup
character that was ah a waiter who
would who was trying stand up for
the first time and he was just
doing weight
and it was all out like that
anyway so told me a good one
a friend of mine i can remember
who told me this when they when
the waiter says that to them i
guess he didn't like that too much
his response always is to be extremely
sincere and apologetically no actually i'd like
to lie in fact i eat look
i eat the light ate it all
alright let's save this is let's go
with the first play which is the
caretaker the caretaker this is addressed to
vivien that's dedicated to viv yeah okay
so our performance will be to vivian
as well also to vivian um and
anyone named vivian yeah even fictional characters
sure
like vivian vivian krillin drastic world did
you know your character
krill
he's on my badge
encouraged that the only reason that anyone
would know that name is because he
was on the better duty when calmly
i don't think anyone i'm vivian was
i don't know if anyone says my
name movie vivian krill get over which
is krill though for sure
alright i think i found
a good one oh that's okay i'm
gonna make sure i'm not the character
with like the gigantic monologue right alright
um yes here we go
ah
okay
family of indians live there
a family of indians lived there i
mean i expected one or two but
a whole family that's incredible i don't
see much of them you don't see
much of them though i mean ah
that can be expected i mean you
know they're not really known for hanging
out outside
shoes
well yeah because they don't have shoes
normally so they they tend to stay
inside and because they can get rocks
in their feet and it's just very
difficult so i it's very understandable so
i get it where
at their houses obviously ah so no
i get it's there's no need to
be defensive about not seeing your neighbors
i understand because you know i don't
talk to my neighbors all that much
either so easy everyone tends to just
stay inside you know i might have
a pair
you yeah i mean you could definitely
get a pair of shoes i think
it would be you would definitely protect
your feet i mean i'm looking down
with those and they're they're bloody and
um you know really disgusting and you
could also stand to cut your toenails
quite honestly pair of brown oh yes
i think
dad i think you could get a
pair of brown shoes definitely i think
that would be that we could take
you to the store do you want
us to take you to the store
you've got to have a good pair
of shoes i agree so why don't
you let why don't you let margin
i take you to the store and
we can get you that good pair
of shoes that you're asking for what
happened when
you got there then
when i got there when i bought
my shoes ah i brought money with
me i tried on you know not
too many parents not gonna be too
many pairs you can try on one
or two until you find one that's
comfortable we'll just we'll we'll have the
measure your feet if that's what you
want what
i said
film it it's not something to be
worried about though measure your feet they
they usually they just take ah they
have a machine that does it you
know they're not gonna get down there
and and actually take a measuring stick
to it or anything see if these
are any good
you these are not shoes these are
cans of tomato soup you can't use
these i mean yes you could put
a strap on them and and affix
them to your feet but they're not
going to protect you from the elements
the way that you want to dad
would they know yeah they would technically
but yeah there they don't have good
arch support and you're not going to
be able to use them come on
dad let us take
add you to the store please you've
got to get out of the house
not bad trim
your stop looking at my wife okay
god this is disgust like you know
try these
you just handed me
two bags of potato chips
they're the same brand the same flavor
can i just open one like you
don't want me to open both bags
do you good
dad you know we love coming over
here talking to you and visiting with
you but um you know we're just
worried you're not taking care of yourself
you know what i mean oh yeah
i mean look at this places is
you know you haven't been keeping up
with it could we pay for someone
to come over here and tidy up
you know every
once in a while
yeah we would be willing we would
be willing to do it i know
it hurts your pride but but you
know we have money set away for
this and and i want to make
sure that you're okay in your old
age ah
yeah
i so you'll let me do it
you'll let me do it
i'll see what i can look out
for you oh thank you dad that's
all i've really want i just want
to make sure you're okay you know
you took such good care of me
god i'm getting emotional use you took
such good care of me growing up
and to see you like this is
really ah very emotional for me but
i want to make sure that you're
okay where are you going to go
i'm gonna go home and i'm gonna
make some calls and i'm gonna get
a maid service for you and we're
gonna clean this up don't worry wood
would you like to sleep here
yeah i would dad that's so nice
yeah we ah
yeah that's great i would like to
sleep here till you get yourself fixed
up i'm doing fine we need to
clean this place up but yeah we
get yourself sorted out
okay now i feel like you're patronizing
me i thought it was night i
thought you were just asking if we
could do like what we used to
do a father and son sleepover party
but ah now i feel like you're
patronizing me for some reason i'm just
offering to help you hear the other
rooms would would be no good to
yeah none of these rooms are good
this is this place is a fucking
shithole dad
there's a bed behind all that yeah
well i that's what i'm saying yes
there's a beautiful bed that we bought
you a california king and you never
sleep out it's there's trash all over
i picked it up just keeping it
here for the time being thought of
my coming andy yes a bed comes
in handy every single night no see
ya
oh huh boy that reminded me of
the scene you did at the shows
not funny oh order that was really
good harold tender not such a great
choice for equity
he just says oh okay yes
um that is very funny very nice
very nice game fun game thank god
for bringing the feature of course well
that's just about it for us so
on this episode we're tries yeah
what if this never gets released because
there's a nuclear war or a coup
miku miku
the alien ship yeah so you think
when we die we become alien was
turned to die my scientology oh i
did not know that our friendship is
alright well see you next time bye
a
this has been an era with production
executive produced by scott ackerman chris bannon
and colin anderson for more information and
content visit airwolf dot com