yeah
three
nah nah i was i mean like
are you mature and the singular ration
la de da da da di what
about when our consciousnesses are uploaded to
the premature simulation oh my god
it will be so wonderful you want
to deal with this but you think
well of consciousness is next to each
other i hope so like he'll put
a baby alphabetical oh damn
first-ever lost all consciousness is lasting last
gotta be lastly so it's like it's
like the white pages yeah it's just
like the yellow pages where it's my
job was doing alphabet but i think
by height order oh my gosh
it's gonna be so mean by jobs
that you have things go next to
me no no yeah different guy wait
who did the ah ah oh fuck
it was cheap
no it's not bugs bugsy come back
timer thing huh
didn't get me but oh oh we're
up there up remembering if you're out
there we love you we love your
i love you we love you telling
us that we can't do things we
wish we could do come over to
my house and do that didn't you
guys just get so excited when they
made these water bottle caps slim
so slim and slimline water bottle this
saved the earth i remember ah a
guy that i knew who was not
a standup comedian okay but who lie
what really bad hair
his name was red herring oh and
he was watching a standup show that
i was on he said i notice
you guys all would like you take
the cap off the water bottle and
then you put it back on you
have to keep unscrewing it to take
a sip of water and it's like
why did you do that it's so
it's so silly
and i remember at the time like
immediately feeling like oh yeah that is
silly and then i realised because if
you knock the fucking bottle over if
you knock it over if dust or
whatever gets inside of termites aha it
can have bugs lot of bad stuff
can move in yes snail and still
something to do with your hands super
long snake what exactly you know what
you need to do so you don't
smoke
oh yeah you said
andrew dice clay he didn't have a
water bottle ah you're not gonna do
the hunger other hand you're going cock
a mouse ran up my clock you
know we can say oh yeah what
if you swap these it was a
great character it was it was such
a good character special i mean it
was special and i
think that the satire was incisive when
you came in on a good point
when you take nursery rhymes and you
throw cockatoo it's like that things are
getting weird up a jack and jill
went to pakokku whatever yet you fail
lukaku what if he had just done
him like a normal person without the
character wouldn't be as popular right it'd
be more interesting to read doc
a mouse on my car that's funny
here
mouse further by ca is a map
great da o mouse ran up his
cock and that was long and haw
it's a great impression though samantha you
know i read a great interview with
her yeah ready to vanity fair why
i wonder did i read it wasn't
just you it wasn't joe you got
ugly um it was jazzy yeah my
lady but she said that the samantha
voice was a voice that sort of
developed over time yeah because
if you watch her finally yes you
know if you watch her in police
academy or i you know i've seen
her in other things but i've never
retained because she's just kind of a
normal person in those races yeah hey
the mannequin didn't capture patterns i'm gonna
have to check it out i watched
her bit on how i met your
father oh good oh how's that it
was cute and she's really
early it's just fun to see her
because she missed her and just like
that i loved dan just yeah thanks
think about how i met your fathers
i got really suckered into the how
i met your mother i didn't realize
it would take ten years to find
out it's like if someone were to
come up to you go i'm going
to tell you a story is going
to take ten years you'd go no
thank you and walk away really long
time so i'm just worried about this
one okay so like if you put
all those
intros and outros together yeah and then
in the middle you fill in the
amount of time it would just take
you to tell this
just to just to tell the story
yeah the plot of the episode he's
doing how much time it takes it's
excruciating deep layer down to really specific
conversations here's what you're wearing yeah said
here's what they walked in here's how
many people were in the bar or
the guest stars yeah i wonder how
much time the story was sorry what
actually take well okay so say it's
ah it was at ten seasons twenty
two episodes is two hundred and twenty
episodes of just twenty twenty two minutes
an episode twenty two potential i'm gonna
yeah my god it's like jim carrey
movie yeah
it's four thousand eight hundred and forty
minutes which is eighty hour but that's
with the story if you're doing aid
over in excruciating detail hours a day
it would take ten days yeah but
i'm saying if you just if you
just give the plot summary yeah so
here let me try these
sport is spoilers for how i met
your mother okay which you've memorized all
the episodes yes so i used to
live in new york yeah right
he's always believed that but what the
kids have to do something oh no
here goes dad with another story hey
hey kids sit out here for a
second okay i used to live in
new york and oh by the way
i'm gonna tell you how i met
your mother oh okay we know she
didn't ask but you know your mother
right i do like you don't run
you off oh yeah because your doilies
yeah to think a divorced no she's
dead is far ah okay so here's
huh the meaning of this is us
the most recent episode had this way
i don't want to hear this because
i've noticed the most it just had
a musical sting at the beginning that
was like boom boom didn't
i swear we were like i'm loving
love and like interesting that's weird yeah
i know my favorite music is the
music from grey's anatomy when something funny
is happening
yes simply wonderful by the way this
is getting sadder and sadder as we
wrap up suh i cried my eyes
out at that miguel episode who's with
me
um by the way my mom just
sent me a text quirky was the
game okay thank you mom um and
she she rapping now
shirin is my name
linda was the game that they gave
me um okay so this is how
my mother used to hang out i
used to hang out with a bunch
of ah people in new york they
were my best friends and one day
they were their names and how did
they dress foe were they wearing one
was jay one was everything they said
one was willow one was the naked
guy willow from
ah that wanting ovi actual and of
course neil patrick harris barney h yes
yes um and then was there anyone
else no christina baia think but no
no no yeah but then then this
guy yeah then i met this lady
and i was like really endure and
that was ah no that is um
i ice
start dating her i tried to data
for a while and it just never
worked out in jay's ya
anyway she's dead now oh no the
only just dropped me off yeah my
god you've got it goes it is
up to you oh she's just oh
yeah this ten years ago that's right
yeah she was a ghost no ten
year old she was alive three oh
oh i thought you were being sarcastic
and paulie or
it was taking so come on d
j pauli pauli hi polly want a
cracker
he want a cracker
my name is qualia
thanks anyways the visuals goodness
i want a crack simply see this
conversation how did you get
right i don't
oh did i get this right
polio
yeah
no it has to be couldn't get
through
yeah
a bow
this is not good
this is good stuff this episode yet
i love it who cares oh baba
but about pupae that popova this is
us is brian cox no longer the
the spokesperson up up up huh i
love a oh blah fuck off blah
blah blah
ah man i love the roy orbison
was able to pull that out ooh
ooh oh hey weird guy what a
weird guy ok know anything about him
except for what if i told you
about this guy
okay my friend roy is coming over
i'm kind of a weirdo is the
only way sunless is even if it's
night you only wear sunglasses she's got
incorrect something he did was just from
a video he was sunglasses guy all
the time he's incredibly pale like vampires
when were as weird well hopefully where
ice weird guys why look weird i
gotta google eddie looks like okay he's
incredibly
oh like a vampire he only wears
black he sings these incredibly gorgeous melodies
but then he decides to do a
cat sound in the middle of it
don't forget about his haircut oh yes
which is just kind of a bowl
cut sort of like a rich little
from the eighties derring-do yes definitely like
a king richard chi
kind of er who am i thinking
prince valiant's that's what value do investors
that but movement with parking
i hope that's called cambridge because of
the real king richard fucking dumb shit
ah
i've ever seen it they're just calling
king richard
again what is it they call him
that because he's good no isaac igniters
and she's like oh like the lingual
because like na king richer than i
was like oh because you're thinking of
the will smith movie what
i felt like i was doing your
machine and richard i think you were
saying king richard wasn't a real guy
i'm saying he was a real guy
the movie is based on and behold
the real king richard who's that from
back in the day like a king
yeah now is the winter of our
discontent made glorious summer by this
my kingdom for one whore you so
you skipped ah that was really good
it wasn't even done with the winner
of this can start to complete that
mad glory osama vi this son of
york this of course is king richard
the third richard as in king richard
yeah yeah the guy i mean we're
good adaptation yeah
ian mckellen one oh i like when
they called him king richard based on
the king yeah email this no
i just mean what well his name
was ricky was like ah okay this
is all just oh by the way
this did call him king richest race
happened no one calls him in that
in the movie but they're done they're
they're just saying like okay this dude's
name is richard and he's sort of
the king of his family in a
way and that's what i am interested
to me it's a title implying like
yeah you know the real king ridge
at this
guys king like king well what does
the real king richard do was he
mad wow because he was right back
there was a few of them richard
the third was ah he had many
physical issues he had sight what does
it called saif sciatica psychosis
what's ah we don't say sipho smart
no i i never do you just
did i did yeah
it's i'm pretty sure it's ah psycho
killer because high focus chi focuses with
k ketosis k y like the jelly
from guitar guy
like the famous weeki going on her
little piece
ah
the other how many red king richards
were there at least three here's how
many king edges yeah there's there's at
least three because he was king richard
the third
thank you how many king richards how
man okay i wrote how man cambridge
oh man king rochelle i know what
you're talking about you can take shape
and still no shell instead it i
accidentally clicked on the prompt we're just
how many richards are in the world
that's so funny how many two million
eight hundred and thirty two thousand seven
hundred and two
two people in the room and ass
well first name richards to typically our
names to our names okay how many
paul f tompkins oh what
come how many pool these how many
poorly he'll me d j lee d
j paulie hale many hail me poorly
is paul a popular name well i'll
tell you paul's popularity is varied in
the united states the nineteen ninety census
shows it ranked the thirteenth most common
male name however
social security administration data shows popularity in
the top twenty until nineteen sixteen oh
my can't just get a number like
richards declining you suck until it's twenty
fifteen ranks of ten i just stay
on when i talked about bananas you
were like who listens to this now
we're reading literally google yeah by the
way three hundred
thirty three hundred and thirty six million
one hundred and thirteen thousand six hundred
and fifty eight people in the united
states of america named paul and if
everyone in the us like richard why
hundred thirty six million oh no that's
just everyone
oh of all the people in the
us how many are named paul twelve
why sorry one million five hundred and
ninety seven thousand yeah when many rachel
wow as many raichur how many lawrence
let's hear it many richards alright oh
it's going to be half as here's
my problem what are the popular names
now um madison still um no i
don't know i mean yeah there's a
lot because of me a lot of
ocd
adults named i hear ya i hear
olivia is yes very popular yeah right
now oh sha la isabelle you're going
to these old-fashioned name yeah i hear
olivia's my mom mentioned that when i
saw her julie robertson phineas and hazel
yeah but phineas avenues phineas is the
name of
of biliary she's brother who's incredibly talented
good-looking and wonderful well you've got me
there girlfriend um let me tell you
something lauren is ranked as the three
hundred and forty sixth most popular given
name in the united states with an
estimated population of one hundred and ninety
one thousand three hundred and seventy eight
hey that's pretty
low that is low is yeah i
feel like i know a lot of
lore i interact with lawrence at all
times
i got a phone call from lauren
today i'm gonna text said with the
line right now whoa i'm the other
night my first time meeting lauren ashley
smith yes well after just ah is
the thing with her online how exciting
was it when it got down to
the fight we weren't going to win
and think guys guys guys guys how
many scots are in the world fifty
million what in the world
if you skip i'll come you get
the world and we just got the
us now let me tell you oh
shit bo shit ball shea letter that
hurts you i feel it hurts my
my feelings hurry you have herpes huh
by the way this guy's be allowed
herpes hahaha
that's to be laughed laptop it's not
the name sigh of that and that's
wonderful it's not the name's got it
scott scottish people
your dumb tried to tease dumbass hey
i did it's i'm not google hey
okay oh god he's too okay i'm
gonna google try to forty eight your
t tried to tease dumb s and
we'll see what comes up as any
picture of you
mother proud mother of two dumb ass
kids funny mom sarcastic women's t-shirts
isn't mad let's get those shirts okay
y'all let's make this main seldom proud
mother of two dumb ass kids i
bet that's not copy written the proud
ma you have to demand they'll cite
him and and then it'll say three
of them underneath
totally proud mother of two dumb ass
kids make the title of this episode
proud mother to casbah yes ray i
love that
it's a beautiful thing new teachers go
ahead call us on our phone line
of t-shirts that's a good towson you
like him
wow okay with all nine of courses
and haha input ah lie and put
haha in bush
i've done alright haha allow you doing
i was doing a great job to
dodge smell i was young yeah i
want candy and aha so many aha
i have something else i don't know
what lot in put haha learned english
haha law in but huh and but
ah
input ha ha ha
sorry i'm tinkering
yeah we have to
haha lion pool you couldn't do didn't
didn't da da da to teach and
continue getting getting to this pp pap
hooper's to bar it's gross
where is the grossest word did you
make cooper's oh my god that's so
nasty when you call poop exactly what
you gonna do with with the hollywood
back by the way where do you
think back when you call his hoop
chunk little bro
did you make chunky little browns
please do it at least once
plea he know i will never you
gotta come up with something that no
other family uses so that i should
be called pew pew you to make
some chunky little brown
did you make some fuel did you
have a poopy did you get a
pupa in the poo poo in the
potty boo boo that's where belongs right
it doesn't
my dog pooped and peed on florida
that was like no uri what are
the others like come on i know
because she doesn't want me to be
in the house when it rains it
pours something i just want a touchy
putin p she's upset about things i
don't really pay attention about something bissinger
yeah yeah boy yeah anyway
would life be better if we didn't
have to do that probably right poop
yeah yeah yeah considerably i think he'd
be fantastic especially vivid palace yeah i
can be able to and i know
we've lived samantha just talked about making
a t go instead of saying because
it's difficult
oh no i had a massive bomb
but if i don't have to poo
oh lovely beautiful oh yeah looks like
he could probably poo out of that
but of his
she's seeing like a hot guy here
samantha i holding jeff
yeah i'm doing the math hey jeff
okay who should i do um christopher
walken that's a great ho or did
you go look like that but over
there i bet that could go poop
with vengeance well i mean that's not
good
i can't this is bad this just
is it's just as grosses are talking
about a penis gysi all the time
she doesn't do that was she talk
about that penis juiced on my on
that penis just all the time
last night was great as been as
jealous all the time
so what is your winning
it was amazing his peer gynt all
the chow huh
swing okay with me it was a
fire hydrant summer your city
never had sex to me or your
lying babies that pete is jim
huh oh he's still going as far
as i know i left him and
you pick you see
that was the day we realised she'd
been lying to us for twenty years
i couldn't help but wonder like and
that's and just like that we beat
the shit out for season two oh
i wanna get on it bobby leaves
on it there's room for comedians he
still did she keep him as a
co
host of the podcast season he's he
gets married at the end don't you
want to be whatever the the the
other person was a podcast is terrible
that everyone shady okay yeah once you
want to be that person why did
i be that person yeah just like
aren't you like a person i guess
that'd be good it was like hey
i gone and i went to the
hair stylist that's like the ultimate parent
advice like money
you be the star of that show
instead of the oh i know i
told you that that when jon stewart
retired my mom texted me and said
there's an opening
place you know our games core honestly
how nice to have a mom that
thought you had a shot at that
job no that's cute i hate to
break it to her rather than a
lady morgana asking me what am i
going to do with the rest of
us she did say when i started
yesterday by the way she was like
so how you do podcast how many
do you do and i was like
oh like three weeks and then she's
like i say
somehow in by the way she doesn't
know what anything is so she's like
i somehow got on a comedy bang
bang thread of something and i'm like
i'm sorry she goes i know oh
look at that oh no no i'm
sorry i know you're sorry because
huh fun stuff parents they just they
don't just understand that's what happens it's
very start slapping it's very they become
your parents yeah you come in yeah
they drop you off and that's how
i met your mother whoa holy moly
yeah sam how do you like it
oh
wow i never thought about you told
me how you met my mother yeah
i just took it for granted because
those were his kids
is everyone needs how he met their
mother yeah
just two minutes ago in the grocery
line yeah but it makes each storyline
ten years and years one million years
yeah it's like watching oh this is
like the hero with a thousand faces
one of it's one of the stories
in every culture that's little stubby duty
this guy holds my ah my ear
buds together oh how lovely isn't it
fun
you have such little things that are
all nice lauren thank you for noticing
yeah i bow to you never have
anything disposable i'd say i try not
to yeah i'm trying not to it's
nice you allow leather was a lot
of permanence and all of your lodger
i got a permanent today oh yeah
here's a thing you can probably smell
it i can't
my mom used to get her hair
permed her sister would do it they
would do each other's hair because they
lived next door to each other nice
okay so they leaned out the window
and do into oh yeah there were
been to enter each other's homes yeah
but she i remember the smell of
the home permanence man it was ghastly
i got a perm once when i
did oklahoma the girl's name is curly
and
there were like well because i have
naturally wavy hair so i was like
well i could just not watch it
or whatever but they're like let's get
a perm in there who
i could just be a pig i
just shit my pupil clearly like when
other guys just kind of hold my
pants and show everyone this is what
they're referring to obvious i'm not gonna
show my penis but i would not
see my pictures so high window into
my denim sock on my penis it's
self is currently it was yesterday
oh la oh oh oh i saw
his currently or gazebo movie as mojang
gas about haha
or gaseous obama doe samantha you are
just saying generous yeah my name is
samantha do do do do do do
do do we do do what was
the actual completion lady was doing to
keep that do believe that we have
dvd labels you do delete
dad even
but i mean i do let me
find it real hard and rose so
that she's she said kerry said she
wouldn't have her back on the show
if she wanted to be back on
tuesday will don't worry it's not a
problem i don't want to do it
yeah but i thought harsh harsh harsh
yeah how how hard is it just
to like go like hey here's a
bunch of lines and you have to
say it just person
go go go like god but she
didn't want to be on anyway so
who cares but yeah i liked her
attitude in the article i thought she
was really she sounded really um confident
and knowledgable our sex and and she
knew all about how jesus' own day
and sonnets and he plays the upright
bass and he plays
is the break
saturday for cable window latin usually some
i know it's fun to do these
things and you're rich and you can
get all you should do wing it
all the sheepdogs the town never knew
such a help i said little dog
raised to leap into
okay studied for years just to play
that bass so did she
let's keep a dab of this sounds
like her together now it sort of
feels this is scary to me yeah
i thought something was going on
i almost called the police i saw
that i called them an ass and
take my laptop a cute guys i
can't have my life i
just give me dial-up
yeah take away my life i am
dee boo take away my laptop and
buffoon tune hullabaloo scooby poo
yeah the big bang los angeles amazing
how may i help you i am
a scatter your mosquitoes guide is cutie
and a puta de pie man please
we the we don't take my lake
joe dog who is charlie lou adobe
when it's okay to call franco yeah
but the loo know it
sounds like you feels like natural to
ba da ba da man american yeah
big trouble in china hey why didn't
you do american three girl put her
on speaker hey hey steven why why
did germanic and three lady when a
mannequin game to show you do manage
to he didn't know what he wound
care day within he still comes back
every dog was all around that day
huh til de dah hey please academy's
the greatest movie about what we do
i want hats off to you absolutely
find a respectful brutalized wow
i didn't blue lie you're trying to
defend us why don't you come and
get me over here my upright bass
is going to block your rear view
mirror blue if we arrest her her
upright base is going to block our
rear view mirror we can't do it
no it's unsafe at any speed oh
god she found out that one trick
what's hollow balloon
me
it's like an old-fashioned word it's like
a party like ooooo a big hullabaloo
because it's oh you're still there oh
hi hullabaloo is the time when you
see that everything goes i see you
naked and poor cases because that yummy
naked on sex and the city one
thousand times you could watch tv yeah
yeah we got there yes the natural
absolutely absolutely wreck our absolutley in my
belly ache was his folly that's right
it was isn't that sad that he
said of course it is sad when
anybody dies and yes i mean anybody
even bad people should never happened to
anyone ever
one was still alive that ever lived
yeah the world was so full and
clogged i wish we were shoulder to
shoulder with boulder holders
yeah it's always about tattoos with you
well they're nice you're obsessed with tata's
oh tap to petitti di hi ta
ta for now i did a two
to t let's keep ba da ba
lu bu bahay but how leading bow
bow bow
if you had to scat with a
jazz band was like a gun to
my head awry tapia i would you
do it and i would whatever i
could do to not do it i
would do that whenever you were like
begging the person like please i have
a family i would fly anything my
daughter
i don't want to see this on
the internet get on the stage and
scat who is doing this
diva damage come crawler you babu be
go see i never thought but does
you know what i never heard him
scare and i only saw him be
a wonderful actor i've only seen him
act and of course i listened to
him be hong kong phooey yeah number
one super guy he should be named
actor crothers because he was better at
that than scattering an actor crothers
you scoff at that what are you
on your first name to be whom
podcast aquaman aquaman aquaman thank you hanako
men hum hum mako man i want
my first to be hua hua who
my god james cuma tompkins who like
oh everybody
i just think it's two syllables oh
my god oh my time because ooma
talking to my tomkins it's a military
chant yeah i like oeuvre i mean
isn't it in being in the military
hard enough without having to do chance
whom i mean like having a having
a rhyme while you're out there like
going i don't want to know what
i've been told and then you're like
okay bold code
fold gold pretty good i know and
you have to up and you also
have to hope that you all come
over the same rhyme or it's gonna
be a messy yeah so are always
cold yeah and that's going to be
like but i think you would assume
cokes are always ice cream chucks are
always cold but you feel like that
just anecdotal you don't feel like you
need that for sure ah source
sorry yeah link my life
i never went inside when i guess
there was this ice cream truck that
used to come to the beach when
i was little and it was so
exciting and fun of wander up doing
it some laffey taxis and if you
can own one would you um know
why why would i want one
because they bring joy to everyone else
if i was rich enough to have
one i'd hire one and then have
it come by once a year once
you just do the wrong message to
already let's do it let's bang it
out when we are at samantha
lets you hang it i never had
zach so that's vague it oh and
bring it in we rubbed on each
other all night long we rubbed any
geez don't lie
um when we were at tim and
lily's wedding at one point during their
vows ice cream truck went by and
thank god it was playing music box
dancer and not turkey in the straw
what's music bunk dancing duty duty
did any di di di di di
di
dude anyway
the other trucks are duly lou di
lu did what is talking to try
to turn you strike yeah good lord
you were doing about picking out dough
yeah it was done
la la la la la la tata
you really lily daly
a little bit bit i say elmo
song they don't sell it so they
went round oh this isn't what i
didn't fucking know making that dough i
just think some know more than that
but big enough dough lilly little lilly
ga you looking for
and that's that meme of him screaming
from the back
oh my god the thing of him
being so frustrated by the rock was
so funny oh i really enjoyed that
that was cute i really enjoyed that
because i feel that showed i didn't
know elmo had more than one submission
yeah yeah for sure he gets frustrated
now we know it's relatable it's related
because those kids get frustrated too because
they feel like you just
don't understand you gotta hear how elmo
can be like you and then you
could understand how it is like when
elmo is in a rage and slamming
doors yeah and he's throwing she's getting
in people's faces yeah hey pointing their
finger their chest and he's left the
omo i was like i'm not touching
you
about that yeah that's pretty good just
how you know you're frustrated with things
you tell she gets frustrated um yeah
this usually starts to go yeah
i cry you're smiling when you describe
because it's over so quickly you could
just yeah turn cause they just moved
on to styles yeah change the focus
but yeah yeah if anyone has tips
on how to make baby stays solely
change their taper that's i'd be interested
i you know i don't know babysitter
lots of experience use virus
it wasn't an every day situation and
i'm finding myself you know when the
time change a diaper i'm getting little
stressed i'm going okay i'm gonna pull
it down if you know as tips
on how to sin run how to
stay engaged during that as soon as
you take my pants off you also
want that to stay engaging the sixth
take yeah you know like when we
filmed a movie together
there is that we were talking well
i mean you have baby you babysitting
stuff and yeah movie stuff oh i
thought you were saying because the sixth
take we really lost lauren every time
know you are always engaged i was
like five take lap guests don't go
any higher ups paulie the weird usual
ops minute
a little lower zoo doing a little
dance and warehousing and turkey in the
straw ah let's do between two friends
to between three firs between two ferns
to that among three ferns see anyone
would have to want that yeah i
know xiaomi samsung refers because i felt
that among three friends i like
that that's what we should call this
show
so take away freedom yeah and it's
called among mums wrong
do do do do you do friends
do whatever we do but if we
did get played style rebranding where we
just called it among three friends keyboard
i don't want that nonsense so i
mad that you guys aren't unhappy but
we but we we pretended like we
were actually doing for episode what if
we just take their own
format and do that yeah what's a
terrible video game that you've played is
your love em all i can't do
maybe isn't the same format just a
new name no it is not oh
i didn't it is not always talking
about little stuff to talk about good
stuff now oh okay great yeah just
like us we talk about good stuff
we talk about bad stuff hockey
do you know what last episode no
michael j o m jays wow we
really got through one hour without bringing
up the ca i feel like well
rowing we're taping this by the way
on the day of the tony nominations
and m j got a lot of
them the day of atonement what yeah
for his jukebox mew
vehicle yes yes this is raw didi
it does seem wrong doesn't it it
does seem wrong and gross also like
he's not with us no events no
he's up there with god so i'm
just saying you get easy definitely miss
slee he's doing a moonwalk with a
little harp on his head i open
my phone and kim control on and
scram oh my oh
my god which i like to hear
me she's modelling model age it's great
in a white pantsuit whibley way piddly
suit
i'm a fan she just talked like
that all the time the answer keys
are djokovic was like look let me
be frank why we don't want her
we let her type out that she
doesn't like being on the show anymore
but in fact if you heard her
speak she sounds like a lunatic zoo
just scats all the time you say
something to her she gets it back
and you have to feed her her
lines phonetically
duda duda de oh dude i today's
study no
oh the two hundred da da da
da da da da da da da
da da da oh the doo da
da de and i was gonna go
high and i went huh you did
emc together yeah when i go huh
yeah see
si lo lo
middle
okay let's take a pic
and i went back we are bad
you know what it's time for a
three cheer and that means before we
do that so i mean we do
this size decide if we're going to
do kate willie d k p s
three ch yeah here's my feeling on
it yeah i really don't want to
i mean that's all i need to
hear but hold on a second let
me say this in fairness in fairness
i want to but i don't think
we can because last week he sent
us a tweak to it he sent
us and we gave him some pretty
clear feedback because he said something about
then they win the big prize yes
it would be like we realised what
is that big price we sent pretty
click clear feedback and we have not
heard back from him no and it's
like you can you he could email
us he could call us our number
gave out the number now did we
take both of these episodes back-to-back you
who knows i mean knows no one
knows for sure no one knows champions
couldn't even tell us very sorry to
say we cannot do your creature this
is now
we tried different one yeah yeah yeah
but the other that's the other reason
we can't do is we have to
do the other oh yeah well also
we were not going to do it
and yeah we were going to do
this one we just wanted to do
this yeah yeah yeah yeah right so
so that's why we did all that
talking just now yeah justifiable that's better
so okay um this game brought in
by paul it's a it's an actual
game it's
tangible it's physical yes you can touch
the song physical game your corporeal yeah
yourself i mean i'm holding the top
of the mood i'm alive you can
see this i'm touching this just voting
in the osi mango you can see
him i'm gonna verify that i can
see malalai always goes oh yeah fi
tom p it goes down tellico
nice that's the weird thing how's that
ghost doing that yeah so this ah
this game is is the physical form
of a game played on a podcast
called i said no gifts hosted by
i love a great ah bridger weinberger
are we just stealing his thing oh
yes he sells this so i don't
know
no you didn't even fucking give it
to me it's essentially is an ad
and we and this motherfucker doesn't add
i paid for yeah that i'm doing
yeah stop listening to this show anyway
here's the rules this game the game
is called gift master you want to
take turns yes okay ah these are
the rules of the game and you
don't follow them correctly or social event
could be ruined and you will likely
lose
friends are damaged family bonds no wise
kidding about that pick up the phone
saying who's calling because he's drunk it
alone pick to begin remove the two
decks of cards labeled gifts and gifty
which i set them in the middle
of everyone set him in the middle
too little now everyone must reveal the
worst gifts ever
received then the group determined to receive
the worst gift of all that person
is now the first gracious host the
other players are now disrespectful guess that's
let's get back to you skipped up
i don't want to blow of someone
spots three yeah we don't have to
be a gracious host deals five cards
from the gift pile you have to
do this for guests including themselves know
this
this leslie the host i'll be the
hall being the host so pulp we
rely on you paul e is um
five cards from the gift pile each
july including you please paul do that
you know we have three early for
okay now if ah what a baby
one favor this baby was shooting and
tasting all night
okay so then once everyone has their
cards the gracious host selects the top
card from the giftee pile and turns
it over the disrespectful guests have thirty
seconds to decide which of their gifts
should go oh i get how this
everyone puts their cards face down in
a pile after each disrespectful guest has
put down their gift card the gracious
host should now flip them over
for one by one each disrespectful guest
must now explain why they would give
that gift that giftee once each argument
has been made the gracious host will
decide which gift is most appropriate and
that gift card will go to the
winner of the round the person to
the right of the gracious host is
now the host repeat this process until
all the cards are gone or someone
has left screaming i just can't play
games with you guys anymore
tell ya who has the most gift
cards and show them the respect they
deserve there now the gift master okay
okay right so we have five cards
of of gifts and we and the
person will have to give one to
his end julia engelmann ruler oh the
merkle unger la de dah
oh you did okay even if i
was doing them maybe doing the weeds
at first and then it just slipped
into it's a slippery slope making copies
i know you can't chime in on
this making copies on mine she's here
on oshie i'm alright i so i
know what i'm doing okay put that
in there
there
okay so now paul is the only
one to have not chosen a gift
from his gift card so i get
a little merkel now what happens the
gracious host that's you paul yes you
read them over turn them all over
and then you decide who's his best
would you just pick your own yeah
right you don't know the case you
have to say yes alright so we're
looking at i
i chose electric meat slicer okay a
brush with death and sleeping bag for
angela merkel yeah i chose a brush
with death because she's you know obviously
from germany and um they're really you
know they're really fucked in the head
yeah they're depressing people and so i
thought that in plus she's just got
a whole thing going on where she's
just so stern and now this is
a gift yeah okay well it's on
the card i didn't pick it you
literally did you gave it to me
you have five cards from ya and
you smelted so it was great wow
okay i chose the electric meat slicer
because i thought she's german and she
wants the meats
you said that like it was a
thing
huh but it's not a thing sir
i chose the sleeping bag because i
think she has retired or will soon
retire because she's been chancellor for a
long time right and she'll probably want
to do so she hasn't now time
to do fun leisure activities like go
camping i love it let's get to
next celebrity please alright wait so no
one okay paul has to pick
who wins
um just gonna pick himself me yeah
yeah okay great but then now i'm
the disrespectful i mean i'm the host
okay and they moved along each we're
all just kind of picking joe no
i'm not gonna just do that okay
just like that i honestly i do
think mine is the best i think
your argument was weird and ever the
fans will liberty is
connie chung oh
um everyone move as quickly as you
can
got it alright okay scott said a
loose ponytail because you know she had
such a tight hair hair style the
entire time she was on television you
know what i mean and so i'd
really like to see her just kind
of like shake it out and take
it out but then you know it's
obviously can't go wild so she just
put
is a real loose money what was
what was the hairstyle you imagine that
she had ah you know just very
tightly pulled back it's not true that's
not true oh it was more she
had morbid now the print value it
was closer to that shit bob for
all of her life well i'm what
i'm talking about she's grown it out
now yeah sure and she's just kinda
like she's learned to be free and
mores they're going like i want to
be the father of a baby with
you
i want to be the father i
chose a moisturizing routine that gets results
i saw you know she's getting older
and women in on tvn not want
to look their best and this is
just a thoughtful gift that i would
take your woman on tv if you're
out there oh my god however only
scenes what if you're not you still
want to look your best but i
would
just say you know this isn't i
think you'll look beautiful but i thought
you'd enjoy these set of creams
and then paul pick all picked singing
lessons and why is that well when
she concluded her show which i don't
remember what the name of it was
she famous news know she was she
had her own show that was not
the news no just sincerity she went
with a little account of it yeah
she went out on the
last episode singing a sort of torch
song by a grand piano she's wearing
a gown doing like the slinky number
and she can't sing so it's a
slam her you would give her singleness
it's just remember that it's labour your
last episode it's like wouldn't you like
to be able to sing your final
episode which was obviously hard enough for
you that you were being canceled well
i'm gonna bring that
up by saying you need some lessons
as well well i guess i mean
it shows that i pay more attention
than to not know what her hairstyle
was for the entire time she's been
on tv com okay i think i
win this one
yeah i agree all right now i'm
the host and still having to pick
one i'm doris no but then the
captain no no gift d card yesterday
ok jeremy renner oh boy wouldn't have
an ad we keep adding two more
to our pack we always have fun
i think so otherwise this number ends
right yeah i'm
thinking if that's you know i think
part of it is you you runt
well i don't know i could be
the print is too small to read
i think allowing weight must go
scott what's been going on when truffaut
time hello everyone
worry this process until all the cards
are gone okay so i think we're
gonna take two more because then you
get different oh no we can't can
play yeah yeah let's only know find
just take two oh but you know
um put it back oh well i
got the perfect one put it back
to bed i have to go through
but why did it get everywhere i've
gotta you gotta put your human person
but kind of say well i'll put
it back tente what it is okay
it's a total kitchen renovation i know
he likes to flip houses okay i'm
just giving worth it okay
we're sad oh okay pick one of
your remaining three for jeremy renner here's
mine okay paul you picked a hot
glue gun yes because he likes to
flip houses i yes and i think
he should ah gluey mouth shut and
not saying anymore
he's given the c lessons lauren you
chose chips and a medium fountain drink
i just think he wants a nice
lunch but ah he provides the sandwich
i chose the avatar official movie soundtrack
because he looks a lot like the
guy who wasn't haven't already should have
been an avatar that's right you know
what i feel like scott won all
right yeah i picked myself
anyway lets you speed keep going until
we have none okay go found okay
keep going to know no one
sidney weaver girl dirty we were got
it oh no my my truth is
revealed alright this is the so
paul you picked casual yet tasteful patio
furniture yeah huh why is that
oh first uber because i think it's
nice okay i bet she has a
nice ah like backyard area yeah it's
for entertaining
scott how scare you wow dare you
i think her buddies ny oh love
i would slap you past the face
yeah
what did you pick like chose illegal
fireworks because i think it sounds every
day that she's buying fireworks for five
dollars in the side of a highway
and i think she should have a
little fun like us regular folk true
okay and i picked a glass coffin
because she was in one at the
ah pretty much at the end of
aliens and the beginning of alien three
and so i think she
enjoy the experience of sleeping in that
again because she was asleep for hundreds
of years right yeah okay so she's
used to it let's vote who do
you think wins same
great you know i'm going to be
the odd man out on this because
i'm last so it's not going to
be a tie one last game david
copperfield okay lauryn you gotta be oh
i know what to get david oh
i know exactly what to be honest
okay i know exactly what's going into
my one car yep okay encarta mysterious
rash i picked mysterious rash
shh because david copperfield who as we
all know is a magician um could
suddenly have this rash and then and
then show it to claudia schiffer and
be like i'm gonna make this disappear
that's his penis and say i'm gonna
make this disappear into every ten year
s yes
okay who's i gave him a word
of the day calendar because i think
it magicians are too stuck on abracadabra
you say anything how about zoot to
helen brunelle okay printer ink i gave
him print rank because he has to
print up instructions for all the people
that help him accomplish his illusions and
he has to post them backstage everybody
knows do this
that virtue diverse point number zero wow
yeah exactly all that shit i gave
it to scott wow just wow you
have ah we both have to when
you have one yeah so it's a
tie so it's a tie between paul
and i do we do do we
do want you be the judge yes
i'm gonna i'm gonna we get five
okay we get five gif
it's going to pick a person yes
i can see i'm gonna okay i'm
taking out total kitchen renovation so i
five okay and you're picking the person
and you'll be the judge okay guys
you're so like the first and then
you will be the judge does that
person is timothy shalimar turkey shalimar a
tae cho
oh man i have some good ones
here what do i do what do
i do
wow okay not get that yeah okay
scott chose their face on mount rushmore
okay so tell me about that answer
scott okay so obviously we all know
mount rushmore is lopsided because abe lincoln's
got that big ass beard and it's
dragon mount rushmore down with the weight
of its
gravity so timothy he's got the crazy
hair going up to the sky suddenly
balance love it and paul you picked
a delicious pizza that's right because remember
in that movie when his boyfriend fucked
the beach yeah i do remember that
i remember that yeah yeah yeah maybe
he was horny and then he eat
the beach yeah
so he will like the regular peach
because he does not have man's just
disappear into that peach i'm going to
give it to paul ya que perder
two yea and that is more or
less how you play gift master thank
you bridger was fun great game everyone
will please call haha la inputs
and tell us what you thought and
we won't listen
okay we do have to figure out
what is the phone and we want
you to do yeah i don't fucking
i don't do anything i mean you
know it was like rita's codes are
like gift cards we couldn't my love
that yes obviously don't mistake this for
your mother's phone number don't mistake it
for nine one one imams number is
haha
in putin
so don't mix it up with important
numbers in your life don't get it
twisted on the la la la la
la song for la la la ooh
la la ooh la la song for
the the the number well also input
do do do i if you have
a saw law in you ever saw
for our number we'll give it a
go but also no reason when we
have a numbers because we want people
to make up songs for the number
call us and let us know if
you would we will just connect it
a t-shirt that we were talking about
as well yes proud mother of two
dimensional underneath and small letters freedom what
about our basic really good sure but
remember faces so it's just confusing because
there's three yeses absolutely proud
godmother of today with people think that
we scott nye are the dumb ass
children because lauren is a lady now
i don't care when i hear mom
she's a lady i know that whoa
hey joe
nondual mo
oh wow want to be the father
he did it again and the show
is over goodbye goodbye goodbye love you
yay be better luck next week
a