title
oh
ah the boots here's that tone that
tone by bobby did you just hear
there that
we're here now yeah no he stopped
and took something it means
it's like an alert alert alert alert
jack wiring test for me when you
were a kid yeah i remember him
from when i'm going to adult i
had to ah it's awesome to get
your hearing checked ah relatively recently wow
i haven't i guess i should do
it it seems like a good idea
yeah i had it i examined their
day which of course i do annual
ali i mean yeah um and i
had to get my eyes dilated which
is always the worst because your eyes
right now they have those dollar signs
in them yeah because you were just
looking at ah paul i'm trying to
sell them yeah i can just see
i want to get and it's quite
alluring i see a big roast chicken
yeah so we're a different places huh
see
okay it can be both um but
now think about selling the chicken how
like nice suits to dollar signs for
paul my eyes anymore
my doctor told me last year i
doctor told me you're better i thought
it was like i said dean tang
while being being my doctor my doctor
told me your pupils i'll die lay
they're gun feel sticky and that's my
favorite part of getting dig the drops
we like sticky in the cruise two
drops you liked that part um and
she cares she told me you really
like i do it gives me what
i'm like i don't like any of
the the process but last year she
told me that my contact lenses i've
been wearing contexts since i was fourteen
i have had glasses since i was
eight wow
she told me and i haven't worn
the same exact ones the whole time
but i yeah that would be weird
if you were the same pair of
glasses roll glasses i mean my contacts
i i eventually swearing her of god
i started wearing dailies many years ago
yeah and then last year she told
me she's like a new doctor that
i was seeing she was like these
cons
next just you know like do you
like these and i was like yeah
and she's like these are like the
iphone four of contacts and i was
like wow i should not be wearing
these oh and it was no one
because everyone just always says are they
okay like you like come and i'm
like meaning though that they're now upgrade
now they're thinner they're lighter they're better
there now and so i got the
new ones
and this because last year i got
a different new one i realised oh
it wasn't the one she was talking
about this year i got the right
one and i put them in amazing
really i can feel the difference and
feel like your eyes are being kissed
by these cons by god and god
i also my prescriptions my prescriptions so
very bad my right i got by
better why right eye contacts know right
i got better that's because i contact
no
as you're getting older your eyes get
worse and worse my but and then
at a certain point your your eye
like around this age even secure i
stopped shrinking yeah channels like four days
anything for yeah we're forty two holy
i'm thirty seven but you're just you're
kind of settles into what it actually
is
i found out lauren lies about her
age okay we not one of those
um
anyways my i got point five better
and i was like so wow it's
awesome and i can you see also
my vision is but yep that's what
i put my context when i went
because i've been feeling like my eyes
are getting worse nope just had the
wrong r x it's getting better oh
and honestly feel so good and i'm
gay
my glasses retail on which i have
oh my your ah that's so awesome
do you get do you go every
year i go over your cars i
have horrible vision and i'm always worried
that something i also have a floater
that's been driving me bananas can't do
anything about it it's just there do
you know i feel i have i
can't believe i don't their surgery but
it's risky okay i feel like it
never happens what's what are the risks
like you can die or your there's
a ring
risk that's a breakup the floater and
then you have a million more and
use it and it's really annoying yeah
or there's also something i'm gonna pass
on them yeah i see what i
said i have a thing where i
feel like there's something in my eye
something in euro
i could not identify the other beatles
nirvana oh i thought it was grunge
beatles so um food from jolie ever
seen the batman
i'm about to o know more about
the most recent one yeah i saw
most of it yeah well you know
what i think i saw exactly half
of it oh well you didn't exactly
how free i say because i remember
looking to see how much time was
left chatting and saying well shit i've
already seen ninety minutes batman i gave
you all i got tell me what
you were gonna say i fee
also so i feel like there's something
in my eye yeah that kind of
allow him food and it happens it's
it's not constant but when it happens
ah there's just nothing i can do
about it yeah and i
now i'm realizing oh this is not
good and i should tell my ophthalmologist
about yes yeah because i go see
him ah a few times a year
a few times yeah yeah yeah because
i haven't i i may have mentioned
this before i have this condition of
my eyewear there's broken pigment yes you
did tell us that could lead to
blow
tacoma would you be surprised to know
that i do not remember you ever
talking i would remember that shockingly and
yet i wonder when one time i
got my eyeballs after lasers so they're
trying to keep moore's law obstruction they're
picking losers yeah yeah they break they
break it up so that it doesn't
ah um ah rub against sm
all gross okay um but yeah i
it was only recently that i was
like this has been going on for
a while and maybe it's a serious
issue well yeah when i had this
floater i got really scared because i
was seeing it for like a week
and then going like oh god what
does this is like something and then
i went in and they were just
you and you could see it on
the thing which is very
validating like when i do that you're
not crazy well yeah like in their
cars and then everyone's everyone already gaslight
you that there was no floater well
because it seems like it's just a
figment of your imagination it doesn't feel
like it's a thing in your eye
yes like the exact see yeah and
so it's very interesting that it's like
no it's just some debris because it's
sort of like you're you see a
thing in the slight disk
since yeah not that something's on yeah
during your visions yeah right yeah there
but what i have to do is
like go like this roll my eyes
like i'm nuts and then it goes
it's because i was honestly rolling my
eyes during the show like oh yeah
you honestly look more annoyed than nuts
mo
but i have to do that sometimes
and i'll be like watching span log
oh like i liked honey i shrunk
the kids myself and get in there
and take it out for you great
kelly
do they have that technique you're gonna
bring a ma pen or something yeah
it's not honey i shrunk myself and
a mop oh okay but he did
shrink down a baseball okay where do
what you gotta come on the show
know what scotland shrunk honey i shrunk
the kids ourselves ah and we get
like a tiny like a window washing
plot yeah squeegee and yeah and so
we're up like like like like
sure i'll wait that would feel so
good yeah and then we roll it
down like they get really clean yeah
right and and there you have a
golden retriever behind your eye who's very
excited to see us yeah oh well
yeah because the one video that's just
kinda lives in my brain and there
and then there's the inside out yeah
cast is in there too not that
tune characters the cast yeah hello there
that movie though the first few minutes
i was a puddle a girl i
was cuddle of coke oh girl melted
gioco politico melted into a pile of
cola i haven't seen that one i
used to be i used to be
current with all of the pixar's and
there's a few now that i mean
i've been turning red and learning but
i love that her disguise i don't
think that's pixar
though it's not that's just dreamworks no
no just disney disney now oh rising
the that style of animation okay but
i will say the one thing like
with soul and inside out and all
this it's like pixar they're very interested
in like these undefinable concepts like putting
rules on them like i don't know
if you say yeah
so like okay so you need a
patch that like it's like like these
are unexplainable explainable concepts we don't need
to like you know confine what's interesting
because for movie you do though that's
the part i don't like about it
is like here are the rules for
to get back your soul you need
five patches
but full patches i know it was
it was just as valid as
any beliefs that well that's the that's
the problem is they're trying to start
their own religion i don't like it
because i'm a scientologist to say i
want to cut that and use that
i have to say that i can
use one when you said i'm a
scientologist to be a quote that will
oh because she's all right
a once and use twice you're gonna
cut it out of the episode but
then use it like i just said
it in real life no one can
ever cut or use that okay um
but the movie soul i really liked
and mike and i were watching that
were like sobbing and this was like
early pandemic i wanna say my comment
i mean definitely came out on christmas
when wonder woman night
eighty four yes okay so it was
a definitely do it was a pandemic
because we watched both of those alone
it was the first christmas after the
during the pin yeah and i loved
it but then i as you're saying
this i'm thinking okay if a child
is getting education from this yeah about
death they're gonna think that they when
they die they need to get
at five patches well it won't matter
then but i think that the idea
that you have an image in your
brain of what it looks like that's
a little confusing to me like if
let's say somebody they knew died then
they're like picturing the little green world
and all these things that are happening
in that and like i don't know
yeah is that good almost just the
sole way again six grams i'm saying
grams twenty four
grams between one and one million grams
we can agree on that right golden
theory how much does the soul way
so the soul is worth it's weight
in golden grahams
the key is soul weighs two thousand
eight hundred two pounds oh okay but
even the fully loaded turbo trim tips
the scale just say three thousand thirty
six pounds i mean not bad when
your serie how much does a nineteen
seventy six volkswagen beetle way
what do we got um
what came up just the value of
tamales here in another dimension another dimension
hey hey siri siri how much does
a sole of a shoe way
one point five to two pounds for
some reason it came up on mine
siri how much do you cost
oh i got dollar signs i'm gonna
sell her mysterious know we all sides
series subscriptions about to run out oh
no yeah i don't know what to
do o serial monsieur when you're gone
hey guys i wanted to bring up
something that i thought was fun which
is um first of all i did
i did a cartoon the other day
de um that i've done before i'm
trying to remember the title of it
something like tender greens or something but
um i i went to it and
is very early in the morning i
believe i got there at eight forty
five and um that's
quite early to do a voice record
quite quite early wider ah veo everyone
was very nice when i came in
and and you know like getting my
info and i was filling out all
the forms and the the nice young
like probably twenty you seem to to
be in his early twenties nice young
gentlemen after he had helped me with
everything before i did the record
it said
oh by the way i'm a piss
pig
i just love you that i'll pass
peg because like it's far too early
to hear that sentence but i like
to start my day with that there
my show last night ah we ah
variety opiates you know we have a
big band we had backup singers last
night and we have them lay there
when you say big yeah
yeah yea popular but yeah we did
giant belgian here too did i take
it so funny that like they used
to be a band and now they
pre-recorded music and a guy basically has
to hit hammer
that is already pre-recorded yeah anyway oh
and so one of the backup singers
had not done the show before and
at the end you know was thanking
her for being there and she stared
service this i thanked her for her
service i saluted her i presented her
with a folded flag you always carry
went around i always and it never
touches the ground never
because i burn it yeah but it's
always one inch above the ground that
early yeah because it's imagined burning it
i'm flag edging yeah isn't burning it
like a little bit dramatic it's sort
of like ruining something so focused like
guys you could just throw it on
the ground saying the idea of flags
being so secret is so funny it's
really like a little yeah and it's
only because everyone says they have to
be that way yeah but but it's
a law like
yeah it's crazy thinking is a law
that's stupid oh saw you trip and
fall holding a flag in public so
i don't think it's wrong because i
think you can do whatever you want
but if you're in the army or
navy i don't want to wind up
on bad legal takes i don't think
it's a law anyway yeah banks dot
org yeah don't work
um it's organizaciones it's organization so at
the end of the show ah you
know thank you for doing the show
and she said i had a really
good time oh and my brother is
a really big fan and he told
me to tell you that he's a
piss pig yeah you have to have
that level of hesitation
and i laughed so hard and i
said i'm so sorry you were forced
to say that well ok so i
did the show in portland and we
know you flew no windows oh i
might sell a different aspect of this
story
went to a place something else happened
no so i did this show and
it was with ah it was with
jenna freedman who i've known for a
while ah and a musicians that i
the musicians here that i had never
heard before but was really good and
then newman then he loves l a
this guy ari shapiro who i
i guess as an npr nice familiar
ah reporter um but a serious guy
say to yeah to convey that he's
like a serious like political reporter i
think so is frowning the whole time
i think so yeah um but after
the show we're all there to promote
kid is chubby was like it hasn't
been doing anything it's totally nonsense
yeah um holly we try to get
her to learn a lot of names
lately and she calls our friend marcus
marquee marquee and to rp she always
says marquis and then when i sing
wheels on the bus she says marquee
like i suppose go marcus on the
bus says i love you i've been
chosen in omari yeah yeah mara no
marquis yeah marquis anyway
i love it i like marquee yeah
it's a good name it's great well
my name sam i mean we're gonna
work on that we're working on we're
working up to it where she's at
the ems paul oh and she's gonna
get to peas and then to acids
yeah fair um so so we all
are signing books afterwards um jenna presenters
so she's not
there but so it's me and already
sharara oh yeah oh my god so
it's it's ari shapiro and i signing
next to each other at the table
and ah are an irish shapiro's fans
are like coming up and saying like
oh thank you so much for whatever
and then i got a steady stream
of at least seven people and very
nice
oh no there aren't they're all super
super nice gentle people coming up and
saying i just wanted to say i'm
a piss pig
to the point with ah he and
the woman who's in charge of the
whole signing are like what is happening
right wow
ah you guys are the best people
say will you sign this to a
troop his
yeah it's so good it's me so
every it's awesome you guys we adore
you as a lovely pissed pig this
weekend as well and she was very
nice it's very fun yeah very funny
really it's a weird thing and again
you guys voted to call yourself that
that's the thing i explained that to
ari shapiro and everyone i was
like i don't like this personally yeah
but we have to abide by the
vote because what are we if not
a democracy it's hard as you know
is hard when you as a journalist
should understand that i think when you
create something you can go to places
you weren't expecting and yeah part of
what it is to be an artist
and i think that we have to
accept that you guys want to be
called a piss pig and you can't
put the frankenstein back in the box
yeah
but you can't put the doctor back
in the bag you can't put baby
in a corner you can't you mustn't
you can though nobody but nobody no
nobody not sure that's what nobody does
nobody does but you can do it
it's totally absolutely physically impossible but just
nobody does it nobody does yeah why
why would you you gotta wonder
guess it would feel anti-climactic like suddenly
it's like oh look babies in the
corner yeah well i've always i've always
wondered what that would look like i
guess i could picture in my mind
yeah
alright let's take a break by
what about la la la la la
rel downtown julie brown here woba woba
web huh hey lauren do you have
the taste test for us oh shit
that's right because i almost forgot um
okay so the other day
i was the other day yeah just
walking down the street yeah and you
saw a pretty lady and y'all know
what to sell this happened all this
happened i was at my friend art
and marines home and her lover had
left a snack she has a lover
yeah she's taken a lover but some
of my business
us to tell you more you can
figure that out in your kite call
her right now
and okay no she's not answering she's
busy
but shit but so arden okay we
wanna hang in our house one of
the things is that i'm really good
at buying snacks she doesn't eat a
lot of snacks or have a lot
of snacks so she's when i go
to her house you just stay there
bring i bring sex okay but do
you bring snacks for days or just
for your personal consumption at that for
my personal consumption you know for working
on something i'm i'm going to be
hungry i want my snack
but her dude had a snack there
that she was like you gotta try
this because you love sex you're gonna
like this well i had one bag
of this thing and then i ordered
fifty more whoa so the previous previously
on three them we had a taste
test of something lauren does not like
but that i liked and paul was
good
as much as i'm gonna like write
genre of thing and now it's something
that i really like and i'm addicted
to right now okay this is called
bada bean bada boom okay these are
the front cheap not being by the
way what the listeners may have thought
she said bada bing i did not
which is was made famous on the
sopranos it was the
the strip club on the soprano yeah
wheat onion and muster so we have
garlic and onion we have that one
we have sea salt and we have
sweet serratia i will say not a
huge the flavors are you know they
there's a little bit of blending i
think now these are bra what what's
it mean when it says crunchy broad
here's how
yeah i didn't know and i felt
good not knowing okay alright i would
like you to try it it's hard
on your guy tear on the side
i'll do you're gonna have to take
up the slack here so they're opening
these body beans now paul's having the
yellow bag and scott is having the
blue bag which seasalt near having sweet
onion and mustard
and now i know what i love
okay one hundred ten calories so it's
and this is six grams of protein
this is great to throw it in
your bag on the go now i'll
eat him at home um
it says broad beans with plant-based protein
and fiber roasted for crunch and season
to perfection yes i did go on
amazon and order fifty bags instantly and
they're vegan and i've eaten fifty percent
of them at least um there's a
twenty five bag but my canary both
eating them so yeah he's he got
into elven right way yeah i probably
i've definitely eaten at least twelve bags
i would say it's reasonable at the
bottom it says vegan that it says
non gmo then there's two circles one
has ah the initials gf gluten free
right what's you i think it's using
you as you cut up yours it
looks like a fuck is you kosher
go fuck yourself oh fuck you why
do i think that maybe k would
be kosher i
i think it would be kosher dear
it means kosher huh way fuck you
why is it okay they let her
you want food means the food is
kosher it was processed according to jewish
dietary laws foods that are certified kosher
can carry a you in a circle
or okay in a circle star or
triangle a d refers to derozan stormed
a kosher product also contains
milk mallow if it hadn't malc it
would say i had melk if it
had mongoose zana malc i do like
i think they're fine they're not i
mean you tried seesaw off about which
i wouldn't say is not that that
is exciting as it gets well i
wanted the bait the baseline yeah yeah
these tastes like um honey mustard
providers yeah i like that yeah should
we cuddle bits can i have a
johnny come around try another flavor
they taste like i mean they taste
like nothing but the seasoning so it's
a success yeah it's good here's a
serratia all of them feature a little
cartoon bean on the package and he's
in a different outfit do i like
on the playbook this is a good
part about this is the good part
of it
well anyway i'm totally addicted i think
they're a great little snack i think
you're great little snack oh
wait a minute oh lord are kissing
no no na na na broad beans
i actually prefer the flavourless i like
sea salt too but i i started
with flavors so that when i hadn't
sea salt it was sort of like
oh it's a departure yeah you go
the opposite way it's the main yeah
so these were having salt on main
yeah the honey mustard not having much
okay this is the girl again that's
you're the only one that i
haven't had
your favorites yeah soy serrano this guy's
not wearing any clothes and his ass
is showing oh man i'm reporting him
to h r all the other beans
are wearing some kind of clothing and
this one's just like life why has
the behind view of the pepper it's
a bean kind of wood to be
i thought it was the serratia whatever
it's a bean
it's disguised as as a serratia oh
for halloween he's trying to produce halloween
ah um so that's a fun snack
for everyone out there yeah i think
it's fun now we're not sponsored by
them right at all but i'd let
me know this is not an ad
if they wanted part of the show
i would totally do it because i
would love them to send me a
bunch of free bada bean how much
i'd have a fifty
e cost i think so i bought
boxes of like to think i was
twenty four about box twenty four that
was like twenty four one bucks and
twenty four one bucks at twenty six
i just mean
i got two that were twenty four
so it's actually forty eight bag hit
i think more about twenty five dollars
for this was like a dollar a
bag at that point
ooh okay so you spent fifty dollars
on this forty eight dollars yeah don't
you go to the store and buy
shit and spend fifty bucks i don't
i've never spent more than thirty three
dollars at the store wow at any
store same i bring thirty three dollars
exactly in cash that's that seems really
hard and what sucks is i don't
look at the prices then i yeah
you know the the
cashier will ring it up and i'll
say can you take that off please
because i have yeah it's like fill
a card and i tell you though
i'm no i've talked about this that
i had a friend whose father would
do that at the supermarket and would
like they'd ring it up and it
would be like one hundred and fifty
five dollars and he'd say i'll give
you a hundred for ah
this sounds vaguely familiar and half the
time uncle at the half time they
would call the manager over and just
be like okay because it was worth
it to not have to it's too
annoying to put everything back on the
ship because he would go like if
you won't take one hundred then i'm
gonna just walk away and he would
and have time would leave it all
there and
walk away that's fucking it
stores work i hate that but that's
how i found out you could do
it because half the time it would
work people can do things that are
crazy all the time factly really it
doesn't mean you should people get away
with that's how i found out you
can break into someone's home i just
and you can put baby i didn't
know you could and now i know
you can i it's making me angry
yeah well i'm sure he's no longer
alive at least that's any consolation yeah
at least is that alright i did
talk about my mother dying in a
funny way less united states and then
find out that there was a child
and yes oh did she fall into
a bucket of pudding was did she
become a pile of coke
i talked to my mother dying in
a funny way
oh into the oh no look at
him pudding it puts the pooling in
the basket you three you push the
note in the basket has to reset
the sign wow
how many days that's a bill cosby
reference yeah click click click click x
zero
let's say there was a child in
the audience yeah yeah and was it
the first time they'd ever heard of
the concept i don't know i don't
know i'd like to think that it
was you who introduced them by hope
so yeah and then it was pointed
out to me that because i think
she's like seven something like that she's
like a young kid and i was
pointed out as i just said well
obviously i'm joking the mummies never die
yeah and this is what comedy is
is you make things up so you
may hate yum the idea of well
is ridiculous i started watching john melini
special other night and then he also
had a child in the audience who
has eleven he noticed the kid and
then they had an intersection was wearing
like a suit like he was
was he actually oh yeah i wouldn't
yeah i know but then and then
what of july special like the the
comment he was making as he was
it was like this is like not
like his other specials where who would
bring the kid because it is that
question like if you're a fan you
kind of know where this one's gonna
go you know what topics oh maybe
bring all
you know he's going to talk about
his paws going to go off the
rails i feel like you're kind of
a safe one though to bring a
kid to where you know your yeah
it doesn't feel like you would offend
so it doesn't feel like you're gonna
say the seaward too i feel like
kids when i've had you know like
a migraine saying horrible things that i'm
like sorry yeah why i just always
assume
like cause i'm not i will talk
i guess i'll talk about adult themes
let's say right huh um like drug
use yes smoking smoking tubes nudity brief
nudity
strong language to show your buttcrack drove
lights
oh by the way check out the
strobe lights you blast robots and you
have your ass out and you're going
to fuck fuck fuck fuck
honestly it's a great show i would
see it yeah i know
that sounds so fucking fucked by the
way next year you got to start
with this so funny
that's just so i'd pass out just
a little bit
strobe lights so runny i can't take
it i need i'm smokey
fuck fuck fuck fuck okay we got
all that oh tits tit six
oh right ah oh i'll tell you
a little ditty about a time i
wrote my ca who here like graphic
violence
um but i i do i guess
i assume that if you're bringing your
kid you must assume that your kid
is cool with this yeah but i
make an ass out of you and
them yeah absolutely how do you feel
about bringing me to a show when
she's seven yeah seven sure yeah wanna
yeah
will she be interested that's the real
question i feel like yeah i didn't
want to bring a kid to anything
no i think can't sit still and
we brought cool up sister to the
bird and the be a great band
yeah when she was twenty and she
hated it so yeah
right because you have to be like
this is our taste versus irritation i
get bored but i always assume also
that these little kids are comedy fans
yeah and that's what i always assumed
i thought because i was talking about
the millennia thing with my friend because
she was kind of like who brings
a kid that was going i could
see a being happy someone took me
at eleven absolutely because i liked gowdy
yeah yeah or if with my own
child i feel like i might go
you have some comedy show because when
you're yeah i've already said wrong you're
just being taken to all like the
world's worst entertainment usually right like you
i'm like let's go to the to
go to the opera ya know i
just mean like kids' shows are generally
terrible oh yeah i think that you
as a kid consensus that
they're bad well at a certain point
yeah it isn't a corner eleven you
would definitely be over any sort of
cubase thing maybe funny if the opera
like the before was like hey there's
a kid here yeah stop the show
let's do it a little bit shift
really should they do kid operas though
where it's like this this is opera
but for kids so it's like no
more than forty
five minutes like kids bop but it's
like yeah we're we're gonna just play
the hit we're gonna sing you know
coming to marana or whatever or is
that just me oh no that's just
classical music right so i got it
wrong what are some of the like
ah ave maria ah you got your
wriggle letto you got your loved on
them up in a lod yeah using
all the hits
like him about his kid stuff kid
stuff yeah so it's i want my
smartphone all night all day as well
hi sorry toss today or you had
some toast today and you wet your
pants today yeah right all classic little
kid things yeah kids have toast right
yeah give it tali alabama kids do
you really and how do you do
how do you toast it what does
that mean when you were young no
i mean like for what's your stove
burner yeah what's my method yeah i
have a toaster oven that i was
actually influenced to buy by dana realised
on her instagram about the teenagers lina
medina dang in the day my cousin
in law and she posted about this
this toaster oven called bermuda and i
bought it quite instantaneously while i was
looking for a toaster anyways and then
she was like showing how it works
which is really fun because it has
this little you open the door and
at the top there's a little slit
your front door yeah yeah and then
you pour it comes with this tiny
mug that's like
this big and in my network lawrence
indicating a tiny mug yeah she has
big arm spread really really really wide
like tugging fill it with water and
then you filled a little slit hole
with the water talk slower there's a
kid here
and then it is the perfect it
makes pizza perfectly it makes toast because
it has a little water that kind
of adds ah timidity to the situation
yeah yeah and the slit and you
is everything's perfect so i make the
toast in there and it's delicious wow
what brand name is bell mule
oda no way well muda were like
dutta oh i wanna take yeah we're
not sponsored by them and this is
not a commercial it's not this is
just part of the show people are
listening on and you know what but
listen bermuda please send us shit yes
send us like oh my god toe
strap me a thing this is a
retroactive ad now p o s toasters
yeah anyway
i really like it um it's especially
great for re-heating things because it can
so like something has been hot in
the past like meats or chicken nugget
and it gives it a nice one
chicken nugget what may i have one
chicken nugget please it gives it a
good texture it would be you can't
just buy one ever right one
yeah okay yeah anywhere right i think
you have to buy them in quantum
biome is lisi six right you just
say sixty i did i love chicken
nugget you know a little chicken nugget
mcdonald tez those like huge containers though
working like twenty forty oh sure yeah
there's something kind of fun about that
not for one person but if you're
having a party do you know
what one time i showed up to
a little house party was a little
house on the prayer yeah little goes
wild i've told you the story no
yeah there was a house party at
the little house on the prairie really
everybody was nellie olsen oh wow ah
manly follow zo ah that was a
question
the people magazine thought it was wow
what show are these three couples part
of and it was like laura and
alonzo nellie and whoever they were dato
won it for
and then another one i and i
as a person who watched that show
religiously but i was a kid didn't
even know i mean really yeah um
hey wait what the fuck oh so
you went to a house party my
friend was john manna he and i
were going here together this was okay
yeah this is a while ago and
ah we see
said let's go through the mcdonald's drive
thru and get like a bunch of
cheeseburgers hell yeah and we got to
the party yeah we got like
you're like thirty or something like that
wow a bunch of them few dozen
of them and it was a big
fucking hit i bet it was especially
if you're showing up when the party
has been going for yes exactly meanwhile
your other friend doesn't even have coker
you know what's up with that no
cook for me he said no coke
for you
coke nazi yeah when will the soup
nazi be cancelled
no there wasn't seinfeld knew just out
there being a nazi there was a
seinfeld new york times article where they
like caught up with the writers and
the cast or whatever and they're like
yeah you couldn't do the soup nazi
today like wait yeah you could you
could even funding not there's the saying
it's bad that he's bad about it
yeah yeah you were saying like boy
we love nah you guys think was
the point
i became a beloved character on the
show do you remember the one when
i feel like when elaine married the
soup nazi that was partly probably yeah
yeah and converted to naziism
do you remember they gave a talk
show to the guy that wrote the
soup nazi episode yeah but what was
it
it was a late night i think
a couple of shows nice yeah really
yeah he had to have this talk
show and then a show about cars
maybe i don't know some yes hey
you something only i do so about
cars huh
but so does jerry seinfeld yeah how
many donuts to jay show up with
at the right who it really was
thinking from billionaire yeah i know you
don't touch your tonight job buddy but
what does that mean what he doesn't
touch it this is a thing it's
so funny this community was a point
of pride for him yes and it's
like
the tour i live off of my
um he's like i say i'm doing
but i'm saving all my tonight show
money i'm never i'm not touching it
i'm i live off of my standup
money well voici sankey is trying to
say that he's like i don't know
that he doesn't have kids now think
now's the time to use it like
he really started like a point of
pride and it seems it's like one
of the things you hear and it
seems impressive
and then you think about and you're
like why yeah why don't you just
live with grandma whoa nice it's a
ton of money also what do i
care i would assume you are why
am i reading this um but back
during the previous writers' strike it was
like he decided to go back while
it was still going on and write
his own monologue even though i was
in the w j which i think
is a regret of his from what
i read but i mean
and his whole life filled with regret
this whole thing was well i want
my crew to keep working and i'm
like touch your tonight joe money just
give that yeah well some late night
people did pay their their crews right
didn't go into that yeah yeah some
people do conan yeah conan did shows
and it was very much like an
unwritten thing where he was just like
fucking around and everything
yeah um and letterman i forgot about
this that letterman had worked out his
own deal yeah he worked on his
own deals he owns his own production
company that he owned so basically the
deal was hey whatever they agree to
we'll we'll do you know will you
do exactly what everyone agrees to what
isn't right well here's my point why
doesn't every company do that go whatever
we agree to will do it but
i don't
understand that retroactively able to he was
able to keep going because his his
show is an owned by cbs or
whatever like the big o he owned
his own show so he made it
oh so i do anyways size gab
he anyone can cut us ideal if
they want like nbc could go cut
their own deal right now yeah they
wanted there are rumors that
disney was going to do that yeah
vulgar disney was going to do yeah
because but they they feel like if
they band together they'll get more much
like the writers are banding together to
get see this has become a strike
podcast i like that yeah we have
all the information and we're sharing it
here
absolutely all these houses the only podcast
you own yeah if you're if you're
out there looking for info about the
strike this is it this is it
so it's an explanation of why we
need writers did i mention that up
top i guess ah but we're mentioning
it now well right now the only
thing you need to know is about
how many donuts jason
iso two hundred because randy's donut here's
the thing whatever the amount is it's
not enough it's not because i saw
twenty-four i feel like he got out
there like day three of the strike
because he's like oh just none of
the strike i gotta make good from
the last twenty years some don't i
go crank up my car and get
cranked up the car
huh
anyway strike is still going on we
bet i'm sure by this yeah i
think so even i hate to say
yeah it's like nine days from now
yeah yeah yeah i think it's a
zeal still be going yeah
gonna be dry um we have to
take a break okay my good
guess what a what paul were back
oh shit really yeah oh yeah i'm
boring i'm sorry you didn't get a
chance to guess ah that we're back
yeah you're right alright we're gonna yeah
right let's hear a voicemail from oh
right yeah lesson piss pig if you
would like to call us dial
hag claims eight and let me say
let me tell you said let me
sell you something something something when i
say the name that when i say
the phone number you should say haggling
eight
should say how high
um i am saying it in the
cadence of a commercial tagline for something
called unclaimed freight and this is maybe
a nationwide thing i don't know i've
never claimed eight but the commercial would
go on claimed fright and then
it would tell you like here's the
shit that people just didn't pick up
and you buy it like what about
one boat ah thirty purses with someone
who's taking a boat on a train
was this a did it start off
as a freight train oh no but
a great that no one claimed i
was like just take a train on
a boat i understand that well if
you take the fox over first send
it's gonna want to eat the trades
yeah so just go to unclaimed freight
and buy all the green yes that's
the whole point of that and if
you're the scorpion be a frog
yep alright but i would start with
unclaimed freight on client right and then
at the end it would say to
again ah claim fright and then the
guy would come in with it's great
wow so had claims aid is in
the pi claims eight
claims hey now you will have that
in your head re yeah that claims
great and themes great alright here's a
voicemail from one of our wonderful assistants
here we go high thought lauren and
paul um i was calling in to
ask what each of you would do
on the playground at recess
when you are an elementary school oh
wow wish you said your well my
first thought was bubblegum bubblegum in a
dish
what is that everyone puts one toe
in the middle circle yes take your
shoes off no i mean you're just
on your wiki thing you gotta leave
your jews oh and i think this
is like to be like play before
you play tag are gonna start with
who's it yeah everyone puts their foot
and then you go on each foot
bubble gum bubblegum in a dish how
many
pieces do you wish lying to you
did you ever figure those out beforehand
and then yeah you start to go
like oh if it's every other way
limits it specifically yes no replies to
do the one we we relied on
the most was ah my mother and
your mother rang my mother what's our
my mother and your mother were hanging
out close my my
other punched her mother right in the
nose what color blood came out to
whoa if it was lying color like
okay r e n spells green and
you are not the one to be
it wow so we would eliminate people
person was it wow thanks a lot
of time yes he gets like that
one fun you got a while to
kill out there we also played the
ground is love obviously floor's lava the
ground is lava there outside ah i
hate when i accidentally call the ground
the floor at base first yeah yeah
bothers me and when i call the
sky the roof
the roof's really blue today cool up
you paul is fucking with his microphone
if you hear that squeaking fucking with
it i exit somehow it's unscrewed some
a little mouse technician if you're here
shooting screwed a student screwed up i
was screwed man i play what is
at hand
dbol what do you call when you
like you get the the dodge ball
and you like hit it and it's
supposed to bounce and it goes above
the line and then you you hit
it with what a bat know you're
like your fists i'll tell you i
don't know or you could like do
with your your some half-assed volleyball know
it's it's against a wall it's
against an actual wall and so my
my school had a bunch of these
walls with like a little white line
painted wide line of approximately yea high
and then we would all play this
game and you had to it had
to bounce inside i guess it's a
lot like racquetball but with a dodgeball
we know racket
we just play wall ball which is
like that but with like a super
ball you know or tennis ball yeah
and i forget the rules of it
but there was something where if you
did a certain thing the penalty was
you had to lean against the wall
with your ass sticking out and then
just like your show there were three
ships like
fuck i them back and then then
somebody would get throw the ball if
you do that that will kill
you will kill my career as as
you have a big sign yeah on
the stage before you get out there
warning this show yes it's robots
brief nudity were you sneaking strongly smoky
it's people
really good yeah and then i go
into my regular yeah yeah i like
it alright with that out of the
way we
your resume
ah but but what the fuck we're
talking about yeah so then somebody would
throw the ball at the person's ass
as hard as they could try to
hurt them oh and oh well we
would do that with the dodgeball it's
the same thing yeah ah interesting i
would play vault or no what do
you call a tetherball apparently where we
were saying no
ohio yesterday the property had a tetherball
i used to love tell them all
you get hit in the face with
that pretty brick and i asked how
was it because because coop and her
two friends were playing and they said
it smelled so bad like the balls
like the blog yeah i'm thinking no
nasty you alright our playground we should
make a tetherball umbrella yeah it's all
i'm
saying i been saying this for years
so smart
the um the little jar was all
metal and wood equipment you know yeah
now everything is so i take holiday
to the park it's so safe feeling
that completely because there's still a bad
was no well i think it i
think at first i was kind of
like why is the floor again ground
excuse right fucking rubber everywhere that i
am right right
but then when the times when she's
fallen i'm like that's amazing yeah why
why wouldn't it be that yes so
why should you have to have a
lesson here like it's like the like
the local playground like the public playground
when i was a kid had um
it was also meant like everything everything
is so dangerous yeah it had one
of those big gigantic
like triangle thing yeah just you just
vital yeah you're just climbing up you're
climbing down it'll be a million degrees
yeah son and then we also my
favorite thing was there was a ah
cement um ah it was a cement
mixer made out of cement that you
climb on and get inside wow you
pretend you were dr
it it's possible to make a cement
mixer cement because how would the first
one ever get made it's it's possible
but it's profane it's against spitting in
god's spit it doesn't make any sense
but i remember getting in the inside
of like where the the the big
cone where the cement would be asked
and it was so cool in their
dark and it was ah it was
a very spicy
feeling i want to live that for
the rest of your life i wanted
to hide from il my pain i'm
sorry there's a lot like being in
the womb yeah very womb like yeah
my mother was very hard i remember
it was hey
um i live three doors down from
a park and i remember because they're
sami eleven from i was gonna say
is that three readers down his name
now yep his view of blink twenty
two from
but it was all sands and i
remember like digging around in the sand
once and there was a broken bottle
and i cut my oh shit yeah
chills what if that happened in dune
yeah that would be a great ceo
that's in the sql he finds a
broken bottle and saying cut zan yeah
i like wow i wish the sandworms
now we have ten minutes
um yeah what else would you do
during chase each other i sliced i
haven't i haven't issue where i pepsi
i realized
how do you like
i like okay um i have an
issue where i i am now in
a permanent state of rush even if
i'm not rushed but i do everything
as if i'm rushed like putting things
away or washing dishes you want to
do that well because you're clyde just
i'm doing it you don't want her
to death and birth and you're like
what am
i'm going to spend the rest of
us probably that probably like this precious
little time i have left i got
putting stuff away gotta get this bad
wash so i was washing a wine
glass
too hard and i fucking shattered my
heart out and then i sliced my
dude that's like my my mind with
my knife situation you've got the hospital
not that bad but it was it
was bandaid treatable but still pretty no
one is really shocking when you cut
yourself like that like you're just doing
something random and yeah yeah edible but
live aid
eatable
oh okay
it was far made shooter
ah and don't go i'm here okay
so i do remember one wow one
recess in particular have a terrible terrible
terrible recess for me yeah exactly sixth
grade
before recess like an hour before recess
so my friends were like cody law
could you like could you lay who
do you like yes and i had
this in hood who do you like
i'd had this crush on this girl
for a long time i'd never told
anyone i was just it was eating
away ma'am they're like who do you
like who do you like and then
they wouldn't let me alone because i
was like no no it and so
finally i said that
and they're like okay alright you're gonna
ask her at the time it was
go around to go around yeah you're
gonna ask you to go around ah
during at recess commanding you to yeah
i'm like no i'm not nearly go
and became one of those things oh
we'll give you twenty five cents to
see my pair of shoes with that
yeah
he does new sharpies
um so so then when recess came
around it became a thing that i
was going to do and meanwhile this
had traveled through the the class and
meanwhile the girls had found out about
this and were trying to intercept her
to say this is happening oh no
and i just went up and it
like
like i was like looking for and
i've finally found it was like hey
you want to go around she went
no and what okay and walked away
did you get twenty questions i am
yeah and i stuck out my hand
they put the twenty five cents my
and i was like just masculine from
the whole thing but you earned that
money yep and i you know what
i've never touched it and honestly the
title touch mike re
yeah you've i didn't say i didn't
put it in the bank it didn't
have any interest i just had this
quarter over there you have like a
deal with those people still where you
can ask anyone to go around which
by the way you want to go
around to know a twenty five percents
police teaching my eyes they're dull guys
quarters is falling out oh no they're
quarters on his eyes he's doing times
in water on
google is a is brain squirm and
like it too
want to do another voicemail what do
we have time yeah oh yeah yeah
yeah we have time okay ah
ah here we go is that the
voicemail
hi paul
eighty call okay hi katie like to
call you guys on my way home
from work
thinking about things so today i was
wondering was on the road
open to considerable adults to be more
than dogs for attacked so now this
is not the kind of i know
i mean that you prefer but like
milling oh my god it came out
we got it do you feel we're
not stupid stop explaining it to be
you guys could answer for each other
she wants to
us to know which animal we prefer
we get it i'm sorry it's not
for oil we dedicate his which do
we prefer i mean what you say
yeah we said she's a look oh
yeah my loyal big loyal bisping oil
baby oil piss bag katie thank you
so much um i think i'm definitely
more of a dog in what way
i think i have more of a
dog energy and that cat energy i
think i want to be i like
you i'm doing what you would like
to see affection yeah yeah yeah yeah
and i think i think you've been
showing your belly this entire not trust
you
i feel like i have cat and
i think i'm a cat i think
you're more of a cat i think
that yeah yeah yeah a cool um
oh yeah your cat with sunglasses i'm
a cat you're you're a california raisin
sunglasses tax wow i feel like i'm
the wiener schnitzel hotdog like yeah that
just makes sense i'm watch the country
yes i feel like i'm one of
those those ah cows that holds up
the sign that says eat more chicken
but isabel i feel like i'm like
this swirl
on the jomba sign yeah saying you
get what i'm saying like i'm just
yeah i feel like i'm aetna the
insurance company i feel like i'm the
alpha yeah i feel like i'm halliburton
i feel like a g remember when
they changed to g ah o blackwater
changed o blackwater changed to je z
yeah o x z x x e
yeah why i don't know they're like
oh people are onto us oh no
we're not black wow gee it's like
mindspring
what's mine called lifespring lifespring change to
landmark forum ah first it was s
then it was lifespring there was land
reform yeah a lot of rebranding going
on in the gotta do it landmark
gotta do it university landmark extended her
three daughters where it's like it goes
from streep to gummer yeah jacobson it's
like hey we're not ah
cashing in on the do you really
keep us all seasons even though we
look and sound exactly oh that is
my mother actually yeah oh merrill oh
in terms of who raised me yeah
in terms of why you find the
interesting and anyway yes no she's great
of course she lovely
oh i love him is merrill's one
of the great strands i feel like
i'm closer and closer to getting a
dog oh well my dad if you
had a dog no you need a
dog viciously the series finale of freedom
the minute you get a dog he
shows over and we just go goodbye
goodbye i don't know why the show
has died but i think
you should get for that dog do
you think it's really fun i do
think we are really fun and honestly
i was having a bad day today
and i had a i on the
way here i was like upi nice
to have a dog just to have
a thing yeah who's a living thing
whose job it is to shit to
joe and that's what that's what
that works just right i don't have
one honestly my dog is very excited
to see me all the time now
she follows me everywhere to the point
where i'm sort of going get a
life dude get to my intern a
little bit much sometimes but it's nice
because i thought like so sad and
i was like sitting on the couch
to have the dog yeah to me
yeah there with me and i feel
like you love dogs
because like you you really when you
meet a dog that means something to
you yeah does and i feel like
that's very special i don't really feel
that way when i need a dog
i kind of like that's okay and
i don't really care because you have
a dog yeah but even before that
and i think you have this strong
connection with dogs yeah and you would
like what kind of dog would you
want i mean
i i i love a dog that
you can actually hug like ah like
i think a little bit bigger like
if he was standing on his hind
legs he would tower above you know
like clifford the big red oh that's
too big okay oh that's true so
like many by the way they're underselling
how big he is he's bigger than
i mean the red part
art is bigger than me yeah houses
you should be clever the gigantic doll
yeah but reward who even cares if
he's read i think be he's normally
it's clifford park with god zilla the
big yeah yeah yeah the red part
to me is the strange part i
love huskies i think they're so funny
oh but they do require there a
lot of work you might have
merlion growing up oh yeah and i
kind of love that and i think
that'd be really fun they're so pretty
and big and yeah i think they're
hypoallergenic too oh yeah i think i
might be wrong but obviously you know
you go to the pound and you
get you get you get you don't
die rescue a dog you'll like yeah
i love those stories people have of
of going into
to rescue place and they look at
the dogs and then they have a
connection yeah the connection to smell that's
going to happen me do it do
it i do i do think when
you go into a rescue place they
should force you to because it's like
basically you just pay them and they
give you the dog they should force
you to do the rescue whatever they
had to do to get the dog
like with molly or one dog just
like a t want to trash dog
who was in the backyard for two
years and like was never inside or
whatever like like we they should set
up a whole thing where we have
to sneak into a compound and like
literally rescue her with like people yelling
at us as we grab her and
like hey get back here with my
dog
you feel more like you rescued the
dog yeah this isn't just it being
a business transact so you can literally
say and it can be fake and
the guns aren't real they're they're firing
away so i'm gonna throw something out
there though i think that there should
be it should be sort of a
fifty fifty chance that the dog has
to rescue you yeah well when it
said who rescued who i was just
thinking that because
oz ensconced scenarios like oh no i
rescued this dog right it's very clearly
didn't do shit yeah so maybe maybe
there's an you flip a coin to
see a dog which scenario doge doge
coin yeah but to see to see
who goes first but you're in a
cage at one point in the dog
like goes up to the cage and
tries to figure out how to get
you out yeah yeah hey guess what
no opposable thumbs not go
to happen and then they're stuck in
a cage forever then you're stuck in
the cage forever yeah okay at the
very least you should after after you
select the dog you feel like you've
made that connection yeah you should then
treat places yeah and see does the
dog now feel the same and now
that they're outside of the cage and
then make the dog go to work
for you and say like see it's
not
oh fun that's interesting i mean you're
in the cage waiting to get fed
that tesla not hoping someone will adopt
yeah and it's like hey see we
liked where we were originally yeah each
one had a thing that was better
that's true here's what i do i
go to the rescue center i look
at all the dogs and i say
count your blessings yes
don't be me right now yeah having
a podcast
i mean i've got some bullshit with
my friends i do i think you
i think you gotta do this i
feel very excited this is a summer
project
don't put a block on this no
no clocks go visit like to spend
the summer going to different things in
like you know see it's an animal
maybe just for fun i am now
a person who will ask if i
can pet your dog on the street
yeah okay you needed i went to
the dry cleaners of the day and
there was this dog in the backseat
was sticking his head out the window
there's so many in the
in the passenger seat and i walked
up and said can i say hi
to your dog and she said sure
and i was his name was nelson
he was beautiful mammals yeah yeah you
had a real nelson perth like craig
to you yeah yeah the person in
the front-seat was crazy
and he said i named my dog
nelson i want people to think we're
the band and he was married to
nelson franklin that's right
nelson nelson nelson nelson just nelsons all
over yeah it's nelson's all the way
down
and you met a great dog yeah
i really i'm doing that more and
more now whereas the dogs and chinese
onboard for a dog if you were
to get one i think she would
be i think she would once once
he took it home
surprise surprise it is there anyone who
doesn't like that someone i know we
have a surprise animal yeah that's what's
so crazy me time you see that
in a movie it's like here's a
dog in a box or something yes
i do think my dad did that
one year he's a lunatic did not
tell your mommy i think it was
a surprise
as to her we got oh wow
oh my god yes to have had
their sunday conversation last long ago so
measure my friends you've got an automation
and they're like this doesn't mean about
why one for a million hours a
day means so much exercise my dad
would take it on like long runs
yeah and um but yeah it was
really wild and it was big
yg in our house our houses like
tight and it was like its tail
with flap and knock everything where it's
just like ah it just was yeah
crazy idea um so we can eat
so it actually was i've probably told
the story it was given to my
dad's friend who had a farm and
it went to a farm so that
is oh can't happen huh i know
i asked as an adult though
is that really true that ah so
they still don't trust you with the
real answer yeah they they put him
down they instantly put him down our
houses big enough for a big dog
we'd have to get like probably a
midsize associate
yeah yeah yeah yes oh yes oh
yes i think you should have a
nice little um a little golden retriever
i i don't know if we have
the room okay then i'm like smaller
corgi size yeah probably not a corey
gorgas right fucking funny corgis are funny
but we'll give you an idea for
a dog that paul should get
just keep lagging down you flag him
down on the street lag him down
you would actually yeah and go hey
jerk face he'll know that it's about
the dog if you say that um
i don't like this
don't do that to me don't please
don't do this
due to lauren no real clumsy don't
know so you don't want any contact
alright we have to go but ah
we talked about half claims a you
know the number yeah if you can
write to us and it's a three
cheer ah cig senate to three dm
usa gmail dot com and send us
like games
you like to play you don't have
to make up a game um yeah
but send us a game you play
cause we're getting endless variations on the
same game yeah that we've played before
you guys play that game um but
ah and by the way if you
leave a voicemail do it like these
two did well the first one didn't
say your name but ah do do
your last week tell us your name
and yeah keep it keep it brief
and you can
be asking us a question
wow that can happen to you wow
you to um you guys are great
we love you and thank you for
listening to our dumb ass podcast thank
you so much yeah and get the
get the shirt about how great our
show is so yeah it's the fact
that you know where believes the shirt
though where believes the shirts a high
hold
an area where always the shirt goodbye
by
ugh