three
ah wow ah yeah day
ah welcome to three um the show
where we sing three really loud yeah
that's what we do and that's all
we do we do that we talk
about naps and farts and now that
we've done it goodbye first-ever yeah
we're getting so close to the end
of our season are you guys said
um no
you said you're can have a little
bit of time off where you're not
going to talk to yourself oh i'm
so excited
tom talk to us scott cool ah
i'll talk to some of you people
listen scott
people think we're friends in your life
don't look like exotic assad oh gimmick
paul yeah radioshack have you posted about
yeah let me tell you something i
made fun of this hat online and
then this little son of a bitch
named kevin barnett bought it for me
and sent it to my house where
your wife sleeps well my
children play with their toys wow
that was generous of kevin he's good
i mean though he's got a lot
of money now is it generous to
do something with someone they don't want
you to do but now you're wearing
it actually looks good while i'm wearing
it because i can't lie it does
look good it looks actually nice it's
like radioshack do i want to endorse
radioshack
either aren't they out of business so
who cares no they're not there's row
but they're still selling and that's the
worst name for a store that is
supposed to be technologically advancing yeah i
thought radios they thought those were the
end of the line know they'll like
oh okay
radios know we have computers sure we
go into your shell shack as a
kid and it was just sort of
so grey in there
technology used to be grey
see lauren you missed the brown period
of america when everything was brown and
tan okay so then it became to
be like now it's really cool yes
now it's the future yeah so everything
is grey but when i when i
was seven days wear earth tones yeah
yes earth challenge everything or ash brown
was carpeted evra yellow everything carpeted yeah
yes i've heard about brown wood everywhere
wood everywhere i don't think that palette
is that bad actually i don't hate
it personally too much brown though what
would you say the palette is now
quite good question i guess white new
joint offline like eggshell neck um like
cream
tan yeah bav everyone like everyone likes
to ah act like you know the
style is minimalism open space all white
i don't like that i want to
have maximalism i want to have a
lot of shit i want a lot
of crazy patterns and colors bay
what i want i want the walls
of my home to be decorated with
tattoo art yes my title is tattoo
art like doesn't start to ours yes
no i said my tyson's yeah but
because she's as well hi guy what
does your head because it's datu art
i weirdly enough i've been doing a
lot of research about this lately and
the nineties where where there was so
much stuff everywhere and all the walls
were different colors and stencils and even
couches had patterns and it's too much
also ugly yeah too much lava lamps
you can everywhere classy
with pattern yeah yeah yeah pretzel gang
talk about patterns
now it's in your head your head
is joshua me writing these summaries are
no i mean that's like that's the
question we don't even know josh is
off to each bip ah going on
some walk about having a vision quest
and then i'm here yeah i think
what it is is josh is out
of town for two weeks but i'm
acting as though he's not gonna be
able to do anything
thing when he comes back to josh
go to space with elon musk and
jeff bezels i saw think that there's
like a change dot org position to
get jeff bezos to stay in space
who would pay what was it thirty
seven million dollars to go to space
for eleven minutes i guess a guy
who's a trillionaire yeah eleven minutes so
what you go up walk around come
back walker boy wait eleven minutes in
heaven whoa with showing up zero-sum yes
he's going to make out is it
sir bezos can we just figure shows
us business lexi inner space right it
does we've talked about that yes is
jeff bezos and what do you want
us jeff bezos and what he wants
to do he's bounding from the
i'm old enough to remember what episode
was a school book website jeff bezos
by the way is not that far
off from most star wars names no
it's not their star wars or that
bad i mean saga rera which is
basically just shagari or saul guerrero his
friend rose yeah ryan
his best buddy they were in homeroom
together
um like you guys lord i want
to ask did you did you watch
probably the same question go ahead scott
okay it say it together yes three
two one did you watch nicole on
july twenty nine celebrity dating no i
taped it and i haven't gotten to
watch a yet again it's funny yeah
i can't wait ah that
show is is so many layers of
ridiculous that i don't even know what
to do with it how how similar
is it to the regular dating game
and who are the celebrities that are
on it so it's hosted by zoe
deschanel and michael bolton
alright i'm going boy
already i'm saying who what where when
why and then it obviously from scholar
michael bolton great choice so well he
is funny um and well from his
valentine's day special i know that um
i only watched the first ten minutes
to show the one where they had
hannah brown from the bachelorette as the
celebrity contestant the differences is the how
many dating shows
does she get to go on she's
exactly the differences is the the person
picking from the three people behind the
wall is a celebrity this time and
the people behind the wall do not
know who the celebrity is oh so
it's it's celebrities dating regulars i know
yeah i wondered if there was any
ginto ah
i wondered if there was any intel
you have how the date went oh
i should find out okay well i'll
i'll text her and ask maybe by
the end of the show we'll get
a little bit of an update on
that and if they went on a
second date and the show paid for
it yeah okay did i tell dev
i talked about when i went on
the ah or audition for the dating
game when i was eighteen na
no you sure have not and here
we go story commencing now okay so
my my good my my really good
friend at the time frank martinez
um the guy who cut my hair
um he say give your friends ah
he said we should go on the
dating game we would watch the dating
game at his apartment and he was
like we got to go and we
can win a trip um to to
wherever they would give trips to hawaii
usually actually a year after this story
takes place i
start dating a girl who and who
went on the dating game as the
person who picked and went to hawaii
and never spoke to her date ever
on the trip to hawaii just hung
out with the chaperone having to go
on the date having to go with
the date to hawaii seems like a
tall order yeah exactly but they send
to chaperones so that you're not stuck
with some weirdo
who assaults you and so she keeps
the whole thing she just it but
it was a woman parsers she just
hung out with the chaperoning okay so
that was i love chaperones yes so
that's my kink so frank and i
were like our shepherds cooks
ah now this is a great philosophical
question are all chaperones cooks by their
very nature because even if you're a
shepherd at a school dance you're just
watching people grind that's right and the
chapter on traditionally somebody who wants to
be with the person or people they're
chaperoning i don't see i mean if
i were a chaperone i don't see
nothing wrong with a little bump
and grind personally but hey publish several
i don't see death row a little
upgrade i don't think you're going to
be selected as a chaperone anytime soon
okay alright ah hey i'm i'm scott
i don't know anyone at this school
but i don't see anything wrong with
a little bump and grind okay just
trying to apply to a chaperone all
over the school system
so frank frank was really adamant and
i was kinda like his girl friday
is my good friend frank barber he
was really out of it which and
frank by the way i should mention
frank
isn't was and probably is a really
good looking guy like like all the
all the women we hung out with
constantly like can anyone robert lee still
is yep
ah sorry failure sure
so he had the confidence of someone
who is gonna go on dating game
and do well and i was like
you know he wanted me to come
along for moral support or whatever or
or he genuinely thought i might do
well but i feel like i sabotage
my chances because i dress like morrissey
essentially were a cardigan and these big
ah late eighties
giant working girl glasses wow what's working
girl glasses we'd like to sleep jessie
raphael glasses yeah exactly so but not
color not to like red you know
no like kind you'd wear to wear
off yeah yeah so we we go
there and they they put us in
a room with like twenty five guys
guys and they have a woman behind
a partition who's asking us questions and
we do it three at a time
and so i'm like third i think
i'm bachelor number three so this is
just this is practices like the additions
like this the audition cc behind the
thing it's like it's like some some
guy
like why would you do it right
yeah that's what we're thinking yeah so
we we she asks ah bachelor number
one she goes if you get have
any key what would the key be
that you could have and he goes
the key to your heart you know
in that masculine way and she goes
my heart doesn't have a key bachelor
number one
and he implodes
he goes oh well i i would
i would then i would lock your
heart up and i would tie you
up with chains oh won the tie
you up and put you put put
you in my basement and lock you
away you know i would have key
he just has a total fucking mess
althouse pieces
i forgot what i said ah i
forgot what i wanna see like a
key to the muster four door i'm
just like morrissey and i'm wearing working
group lessons
so it doesn't matter what i do
diaries
um i imagine i did relatively well
in the talking part of it but
there was no way i was going
to get cast looking the way i
looked because everyone everyone this is i
mean this is nineteen eighty eight and
everyone is wearing like super open shirts
and his huge think they're all huh
can you believe he had to be
in that time yeah so the only
other
are things that i remember is finally
when they revealed who was behind the
partition
and they opened they opened up the
partition and it was a really beautiful
woman and everyone applauded
yeah like whoa we never expected she's
fucking weird like that
that's all that's all i'm saying saying
yeah needless to say i never got
on and neither did frank weirdly enough
because i thought he was a good
looking guy but ah well i think
i told you about wanting edition for
america's next top model when i was
in college that's no deal
ah what the fuck is going on
here today
i told you about this insane thing
that you would remember for the rest
of my life i told them on
some podcasts but um i was in
kalos ah fresh know i was a
sophomore in college and
they were having like an open call
for america's um in chicago in chicago
in the okay and my friend my
roommate was like you gotta go do
this just go so like hey you
ever modeled before and windy narrow think
you should do it um because i'm
skinny i think that was like the
whole thing basically it was kind of
like just go maybe
get on you'll be like the comedian
who's like a model or something to
be reared you know such things like
an angle yeah yeah there there was
i remember like in the second season
or something basically a a total dorky
girl who just happened to be tall
and skinny and they just glammed her
up and she was well yeah they
always have one of those they they
suddenly she suddenly had this like so
sexual liberation where she cheated on her
boyfriend in a hot tub and was
like i think i'm gonna know like
i she was a nerd who had
never been considered pretty before whatever so
yeah i can see this yeah okay
so fuck you
a talking dork
yes they do they often do have
like people who are just kind of
gangly who like have no idea what
to do with their bodies and then
somehow on the show and so you
know it's not totally out of the
realm of possibility yeah um is what
you told yourself yeah when i was
like i don't even we took some
pictures around our apartment oh do you
still have them busy yes i do
oh
please post them to the instant i
i'm not gonna post them because i'm
in a bikini oh yeah yeah i
know you had to do a bikini
picture but but i was being funny
because i couldn't help myself and i
couldn't be normal so um have i
do our you how do you how
are you how can you be funny
in a bikini how we get any
funny below drag my hair
and making a face but standing in
the tub yeah yeah yeah i'm electrocuting
myself ah that's funny it's not funny
so i don't know if they ever
so well the way that it went
if they ever even opened your envelope
a little i don't know if they
did because i i don't mean i
don't know if they ever saw the
pictures because i had to go in
person i was like a cattle
call and so i went to this
um hotel downtown in chicago and i
was what my friend came with me
at first but then she had to
leave they only would let people stay
if you are auditioning because they were
just hundreds of people oh yeah yeah
so it's not on top friends yeah
what a racket though to be like
hey come to a hotel i
i want beautiful women to come to
a hotel okay harvey one gives me
pictures of them in bikinis
so i sat i like went up
into this big ballroom where you had
to like fill out some forms and
um a way to get putting like
a given number i promise i will
be a model if i'm yeah
yeah away right i will uphold the
duties but i've never met chester i
don't know what was um so then
i sat down on the floor and
i was like filling these forms i
remember i remember talking to some other
girl for a while while i was
there and then um we had to
we eventually like numbered up and you
had to get in line and they
had us like walking a line going
to this other
our big um sort of ballroom events
like that it wasn't even that big
was kind of so it was kind
of dark and weird it was like
this weird big empty room like a
meeting room and they had us line
up around the perimeter of the room
like girl style but we were basically
front tba
like my chest was to someone's back
and i'm saying like we were in
like ah align okay and no but
other things but you weren't side-by-side we
weren't facing out and they also said
they kept saying get close together get
close guy run run and you couldn't
run it was one
like they were just being mean they
were like ryan like get closer together
like and like squish it as much
as you could you basically were touching
the person in front of you like
they're back and then you turn your
head out what they had this are
you running in a circle or what
well they were they they're saying run
like like get rid of the gaps
so go together
oh so there was no ability to
run you i was one inch away
from the bridge together i'm losing my
erection
so there were there were these like
three or four judge people i know
they weren't from the show i mean
they weren't it wasn't tyra know you
rising judge joe brown
judge reinhold
the judge dredd ah and so we
like then you they would pass a
mike around the room and then you'd
turn your head out from your perfectly
like um you know sideways body and
say here name age height and weight
and um i remember a
same time they also need yeah they're
like we got a couple
but they would be zooming a camera
in across the room on each person
as this happened and i remember it
being really weird because there were a
lot of girls there who were like
five four and i was like this
before before they changed the rules that's
right i forgot about that because there
was a rule about height yeah i
kept i was sitting there going this
is not even
fare like that like i'm squished in
here and like half these people aren't
even tall enough to get on like
it's just like rick yeah yeah and
but besides being tall is your thing
well it's just only mine just me
and then they picked the way they
go like ok number forty two one
hundred twenty thirty five and then like
that was it they picked like a
few people
from it and then they got a
whole new batch coming in and that
was the end of my journey and
i was oh my god but you
had a video package right when you
look up from your journey yeah yeah
so it's compelling um and it also
your story was also reminding me i
auditioned to be a model when i
was um in in high school my
from my friend wanted to do it
and so she asked me to go
and do it
with her and it was like this
weird open call thing it was it
was just like some who even knows
probably in becca seventeen magazine or something
like go to like them all and
do this thing or it was like
some weird ass convention center and i
got to like a i got a
couple rounds pass my friend which that's
doesn't feel good that's just sad oh
yeah
when you want to go and you
were just wanting to go this is
the typical story you hear about auditions
where it's like i just came to
yeah i'm sitting in the hall and
they were like you look like you'd
be an amazing actor yeah and then
i didn't get anything out of it
and who knows if anyone did but
it was super weird looking back at
it like just thinking about my little
like self being like hello like
all scared my braces what if you
would become a famous model now you've
ever been a babysitter
well the part but i was worried
about with america's next top model was
like i don't want this to be
how i get i think going because
it isn't my intended path like i
don't want to be but doing this
can i do it i just did
it because my friend said i guess
yeah paul vi it was it was
something to do yeah paul
all of you ever audition for any
weird show i auditioned and won american
idol and twenty sixteen oh that's right
oh no i know i don't think
i ever did i mailed a shower
or no and never audition for a
game show i never i never knew
like when that was happening or and
i never thought about it and you
know what i mean the the weirdest
audition i can remember something that i
was not qualified to do and i
may have told the story before it
was an audition for the original mad
tv and movies like you have to
have five characters to do in the
audition and i was like i have
zero character so i did that for
the data carvey show yeah so there
night before i was like one of
my what's a character like i had
no idea how to go about it
and so the next day it was
just me and the casting person um
um oh goddamn marsha can remember her
last name marcia it was marcia marcia
marcia gay harden and cult jam um
there this before they met lisa lisa
and i sat in a chair across
from her she was sitting in her
desk and i did these just made
up things
that i had not fleshed out at
all i had no i was just
like i just gotta wing it and
see what happens and she had this
frozen smile on her face she was
so she was smiling at me like
she knew the entire situation like this
guy doesn't know what he's doing
yeah it was given this audition he
doesn't know what he's doing and soon
this will be over and it'll be
fine and there was i did the
same thing for the dana carvey show
and one of my characters was the
guy who's left-hand slightly shakes when he
talks and you just do normal my
just like it's just a monologue buddy
will like his hand was shaking and
it was just like
like what the fuck of my day
and then i started turning down auditions
because that i wasn't right for because
it's just a waste of your time
yeah hey there time you know everybody
just thought you were nervous oh no
i used to i introduced it as
the way this character also his handshakes
this oh my oh good handshake and
they all um forget what they're talking
about midway through oh this character also
may or may not have a wet
spot spreading out over
ah
i i audition for two game shows
i audition for i i auditioned for
luck and like press your luck no
just luck it was called luck um
and the hbo show that kills horses
yes i wanted to kill the horses
and then i and then i when
i was a kid i audition for
jokers wild did i tell you about
that
that sounds familiar actually but i was
like nine and i auditioned for the
for the kids version of jokers wild
and it was so painfully shy version
yeah they had kids on it and
i was so painfully shy and knowing
i was so painfully shy and not
giving them what they wanted and i
wasn't outgoing and they would ask me
questions and i would give one word
answers and they were like do you
have a girl
friend and i was like no they're
like okay thank you so much for
coming and my parents had driven me
down there and i felt just this
crushing like what was i doing why
didn't i like open up a little
more just like felt horrible when why
can't you be like that on this
show
like like less outgoing yeah and yeah
can you be like less self-confident i
wait i'm trying to forget it i
can't get it but now i will
waste everybody's time trying to remember i
will always i always wanted to be
on game shows i love gameshow so
it's been cool getting to be on
some and i find that to be
like one of the most fun random
things to do as like an actor
it's so fun to get to i
was on um what's that one with
meredith vieira hold on i'll get there
they have to guess the words while
i was on it i can't remember
what it's called i mean she did
millionaire but you what's the object of
the game um you're with like people
who are you're like on their team
and like you have to guess words
with that pyramid is
no it's a different one oh wait
you are but where you were on
pyramid right because i remember that was
the one thing i told my agent
my agent after i spent wrapped bang
bang was like what do you want
to do with your acting career i
was like really the only thing i
wanna do is be on ten thousand
dollar pyramid i want to be i'm
human but i was supposed to go
to new york and do up in
the pan that the pandemic happened and
i couldn't go oh you didn't go
knowing i was so jealous when you
told me you were gonna do oh
my god i was so excited know
they um the show is called twenty
five words or less yeah and so
you have to get your thing across
in you only have twenty five words
can't say the words you picked out
on this show
i'll just say twenty five words or
less good luck
um but it's really fun because you
get it's like it's high energy in
the present like the person you're playing
for wins the prize or which is
which is really fun to like it's
like fun pressure to have on you
that you want them to win yeah
and i enjoy that the only game
show ever ever been always make me
laugh but i was oh yeah it
was instant yeah you were you were
i was wanting to be made laugh
no no i was like the contestants
the contestants have to not laugh for
sixty yes i remember the money i
think that was the first tv show
i ever did wow what do you
guys i i first of all went
through all of my i did a
number of tapings of that i think
it did like six show
something like that and i ran through
like all of my philadelphia standup material
like in record time and never made
anybody laugh and then it got to
the point where i just had to
like make
yeah there's something so brit about someone
just staring at you not lasting a
horrible yeah that's a horrible like he
has something you have to i think
you have to come out and be
like a monkey or badly sorry yeah
yeah guy was that was sort of
what i mean no so so we
did the audition where where there was
like you know it was it was
like
your audition lauren where everyone was in
a circle and then you went into
the center of the circle and tried
to make one person laugh you know
god that's yeah and i remember like
destroying someone within like three seconds she
just like burst out laughing at what
we were doing and then choosing me
to my for me d
i'm handsome i love to get help
how hard you are but so so
then i got on the show and
um the they the contestants were introduced
and we walked in i heard oh
no from the from the crowd and
they were not supposed to do this
but the person that i'd made laugh
in the audition
was my contestant they were never supposed
to lie yeah and so she already
knew what i was going to be
doing and so i knew you were
the funniest guy in the world but
you blew it because she was like
that's not funny anymore yeah so i
i don't think i made her laugh
in in on that show but i
ended up doing doing three episodes dead
i don't they should have had the
contestants be mixed into for the warm
yup it's like you should not be
privy to it anyone to do it
should be like the people on the
staff for whatever people don't stuff to
eat on it
but i do the other part i
remember about that audition is like the
the executive coming up to me and
going like hey you guys really funny
and no one else is getting cast
but you guys are
and in front of everyone yeah well
to off to the side right and
and because i was a new you
know person trying comedy it was like
oh wow this comedy central executive who
is probably like what a twenty eight
year old dude yeah you know yeah
likes me wow this is good you
know it really helped me
career yeah here you are now with
us yeah here you are out with
us do you have thoughts about that
like well like now like if so
if that person kept you now and
you had the perspective of your just
a younger person who's telling me this
or whatever like does that change like
does that change for you i mean
it's also being in the business longer
and things but like when
someone's younger than you in a position
is that weird i find it weird
when someone's way younger than me it
is sometimes i remember having a meeting
i had a pitch meeting and i
went into aa to pitch this show
and it was two young women and
one i had met before when i
had not met before and they were
they
they were like i think they were
both in their twenties and yeah so
i'm pitching it in but which was
fine but then like at a certain
point ah the just for laughs festival
came up and i think i said
gfl and i said to the person
and i didn't know ah just for
laughs and she went yeah no it
just flashes i've been
there i've been there many times yeah
and i was like inside i have
not even done the pitch yet and
this is over yeah yeah and it
was ah yeah but i like that
you sign it's pronounced shuffle
but that's like her insecurity for being
young like you know like no i
am established i do know what this
is and oh yeah so it goes
both ways but yeah yeah i don't
mind it i love youth and it
just makes me feel figure-eight anytime i'm
in a room with it and i
don't like young people but i do
like their blood which is helping me
stay immortal yeah i love that it's
great
right and you're getting that put in
like every night i'm doing a pudding
every night which is young people's blood
things with chocolate it's a delicious go
down a little yeah yeah you're getting
a pudding every day i didn't think
that it's so i took it around
with it we take a break i
got the body up saying my jail
cell
whoa
huh
we're back with frito ma yeah last
you a lot during the break we
go to a cold dark place and
we get really scared we missed the
the listeners would like the phantoms in
defensive zone
so are you doing you left at
that like you you knew what he
was talking about they don't know he's
doing that i know dallas but i
still think something's funny i don't know
what is going on that's always the
funniest things yeah right when you're like
you walk into a show halfway through
that your spouse's watching and you're like
whoa
some so rude for nothing really ask
us what we're doing tonight while you
looked like you didn't have anything to
say wow i love this show i'm
trying to help you man can i
ask how are you guys do you
feel adjusted to life again or are
you still is it still like an
adjustment
i'm i'm slowly getting there i i
um you know and as everyone knows
we record these a bit in advance
right now but when i had my
second shot and i'm
your second shot is always had yeah
but i'm i'm not at the point
of it being fully right whatever you
have an couple weeks or so have
another week another way
but it's making me feel better just
to know that i have it yeah
yeah like i had to go do
a voice over job in person yesterday
but they had it set up where
actually i walked straight from the outdoors
into like the area where i would
be recording and i never interacted with
a person even breathing the same air
so you like how to set up
where you went from outdoors to indoors
interesting yeah but i didn't talk to
a lobby or go
booth boothroyd the guy is and then
go damn you straight into the break
um and it was just nice just
to feel like oh it's not as
scary so i'm getting i'm like slowly
experiencing that but i do feel like
because i i waited a bit to
get it that it's like everyone's living
so fully i'm kind of like
just not there yet and that's been
comfortable for me but also just weird
so i'm i'm looking forward to being
able to just go like do all
my little things and have to make
some appointments and also see people i
mean i don't know i'm like i
got invited to a pool party on
the fourth of july and i i
mean if i had had my baby
by then i'm like
maybe well maybe maybe
cool party and they'll be fun to
see people and like have a moment
that feels normal for a sucker which
could be great i feel like i'm
back already you know any mean like
i feel i feel like i'm just
ready to do normal things again and
it's it's kind of i'm now at
a point where it's kind of surprising
when other people
apple are still i mean we with
the mass monday was lifted i still
like carry one with me just in
case because there's a lot of places
even last week that i've been to
that are still like you have to
wear a mastcam i have one in
the car usually and i went to
an eye doctor appointment and it wasn't
on the way i was like let
me just make sure i have it
and it wasn't there and i was
so i hadn't even thought about even
wearing a mask wow
oh yeah to it it's it's like
a switch flipped once i got past
that second shot yeah and when once
i went into the first restaurant that
didn't make you have a mask it
just feels like weird to have one
on now so i know but i
also like i mean it's interesting like
i have um a cousin who lives
in the midwest
rest and in ritchie cunningham area milwaukee
perhaps rhonda wearing a mask for her
comfort but then some people were you
know people tend to be judgment because
the town is really republican you know
yeah not yeah yeah into it and
so then that's like a whole thing
too it's like i just want everyone
to do what ever
one should be able to do whatever
they want to do my mom was
telling me that she still wears a
mascot church because you know she's down
in orange county and they're singing in
it's yeah doesn't want god to be
the identifier
why a lot of people there had
gotten vaccinated is that i said i
would imagine it's a little lower than
law but but she just you know
and she's vaccinated and but she just
for safety she wants to to wear
it for right now and she says
everyone at church glares at her at
church see that's the thing i don't
like the judgement around it because i
feel like it's
just like if you're gonna it's a
it's a it's a big adjustment after
wearing it every day yeah for every
little thing i'm being nervous about everything
and then just exactly back to everything
so not happening it's it's so weird
that people take it personally like yeah
wow we all know why yeah but
it's it's so it's wild it's still
so wild to me i can't wrap
my mind around so it signs
yes everything is so nuts but i
will say that i like we're flying
soon um for a funeral angeles yeah
and then later um and then later
and in august we're gonna go to
the south carolina oh and you get
to go again yeah i'm i'm we're
both so looking forward to
ooh it um but i i don't
think i'll ever get on a plane
again without a mask yeah i think
i think that's a good thing like
i mean that'll probably just help a
lot of people not get cold just
seems like yeah i mean i feel
like jimmy pardo doesn't he always get
sick on a plane anytime he has
to travel so like he should just
do it straight away he should yeah
because i would like why
wipe down my stuff if i had
clorox wipes on me or something like
kind of before everything like when i'm
flying just like we never do that
every day because it was like oh
sometimes it would seem really gross and
other times i just wouldn't care but
i do think i would do that
now and i don't know where mass
do they do they make you wear
a mask on the plane i don't
know
we don't know yeah we were traveling
in in july as well so we'll
see but man i sort of miss
the days of planes though like i
remember when i flew back from milwaukee
to to move back to la and
the guide next to me in the
seat next to me just like pulled
out a flask and was like yo
awesome it was just a fox and
our normal imo
those days when you're gonna smoke on
the plane now i although my first
plane trip i took there was a
whole smoking section it was it's bizarre
it's still fantastic there's a section section
like you can just pull a curtain
yeah okay so i smoked on a
plane to la nice and it was
after they banned smoking on domestic flight
lights and then after be gone or
ah yes it was ridiculous it's like
oh wow
a smoker you must have been like
thank god oh yeah my real do
indulge my disgusting habit yeah and the
plain stank
this was great but yet too interestingly
you guys are like fully living your
life
i mean like mike basically is too
because he's he's vaccine he's been vaccinated
much longer so like he's been doing
stuff and it's just so it i
feel a little bit like a shut
in a little bit still like i'm
kind of living i do i honestly
like it hasn't gone back to normal
yeah it's it's where we're still at
home more often than we're not i
i think because we're only seeing vaccinated
people and we're we're yeah we're not
going out to eat all that much
and we're you know it's just like
baby steps in a way but i
feel like one when i am with
people it's now not even a thing
like that jack nice that's yes absolutely
i've been running ah like back to
like running errands a lot during
the day jazz nightmare yes i love
that yeah it feels good like i
used to yeah it is you know
it used to be a pain in
the ass i was like oh i
gotta go pick this up that go
dropped out of law and now it's
like yea guy gets go to the
post office i get to go to
the dry cleaner or whatever yeah i
really enjoy running errands and i
like idly shopping and i love going
to the mall and i love just
like i like just do whenever i
feel like doing all day
probably swimming in the only river
like shitting in the middle of the
street but i will say i was
thinking about this today because i'm listening
to amanda klute says ah audible book
and shooting the hoots amanda clues her
husband nick cordero was oh nice passat
getting out early enough yeah
just kidding but um it's not a
shino you're too it's like i know
that name i've still gonna go for
it i listened to her audio book
and it's really good and um i
really i'm really enjoying it but it's
also making me feel like i don't
regret at all taking everything as seriously
as i did the whole time and
yeah absolutely being super obsessive about all
my
a little habits i yeah i'm totally
happy i was like that and i
i'm sure i'll be able to drop
it all when it's fine but yeah
yeah you just never know i mean
and and i was kind of like
when i got the the second vaccine
and everyone was like the second one
is bad and then i had no
symptoms i was kind of like i
wonder if i wouldn't have had any
symptoms if i got it but then
i read
read an article that was like it
did it's not an indication of how
right yeah i would have i was
worried about that too i was worried
about cause everyone did kind of relationships
that i just like all the people
who still have weird smelling problems i
know that there's so many long-term effects
you could have so it's just like
yeah just feels really lucky to get
to this point and yeah we were
very fortunate that we were
able to continue doing the show oh
you know not only over zoom but
in the backyard yeah it's it's ah
your listener yes we were very lucky
to have jobs that allowed us to
do that yeah yeah oh yeah i
that's a big part of janie and
i were talking about that that's like
we have the the luxury of being
able to
like be under lockdown and keep it
really tight and even though we did
we follow the protocols we still felt
lucky that we never got coded yeah
of course i mean i was still
going to work on good girls for
a lot of it too and like
it was it felt as safe as
it could because they were testing so
much and like we got tested twice
a day
and i think hello did a read
a relatively good job with of the
you know what i mean like you
there i mean actually it was still
weird because it's like as the actor
you have to take your mask off
and everyone everyone else was wearing a
mask and a shield shield and saying
because they didn't like you didn't hear
so you got you heard stories about
you know production shutting down
yeah but you didn't hear these stories
about like well you know the star
of clarice is dead today right
yeah no i know what i'm so
scary if it like started becoming like
that where like it was totally out
of control i think there were a
handful of stories i heard about sets
where it was spreading or something or
this was like the risk and it
was kind of scary um but the
show i was on i'm like grateful
it was really safe and that's another
thing i mean i'm just so happy
like my work
work like i didn't socialize basically at
all being because i wanted to be
able to go to work not risk
getting sick and ruining that for myself
and everyone and i was able to
do that so i'm just really glad
where we're very lucky sample
i beg your pardon today put you
to sleep i yawned okay so sorry
give me thirty lashes i don't care
you don't do you you truly don't
give a shit in short you're like
you love chaos you're like you're like
this guy mind me somewhat yeah does
he was his name his name oh
i guess you could call them read
their moral the deal was speaking of
i just got i too am watching
star trek voy
ager as you know is yes we
are in a race to see who
finishes sexy will win why won't you
almost caught up to me i'm watching
like one a day um when i'm
glad jim yeah i'm also taking my
very tall and my scent from silver
eye by the way speaking of going
to the gym and watching a show
i started a west wing rewatch and
i i emailed josh
him i was doing it i was
like anytime i get on the treadmill
i'm just putting on a west wing
and it helps me get through it
and then like a year and a
half later i was like well i'm
up to halfway through season one
i don't think i'm getting to your
episodes ah um i there was a
there was a a moment in an
episode where ah neelix the weirdo no
um he's a weird alien ah but
i don't like about him more than
him being a weird alien is just
how jealousy
he is he seems like he's based
on sitcom dads in the nineties he's
got severe emotional problems and it's drag
yeah granted i'm only a second season
may be trippy yeah they do try
to rehabilitate some of those problems in
an episode of yeah which i just
watched the other oh you do okay
just now i'm hoping now that that's
all gone you will see i'll keep
you posted okay yeah well sure
right now apparently you are because i
may ask what i watched i may
have pulled ahead yeah oh i'm i'm
pong in between deep space nine as
well right i'm going by air date
order for all things star trek yeah
that's demented um i there was an
episode where ah neelix the weirdo take
a breather lauren you can just send
you thinking about something
well this as you are lawrence you
might find this interesting and i'm the
sandwich so that weirdo alien drink compliments
the captain he's like saying you look
great today is that a new shade
of lipstick and it seemed weird to
me and she says no it's the
same when i always wear and it
seemed weird to me that in the
caterpillar torturing universe in they are eqn
knowledges thing that the with the women
who work on this fucking starship are
put a lamb themselves yeah yeah in
the twenty fourth century like yeah because
you know easy especially the cat is
zoom yeah so it's weird to break
the fourth wall as the character and
talk about how you got ready today
yeah but i
also think like that in that in
the future that you would have like
tattooed makeup and they wouldn't be like
or whatever now look like that but
here's the thing nobody you but like
i like you know i wouldn't pick
she'd be a space shipping like i
just got this from so for yeah
i think you'd have like the holographic
makeup yeah like basically a facebook filter
for your actual face
nobody is really just nobody like on
the crew is really made to look
like they're wearing makeup you know what
i mean they're wearing like tv makeup
they're not wearing like going out to
the discotheque makeup right yeah you know
so it's sort of worth commenting on
it it isn't natural yes that's really
my cup so where you don't notice
it yeah i'm not saying a little
grass like this
hey just like a woman would notice
did you find her attractive paul
i know someone would notice of another
woman had lipstick gun even if it
was supposed to look really naturally a
guy might not really pay attention to
it but in this in the context
of the show it's really weird that
you're going to comment on the tv
makeup that's natural it's like i no
one does that on a regular show
like you wouldn't be watching you know
at basically any tv show that like
like live tv show this is so
a million little things all my favorites
but maybe you're not gonna price is
right you're going to say like nice
lips i didn't spend a great wheel
i do want to say you did
i after i went to bill maher
ah the our friend i think i
went to bill maher remember i need
to build a boat like a story
where i went to an episode of
bill maher like fifteen years ago and
they made us really standing ovation yeah
real-time oh yeah that's right that's right
and and after we did that my
friend who is one of the producers
took us down to the prices right
stage which was underneath and let us
spin the wheel yes which is very
exciting yeah very exciting i did not
get a dollar i got that was
the only thing i
really enjoyed about working on that show
was that i got to see the
prices right stuff every day and one
time i saw them i saw stagehands
pushing through the hallway a brand new
car whoa it was really exciting they
had like gloves on they were like
you can't scuff it or whatever and
they like had it been nice rock
whatever yeah the baseball gloves on speaking
of game shows since we're talking about
again i did technical but it went
green and i recall that she tweeted
about being on a plane so she's
oh when i'm two friends who were
just on prices right and one one
car drew carey and bob barker yeah
they went on together
almost a newbie doesn't then you'll host
an all being tested so they they
want a car our friends sang one
car yeah that was great exciting and
then our friend rita didn't didn't i
mean she won the thing that got
her up you know to play the
likes of weird arm more she did
the she didn't it was celebrity from
broyhill she did celebrity prices
right so she played with tiffany haddish
and oh fun i didn't know there
was a i didn't know that was
everything's going celebrity thing yeah i think
if you put a celebrity i mean
we should do celebrity freedom where three
replace us
we're just one celebrity per episode a
different celebrity every time um rightfully we
were like yeah good good good good
good good good forget it was it
before i interrupted about the prices right
well we were talking about ah florida
it wasn't it was after that it
was we were talking about the hours
of star trek i mean no no
no not back that far bob barr
walker but pippi
i remember brand new car i had
a very weird sort of reunion the
other night i mentioned before on the
show that i sometimes do streaming improv
with my friends the sunday service up
in vancouver great very nice guys very
nice and they had me back on
the show this past sunday
and they had another guest on the
show who turns out was someone that
i did not really meet but i
was at the same blue jays game
um when i was in toronto a
few years back i wrote i think
i discussed this on stage i was
doing a show with marcum and jackson
i said there was a woman in
the stands
who want a car during the game
and was the most bored person i've
ever seen just one car and that
person was on the show with me
on sunday why really she is an
improviser an actress in canada you ask
her about it no they brought it
up
they said i think you mentioned this
you mentioned oh it was her russia
story she had won a car before
a big hassle
so she's going god damn damn i
she was like her shoes cause she
was totally like kind of like like
stunned that she won this car and
she started thinking about the the stuff
that she had to is now i
gotta contact the dealership and yeah it's
still at the end of the process
it's like ten grand at least yeah
i mean she was she was
eventually happy about it but their reaction
in the moment was was hilarious wait
what's ten grand like if you five
it by the time so you contacted
dealership and they and you say you
don't want the car and then they
give you like what you know after
that they'll say okay well we'll we'll
give you this amount of money for
it which is less than what it's
worth
and then you have to pay taxes
on top of that so it's like
at the end of the process you
take the car no matter what and
give some people do yeah some people
do some people do if you don't
need metal do so i'm able to
buy all of the of the of
of my feeling when they called to
say that i that the bang bang
tv show got a second season it
was like yay
oh wait i have to lose all
that way again because it had been
so long and between the wrapping and
getting picked up and then they had
to take a wall out of your
house to get you to the hospital
an airlift
ah
well you guys are good right alright
oh guess what we're back you fuckin
never thought it would happen you thought
we were gone forever
you should look at how much time
was remaining on this episode realised we
would be back what a weird assumption
you made were here um i just
saw that
we're we're good to dish i just
saw that bobby lee posted about carnation
instant breakfast bars do you remember these
yeah absolutely we're so fucking good want
one right now yeah made me salivate
i know i just went oh man
i wish i was still a thing
those are so good like figurines they
were delicious
fig yeah it was a little something
we call a three-acre yeah this is
the favorite part of everyone's day
this is a game i'll read the
description i have to quit out of
fullscreen why did i do this mistake
ooh key everyone shut up this is
submitted by ad to movie torp hey
movies were t w i rp so
it's done song okay go around the
circle and we are a famous circle
named bands or musicians that begin with
the same letter picked randomly if you
can't think of one make one up
if you may
make it up and the next person
calls your bluff yeah if someone calls
bluff and it was a real band
name there ah okay alright so why
don't we ask our ah oh wait
we have something in the chat somebody
give us it i think it was
the google doc of years ago
which is helpful oh thank you google
reader into the chat yeah yeah our
producer marine would you give us a
word or letter just give us a
letter that or put the t
okay oh team but you can't use
time it's some rules okay i like
this yeah i like it too
okay i'm gonna always start start with
the the top of the circle scott
oh am i the top of the
circle yes okay let's go scott lauren
paul okay um telex
um talking heads thompson twins
i'm sorry i wasn't listening to the
rules do we still keep going on
t yeah
okay what were you doing
because if you don't know what you
can get up and then if someone
says that was fe ok gotta gotta
go yeah got ah um
ah tamo chanter tame impala
is anyone allowed to call bluffs
not if the next person goes before
you go ah yes ah ted leo
well that's cool
um ten odd foot of grunts is
that what it is and i'm gonna
call your bluff yeah what is it
paul it's thirty odd foot of gras
okay guy would work okay so cares
about ten out of grunt i think
you're out and then me and paul
keep going here you're able to come
up with another one
and that's what it's all aboot okay
so whose turn is it my turn
yes they might be giants all good
one yeah tex ritter
um
hey
wow i was debating i wonder to
go the sequel but i was like
i have to look like i remembered
it ah so you're trying to yeah
yeah like that there should be a
time limit right so you win okay
let's do another letter okay um you
can just put it in the chat
marina
alright here we go our is the
chat another good better okay i'm gonna
start you're starting okay even though i
want good okay you should go if
you want nice when you get to
get one out without anyone exactly okay
um
i honestly cannot give you the buzzer
hey alright you're out alright but don't
forget you can make a fake one
okay fortify that was weird replaced with
weirs
radiohead
radio four
buzz you're lying i think radio four
is a band when you look it
up fuzz you're lying buzz my name
is ross by the way the scheme
our greatest marina says it is okay
fang game continues nobody will know you're
out when you can try to change
the rules
alright game continues that i suppose
that's actually want trivial pursuit harry next
round all right ah let's have another
letter if we could marina g g
the go-go goes guar
ah gordon lightfoot
um
the gap band
gray come on david
yes no that's how it starts with
it startled by stark yeah you can
take it again though you can take
it again grateful dead there we go
okay
um
glen campbell ooh that was fucking close
gin blossoms
gideon perkins
i'm gonna call that no
ah didn't infer you've got to act
ah ar i learned ah goo goo
dolls oh um
ah oh god all i can think
of is an improv group good neighbor
probably abandoning ah goop
i'm gonna call you on that yeah
i think yeah my buzzer went out
building pets
alright paul won again i want to
yeah forgot about good charlotte oh yeah
i was gonna say gary puckett in
the union gap whoa that's didn't he
have a number one single i think
so what let me look that up
because i think i think i have
one song by him and it's a
huge dropped a bomb on me
bay you dropped a bomb on me
and you turn me up girl it's
a good song do we want to
really wound yeah let's do it because
around lauren wants to win so i
started i'll start this time okay hey
hey oh okay animals audio
slave
alvin and the chipmunks
yeah that counts it doesn't matter they
had a number one hit alabama shakes
alabama
america close allman brothers
al yankovic
arkansas
i feel like i gotta call you
an al yankovic yeah he exists does
he not be don't know him my
thing is i believe his stage name
is a bit longer than that i
know i mean i think that's just
the way people describe you're out wow
okay yeah and it's to me i
believe yeah ah amy winehouse
um
acon
andy williams
art garfunkel
and to gib
an alien ant farm avett brothers
um
um um
ah abel and cain
i'm gonna call you
my face i'm sorry i tried to
hide it
as to not give it away
was new buddy it was a good
one ably yea it's not a bad
name for a group's trillion people in
cain yeah so paul wins again so
that takes you to three so you
are the winner do we do brackets
yeah always do brackets so play against
yourself anyway who is keeping the brackets
because we're not
somebody's supposed to be in charge all
the final round is you have to
do ten in a row again if
you if you can do ten in
a row you win ten dollars okay
and someone will pay you yeah alright
okay marina can we please get a
letter let's get a letter you got
oh no you got hold on hold
on okay okay start you gotta do
it in a minute laurie anderson
ian loretta lynn lottie lainnya ah los
lobos um ah lee lo les paul
um ah a led zeppelin lead belly
um
ah leonard bernstein um ah little oh
well linda ronstadt um ah luo larry
clark um ah
ah one more because i don't think
leonard bernstein counts lawrence latitudes ah one
more one more you got fifteen seconds
um yeah okay yeah huh can't you
have ten seconds go go your lumineers
yeah all you intend to why does
her bernstein account i because i think
he's i don't think he has like
a like a performer he's a writer
of music right i think he also
didn't conduct it that's gives a shit
about guys you know wave your land
plastic paul won three rounds in a
row
a beat himself in the final round
against himself where grand prize total of
ten dollars that was a game show
and you were on it but yeah
yeah hey day actress clarice dead at
twenty eight
gruesome i'm just doing the issue i'm
doing the throat of the local news
thanks everybody listen all the plans we
made of course by this time will
have been shut down by the delta
variant but thank you for listening ah
we're a three-time usa on twitter and
instagram three m usa we truly are
or their their future no dispute about
that fact and scott writes ninety percent
of the posts with his oh yes
and he's very scott lets himself feel
on instagram yeah that's really sad it's
really the only place where i can
truly be myself and yeah drop the
whole act and i wish you could
do it on this show but it's
impossible now sorry no you know one
of these days
scott told if we got by the
way every story i've ever told on
the show is fake you will yeah
scott said if he gets to seventeen
thousand followers on the three-time instagram he'll
post a nude of somebody one yeah
not of myself no one i know
no one wants to see that ah
we do it's gonna show you guys
want to see my new slant news
attach
this luckily of course i would see
all my friends nudes
alright well goodbye everybody the show is
over later it shows because it's truly
over goodbye go to bed
uh