three
um yeah oh yeah wow yeah huh
kelly's gonna do do do do see
about the doo to do
well you always have to have the
last scat
that's true that's true
i can't help myself i just love
it it's an art form i think
it's great it was the first person
to scat gave man
yan lei shu ooh so do we
do to draw oh dear
oh it's chilly
ah welcome to three adam the caveman
podcast where we say everything was done
first by the cavemen yeah it's a
true thing first man on the moon
cave
who took the first drink of water
caveman last lester who was the first
where stripes gave him it meant of
course do you
yeah imagine you're a caveman right and
okay and you're thirsty now i can't
follow what you're saying and you see
it
lost me again ball because now i'm
a caveat i don't speak email i
know i hadn't considered this how do
i remember to get her back dia
will never get her back she's catching
she's a caveman imagine someone elses a
caveman and they're really thirsty and they
see a stream like they post like
selfies all the time and they're really
thick
to seize the idea the idea of
a thirst trap like they got you
big on you you fell in that
tress i looked at your abs
what do you what
thinking
oh
what do you guys think when you
like just scrolling in the new c
like your friend like basically naked
i mean sometimes i'm like i gotta
i gotta admit sometimes i'm like you
know what good for you sure i
don't think any advice on how often
they do it grimm what's got i
don't think any of my friends are
naked on instagram so you gotta get
it right
but there are but yeah every once
in a while in the explore or
whatever i'll see some like improviser in
there wearing a g string and it's
like
ah hurting your personality ah it's so
true
look with scott if you had an
ahead of fuckin slam and bod right
yeah i'll never know
don't say that you can starve yourself
slamming bonds you one gay so ripped
and start posting gesturing photos in like
crazy
you go that far i mean if
you're if you're out enough you should
just wear easter all the time
if you are hot enough there's no
reason not to that's the thing you
work hard at it or you were
genetically born with it or whatever you
know it's like right maybe it's maybelline
yeah could be any of those options
show it off if it's maybelline show
it off i remember seeing a clip
on youtube of some usb show with
some
team that mary holland was it and
they did a scene where people showed
up in bathing suits and mary was
wearing a bikini but did she do
she drew abs honors
it is really funny that is funny
ah stuff yeah that's really cool that
married it's been great okay moving on
libyan leader
she never will be just want to
reiterate marry hollywood never be on freedom
that's good promise we should if we
if one of us can't make a
show we should have to cover our
shift with someone else
that's weird like like when you're a
waiter like if you can't make your
know i got the councillors indeed doesn't
have to be about waiting tables or
just think it makes sense it's like
a restaurant has these people that take
dinner orders from the patrons well here's
the thing like it's like it's cafe
cardinale like if i couldn't be there
then like i would get someone to
cover my shift so far so thorough
graphic audio it's my we're still around
you would be in there every day
it's saying you know arose i'm honestly
so gross
it was good i if if it
were still around i would go there
i'm kind of disappointed i never got
to go there yeah i went back
after i quit what jobs have you
ever been to after you quit oh
my baby sit any kids after you
know but i i quit jobs but
like i would only every other job
like i've mentioned i would only work
for like two days
and then i would have so much
stress about going again that i couldn't
ever go and i'd have to quit
but then i would like sometimes go
by the place big e like i
would just be like nurse go back
amy and i can never go back
in of course yeah think of places
for my ah how a house no
you ever buy my house here my
house
nearby whorehouse after you quit a house
have you ever bought it
what did you want to say have
you eaten did you ever buy a
habit hats in the belfry after you
left yes but i didn't quit there
necessarily i was just reminded of this
the other day i left that i
lost that job when the place went
out of business and then like a
year two years later they reopened in
the same resolution
no same name it was weird and
like the places with the band breaks
up and then they reform different name
just without you
that's happened to me yeah that's how
they were trying to get rid of
me they couldn't fire me i had
an ironclad contract the naked postman broke
up and got back together as echostar
without me it makes sense well they
took off i'm there so famous
um but i i
have gone i did go back into
hats in the belfry after i didn't
work there anymore other places i got
most places like got fired
so hey did you ever go to
tower video after you that was one
of the only places in town to
rent a video i did not i
think i went in there one time
for some reason and i was kind
of i felt really weird about it
it was way after it was so
long afterwards but i remembering a fake
skin flap over your moustache a fake
skin flap
to disguise yourself as tower does our
video went out of business before i
grew the mustache oh yeah that was
was it like a race between you
guys yes i swore if they go
out of business i grow cancer bottom
line and getting like little sprouts and
then they were like quick shut it
down
i remember after i got fired because
i got fired for stealing and after
i got fired i ran into one
of the employees who i was friendly
with um someplace else and so how
come you don't come by the store
and i'm like i got fired for
stealing it's like nobody cares about that
they know my i know i don't
you guys don't but i think the
manager probably oh okay he
wasn't in charge he was i was
just like typically yes i was specifically
told never to set foot in that
store again really oh yeah yeah oh
snap part oh yeah the guys the
manager said and don't ever come back
here whoa what if you came back
the next day i know like did
you need to tell me that yeah
like you already have shame you know
what i
get what's going on here just there
are people who would just like come
back and just like what you know
they're just like weird ass fucking people
man i cannot that's true you can't
account for how weird ass people are
gonna be you just don't know you
just don't know people can be normal
and then turn around be weird ass
it's true or they can be someone
who's like really upset about it and
come back
i'd be like imams hey she's not
gonna work here or something and then
like you're gonna work there
start they start organizing things on the
shelf what are some of the places
that you
we're like scared of you not places
that you worked at but places you
were scared to go in to because
of like any manager oh yeah sure
you can win an old rich man's
money if you stay the night there
yeah i mean think about that i
definitely well the first thing that comes
to mind is like the i'm sure
i've told this story but it's not
greater and thing but i've i've told
you i'm sure with preamble
ah but when i was little i
was like um running around the neighborhood
and i picked all these flowers and
then they were in from someone's yard
and the guy came out and like
yelled at me and i cried like
ran home and like threw them in
a ditch three hours in a ditch
and i was getting from my mom
and i don't like to highway
my role in to go buy his
home sure and then we also had
our neighbor who was um did you
tell first i'm sorry to interrupt did
you tell your parents about this encounter
i think i did run home and
cry but because if you had just
like gone back to the house and
apologized he would have been like oh
it's fine and you would have felt
good about it and you
could have gone by there whenever no
i don't recall anyone telling me to
go back there that's poor parenting well
when some old man comes in and
barks at your ass
he was barking oh yeah oh yeah
yeah he
he was short grey and forelegs whiskers
big long tail he must have been
retired he was home all day
but there was this woman who was
um and i'm i'm i'm sure i've
talked about her too but she was
mentally ill and she lived near us
and um we would sometimes cross to
her backyard and see her and the
window and it was always really scary
because we had a couple encounters with
her and tell me if you've heard
this before she sent a christmas card
to everyone in the neighborhood that said
go to
go to hell yes
and then she showed up on a
rainy night and like said she and
my dad are having an affair then
like the police come you did not
i have not
oh i remember i remember that going
to hell either i don't think i'd
ever heard the that's incredible okay yeah
we everyone in the neighborhood got a
christmas card from her and then you
open it up and it just said
go to hell so good i love
i know i know i know it's
kinda great i'm saying that she didn't
have a christian liturgy she lived with
her on the harry and ron yeah
yeah
yeas and then um well this is
oh she lived with her parents everything
go to hell or yeah she wrote
that in printing oil okay no shim
pay for that okay and wrote all
of them go yeah oh and everyone
should everyone in the neighborhood checks notes
with each other and said we each
got to go to hell
l or was that specific possible we
don't we were the only ones who
did know but i do think other
people the least another house did because
it was it was one we've talked
at least my person so it seemed
like it was going around the neighborhood
and then she won i remember she
showed up on time and i was
really little and i was watching through
the you know railing
and there was a really rainy night
and she was getting taken away by
the police she was she was harassing
my family wow and standing outside and
yelling and like saying all this stuff
and he was arrested for having an
affair with your dad why i don't
think i don't know dad arrested taxi
i dunno she was arrested i think
she was taken home right right but
she was being you know she was
it was not true and i mean
i would hope given everything i know
about the situation that that wouldn't be
who he would start it up with
yeah to go to hell just like
romantic music starts
oh she was saying that that your
dad was having an affair with her
yeah it was something i can't well
i was little i don't remember all
the details but it was something about
like that he was supposed to be
with her and now it was like
a delusional sort of right yeah thing
was he holding up a sign that
had a picture of a screw and
then plus in a baseball or yeah
that's how he always communicated ah no
i don't i don't know i should
ask my parents the ins and outs
of that of their sight of that
because i only remember from my perspective
that there was just like let's call
him right now he was fairly low
key inside the house but it was
crazy outside of the house yeah very
whatever happened to her storm she eventually
passed away i don't know how y'all
will yeah imam but i was always
afraid of her house because you know
when you're a little kid you just
don't understand so get a few houses
in the neighborhood that were don't understand
parents just don't understand we had a
few scary houses in the neighbor
but there was one there was a
house on our corner that was unlike
any other house in the entire neighborhood
it was this really it it was
like i wonder if the person who
who lived there was the person who
built the house because it was kind
of modern it was on this big
kind of property like they had the
whole corner to themselves we call it
we call it it was alternately called
rob's hill or hippies hill because of
people that lived there were like hippies
man but they had a um the
two big attractions there were they had
a crab apple tree where these shiny
grapple hill
well well that's you're taking rob out
of the equation i mean it says
why didn't they call it crabapple like
simpsons i think because the simpsons haven't
happened yet and they couldn't do it
they never thought of it yeah um
but the credible true is huge leads
to go climb that we never by
the way never saw the people that
lived there never was a property like
in there
front yard but you would still climb
in their tree or yeah no the
tree was in their backyard they had
lard it was weird because their their
house did it sat on this corner
it was like this this no-fuss hill
around no fence and so sometimes we
would cut through to go around the
corner um and we never saw anybody
that live
phd there but we would look in
like like they had a glass front
door those behind this this foliage we
would like look in it and you
know see this it was like kind
of a grand cool house um i
wish i wish i could have gone
inside there at one point but we
never went in so so the crab
apple tree we would play in the
crab apple tree my little buddies we
would get crowd apples and throw them
at shit
now throw the cars and buses does
anyone eat crab apples like is there
a crab apple pie recipe there is
actually yeah yeah really you can put
crab apples and things you can't crap
up i don't think as a thing
you can bite into and be like
yum yum
think you can i think you can
use it in cooking um the other
attraction was they had a big ah
garage like a multi-car garage and inside
was what was a dog but to
us was a terrifying monster because i
think it was like a it must
have been like a wolfhound
nothing like that like a big dog
because it would jump up to the
window and like it would bark like
crazy and jump up to the windows
so you only got a glimpse of
it um you know like this just
like fangs
and this horrendous noise but it was
like we would like creep up to
it to see like how far you
can get before the dog would go
crazy but i remember i remember in
my i clearly remember the the realization
when i when i realised like oh
no it's a dog it's just a
dog
yeah i'm bigger than it now yeah
probably yeah but it was it was
it was so scary and i think
nice dark in that garage it was
well maybe i mean maybe you were
only passing by during the day and
they were both working or is a
single guy who was working or saying
leaving his dog there i think there
must have there must have been multiple
people who lived in that house at
one time um
and that's how i got the name
hippies hill but it was like we
would go we would like moon children
it was like ah yeah moon children
probably
you know it's got something to think
of it i think it was moon
children that's what it was called you
just forgot but we would like slid
off of that hill it was not
like it was like super steep but
it was enough that you could get
one of those like round coaster things
you know and you can slide down
you could slide down the hill and
and would take you all the because
we lived on a on an a
grade an upgrade
all it would take you all the
way down the street so could glenn
it was it was great fun never
saw hey why would never anybody come
out of the house even to say
hi they were clearly okay with it
have you known me how saying yeah
google maps recently i have actually like
yeah because i was trying to i
was trying to tell jane yeah but
um i will
i'll try to it's it's kind of
hard to get the sense of it
i really wanted to see the house
itself but there is so much greenery
around it you especially if it's ever
been on sale in the pictures from
the inside or what yeah yeah yeah
i would love that i would love
them or whatever yeah should look up
the address was hard to find because
i couldn't remember the exact address right
but i'll get on the case i'll
get on like yeah
we had a house that we called
the mansion was like i have to
look it up too because now it
probably would be so small but it
was the biggest house in the neighborhood
for blocks and blocks it felt like
it was two stories maybe and just
like bigger than and it i think
maybe the style of it was it
was like an old kind of southern
mansion or something like that and we
all called it the mansion because it
was just the biggest grandest house out
of out of the neighborhood and they
once for halloween they they really did
it up they like that's what all
of the adults like four of them
all dressed up like mannequin like like
ah mannequins on the porch sitting in
rocking chairs that you thought were like
useless dummies and you would go up
to the front and be like oh
they're just dummies that they that they
put together and then all of a
sudden they would come to life and
like start to come at you and
stuff it was oh it was wonderful
did any of you remember urged like
on youtube i remember somebody who's like
dad sitting outside the front of one
of the houses when your trigger treaty
and then like you think it's like
a scarecrow things like wow and it's
like the scariest shit i'm like thinking
about the guy in there is funny
it's fun to think about the guy
in there just sitting there for hours
just like waiting i know because you
have to be ready you know you
mean so like what do you are
used literally just sitting there that's psychotic
i did that one time what i
mean shit when i say it's not
fun to think about them now when
i was too old to trick
or treat like around the thirteen or
thirty nine or thirty hours
i would just sit in the bushido
and and jump out at people like
as they came up but ah but
then i'm just like sitting in the
bushes for you know like yeah weirdo
no
alright lauren
what the fuck i look away for
one second and you're like i don't
know tensions on me i'm scared
i'm hire did you ever trick or
treat a year past the time when
you were supposed to fill yes yes
yes i mean even even like um
i think like fifth grade started to
feel a little bit weird but then
like oh wow definitely sixth grade was
two two yeah junior high is probably
too old so
seventh grade is too all right but
that's when we would go smashing pumpkins
and you know be crazy together with
the with the boys was epic yeah
in chicago and smashing pumpkins is from
chicago yeah so we knew we had
to do that to keep the band
alive i remember we used to go
guns and roses yeah from philly no
no
but it was food in their sighting
like once you like once you became
a little too old then you're like
now we'd hang out on halloween and
then that's like a different kind of
yeah yes exactly lumpy scares that turned
into make outs the embarrassing halloween party
i had
um nobody came i don't remember if
i've talked about it so i was
in seventh grade and my parents were
like oh yeah it was your birthday
know and it was halloween theme wasn't
it no it was halloween and it
was louie theme and you had a
halloween theme birthday what does an amazing
idea
i would like a christmas themed birthday
love my days in september i remember
your first birthday
i'm gonna make my kid do weird
shit like that where it's like you
only pick other holidays to be your
theme you cannot have your own theme
it has to be something already exists
are you plotting out all the weird
things that you do with your child
i have a whole binder and it's
really thoughtful
wade scott so seventh grade halloween party
your house is far i'm here mike
oh gosh oh wait i do
the hell
is that a new zoom earn your
mic down she looks so relaxed and
began seeing
that's dive just rainy
um so i i was it was
seventh grade it was halloween i was
too old to trick or treat but
my parents were like why don't you
have a party over here you can
invite your new friends because i'd just
gone to a junior high and made
you know some friends and so it
was like they set up a whole
thing where there was a way to
this karate school called cobra
chi
they they got a cauldron and my
dad got dry ice and made it
like bubble wow and and we bobbed
for you dad it was like bobbing
for apples in this cauldron you know
that we did tell dry ice keep
tugs that i remember and it was
everyone had to dress up and it
was it was those first time that
i had ever realized that
what we were doing like i'm on
instagram
it's the first time i ever realised
how juvenile like this was and how
uncool it was and i felt mortified
that my parents went to such trouble
to make it like spooky but in
a kid's way and yell with fake
cobwebs and stuff and i just felt
really judged by
these new kids you know that's awkward
were at this like stupid party you
also had a murder mystery party was
which was a lot like that too
yeah you probably got beat up at
that one um what what i i
think though what's funny is like that
at that age you think oh this
is corny but if you went now
as an adult and somebody did that
in their house you would think like
oh this
oh i love it yeah absolutely there's
thirteen to eighteen year old period or
something like that where it's everything is
uncool yeah there was this ah person
that even making up used to be
friends with who had an aunt who
would have this like cool halloween house
party this
was in la and like los angeles
for the listeners it was a huge
huge property and then they go all
out so it's like for kids and
adults with this big you know just
stuff everywhere and like activities and it
was so cool james may's house right
oh yeah
his aunt his age spades and went
furthest
again imagine david elster like putting anything
like that together and being like here's
my halloween party
and i like to picture people's relatives
looking exactly like their female relatives looking
exactly like them in a wig yeah
like david spade with old lady makeup
on a gray wig with a bun
just something exactly like david spade
there there was back to places that
you're scared to go into and i
don't think i've talked about this i
pray i haven't have i talked about
the seven eleven that i avoided for
for years now i don't think so
but i'm aware of okay well two
weird things happen in the first i'll
talk about the other weird thing that
happened at the seven eleven which is
the only time i think i've started
with other life yeah the only time
i've ever called the cops in my
life i believe was ah cool up
was at the seven eleven by our
house which is a block
a from our house ah getting something
and some guy started talking to her
and asking her questions and then followed
her back to our place wow from
the seven eleven and parked outside of
our place like just thanking it and
so i took down his license play
called the cops all that kinda stuff
ok so that
was the weird thing that happened seven
london but so on i'm very embarrassed
by this story ah so my my
local seven eleven i would go in
there all the time and on thursday
nights the new entertainment weekly would would
be there and so i would always
like take a trip there on thursday
night and get an entertainment weekly gotta
get the fresh jim mullen's hotsheet
okay
and so the guy who worked there
i can't remember his name but he
was a cool guy and i would
always talk to bonzi yeah yeah that's
yeah he would always hit the jukebox
this is my office yeah exactly several
bathroom um no he and he was
like hey are you in the movie
business because
i was always getting in entertainment weekly
oh and i was like i mean
kind of
i guess i was at the time
ah and you're like i'm in the
business of watching them
exactly that's what it felt like but
he was like well you know in
my in my country where i came
from i made movies and i was
like oh wow is it really is
like yeah i'm a director and a
writer and and you know i'm trying
to make him out here but you
know like i was i was kind
of a big deal and in my
home country
and i was like that's so cool
and he's like let me let me
loan you this movie i made and
i was like ok and so the
next time he next time i came
in he had this dvd that he
gave me of this movie i can't
remember what it was called um my
forno
starring me me and my piano
nobody was like ah it was it
it was a drama and i read
reviews of it and it was like
it's supposedly a really powerful drama from
india and all this kind of okay
and it's sat there on my dvd
player for a year at least oh
no if i go back more
work to me you can never go
back and i every time i would
go and he'd go you watch it
i was like no not yet and
then after a while it it turned
into just have it bad disappear
and oh and then so then i
was like avoiding the seven eleven i
would sometimes pull up to the seven
eleven see he was there and turn
around and drive away and i turn
in finally i put it i was
like right to the window i can't
do this in person i put it
into a manila envelope
and got there during the day when
he wasn't there and said hey could
you give this to this person and
and they said sure and and then
i still don't think i ever went
back to the seven eleven and this
is a block away from my house
i never go to it yeah you
never you never watched the movie i
never watched the movie i'm sure it
was good but i just never found
myself in the mood to watch
like a subtitled like super dramatic thing
you know i don't know anyway that's
definitely have placed that is my shame
like that but i can't think of
them right now but i know that
there were places where like did something
weird and i was like i can
never show my face in there again
um know what should have been the
studio that we recorded
i should be so embarrassed that i
never show up to your yeah you
never know three remember again i can't
believe i did know that until those
stories
there's probably places i shouldn't have gone
back to ah they should have been
more embarrassed to show my face in
there again just many bars where i
got just sloppy drunk yeah
you miss those days buddy my god
not that i can't i when i
think back on that i'm like how
am i alive yeah like it was
dumb like i remember i remember like
going to the cat and fiddle and
then like closing it down being shit
faced drunk and walking home to my
apartment
yeah that was kind of a bit
of a hike that was like a
twenty to half hour twenty minutes a
half hour walk now like i'm i
like staggering like that's how drunk like
anything could happen to me like if
i if any any criminal saw me
like absolutely well this guy for sure
gotta gotta
got hit by a car yeah absolutely
absolutely i took a lot of i
took a lot of dumb chances i've
never quilted black out on the street
my wish um i've never called the
cops i don't think i have either
don't think i ever have
yeah there's usually not a reason to
yeah i mean like i've never been
in in a situation where it was
like oh my god this guy you
gotta find this guy that did the
thing just now you know yeah i
guess it's the only time i i
would i guess when i was young
we called the cops because some guy
tried to pick me up on the
street
so he likes you heavy
well i was just going around during
a lift people hey can i lift
actually i kind of remember maybe i
did one time call but i don't
know if this happened to me or
somebody else and i'm just pretending it
happened to me but it was i
in my memory there was a guy
who was running across the freeway and
it was like terrifying like he was
oh i like men i guess recently
nine one one because there was a
guy walking
on the freeway in the second not
the right hand lane but the second
to right handling yeah on the freeway
just like in the actual lamar area
in the actual like just walking and
like i slowed down in and you
know like drove behind him for a
little bit so no one would crash
into him or anything and called nine
one one to get people out there
and they had already received calls about
the guy yeah and they were sending
someone to they were like what else
you got anything else was using listening
that we don't know about
recovering that one bud
the guy who tried to pick me
up on the street i always remember
being so ah not embarrassed but ah
regretful that i didn't get his license
plate number like the minute he drove
off i was like oh i just
got his license plate number yeah you
like drove up to me i'd never
seen me say sweet
thing he's like literally on the street
i live hey good looking we'll be
back up later you're thinking of the
simpsons paul
it's just like hey do you want
to ride to school yeah oh ooh
kid oh yeah yeah yeah never seen
the guy he wasn't a neighbor or
anything like that and so you know
it's thanksgiving thank god that i you
know of course was like no
thank you was like who wants to
go to school asked to get into
people's i'm on my way to work
multi-cam team here right
you had a friend who i learned
was asked to get in people's cars
multiple times like as a kid cheese
same person or different cars
different cars were the one wishing they
were car shaped and one came down
here belonging here and tried to get
her to get in and it was
like oh your mom told me to
come get you like that kind of
thing and then there was another time
that happened i mean there's just yeah
the mom told me to get you
oh god let's see how happy you've
got to tell
kids pretty young about this kind of
stuff right i mean i was just
gonna say i don't i don't remember
being told that stuff but maybe i
was too young and i don't remember
i don't know whether i was told
by my parents or by by school
but since you've gotta ghetto grab really
early we had to like go in
the auditorium and watch like an old
video of like you know per how
perp
virts talk and then you filed it
away and said i'm gonna do comedy
someday based on it's use all of
these sources hell pervert sock welcome to
comedy bang bang
they know ah but i remember that
and i remember excuse me i'm sick
so so god
pervert oh i'm joking
emotional the third passion by mouth
i remember that i'm er learning like
that you could have a codeword with
your parents so like if someone was
going to pick you up that that
person should say this word what word
do you remember yeah i don't think
we like may at least
please i pretty much would just know
i shouldn't go with anybody yeah right
occasionally my friends they weren't even my
friends people i knew at church would
would because i walked thirty five minutes
to school and junior high would like
pull over and say get in the
van but then other times i would
see the dan patrick henry rollins know
it was nice they were like none
getting the van none of the kids
liked me but they
but i went to their church so
occasionally you'll be like good hands yeah
so yeah but but then at other
times i would see the van passed
me by and i would know they
would be like we're not stopping for
him today like what is this an
everyday thing yeah i draw the line
somewhere yeah
like once a week maybe yeah alright
we have to take a break speaking
of okc we do this once a
week we take chicks break once a
week here we go bike
and we're back and learn over the
weekend you send an email to all
of your friends saying you were taking
a shower what is that oh my
god shower you had a baby shower
i'll drive by baby shower and it
was very nice it was really boys
in the hood
hood way just like that that was
the theme um no it was very
nice and it was it was very
um special to feel like you know
there's a community it's been such a
weird year obviously i don't know um
yeah know because you you had normal
year where you just do whatever you
want the whole time
but break
you know it was just nice to
see a lot of people that i
haven't seen in a long time and
to feel like um they're all still
there because i mean you know i
think i feel i've ever know i've
stayed pretty connected with my friends through
social media and whatever like i feel
like i am aware what everyone's like
up to but it's so different when
you're just running into everyone all the
time
i'm yeah there's just like that kind
of like the friendship is sustained by
you just like seeing each other all
the time at the theater and whatnot
yeah it made me realize i want
to see people i want to make
more of an effort to see people
because i realized you know how much
janie and i've been homebodies before quarantine
and like
we're happy to stay at home it's
not like we hate going out but
we i really did miss seeing so
many people and it made me think
like i want to have people over
to my home you know i wanna
yeah like sit around a table and
share a meal and and talk and
laugh you know and i want to
make an effort to to to i
want to really make an effort to
do that more to make it a
regular thing yeah it's not something that
you just keep thinking like oh we
should have them over some time and
then you never knew him i know
well how was the barbecue went to
paul
it you know why it was a
real it was fun but it was
kind of a challenge and it was
ah ah a strange return to normal
life that i hadn't thought about because
it was a part it was a
small party about you know twenty twenty
five people and it was half people
that i knew and have people i
did
didn't know so it was just enough
to give me like a little anxiety
you know what i mean yeah that
that feeling of like i'm sitting with
somebody that i don't know super well
but i kind of know and i
felt the um the the not pressure
but i felt the obligations like keep
the conversation going yeah but you haven't
had to do it
which i'm going to do in a
while but i i what i realized
is ah oh here's what i'm gonna
do is ah i'm going to keep
asking questions so i'm not the person
that has to ah keep talking yeah
yeah yeah and so i'll let and
i'm fine till like literally a person
and my age and everything it really
is yeah i'm fighting like hell
figured that out you know like in
my early twenties i was like oh
if i ask questions like the conversation
is way easier if i have questions
about this person i don't give a
shit about yeah they'll keep talking and
then someone's like we did something and
honestly it's like now you have a
a perfect icebreaker you know is to
just ask people how are they feeling
about things
you know and don't don't ask them
how their year has been but asked
and how are they feeling about things
opening up and everything like yeah because
everybody kind of wants to talk about
it and and talk about their feelings
about it but i i did feel
like and then when it was time
to go it was also it was
an afternoon thing and so like step
i'm not a big fan of afternoon
parties
there's like a standing in the sun
aspect to it that i don't enjoy
it makes me tired and um so
when we were getting ready to go
then it's like you get stopped by
people that you know and now it's
like everyone you see somebody you haven't
seen in forever i know so it's
so weird yeah but i gotta say
i felt like everybody was on the
the same level of understanding you know
yeah everybody got it everybody was like
yes i understand you're leaving i'm not
going to like keep you it's good
to see you you know so it
it felt very um it felt very
welcoming and and easy in that way
but yeah i did it took me
a while to process like oh why
am i feeling this way it's like
oh yeah i'm at a party
yeah i haven't done that yeah i
mean the the shower was like a
step a dipping up for the toe
because i was like having wasn't everyone
chances but it wasn't everyone at the
same time and that was getting nice
and i had like a little moment
with everyone which which worked well and
i feel like for a shower that's
typically what happens anyways that you kind
of like have the
conversation with each person about how it's
going what's going on what are you
thinking about and then are you traveling
anyway are you sad you didn't get
to do the traditional shower stuff of
like whatever game i've been to a
diaper gain yeah where you have to
guess the shit um i what is
highway eighty personally bars in
diapers and you melt them and then
you have to guess what they are
who started this oh the i don't
know some some of them are candy
company and i want to start in
this game some of the those baby
shower games are so weird though i
mean like i don't really miss that
part of it i did a zoom
family shower which was really nice but
i was
um i was sad leading up to
it that i wouldn't be able to
be with everyone yeah and that was
kind of hard i was just like
worrying that i wouldn't feel connected to
everyone but my sister-in-law organized it and
it was really great and she put
together like videos from friends and family
and like a powerpoint rangers you know
active
eighty sort of thing strangers mark cameos
from like a bunker where guys would
be so awesome if someone was like
hey this video for your birthday or
whatever and it was just strangers reaching
that's cameo and yeah like yeah i
really care about you huh all these
people hey your friends tell me you
were born
um and then i you know open
presence that my family had sent and
stuff and it was really it actually
felt really great and it felt as
normal as it could given the circumstances
and i tell you i kind of
i've been to a couple aa drive
by birthday things showers whatever i kind
of like it and i think it
should stay a handful of people
well said that as they were coming
through like this is how everything should
be it's like i they had a
scheduled window of time to show like
got to talk for a bit have
yeah and then they drove off and
it's like low pressure it was yeah
very easy and i do think that
i think you should install a drive
through window at your place yeah yeah
and then if you want to combine
say
it's something i mean i think it's
nice also just because of this year
like not really socializing it's kinda the
perfect amount of socializing like yeah you
don't want don't have to talk to
one hundred people like you know everyone
who goes to the party doesn't have
to talk to everyone else it's not
like the whole thing we were like
now have to go and be there
for an hour whatever it's like you
just get to have a little moment
and of connection
which is nice but yeah i went
to a backyard barbecue the other day
and it was probably fifty people ooh
so and the minute i got there
we were some of the last people
to arrive i think because it had
been going on for four hours before
we got there i think and immediately
people started hugging us
and i was like no we're not
bringing this back we learned oh i
don't have a wrong with that at
all it's got never liked tugging that's
true all i'm a hugger yeah i
just like i don't know and it
wasn't it wasn't people i'm especially close
with well that's part of that's part
of what i mean i feel like
when this when this happened and then
you work you know we're kind of
reflecting
six months in it was like i
was always hugging everyone you know like
i i did have that feeling like
i'm not really a hugger but i've
have become one kind of social hugger
of the climate yeah yeah everyone does
it and it's like eight but then
there's the times we're like i'm hugging
someone and i feel like we've neither
of us want to be hugging you
know it's like why are we do
this yeah and ultimately like people were
hugging because it's like we're out in
the world come here yeah yeah okay
i mean and there and there were
some people that i technically would would
hug in any situation but i was
just like i thought we were getting
rid of hugs and shaking hands and
stuff like that and then the first
social situation i'm in people are immediately
like grabbing me yeah
yeah i really want to get rid
of handshakes and then the last couple
times i've seen people i ended up
shaking yeah i met some guy the
other day i have to make i
feel like i have to make a
conscious effort to not do that literally
the first day out the first day
that cool up and i were both
vaccinated we went over to our friend's
house for mac you don't have to
i have to stop you for one
second and this is very embarrassing given
how long we've been doing this yeah
who's club oh shit
i'm sorry and i also have no
question it's going to sound really insane
you keep saying like me and i
just talk
ah
but i went to just a small
thing with like eight people and one
of the people had a boyfriend that
i had never met before and he
immediately stuck his hand out was like
hey nice to meet you and i
was like dude first day and i'm
to shake a hand first day
yeah it's law
i look like i'm not fully vaccinated
up i look forward to being fully
vaccinated that i can go do some
things like i and the things i
wanna do are really they're really dumb
but i yeah sure like i wanna
start when i go to target yeah
so i'm gonna be that guy there
who works there made i have a
screening in my home of that movie
um no i want to go to
target really bad i want to like
go get my haircut and like not
be i haven't been to a salon
this whole time i've just gotten haircuts
through random what you know ways and
means um so sure through work for
example rig thing we have here at
work because i hadn't
but in so long so i was
those were the best when i was
doing the comedy band going tv show
and to know that i could get
my haircut like for the entire five
years that i was working on that
just like never having to go to
ah it's really nice and what's really
nice during this time but and then
i had like one hair cut on
my porch like in july last year
which was said one so sweaty and
you know it's just not fun um
but i'm i'm looking forward to like
just doing little things like that just
by myself even like it's not even
about like how i want to get
together with everyone so bad which i
also do but i'm like i just
like running all my errands and taking
my time and not really thinking about
anything and cool up this morning was
like do you want to go see
a movie tonight at it like a
thief
later and i was like well i
don't think there's anything you want to
see because only a quiet place part
two is oh yeah no i can't
see that ah yeah um but just
the idea of that was very is
it just called a quiet place part
two is at the title probably i
don't know quieter place is even more
quiet place allowed by a place with
the
a is a two way
found love in a good place why
didn't they live in the waterfall
well this is the thing building the
nice frank lloyd wright style house above
the waterfall and you've got something there
all you gotta do is look i
know there's aliens that attractive sound just
build a frank lloyd wright house waterfall
yeah the building part won't attract anyone
you won't die
um did you guys watch murphy's town
are you all yeah watch that shit
now i only watched the first episode
and and then everyone's tweeting about it
and i'm like will do watch the
whole thing now i've skimmed every tweet
i've avoided reading that's how i felt
about king of tigers or whatever he
was that he was the tiger king
oh thanks guy ran down fakers
um i only heard about him so
much for like two okay fourteen just
started people needed things to do there
was an our hearts um i sub
tweeted the the about the ending of
the show and a couple people got
mad at me because they were like
this is me
major spoiler and you ruined it for
me and i'm like when you tweeted
that i was wondering when i didn't
see your tweet i thought okay i
can either let my mind go wild
and think about how this implies that
this yeah this happened and then i
thought like are i'm not gonna watch
this show yeah but if i do
hope they'll have forgotten this tweet by
then and you know i've yeah i
see
will remember i'll never forget it i'll
see whatever forget me you but to
say that if you haven't watched yet
it's on you but it's like no
no no i'm not gonna say that's
what i was gonna say
oh you were gonna say you're a
dumb dorothea lay grow lab guess wow
now castle um i was what i
was gonna say was if you were
able if you just saw this tweet
and you put all of that together
without first of all that is a
knock against the show and also you're
a better detective than mayor yeah
yeah i thought when i first started
watching that show they called her mayor
because she was the mayor i expected
to be like mister mayor that is
a sudden was spelled m a r
e that thing that drives me nuts
about the shows that it's based on
a an accent pun
oh it is no mayor it's mayor
elizabeth what's your actual new they name
is marijuana said yeah ariane mayor yeah
no they're just like hey mayor like
you would call marianne like if i
were sitting call them they call her
mare for short but but titling it
mayor of east town is like that's
how people in the region say mayor
right so no well that's what i
thought it was but it turned out
not to end in the final episode
where they're like marianne hey mary i
was like oh that's why it's called
mayor of your town even though they
called her mare the whole time i
got it you why but i wondered
if it was like who you were
calling her the mayor no
even her mother was calling her the
most like her nickname because she was
so good at basketball they were like
wow you should be in charge of
napster be grateful that it was sure
your little star you a horween rusty
genuineness you're being disingenuous god no matter
why are you rubbing your face i
got a little tired from this
mayor of east town i love kate
winslet though and i thought the accent
she was doing was really well done
she did i thought everybody did a
good job with the accents i really
do i thought not everybody was perfect
but she was she was real especially
being from another country like that was
the time that's what i'm saying strictly
that's very specific acts
yeah quicksilver have the best accent i
thought i thought he did great evan
peters did great yeah he's hickory alright
well we only do this once a
week but we have to take a
break
and we're back i'm paul i'm scott
i'm lauren and it's time for one
of our famous three cheers that's right
these are world famous people around the
world know them what they are are
are you mispronouncing creatures no no
no it's three cheers it's like a
feature but there's the three of us
three cheers it's a game and i'm
paul and what we do is we
play a game and sometimes people send
in games um like luke benson did
thank you luke benson for this game
called i've got some bad tunes luke
i am your father huh
look i'm your benson robert e o
one player here's how we play
it's heavy
turned to the camera oh god and
then the theme from benson plays but
it's darth vader what is the theme
for independence of the na
talked about the damn that and damn
that antenna tent data it's almost to
be wished yeah it is we literally
had this conversation that we looked it
up
no we didn't we've never talked about
benson before we have not talked about
the benson theme song before i ok
i swear this is the first time
i've ever thought about the benson okay
in my life really yeah i read
on and you can double spank me
one show was ah ted danson cheers
no johnson me
backer backer and better things decker jimmy
morneau had a very funny scene on
becker yes he did sort of the
sklar brothers and my friend aaron reed
dance to the becker theme song for
one full hour on youtube
the sklar brothers posted like a video
from a bar mitzvah they were out
when they were kids and they saw
the same i loved it sadly the
same yes it's it was wild but
our timeless they are yeah ah alright
so everyone shut up because here's the
name of the game is called i've
got some tunes one player chooses a
scenario where someone has to deliver some
bad news
news another player chooses a song or
tune that the other players will know
the third player has to deliver the
bad news from the given scenario to
the melody of the chosen song okay
got it got it got it got
it so who's doing what okay so
i'll say i've got some bad news
power okay so you're the person doing
performing it okay so paul you you
picked the situation i'll pick the song
okay the situation is ah
ah there has been a massive fire
your house has burned down and your
car exploded when it caught on fire
okay song my song is paradise city
okay
hey paul yeah
um i've got some bad news i
need to share with you know i
like good news this is bad hey
what about me are you talking to
me too sure why not you do
live there so yeah i'm his roommate
what do you mean you live there
it has something to do with our
house wow
yeah
he's been fire and everything's burned everything's
gone and your car has gone to
it exploded
wait everything gone what do you mean
the whole house
your clothes are gone and kitchen is
gone you and your employers god
fire
but the car is still there isn't
it car explode when the fire went
off
yeah that's gotta get in the car
it's ah
ah
one
alright oh god i'm so even the
question
should be collin shirts
there's no pointing gun and shit
not even a point
don't wanna know how's not gonna do
anything
wait do you know something about how
it started
via start away
when i walked right by and enough
linked to match and oh yeah hi
yeah child she's gone and i can't
see your insurance last week
hi how did you get our password
i figured it out when you patch
big dicks
alright proof of concept that was um
we can continue playing the game okay
it is now i only need miss
song know you're you're doing the song
i'll name the song okay and then
that means that i have to do
this situation because paul's already doing the
situation okay so paul you'll saying okay
ah
this is the song i know yeah
ah the situation is you're telling someone
that you have to amputate both of
their legs
okay and the um song is longest
time by billy joel
ah
hey ding-dong was a blast caused the
door o answer it oh okay hey
paul hi scott hi kingdom looks up
plays
ding dong i just i just got
your test results back oh yeah and
i'm one of those awesome bad news
he can't you do house calls now
yeah i just wanted to hear your
famous catchphrase didn't well i sat on
the phone too but i'm glad you're
here
um you might want to sit out
okay because that's all you're able to
do
you used to what do you mean
i have god so awful news to
tell
you will soon lose both your legs
as well oh they must be chopped
off and i have got to chop
them off because your legs are being
amputated oh i do have to chop
off via your legs i do
do have to chop off your legs
i did not want it to come
to this is that you would need
crutches now too
yeah i'm very sorry your legs are
calming with me
both of your two legs hold on
hold on hold on you're gonna do
it now and you're taking them with
you now i have to chop off
those two legs okay
say i know that much is happening
why is this happening yeah what what
were the test results i mean what
what specifically you have di ya bds
type sixteen is ah worst case i've
ever see
your foot won't be enough i've got
to take the whole leg i have
gone to chop off both of your
two legs oh singing huh god sorry
to lose sense it is how i
deliver news i was away how did
this start when was the first person
you ever delivered news to this way
when i was jaws born out of
the woo my ho da la around
the delivery room wow i said to
my mom this is how i deliver
new so you better get used to
this thing
ah okay you see this thing
okay other questions ding dong no no
i'm good just chop them off and
go
ah okay now scott has to say
we have to do the situation okay
laura and you cope with the song
okay yes um the situation is
that
um tonight you're going to choke on
some bubble gum and
psychic prediction
i mean psyches can deliver bad news
it's yeah it's a it's a psychic
and they're telling you the ram though
yeah you're okay
huh yeah you're touching terrible news
very same i'm telling you to one
of you okay got it and they're
gonna choke on bubblegum and they're gonna
um die but it's gonna be like
in front of a crowd of people
who thinks they're kidding okay yeah and
the song is the star spangled banner
okay
ah paul psyching scott what are you
doing here ding dong yes
i um god there's no easy way
to say this but what are you
doing holding that crystal ball this is
a housecall you'll make you all not
real crystal glass
oh okay it works though it works
though glass ball it's a class ball
it's it's actually a bowling ball weirdly
enough it's it's got the three holes
right here oh i see yeah i'm
going bowling after this it's not what
i used for my premonitions but i
did have a premonition and i want
to tell you guys about it folk
well could be good
oh paul anding dong what's up players
two nights some things gone wrong
you will chew some bubblegum oh um
having split it in twain yeah i'm
sorry jackson we're both you're answering my
question thank you it's taking half a
piece and chewing it all now
ty i'm so sorry what brand gum
dentyne is a brand of gorm you
shall chew it tool to a guy
what what flavor of dentine spearman's makes
the wave tapper man's is like a
variety pie
do they make oh sweet we're splitting
where it's one piece of gum that
is both spearmint and peppermint one of
you takes half a piece of peppermints
and the other takes off a piece
of spoon why don't we eat shit
why are we doing half of gum
looks too big
for you to fit into your mouth
so you did i lose the sort
of sudan
oh where am i
oh say canada's star okay ah the
gong looks too big for this to
who fit inside your ma oh so
both of us the gum looks too
big so you oh yeah in your
ma
pause and you show the ah kow
to it in your mas
dw yeah yeah or gaping our gaping
mouths gaping moscow
okay i just didn't understand that word
but yeah um so that's all true
i mean i don't know half the
shit that i come up with isn't
true so it might it might mean
mate you come up with it it's
not something that's really yeah i come
up with it but then it comes
true so hey you're talking to
you want me to start over
will you please take the gum from
us take this gum out of our
house
oh paul one's me to unique who
you just come out of the the
you having an aside and not you
i do that then my premonition might
not come true
i am so ethically torn should i
change this future i've seen if i
take this com out will he go
buy his own gum no and then
there's totally i'm gonna jump on come
on come yeah just kind of zoning
out while i'm singing
to myself should i try to intercede
and save both their lie yes i
will not take these gone from there
huh how's no nah too hey i
i wanted them to da high and
my wishes calming drew yay
play ball well your wish is coming
true how interesting yeah oh you guys
heard that there was something that you
wanted to happen but then you just
happen to have a second premonition about
it i've been thinking about this a
lot for the longest time well that's
how you play i've got some bad
tunes and will probably do that one
again that was fine
and good luck benson i'm your father
all right ah that does it for
this episode of threesome lesbos if you
want to get some of our fantastical
merch ah go to pawed swag dot
com look up three-time stuff and it's
all there unless it sold out um
any week you can follow us on
instagram and
twitter at freedom usa ah and if
you want to submit a three cheer
like luke i am your benson did
then write to three m usa at
gmail dot com and that is how
your life will get good and i'm
really engaged with the fan so i
love it when fans follow god and
always ah the one who man
the instagram and you will see that's
very evident um and i know fans
love that so we really appreciate you
doing that scott it's the only place
i don't even do it on my
own social media but it's the only
place like where i can really connect
and get real with them yeah yeah
it feels like that it feels like
that so there's strength in numbers oh
safety numbers yeah anyway
stop stop listening listening to us i'm
listening self-analysis now listen you're gonna hear
this ah
alright bye
ugh