get extra yell i'm feeling generous girls
later
uh
wow hey you're all in the opening
credits are you polar you are you
okay i wiped out yeah you're out
of bread wiped out yeah your head
is down between your knees yeah but
that's just because i almost fainted ah
is that dirty breathing i guess over
you though
breweries ways were the shit that's a
bush yeah they have a song about
sexy nirvana somebody was fainting for them
breathe out i guess someone being alive
though have you ever fainted either yeah
i felt light well i'll tell you
what i went to the doctor the
other day speaking of breathing i went
to the mountain
oh oh okay that works i'm want
to talk about this um but i
went to the doctor the other day
i had to do that ah you
know breathing test where you have to
blow into the same doctors but whoa
whoa whoa lauren you note that is
not true i know i'm not a
guy i suck at this bottle for
if you
we're okay for women who don't know
this we go to the doctor they
just reeling by the doctor he takes
his pants down turns around says blow
into this
it didn't make my butterfinger you pass
blow me up like a balloon
and then you do and he's going
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah um
wait is it that where you have
plastic ball go up well this didn't
have a bali it was an electronic
thing or whatever and it was like
it's basically take the deepest breath you
can blow into it as long as
you can it is hard as you
can hardly that one time the hard
part would make you fuckin pass
yeah and what must seem really really
hard to do actually lets you have
a lot you have to fast for
twelve hours before you go there now
imam really oh yeah you're just wondering
why the fasting because they're taking your
blood work i look yeah thanksgiving dinner
but i can't remember why because any
sugar in user say when i had
my septoplasty where they lasered inside my
nostro
orals oh right because i had a
deviated septum but i think it's back
baby oh it's your nostrils aren't gonna
fall out like last time right yeah
and i had a big slug of
blood come out a ball i had
a high blew my nose today and
i gave me a bloody nose wow
it was scary
you're supposed to happen right when you
look in the tissue and see blood
it's a bad sign
i feel like robbo m yeah if
you were in a movie like we
would know you'd be dead within three
scenes yeah well it's better if you
cough inhabit it is better you feel
more sympathy because if somebody blows their
nose too hard and there's blood you're
lining up your nose two guys gross
yeah yeah but then the jokes on
you i'm dead
ah so anyway i blow into this
thing and and ah my arm starts
spamming whoa what i'd never felt anything
like this but it's it starts and
i said oh i feel weird and
they're like ah okay ah let's get
a cold
cool compress a cold compress they put
it on my thing i didn't end
up passing out but i was saying
put it on my thing
put it on his thing where's this
doctor is i'm going crazy put it
on this thing
so so but you also get smelling
salts didn't you know for when i
when i had my balls drained yeah
oh okay when they went farm to
table yeah that's really fucking awesome
wow yeah but no but they told
me that people pass out all the
time for that test but they won't
stop doing labor yelling your brains out
i mean literally yeah thousand a lawn
we we don't know how else to
fix it we just need to do
this yeah it's just huge blow the
ping pong ball up you just do
there's no other way there's no way
to know also my doctor really apollo
guises every year when he has to
do the finger the prostate thing and
he's like there's no other way to
do this i apologize when they invent
something i'll be the first one in
line to ask ah yeah maybe gross
question okay how could it be
given the topic we were just ah
i can't imagine how this could end
up gross now you ever that you
you ever
are you standing here
haven't you seek out a duty to
your butt
ah
has that happened just in there just
so you have to nestle they get
poop soon but like you didn't time
it right and then you have this
test and then what that is what
happened to me i mean your fafsa
pretty specific problem i guess eau de
festa number one reason they asked you
to fast is because yeah i don't
want your shots you don't hear about
that actually does do some
things problem um i had a dog
question i have a doctor once do
it and and he was talking to
me while he was doing it and
then after it was like see i
talked to you to distract you from
ah you know what was going on
i was like yeah i got it
yeah and i was pretty hyper focused
on what was happening yeah it didn't
quite work but i appreciate the effort
so yeah that a squeaky toy and
was like two in front of your
face jingling
so in terms of fainting yeah fucking
painting yeah i faint i have fainted
i think twice and almost fainted a
couple more times but it was all
kind of in the same period of
life i'm not mistaken it was all
like when i was like sixteen seventeen
years old and it was happening one
time i was at a funeral and
it was really hot and a lot
of people were fainting
ng which is really wow do you
think it was a combination of the
motion and the heat or was it
purely just heat i think i mean
motion of the funeral i'm sure people
i'm sure being sad i don't know
if that makes you faint it was
you know what i mean like people
hyperventilating crying you'll make but yeah it
was really hot in this church and
really packed and so it was there
was an officer luther came up
yeah it was sorry that we talked
it was the only person that good
tracks and a lot of people from
martin luther king yeah luther king martin
luther king and the timing was passed
down to mcdonalds and then because you
wanted it so bad or because i
was really hungry wait to me i
think i was hypoglycemic at that time
probably at that time hypos
assuming yeah you're shouldn't change yeah anyway
was nice
so that happened it's not that interesting
you know just a few more little
times like that i famously fainted in
church when the pope got shot and
really the skewing oh yes he got
shot in front of me i was
like oh dear
um we i was in grade school
and they made the entire school go
next door to the church and start
praying furiously for the holy father jesus
like well what like god is gonna
be like should i let this guy
go wow these people go either wow
praying
that's the whole thing about how much
you liked this guy yeah it's like
it's not a preponderance of like how
many it's so i know praying associates
so yeah i mean i don't think
it's so stupid anyone who's ever anyone
to ever pray just an idiot okay
i was like blindly agreeing with you
cause i was thinking about choose and
then i thought i shouldn't say so
were you thinking about repaying for shoes
yeah it was wishing to god though
it
get some please god you haven't had
choosen ten years yeah it's mostly biff
at life for me different different life
so wait so you just pass out
from praying there was
it was i believe it was summertime
and it was very hot and it
was it was packed because the whole
the living museum was there yeah my
my father's rich my mother was very
good looking wow um and you are
aware of that i remember the feeling
of it of like it getting like
statically and yeah that's what happened it's
like feels like everything's shrinking yeah
to a little dot yeah and then
i woke up in a nun was
loosening my tie oh yeah what a
fantasy yeah does it mention looser building
a lot of non fantasies i've never
thought about that level oh a lot
of an artist fantasies nine yeah it's
called regular life yeah mom there's probably
none porn freaks out there
oh yeah sure yeah frail girl thanking
you know that kind of thing oh
girlfriend dressed up like a like a
sexy nun for halloween like an latex
nun costume of the shot because it
was cool yeah it sounds great five
i'm not catholic or anything so it
had no it didn't have that type
of effect on me it just was
like oh i like the fit of
this because i want like here
tits and ass in the late text
my dear my darling
i brought you a flower from the
garden
my dear my dear one i went
to catholic school do not have a
nun fetish could not imagine having one
okay sir ye was in there was
never like miserable there's never a sexy
they usually mean old witches from what
i understand you kind of yeah i
do not only sexy nuns there was
one remote
for one attractive none from my high
school talk slower
she was mean though oh really i
was faster she was like all attractive
women choose wow talk as best you
can to me
i remember we had there was one
very attractive teacher that everybody kind of
had a crush on who is a
religion teacher oh and so that made
things very complicated um because it was
of course she's talking about god and
stuff and you're thing i want you
to talk about yeah to make out
with me yeah did she ever like
sm
which topic suddenly to talk about that
yeah it's like wow it was like
all my life i've forgot what i'm
saying she said i wanna make out
with you
there was this crazy story that i
don't think i've ever told that i'm
not going to owe all the details
of tell okay but once i knew
brought it up you'll you'll know right
away i think okay but in so
in middle school there was this tape
that was circulating today ever tell you
this i don't know you i've just
the ring yeah and this little girl
came out of the t
yes you've told me and it was
made into a feature film twice okay
okay so you have told you um
no there was this this tape this
v h s tape that was being
passed around that kid at school had
made and and in it he was
doing really embarrassing things this sounds a
little okay maybe i tell i don't
it doesn't sound familiar to
are saying things like i can't really
tell you all of it because i'm
too embarrassed he was forgetting the name
of an old friend
he's saying oh hey nice to meet
you oh we've met before he's worn
front of his boss and i've told
him before i probably gave more details
that i'm giving now because yeah anyway
i was just reminded of it because
i was treating me like hot teachers
from the time and none of them
were but i was thinking about how
basically this this cooler kid had like
i played video games to this kid's
house taken the video i don't know
how he knew about it me stole
it and passed around school we all
got a chance to see it at
a certain point it was my group's
turn and we went to my friend's
basement she had this huge tv that
was like the deepest largest tv anyone's
ever had at this time did this
kid know that this tape was making
rounds i really like it i don't
know if he knew that you'd like
to i don't know if we even
knew what was gonna happen when we
put it on like we didn't know
and in it he was nude there
was new there was nudity there was
a lot of movement not any masturbation
or anything like that but it was
omega it was actually like chickens next
round
weird or that he wasn't doing that
and looking back at it you know
it's like what it was really shores
it was it was it was an
obstacle course of sorts
wow okay we gotta talk off mike
but yeah this is awesome
of course of sorts
i was just so we were all
knowing nude mouse trap essentially he we
were all screaming and i was like
a bunch of girls with this in
this basement and then we we pass
it onto whoever's turn it was i
don't know how this was happening you
know who was it was just the
way things were you know do you
think it was eventually handed to the
kid like you got to see this
and he puts in me i don't
know the prince
apple found out and our principal was
like when do i get to see
this day
he was like robin williams with a
really high voice he was like i
what like funny like him or no
he looked like him oh okay to
me i don't know if anyone will
agree with that and meaning people from
my middle school who hear this and
then they got in trouble and everyone
like the kid got in trouble and
all of a sudden the kid whose
tales called trouble i don't know what
happened to him but the
other kid got in trouble and then
for my whole life i've never forgotten
this and i've been like and i'm
sure that's not good for the kitty
there because that means me a lot
of us haven't forgotten it and it's
one of those things that really sits
in your brain as like a crazy
almost urban legend of the time yet
so wild and that's so fucked up
and i wonder how he's doing
hey if you're listening if you're the
nude obstacle course kids we'd like to
hear from you but honorary piss you
will be our guest after i know
it'll say oh i don't remember oh
hello
new kit yeah oh absolutely personal care
here hey hey listen i just want
to know this oh yeah this boy
i'm a pittsburgh hey thank you what's
up listen lauren told us the story
we're no tape soldier yeah oh shit
well i mean we don't know just
calling
guy for no reason yeah i didn't
know you'd tell the story oh my
god call yourself the obstacle course
good yeah of course i do
oh okay yeah listen um oh shit
i wanna tell my wife about this
in my family
good yeah thanks i got married to
my obstacle course oh no i don't
know how that works but it's like
saying that was one of the cones
okay isn't a work in that sense
of like okay well my boy totally
guys wow man baba buddha sees fava
anyway
member's name which i think is better
for everyone involved yeah i'm glad you're
not saying his yeah well no i
don't i'm not even sure what it
is and so there's no way you
can ever look him up or hey
tommy know i'll never be able to
figure it out then yeah although you
probably mutual tim no bunch never be
able to figure it out i'm protect
sherman
sherman that sounds great have you ever
it's chairman warman
we're german wurman yes vermin but do
anything for me or the high school
middle school that's like interesting in that
way like like a moment that like
stood out as like ah or like
a rumours i remember a rumor about
these two girls they were twins um
and this was when
they would have been there were younger
than me i think it's when they
got to high school they went eighth
grade or something like that i remember
till younger than you know no they
wow they're about to pull a hit
oh she's really weird because you did
that pause couple of years yes i
want to suspended animation for the corn
to be
i was like oh wait we want
oh you did a rum springer yeah
yeah but i decided to stay in
the real world like she's spending to
make tons of meth and like mountain
dew arms of mass mountain dew yeah
um ah and i remember someone telling
a group of us that these girls
ah
like at this you know fair or
something they snuck off with these guys
and did all this stuff and and
and like at the time i believed
it and then later realising like that
didn't happen at home yeah i didn't
do all that stuff yeah children this
honestly my story feels like one that
would have been a rumor like we
saw a thing where he'd and you
go later you've got no there's no
way right but you actually saw it
but i did yeah there's a certain
part that haunted me i'll tell you
about later oh my god this is
christ hey have you ever had the
experience of somebody that is in your
life and maybe i don't know like
a peripheral way not so
n-body you like you known new
somebody who never thought of as attractive
unattractive never thought about them either way
and then all of a sudden you're
right that person is very good looking
oh yeah for sure it's so weird
yeah so weird and you're like what
was i thinking the whole rest of
the time i'm like what changed or
why it does feel like it happened
overnight yeah like yeah oh
what a pleasing looking person i know
maybe you've cheney
i'm saying that as me you had
better i'll leave janie yeah i don't
like the scenario as a fun bit
yeah take it back bitch alright i
take it back bitch she isn't thank
you bitch
she's in palm springs right now oh
shit housley the woman you find so
attractive yeah my wife she having a
girls' trip time she is one that
she does every year she is inadvertent
it's not it's different trip we were
supposed to do it together and then
something changed my schedule i couldn't do
it anymore so one of her good
friends went with her wow and there's
nobody at this place where they are
that's great i wish i was i
mean doesn't that sound fun it does
yeah it does but i have this
rarely happens in the house to myself
oh what are you gonna do party
i'm gonna cram in as many movies
as i know she will not want
to watch
i watched the dutch okay promote things
but i watched envy of the dump
you said that done i'm gonna try
to go watch ducked the dunston checks
movies those dogs that dunston checks in
movie and it was great but you
loved the book right
you watched the movie but you love
the book dunston checks in the book
it was pretty faithful to the book
in the book there's two dunstan's would
end he never chased in the movie
he never checks it but still called
that yeah yeah so it's sort of
like ah waiting for you it's like
no thanks for checking in chinese with
all this friends yeah well i'm going
to write i think i'll wait for
government and godot and it's gonna find
those two projects wow i love that
wow
and waiting to exhale throw that in
there sure why not sure send the
car on fire well i know with
guidelines net during the pandemic i believe
for the first time you should only
really enjoyed it now i would love
to set a car fire oh yeah
but it's you know what i'm really
into it kind of remote something that
has nothing to do with acting as
long as you have nothing to do
with it you can yeah okay i'm
i just discovered we were also
supposed to promote things let's not promote
it at all let's not oh and
they don't yeah no fuck it i
won't say it no i'm supposed to
promote old stuff yeah it's all because
this is old so why so my
howell cold barely legal ah it's a
yeah because i guess it came out
a year ago oh yeah you know
it's kind of like
like firmly legal yeah like like la
times measures like twenty years later oh
concern it's laughable your asking huh oh
we went jane and i went to
a birthday party and we there was
that moment we're going into this bar
and there's a guy outfront
and he just like smiled at us
and we went in and they're like
we realised it a second later like
oh not even that guy was absolutely
not even close to carting us when
he saw right like not even as
a courtesy like we gently card everybody
here i was like no these people
are fine i find it yeah when
you go to a place that has
a big sign that
says we card anyone regardless of age
and then they don't card you it's
like cheese am i really that old
looking i mean you don't look seventeen
i walked right up to me so
what if i had progeria
what if i'm a jack what if
i am a jack alright we have
cigarette
and we're back and we're back and
um i
i meant to ask you lauren if
we can read this
this thing that i sent you remember
i said we should read this on
the air know this thing oh that
yeah yeah okay yeah what is i
don't know what this is well okay
that was doing one of his regular
checkups on me yeah yeah one of
my regular specifically internet's check who's talking
about lauren who's talking about lauren um
no this got sent to me in
a goog
gl alert i think for comedy bang
bang um but ah the the headline
made me jolt owe this honor have
time for headline headline i had donuts
for you guys by the way the
author of this piece is rashmi wish
i could do more but i don't
touch my tomato money rashmi mathur
wrote this ashby or three weeks ago
brushing my davis
hopefully deep
rashmi amadeus
ah for the title of the episode
it spelled r i absolutely am i
oh yes
me on a davis um okay so
here's here's the headline effect check
is loren lapis pregnant in twenty twenty
three oh i love these days so
a whole website that i love these
things wow the writing is crazy yeah
it's it sounds like it's written by
ai but i don't think it is
but here okay here we go it
sounds like it's written by ai but
it's probably written by a guy and
he's crazy
alright a name is trending on the
web and gaining the attention of the
people wow thanks raspi yeah yes we
are talking about dorothea laura laguerre lapse
yeah right she is in the headlines
because of her pregnancy news it's not
true she is an ameri
can actress and camino oh i know
i'm in the headlines ago yeah she's
an american actress and comedian she's mainly
known for portraying susan fisher in the
netflix show orange is the new blandly
yeah this news is getting circulated on
the web that she is pregnant now
what's this news is gaining the attention
of the people people are hitting
the search engine to gain all the
details about the news what happened what
does the entire matter it sounds like
one of my school papers just filling
space is she pregnant matter we will
try to cover all the details of
the news let's continue the article imagine
if you could like it said that
up your word count yes it says
but in an essay
a for so like let's continue the
essay yeah i'll go should i go
on well i guess i shall continue
here we go dear reader that is
not yet islam life gets pregnant in
twenty twenty three he would know she
is also prominent for her portrayal of
jess in the series crashing okay she's
also appeared in many tv series she
played the voice
of lada in the animated comedy series
harvey girls forever thanks she has worked
as a cast in the twenty fourteen
jurassic when she filmed both in hawaii
and new orleans yeah and it came
out in twenty fifteen several of her
scenes were improvised several things remain to
tell you about the news which you
will find by
next section of the article what it's
like the night guarding the holy grail
everything for me to tell you the
story alright tell me what's next according
to the report okay she released a
weekly podcast newcomers with co-host nicole byer
in which the two friends she has
appeared in metal podcasts
okay including improper humans comedy bang bang
now why why why does comedy maybe
get third billing i think he's not
a fan maybe okay rashmi am on
buddy talked to me reach out and
found damon and her very own podcast
oh if we talk about her married
life so she is married to mr
mike castle oh wow and they tied
the na
on five october twenty eighteen does he
prefer to be addressed as mr mccaskill
that's how i talked to him oh
yeah okay she has made the announcement
that she is pregnant when people heard
this news they got happy and curious
to know about the news okay scroll
down the page to know more information
about the news laura because
is pregnant that makes you so happy
what does it mean
i want to know more information about
this news the announcement has been happened
on her social media okay she has
revealed the news now i know where
this guy to show her cute baby
bump photos ah thanks rashmi her husband
appeared with a baby na the couple
that count parents for the first time
in twenty twenty one in summer apart
from this she is in the spotlight
in twenty twenty three because of pregnancy
news but she has not said anything
about this news because it's not real
there is no evidence that she is
pregnant that's what it says this news
can be fake which is spread by
the spreaders
it does not say that we have
shared all the details about the news
which we entered of the spreaders which
we have fetched from other sources to
make this article if we get any
further details we will tell you first
at the same site stay tuned for
more updates so we're supposed to just
continuously read this pay yeah yeah because
i would especially like professional writer
or updates because i might have added
some como rashmi yeah oh my god
you're now pregnant i'm now pregnant you're
down you're now in his pregnant i'm
pregnant with a noun well congratulations lauren
news a special lawrence topics yeah and
i'm curious it's just to make it
very clear it's not true and rashmi
doesn't know me and doesn't know what
they speak of hey the story about
the stork yeah right
yeah what did did parents ever really
say that i mean why don't i
just learned something oh what's that my
friend just had a baby and she
and the baby has a little red
mark on his face oh he says
called a stark bite yeah i've heard
of that i haven't heard over neck
that phrase yeah and i thought that's
kind of q and so it makes
me think that
apple didn't use that enough to make
that well how do they explain the
mother's change in size but didn't like
well i guess it's like how the
you don't want to say how it
came out so yeah like the mom's
gonna go to the hospital in the
store comes and brings the baby right
but how do you explain that the
mother is growing in size ove
over the course of nine moles the
stork isn't there
that never occurred no way i've thought
because the image is always the stork
flying with a with a diaper is
it from the fifties only or i
think it goes back further than that
yeah i think kids are too polite
to talk about mom's weight so they
assume she's really kids are notoriously polite
that's true they never call out things
that are abi i don't want to
bring this huge never coming
some people sensitive about this issue
there's just some stuff how would i
feel there's a cute kids book that
i got for holly's birth there she
got i guess i guess your birthday
for my birthday well it was my
birthday her birthday i gave birth what
are we talking about she got a
book called bodies are cool and it's
a cute book and tell about different
bodies and it shows all the different
way
these people can look at every single
honestly push seven billion it covered body
o a lot of territory other hot
people in there um yeah but was
there like this person's fat this person
skinny and these people are also hot
and this is what you want to
be yeah it's it's it's really like
that but you could look like anything
and be glad you
to be thin you'll be hot
you could look like anything can be
thin you can be muscular you could
be hot you could have great hair
great great abs you can have a
perfect tan and you can be that
perfect ten and you can be oiled
up in the summer you can be
greasy as hell greasy
i'm the one brought me a little
hammy down git o j o y
did today good one lauren is pulling
out something now it this weeks ago
we used to get a lot of
clothes from lauren moore
oh my god little cowboy little cowboy
boots there so wow now i have
to warn you oh my god there
yeah sure and then you have them
perfectly before like this she doesn't seem
to like hats or shoes i think
you'll be able to get him on
for one picture angle yeah a little
bit holly wore them maybe like three
times yeah
she bore them out one time and
it was the cutest thing like with
address it's just so very cute they
have ah is that what's the stitching
eyes at a flower cause you know
far yeah it's called it's just a
sort of it's just a cowboy design
wow yeah they're incredible they're fun this
is our next shoe size maybe she'll
usually by the time she grows enough
to wear these
you will have to wear them eventually
yeah when she's walking and meeting to
have that support she made them now
ah last time we recorded cool op
had a gift bag for lauren to
give to yes yeah then lauren was
nice enough to send a video boxing
video yes it was so cute as
a little dress which we have the
cheat but she saw
seemed to like better the she liked
the plastic bag that the clasping came
in and set it on her head
as like a hat but also like
that she did open something up but
she turned her back to the camera
miles davis style
eddie van halen said it was real
he turns right because he would always
turn his back to the audience so
no one could tell what his technique
was because it was so revolutionary and
then everyone copied it once they actually
were able to figure out what like
the job of the audience around
like david copperfield
savior
mostly me have a dongle my sure
you dongle
at one look at this dress when
you opened it let's see what's in
there
this is so cute she loves to
open presents now that she just darling
who doesn't we see sorry we're not
supposed promotion thing
i'm pulling it from her trying to
put on the video
huh
anyway anyway you've you've all heard any
way up and you know what sounds
like that you might talk more you
she doesn't
she's walking with it on her head
now but a very cute picture of
her in a big plastic bag owner
yeah yeah i'm not over her face
not over her for guys come on
i stop everyone you know by the
way not that big a deal but
you know what on the internet like
anytime you post anything like i saw
a celebrity posted a picture of his
child in their car seat is like
really sweet picture yeah and i open
in the comments going someone's gonna say
to raise the clip on the carseat
yeah it was first thing i saw
someone commented there's always one i love
seeing it when it happens live when
you like your kind of thing and
then the comment the judge comment comes
up yeah cause you're looking like yeah
yeah it's really i didn't have to
scroll it's really crazy how everyone tries
to control everyone on yeah i mean
like when i first put holly in
the carseat i was doing it wrong
in a friend message me and told
me that i was like that's helpful
that's the way yes like but i'm
like at a certain point i think
people know what they're doing it was
like right one yeah exactly what were
you doing wrong the chest clip was
too low this is the common comment
and i'll say it here in case
anyone doesn't know this it should be
between their armpits
because in in case of an accident
it protects your chest and it wouldn't
go into their you know that way
so it's helps keep on hearing right
back yeah i mean people should know
that but it's just my library he's
waiting on the car for a week
oh my god wow
that's well there's our super story we're
like yeah yeah someone left their natural
we are for but for you to
on a hot day no us again
have to say that p s a
for when i was a kid hot
enough to fry an egg on the
sidewalk hot enough to fry a dog's
brain wow yeah my car says reminder
look
in the backseat when i get really
far yeah if i have like when
your car mine talking to my car
until you do it yeah sure should
also say that when you can into
the car just looks like a scream
face so your face kill like a
vampire or something yeah vampires can't get
into carlos are invited it did that's
just plate that's houses and stuff it's
not cars your car
car is like an extension of if
you live in your car which i
do oh i mean sorry about the
mess name one celebrity who didn't
i've wounded live in a car
tiffany haddish no shit y
ooh george washington carver he did he
came town butter and honey he did
really i think i think so that
feels familiar topics no he didn't okay
he was pretty successful off the bat
so he was ah did pretty well
right yeah he would have based it
on easter he was he was literally
babysitter to bosom buddies
and he was set yeah i'm running
the bosom buddies so everyone understand it's
still funny probably not i mean i
don't know that who knows it feels
like the premise a lot of it
is flawed now a lot of it
was just like oh my god i
love these guys being so outgoing
yeah you know like they just went
for it you know what i mean
like they just were like very they
did a lot of funny stuff like
your flashes that i have of it
of of bits that they did yeah
that are still funny to me yeah
do you recall that show that they
made for cbs like not that suicide
ago that was like a version of
that yes yeah but i think audition
for that i'm sure yeah i'll
edition and i i audition for the
wrong part this had never happened to
me before ourselves where i thought i
was auditioning for one of the guys
who dresses up in drag there was
like there were a few things like
this where you men can't get jobs
anymore so they have to go out
without a woman's job dress up as
a woman
and this joe oh i thought you
were complaining of this like the to
the audition i was like yeah this
is what happened to meg get good
jobs anymore you go in audition so
yeah dress up like a woman i
didn't book it because men can't get
jobs so i auditioned i got there
and these and i started
and it was apparent obvious immediately that
i had the wrong sides oh wow
and i was like oh i'm sorry
i i was told this part it's
like no we wanted to read this
other thing i was like can i
just do this just so you can
see it see yes he would i'm
like and so i did it and
then they said here here's the other
part and of course it was like
hello can i take your coat
mister lead character so it's like it
was like the dia like the bro
e you know friend who's not doing
this but yeah yeah talks to them
about it at the bar whatever so
a lot less like yeah exactly i
was like this is actually gonna be
worse guys
and it was nye yeah i love
that i love that i auditioned for
what planet are you from and oh
yeah i worked on it all day
and i went to sony and it
took me so long to get there
and finally i walked in i finally
got there after an hour and forty
five minutes or something i walked in
the casting director took a look at
me said oh you're not right for
this yeah nice tell you what just
read this other part
and i looked and i said this
one line and she goes yeah alright
i'll do it with you um hi
yeah can you come in here and
i said no she went that's great
is that her fake papers to guest
people who drove their ass off yes
bad i'm like but just let you
do the audition like just like just
just let me it takes five minutes
yeah let me just do oh sorry
i feel like it was the part
like good i've never seen it so
i have no idea i don't remember
but it was just one of those
like things that made me
go like hey i should stop please
i mean auditioning maybe doing things to
make you go maybe just up um
because things like that are like unless
it's a specific physical type that yeah
stipulated in the script right which it
wasn't but i think she just who
knows maybe i was too tall too
intimidating to me
manly too cool right yeah yeah those
are your issues i did i again
had one of those i just wrote
part like that again years later oh
my god
so this was an audition for a
ah semi scripted sitcom about relationships so
it was all these different couples and
everything and this was shortly after i
got back from new york i was
getting back into auditioning again and everything
and i remember sitting in the waiting
room i was the only person there
and then someone that we know walked
out of there ah and said to
me
run ah whoa run run and i
went what he goes seriously just go
whoa and i did not and i
was called in experience i i started
reading this part and the guy who
is the creator of the show is
giving me direction with bad direction and
the casting
a person i could tell was like
trying to deal with this guy and
embarrass i don't think he might be
i don't think um you know he
might be too kind of intelligent for
read too intelligent for this part so
maybe he could read the other part
and the guy was like um yeah
oh right and then i read it
and it was
like this guy was clearly like did
not know what he was doing it
was really it was so obvious right
and this was his second show oh
wow and i think his last i
don't think this one went i need
to know who this is and if
he's ever done a new obstacle course
during the break a new optimal course
i was told in a frazier dish
isn't that i was really bad
nah really you told us that yes
they said you your bad said i
was bad and then they come to
your face yeah and then complained about
me to my agent too it was
like he was actually today's okay that
was really bad yeah that's what they
said i think so that's so great
something like that was just the issue
where you were like under your breath
you're hung fuck frasier frasier
in the butt and then once i
audition for a hundred relates you said
nancy i auditioned for hurly burly just
like in law my god hurly burly
and justin long a stage adaptation in
long beach yeah just a smaller part
and i did my audition the director
goes yeah there's that musical theater training
wow
wow happy so you will excuse me
your play is hurly burly and what
do you expect me to do her
labor law hey yeah anyway so obvious
auditioning in person yeah okay do i
know it's really are you just self
taping now is that it's also keeps
yeah i think so
yeah i would prefer i haven't even
got going oh right oh no i'm
getting it right right doesn't really it's
not what it's about because i feel
like what you're missing is like the
charm of talking to someone in person
i not about okay you want to
get it right it's not you're not
like really showing you can show like
if you mess up in an audition
and then keep going yeah impressive like
there's a lot of things that work
with it if i just
self tape i would audition again yeah
well why don't you just do it
okay they all will you be my
adjutant yeah people send you all the
ones that i get also do okay
i'll take place they see thousands now
just absolutely they see yeah he'll just
pop right in yeah they want you
to believe that they're actually watching a
thousand videos yeah i'm like what are
you wearing
blue screen that you'd do it in
front of yeah i really like oh
this is so new to you okay
no idea how we've been living for
lying down for years now you know
why i tell you this tax strike
is really hurt me yeah that's what
i like to say yeah i'm gonna
be like can't way to get back
on zack is that four hundred dollars
so yeah alright we have to
take a break come on
we're back and
oh what you're thinking there at a
time they can't do a three-tier you
could not be more wrong now it's
time to do when i'm weren't going
to do one and we even know
what it is yeah features when we
play a little game and it's not
this is not called it's called a
thatcher while we play game yes we
are and if you want to send
us a game to play you can
write to us at
three dm usaid gmail dot com and
now yeah this is one called rated
scenes we've done it before this is
submitted by kristin kelly double k thanks
kk two home runs and this is
like outs strikeouts yeah well they should
do it for home runs too so
there'll be more case have fun or
what kk
slider yeah what about musician my god
i love him you know he's he's
my favorite museum always plays in my
town square he plays my town square
to my town square does get around
yeah he travels a lot i mean
that's hey that's life on the road
that is i'm not disrespecting him or
even talking any trash but when i
think it's great when he plays everyone
in town comes out
hi everyone i in my town comes
out to yeah yeah i mean you
can't miss well because the songs are
really good i when the credits roll
yeah yeah yeah alright this is
we improvise a one to two-minute g
rated movie scene
and then we do the same scene
again but we make us pop we
make a pg than we do it
again s p g thirteen and then
finally as r rated wedlock but what's
the difference between the g and the
pg g is all ages pga is
like rental guidance but like something but
pg thirty it feels like pg and
pg thirteen
are the same these days doesn't it
or i don't know you'd know whoa
wait what i don't know gee how
many is g p g p g
thirteen cut out either pg or g
thirteen beats cut out pg yeah yeah
g p g thirteen oh yeah grant
right that's better that's much better that's
why i brought it up better that's
my years yeah
or complimenting him paul is a great
idea somebody suggested it was great to
call it out cause it's kind of
like what is the difference between g
and t g your name jacqui i
think that's what you are getting at
but this was yeah i'm glad you
picked up on it i did because
it's really clear when you said it
um okay
here we go your kids play softball
on this team
yeah um what's up
you ring the doorbell at the park
no i'm saying ding-dong hey wow that's
some players i i thought you walked
up what's up player girl and restart
restart ah
trying to shoehorn create a scene that
was a scene okay listen honey you
have to go to bed because otherwise
santa claus won't come no i'm too
scared what if he would refuse like
looks in my room hello santa claus
here no easier hi i'm coming down
the chimney who could santa clause actually
be hope there's no one
too scared i'm scared balmy it's okay
santa
hi everybody santa claus here and i
have wonderful toys for everyone a goldfish
for you who a good toy yeah
stuffed goldfish have anything for me so
stuffed i was supposed to have anything
for me santa i do what but
i'm an adult i know check out
your hinge profile
what a husband
that's g all right
alright p g no g thirteen did
you thirteen excuse me remember your idea
yeah
ah okay okay i can't discuss i
don't know the difference between them devise
a beach it's not pg thirty eight
alright honey shit you have to go
to bed or santa won't come i
really don't want to damn it well
why don't you want to go to
bed i'm afraid what if he comes
and looks at my
room i mean i hope santa looked
in my room a little bit ah
fuck that's your one another if you
can say it santa ana hi everyone
it's me santa claus oh i have
a wonderful toys for you wow what
is that ah
this is k y jelly what
that must be for my mom she's
in menopause yeah pretty dry oh okay
here you go sorry i got mixed
up like this does that really what's
been going off but nothing oh yes
we check out your grindr profile
okay merry christmas santa
and see oh wow are the fuck
are you doing up i'm not ever
fucking going to bed mom i told
you i was gonna run away if
santa ever tries to look in my
room again you piece of shit get
your fucking ass to bed right now
cock sock guy carrying your boy
friends back oh really he's my boyfriend
yeah yeah i'll take off my blouse
that's what i do my boy okay
those tits santa oh yeah it's me
oh my i've gives for you here's
a vibrator all right what am i
here is pornhub pornhub as a warning
yeah you're gonna yeah the internet santa
here you go you do it
yeah oh you don't even have an
internet connection here what's going on and
your butt flaps open this is your
dick flap
i love these pants are on backwards
weight is shit yeah shit santa shits
is so weird about that yeah right
that's disgusting no child should ever see
this and seen we did it
that was perfect that was fun that
was perfectly no notes none taken alright
um well i loved it and i
wish you a merry christmas and happy
new year let's see one more alright
get more on topic more more on
top moron to a more on topic
yeah let's see being dumb yeah i
don't think they think about that honestly
hi honey
oh hey you're back early
do you want to um
go to fairyland i do i was
i thought you'd never ask we haven't
gone since we got married yeah let's
go to fair i mean it it'll
be so fun i mean that's the
dragons and the unicorns doing welcome to
fairyland oh thank you we'd be so
much more welcome do we do we
need our passports no passports
are necessary in fairyland so doing for
instance we've been yeah i thought we
were supposed to like sign in with
a qr code yeah no no no
that is the mortal realm oh that's
right this is very late you're in
fairy land you sign in with a
dream and a wish oh i've got
mine i've i've got my dream to
have my wish okay well i say
my dream you can think of your
wish
okay my dream is to create a
world where no child has ever had
cavities sounds like a wish and you
mortal my wish is to create a
world where lots of children's have cavities
because i'm a dentist and my wish
is to have a million dollars see
the difference oh i see and i
wish to have her million dollars after
she goes you made two wishes
i didn't have a dream oh
oh no what happens now ferry oh
no one thinks now which is covering
don't lie man don't know it's disguise
turning green oh no well it's not
too scary oh yeah yeah it's just
green it's just green sky which is
a little different plants flowers are pink
the skies green yeah feel normal we're
not in no lot of danger we
could
just leave the cloud of pink the
sky is green a client several walks
in the sky is green and walk
huh the ween oh my gosh i'm
going to poke you oh my but
oh my wrist oh my elbow how
my eye and i'll keep that scene
npd thirteen
hi honey hey you're back early from
your date with that woman
yeah sticking together not you know i
answered honestly the date made me realize
some things but really that i love
you and i want to go to
fairyland with you oh my god i've
been waiting for these words for so
many years we haven't gone in so
long we just want since we've been
married i know we i mean but
you know i'm tired
all the time and but let's just
go let's go you're welcome fucking mortals
oh very sad that's the one high
we haven't been in so long we
passports or yeah do is qr codes
a dmb issued license or anything like
what do we owe need passports you
just have to show me your underwear
oh no
no problems here going i am going
commando not again yeah well i was
on the date mar easy access baby
that's disgusting we're trying an open marriage
because we've been having issues yeah we
tried to need your life story okay
oh here in fairyland well really that
show
shit to yourself okay alright so do
i get to go in and he
doesn't yes foe to the skies turning
green what's going on oh no an
evil witch is coming god damn hahaha
the wege
yeah maybe yeah what watch the stab
oh my stomach no blood but wow
it hurts you still like your idea
of an open marriage you're the witch
this whole time punished shit my eye
unique
scene
and radar
right rated r far ok honey oh
great you're happy to see me hey
it's what is it how was your
date with that slut
she blew me oh good i'm so
that we're so open and honest about
this i know but look i didn't
enjoy it oh even better a torturous
blow job from an ugly slot
meanwhile you can be home with your
wife a different ugly slug well we
have even gone to the very land
she got married said the
you want to go to fairyland really
i've been hoping for i didn't expect
it from you but if we could
go maybe it would fix everything you
know make a wish make a dream
something could have been fairyland since we
were growing up as kids you know
but maybe it'll rekindle some sort of
spark between us let's try it oh
no these cuts
this fucking bitch i remember her from
november oh my god always asks for
me and passport but willy oh yeah
and that's not all i'll give you
oh gee oh what did you just
do her okay she poked you what's
my wife were having problems but we're
still married we're trying to make it
work he said he just got a
blowy from some nasty little lady out
in the world some nasty little some
nerdy little slurp who i told him
he could go out with because i
approved her image on an app and
you are watching us the whole time
time oh okay we had that sort
of thing with the fuckin camera on
yes making me hard and i don't
have genitals
your skin is really okay well look
what do we do it just show
what it can do generally hard let
me try to shoot you what do
we owe i didn't learn i told
you stop carrying it around you're gonna
end up killing someone i'm holding sideways
i'm really cool wow what do we
have to do to get in here
um let's see you have to you
don't
even know how many people come through
here every day and you don't know
nobody fucking buy ticket show a qr
shore passport you gotta fuck right in
front of me i can't do it
i think we should get divorce instead
of fucking in front of this what
are you again i fuckin ferry dickhead
you with your perverted freak is what
you
you are maybe and you're under arrest
wow that's right we're not having marital
problems we're not even married we have
created a scene at our house to
build a backstory yeah get your knew
i was watching yeah you're always watching
that's your liking oh yeah that's why
you're arrested click click you're under a
row fuck now getting
this little satchel
get in at bitch and i go
she
jean
oh i'm too late oh well that's
what happened stuff i went to see
god yeah got our q late got
our q late got her to later
dialogue i've got her q late
um well that's gonna be it that's
yeah that's gotta be it that's got
again our email addresses three mjo sage
email dot com or on the socials
at three m usa and if you'd
like to call us leave a voicemail
the number is heg claims eight that's
right and look i have a show
coming up with my other show scott
hasn't seen it's
it's august nineteenth dynasty typewriter in l
a and ah look you know we're
gonna watch mamma mia here we go
again and do a podcast about it
special rowdy screening whomever that means to
you that's fun route is screening and
me and watch my old improv shows
that have passed on the video voltage
die writer dot com
down but they're still available to watch
um and i'm sure i'll have a
show coming up check my insta and
be sure to attend and me well
i've got a show with my old
friends super ego we are reuniting wow
so good while it does feel so
good we're gonna do a forgotten classics
um at dynasty typewriter
august twenty fourth about five days after
my show i know it'll be live
and live streamed my sloppy seconds yeah
that's that's what we asked for um
we have not we have not revealed
yet which book we are going to
be doing but forgotten classics forgotten classics
is where we improvise a book that
no
none of us have ever read using
only the first line the last how
do you check the names if you've
never read them do you have a
list of every book yeah we have
a list of every book that you've
ever read yeah we live in the
library of congress oh wow yeah so
we'll be doing some tweets do that
we haven't written um and then of
course september tenth at lodge room
it's me and nicole parker doing our
first ever variety show together called something
for everyone and that it's going to
be a lot of fun go to
paul f tompkins dot com slash live
for tickets or else we should say
partly yeah or else hundred percent yeah
or else you're in trouble yeah i
mean paul you vowed retribution to anyone
who didn't buy ticket didn't you yeah
i mean that was something that i
thought we were just keeping amongst ourselves
and oh surprise spot yeah when i
when i took my retribution but okay
now you know you're on notice you
don't go to my show i'm gonna
murder you yeah and so if you're
dead
it's because paul if you're dead you
must be
drop dead
right well we'll see you next time
that's good huh we didn't even see
this time we imagine endless frankly every
episode we imagine every single whatever we
hold hands in a circle and we
picture all of your faces and you
are a good looking bunch and like
decide you're so handsome and beautiful oh
my goodness
spy guy
uh