nah
oh i rolled my ars on that
read oh yeah freedom wow much like
the lion from zoo belize zoo
i don't what does jubilee simply say
it was a pbx program parental buying
inspection yes and this is for the
bison inspector yes yes apparently spectrum
apostrophe spectre um
a show where these grown actors is
grown ass actors lead animals who all
had different personalities and they interacted in
a sort of what i'm like real
life sort of pretty much the same
liminal space words worms favorite like obi
a white stage with like little pieces
that would come out like mac pc
commercials it was
basically like that but then they'd have
like a little set like little pieces
of the set that they would use
from time to take a chair sure
but yeah it was very very half
a table bare bones but the makeup
was well done there were skeletons they
were animals animal skeletons in underneath the
like makeup the costume
the human skin there was a scalp
they were barebones yeah yeah and honestly
most people just described them as just
walking bones
did you meet that piece of walking
bones the other day that boy like
so fucking oh yeah hot piece of
walking
damn those bones walked well hey welcome
to threesome skeletons are funny my name
is paul skeletons are silly my name
is lorien skeletons are scary my name
is scott z three personality yeah very
different that's how we interpreted skeletons yeah
and i see a little taste of
what you'll get on the episodes of
freedom we if you
ever listen to one good skeletons if
you ever saw literally what they show
at halloween but literally a human skeleton
into brain came around you don't see
that in horror movies ever but it's
so famous in halloween skeletons are everywhere
everywhere what if our skeletons actually had
like
like little ah you know like rivets
where the arms and legs your what
are they called you know on a
cardboard skeleton decorate oh yeah like that
has the rat join brad's yeah right
but they're not really brown gold circle
like the absence of brad yeah yeah
yeah zo brad yeah but if you
saw literally
the bones that would be in a
human being you're not dressing it up
or making it scarier whatever they just
walking around your house it would be
scary movie scary you don't need to
dress up a skirt we don't dress
up skeletons we don't need to put
them in top hats no we don't
need guys who it's fun to to
do it first amendment potatoes the kiehl's
skeleton yeah yes you know you've made
it when you've been asked to sign
the keel skeleton we don't we don't
talk enough about the kills can we
tone and we need to because honestly
when you think about it is that
their mascot they do all skin or
something that is the absence of skin
itself right so if you use our
stuff long enough this is what you'll
end up
you scrub your skin too much there's
no model that they use i don't
think who has the best skin in
the world i mean you can't can't
quite who has the best skeleton in
the world me i know think so
i know i have a good skeleton
strip away everything yeah and your skeleton
is really really tricky yes all were
so
skeletons like log in one hundred years
when we're dead and we're skeletons and
they pulled up all three of our
skeletons anyone could be able to go
that's lauren that's scott and that's probably
from how tall we are probably we
gave out our heights we did give
them and i mean i never should
have done that i'm also not male
and i think that that should look
different because you wouldn't have a penis
bone
so yeah you direction but yeah when
i was thinking that's probably my team
six feet out
that's how that's why they need caskets
because otherwise exactly i mean breaking through
the ground adds why we need casco
yeah yeah yeah it took them a
long time to figure that out right
what if you saw in your house
and it's let's say somebody you knew
and they called you said hey i'm
gonna come over there is something different
about me and i want you to
be freaked out when you see it
okay
but they don't say what it is
they don't say well god i would
be driving as fast as i could
you're driving you wanna come over to
my house and show you i'm gonna
come over there come over to your
house oh they wanna come over to
my house yeah yeah so you're driving
away from your own home no i
thought they want me to come over
and snuggle i'm coming over okay something
is different about me and i don't
want you to be freaked out but
then i'd be like we're just getting
you shouldn't have you should just be
you should be outside i can't wait
any longer what is it i am
outside
good action i'm calling good and thank
god yes alright i'm coming yeah what
is it and then they come in
and their head is just a skull
now like the rest of their bodies
yeah that's fine but it's just a
skull they can talk where does the
skin they have hair no no hair
skin start under the jaw line or
or under the neckline under the neckline
so
if you're if they're wearing a polo
shirt yes would you see any skin
they were i would say they would
probably try to make it so that
you couldn't see the skin if you
were michael caine waiting on ripping open
like a tennis jacket i'm just like
pulling it down when you get down
to chef service you'd see some of
that skin yeah you'd probably see some
of the skin i can't i can't
tell you exactly where the skin joins
it probably doesn't look great i'll be
honest is it does it meld in
like like gradually like an ombre hey
man i don't know i think i
think what my friend did and just
feel like you should know this and
your friend is trying to shield you
from that and they're wearing a turtle
neck
owning my little boy yeah jack is
sticking up on this and the skull
atop my first reaction is i'm not
opening the door to that i might
be looking through the window going what's
going on what have you might be
saying like hey take off your mask
and let me show me the real
thing was i can tell us on
a map because it's smaller than what
they want a lot of noise these
fake phone calls were there using real
people's
voices spoofs but if they're called spoofs
i think they're called up i think
if you had like a an unusual
like sudden birthmark syndrome
um and you said hey like there's
something weird about my face or like
remember when carrie underwood just kind of
said that's all of her fans nothing
was different right i mean she's still
had a shit she had um and
birth plants sort of accident but she
looked fine sbs but if you have
felt different too there was something everyone
kate middleton was like i like i
just faced tuned my face but then
it turns out she was actually werewolf
yeah but if you had something like
that showing up with a skeleton mask
first is a good idea to be
like then you pull it off people
get older just it's just it's just
a birth but i mean they're saying
it's it's let's say it's mary holland
that's why i'm imagining actual number because
i was imagining her coming up to
my house yes and then i'm thinking
okay so i know it's her because
i know
know what she looks like yeah normally
and then i'm seeing that the top
hat part the head is just a
skull yeah
i think she'd be crying i don't
think she'd be like would tears come
out if it was just well i
think she'd be distraught y'all know of
course you'd be your doctor on top
of the school aren't they on top
of the scar on top of the
you they're not underneath the skull are
they or are they i don't know
where the paradox the tear ducts i
guess are part of the circulatory
system which which are over the school
laid over the school yeah so she
wouldn't be crying
inner voice should be yeah she'd be
wishing she could you know what let's
say she can cry and that there's
tears coming out of the schools cry
i still tell you what it felt
like way to schools cry i think
it's still keep her outside ideally your
friend marry you keep her out shy
leading i don't have this conversation just
like sitting out front kind
of like i don't know that i'm
going to why i don't know that
i want to bring her inside because
i don't know what's going on that
there's all the she's telling you what
did she say well you have to
let her in why because she's your
friend and saying what if she's a
zombie she's something she's not me she
said that on the phone and she
said i'm not i'm not a zombie
and she doesn't look like she looks
like on my phone
something's different about me yeah i'm not
a zombie yeah that's a weird that's
a weird one thing to call i
don't want to say it over the
phone i'm very embarrassed so can i
please come to your house and get
inside quickly as possible
bring outside a hat and like oh
my god lauren maybe like paris like
a mad really getting to learn a
lot about you look and i'm not
letting her come in because when it's
catching it what it is and then
you're making it worse it's not catching
but so what and how do i
know she just says she's not a
doctor she no doc
he has told her here's what i
don't want what i don't want to
say she hasn't gone to a doctor
phil i don't wanna be in my
own home and then later when she's
not there thinking a skeleton was sitting
right there yeah she's a skeleton but
what's her head is a skull she's
not the only different she's still your
friends she's still your friend your good
good refrain is good
what her brain is yeah right it's
right there even better you can see
yourself yes this experience it's so her
brain is better because she had this
experience yeah if you squint through her
aisle yes your brain is that how
you think about like life and experiences
your brain gets better when you have
a bad experience the worst of course
the famous zombie move
ivy's is everyone's like oh how do
we kill them wouldn't you be trying
to cure them like like for like
if it was your loved one you'd
be like hey what if they'd come
over the cure tomorrow i feel like
it's every one hundredth zombie movie doesn't
say shit dealers zombie movie yeah where
it's your life and you're like i'm
really trying to make this work my
salary life
very nice zombie love zombie wife
zombie wife nice my
zombie why is up for g
my salary wave
take my zombie wife please do you
take care of her do you
please cure please cure my zombie wife
please do you think i sound like
a musical zombie um ah i think
what do you think that when that
joke take my wife please please yeah
it was first set i think it's
still funny but anyway go ahead
because it's it's the idea is you
would think he's saying take my wife
for example yeah it's a he's saying
like oh there are all sorts of
people out there in the world take
my wife please yeah huh
oh people laughing at vaudeville that's wild
how many people really hate their wives
so let's do a full fifty percent
fifty percent get divorced yeah but
how many divorces are amicable of that
fifty percent
three percent maybe
i don't yeah i don't think taking
my grow new amicable down the line
but i think three percent are like
you know what this is probably the
best thing for both of us and
there are no bad guys in this
situation yeah yeah i've heard of one
right no good what's that so i
don't know there ain't no good guy
yeah there's a song i know bad
guys there's really
you and me and we'd agree ooh
anyone yeah divorce you should play with
it yeah that's all no that's all
middle yeah it'll arrange it just sort
of stays in the same place slight
variations up and down it's like an
e k g it's a good karaoke
song
i meant yes absolutely dave mason by
the way thank you if we want
to hear a little bit of it
sure would do first off this is
a an adjective sounds different
frank something that last vegas weiss twenty
twenty four i don't know what this
is okay
this song rocks my saw some rocks
what year was this did this come
out oh my god i'm banging my
head ninety seventy seven okay
released on
i don't know even this part like
it never changes it never gets a
better way okay let's hear some comments
on this this is one of those
songs that just touches the soul and
makes you think about life slash love
and relationships because it's about that you
could never understand why this great song
by dave mason didn't get more
more airtime on the radio i've fucking
heard it yeah i've heard it a
million times it's truly hidden gem among
rock pop songs so i think i've
only heard the song on the radio
yeah i've never seen like keep it
going
here's another comment oh that's me
been listening to the song for over
forty five years we are continuously
please come get me
trapped in a place where they keep
playing the song here's it's only you
we just disagree this is the very
first time i heard this song i
think it may have healed my broken
heart when the love of my life
took a different path all those years
ago death now when you just heard
it the first time it healed your
neighbors all those years ago and find
just today you're a racist comedy what's
the date on the clinic one year
ago
oh wow sixteen replies to that comment
hey i never went anywhere great song
to recover yourself in right on brother
this song has that effect yourself
say is a special sing song
don't you see one hundred emoji party
food don't you feel like i feel
your pain a clean sweep of like
internet comments going past ten years ago
like let's just like erase sweep em
all down yeah twitter anything anything sweet
tune you're too much history is being
built on the internet i think we
need to like clean it up i
disagree why because i think that it
teaches people you can put this only
gonna be there forever yeah so think
carefully that does not work people wear
whatever the fuck they want that's right
they're dumb hey breaking news i have
a press release just sent to me
two hbo renews real time with bill
maher through twenty twenty six
nah dunn and paul have tom gives
his back on this show watch
could they could they were new year
contracts sneakers later yeah weird without anything
you had to do it
fuckin imagine
oh oh there ain't no good yeah
hey no bad guys but that's what
i say when i see oh and
bill maher and we just disagree
i and my segment by singing that
entire song to bill every week every
week and he's loves it and he
keeps me on the show i got
into an argument with someone that i
know about um like people being too
sensitive these days or whatever and so
we're going back and forth and then
he finally sent me a clip it's
like well what do you think about
this
and it was a clip of bill
maher and i'm like i automatically disagree
i don't have to watch it either
i will not watch there are no
good points that are made there aren't
good
and only bad foods
ah now you're the audience you were
on it the first season yeah like
regularly every week he did an episode
i thought very funny wow thank you
very kind to say he would write
a new thing about something that was
going on news i read a new
thing about something that was going on
the news wow scott pitched it perfectly
that's what it was yeah every week
he would
and what were some of the subject
matters you're the only one i remember
the only one is there was a
you know one of those times where
there was a confederate flag issue where
they're like jim crow sure that i
was pro but i made a pretty
good case now but i remember the
only thing i remember is that at
the end of the segment bill felt
it necessary
need to point out that the civil
war was ah not just fought over
slavery but it was other states' rights
right yeah awesome yeah
yeah it was it was interesting because
i was that was like around the
first year that i was doing the
the live show down at mbr two
thousand and three yeah two thousand and
two was when we started and he
would come because he would have comedians
on doing their bits he would come
to the the show that i was
producing right and recruit national pull up
a recruit a lot of the ap
acts like i remember jerry minor had
a really funny military minor and funny
bit on there yeah anyway those were
the days good day were the days
well he had nothing that's crazy that
you did twenty ten years ago or
twenty one years ago that's when i
met janie yeah as a result of
that show i would not have met
janie had an up and wait why
because another i are used to date
her
brought her around
she left him for you this is
hey nice yeah um i met a
guy who worked on that show who
we've similarly felt out of place um
and he invited me to a gathering
of friends at a place called cafe
deserts and i is it still there
no it's not there anymore you know
a cool up and i still go
to the place where we had our
first date quite often was a cafe
desert but pasta maniacs
this used to work there in minnesota
well it was called possible kogan possibility
x yeah hulk hogans pasta mean yeah
that's she worked there when she was
looked at by postmedia know your brother
honestly yeah my nicole heal you our
first day was sushi and tap and
it is changed into now sushi dan
rock and roll sushi and we eat
there quite often in studio city sushi
yeah yeah i used to go there
yeah ah no no tap dancers anymore
yeah yeah oh i forgot that that's
what the tap part was yeah what
did you think it was beer yeah
of course it would happen every i
think they would probably do it every
forty five minutes to make sure that
every customer got
to see one performance and it will
be the same performance every time i
don't know yeah probably a few lingered
you probably wouldn't see the same thing
over yeah yeah maybe maybe you'd see
twice and there was like a stage
no i think they would do it
like in in between the tables as
people side tap i think it was
table service i don't want to see
that why did they do
tabletop taxing tap dancing yes it's crazy
it's where you tap your feet it
makes noise i've heard it's more special
shoes i still have my tap shoes
i saw that at the cosby show
weird i know i haven't i haven't
tapped danced anything like gregory hines savion
glover savion glover um i think i
do
i a challange i might attach him
to the comedy shows but but really
i haven't tapped danced for like for
good for now thirty three years yeah
well my horny we actually see at
the same time for me and i
was doing the bart man in my
hotel
for this the part man we did
a tap dance performance to do the
bartman and was there a dancer one
with the barman on the yeah i
don't know but can we hear it
yeah i mean obviously sticking his button
the camera right yeah that's the main
cause he's route yeah he's a rude
dude he's insouciant attitude okay so first
we'll see an ad for why
oh the cat was gonna wait help
kids lie oh okay so youtube theirs
listen you're so boring
this is the video tape simpson sing
the blues which just such a great
tape sure yeah i love tapes yeah
and a couple great tapes that my
ah godfather got me from the moral
bureau like system of sending packages like
marlboro mile yeah yeah marlboro christmas tape
that i loved as a kid i
watch that i got with marlboro miles
and i kept it for a really
long time to show him the marlboro
logo there's so much cartoon before the
song starts we have to sig break
so we'll be right back okay so
much cartoon
uh
and we're back and are still going
still hasn't started
ah but waiting for it the fuck
is he doing he's it's like a
school recital and he's trying to speak
in the little karate noises or so
he's trying to jump up behind everyone
because his parents can't see an oh
now he's plugged in his own walkman
to the sound system lorica you still
do the dance especially while pregnant yeah
i can do the full tap dance
tap tap tap text
oh my god let's go yeah just
come on the table wings with that
guy
whereas
i'm sorry this must have been so
cute when i was doing this test
scores together
i've been um
that's the funny thing he said about
yourself because i can't really picture being
myself watching holly do that now and
i think this mercy
i've been going through the
the billboard r and b charts from
the eighties dead on there no but
i i'm reminded when i see this
have just like
there was a certain same ashford a
weird time or sometime around nineteen eighty
two where like every comedian just put
out their own rap songs alertly and
some of them would chart because there's
like ah mel brooks charted with his
ah good to be the king rap
or whatever then rich little charted with
the presidents rap no
no oh my god yeah right let's
learn a little bit of the presidents
rap okay yeah wouldn't help me memorize
the order probably not i have a
i think i could get to the
first four presidents and that's not many
well yeah there's a large yeah washington
adam and then i can get it
from i waited on what
wilson wilson the black label here yeah
oh well you ruin the volleyballs president
he got allowed on rich little yes
so much done this nineteen eighty two
nine minutes long
because he was meant to be played
in clubs and shit
and it also yeah it uses the
the the tom tom club to imagine
your cooked out of your mind you
go to cure us a little yoshi
what james this cozy guest comes on
here's some credits ronald reagan rich little
nancy reagan melanie chart off she played
melanie partout yeah it's it's great she's
an actress remember
this also was the year that everyone
was ripping off the tom tom club
song and using it for their own
songs which one do they start rapping
i don't know they when do all
the presidents star rusty now be honest
it my age do you think i
should be doing something with this
believe me talking about sex once in
a while it's healthy to me is
sort of thing well that's exactly what
nancy reagan sounds like yeah it's landing
hello
just stay blue or skate shop with
enough
oh no we're the laughter chunk right
but john that's right i forgot this
has left toronto canada just like a
normal lounge type on it you look
cool d i like the way you
look and the water wings
oh no it's a it's a holy
shit had sung all the way around
do they rap i know better
oh my wish alright one of his
eight minutes of this and then one
minute of rap good lunch and shower
in the morning i think it might
just be jokes and no rapping must
have that shot it's the tour fuck
that shinji wednesday okay if you picture
via record it's presidents rap you want
to share him without of course you
don't want to hear club jokes
with a laugh track i don't think
jerry nancy reagan church and dancing did
this in a club
and be like yeah it's like requesting
it from a d j when i
was coming up in comedy at the
comedy works in philadelphia which is my
home club that high yes there would
be a song was played after the
shows of course have told you about
the terror early show curly shuffle yeah
that was a different that was different
by
the way a forty five that i
bought as a kid yes sure of
course yeah um your own money with
my own money did you do to
earn it probably all that weeding with
all the roly-poly bugs when you were
like at the store and you were
picking it up was there a dying
soldier saying earned this
so yeah it's crazy to think that
like my grandfather and fought in world
war two and my dad fought in
vietnam so i could save money by
the curly shuffle record yeah best country
in the world what a disappointment i
am
we didn't have any good wars you'd
go now yeah go fight someone right
now i'll find one i saw outside
to the death what do you think
would happen if you went down to
like an army recruitment center at your
age yeah i'm saying i want to
here's the thing i'm a pretty accomplished
guy i want to go straight to
genera
and i want to do it like
i'm not gonna like go to you
know boot camp and all that kind
of stuff i want to go straight
to one star general skip the process
but i wonder if it's like college
where like you know occasionally i'd be
recruited of like oh i know you
haven't graduated ah you know junior college
yet but we'll take you into the
graduate program at temple or whatever you
know right away
but you know what i mean like
like oh you seem like a cool
guy you've got a good head on
your shoulders you're smart yeah well you
don't have to do private sergeant all
because it will just go you right
to general right from enlisted yeah temple
in there yeah no temple university yeah
why did you temple university i think
they offered me to go to like
acting real school yeah what if we
admit in philadelphia while
the army easy
zombie army
but you would have been a couple
of years behind me so we wouldn't
have met in school because i did
not last ah yes we're not have
been college july just wouldn't have happened
but wait here's what happened you need
to bill murray days when the happens
here's what happened after the show at
the comedy works yes they would play
this song called fat is in
and this was baseball player terry forster
who was making hay out of david
letterman calling him a fat tub of
glue and so he recorded this record
where i think he just introduced it
and then the owner some of the
comedy works did the song he would
perform it
not always a record they were just
oh okay
how many
so this is somebody who held a
tape recorder up to yeah well they
held them better still hours away this
is not an official my neighbor played
the song
i don't feel like terry forster uploaded
this hot chocolate cone instead of chocolate
ganache like that is where being overweight
is
you know and so the owner of
the comedy works this is him yes
sir
it's pretty good
don't you break that door be thin
i can't this is okay so they
will play this at the end of
every show played at the end of
the show yeah after the show's over
its and that was how many of
the new zoning that was what the
quality of the recording but how confusing
to the audience yes it was recorded
into a wastepaper basket how confusing to
the
audience who doesn't know the connection of
the owner of the comedy works did
this right where suddenly they see a
great comedy show yeah and they're getting
up to leave and suddenly fat is
it yeah they're like they're absolutely not
paying attention oh okay i don't think
anyone ever registered that the song was
playing accept the kava can you talk
about wastepaper basket yeah yeah let's do
it garbage basket
trash trash and waste bag garbage basket
before
is that a guard barbara hale i've
heard garbage pail garbage army yeah yeah
i've only heard garbage pail reference to
the kidding waste paper basket so specific
it's only for wastepaper yeah trash receptacle
bin dumpster
there's too many names dumpster i think
was the first one to do the
thing where they took the um the
vowel away oh it's wu m p
s t r what what's a dumpster
know i know what a dumpster is
but i don't know if mt and
p r that's how it's spelt no
it's not yes it's a brand name
dumpster is a brand
oh yeah but a dumps were saying
what's dub stern you're wrong it's dumpster
well you also were like you don't
know what a dumpster is when we're
asked and they were like don't guess
we do what you like do u
p s c r and i'm like
but what's that my confusions not crazy
no way you could just say no
because you're going but because it was
hey der with no e a dumpster
is with any what is it it's
lowercase d lowercase d with an e
r but that is now like a
kleenex thing because the players jerry but
i also cannot find anything with the
brand name of dumpsters
did that clear it up for you
know
dumpsters like outside bins yes whoever invented
that called it i don't ever heard
of that but it but now you
have there is no information regarding this
on the internet anywhere oh my god
dumpster breaks weeks so i'm a little
so just like i dreamed this maybe
this isn't this isn't real we were
talking about grinder
it's back no but dumpster with three
of section adduction with an e like
the normal way of spelling blood dumpster
is kleenex it is like that the
term is a generic sized trademark of
dumpster and american brand named for a
type of mobile garbage ben okay but
it had any it did it was
spelled the same way i apologize pause
is
trait everyone but they did it with
a capital d sure yeah ping pong
with a hyphen is a trademark pong
with no hyphen is a non trademark
term for table tennis fuck off this
is all these are old names that
might surprise you know me i'm always
asked that's bad trademarking when you're when
you don't cover the hyphen part of
it yeah and you let anyone else
just use it with
if the person at the trademark places
like doing this i'm like oh you
don't want to cover it without the
it's only one more dollar i was
up to reading some more i saw
her recipe is one of them but
now i have to subscribe to their
orlando sonu signup no orlando sentinel you
out of your mind what what are
they called again where it's the theirs
a term for it whereas like cleaning
dumpster
here brands that are likely next that
are so common they become more is
they're so generous sized that's for later
that one is gonna surprise you escalator
with no a the term escalator was
coined by charles c berger who partnered
with otis elevator co to create the
first commercial to being one of those
two fuckin weirdos see berger what fan
and date of course chapstick q tips
jacuzzi jello popsicles jacuzzi johns oh that's
cool guys the girls start to get
jacuzzi frisbee zamboni sam bony that makes
sense xerox yeah today's clorox apex hydraulics
i
guess i didn't know till recently oh
okay do you need some hydraulics
honestly see it's like it sounds like
a cleaning product i didn't know till
recently that lasers and acronym light lion
yeah saudi oil is the grey
lays out equals re oh my god
have you seen that they're bringing back
the motorola razer phone which was a
phone i had by million years ago
i want i loved my love to
have the hot pink one what are
they hundred dollars which was disgustingly steep
at the time it's yeah it's a
flip phone it's now it's still a
flip phone it was a flip phone
guy
i want it and i think about
maybe you'll make enough money to get
somebody i will the problem is i'm
so tapped in with his iphone situation
i know but i really love the
idea of closing a little flip phone
and tossing it's such a thousand shit
it's my barbie's family we said to
the static feeling that i want buy
loved it and i
wonder if i could regain my t
nine texting skills i don't think oh
yeah yeah i think it's a smart
screen oh and i do miss buttons
i miss buttons but do you think
you'd ever get a dumb phone maybe
i tell you what i'm i'm getting
kind of an i'm i'm weaning myself
off of my watch because i'm sick
of the
yeah you did mention yeah i just
don't like it anymore well i wanna
wear like a regular walk yeah i
loved watches and i mean it is
fun i think a lot of little
plus style yeah exactly and it is
like app the apple watch to me
is not like my style but i
liked i have a different band but
i got a different thing happened with
cool up in as well as you
paul words
where he'll check your watch because you
get an email and i will assume
like you're out of time or your
lads distracting to also be able to
get an email while doing something yeah
i don't want that i don't need
that yeah i want to get all
my emails at like eight pm every
day like the whole days just sending
t all yeah yeah what about and
i'll take it
nine am no then i have to
get back to everyone all day this
this other game that you guys are
playing with the circles and the width
okay oh you'd love it ran strands
i don't love it i'm i'm struggling
with it today's was hard i didn't
do it to yet but yesterday i
did it with no hints and i
was that was the first time it
happened i was pretty proud and i
got the symbolism
or whatever program sangram what is the
stone space to our words my dear
boy but you don't know what the
words have you ever searched for words
i've been lost for them so it's
ah it's a what it looks like
to me is a pile of gobbledygook
okay where i'm like what is this
i know i can't see anything there's
ah the title of this of the
str
and is called something like the first
time it happened i was like my
beautiful minding right now because this as
you are seeing now i'm seeing all
these like just gobbledygook in front of
my head i thought that like ah
you were hitting on someone and maybe
reminding i don't like or you know
body right now i am asking for
will you hold it against me right
now yesterday was the first time i
i could see the words pretty quickly
yeah me and the end of the
first word i guess was one of
the real words and so then i
was like oh i think i get
what the theme is there i needed
two or three hints i say get
a little light bulbs there yeah it's
in beta and i don't think it's
ready for primetime while the numbers one
was in beta and i used to
play it and then lisa numbers it
was where you you have to
figure out like they give you ah
six numbers and then they give you
the target number and you have to
figure out how to add and multiply
and divide the numbers your six numbers
to reach that target oh my god
but it was in beta forever and
since then i went back on it
and it was like beta has now
concluded they never eat didn't nobody likes
that yeah no one liked it this
transit keyless i also don't like
the the um score sharing it just
yeah it's not it doesn't it's not
as viral as connections are as well
yeah it doesn't really give you any
sort of like idea of what happened
yeah we were in the world rut
for a while we were it was
like audit we were automatically sending each
other worlds yeah we were really young
and then i think paul's trying to
break the chain he's going we're not
gonna keep sending connections every day
day and then we went we'll still
keep going but you don't have to
play but it will now you're adding
stickers on top of our school protests
why
why are already protesting by now wanting
to confront you why why because i
don't care man this is an intervention
ally i don't care why read your
letters go ahead read your letters no
this is an intervention read your letters
okay oh okay paul yeah
it really really hurt me that you
put a sticker over scots of course
draft
it was the icing on the cake
it was the cherry on so you
liked it it was
icing on cakes is pretty good yeah
maybe better it was the last straw
oh that sounds bad but still you
go straw
it hurt me so bad that i
didn't know what you got on your
score but you were putting us pasting
a sticker over his score i didn't
have a score
this is my letter would you please
listen to the letter without interjecting listen
without prejudice as ever just sure yeah
part one the end was that oh
shit i was so close to yeah
i really wish i'd said you think
lauren volume one when are you gonna
read yours oh yeah that's in your
letter
yeah what are you going to read
yours yeah you asked me yeah that's
right yeah it's just been everything oh
i said the end what he read
yours paul your friendship means the world
to me you've been there for me
through thick and through thin i shit
like that yeah you really can't know
i want to be there for you
in your time of need
you fucking jerk hey hey this is
your letter your letter my letter i
have to listen without prejudice while you
won't stop putting fucking stickers over my
scores that lauren wants to know if
she can do better than you know
if i could do better if i
could do and she can today she
could've today because i had two or
three labels see i i'm gonna do
it later okay today didn't make any
sense
i have to do as long he
used liquor and made me i finally
figured it out like an hour later
i was like what does that clue
even me give it a glance give
it a little quick clan take a
look do you know i've been trying
to think of ah someone's last name
is somebody used to work with many
years ago
and i can't remember her last name
but when i try to think of
it paired with her first name my
mind always goes to the last name
glancy which is someone else i worked
ah i tried to think of someone
that i know very well yesterday and
i was like what is their name
i can't their first name looming yeah
i know it no brainer you guys
brand whole podcast got good brandy yeah
your p f t thing yeah that
whole thing is like good brand i
don't even it wasn't even my idea
whose was it i don't know people
have always been calling me that yeah
yeah people ah throw my life of
called me laugh
e laccase people call me by my
name a lot yeah you got one
of those last names yeah but i
i've never thought of it that way
i'm always surprised by it not always
but it's just i call you lapses
sometimes yeah that's that's australian lassie lassie
law law opsi plaza i was tough
oh i'm just trying to do every
vow like they do can we talk
about australian traders finally rally weekend know
what am i guess i talk about
it you can
thank you scott shut up q i'll
go because you ever watched it yet
i have watched then enabling i won't
talk about australian winners emily heard it
just in passing because mike watched it
yeah i'm kangaroos zero five episodes in
hd okay grew so far interesting yeah
yeah yeah i was a bold choice
assume it would be all kangaroos but
you're saying none had those people how
do they keep the fingers out of
the shot yeah i don't know what
they deserve camera you can hear them
trying to get kangaroo wrangler going like
sti back kangaroo yeah oh okay marines
there oh he's right he's the best
cango wrangler i don't the host is
the least the host is the fuck
one of the hosts so far ah
tough yeah you don't i don't know
him he's he's out there no he
is australia so that's the thing like
usa traders you got a scottish guy
you should always be someone from a
different country only interesting you know to
add like a bit of mystique like
get an american over there yeah oh
what's more mystique
um what if it was like a
french person that hosted the law you
can give gifts the sort of the
air of like we're in a game
that i am leading you you are
traitors like like on-coming yeah accent is
so it doesn't mean well if you're
just australian it's like oh so you're
just some guys don't live down the
street yeah it does take
away a little bit though like sort
of game play mystique there also in
the australian when they were in a
hotel instead of a castle and it's
a holiday and instead of
instead of although it does seem like
they actually stay there whereas yeah you
can tell usa yeah they never say
well in the usa when they don't
acknowledge that they don't stay there but
in the u k want it's like
okay the cars are taking you away
now you can't be here i guess
one thing that is not explained that
i wouldn't mind being explained as where
they go and how they're separated so
that they'd
never know who the traitor would you
like to know you know yes oh
okay sure they essentially stay at a
holiday express or whatever by the air
i hope it's not dying there there's
sequestered like jury style yeah and they
can't talk to talk to each other
so they bring them food and shit
but they can't see each other talk
to each other and like so i
guess it must be on different floors
and
you're not hearing a door slam at
eight pm or just so true you
don't hear yeah yeah yeah we killed
another one we are the traitors okay
we have to go we'll be right
back and this is very exciting we
have very exciting three oh he's a
time yes oh boy will be real
excited
hi we're back he's going first i'm
going fast so she can she can
wash can't you know because i can't
i can't walk yet cause i'm gonna
know what the flavors are we need
to okay so hey we're doing this
out of three gallon we're setting up
right now we're doing the pepsi challenge
paul was gracious enough to go buy
a market on the way home did
you
go on the way home paul e
and he picked up four different types
of cola including coke and pepsi now
if i may remind you a couple
of weeks ago
lauren we talked about the pepsi challenge
and lauren was incredulous thinking that anyone
could not know the taste of coke
i know and i'm getting scared now
of course she knows the taste of
coke like the back of her hand
she says but i haven't had it
my most recent sip was oh now
she's backing down a little but i
am saying my most recent simple is
at christmas and then i was like
i actually was
like everyone is drinking coke and i
was like i want one and then
it was so strong to me that
i actually backed off right okay so
now what we're doing is paula's porn
and paul do you want to say
with the brands are
yeah can i turn around no no
okay
but do you want to say with
brands
second get multi one thousand one one
thousand two we of course have coke
we have pepsi we also have boiling
earns ah can kill us and we
have ah fenton's curiosity sounds too much
like fentanyl random yeah don't tell what's
what's going to be called boy
islands that's a is that a market
i don't i don't know i've heard
of it but okay don't remember what
it was boiling bottling company so here's
the thing just we're gonna do we're
gonna first say which one we like
best out of the taste test challenge
that's the spirit of the pepsi challenge
the original pepsi challenge was just to
say which one you like best scott
your glasses are ready
i can turn around yes let me
know hopefully you cannot see writing under
there i cannot see okay good okay
so turn around charles way am i
gonna be able to see what his
answers are when he's getting wrong yes
yes okay just making sure that's okay
so we're gonna go me then paul
and lauren so we're gonna do two
things which we like best the spirit
of the pepsi challenge
and then which is coke okay we
don't have to identify the other ones
now okay i think that's fair we
can extra credited if we want but
okay alright so for the first glass
taking the sip interesting he finds it
interesting because caramel second glass
i'm gonna do a photo so we
can post oh gosh okay i won
got i'm a little bit wow
non-committal judgment
don't like that oh he doesn't like
it okay i have my answer okay
right which one is your favorite favorite
is this one okay and which coke
is this
do we tell him yes we do
yeah scott yes you did not guess
your favorite one correctly what do you
mean
oh shit your favorite it was boiling
cola yeah really and you identified coca
cola as pepsi cola was happy to
identify pepsi and coke that was pepsi
and which one did not like that
was that was a curiosity cola okay
so the first one was coke yeah
yeah okay yeah the oil is is
delish
this don't describe anything okay lauren your
next okay i can't wait i'm gonna
go turning away lawrence turning away this
is so exciting and now i get
people so exciting i'm really i'm just
i can't believe it yeah this is
this just can't be one of the
most exciting things we've ever done on
three ok and that's saying something
say we suck
because this sucks
yes one of the most exciting none
of us like it and i'm really
excited because i genuinely don't know what's
gonna happen right now i really don't
know yeah wow this is very exciting
paul is pouring right now tell me
when you're ready to go yeah it's
of course feeling we're just gonna
rice we're gonna finish and then just
never let you know the huge turn
around okay okay okay okay okay okay
there um we have one more lord
and then you'll be able to turn
around pulse pouring skills by the way
are exceptional he's not leaving a drop
on the table he's twisting the rim
thank you as you would when you're
powering wine got a twist them in
order to make to spill any drops
alright it's lauren you're ready okay don't
drink those tissues there in front of
one of the glasses oh she's like
cotton
okay okay alright going for the first
one
i'm so nervous
remember how confident you were that you
you knew you know show that he's
like fucking ass
that's horrible
oh she's tell she's palate cleansing rinse
with some water on curiosity i'm interested
you will see
okay she's takes the second one
i don't like that oh she didn't
like it okay didn't like it okay
she's trying to do better mean she's
doing why are again she's doing laundering
yeah i gotta be able to yeah
truly
cleanse to serious taking the sip of
number three
okay okay now number four is approaching
her life she's taking no water and
no do i am down now it
takes the water huh
she almost slipped up
i've got a few percent she's got
one hundred percent now to tell us
your favorite the spirit pepsi challenge my
favorite is this one okay okay this
one's coke okay we fucking nailed it
yes your favorite was obviously hey my
favorite quote unquote is pepsi because that's
the pepsi challenge that i'm supposed to
make that my favorite know people that
know your soul
just to say what your favorite is
to be honest about this so my
favorite when you're not trying to get
on camera like i was at magic
mountain that's right the pepsi challenge oh
what does your favorite whatever i guess
i'm right yeah but what does your
book because my favorite really okay she's
crying let me go back to the
well hold on
yeah i love the hokum okay i
got home alright lauren are you gonna
blame because either you're was right that
this was curiosity yeah yeah i got
them all right you've got them all
right yeah you did guys come on
i just replies but then you didn't
play it the way that we said
so right
alright alright mix those up for paul
so you know what to do i'm
going to look at my phone this
is some great phone time
you're leaving me to do the play-by-play
really you could really how can i
do the play by play you can
talk about i'm waiting for the thing
to happen what about talking about what's
outside the glass
well the glass
god that's funny when that scene is
so funny though though what's what's guys
a box because you know it was
like take a one hundred and twelve
yeah and he's just doing a different
just to do a different watson law
does that thank you mister fincher oh
yeah it does i'm gonna put that
one in don't please don't put
that way and everyone's gonna make fun
of me it's a good movie
rep is very dumb in that movie
yeah like a character used to play
dumb guys very well yeah it's not
really i mean i still does in
once upon a time in hollywood he's
pretty dumb i didn't think he was
dumb in that
thought it was just like a very
simple living person in a way right
to annoy me i do know what
you mean paul there's just no pretense
wow that's a heavy poor
yeah alright paul i believe we're ready
you made make sure that's obscured yes
very good hold on one second okay
very good very good alright okay ready
to turn around right guys
just in front of you we take
a picture because it's actually a better
angle for the picture yeah the color
is all is pretty consistent it is
honestly it's pretty confusing alright i'm gonna
go from left to right left to
right much like we read books in
america not japan
he's taking the sip of the first
one
took a healthy sip
he's testing a little bit on his
lips he says after the first one
now he does not have a palate
cleanser no no not everyone still forgot
to bring my bottle so he's going
straight to number two
took the sip of that nods to
himself as if apta knows exactly what
that is
he's taking a sip of the third
one
tasting it on his lips
to get off the cliffs looking seductively
wasting out ah yes which one it
is like cooking one finger and ain't
come here
come hither
he's taking his sip of the fourth
one and he grimaces that's curiosity okay
wait
i mean we all know hearing some
challenge that's other way is on the
curiosity challenge i just wanted to call
out but hell yeah we spirit of
the challenge that one's really got a
lot going on yeah in the spirit
of the pepsi challenge which is your
favorite i'm gonna i think wow
if you need to retake sips i
might need to retake retake some say
because i know i feel like i
know what these are and so these
i'm a little art okay re take
some sips he's taking a sip of
the first one
he thinks he well he pointed out
with the fourth one thing very seductive
on that one yeah but he's taking
a sip of one and three he
says he knows what two and four
are and let's get some guesses out
before he says his curiosity was my
favorite type and ah this one's pepsi
wow that's yours
yesterday away coke is not what pepsi
this one's cook your favorite that you
said is coke is pepsi the true
pepsi chow it has tea is coke
you got it right i got pepsi
channel you can change know i spoil
this is my favorite okay
this argument disappoint you know this one
is boiling but i didn't like it
as much you didn't like it i
thought it was like boy this curiosity
is why it's really bad was so
much going on i couldn't find r
c
yeah r c would have been a
good pepsi ah comparison yeah probably not
our c in a million you mean
either but i might never stand for
royal crown royal crown um or silicon
was a blast i have to say
it was fun i finished oil is
if you know of course yeah give
me the rest of that bot
stands for bottle stands for yeah shortfall
that was really fun how was really
fun so now lauren you know what
the pepsi challenge and i know that
i know the difference between coke and
pepsi and i was right and you
were right and you still like coke
which is surprising but pepsi was harder
for me than i thought to determine
the difference between you if this is
you did
truly what the advertisements were which is
you move pointed out and said this
is coke and this is my favorite
and then we revealed it's it's actually
and your favorite is pepsi you lying
but but and yet i know that's
not true yeah but you know what
i mean like you know what it
is because you didn't know what it
was and that was if it's love
is blind
it's truly a love is blind yeah
yeah cola love is blind love is
blind cola edition that's what this game
is yeah that's what they should call
the pepsi challenge on the day let
us join cola edition what is the
regular edition
now i can taste the difference now
that i know activity i can see
that day yeah interesting interesting you know
what i heard about coke and pepsi
was that they're the same company there
the same coffee yea of course that
whole thing is cool that's i think
there's a rumor about everything
they're the same company and they just
model is claiming to be one hundred
percent recyclable and it says recycle me
again again jesus christ you freak i
mean it seems like i do this
would you take over for sickly color
i'll make recycled myself getting nasty alright
well listen this is freedom that's how
it goes and thank you for listening
that was exciting i got to say
that it was really fun it was
i love when we we love stuff
like that yeah um but look if
you would like to send us a
creature that is not drinking sodas because
we just did that yeah then send
it to us we drink things you
don't email us something to drink no
don't email us drinks email at us
at ah three m usa gmail dot
com um and if you want to
leave us a voice mail go to
hag claims eight dot com yes the
number eight and leave us a voicemail
and we will answer all those in
our three new episodes which we put
out every other week yeah at cb
world as well as apple podcast premium
or something to that effect you can
also hear ad-free episodes at cb worlds
and ah on you know if if
you don't want to sign up for
cb world but you
wanna hear our old episodes we release
one a week that's on tuesday and
it has the elegant name of three
visiting on the tubes that's right what
else could you call it everybody loves
it but it is and we love
everybody and as always to play us
out here is just mckenna singing religious
generally should we always do oh singing
cna h jingle this is the scene
age sugar jingle h c and h
my mom used to make her cakes
it makes the greatest cookies snacks and
candy their dan dan dandy island kids
all love o'kane it grow so clean
and sweet they eat it when it's
freshly cut and then that's why
a tree meat touched by sun kiss
bahrain c h comes from the sugar
cane it makes the greatest cookie snacks
and candy the bright pink package