three
oh
ooh
oh oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
oh oh yea oh yeah welcome kuhlman
back to three-time it's christmas eve guys
it's christmas eve sanchez favorite nice guy
here sleep the
why's it santa's favorite and i do
because it's the one day he gets
off his fat ass and goes out
and works for a living whole lot
he's making the toys know he has
slave he's in the toy to make
choices you don't think he makes any
of the no he doesn't make the
choices view scottish saying this the one
eight of the year center works i
disagree i think he does work
take all your loss i mean maybe
no supervisor he's walking around he's checking
he's a he's checking lists he's checking
the per the progress of toys i
think he does all that on christmas
eve i think he does all the
list stuff like running down the naughty
and nice stuff he does it all
on christmas eve and so the other
three hundred and sixty four days a
year he just coasts he can't do
he can't run down the
list on christmas eve he's gotta to
deliver the program if he doesn't tell
me nighttime he doesn't do it til
nighttime the presence are just so he
takes he takes the presence from a
large pool of presence that already exist
and he goes okay who's naughty or
nice today today and he like looks
through it all and science presence for
the bullet present this is absurd you
think
santa is just making random shit yeah
because they're all kids just want the
same stuff play stations or whatever wouldn't
you horse there were kids who actually
got a piece of coal and that's
it yeah i think i think that's
been done and it's paradise there's a
shitty parents have been around forever i
wonder if there's like a jimmy kimmel
prank thing like the halloween thing where
like someone unwrapped gifts and it was
just a lump of coal and they
said what's this those videos with kids
make me feel weird because the kids
are like that's okay i love you
yeah i would never have i don't
know what videos you're talking about jimmy
kimmel will guess yes
fair enough alright so it's like either
way like three of them i'm scott
i'm paul
hi
if you can't deduce it from there
if you haven't okay here hear the
names from scott and paul and your
auto detect business
i think someone's turning this on having
no idea what's going every episode of
someone's first alright i'm lauren
i think that from the context clues
that have been given that jimmy kim
will do videos where ah ah an
adult gives a child a gift and
the gift is intentionally shitty and then
the child has to reassure the adult
no no but you're not not too
far off so it's wrong hall it's
a
halloween praying oh you were just like
oh well yeah telling tom okay where
is the adult gives bad candy and
then the child has turned out not
quite
keep passing
the adult pretends not to know what
the child was dressed as can i
can i give you another hint yeah
these are videos filmed on november first
the videos where the adults pretend that
they've eaten all the candy yeah pretty
much we'll give him that right judges
will get that or they threw away
the candy yep
and then they usually say i ate
it all okay and then so the
child is upset but then they does
the adult pretend to be very remorseful
i don't know if that makes bag
with like how the parent acts sometimes
i guess the parents are like times
i'm sorry but all this candy was
here tonight the kids are upset but
a lot of times the kids are
like that's
okay and they're kind of sad and
i'm like okay and it's really sad
i don't like that at all you
know and then they're like just kidding
and then it's like okay and it's
like just why are we going on
this roller coaster to slip another fucking
candy well does it make you feel
better paul to know that jimmy said
he doesn't want to do it anymore
and
because it's too mean yeah and that
people still were sending him
these videos this year he was like
hey i have an for these i
don't want to do these anymore but
a bunch of people sent them so
here they know buddy show
on jimmy jimmy jam hey show them
what did he have didn't he have
like ah like a sort of yeah
he had something where it was like
almost like a visit to santa claus
but there was a michael myers guy
oh that's interesting side and so kids
went in and it's like and it
was oh inside like santa's village or
something yeah but i think
it was i think it was around
halloween time so it wasn't like oh
you're gonna see santa and then it's
michael myers in there because that would
be awesome
that would be the scariest thing ever
but like there would be over there
were just videos of people walking into
this room seeing him sitting there yeah
it was like visit michael myers like
you're gonna visit santa and he's sitting
on a chair that's amazing and so
people would walk in they'd see him
and then michael myers would like stand
up out of the chair but people
just run
adults and kids or i feel like
it was adult and kids i love
it like that just leading people into
like sit on michael laughing let him
know what you want for it oh
yeah to me to keep referring to
kids as people even though i know
they are but like and all these
kids are people too but i think
it was kids and adults yeah but
um yeah i don't
think it's like a great prank to
fool the most easily fooled people yeah
yeah four year old eating what are
good prank yeah you don't know what
the world is i'm telling you i
was getting paul do you do you
like any pranks what's a good prank
the the first thing i think of
is and it's not a good prank
it's terrible because i knew this prank
that i pulled on my lovely wife
that i knew would have the exact
reaction that it got and you feel
bad
oh wasn't i bought we don't have
any pets
everyone's around what is that now that's
an airplane that's an airplane different totally
different time we don't have an airplane
we don't have anything no software playing
sorry yeah sorry it's not loud enough
but i do see a helicopter do
you really i say one too yeah
but it is not loud enough
it sounded like an airplane to me
yeah but maybe i don't know who
knows well we missed our boat oh
and there goes a plane or a
bird honestly i don't know and i
just superman
it's a plane
wow this guy is murdered to play
superman oh it's opposed right it was
a play that old man plays to
superman's real um we don't have any
pets every once in a while ah
janie will make noises about getting a
dog yeah and then for
our fault yeah and i'm like i
get what you're doing um no but
then that discussion is squashed ah because
neither of us wants to we would
like to have a dog we don't
want to take care of a dog
yeah what are what what do you
think what what would what are the
impediments to taking care of it well
now we've talked about this before and
the biggest phenom
but for me it's shit
yeah you both told me how you
now you love your dog shits and
how well you know the other day
just we have today we have two
dogs and i bar i'd take him
out in the morning and i and
i let them do their business and
i clean it up and they took
so long in between their shits that
i realised i'd been holding the other
ones
shit for five minutes in my hand
and i just laid in your punk
music hey go eat a bag but
i was just like you know is
there is there something to the fact
that usually it's just a like purely
a three second thing where you will
you you are grabbing shit and then
it's in a bag and you're fine
and you know but at this point
it was just like five minutes i
have just lumped shit man yeah much
like those lumps of coal that's right
from shitty parents um so i bought
a because you know i'm a i'm
a fan of turtles and tortoises okay
and i bought an extremely lifelike tortoise
going to have you on the turtles
probe
i've been on it oh that's right
i've had an extremely life like tortoise
sculpture that i put in the yard
and it looks like we have a
big fuckin glock galapagos tortoise wow like
ah like this big i'm holding my
hands out it's like this big yeah
wow yeah and it's it looks great
and so i bought it and she
laughed at me which i
i absolutely expected to deserve not with
you
we were laughing together but she was
she was laughing like i was ridiculous
and yet and she was right and
i shouldn't say it if she we
we don't have that we don't have
like a sitcom relationships
well you're a great person you're gonna
need yet i don't think i'm going
to eat you no matter what simply
false you could be both okay name
one person who is an idiot was
also the great idiots of our time
lennie from mice and men you know
what wright thinks sounds great person than
an idiot
um and so i bought this thing
and then we put in the yard
and then i at one point
i moved it so it was on
the back deck of our house and
i knew that she would walk into
that room and see it
and i heard her yell and it
was satisfying and also immediately i felt
guilty yeah yeah did i tell it
okay so pranks on our significant others
so what club gets very scared and
there was a period of time where
she liked going to haunted house ra
for universal studios
but there was one halloween period where
i said oh we're going out tonight
it's a surprise and tell us the
story and the surprise was ah yeah
yeah so then after that well the
surprise was we were going to a
haunted house and it's one of the
few times she ever got like credibly
mad at me and left didn't go
with us and um it was a
problem and she's still bring
okay but then
huh when we went to ah
this is twenty years
oh but then so then when we
went to
mexico would tell john one year just
you and him ah no is cool
up ah nora and some other people
who shall remain nameless smothers brothers the
smash brothers yes
want to protect their identity smother people
who show room yes they're in the
witness protection program and i don't want
to blow up their spot and get
the murdered henry hill yes and henry
higgins weirdly enough ever since i was
a kid i always wanted to go
to mexico to tell john ah yes
you will from the bureau of that's
me
i'm doing henry higgins short talking to
henry hill um so we went to
mexico and we stepped off the plane
and then we all got in this
shuttle that was going to take us
to the property and um we stopped
at a and by the way isn't
it great that when you get to
mexico like they and their you're in
a shuttle going to a property they
like go yeah
here's some harder label here's a margarita
are here like yeah yeah yeah then
i've never been a you never been
to mexico in mha we should go
once but it was for a job
i didn't really have that experience drug
meal yeah
so anyway but it's great that they
let you drink yeah maybe it's not
legal i don't know but it feels
legal um what's something that's not legal
but feels like i cannot handle those
tweets anymore
they'll be gone by the time this
comes in i hope so god damn
i hope so people are still doing
wrong answers only like hey wrong answers
only i'm like they're only are wrong
answers when you make up a fake
question what's the it's so it's not
funny yeah well i know i damn
sure i'm somebody stupid and like what's
this album called wrong answer
is only taking yeah there is no
right answer why don't i just write
whatever the fuck we want yeah i
did one that was like what's the
square root of eighty one wrong answers
only or what's not the square root
of eighty one wrong answers only people
were like nine nine nine they didn't
get it anyway
i'm not the square root of eighty
one wrong answers no i don't know
what it was i can't remember but
i remember everyone betting me right now
everyone giving me right and nine is
the only way to answer that oh
no i think i think i was
saying what's not and then people were
like a fruit and i was like
no that's not not anyway
um so we go to mexico of
fru we go to mexico and we
get we're getting in the van the
van goes hey do you want anything
from the liquor store you want van
could talk savannah's like oh yeah it
was related from two kids if you
can believe in what it was like
kids uncle it is just a shuttle
for airport yeah it loves it what
a waste of tech
well it's hard bang yo the wii
u no relation of a celebrity do
you know what kid is kit gotta
get that car from um hold on
i do i do now he just
got married to me that's right thanks
um so we get into then and
they go there they stop
op at the liquor store and they
go hey do you want anything and
tell john's like oh yeah let's get
a twelve pack for the ride and
all this kinda stuff so but we're
already a couple margarita is in in
the liquor store yeah in the liquor
store i see the half like ah
and this is a halloween devil mask
and i'm like is it even close
to halloween it probably was now that
i think about i think it was
it was in october so um and
it's a rubber mask i'm like oh
like over your whole head that kind
of mass yeah yeah or at least
the front half i'm not sure your
face
you know that front part isn't
his eyes and half of your head
so i buy it thinking hunched in
the front half of kid
i'm going to put makeup on the
front half of my head
if you put up on the back
of your head every day
so i mean like really peculiar
okay so i bite us matches i
yeah from the books i've known that's
a name that i recognize i've never
really been clear on the bible until
you understand idioms so she'll be like
ah amelia don't let the cat out
of the bag and shake some hello
real cat outta the bag or are
there like amelia can you um
you know like so she's like ah
drax from guard like dressy dress the
dress sounds like a rip-off yes the
turkey and then she puts it in
a dress is this her whole thing
yes you
a series of books that pissed me
off as a kid i was like
can someone just slow down and explain
to her i found stuff like that
frustrating too i didn't it wasn't funny
to me yeah well that's cool i've
pointed up she's been watching these dumb
christmas romantic comedies on netflix she pointed
out that bringing back to christmas she
pointed out that these movies would all
be over
within two minutes oh my gosh someone
just said like hey by the way
i like you yeah basically yeah yeah
yeah yeah did you watch midnight at
the magnolia i didn't watch any of
the guy and i was really fascinated
by this film and i looked on
m de bay and saw on the
right
owner of this movie has written like
fifteen christmas movies and i was like
this and that's it yeah and i
was like this is fascinating this is
a yeah it's a genre yeah that's
always good what's another thing happen at
christmas what's another thing so i watched
we watched the trailer to one it
was like these two who have a
radio show who gets that that's what
it was and there i am in
the trailer
for that trailer is chicago it's the
most canadian thing ever i can't stand
and they're in a large large room
like a box without any like sound
dampening stuff and they're supposedly on the
radio and they're like old family friends
as i would yeah and then they
basically decide they both have a boyfriend
and girlfriend they side they're gonna introduce
their boyfriend girlfriend to their fb
families on the air for this christmas
thing to like get the syndication thing
or something oh yeah and then they
they both get broken up with and
then they realize okay fine let's just
pretend we're together and then they really
have feelings for guy and that and
the fam i mean the movie is
i mean fascinating i romantic comedies is
like the stakes
of other movies are like oh is
the earth going to be blown up
by an asteroid and then romantic comedies
are basically like are these two people
out of the billions of people going
to kiss and the answer is yes
because it's a romantic comedy if they
give should be well i like it
i think romantic shakes of a romantic
comedy would we're like okay
how many people are in the world
eight billion something like that if a
hundreds if four billion people were in
kiss the other four billion people at
the same time then the stakes are
like you it'll be really weird that's
an interesting premise for a movie but
why i don't think that's changing is
more interesting than people kissing her nah
hey tattoo
i have to divide the population and
give the kissy just the same size
for charity the thing that bugs me
about romantic comedies is the that the
what is it the third act where
they have to be a part for
summary yeah where there's a finally get
to where there's misunderstanding and then yeah
it's like you lie to me yeah
and then they're mad for a week
or whatever and then and then the
person catches up with them yeah i'm
sa
sorry i lied i did it because
i like you too much wow what
does that do you as as a
fan of rom-coms do you like that
part is that satisfying to have that
included i think it ok for f
i'm thinking of like a great one
like you've got mail which i just
rewatched um it's great because they they
get there's the anger there's
the upset there's everything and then the
reveal and that one's really good because
she still doesn't know that the person
she's been ran into was him the
whole time she's mad at him and
the whole thing but then it's him
and she's like i'm glad it's him
and it's this that's a really i
find it unbelievable to tom hanks would
be friends with dave chappelle that is
unbelievable
you know that's the worst part of
that movie isn't there a treadmill in
that movie yeah they're on it yeah
just don't buy a treadmill and they
talk to each other on a treadmill
i just don't buy it so you
don't think that they would be friends
and i don't think that they would
be on treadmills well i think they
weren't together
so it's it makes it a little
less random
random so i buy this halloween mask
thinking i got thinking oh my gosh
this will be really funny i'll one
night in mexico slayer and next scary
cool da bao bao and so i
i buy it and i stick it
in my pocket thinking oh i'll i'll
break this
out at an opportune time and scary
knowing knowing how she doesn't like to
be scared and then by the time
we get to the property i'm like
what the fuck am i doing this
we're on vacation i'm not gonna scare
cool up with a halloween air toll
jong yeah what a horrible terrible idea
so i just kept it in my
pocket and then i hit it once
we got back to the states i
hid it in a closet
impacted yes why not just throw it
away i don't know and i hit
it in a closet thinking well maybe
i'll need it for something and then
finally when we moved a year ago
i was like some just to throw
this away i've been holding onto this
you know i never told her and
don't you tagger i'm gonna snitch
yeah cool
you're six here right now i stop
him i have to use the restroom
but can you guys just keep talking
no we're gonna take a break oh
yeah we're gonna take a break we'll
be right back
alright we're back come back in and
christmas eve is upon us and ah
you know what that means tomorrow's christmas
that and you know what that means
that after that is boxing day boxing
die and you know that mean he's
boxing guy sale sale sale
boxing gloves galore red friday what red
wedding i've ever shopped on black friday
no i you know hey nae nae
they they they get you by saying
like oh we got a tv for
three dollars i'm using exaggeration for comic
effect
yeah thank you and they've only got
one of those in the first person
in line gets it and then you're
like well i gotta buy something so
you spend eight thousand dollars on a
tv instead i'm again exaggerating for comic
effect i haven't shopped on black friday
but i have taken part in many
black friday stampedes where sure i will
wait in line it's like the running
of
the bowls ever since you absolutely couldn't
go to pamplona that one year i'll
wait around for fourteen hours to so
i can be the first crawl under
that metal gate yes guys didn't just
stamp over people you imagine when when
i see people doing that i just
and by the way here's a here's
a helicopter when i see people doing
that i'm like are they doing it
truly because they don't have a lot
of money or is it just because
it's like they want to game the
system somehow and they want to have
done it or you know what i
mean i would imagine it's both it's
that you know they're offering these high
ticket items for these deals that they
only do once a year and you
know people see it as
is there shot there's also people i
think that are buying the song never
turned on this fight and people are
buying shit to sell as well because
it's going to be in high supply
i have gone to black friday couple
of times a used to know somebody
who enjoyed going to that really i
mean it's kinda like a game joy
dance so it was a game
in a way it was a game
and it was like a four am
three am getting line kind of city
which you know having spent the night
like for concert tickets or whatever it's
like that can be fun or whatever
it was interesting for done anything like
i got the full bugs from cleanest
city know what's it like it's fun
i mean i don't know do you
like dreams and don't know what
that is oh fleetwood mac sang about
o launcher three candidates commercial glad that
that guy is getting somewhat he's in
a snoop dogg commercial it's really fun
yeah well you look at his twitter
and it's ah his agent is is
what his twitter bio is now well
good because yeah i didn't like how
everyone did their version and then i
feel like he was getting
erased well i mean to be fair
ocean spray did try to take care
of him and bottom a truck yeah
because he does but i feel like
we talked about this on previous movie
so i think we can stay think
companies saying jack shit are these crocs
getting hot or you're crossing just me
to me like the heat up more
than a regular shoe yeah because they're
a little furry right i feel like
my feet are on fires every weight
show us what you got show was
what she got fucking not knowing the
schering ice charles i have dual crocs
comfort there they have like fur fur
and i think i need that for
my narrow foot they're good they're very
comfortable but my feet
now are high so my foot too
narrow i need fur yours look plastic
there's just my issue with they're made
of the same material they just don't
have fur inside what is what are
they feel like without fur because the
fur ones are very they feel like
hard plastic scott you are right from
the beginning it's not plastic or it
is i don't know
i can't deal with moving every time
the sun moves we gotta figure out
something well you guys can come earlier
well what i'm going to be here
at eight am doing as you imagine
i can't imagine black friday i mean
i guess i guess i could do
that and just get it over with
if if if you
like sitting in a more comfortable chair
that was easier to like scoot backwards
that could also ah um but in
any case paul you're good we're all
i'm a good person you're an idiot
though i like me my wife likes
me how about the song and let's
see if you know who sins
this
and the moneda and now amoeba friend
yes i am jade i'm jonathan josey
no it's not joe to see come
on joe to see do you want
to know a hint
your hint is it's joe to see
then yes no it's from a comedian's
music album oh yeah jimmy fallon yes
oh so listen to it all the
time really when i was a child
great and i really liked it and
someone recently tweeted about it and i
was thinking that was funny there was
funny i gotta admit you know you
did a whole thing and that was
it it was like troll dolls auditioning
i'm out
i was
all those famous impressions like it is
like sting kerr chris rock i don't
know wait why were they but this
is all audio why were they trying
i don't know and i gotta remember
that who cares paul christmas memories laddie
saved his finger pie full christmas memory
by the time i got for chris
was this weird command
in time for christmas i got a
new cd player and a bunch of
cds and it was awesome what cds
you remember the jimmy galloway matthews and
ah you too which you to um
i don't know i just got like
a ton of like a youtube tribute
to dave matthews classic cow bombs you
know and it was really exciting and
i was saying you hadn't
had a cd player i have a
pi had had a shitty one and
my parents got me like a stereo
and then they bought me my brother
we each got a stereo and we
got a bunch of cds and that
was our main present so were you
let me guess how old you were
thirty two da doo dah i was
probably so you owe fourteen okay so
i'm i'm in the
ballpark yeah um paul is now leaving
the chat room i really used to
love you're leaving right
oh he's he's trying he's trying to
move lawrence umbrella i really used to
love sitting in my room and listening
to me closer to her oh this
is going great you go thanks so
used to love sitting in your room
and listening to music yeah i know
it's not unique but i don't do
that anymore my tastes are unconvincing i
don't think guys
it's like that was such a cool
i don't do anymore i sit in
my office and do it i sit
on my toilet and do it
i the other day was listening to
a couple albums that i i um
that just recently came out what do
you listen to i listened to um
material flats tony newsome and bethany thomas
and i listened to the latest fiscal
maps open notes what i said and
i listened to the latest open mikey
o anime trauma and divorce and i
listen to them both a few times
through which i hadn't done in a
while and i was just in a
mood where i wanted to listen to
music and it was really enjoyable i
hadn't done that in such a long
yeah amazing it's rare to just sit
there and listen to the whole album
from i mean i always like doing
things that's why album and i had
the albums i think
last time i was like i put
on an album and just sat at
my desk and listen to a full
album because i was like really intrigued
by it and this might sound dumb
or weird is going to be the
jimmy fallon
and like taking notes in the troll
dolls sting
i yeah it was like all these
people auditioning ah to sing the trolls
song or something but they were singing
it as he was saying different impress
stop i was a kid what the
fuck do you just stop talking about
it now when your adult can answer
um was ryan adams covering taylor swift's
oh the disgraced ryan adam i know
i don't like but i really loved
the sound of that and i was
really out there i was like wow
i haven't sat here and like listen
to album well this is why albums
should only be like thirty five to
forty minutes because everyone like runs out
of time after that you know there's
all
these those songs you never get to
yeah you're just like okay and i
started over because i liked those in
the beginning i don't know if i
liked the later ones i'm not gonna
risk it every time i'm driving i
just you know risk it for the
biscuit why would i exact only for
limping i did it all day this
is fred durst would you risk it
for the biscuit ivies
holiday season durst merry christmas and happy
hanukkah high five questions this is fred
durst it around
merry christmas and happy hanukkah i have
a question for you one two three
would you risk it for the best
guess
ah god now i want him to
do this fred if you're listening would
you just put out a video of
you wanna just that there's so no
follow up on the website to go
to my risky somebody really famous who
listens to this ah hussein obama
i mean i think ah our friends
ah bannon ione oh yeah the guy
guy guy never met you i only
but ah ben i had on a
different shoes you know oh she's a
lovely person i may not be pronouncing
your name right oh yeah i'm good
okay great i was supposed to have
quarantine drinks at their house
and then it never happen because i'm
going to australia ah what would that
entail like how could you drink through
a mask well i guess if germs
can get through a mass sitting far
rings so can booze sitting for our
part like we are now yeah ah
but you know what i will say
i've barely done that this whole time
yeah i have barely had any we
had one over here brunch but in
our ne
neighborhood what do you mean like people
who live nearby yes yeah yeah cool
i've had a jacuzzi party yesterday with
two other deja vu all wearing masks
the entire time and a jacuzzi yeah
you know about that feels hot the
mask part of the jacuzzi the jacuzzi
huh well that's how you get into
a temperature you
like and that's usually how to choose
and i just feel like i have
a sort of i'm in this mindset
of like i wanna just wait for
everything to be fine yeah sounds depressing
maybe wow am i doing enough things
that yeah oh and and even just
i went back to work last week
which by the way it was like
extremely draining um because i was working
and it was just like is a
whole thing with the protocol the covert
protocol on a set we talked about
it on our first we have talked
about it but i hadn't experienced it
yet and i found that it was
very exhausting and a different way than
it typically is and i just felt
like kind of just want everything to
be fucking normal
and well to a point of which
i've been at every month and every
day but like it's just reaching like
another point of like oh my god
i just want this i do feel
like even if there's a vaccine even
if that the vaccine come soon and
everything works out i still feel like
i will wear a mask on a
plane well i feel like no situational
people were saying like
you know lauren you know this when
you go to japan good lauren oh
no this everyone like western jail somewhere
a mass probably half the people on
every subways yeah masks right yeah and
like that they think that we'll get
there in the united states of like
okay yeah even if a vaccine is
ninety percent
effective still like why don't we now
that we've normalized masks why don't you
why don't we wear them when we're
absolutely worked on me like i used
to see when i would see people
that were wearing masks i didn't quite
before all this happened i was like
i don't quite get that yeah why
that is a cultural thing and now
i did well it's yeah i mean
in japan it was like i was
kinda like well there's there's not a
pandemic going on why are they wearing
masks and i looked it up and
it was just like once they got
normalized people just yeah figured like why
not why if you have a coin
yeah yeah essentially all these fucking masks
yes but i was reading about the
fashion model who were the mask as
well and like because she
i was hiding her face they were
all intrigued like what's behind that mask
and she got famous because she was
run over face yes from the front
half of her head
and she became famous for that and
then she revealed it and she was
like oh yeah oh oh equally gooey
what we were making face also i
don't know what you're talking about the
fashion model who wore a mammy while
i was trying to thank you i
was trying to say it is few
words without being interrupted and so maybe
something got lost
hi okay baby
a story to be from the beginnings
and endings need to be cut off
why are you fighting against what's natural
you're right
but what was this what i don't
know what to know there's a there's
a japanese fashion model really
jesus you know what i like about
fashion models yeah the japanese paul christmas
memories any random one we haven't talked
about what's something you got
out of your ass what's what's something
you enjoy dany do on christmas you
janie you do well we always would
go to south carolina to be with
gee yeah mama i mentioned something unless
you have more to talk about with
i think she's going no that was
great
you're gonna trail i was gonna know
i was gonna try i planned on
trailing off i didn't mention a couplet
i was not going to mention something
although i knew i was gonna mention
something you do oh shit which is
ah the nicholas nickleby which we came
over to yes yes yes yes say
this is this is a little download
traditional and the download that i
have because you want to share are
you scared no i'll share you with
howard it's not i am a coward
but unrelated unrelated you're an idiot a
coward but our thirty's a good purse
good person ah um i my favorite
piece of entertainment art whatever you wanna
call it that's
ever existed is the royal shakespeare company's
nineteen eighty two production of the life
and adventures of nicholas nickleby by charles
dickens it is an all day play
it's eight hours and only went to
see that all day playing yeah we
started like a six hour place which
was the never happen again his call
old havana actually i'm accessing files no
brain files sets than i not the
institute what was it it was great
it was just nominated right people it
was based on howards end i can
look but didn't close down well everything
i know but i mean before that
i think i think it like weirdly
stopped early know why can't we think
of the name of it i'm
dying that i can't think of it
i know it they said it throughout
the play they say the title i
sat there for six hours and then
they're like about it hey months we're
in the okay i'm i'm looking at
it but go go on but but
did i tell you by the way
that i saw it when i was
maybe twelve when winter to come out
eighty two issues so i saw
i might my father occasionally would do
something where he'd be like stop watching
happy days or whatever turn on something
good and i remember once was mutiny
on the bounty and each time i
liked it each time like i liked
when i returned it on but i
remember he was like turn on pbx
instead and and nicholas nickleby was on
and i think i came into it
like twenty minutes later whatever
her and was immediately enraptured and deny
her inheritance and did not realize it
was an eight hours it's life like
when you go into nicholas nickleby not
knowing how long it is it's like
this is still going on she was
a grandma with a big long beard
um i the isis inheritance was great
ice it was great i saw nick
zinc will be on tv when it
when they put it on tv and
when pbx put it on and i've
loved it ever since and then i
bought a i bought it on disc
four disc set in the late nineties
or something wow and then of a
few years ago i started this
i know it was not meant to
be a tradition but it became a
tradition where i said i'm going to
watch this this is gonna be a
whole day and i invited a couple
of people over that i thought would
be that this would be up their
alley and it turns out it was
not up the alley of all of
them there were only two people that
stayed and so then we
stay the whole time did we know
that but you are not the first
year okay then so i would try
different people there were there were two
people that went ev that would go
every year and watch the entire thing
which to me was weird because in
my mind i was like well i
would i don't i'm not opposed to
doing this every year but i would
imagine it would be new people right
yeah do
it um because why i it never
occurred to me that there would be
other people who would want to watch
it in it's entirety every year right
so you thought people would come and
go or it'd be different people every
single year they're just different people but
they watch the whole thing yeah they
watched her we'd spend the day together
like i said this is what we're
doing this is what it is or
was
in the entire thing from start to
finish we're not saying we're not really
taking breaks like image will have food
in between the the discs you can
you know well i've obviously you can
get up and get something while it's
happening you can only get up when
the disc changes
yeah go to the bathroom hold it
look this is my idea of fun
it has a lot of strict rules
um and so yeah so i've been
doing it for i think five years
now something like that ah and it's
it's really i love it this year
it'll just be this year i don't
know if i'm going to do it
because it would just be me and
janie yeah so i don't know if
it really and how does cheney feel
about it each year
she likes it she always she falls
asleep in a different part each year
i think the year we were there
i fell asleep and some point i
can't remember what which i look we
have a fire going there's a fire
there's drinks yeah it's an exhausting time
a year and i'm and i'm like
prime nicholson and i'm a guy who
loved it when it came out absent
i still know so
utility man you love because you said
your passion is hurting oh i think
i probably knowing me just put time
and put the decorations up it's gonna
feel christmassy yes yea right well another
christmas tradition that we started last year
that we won't get to do this
year was going to the primary family
and amersham tammy
gender and lauren you were with sarah
but i thought i'd be there this
year but here we go ah and
and it was great last year we
there were only eight of us there's
a group of ten of us who
do things together and there were only
eight of us because lauren and mike
couldn't be there but um it's this
wonderful prime rib restaurant and they have
carolers wandering throughout and they take ri
requests and we ever it was all
these old like hymns almost for christmas
songs they were singing and and i
think what based on the request yes
based on the request but we were
like let's just this place up a
little bit but wasn't jessica who was
like ds do you know mariah carey's
all i want for christmas zoo and
they were thrilled oh yeah finally
got to sing it and they did
it and i didn't know whenever asked
so i'm gonna do some they didn't
incredible acapella version of it and the
soloist was amazing it was so much
fun and jessica was loving yes it
was loving and we were all loving
it and it's so fun and and
i've been looking forward to it ever
since then yeah we're not gonna be
able to do it but that's you
no let's stay safe you know i
end up going to that restaurant at
christmas time i typically end up going
to that restaurant several times sounds great
with because i have various traditions i
ah my friend scott carter and i
um have been going there for dark
carter what that's a jazzy song alright
and we have been doing that for
years
then i started going with super ego
my friends super ego we started like
a placebo
look you got me i think you
have to admit it hey guy that
would beg you and then we started
a new tradition which immediately was snuffed
out yeah and and then i'll just
go there with other various friends i
love it me and jessica share that
where we will go multiple times yeah
throughout that throughout the season well that's
you know that was ah my my
other christmas tradition that i'm bummed about
and i thought of it the other
day i was like oh man is
and it sounds so stupid but it's
going to eataly like i can't wait
it's it's going to eataly
better than i thought pity mall and
then i'm going when you get ah
we got a pizza it's not even
about what we get i just love
christmas been wandering around reddit wondering around
that mall and eataly yeah in particular
with like all the market elements over
the sand sits and and and then
we go to the amc theater
next door and see whatever is in
the the big loud theater ah and
it's been the one where you can
yell
it's usually rocky horror picture show it's
like a mommy and me with no
kids just writing but um screening the
lights are all up one year it
was spider verse last year's star wars
which is really bad but um but
ah sorry ah and
my favorites apologizing doors says such as
but that's just like a fun and
and we we we did it the
first year because we'd always wanted to
go to italy but it was from
from our place to century city the
traffic is really bad but not right
before christmas and so it was like
boom were there in twenty
minutes it was amazing and so we
said let's do this every year right
before christmas we're not going to be
able to do it nope
and i've never waiving all now scroll
oh good not been in chicago for
christmas i i've ever spent one year
wow this is your first non chicana
hammersmith so um wow laura i'm sorry
yeah it sucks wow thanks yeah well
beyond zoom with beyond zoom lane do
you and mike have your own christmas
traditions
well they all take place in chicago
because he's from there too so his
you go to sears tower we gonna
see power we kiss friend john hancock
going to bean um we just have
the cheers bar family traditions with both
of our families we've done a couple
things like that over the years and
you know it's just um it's just
different this year yeah and i guess
we can get through it we can
go through it can get through at
my my mom was like it's just
a day and i you know if
it came to it next year i
can travel i would celebrate christmas in
july you think i wouldn't go hell
yeah go to australia someone write right
there do it on netflix
my it just seems like a thing
it'll be on netflix well that could
be my next um mike my next
movie on my mtb of one hundred
christmas movies that i've written yeah christmas
in july it's a way kinnaur style
celebrating the fact that netflix looked at
the hallmark channel and like you know
what fuck you what cars do they
buy
start doing by like because they they
feel like hallmark movies absolutely yeah and
by the formula hype is that died
from some like i don't understand what
is happening i thought they were running
hallmark movies on netflix yeah and i
think they're just making their own thing
they're making them for two dollars yeah
because i and it shows yeah
it's all there the screen
i mean i'm i'll watch it i'll
watch anything christmas while are you guys
getting presence for your significant other i
haven't i mean yes i will but
i haven't been thinking about it feels
like five is a little yeah and
usually this we needed like i'm like
wow and thinking about it an orange
off and sending it and blah blah
blah
and i haven't done a single thing
i haven't done it yet but i'm
going to i don't know what i
don't have any ideas and i don't
have any ideas either i'm any ideas
and i feel like what does anyone
want right now i'm realising i had
an idea oh no okay remember okay
but like i like to sometimes it's
like oh well i'll pick quick one
for like my aunts and uncles i'll
get
them all one thing wow and get
like a verb different version for each
person do you get do you get
them a card that says from your
nice no merry christmas do you get
like relationships specific cards for people like
my wife grandma to your grandma you're
the best grandma yeah wow from a
loving niece it says yo
or the best grandma
dubai inside it's blank
this is from your niece
well let's start selling these this let's
put these on the market this look
i know i'm freedom cards and i'm
just doing wonderful grandma from sweden tell
you your great grandma i know i
know i'm not your my aunt my
grandma i don't
sure by all accounts your credit should
stop me from telling you because it's
my relationship to you i witness it
and i see you are a wonderful
grandma i like a card that says
by all accounts
word on the street is i have
no reason to believe otherwise you are
a wonderful grandma alright we need to
take a break we'll be right back
with a reacher
we're back san and just over yeah
that's okay you should why should this
be any weird thing to say on
the show
talk to everyone you're welcome for that
that's the one part that's sacred yes
i need total silence for this um
you know it is christmas eve and
ah we decided to bring a game
back a three-tier back from last year
and i think it's one of the
only three that has a theme song
that's right shall we sing it ah
yeah
yes but i don't remember it here
it comes first mission to find out
who game christmas find out who game
christmas my guy who gave christmas game
um why this is why are solely
the christmas right out who gave him
theme how dare they've heard to have
to that suh
so this is this is a get
to know you type reacher where really
telling we're gonna ask these christmas syp
christmas themed questions questions saying who amongst
us is is without sin
and we decide and then we throw
stones at the person person gets stoned
um no we ask these these christmas
theme correct questions and we all tried
to decide out of the three of
us christians make sense for christmas president
crash yes we tried to decide as
the three of us who is the
most likely to be that person and
we're all gonna write down and you
don't
i mean by that person that person
so well and we all honest who
is most likely to be that ho
over there
not so ah you pronounce it taught
you pronounce it taught not thought it's
to hot it's too hot to hot
tea hot it is be sure to
see that from now on i'm taught
um alright so so we all have
our notes apps out and we are
going to write these down i'm titled
in my christmas blimey capacities apologies okay
all your notes you've written to post
yeah just in case things from the
come up with this shit is gonna
come out eventually sure um all right
are we ready for question number one
no yes
i'm gonna say it anyway as dead
air is sorry there's some entered of
the podcast yeah you could say other
things to thank you for just say
it what there's a weird one ah
somehow the weird table got added into
my note table yes what does that
mean
mean you know like a table in
a document
no dining room table no that's what
i mean
someone's one oh my girl dining table
might note time you read the question
before i go absolutely batshit alright who
amongst us has never had a white
christmas
go on
paul are you ready yeah bitch she's
so unready for a long time i
know right who around who has celebrated
christmas in another country
okay
okay who has returned a gift she
or he received last christmas
okay who has seen a real live
reindeer
who has seen a real live rain
question about this game yep
is it good it's unrelated to any
of these questions but are we including
ourselves yes okay so lauren has seen
a real live reindeer i'm gonna change
my answer
yeah it was unrelated to any of
these really was yeah yeah okay huh
but for some reason the very last
question prompted me to ask
who believed in santa claus until she
or he was ten years old
question six who has oh and we
know the answer to this who has
all of his or her christmas shopping
done
we all previously just said we hadn't
even started
who has been to bethlehem
question eight who went christmas carolyn last
year
question nine who has peaked and they
spelled wrong who has peaked at a
present who is piqued first of all
peaked at present know who who's who's
just p p a k e d
at a present um know who's peaked
at a present before christmas
and question ten who still hits home
on a second i only have eight
that's a problem um but there were
two where i thought nobody would have
it and so you just say nobody
wait a minute now i'm all fucked
up yeah alright well which one did
you mean oh no
what keys read the tenth one and
then when you read the questions you'll
you'll remember what's next like a tenth
is who still gets their own stocking
filled each year ooh la la
okay alright
we are going to go back to
question number one paul this is who
never had a white christmas who has
never had a white christmas did you
answer that one i did answer that
but she would just go through and
then i'll catch up yeah yeah okay
so and all it's all answer first
so that it's ok i'm not influenced
okay i'm going to say
scott has never had a white christmas
of the three of them i also
say scott
i said me even though i have
had a white girl my heaven where
gay men away or were you i
was in arizona where my parents used
to live of all places and up
in the mountains in arizona and ah
yeah they usually it's a white christmas
and it was beautiful and then last
year it started snowing
here in our place
in your home in my home know
like oh la yeah in la on
christmas day literally the snowflake started coming
down now it didn't cover anything because
they know so immediately but but no
in arizona i had like a complete
like everything white that's wonderful it was
it was inside you've had that experience
i figured that the both of you
have
oh snow place plenty of times yes
and when it's not away christmas it's
very disappointing really yeah when it's a
grey melted christmas is bitterly cold yeah
but would it always so snow in
philadelphia now always sunny it it snows
every year in philadelphia but not necessarily
on christmas
so there's never been a year that
it never snowed
for the entirety of winter can we
start going alright number two who is
celebrated christmas in another country i said
scott so did i
i said me too because i did
great we're all right yes where were
you ah i was in ah either
tokyo or kyoto i can't remember no
kyoto was kyoto was new year's eve
so i must have been in tokyo
yeah man i wish you could do
that right now i hate everything matt
didn't oh i meant to say i
was thinking about this early
earlier in the show in february i
think right before all this stuff happened
we were looking i heard a sting
song the other day and it made
me think the auditioning for the trolls
world yes he was
so i heard the sting song from
his musical that he wrote and i
remembered in february he was at the
pantages they were putting on his musical
and he was the person singing at
it right and i was like cool
up should we go to this it's
like what a weird thing to like
seize yeah sing his own musical and
then
we just ended up going like nah
forget it in february yeah what i
would kill to see sting seeing in
his own musical from the bad pages
to the contagious
we'll be right back
okay number three who's returned to gift
that they received last christmas this was
tough and i just said lauren i
said lauren as well i said lauren
as well and i did ah wasn't
so tough after wow
what
hello my name is jimmy no no
stop stop stop it now stop looking
i don't want it why is he
doing an english accent when he's saying
he's himself series of commercials so thanks
for coming let's just stop please just
turn to your daughter you're going to
do other voices
vocal
who are the screaming people like sweating
at me like i can't believe you
guys jump scenes
i mean like who does this
i mean like sass so freezing me
like you guys i can't be a
daddy nobuo uematsu just a big kid
today
i mean don't know high gas spec
so this is like a severe night
alright thank you lauren we sat through
it for merry christmas that's their gift
to honorable to laugh
ooh alright who has seen a real
live reindeer which what numbers this this
is for who has seen a real
live reindeer i for some reason said
laura i said for some reason lower
mito and i have where
oh metro swat off around your party
event reindeer factory where it's like you
can get cider and see your reindeer
and knew you know that kind of
thing can i say we we one
year during christmas um i used to
love i used to live in toluca
lake and um we go they have
a
parade every year or they they would
go at this age but they have
a christmas parade every year and it's
like if the beginning of december and
like the clothes off the streets and
you know they have floats and people
you know doing dances and all everything
it was just like on the street
that i lived on and they
they closed all the businesses but the
businesses like that remain open give away
free stuff like cookies or or stuff
like that it's so great and i
and and i would get the date
wrong every year and i would forget
about it some years and reaching a
parade like the wrong day one
it was really street from my map
but um i went with a big
the most fun years i went with
a group of like fifteen people and
we just like went walk down the
street saw the prayed wind and all
these places and we went to get
um cider in this one place and
um i'm not gonna name drop and
say who it was but a very
famous person
we were with santa claus got that
it was santa claus and he was
like whoa whoa whoa
okay green giant it was agreed that
um why and um no he he
got the cider and he he turned
to me and you said you know
what this cider house rules and i
thought it was so funny it was
john irving yeah it was
impersonating owen meany auditioning for the trolls
okay okay who what number five five
who believed in santa claus until they
were ten years old i don't think
this is true but i said me
i also don't think it was true
but i said me i don't think
it was true but i said lord
as well i had the spirit i
knew i knew it wasn't at that
point it had been ruined for me
in second grade but i tend is
too old but my mom still want
me to believe it when i was
really attend still i for i remember
being six or seven because i was
in my old house that we moved
out of when i was
aid so i remember distinctly like where
i was in the kitchen and all
that i for me i think it
was ah it was like a i
figured it out kind of thing i
figured it out where it just gradually
drew it just sort of receipted you
know what i mean where it was
not like i don't remember having a
moment of reveal yeah where it was
like oh my god this has been
one twenty gen
her reveal party and then yes it
was a whole santa non reveal body
i think my mom had an upset
none reveal party now we gotta tell
me to gone and then my mom
was really upset and i think she
called the mom of wow as i
was la hood seven or eight come
on don't call it kid i love
just lack of imo i think that
happen i love
stories of siblings who don't spoil it
for the younger sibling yes i think
that's i think that's a wonderful it's
so cute yeah i have i have
a couple friends than they are a
couple ah who have kids and for
for a their oldest it's a couple
thousand them both offense
their oldest asked them you know is
there a santa claus real and tell
me the truth and they were like
i guess we get he once he
says he wants the truth i guess
we've got to tell him the truth
and he was old enough where it
was like yeah this israeli israel yeah
okay and he and so they told
him
and he like had to go to
his room and he cried for a
bit ah and then he came back
out and he said
i'm ok i'm ok and then he
was like really other you know you're
worried me but they and they said
now you can help us you know
with with the younger kill that's nice
you know and he was like great
okay i want to do that i
want to do that now you're on
our side yeah i thought that was
really sweet now you're double agent father
the the guy who's who's my friend
said when he foul
and your friends would bow when he
found out he said to his he
was livid when his parents told him
and he said to them
you made a fool of me yeah
yeah
oh that's all my friends suck
so being talking santa claus to their
grownup reaction
oh i love it okay number six
who has all of their christmas shopping
done
despite what we've all just said i
said me
despite her just saying minutes earlier she
had nice lauren i said none okay
that makes sense alright third way who
has been to bethlehem two mm amongst
us has been to bethlehem oh okay
i see what happened i stopped i
said no
none
i said lauren because lauren does a
lot of traveling but now since she
has no i've never been to bethlehem
ah um so no one alright but
interesting um who went christmas carolyn last
year last year this is question number
eight i said scott i said paul
i said lauren well i certainly didn't
but i could imagine oh henry o
doing some sort of christmas singing in
a show is that is that true
ah it's true that that is something
that i would do but i did
not do it carolyn you know what
that's not true i was part of
a christmas show last year it's not
true well there we go that's also
no drinking and that's why i was
wrong um but carolyn does have to
be house to house yes that's carolyn
that's just that's not just singing a
christmas carol yeah the fuck is going
on with okay next okay neck
ah who has peaked at a presence
before christmas
i said oh
we forgotten so soon i said lauren
hasn't scoped i said scott because i
have idol i have never done that
on purpose i hate ruining surprise oh
really i for some weird reason i
used to search my parents' closets for
christmas presence to know what was going
on maybe two with their marriage
which i don't know to mitigate like
a bad reaction if i didn't like
it or know i was just a
snoop i just want to know i
remember one year doing that like five
i remember not like not searching that
hard and finding more i remember not
searching for when god who caught
and you found them and we found
them yeah and so like very me
and my little brother very carefully like
peeling the tape off the oh they
they went to look they weren't wrapped
they were right wow yeah they were
just like this is a month before
this shit was wrapped and wow that's
potentially looked that was a wrap and
that's what we got was wraps they
were chicken wraps
and they were by the time we
opened christmas day oh ooh we ate
them anyway and we all went to
the emergency room i remember very distinctly
finding of intrinsic was dummy that i
got one yeah
yes that's i wanted a vigil like
was doing what which one was and
i believe that why are there only
eight or well know that i remember
the cigarette catalog there were there were
specific ones you may have had a
danny mahoney probably yeah wow no you
know that's interesting know my dummies paul
and i probably
got a lot of shopping done through
the sears catalog yeah that's where we'd
like the majority otherwise yes it was
always star wars stuff i remember when
the sears catalog comment it would be
like all the star wars toys are
there god damn i loved that guy
that was so exciting i got some
millennium falcon one year ooh la la
that was probably the best ooh la
la ooh millennium
oh fuck oh la la bad christmas
presents or christmas present that i wanted
that i felt disappointed by i remember
there was a spiderman that was about
twelve feet tall that like to clough
fetus not just
because to me um
those two social distances it was it
was a sixth of me um that
would climb that could climb up things
like motorized climbing up thing i remember
that guy yeah you remember that guy
yeah i tell it once like an
hour into it there's nothing to do
with them yeah wow that's all he
does right that's all he does yeah
it was ah man we gotta stretch
armstrong one year it was the same
the thing was like okay well we've
pulled them in every direction wow the
next step is poignantly breaks and seeing
what's inside here's our step was we
thrown out the window so he would
land in the snow and make a
whole like a cartoon that's fun and
he did and then we forgot about
him and then when we discovered him
in the spring he was all cracked
huh frozen rose let's go
yeah oh laura lauren you ever get
a bad christmas present or not a
bad one but like when they run
that was not living up to what
it was yes to me
ah you know i really nothing's coming
to mind as like i thought this
would be this then yeah i get
a lot of fun things you know
one thing i really loved was getting
an american girl doll that was very
oh did you ever go to the
store at the grove i have been
to the store at the grove that
places nuts like walk in and it
looks like an
normal store yeah like all the stores
of the grove like apple store whenever
they're cool but i went because i
think you know you will you go
there for tea
well we went just because i'd never
been yeah i was like what's ventriloquist
dummies so play sports
find him a date hey guys just
cool we bring up my dog
be so fucking noisy dog you know
heard but i was a kid it
was only a catalog and so and
there were only four or five dollars
to choose from from different decades and
i ended up getting two over the
years but when i got old too
old for it is when they started
doing the ones where it looked like
you when you can like make it
really sit back and then they had
cool clothes
as for now and blah blah blah
i loved yours have a name like
a pre provider name samantha parking ten
some she from ninety no four and
she was victorian and she was from
a wealthy family sure and she was
really pretty she had brown hair and
then i also got i later got
kirsten who was the i guess it's
curious tim but i said kirsten and
thursday
um swedish doll from the eighteen or
organ nine these probably interest in when
shiny was very traditional swedish clothing and
love them both and i saved you
can't pick a favorite saved up one
hundred dollars over a period of time
of many holiday money dollars
at a time i don't know how
many i got at the time but
i saved up one hundred dollars and
i bought a handmade bunk bed from
a store in my town to make
clothes and and furniture for that fit
american girl dolls wow actually american girls
that's absolutely expensive well i went into
that store and and it it looks
like just a normal size store and
then it
just keeps going like up and up
and up and they have a hospital
where you bring your dog and my
dog to the hospital once but back
in the day you had to send
it in the mail you they because
there are stores right and so i
sent it and then it came back
fixed and it had a balloon and
a hospital gown and it was so
i just kept going there's room after
room after
a room and then suddenly there's a
theater there and it's like ah it
seats one hundred people or something like
new girl tojo lie wait you just
reminded me when i was a kid
a girl i knew from school was
she played addy in one of those
um short for adderall i don't think
so
but that was really exciting i went
to see it you went to see
the movie are you in sooner filming
that movie no oh that was like
the closest thing i'd ever gotten to
seeing someone in some are basically american
girl dolls they're like cabbage patch kids
so that was my generation we are
not i never had one or more
hey that was my agenda we were
searching and cabbage cabbage patch kid oh
you did
but they're more this is more realistic
and yeah because there's no last year
details and accessory all these fuckin details
on this thing okay you go wait
wasn't there a question name the one
i don't think he read the last
no i didn't owe because this is
part of the game as we get
off topic and we talk most detours
were taken in a game yeah um
last quest
tchen who's still give you my heart
my guys question my gay ma gave
you my aha and the segue into
careless whisper for my grandma um
for one output
last assuming last question yeah that may
have been the the funeral live with
the white tube okay um for how
this be one thing you never wear
way to my food raw boy um
who gets their own stocking filled each
year
who gets their own who gets their
stocking who gets to christmas stocking filled
every year oh instead of filling like
a kid's stocking right right
i'm gonna say me i'm going to
say me i'm gonna say me i
as we all do well say huh
only started doing that oh because my
ah my ah mother-in-law and um the
old battle brother sister-in-law came the old
battle axe i love dearly um this
is they spend christmas with us a
couple of years ago
i was like i'm gonna get stockings
because we never have done that before
and now it's the age stays i
love it but now i have to
do it on my way i usually
have a whole plan and chicago so
i gotta figure all these things yeah
well um that was christmas find out
who game by the way if we're
talking stats i never guessed paul for
anything it's true
wow that's really hurtful yeah i don't
know why i just felt like lauren
for most of it because ea for
the sea
alright well it was great how close
it was a beautiful christmas find out
who game christmas find out who again
christmas find out who again greg
a i hope everyone has a great
christmas row even if you don't celebrate
i hope that the day of december
twenty fifth is beautiful and should we
sing a christmas hymn or carol ah
here ah like what would we saying
if we were coming to someone's house
out on their doorstep christmas carols oh
no
nah
ho li na ho call o s
bra ra na
a ma da sha o o e
a infant saute
ma old c
yeah m e e s c
a e s merry christmas everyone hey
happy holiday season to you all will
see it and actually next week for
the new year okay you imagine can
you imagine it's hearing a week twenty
twenty one and everyday five next next
week as new
new year's eve in the game it's
really for that one thing that next
year oh about ah next episode on
the next but let's sing the next
episode if it's on new year's eve
it's not too early in the game
smoke
hi
ah
uh