zimmer did you hear that i said
freedom did you say better freedom i
think somebody said murder
oh my god did you hear that
i heard somebody screaming for help
ah oh my god somebody laughed when
night and someone said i'm dead and
someone's like call nine one one interesting
all the clues are there major steps
here
the lights on matt we're gonna solve
this murder hi everyone welcome to three
adams turn the lights off turn the
white tone when the lights go out
if they were all very casual about
lights on being out there like oh
i totally by the way someone turn
those lights off and i'm like they
were gonna do an episode oh really
been enjoying i don't know why you're
analyzed but that was weird timing e
z did thee i love the part
in the deep ah wash him why
am i blinking i'm gonna show cruz
over brooks's first film real life is
yes so nerve
whereas the guy giving the the the
he's in someone's housing is giving a
presentation he goes lights and looks good
he's in over brooks's housing because you
just asked me to turn off like
you can't just say lights there's not
a guy on the lights just asked
me to turn off the lights i
have an albert brooks marathon someday yeah
like
make him run a marathon i watch
one of them yeah just watch one
a fatty and call them around yeah
that's what you would do yeah oh
scott that is bad and it's hey
you've been dragged to phil can i
just say we received christmas cards from
twenty twenty while we just opened
mail today so we got there's so
much mail here and thank you so
much to everyone who sent us stuff
yes we we there were christmas cards
from last year that's how they were
happy dance we've been here that were
expired can you imagine we ate them
all these have in my diary i
feel bad thing rica okay we are
not my anus my diary
mike
oh my anus don't say your age
my name is hurts because the area
flowing through it actually burning through it
it's being of embarrassing things were last
week yeah you may want
i'm embarrassed to tell you i'm currently
having active diarrhea so i can't go
to the po um when i was
again when i was in my ah
early twenties early twenties but probably i
might have been nineteen something like that
living heart living downtown i had a
purple heart cycle did you see it
i buy subscribe to a service that
would take pictures of my heart and
stuff
and this is pre instagram where you
know pre selfies what was fun was
i never knew and the picture was
being taken they shouldn't tax rate selfies
this show should who will use their
phone should be able to take an
x-ray of you so you don't have
to go down all town and reach
give you more cancer than it already
yes so i woke up one day
in my
swallow on apartment new and i got
myself a gun
i don't feel down down your skirmish
i had an excruciating pain in my
rectum oh no and i was like
all that's going on excruciating like you
couldn't stand ah pull you get funded
i couldn't do anything it was
it was it was very scary next
machine fucks you in and like felt
around there and i was like paul
do you have a sex machine i
am a sex machine oh so when
you are i wish you guys would
read my t-shirts yeah i see that
i make a boo i make them
myself i'm like you know i start
doing more to to free ladder was
making those hats wow
you still make them
real lore he must still and then
realize he made them and thought he
just had no he made them there
was ah it was found in his
house rock it was a running joke
with me and a friend of mine
which came first whenever his name came
ma he he had them in his
standup i believe both yes now it's
certainly i've always been a part of
him and it was always mentioned anytime
anyone talked about him that he made
the as himself and
so was a running joke of being
a friend of mine anytime his name
como se you know it makes his
own ass and um i'm saying you
think he has enough my word he
can pay someone to make the apps
he loves doing it i but i
wanna make his hats thing for a
nominal fee how much do you want
you want to be like this it's
apprentice yeah until you can make your
own you want to make
reality show called the apprentice where you
make jennifer sure they're not doing the
apprentice anymore so why not it's right
there this is the night doing it
so tight right right is die if
you had the thing what if it
went all the way paul push the
microwave from his and anywhere always went
all the way around in the head
and came back in the head
belonging oh wow and she goes you
know what i didn't get and then
i'm sad i didn't get a mcdonalds
happy meal halloween bucket what are those
they brought back the nostalgic buckets from
my child what are those their their
happy meal buckets that what are those
fuck you you know males coming a
couple of trick or treaters this
last year had them yeah and they're
pretty small well i don't need to
be big sweetie it's worth a small
compared to the trick or treater decoration
for under the halloween tree okay honey
that's fine for you separate these two
okay oh hey back hair any interest
in making doing my story yes yes
so i
i thought ah oh no my my
rectum is like distended or so anyway
i thought this was like oh yeah
you're right my hurting recto said that
you're still talking about the kids who
showed up with leukemia yeah that's that's
the that's done i know but i
just was like this how's it this
way asshole but oh my rectum but
don't let us get off topic it
was not that long ago
i know but it's still throw of
course what i did first was called
my mommy corn and say mommy why
do you do i'm scared don't hurt
i think my rectum is distended she
was like oh my god oh my
god i'm going to send your father
down to take you to the hospital
down where where were you you are
going downtown that's i think my rectum
is distended yes very good
thank you do you understand both proud
of myself to work so do understand
the words that are coming from this
and the pain that's coming on my
butt so my dad shows up takes
me in the hospital did he look
at it or were you like this
is a prime book why won't look
that amy assess the situation already cooling
mom and dad what if like you
he
game over said all right let me
get it let me see you pulled
any pants you just fart at his
face and you're like gotcha
to drive thirty minutes just foreign university
pretty good prank whatever pretty good for
all it's so go to the hospital
i go you know to the emergency
room and i'm taken to a little
um what you know and i haven't
earned a toy car
don't spoil it okay so the doctor
says um okay i have to ask
you some questions i don't know if
you want your father to be present
and i said no anything you could
say to me you could say i
said yeah that's fine like and my
dad was like oh wait outside again
my dad was afraid to find out
i was gay
ah so the doctor asked me you
know like did you put anything in
there do you have anal sex you
know all this stuff and i'm like
no no no do you want to
right now that was later i found
this card up there so um he
he examined me and it turned out
i had haemorrhoids oh chiba chiba taboo
horrible yeah but a relief that i
don't have some weird cancer you just
had to put a little krem i
had to below crown fresh i go
back and i asked my running right
hey will you go fill this prescription
for me shove it up my gimme
this stuff
you said this your roommates and i
switched my roommate can you feel this
can you get this why why don't
you want to like why do you
didn't wanna do it i could barely
i fuck oh you can watch oh
sorry so they didn't just go away
after the doctors so i thought maybe
like no it was killing him and
made him feel but it was bad
it was really bad it was really
bad it was bad so my roommate
wait um goes and gets the stuff
yeah roid rage i had
ah
sorry i flipped you off right right
you see steroids ah guess again motherfucker
so i had to get it was
a prescriptive force depositories um and like
preparation h or whatever and so he
came back and this pause tories were
called an esol yeah and when he
came back he tossed it to me
said there you go there's your anus
all i was like it's useful
it may as well be me let
me well of course what it is
yeah of course that's what it is
yeah
i seen the commercials and i could
pronounce an aneurysm and you saw a
missile like uranus just
this whole ah
and then oh hello i was embarrassing
yeah tell you
an enduring this
ah
so you want to have an embarrassing
moment now yeah yeah yeah so i
can tell you later
ah
see if you recognize yourself in the
story
oh sorry these two assholes
know they feel like shit comes interrupting
my story having no head pumps in
it or whatever the fuck one guy
thought i told trick or treaters my
rectum was suspended
able to say oh no oh scott's
leg is leaning against it and he's
shaking with laughter like santa claus himself
jelly and whatnot
things of this nature girl santa claus
isa but hopes it humming serious doing
it he's hailed around the corner now
may soon do you think emeralds on
the nice list emeril wow damn do
you think emerald is on the nice
list i can't tell you how many
times this has happened where something was
her name oh nice emerald and just
cameral
emerald is such a good name okay
i love it when i first saw
it so is emma roll okay but
it's not to be confused with um
but when i first saw it on
the invitation to the baby shower i
was like so excited i love the
name i was hype i was hype
i was lit i was i was
liddy
i was going with her name i
don't because i i don't think it
would go well with my last name
although would go go to castle it
will go google google emerald castle i'd
be like oh my la wow
it's to finish i don't think his
known as the store was name the
city mike city ah emerald city cool
that'd be cool my name was saying
it would be cool what did like
castle is cool what is my love
that i love the name what are
the big precious gym names so you
got ruby we got emerald ruby ruby
ruby ruby soho um oh
opal is one pearl is one diamond
and sapphire yeah
fire based on level push
um by your hemorrhoids
i feel like every every one of
them is basically yeah what would her
orgasms and that's not topaz to ah
what's one amber hammer yeah or ebola
jam in many ways an alert yeah
yeah did you guys get the flesh
littler
or ideas it was fun and it
was serene was a child yeah no
it was incorrect they did not mean
to really but the it was going
coming down in sheets when that got
that yes but it said do not
travel anywhere it was like two people
in l a it was like flash
flood warning if you do not get
out of your cars do not travel
anywhere
i was looking at this going you're
telling l a to i mean you're
telling l o los angeles is just
supposed to like pull over whatever and
it was only meant for like a
little tiny pocket elsewhere not l a
i was like are they trying to
suppress the vote because it happened on
voting day oh made me think that
rick caruso had his hand
on the leavers of politics itself well
as it was happening it was storming
and we decided to have a little
movie time with hollywood we put on
oliver and company which cute movie from
lady with billy joel songs and billy
joel's voice piano billy joel's but he's
got a dog button real life famously
um really like it
what kind of dog is is is
he oliver in the mo oliver's a
cat played by joe lawrence wow i
did not see that coming
bass riffs se suno was a dog
the premise is that there's this little
cat litter and he he falls into
a pack of dogs in the city
this is the company yeah and then
to a willing little girl like professor
and marianne you know just being the
rest which every dog is company the
cat in and then he gets stolen
and
and ends up being a whole thing
where the dogs had to get him
back and little girl and they're riding
on the top of a bridge it
was really stressful but isn't it based
on oliver um obviously oliver told her
oh and they're like all of our
twist all of her twists that said
that nipple fetish boring
for all of her twist
oh man people are really gonna like
this
i used to we ever put together
that it was when i worked at
the video store i didn't even know
we of course had a porn section
that was famously not like hidden behind
a curtain or anything like that but
you had to guard just an aisle
i guard it because those purves would
come here are you zoom perverted he
would just look at the covers and
go um but
i used to like i used to
like to look at the titles it
is based on oliver twist right the
one i remember the most clearly that
i thought was it was because he
was a cat yeah everything else is
the butler people don't realize that oliver
juices cat yeah i know he didn't
do it he didn't do games never
says it he's like people don't really
dickens was cat that's the thing
like everyone some others have flying meow
we have to marry it's like why
should he have to say that why
she doesn't have metal key does it
have to say the title i liked
the most was a rear and pleasant
danger wow i don't do they don't
do the funny titles in danger from
what i am
no really it just takes solid like
doctor who a porn parody or did
they just call it like fasting for
hours
it's because out of fistful of dollars
no i just mean it's not it's
just just describes what it is
ah is it if a war with
the number four fisted for history's cold
for hours it's three hours in your
colon yeah
oh gosh oh gosh gosh guys yeah
christmas is rider because santa he's still
up to it what yeah so what's
the date
don't you pay any mind oh no
what's the days misses coming and the
goose is getting fat please put penny
real manhattan know obviously this is december
eighth clearly you when this is being
released a day after they were living
we have some fun christmas plans coming
up we'll whoa what you say with
you what you're going to do when
it comes
for you
new song what if yeah santa what
you gotta do what a santa i
want you to be like a santa
cop uniform it's a blue with like
the hat sie ab we all agree
santa does great stuff he does great
one of the greats what a brand
we love everything he does yes yeah
and he's the only pricey
he asks of us is occasionally some
milk and cookies but what if he
kidnapped one child every year i know
first of all would we still be
like he's great and let him do
it i feel it depends what he
does with the child if they become
like have a fabulous ivan can you
separate the art from the yard but
also this and ask for the milk
and cookies he asked for us to
be good
good but he and we give him
it's ok lie guys are good it's
imply you know you want you can
still of course you want somebody you
could still get your presence without giving
milk and i can't wait for holiday
to have christmas is here because she's
gonna start to have an idea oh
yes it's very exciting it's very like
the halloween tree oh yeah
yeah she was very delighted by you
show me the video of her watching
the rain which is so sweet she
loved the rain yeah she lands down
there she wanted to go out into
it so i had once it stopped
she'd crawled right outside into and just
sat in a puddle
ah honestly same high now so she
is sitting on toilets she's crawling yeah
she doesn't care what she sits i
love it yeah she's getting dirty like
a boy yeah i'm gonna say that
to her make it very clear you're
dirty like a boy she's like what's
a boy let's start to hear it
yeah has she ever
i've seen another child yes well she
just got your foot in mouth from
some of them last week actually which
is a nice little disease virus it's
so weird i only feel like i
am aware of that in the last
few years as being a thing that
humans can get yeah i think it
was an animal thing yeah i didn't
know anything about r s v until
i was too young and mouse scary
i know
oh what's what alright sb it's like
a little little it's a virus that
little kids can get doesn't reset for
virus probably was responsible and up in
the hospital often roberto's because they need
to be on salamanca breathing things he
can't breathe um yeah it's like bad
it's going around alright i only it's
already me to tell you this last
night
firstly carpet site and there's no vaccine
worse than kobe because the worst thing
that ever i mean it's worse in
the sense of more people have it
now oh god i thought girls i
thought you were just in cove it's
damning work that three hole right now
yeah that's interesting actually yeah fun and
that's all very nice but right now
my sister is a nurse yeah virus
which is so great and she says
yeah you really gotta watch
up for the artist fee because that's
where everyone has it had the hospitals
now they're overrun now how how is
that happening is what i'm how how's
everyone getting our sb i'm like a
cold it's like a kissing chain okay
ooh well the fun thing with hand
foot and mouth is that it's spread
through saliva and when i told you
how i threw up on me three
times yes
it was definitely that and then you
betrayed our lord yeah alright we have
to take a break huh
and we're back my bitch mallaig da
just met a girl named berlin duh
and sodomy i ah da da me
hey my da
santa reggae demo was movie successful you
know like it wasn't right now kinda
eat shit weird well it came out
in the middle i mean people weren't
going out during covert yeah that's right
we ah we rented a theater and
so that's right casey wilson and i
that's right did a co screen co-head
mining screen we both had lines yuko
presented because you really want to talk
beforehand but she she thought you here
in l a i don't know whether
you could do it elsewhere you could
rent an amc theater for a private
screening for up to fifty people i
would imagine you can do it anywhere
no i think it was other places
it was chicago and i mean it
was not expensive
so it was not attic so two
hundred dollars for my friend too and
yeah it was it was essentially like
twenty bucks a person yeah if you
have people to go but casey kind
of thought that it was more like
a private screening thing where she would
be given an opportunity to speak before
and this movie that was like nothing
to do with no it just like
starts at the normal time just like
going to the movie
he's like a mc promos and was
everybody in there people from that party
because i feel like there were there
was like thirty one couple that has
everything to do with us right and
no no they know that those were
like casey's okay okay god i don't
even go yeah good good good yeah
but it was fun it was fun
it was the most fun and it
was like a thing
lauren i it's one of those i
yeah it's one of those things when
i when it happened i was like
oh i have to remember this is
a thing you can do because it's
really fun and then instantly yeah never
did it oh for sure yeah i
always see dear evan hansen my friend
got this the screening or whatever and
that was fun but because you kind
of yell and
wow you suck yeah rowdy screening exactly
i love rowdy screening i love his
yelling some swears at some point and
then there was a job we did
that for jackass for new printer child
ah it doesn't matter and they were
fine with it we did for jazz
foreign was it was a janey who
had never seen any of the movies
before and had no idea what she
was in for
she had the the vaguest idea of
what jackass we get to hit the
nuts occasionally know there's a lot of
cock jazz so many houses in it
jane edith yeah no i love it
um she there was a lot of
stuff she could not look at because
it was so stomach turning
a man's penis and discussed a change
and everything mine wine wow you just
do like a sort of what makes
a binder situation on that were in
the dark all the time yeah yeah
and there's someone turn on the lights
there's verde of blackout curtain there can
be murders happening all the time we
have no idea you never are seen
just in case your penis comes out
oh no we have flashlights that we
hold up to our faces and a
tiny flashlight for you
no no batteries in that because she
can't see yes that's what i mean
you hold the flush head off up
to it yeah
the flashlight coming out from it make
it look bigger but she can't see
it can't see she can't feel it
no we've never met huh
huh we live in the same home
that makes it easier yeah our wedding
was weird weird stuff well how many
roommates free fall in love
what a beautiful question i wonder what
the percentage will make falling because we've
all had roommates weed by the way
we have not returned to our roommate
we have roommate right but the problem
is oh that's right where we looked
out about that shit we were going
to recount all of our origin never
had cannot go back to it unless
we know where we left off and
some are made don't want to talk
about
i feel like about all of them
i remember where i left off i
think but but in any case everyone
who's had a roommate what percentage hands
up what percentage of the following we
can see you right now like they
don't ah even if they know each
other beforehand whatever how many roommates fall
in love i would say maybe
point five percent i think it's fifty
percent wow yeah i think it's like
eighty nine percent fall um
what's left eleven percent are falling
by the way reality are you up
yeah yeah now the distinction on the
bachelor is i'm falling i'm falling for
you i'm falling in love with you
i am in love with you which
is like no back in the day
you just said you can't say if
you sam follow
i'm in love with you that means
i'm in love with yeah bizarre yeah
i'm almost there so crazy i'm so
close to being i can tell that
i'm about to be yeah with you
it's like what do you mean by
this time next week yeah although with
you then again to have gradients on
this stuff it's like why does it
have to be just a dichotomy of
i'm not in love with you i
am a little do you see that
rally recap ya go
gabby and the guy she picked have
broken out no just a mere couple
months so you're saying i have a
chance yeah gabby would show is from
bachelor and bachelorette which guy did she
pick i forget everything about the previous
season moment of stones air actually yeah
now so there's the bachelor which i
like her but a lot of vocal
fry no i think she's going to
say
yeah i love i think i'm falling
qui i really think i'm filing hey
that was actually really good she's one
hundred years old yeah she sounds like
it but not her like i'm falling
food oh by the way the guy
on
bachelor in paradise my mother girl i
think there will be you and i
and lovely sushi i haven't watched an
episode this you haven't kept i gave
myself well i have to say i'd
say ship is doing standup comedy now
he's a good you been watching bip
bip bachelor in paradise oh no you're
not you just shop this ship
op is from southern tron okay oh
he's doing standup where he did a
couple of gigs in new york where
of course he just told stories about
carnegie hall that show yeah he opened
carnegie hall that's the thing i just
want to try this out that's the
thing though no he he did a
small room in new york and um
it sounded like every room small and
short so it's like have you seen
apart
once there what about seinfeld it wasn't
a nice big space that's true that's
a good point like oh he's really
see part of it what a seinfeld
was
what if seinfeld somebody very wrong we
don't go into jerry's room have you
ever going to change no i think
you were yeah you've been in there
like a couple episodes really yeah i'm
pretty sure i can wake up with
a woman type situation i don't think
i haven't always got a weird thing
that you can't get past yeah of
course like a shah's what if he
says she's not seventeen years
old cars hey
paul you're bad or naughty and i've
never done why he i'm bad i
know i know he speaking of you
i've finally watched the weird al movie
oh i watch and we have sown
your very good nipple i saw the
spoiler that your gallagher is try and
play the committee of the irish comedian
gallagher
and money it was it was a
picture you posted thank you um it
was i was very grateful to be
a part of it ah and i
finally watched the whole movie and man
i really laughed all the way through
it yeah it's very just really fun
watch it it's really funny a lot
of great performances in it i think
daniel radcliffe is amazing yeah he can
do it all
jacked and other stuff i guess i'm
curious what jazz i actually can't be
jackson and jack don't you ever come
back i can only imagine him doing
this role so i'm very excited to
see he's great in it and i
will tell you that when i was
on that set
him in that costume and the wig
and the mustache it was never not
funny like every time i looked at
it yeah it was funny to me
yeah and then like just standing there
but then when he was saying stuff
it got even funnier how long have
you known now
i mean yeah around the same time
as god you met him at the
same time i think ten years maybe
will now it's i mean we've longer
for fourteen six fourteen yeah at this
point let's say fourteen wow i kind
of wish i know he's more handsome
now but i kind of wish he'd
go back to that old look it's
so iconic what if he did it
for like a year just a year
or that's all we're asking owl one
year of your life that hair back
into my head squirt that hair back
out on my lip yeah but those
glasses back oh yeah i forgot he
doesn't have a moustache your moustache in
the street and he straightens his hair
i think wow yeah because it's curly
naturally know he's straight i believe it's
but
yeah longer so it's more maybe uses
a product games yeah he's a permit
or some know it is still cool
but all we're asking now is all
this is oil i don't imagine that
al wakes up every morning and runs
a strainer through his hair you don't
feel like he you accept gallery more
taxes here just even that is weird
that you don't think he
wakes up and i don't think he
does you think i was just awake
all the time don't think even with
constantly wake or rolling out of bed
asleep and continues using sleepwalking through his
whole life i just get someone to
just get my shake he's gonna wake
up sweating a danger i made a
movie isn't dangerous to wake a sleepwalker
or is that just may think it's
a myth let's ask what might her
biblia
nobody likes you and sitting here this
whole time nobody ever says what happens
if you wake them like viggo they
just it's very dangerous just in tv
shows and movies and shit yeah i
know they do i tell you about
when they do they'll punch you
violent i tell you about when i
was in this f serious winter camp
why would a winter catholic hey my
carol shaman want you to be home
for christmas i go to summer campaign
with winter games never anywhere to hear
why was you in school dearie
because it was a weekend so summer
cables a week you went to into
ramp on the weekend once
yeah that's my story viet ah ok
what there was this there was a
guy who was a i guess a
sleepwalker who got up out of we
had bunkbeds in the cabin and he
got out of his cabin and he
started arguing with his dad
in the corner to the court ahead
wasn't there oh and he and we
all didn't know what to do and
were like do we wake him up
to anyway do we do we do
we comfort him do we wake him
up and we just let him have
this argument going no no no you
don't know what you're saying you don't
know what
yeah well that's yeah that's really embarrassing
he's still having the argument we never
woke about but wow my god he
still that can still they tore the
camp down he still does the blair
witch and it aged and he's just
standing there and his pajamas are too
small the other night i had a
dream where i've been having very pleasant
dreams lately and i don't know why
and i will wake up at four
thirty eight
a am every day and have an
hour of pure anxiety about things that
have to do then i go back
to sleep but my dreams are extremely
nice i remember having a nice dream
is like so amazing it really is
eastern china it's such a little treat
mainstream but i had a dream where
um i was with a friend of
mine i can remember who
it was now but they had like
this cute little dog and i was
in the dream or like oh my
god your dog is i love this
dog like give him a kiss he
loves he loves little kisses and so
i was kissing the dog on top
of the head fans a bad dream
for me and i fucking eight year
pillow i woke myself up making kissing
sounds ah
suddenly you're shit i was like who
are you china i saw i thought
for sure that was gonna wake janie
up because i've i've done that before
where i've i've i've gone from saying
something in the dream yeah just saying
it out loud right yeah and then
it wakes her up but she didn't
wake up for a lot i had
a way like i do is like
yeah it is danny
is it easy mean i had two
nights ago i had a nightmare and
either i woke inside her what in
cyber means i'd wait and that's what
i'd say um i woke myself up
from it like going no no and
i i could tell like i had
woken up i'd woken
up cool or whatever and i like
rolled over but she didn't say anything
she didn't like come for me or
anything so i was like oh maybe
i didn't wake her up the next
morning she says yeah you started making
really scary noises to the extent that
i thought you were messing with me
wow like oh so how does that
kind of mad had i just gone
to sleep she's like no i was
awake for another two hours after you
and just sleep i was like what
why two hours into sleep would i
start fucking with you
by i mean it's a perfect setup
you're like wait wait two hours down
you are doing i think it was
just like ah stop it stop it
yeah nothing
ah
but like to think so poorly of
me to think that oh no i'm
not concerned he's fucking with me yeah
what the hell is dead last much
that's a good point yeah once bitten
every time shot yeah everybody used it
on her ever forget who did take
her to one hundred hours ago
she hated it
well i didn't take her because she
made me take her home but that's
right that's right yeah anyway i don't
know and she would have hated it
because it was one of those haunted
houses where he had to crawl now
so where'd you know in that they
dug under the into the dirt and
made a tunnel under the dirt that
you had to crawl through i was
like that's fucking ridiculous that not wanting
to do it
at all that's hell no she took
her tip college kids yell at you
forget it well there's a place called
delusion it's like ah get your masters
and manjula bra
enchanted clay hunted play okay that makes
more sales a hunted play yeah it's
very scary i went one year but
i actually get too scared i don't
think i really scare just too scared
like we're doing it i'm going like
and i'm like if they choose me
for this next thing i'm really gonna
hate it like what do they choose
people for like so basically they what
they do is they take like an
empty mansion in la
a like like an old house and
they do it every different one every
year and it's empty you say well
like nobody lives there but there's furniture
nice with props and that's and then
there's like a story so it's like
they you walk up and then like
the connector like what's on time and
be like for instance oh wow yeah
it was a dark stormy night you
have to help me there
something happening in blah blah so i
heard for this year what they did
was that they they were like oh
the monster is coming the giant did
you go to man ok like someone's
coming who scared the monsters coming everyone
needs to play the back of this
treasure monsters coming everyone has to play
like you're dead in the back of
this truck bed then they drive you
as you're laying
saying they drive you somewhere yeah to
like them where the the second location
the home yeah are you touching bodies
with strangers probably and then like all
my friends like this kind of stuff
and anything it's like well the purves
okay anyway i find it boring to
me i think this is the part
where they actually do kill you yeah
so they take you to this place
and then does the monster come
like he's running fifty minutes like go
through the house like you know there's
a story that they're telling you of
like oh come this way do you
have to do this thing and this
task has to be accomplished you have
to like work together like do something
then you have to get into this
yeah i'm assuming here that i went
there was like a giant table that
you crawl under like as if you're
small and then rolling big
legs walked by and it was like
really cool interesting that sounds cool because
it was memorable and it was cool
but i there's parts where like someone
gets chosen to go into a room
with someone and then something happens and
then you don't know and you get
separated from your group and i was
like i do not want that i
like to huddle with everyone yeah i
get too scared yeah that's to be
pulled away from the group is ce
scary and then you kind of like
acting with them because they're they're kind
of like i don't know maybe twitter
is an actor well that's like you
know they're an actor they're gonna come
in that's the thing you're not getting
paid to act so it's like making
hey were me i would be like
i'm sorry but my name is scott
aquaman this is fake you're all fake
give me money if you want me
to know but i think i
i feel confused about what my role
is like am i supposed to go
in and be like really doing it
up or am i supposed i know
acting like how hey you need direction
yeah it needs it's also a second
take points away i love that it
should be the that shouldn't be a
one on one thing i don't know
but i'm sure people people like your
people aren't performers yes they probably don't
and also my performer friends like it
while they're weird okay
or what about your friends who are
thinking about performing but they only have
living room but don't think i have
one friend like that i think a
very simply don't do it or they
do it yeah yeah i don't have
any friends who doesn't do it who's
sort of like your thinking about getting
into the business
some fellow middle aged people i'm gonna
try
why not
hey look again there's a lot of
stories like oh yeah horse they covet
it's just i think you've been doing
it too long to meet people it's
hard i met some people yeah i
mean you've met all the people you
ever going to be dude i met
some people the other night it was
so fucking bored
just like just why am i doing
this i don't want to meet any
more people i'm done it's a lot
when you start yet because i wonder
you're you know you've had more of
that than i have so you get
to a point where she's like i
don't want to start over i i
don't want to go that's already going
you jerry seinfeld that's why he got
married you said like i kept hating
repeating
in first date talk yeah just marry
one of you're fuck
yeah take a break
where mac it's three church time and
you know you love it you know
you love it you know you need
it you know you're making this for
your earhole like piss pigs your piss
pigs and hey mistakes guess what son
for three hey piss bags or back
i'm sorry
that that's the collective name for fans
but you guys voted and you got
and it's just you have been following
this this pig you are you're more
like this big then you aren't so
that's what you call yeah we love
our fans a little pittsburgh so most
people are phillips figure
okay ah we're gonna play a feature
that we've played many times it's a
favorite of ours and hopefully of yours
too it's called hitting the posts and
this is where we play songs from
our phones and the challenge is to
do the perfect d j thing of
dabbing over the the
the musical part of the song before
the lyric start i wonder vocals and
i know i know it's like rude
to be talking over someone yeah which
is why we try stop before the
voice yeah never do that over you
never talk over each other we know
we'll stop before the voice me too
but do you think there was ever
a d j before this became customary
who just
talked over the lyrics and was just
like yeah hey shut up back there
anyway um who was the first d
j to decide yeah the sounds go
for this part yeah exactly because normally
on the radio is like you start
a song yeah and it's like oh
i should shut the fuck like i
was uncomfortable silence yeah and he's like
nobody talking yeah
anyway so takes too long due to
the huddles alright so who i have
the dongle so your possession i've got
on clay so who's gonna talk is
it clockwise or counterclockwise i'll do it
okay you ready or volunteers distribute hunger
games here we go and
it's the weekend folks you know what
that means it's time to party get
your red solo cups and your ping
pong balls and go over your best
gals house and start slam dunking them
beers call me in the morning and
slap my ass and commies
call me no we'll never know sally
ah i didn't want so long was
that i was velvet crush with speedway
vc with sb
oh tight go around the other way
go around the other way go around
the other tight around the other tie
tight dongles
oh honey oh honey oh now this
thing me i love fucking that's cloudy
that's claudia
claudio claudio hey hello
oh no wait are you ready high
does it mean yeah mr whatever it
is you are you ready
oh boy
ah oh boy to listen to ah
but that's what happens with bobby get
another knowing why because it's fun but
that's how it ok fine that's fine
that was this turn no that's not
fun for me okay okay
huh oh boy you know what's going
to happen now my boss is gonna
fire me for saying shit
we know that's really yeah yeah so
great so
absolutely no no no i don't know
it's just easier if you know the
story yeah he that's why he knew
to stop yeah that's right yeah even
dongle quite quickly gave it a dog
oh
namely that dong bo it was so
it goes by nick lowe in the
previous song was my life is right
by big star um okay ready
hey folks this is scotty the body
d's nuts
and i want to let everyone know
that every time i drink a carbonated
beverage i float about two feet above
the ground and i'm doing it right
now somebody grabbed my ankles because i'm
a vowed to fly so high
wouldn't make me up that was bruce
springsteen with thunder roads live at wembley
wembley he played wembley yes so fucking
cool play wembley everybody knew his songs
that self even though they've never even
though they have old jersey there wow
lol jersey there oh wow
speaking of old jersey how's kevin smith
do it oh you fucking god
alright ready lauren i am here we
go
college starts today everyone all across the
usa kids are moving into their dorms
and sam bye-bye to mommy and daddy
will get ready because it's time to
learn everything you're gonna need to know
folks sheds a human man
we've got velocity we've got history we've
this is still the backup seniors this
year we've got music we've got english
now please bring your textbooks and be
ready
for your textbooks i'd be ready to
be and i should learn how to
sum up my sentences before that was
barbara lewis with asks a lonely don't
think that we're going to go that
way okay can you go that way
ding dong
shalom
let's see now i'm like what song
don't you know alright here we go
ready and
hey folks that c o two alarm
has been going off in the studio
but it is liberty weekend and i
want to bring you this music for
as long as i have breath in
my body which shouldn't be too much
longer so turn your radio all the
way up and call an ambulance and
send it over here just in case
ace i love each and every one
of you more than i love my
children whose names i cannot recall
i think one of them's jeremy that's
the word
some so backup what he does that's
real real by sleigh bells sleigh bell
hs ring o or yell in wow
in and the les is yeah move
that dongle over lauren a beautiful sigh
dare you she just threw it at
me were happy she was almost time
for christmas music should do christmas round
i don't have any christmas music in
my younger life right now i have
lorne and habit you have sound effects
you know
just true i might enjoy higher lotta
high you know what you call it
subscription new insurgency song you want and
you don't have a spotify would qualify
i'm just saying i thought we were
playing songs from our phone phone not
our spotify my spotify is myself why
it's my spotify is my phone i
keep my songs in my spotify because
that's where i listen to my music
is that weird no i think it's
normal right scott are you ready yep
hey everyone i was thinking about joining
glasses or not let me give you
an example i'm gonna read this sign
that's over on the wall over here
it says gee maggie de mijas
okay that's what i'm reading but someone
told me it says gentleman's room okay
maybe it does maybe it doesn't how
am i supposed to know also
yeah i was really hoping it was
all instrumental it seemed like it was
going to be that was the action
news theme from doi p vi tv
and philadelphia oh wow and you listen
to that for pleasure ah no i
got i got it because i wanted
to play it i wanted to come
onto it when i did raised by
tv in philadelphia yeah yes
and people fucking loved it yeah they
did i came onto it right don't
you and i sang it everyone's saying
oh i remember this i mean it
wasn't there no you don't work well
but you try to listen to it
i told you in detail about it
yeah hi lauren ready here we go
i gotta give me happy birthday to
my bus jared he is turning fifteen
and yes it does bother me that
he's so much younger than me and
he's my boss but what can you
do you know where you get this
asian for forty two years and a
fifteen year old is my boss
all the electric prunes alright you gotta
love dps you got to the executive
producers of that album
i made all the money okay you
ready palm yeah i don't know what
this is i wanna press play everybody's
got to feel good when they put
on a new pair of socks that's
why the salvation army is cleaning all
of the socks and sending them to
you as if they are brand-new because
they want you to have that feeling
but they don't want you to know
that
someone had the socks on before you
i shouldn't be telling you this it
should be private but there you go
now you know the rest of the
story
and it goes on a stormy around
the clock they're open twenty four hours
this month
but ah i didn't know it's for
you holiday remix by lee hi i
just went to a holiday thing
where's that play from what was my
phone
i play by accident was at an
ihop commercial yeah
it's like a folksy kind of music
that's like oh you got an ihop
and get the three ninety nine special
okay you ready scott oh yeah here
we go
hey everyone have you heard of this
new thing called sex i guess it's
swear you take your private part and
you rub it against someone else's private
part i don't know it felt good
to me when i did it for
the first time the other day
so i want to let you know
about it um give me a call
let me know if you've heard of
this thing and if you have any
requests until then here's harmonica joe with
this is my first lesson in someone
who's saving it aw on the two
zahn threes and fours we skip the
fives
come back around on the six is
seven o'clock we take a big long
break because we're very hungry and we
need a big buffet meal we go
to hometown buffet we get the chicken
and the pizza which is not something
you normally get at any other restaurant
but when you see it on one
of those buffets you just can't help
yourself because the flavor profiles are
too good
two goods or reviews is what i
say and why would your reviews it
i mean you're paying for it and
they throw away most of the food
when you're done so why not eat
all you want when you're at that
buffet is really a business model that
cannot fail make a whole bunch of
stuff a bunch of people come to
get it
they pay you
hey hey you've got a color oh
yeah god color too hello
i just wanted to say yeah i'm
a big fan oh thank you so
much oh i was wondering if you
could play a side for my wife
she just died oh yeah how was
she going to hear it though oh
hey good point goodbye jake wow
getting a phone call
perfect
wow those yeah of course it was
an instrumental and you knew it was
and i do it wow larry yeah
definitely we haven't done that before have
we not i don't think we have
and it feels like we all should
but it was about time it's about
time to do it it was about
time well there you go that's how
you play hitting the posts and ah
that was fucking phone is always logged
because i'm
hearing that buzzing in my rear and
i would love to not hear it
there we go how's that dear that
is wonderful guys another fun episode and
really i'm happy to be here with
you all and to be recording the
silliness and there's a sincere thought out
of me so do with that what
you and we're not going to see
each other for another two years
is at this point right so yeah
so let's make the most of this
we've recorded the next couple seasons yeah
in advance like this yes yeah um
they're really good i mean they're all
their crimes they're so good i can't
wait to hear them but yeah we
will not be seeing each other in
person for another couple of years i
can't believe it's almost twenty twenty three
yeah i know did you ever think
you'd be alive
yes before you were alive i mean
oh yeah
you have to understand when i was
a kid this is i couldn't even
imagine a year like this i thought
two thousand twenty three is just silver
i thought i yeah everything is er
yeah it's not
i like how on t h x
one one three hundred nobody just shakes
their head all the time i know
some things percent razors takes a lot
of time are we gonna um wrap
it up yeah it's done so um
freedom usa on um instagram and twitter
freedom usa gmail dot com if you
want to suggest a three cheer to
us you can call us
we haven't listened to voicemails yet but
we have them ah haha lime poo
if you want all only if you
want to tell us how great we
are
that should be no i for sure
only cause if you have an interesting
question for us to talk about yeah
but but you can include the include
share but okay just get out of
the way real quick just say hi
you guys i love you to death
you're the best sign now here's my
here's my interesting question yeah it's phrasing
everyone yeah but but word for word
and don't and don't make the question
it's like backhanded like why aren't you
better at you know yeah like like
oh yeah and our last convo starter
yeah if you are good-looking what's the
first thing you would do things like
alright everybody is a good question thank
you firstly i would do yeah if
you want to hear ad-free versions of
the show you can go to stitcher
or to cvb world dot com um
and yeah and guys oh shit
i don't even remember what we call
it a marsh but does read designate
three visiting on the two resisting on
the choose where we're re-releasing our older
episodes on tuesdays and they're just as
fresh as a daisy they are indeed
um so this tuesday will be releasing
of epic episode four i think i
think so
which but you know really in the
star wars universe is a new hope
that's right and that's one we are
retailing episodes one through nine two according
to the star and after that ten
is through you know what we have
now is what we think the episode
should be called exactly putting it all
together stuff the star wars ten
yeah there's stories eleven whoops where are
my keys to the millennium falcon star
wars twelve aha are your locks on
any of the spaceships in the star
wars universe i don't think so you
never say it they just open and
shut yes like
ah you should at least have like
a key that the controls are almost
all exactly the same i know yeah
there's no one knows how to fly
everything yeah although they're always looking for
pilot sounds great but then anyone who's
yeah yeah exactly anyone who gets into
ass things it's like they go ooh
that's a really good boy we need
a pilot
we all have spaceships but i don't
know how to drive alright that's about
goodbye we love you bye
uh