three
be
can trade
one two three huh
oh i didn't realize you got yeah
wow happening during oh yeah denial anger
bargaining i didn't see
i got a real question for you
guys what's root for you guys what
to get to take for me to
get you into a pair of cracks
the croc sales writing checks are gonna
get you out here are the largest
of air shoe you've ever felt by
the end of the day come on
we're just looking sorry
non-muslim and upendra well i don't i
went on the crux we thought this
was a different store on the rocks
right nasty we thought this point june
like that song that is really shiny
right put on troppo da rod you
put on the left and i'll put
on the right on one boy yeah
you put on the right and i'll
put on the left ho downs
because we're in the middle we have
a three legged board
perfect perfect perfect now you know i
did buy crocs for a cake boss
costume and i could not believe how
comfortable the thing i'm about to buy
them because nicole byer is obsessed and
i and she just told me right
now most comfortable pair of shoe i
own no boy yeah we should be
sponsored by crackles comfortable parachute
when i put all the crocs i
feel like a walking on the clouds
literally woke up when i spoke to
see myself at the sky when i
pull out the cook i feel like
cub will go like a little little
marshmallow when i ah
i want lily pavel i thought they
were just like a hard plastic shoe
like come high
does the eyes their their sace this
way
valley these crocs maybe this is it
because here's the other thing we're not
going anywhere we're not seeing anybody oh
i wear sandals any day now what's
preventing us from doing it just the
humiliation sure yeah joe gets her spouse's
hayes i'll get him in those crocs
in a second no i don't see
the face and i want to see
the that's a reference to this
a voice life oh i liked quoting
you quoting shot opener yeah you are
phrasing about anthony day you lined up
the arroyo grande a sick why my
person in line why opening day to
you why do you remember why do
you care what is i remember where
i saw every movie
every movie is that you're like um
especial like vero luana one yeah no
one cares and and and my wife
tests me on it she goes what
about this movie and i tell her
and she goes okay like boring yeah
but for some reason the theatrical experience
so why who wouldn't take your word
for it i remember i'm gonna challenge
that i remember why
if i saw something in theaters like
if i watched a movie oh yeah
some things but i don't remember it
was opening night it was like tobar
two it was two thousand and three
you know i actually don't think it
was opening night because at the time
i was in theater school and probably
could have only seen it on a
weekend or a monday so it was
probably a saturday but of opening weekend
like god i see why coop
gives up yeah hi everyone i'm scott
harbin hi everybody i'm all of tonkin
hi everybody i'm lauren left this is
three m of course yes paul you
were gonna say yesterday i was ah
on the set i was on sir
me yesterday
but it feels like it was two
days ago
what does our true it was a
long day and i still feel like
it's going on yeah i woke up
at five thirty am and when i
woke up went to sleep at two
thirty oh no that that by my
math that's three hours of sleep it's
not no oh meaning you are up
until two thirty two thirty last
oh windies go to bed the previous
night that's what i'm interest previous night
i took a little sleep gummy oh
okay sleep gummy cbt gummy easy
maybe more t actually no th i
guess their th stop saying letters psi
checks one one three eight copy artless
i will have a teeny bite of
one of those that i'm like a
fucking stone out of my gourd i
don't know over i don't have trouble
getting to sleep i have trouble because
i'd just wake up after but i
wake up at like
five am no matter what well last
night i was up really late because
for whatever reason who knows o crying
and ah so i was up till
like twelve fifteen that's late for me
and yeah because oh yeah because we
were texting yeah and and cool upset
it was like you haven't been latest
i've ever seen it yeah and i
still woke up at
at four thirty and then i was
like no let me get poorly thirty
yeah and then five thirty pretty much
so and then six thirty and then
seven thirty all the thirties because she
kept hitting snooze i usually those things
will like they're good for helping you
go to sleep yeah which the fuck
to sleep go to my favorite book
look but i was i was i
had the feeling of i it wasn't
i couldn't sleep i think i always
have trouble sleeping before an early call
oh yeah i'm so anxious about us
missing about being bad yeah in the
show yes yeah do i act
oh mommy but i i so i
had the feeling of being mildly high
and not also anxious like being sleepy
but not falling asleep which is more
at
hey so wait so you got to
set let's break this down there was
a film buff that was on the
side one of the people i was
working with was mentioning was referencing a
lot of films mentioning films and what
they remind you of my character for
how many bags mainland that was more
and that was so funny oh thanks
things go on in georgia i know
food's great
um no this is somebody who i
never thought about anyone that was the
person was not being annoying it was
just when they would reference these films
they would ask they would like we
would talk about movies and i realized
oh i have seen that movie i
don't remember anything about it yeah yeah
absolutely i know i saw that movie
i thought
and i'm like that too i don't
remember this boy's life i remember ah
leo dicaprio suddenly like being older in
the middle of it that was very
striking it's the movie about it's about
a guy with an abusive stepfather it's
ah yeah it was based on a
memoir written by tobias wolff who's a
who's a well-known author yeah well but
usually i play that like
it's amazing it's crazy how he types
yeah he he built a special
ooh it's like those cars for little
people well what's fascinating about it is
that he created a typewriter that has
four big paws yes yeah keep your
project but the space on the angle
with which he touches it and actually
well it's like a bad it's like
one pad contains like a fourth of
all the known words yeah and he
just has to keep it until it
gets to the yeah yeah it's like
dna diving bell it's like diving firefly
it's like diving note the t nine
terminator nine
that's all i can think about
nine other ninety one before the tip
to nine movies yet terminator ah they
have the right terminator terminator two terminator
three i was called terminator two now
i'm back yeah well that was probably
the tackle journeys back i am back
i am i when i say you
one million dollars from the tagline was
he's back yeah alright i'll google it
do you know there's certainly i would
love to take a million dollars from
you
so you accept the bet oh yeah
well no i'm not betting a million
dollars that he don't just have to
give it to you oh for those
bets where you have different completely different
terms yeah i just don't find anything
and you bet i'm good if i'm
wrong i'm just wrong if you're on
you owe me a million dollars it's
so worth it to me
tagline is and you're not gonna like
this this time there are two ah
that might be in our tina huh
oh no here in america it's it's
nothing personal it's nothing personal was the
first one personal or something where people
in danger of taking the term bitter
personal also the
a that's the antithesis of every of
the stakes in any movie like this
time it's personal
that was the jaws three right that
was just three d yeah jaws was
doing nothing jon snow oh just for
the war was the one where it
was about her fanboy i saw jaws
three d in texas things what my
my grandfather let me see yesterday was
not in texas it took place on
the
buddy passes nih grant but can i
please go see well okay my my
father was sick for a whole year
or summer or something so idyllic so
i spent i spent respectful i spent
one year father was rad for over
a year
so i spent one year of of
junior high like you spent yeah like
couch danny and i was in high
school yeah
it wasn't couch surfing it was just
like going to different family friends or
relatives and spending a week or two
put on their couches yeah don't don't
try to avoid it that is what
that is doe but i do remember
in one of those trips spending it
with a church friend and they had
to walk jesus and
i put on headphones for the walkman
for the first time and i turned
on kiss fm and it played michael
jackson's don't stop til you get enough
you literally have to bring him evidence
and then i'm like your life sounded
so fucking good literally heading your anyone
what is this i'd only put on
headphones hero once before and he does
music
i'd only put on headphones once before
when my cousin um when i went
to go visit my cousin she had
like a hi-fi this is in probably
nineteen eighty or seventy nine and she
i fall she had like a hi-fi
system and she goes check this out
and she put headphones on my ears
and she played turning to stone garden
state much ever heard this
um but you know how like awesome
turning to stone sounds in the part
where it's up
shallow i don't know that song yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah turned to stone
the electric lights oh where in there
had that part where all the instruments
treat yourself and i was like holy
shit this sounds awesome i never put
on headphones and maybe feel like i
was in a mental asylum put the
song on but so i put on
these headphones and and don't stop till
you get enough was awesome and then
i also remember seeing the st elsewhere
ah ah season finale there with the
snowglobe i'd never seen an episode of
the show but i saw the family
where now now we're just remembering things
that you oh i'm telling you like
i remember from zhan week those and
other place to do it i also
like me they did a snow globe
but it was a special additional holiday
she didn't download it illegally online to
watch it no i didn't join ham
was any man i know oh i
did see that see
i've seen it twice but um ok
but i also saw the rudolph the
red-nosed radar over him stand wait they
knew him he speak came over one
day wow did he think you were
yellow huh what was the first time
you put on headphones what happened my
point is
that i stayed i don't think i
remember oh i stayed in touch with
my grandfather he took us to texas
he took us to the carlsbad caverns
of for a couple of day he
flew us there in a helicopter because
he was a pilot as well as
my dad and we find harley's yeah
yeah
i don't think ever said that yeah
he's a hell a year he wasn't
a college or piety in vietnam he
said if you want to pile it
ebay
tommy okay talking about vietnam so you
should probably start white rabbit
oh um yeah so legs you nineteen
sixty seven one boo baby oh my
dad signed up for helicopter pilot training
before he got drafted because he knew
everyone was going to get drafted so
he was like if i remember yea
if i get in early and often
um i can
can i count up a pilot instead
of just being like an infantry person
so he was a pilot he my
grandpa was a pilot in world war
two really as was mine cool my
dad was yonder navy guy in world
war two wonder if they were buddies
that would be weird if i were
buddies crazy i've ever known we would
never know because we found an old
picture
or what if they had a secret
affair hey why would be insane
i would love it
um no we basically related because like
if they could've they would've had us
as babies but we went to carlsbad
caverns and my grandfather was so tired
i remember him always taking breaks oh
i hate these caverns yeah he was
so tired to walk around at one
point it was like you guys just
go ahead i'm just going to stay
here they have slag tights and slag
mines of course they had both of
them here there's a phrase someone
taught me once to remember and i
always mess it up stalag might fall
upon you but a slag tight is
fucking tight because it's on the ground
oh it was like slag tights might
grow from the ceiling but they don't
know that it
i don't know i don't say but
i don't think it's ah i remember
reading the the phrase the pace of
about still lag mites and select tights
when i was seven in a spiderman
comic and i always remembered it but
i've forgotten it this point still like
i'm gonna look it up slags look
it up mites might be the ones
you like just allow me it's all
based on i like yes to lag
tides it's a tight squeeze squeeze as
to when i used to lag or
not okay wait this is interesting oh
finally guys stakes have been raised on
this about fourteen minutes in we finally
really i think many people
will find this exactly not interesting but
i do think it's interesting the difference
and this isn't really a fun phrase
but it's a thing the difference is
that a stalactite hangs from the ceiling
while a stalagmite rises from the floor
a mnemonic device popular among schoolchildren holds
that the sea and stalactite stands for
ceiling while the g and stalagmite stands
for ground another use
vol one is hang tight so still
like tights go from the ceiling it
doesn't feel like either of those are
the one that i learned hey curious
they're not they're not why do they
have to have different fucking ne you're
not going to your clock saying say
yes it's like oh that looks like
this but up there i'm sorry to
say we're like wandering around aves all
day
yeah we expect geology i literally had
to leave
i have a mala polisher in my
home i literally love fool's gold
whoever whoever gets really upset has to
jump pool
ah and swim away if you get
really you have to jump the bullets
that's the role you got really upset
yeah yeah we don't have producer kevin
away yes swim around the corner to
another body of water somehow we don't
have producer kevin anymore he's no longer
working on the show he hates us
yeah we haven't produce
acer josh who's not here not here
but we're in our back room
we ate him and we ate him
josh we don't hate you but we
did eat you we loved you your
delicious it tasted like marshmallow crock so
you still lacked the pudding i thought
you said still lag marshmallow there's still
eg types like my still like marshmallow
stalag mites might grow from
the ceiling but they don't that's what
it is i guess my point was
that my grandfather got so tired oh
yeah and didn't want to deal with
us that while we convinced him that
we could go see an r rated
movie and he just gave up and
was like yeah we'll drop you off
when we were not allowed i mean
i was eleven or twelve hours of
war that's the bag o c a
kid i don't give a shit at
the best to go to an already
movie when you're too young oh my
god that's absolutely sneak in my parents
let me see cujo because they they
would go see an r rated movie
occasionally and then deem whether it was
okay for us to see and that
was just based on violence so if
it was that was the only thing
i was the only thing it was
violent it was fine and
the same thing with like fine i
get that's not worth nine you save
it was to find if there was
sex it was bad what about swear
words swear words i think they would
get upset and at an f word
but i also think you were able
to say f words in pg movies
at the time when you know you
could say asshole on bravo and i
find that pretty shocking who's been saying
asshole is
everyone jane lynch just set it on
bravo wayne lynch on watch what happens
live who's that bravo andy cohen is
yeah like shown his asshole or something
i guess he's smashing this out it
was free to say then because you
saw one who swam know but i
everyone can say asshole on most tv
yeah you can say it on cable
but like they said shit shit show
on cnn recently and
when dana bash said it she's like
well we're on cable we can say
this it's a little impolite but that
debate was a shit show well it's
like if you're gonna give so many
caveats to it i'm like just don't
say it yeah i don't like people
like forgive me for saying this but
i just have hearted me that really
you fuck you you bitch well yeah
duh you already you already gave yourself
enough time to think of different way
words i swear because i can't i'm
i'm thinking too fast you don't like
it's just happening i if i'm giving
myself the time i'm not going to
or i'm apologizing in advance i could
change the work and i tell you
something that drives me crazy and it
is not from a not from a
level of prudery but
kurt when people curse so much on
like a thing where you're not allowed
to curse so much and there's constant
bleeping yeah it's like no one that's
fine for the studio audience that got
to hear that word but it's irritating
to me as a viewer if it's
just constant yeah leaping it's like a
grade that's like you're writing it
it come up with a better thing
so i don't have to listen to
know every i mean we would do
it on bang but we were allowed
five curse words never never what they
called the fcc which was fuck clinton
cock sucker um but we were allowed
as a little intense it's a little
intensive smoker i feel like condo would
become less intense
it's yeah yeah i think people are
going whatever but we were allowed three
or five as i recalled before we
had to bleep him and so if
we ever and we just wrote it
without thinking about bleeps but if we
ever had more than three then became
the discussion of which of these is
funnier bleeped yeah and which are like
yeah when you can't do believe and
that's very sparing
only which i think is fine everyone's
one other b show where we curse
six times though and it would be
like oh fuck which which of these
three we bleep i don't know i've
never seen the show oh what is
the show yeah um when they were
talking about sounds intriguing last year and
you made it last year whenever it
was when they were talking about shithole
countries
ys ah because hunt trees yeah but
they they said it was when the
story first broken they were like ah
he called them shit pardon us for
saying this but shithole countries and then
they started abbreviating into s hold that
drink anytime i heard it i thought
they were saying asshole asshole asshole yes
whole country yeah effing asshole which is
just worse to say oh by the
way if trump said the war is
what you're saying he said shithole countries
near quoting him you can quote that
that president said that you'd deprive like
a quota i feel like you should
be able to go he said shithole
countries on the penny abraham lincoln i'm
saying said it is edit
do you think he ever did it
out or did it happen after he
was um dead were you gonna say
born yeah yeah um we are talking
about r rated movies that we've seen
lauren woes your first r-rated movie do
you remember um you know i definitely
got to see a lot
out of um stuff that i probably
shouldn't have seen but i remember my
fave when my when an already movie
i remember this movies art ah but
tell me tell me what i had
to sneak to see this um scream
scream zarya yeah i went with friends
and we had to sneak in i
don't know how we did it i
guess we missed about tickets for a
different thing
yeah i wouldn't put on that which
was amazing to me three i loved
that movie so much it's a good
mood i tell you what happened when
i went scream three know i went
to the theater which was the galaxy
which i don't know if you recall
the galaxy but aleksey know they're turned
into to the knitting factory i believe
and yeah now it's not there anymore
yeah
but i went to the galaxy and
i went early because i like to
sit on the aisle because of my
long legs and i like to be
able to kind of stretch them into
because you wanted to get a really
good subvert the siskel and ebert that's
right yeah why because they would surely
say you gave us the aisle so
yes oh six i'd be like if
they show up fuck em fuck you
you guys look like the number ten
i love we've talked about this
i bet probably but i love the
um the videos of them fighting have
yeah there's so oh when they're doing
like the promos classic they used to
like to say like well even though
they fight they have such respect for
each other but i think that was
bullshit know and they're so funny being
mean to each other those yeah larry
to where they can't help but laugh
yeah like yeah those things clearly
advise each other yeah you gotta find
a clue i mean it's truly a
wow finally after i talk about screen
three okay um and roger ebert is
devastating like you know he's slam dunks
cisco i gotta say since guess fucking
mean to but he doesn't have the
those big killer oh wait yeah he
just like he's like alibaba and then
like up in mop then like keywords
like
a slam dunk thing goes popping oh
my god like he has like laugh
like he can't believe people find it
yeah yeah um so i'm i'm sitting
there on the isle silliest good i'm
sitting there on the i'll see probably
five seats from the front or something
i got there early enough to get
it and this dude wearing like all
black golf kind of ah clothes comes
up to me and goes like hey
man there's a group of us ah
fifteen or twenty or whatever i'm us
goth and we were all hoping we
could get an entire aisle here so
i'm wondering if like would wait like
they would all line they would all
sit in the aisle no they would
not denial i mean with a row
yes sorry so
the roaches are weird that's a mistake
like if all of you if you're
in a group sit behind each other
huh yeah no blocking are likely to
be like other yeah dumb part and
this is before reserve seating if you
recall um came into our reserves i
don't know how it in some ways
like it in some ways it's a
bit of yeah we're so much
stress going to a movie you remember
paul buy or reserve member i'd have
to do better sitting in la
ooh makes you bigger
you had to ko his you know
if you are gonna get a seat
no i mean when especially when we
would go in a group with like
thirty people well yeah that isn't that
so much so many times connor was
ah batman and robin yeah fine life
it is fine too but so this
guy wants me to move to like
a non-ideal seat um you know somewhere
else
he's like there's plenty of open seats
that way we just want this entire
row and i go oh sorry man
i got here early so i could
get this i'll see this is the
one i want he goes cool cool
cool alright and then five minutes goes
by and he comes back and he's
like hey man just you know the
theaters filling up and all of it
is you know it's
just not available but this row still
open i'm really i think it would
really help us out if you would
just move to another scene i go
ah that i you know the thing
is is i got here early on
like you so and this is the
one i want to fight i know
this is the one way it goes
cool cool cool cool
five minutes later he comes back and
goes alright i'm gonna tell you a
secret
it's for marilyn manson
oh my god and i go yeah
not a fan and he was cool
and that was the last labour yeah
see and then did you see marilyn
come in i did not care i
based the name on airline i've never
thought oh that's the strangest thing it's
not a guy's day what does the
real name who's really this br
rye which is perfect what if he
came in and you said hi brian
i saved you see
sir brian manson he used to leo
his i forgot his last name brian
something he used to live three doors
down from me like the bans are
yes exactly he was in three doors
down that's what i meant to say
yeah um because he remembered to live
i lived on level forty one and
he lived one level up from me
oh that's right level forty two
my name is brian hugh warner that's
right brian warner yeah hugh warner b
h w o six one i say
i thought he was like really tall
because he's so willowy or is it
joe is dating really small when when
you there's also that when you envision
six feet to envision him now instead
of me y'all picture marilyn manson laying
down marilyn manson's when i picture six
vi
picture um myself or my dad my
dad six five my last episode you
pictured me well it's a lie
you lie
i remember him yeah drakes him great
guy great guy you la
good guy alright well i will take
a break i'm on my first r-rated
movie fuck why does right continue to
happen oh yeah being the middle child
of three dm know you pause too
long what was your first raid was
you paused just like a wolf hey
are you turn to lauren ask her
a question and it for me everytime
i've got to be like also here's
my ex because there's only
hi all you have to scream over
everyone don't you oh your name should
be positive tompkins should be one positive
tommy oh yeah it should be tell
us about your farm animal house yes
animal house yeah where'd one a family
friend took me to see that this
was a family friend like you to
see it by your butt just the
two of you
just the two of us yes because
he thought either he this this guy
he was a weirdo he turned me
on to the magazine national lampoon am
i mean to family friend yes how
old was the organist at our georgian
wow wow wow now it's like you're
punishing me interesting yeah for myself that's
true yeah that'll teach you okay and
so wait so it's just like hey
here is the organist church but he
edison to humor a wicked one in
fact and he liked national lampoon mag
did he know you were into comedy
or did he hope the
boobs and i would give you a
bone i think a little bit of
both owe it i hope you guys
daughter how old are you i would
have been like thirteen okay thirteen now
yeah weirdness yeah but this is a
guy that i later realized was a
horrible person well that's like checks is
a fucking racist used to tell me
like judging the n
worden and stuff like that like wow
shot huh
we might church group the guy though
our our youth leader got in trouble
for showing us trading places he showed
us trading places and was like i'm
gonna like a fast-forward through some of
the parts that you shouldn't see but
he let us basically reverse beast yeah
there was a rumor that this blackface
creepy science
teacher at my middle school once you
eddie murphy is black oh that's right
i'm sorry
that's creepy science teacher who i've met
fee is like an i've mentioned once
before but he had fair and we've
all talked about our grainy side teacher
is at you with my story he
had fared too he would let run
around in our science tables and they
would poop little like poops elliptic worms
and the rumor has it that ah
on rumour has it hornady graphy instead
of assigned city who is supposed to
show and then like was like accidentally
or on purpose that's like accidentally in
love what is the psychology behind someone
who's likely all turned on by oh
man i'm gonna show i'm like it's
literally disgusting i don't know if it
was one hundred percent true but i
believe eight minutes
it was just a crazy three minutes
in oh this is the wrong film
well there's there's usually story back then
in porto you couldn't tell
kill so is this a side film
report these people are talking what are
they talking about pizza delivery how hard
well pieces around we need to teach
their comfort rouses part of science
alright we'll be right back
alright we're back and he was like
here's maybe it's a compilation i haven't
seen it yet this is called siskel
and ebert fight about everything at the
movies um let's hear a little bit
of this room yoga merging and it's
very fun humor it's very funny if
you think it's funny this isn't the
one we were talking about murphy
wrong no do um do a siskel
and ebert or promo it's bathroom says
alex just you and ebert uncensored does
that to your neighbor it's like they're
shooting a poe he's tell you they're
shooting a commercial for the show a
promo for the show
well when i put in siskel ebert
promo what comes up vs siskel and
ebert on sensor to a promo i
know i know let's hear a little
bit of them on sensors will see
exactly yeah no that's it
i know lowering a brown is not
the parts of both the match like
sling like what are we doing now
the promo
you know what they have to match
nothing
no promo ever have imagined lover baku
welcome to the exciting world of television
i feel for you to begin to
learn
jesus lover well that's something that you
rarely hear
really paid to you that wasn't very
good well you had it but he
felt he had to keep explaining kevin
costner the pentagon thriller no way out
this week on siskel and ebert
i think you're gonna have to read
through jesus slash brain with the speed
with which he read across both stars
and titles you won't even hit that
you want to have a second half
of it
okay fine
got a little excited game and less
excited roger oh i'll be doing it
because of what you did oh i
never really gets our week on siskel
and ebert at the movies and we've
got three oh and the movie not
after movie
we're doing this wait till they say
to me we didn't say the mcdonald's
thing remember that number a week on
fifteen labor in the movies and we'd
be able to move nice and quaid
in the big evening michael caine in
the fourth protocol and kevin costner and
gene hackman in no way out fifth
week on siskel and ebert
and the movie
and the apple right
over data roger has rocked by the
way just to clear i'm not trusting
yeah whatever it's i mean really crackly
sounding and just the audio well sorry
i lied there's really funny really intense
burst of static yeah between hearsay yeah
yeah yeah great but anyway google it
you'll like it googling yeah
yeah the lead chef kevin where are
you now where in the world is
google it chef kevin we're already hearing
a little bit of one of those
aforementioned helicopters fly above i wonder if
it leave us from either of our
grandfathers from huh oh i'm assuming yes
copter ghost scepter that's not
not a bad idea yeah is it
not about e-mail it to myself okay
ghost copter ghost coast copter lay the
ghost of a helicopter not yeah not
the whomever was piloting this it's like
the flying dutchman yes exactly if there
aren't enough ghosts of inanimate things you
got flying dutchman you got you got
go
you got christine
yeah what other vehicles three thing about
a haunted bicycle
yeah laura no wanted skateboard that i
like that's cool that's so rad that's
haunted segway oh you know why didn't
you post that pic that video of
that guy skateboarding to fleetwood mac
he didn't post you just sent it
to us skateboarding to fleetwood mac where
he's like nah he you go no
it was not it was not that
he he sent us a pic of
a video of people dancing to a
tick tock of two sets of three
cowboys that were just thrusting their hips
that was different there is a video
of this guy
guy was like a shaved head on
tattoo on his head and he's like
drinking a beer and skateboarding down like
the highway and he's he's listening to
fleetwood mac and lip sinking into awesome
i have not seen that vicinity okay
please i wish you would speak to
a haunted segway see um
this segway is going to be clunky
ah very clunky but would you guys
do it's already there what did i
do for halloween it's not it's october
noel where when this comes out it'll
be afterward why can't you ask us
what will you have done for halloween
well what are you going to do
for louie
like a scary kid trying to make
friends hey boys
kid what are you going to be
for halloween well what what are you
doing for halloween hey back off you
what's your best costume while i was
a cat for like ten years running
that's a different types of cats and
we talked about yeah have but i
was a blind man on roller skates
one year that's fucking hilarious i is
that would you be cancelled for that
now
now i would and should my are
you offering yes please delete please cancel
my childhood
i wasn't i was a power ranger
ironically one year ironically as i write
because i was in fifth grade and
i thought i was too old to
watch power rangers so you thought it
was funny yeah like ah but then
of course anyone would think i just
was yeah your ten year old yes
like plus the power rangers are cool
but i thought it was funny and
um color
or what color it was yellow and
is funny this year i um i
don't think i'll be putting on a
costume that's for sure but i might
watch a lot of scary movies i
kind of want to make it the
month of halloween i bought a helloween
jury which i i love no thank
you this is my big thing i
was like i need some joy
i yeah thing that is pointless and
fun and so i got a halloween
tree it's bright orange i put um
halloween ornaments on it and it's so
nice and fun and it's just great
to turn it on every day when
the clock strikes four and i am
going to watch a bunch of scary
movies this this halloween and i'm going
to watch hocus pocus classics never sierra
so difficult
a website you know is there a
significance two to four p m um
that's what i consider nighttime now i'm
just like it's closed the blinds like
i'm kind of like oh wow winding
it down yeah you know four or
five yeah jay and i would do
when we would we would we would
call it making a cave when we
would
we will like hot days which by
the way today is one hundred times
yok tobar and whiteside anywhere out and
we're outside and he has were drinking
margaritas of course so we have no
regrets um we we would we would
remember what we started doing it but
we've started chanting kafe
okay okay that's so fun because you
but like would one person start chanting
when they wanted it to happen or
or guys gay would look at each
other and both simultaneous dad never happen
which i wish it did and that
would have been don't you love like
when you like me thinking about you
doing that is very delightful because of
course mike and i have a bunch
of weird things that we do but
you always think what does everyone else
do what you love the thing i
like you're like this so we all
do like yeah that yeah it's very
it's comforting and sweet with the cave
ah coincide with like okay now it's
time to start drinking as well
i mean yes yeah no it would
not not not minister okay because that's
what that's what i think of when
like around six thirty is when i
finally walk the the dogs and it's
time to open up a bottle
yeah i did not pull the curtains
so the sun doesn't come in let's
open up a bottle doors and loretta
la bottle i mean it seems fun
i don't really drink at home which
has been a disappointment during this time
i think i have no choice because
i've i always feel like i'll have
a drink if i'm out with friends
like dinner whatever you're not a big
drinker never
strikes me to go i should have
a drink at home i just don't
think of it there's nothing else to
do no but then the times that
i have done it i'm like i'm
having fun like it's like obviously but
like i just find i just never
think about it's so nice like i
had fun for one i'm like oh
i'm having fun now containing i do
that to our podcast on friday nights
and we know funny we have
dinner and then we have a drink
while we record the podcast and it's
it's very it's really enjoyable it's very
pleasant it's very pleasant yeah but there's
nothing else to do during quarantine bud
drinker eat well there's also watching a
ton of tv i've been doing a
lot of that yep that's my thing
did you ever watch the haunting of
hill house i watched a lot of
it and i really liked it
i love i get scared but mike
was watching that and so i saw
certain parts that were amazing i love
scream you're gonna turn all of this
i know but all of october into
watching scary movies scream the michael jackson
sony i'm pushing me happy yeah makes
me wanna scream um i say i'm
pushing
myself to watch scary movies i usually
like hocus pocus halloween movies but i
don't think i've ever seen it but
it doesn't have a single scare does
it it's married for kids not scary
for real what will i be scary
about probably scary for you right yeah
yeah those buzzers when i saw that
ah at the westminster mall ah
when we're in the library boy that
was like one of the scariest jump
scares that large margin oh and yeah
louise when i saw that i saw
i saw pee pee in the theaters
people screaming in both of those it
was so that was one of the
that was the only time it was
fun
fun to be scared yeah like no
one saw that coming you know scared
to happen and we i laughed i
remember me and my friend mike turn
to each other we say money we
laughed we laughed for like a solid
two minutes over that that's what yeah
i mean oh it was so much
fun what about ernest goes to camp
that one scared the shit out of
me never
yeah it because of camp or was
there those are somebody just doing service
movies he there's something really scary and
somebody somebody reminds me what it was
online making remember now so it's like
something happened at night at camp it
was like some fucking boogeyman type situation
and i was just ligger man yeah
what was that guy was suppose
xd to be like a damn parody
he embarked in verona mean yeah he's
dead know what i mean he's
hello one of that one here is
is it his work well it's one
of the weirdest characters that started off
in a car commercial yeah it was
it was local car commercials out here
in l a he just started doing
it for these commercials that's astounding right
he would talk to the camera and
be like hey you gotta go down
to ford whatever you know what i
mean vern yeah they
have great deals and they springboard that
into a successful movie french really no
word return really is confusing to me
as there was a national soda campaign
first he did speakers for sprite ah
and then the movies why i think
he was a groundling that's what i
would guess he might have been yeah
yeah wow
isn't it i mean what look there's
so many different ways to get into
showbiz i love that i love that
you know i mean jim varney started
doing commercials lord left guess i also
didn't stop doing commercial
have you done commercials what commercials have
you done um i did a few
commercials before i booked my first pilot
and then i didn't do any one
know i did a couple after i
did bing dot com was my first
commercial dot com you can find online
yeah google how we yeah turn search
term animal house will find that commercial
because
that was the that was my line
in it but it was the theme
of it because it was an animal
it was a grocery that was the
first iranian movie i ever saw true
so the bing dot com commercials were
like a um sounds familiar train of
thought like ah one person says one
word that represented says what makes them
think of the deadly that kind of
thing yeah and so it's all these
people like and isaiah campbell
oh but that was my word i
worked at the grocery store and like
animal house and then i do remember
the snow yeah but i don't know
if did we know each other then
no do we know each other two
thousand and ten or eleven yeah how
long have we known each other i
think since two thousand twelve or thirteen
i would guess did we first meet
doing bang
bang together lauren yes that was the
first time i ever met you yeah
what is doing i would alien why
would we meet you did ask cat
no but i have i have a
very clear memory in my mind of
of susan hale saying you've got to
meet lauren laccase on the show oh
that's nice and thanks to that i
feel like that's why i met you
but you did ask kat and then
doug and susan was always there oh
man maybe she was like hey lauren
zinn tonight yeah oh yeah you gotta
you gotta watch her
that's that's right yeah i've been yeah
but i do remember like an email
from her or attack saying like get
lorna show susan's nice she won't want
to tie the commercially fast ok snickers
with joe pesci and don rickles wait
a minute what yeah i saw those
commercials how-tos i was one i got
a fuckin were using to play the
snicker no
i played the friend of the person
who turns into don rickles because they
got hungry hungry hold on one second
scott you know that you didn't play
the snicker and by the way there's
always just one has one it was
cool and then i shot a commercial
for jack in the box shot a
pilot and i was in a driver
i was in jack in the box
football it is
the third day or second reason something
oh god but like comedians have piot
p t s d from that i
know what that is i was i
think it was the first season of
ah might've been ya comics last comic
standing yeah there was a comedian who
did the same jokes every week and
one of them was like she came
i'm from an italian family and she
was like so i called my dad
up and i was like hey man
i shot a pilot he's like ah
get rid of all the witnesses so
i'd say that over the phone yeah
that's right god so anytime i hear
i shot a pilot
yeah wow yeah you're not allowed to
do the same jokes every week on
that show are you i mean that
seems you know no i don't it's
not around anymore but but back then
you were and and they would get
complaints like because they had comedians on
who only had ten minutes of material
yeah and they were always one and
if you win that's crazy if you
win you are like yeah
during an hour yeah but they were
they were getting people who had only
worked on ten minutes madness i remember
i i knew ah when the show
was hosted by jay moore when he
was brought into the house
you get the keys to allows the
production company was ah magical elves and
i know yeah i knew you nail
it yeah i knew those people dan
cut fourth was a friend of mine
um he still is i just haven't
seen him in forever dan i miss
you i'm these gentlemen we all miss
you um and ah there
was ah there was a a throw
to commercial ah it was like late
in the season of last comic standing
and i knew some people that were
on it so i was watching it
and there was a throw to commercial
where jay more to say like when
we come back you know do the
whoa this happens this happens and somebody
went bitter recriminations
and it was so funny to me
and i i didn't say that sometimes
just it's lauren
i'm like i've heard in my head
forever inner recrimination and i made fun
of it and dan told me he
wrote that ah he was very good
sport about it was like i wrote
that my god it's so funny
on that show bitter recrimination i like
that it's dramatic
finished my commercial for money but met
my commercial resume a bonnie orlando mayor
buddy comedy about how where are the
documentary about how women are funny um
the women are funny yes oh it
was animation to prove it yeah i
love bunny we okay gentlemen ma i
like rich everyone's great jack on the
oscars together jack
jack in the box drive thru commercial
breakfast all day i like where it's
an opera singer singing and i'm sobbing
in slow motion because my dr who
are you if you want a car
yes dear yes dear are you a
car dealer and then i did a
sierra miss commercial never aired and mean
i did i've done i stopped in
commercials but then i got to do
to like campaigns that were kind of
cool but they were only it was
great because they were really cool cause
they were only online and no one
ever saw them one was for target
and one was for i was like
them and the g was really really
hard yeah come on you're not gonna
give it up for j j j
and j g o
got it now you're talking about jay
morgan
the g one was one of those
days where like you are amazed at
what your brain can do because i
had to memorize like really difficult jargon
you amazed what your brain can do
and then an elevator and every commercial
like a series of commercials and everyone
was an elevator pitch so it becomes
like everything had to happen very quickly
and i had to stay this long
thing just by myself yeah
while the elevator was taken apart and
things were brought in and like all
the whole oh yeah and had to
be done exactly right it's like that
riki lindholm video for the jim carey
show i don't know about that the
one take vit like there's a whole
one take montage scene where they and
then they they put out a ah
making of video oh cool where like
the cameras circling the entire time and
they keep switching out the backgrounds as
like time pass wow just finished show
just kidding
yeah just it's called it's just kidding
i'm carey show just it's just kid
notes just everyone gets wrong it's just
kidding just kidding
huh
um but anyway do you guys do
commercials oh guess who sings i ah
yes this is the answer yes it'll
surprise you guess who sings american woman
lenny kravitz
i don't get it oh not good
enough we mustn't three months but isn't
some sick joe guess who sings american
open logic jo guess who's things american
oh guess who of the who what
oh who guess who things american woman
who know guess who thinks american woman
i want to kill you
i literally thought i understood what was
happening so i think the band just
the guests you know but you kept
saying ooh guess who i said and
then i said the who and then
i said who
everything's happen there that's really what transcribing
this
so so did we ever do commercial
i did i think i'd told you
about the golf industrial i did that
was the closest i ever came to
oh my god i didn't industrial once
and it was so weird but i
was really excited i don't remember the
did i not talk about it on
here i maybe i talked about it
on the rpm show or something but
i mean i definitely i think i
got my taft-hartley because of it but
smartly
lee but i i got taft-hartley from
the bing dot com commercial nice i
became sag eligible i went into a
taft heart lead from the stephanie know
what mister show i think oh really
yeah i'd have been my first thing
yeah um i went into the audition
in a hotel room no nothing weird
there will ever be weinstein two dudes
and a woman there and there sounds
like you're
dream and they were like the alia
and they were like okay there's a
lot of physical comedy in this can
you do a pratfall and i like
without thinking like did a weird trip
and fell face first into the couch
and they were like brilliant you got
the job that sounds so weird and
that was it to be losing this
couch in the commercial and then they
were
are so upset with me the entire
day because i was not funny enough
according to yeah they're like you know
some of that stuff you did in
the audition you know couldn't you like
do a funny fall hear something like
like you need to miss the the
the golf ball and go flying into
the lake like all this like weird
shit oh it was funny jessica alba
she's
my favorite female comedian she does do
fully stuff like she does yeah so
that but that was just one of
the many examples of being onset and
feeling like you are doing such a
bad job and everyone is upset at
you and and you're not giving them
what they want and they're trying to
be patient you know i had to
do the the job that i just
finished i yesterday was the hardest day
because we had a
hey so hard to stay for today
we to do there was this really
this very physical scene where sexy i
flagship physical physical let's get physical nah
i'm doing to do i'm doing the
dua lipa version oh it's not a
version it's a her own original new
rules we don't do do lipa la
ram and the new rules and unless
their kids bop verses i wonder if
there's a kids off
offering awesome it's not the song when
we think we all look this up
to continue your story um i'm hot
i had to also say oh oh
wow wow wow wow
wish one to pick up the phone
in oslo clinical oh here's i just
looked up kidz bop physical you i
think these headphones my hand um there's
videos of them getting physicals know they're
the first
the first thing that comes up is
how much do kids bop performers get
paid a dollar who thinks it's more
that's kids about performers that are googling
that yeah kidz bop talent search for
kids singers dancers pay his five hundred
dollars a day
how old is jacob from kidz bop
dream big sing la since he was
six years old jacob has always dreamed
of performing onstage he can't believe his
dreams are coming true he cannot wait
to go on the kidz bop world
tour this year so record songs shoot
little videos point of course meet the
amazing kids put together from their base
to english centre fifteen one
um i cannot find a version of
physical like gun fire yesterday i had
to just play this saturday i had
kids pop up yesterday oh that would
be good this is dance monkey i'll
just play this on her any to
do this just fine yesterday and the
problem was was that i'm in very
terrible shape
say i am the heaviest i've ever
been um it's very depressing and ah
makes me i've to fight against self-loathing
all the time but this way you
feel your routine that are you talking
about yeah yeah didn't do this scene
where um you know me and this
other guy is
circling each other in a fight i
also had to take my shirt off
and wear a tank top oh no
she was i think i would turn
it down just from that in the
past i did things like that when
i was when i was younger in
fact they wanted to eat everything lately
got a naked baby from the nirvana
nevermind skyler and grown-up
jimmy kimmel once and i was like
oh no with your new account
with a little dick out they wanted
him to show that it's likely the
same you got a little dick right
you'd be shocked by how some things
haven't changed so we had to do
multiple takes of this thing the kids
up split going to multiple takes of
this thing and it was not the
thing that was so mortifying for me
and everyone
one was fine like nobody was i
wasn't holding things up or anything but
i it was so non taxing you
know what i mean i was having
i was struggling with what did you
do we circle each other to all
his dialogue and then i rushed the
guy and the idea is i'm very
drunk and so the
guy just like gently takes my shoulders
and guides me down to the floor
it was it's funny really funny and
i instantly pass out i'm like as
soon as as soon as he touches
me i just pass out and i
just go down i just slowly gently
go down to the floor
but i would like when i would
get depending on how i landed
it would be like i'd be out
of breath and it was i was
so i had to fight so hard
to not just be full of self-loathing
it's like no you have to do
your job and you'll do that you
have to be good at it and
you have to be funny and the
character can't be self-loathing current healthcare can't
say i hate myself hey down here
i don't like myself
right now and of course that's the
day that the set photographers there and
like as soon as my shirt came
off it was like just yesterday you
would you pose for me and i'm
like so yep i will do it
news photographer like hey you know what
i'd rather not of course i could
have of course i couldn't that's the
that's what it is to be an
actor i feel like oh hey look
this is where i am right now
i have to it's not it's not
her fault that i'm in the shade
she doesn't fucking know me you know
what he means do they give you
photo approval can you kill certain photos
i probably could
you know but what's the point i'm
not going to like any i now
who knows you know even put it
anywhere lot of times those pictures don't
even yeah go anyway i think that
all the time like where pictures end
up now reserving the blazers for the
yeah during turns movie you know there
were quite a few that they took
and i killed a few but then
you know one that sucks is like
the new york times oh yeah
you know before i've killed a few
but it's like this situation it's like
these are the only pictures they're taking
of me yeah so it's fine but
it was i it was a really
internal thing because it was making me
i was like i can't let it
affect like my memory of the lines
i can't let it get in the
way can't be
practice i have to fuckin forget about
it i have to just let it
go and do it get about it
forget about it i thought oh definitely
like i need my head to be
in a bathing suit it's a year
thinking about all these things like yeah
great now i have to walk from
there to there and now it's the
same mobile but it's like it's too
much to you how do you just
have to not think about it but
then that's that's like a
strength it is so like it's like
a muscle you like it's ok i
don't care what i have to make
yeah yeah you guys should just write
your own shows and star in that
and then just be making and be
like see what do you want this
is what i really want i thought
about that when i watched the wrong
missy because i i of course instantly
think what if i had to do
that yeah what if i had to
be
in a bathing suit but i don't
know it's it's also it's harder for
me to have sympathy for people yeah
i haven't been sin and being fat
it's harder for me totally i get
it but i'm saying like even then
like you're still thinking like of quot
while i hope everything stays in the
right spot or like i don't get
big
a wedgie when i get out of
the pool or something's in the right
spot what it's gonna be great when
mccabe suits or something and you're like
oh great ah because i also had
a crowd to the top of ah
jeff pearson's head in a bathing while
i was in a bathing suit and
i'm like crouching by his head you
know i'm just like very nice well
i will save i don't remember you
being in a bathing suit gray so
it did
it wasn't like it was like shocking
or anything yeah it was a one
piece it wasn't you know like when
manila your friends yeah what nude scene
in a thing or whatever you're like
ooh i shouldn't seem that or whatever
yeah um i don't remember when you
don't know about it like when you
don't know all of a sudden of
a person you know is going to
be new item well that was like
leia louis c k in his own
show
it's like you're writing yourself nude in
your own show mate you're making me
look at your but why would that
guy to that oh my god we
gotta we gotta take a break wow
you really walked into that cool your
back
welcome back and pick all you have
commercial experiences don't you yes the hanging
chad of the previous segment of course
yes florida looks like a chad doesn't
know what do you think a little
chat don't you put your florida zoo
pixel flow
there were schindler oh chad chad
yeah that was the monsoon season
daz daz disco disco jazz
was when we were doing that movie
wasn't there a guy named brad or
something and and i was onside going
brad brad also also chad or something
like over what it was wow that
sounds familiar which which movie was remember
the movie that our friends directed the
the i is is set in a
strip club my scenes yeah
yeah and tell me that i had
to do like a majorly touching like
it wasn't in the script oh by
the way you're gonna go like take
the bottle away from the main character
and be really concerned and so every
other thing i'd shot i'd been doing
really like sarcastically and like with a
weird character and then they were like
oh by the way you have to
be really this is the emotional core
of the movie it was like
it's little schizophrenia performance i'd ever given
but you also had to drive in
it and there's a really funny school
where a car pulls up and paul
had never driven before so cars just
like basically coasting in and then suddenly
brakes so hard like straight shutters to
all and and it's just joel
lt's oh it was more people so
there was a screening of people laughed
yeah people left it was on top
of the ah more mosa for me
all covered with i was just spaghetti
covered with what is it she's she's
i it was on top of the
formosa on top of the formosa was
where the at least the party was
the the screening was at that theater
sort of over by it's no longer
there but it was like there was
a second level to the foremost well
there's a roof and so yeah oh
yes yes right that was my first
screen kiss ooh with whom ah some
lady yeah i don't remember in any
case i sang that song so i
did
i did two commercials one for the
ford focus where i was the voice
of an orange puppet that the commercials
were very funny with me and john
ross bailey that's how i met him
ah and we bonded instantly became friends
forever um but i was only the
voice because i
i did i was not a puppeteer
and i think the people producing the
commercial thought i could just pick up
this very specific skill in a in
a weekend like they sent me to
sort of puppet boot camp where i
learned why like puppets don't have suits
because they don't have some to my
legs dangle over why not just record
you
your lines and then have the puppet
match them
i did on the dark crystal that's
what they did in the dark crystal
man hey well we will making the
dark crystal one pill hey very johar
and a buddy people in college sigh
yeah grandma the vois little um does
viagra make you horny or just makes
you dig god can i
you may actually learn something like i
don't feel anything vulgar like what the
fuck i can't tell you something that
i'm trying to please your forty things
i'm trying to clear from my memory
the time he used bags so much
so you're excluding um i was talking
to my mom the other day because
she wanted to update her like medical
information on some website of
like for soldiers taking viagra well no
she was like going through all of
her medication i had to end it
because she doesn't know how to do
computers so she was going through all
of her medications the milligrams the dosage
how often she takes it and then
she was like can you do it
for dad too and i was like
ok sure and we went through all
of the stuff on the very last
one was viagra
ah whatever milligrams when needed i was
like okay and i i was dying
inside because i wanted to say something
so bad i was like right that
is entered wow that's so that's so
it's a prophecy so much to me
that she told you that and you
act like that was fine and you
just moved on i would not be
able to pay wouldn't be able to
go thing i i feel like i
said was like boy i'm going like
sick or something but like also good
for you but
try way like i don't want i
don't want to see that also yeah
i tried to be an adult about
i was like yeah great okay alright
that's good i'm just helping you
ah if i had to do that
to be very surprised oh well especially
these days mom do all the dads
is apparently cheating on you and the
local ah um so you're a puppet
boot camp so well i'm a puppet
camp and it's very obvious that i
can't there's no way i'm gonna just
be able to do this so
you gotta shoot the first commercial and
i'm trying to do it i'm doing
a terrible job of crash but it
suppose to be a press conference i'm
crouched behind this podium like a potato
real grouch but
what do you call puppeteers who ah
dough too late as crash potatoes but
since you are lazy we call puppeteers
watching tv all day on the couch
across potato what
please you please stop bothering me sir
i'm trying to check out
at the grocery store
so i were doing and it's also
improv so these take the right take
is just going on and on and
on and eventually i have to say
um i can't do this anymore like
fucking are i can't do it yeah
it takes yeah your arms have to
be super strong
for that specific you hey shut up
mushroom memory and stamina that just comes
you know that's not something you'd pick
up in forty eight hours at a
boot camp there was a cool idea
i'll get into boot camp in bust
magazine recently about smaghi muss toe you
not familiar with feminist winnings or anyone's
minds horn it's bus
as with big tits but it's um
it's a magazine but they had a
section about an article about female puppeteers
from sesame street and it was so
cool to see i wonder if your
friend was in it wasn't she in
sesame street or no i don't know
i don't believe anything in my friend
maria ah
she lives i just met a girl
named maria maybe it's the same one
i'm gonna girl name or yeah lives
on one two threes doesn't mean i'm
we we enders a green monster we
have to play reacher if that's okay
this is our final segments that we
were gonna play three churches we if
that's okay we have to be overlay
thing okay so
this is called this sent to us
by josh the name of it is
this essentially josh
this closer just sensuous by josh he
sent to something called a secret just
read emails from john secret were hymns
secret word okay okay one of us
thinks of us any word and and
and as we've played this before jay
in the english language in the english
language
but also it can be like two
words like big bird or it has
it's just a thing like you have
to become you know her name proper
name keyword it can be whatever it
is it can be a sentence one
of us thinks of that word then
another one of us says any word
okay the person who thinks of the
secret word keeps it to themselves the
one of us says n
any word and then we go around
clockwise saying whatever word that makes us
think of
and the person with the secret word
is trying to steer it so one
of us says word okay and and
if that happens they win otherwise if
we take too long or if we
repeat a word then we're out and
give that same one march right down
our secret word i think we can
be honest about it unless i think
you're gonna forget i need to hear
the structure of the game again okay
okay so why am i literally here's
what goes i i'm thinking of a
word and the word is giraffe got
it and then y then the one
of us like i say any other
word because you don't know that i
thought that yeah i think of any
other word which let's say leaf and
then i go was tr
three i was gonna say to do
yeah but we're trying to be we're
trying to get anyone to say that
secret was a person who thinks of
the secret word is trying to lead
us into saying like so i would
eventually like bamboo and then you'd be
like lee panda and then that you'd
be like oh eucalyptus and then i'd
be like
animals just like password essentially yes sort
of let's just play it you gotta
you gotta just play but if we
take too long or if we repeat
something that someone's already said we're out
fancy other way to win is if
the other two people get out okay
alright so who wants to think of
the secret word
me okay you say you what you
i think lauren should because paul still
does not think you're getting yeah yeah
i get i completely get it
you went from my mind was wondering
do i completely get it yeah because
the first time what's big
you gotta just like an existing game
you always hear word of god you
got the secret word yeah i got
the secret word okay you say yeah
or maybe i should start terrelle guess
i get it
i'll start so that paul is the
third and will will go clockwise okay
um
i'm just now i'm thinking i'm looking
around at things that are in my
life smoking doesn't matter i can say
moo okay to we know where he
wants us to go different other
you're taking too long bird what is
other what is bird have to do
oh i get it now now see
so you're learning you're gonna try to
steer us but it can't be that
yeah yeah i guess anything can sound
ah okay i'll know the three to
sounds starting expect okay and let me
go into my head where you're starting
it and you have this you know
mean i have to go we're going
you're okay which means paul will start
the secret word is in my head
now paul you start by saying any
word
ah fear frightened scare
terror scream surprise
shock awe
joy
happiness
gun
flower drum
song
musical
theatre boards
um congratulations boards i congratulate you on
board of a theater or something i'm
treading the boards oh i didn't know
what you meant but anyways what i
said
okay congratulations to paul
cheers coach
um gatorade
thirst trap
um lower
catfish
what's that guy's name neil schulman ne
yes dancing with the stars he's on
it
wow
carole baskin
tiger
king lion jungle
um growth
tree leaf
plants
soil
dirt garden secret
wall
roses
thorns bush
grass green
kermit
miss piggy
muppet show
love
paul rust
killing jacobs romance
sweetheart
cool op
valentine s day
garry marshall you know you're trying to
get to the word of a certain
point right like no we're not oh
you're not want us to pay okay
gary marshall yep um
ah new year's day
you too
pride
ah what's it called um float
from the movie pi folks
from a price parade
junior high
what else floats this is a whole
series of fall you're out oh wow
come on what did you say you
say so you got so well if
you and if i say okay we'll
keep going anyway singer's what she thinks
thinks ah faucets
water
drip
paul
yeah sla beatles
ah the rolling stones mick
um ah every rose has it's thorn
almost one i want to learn to
be out because of that time sorry
music
ah cliff
um beauty
mole
awesome powers
um daisies
like you know the kind of flying
ravi yeah baby
a gift shower clean
fresh
powder blue
colorful rainbow
roy g biv
um
hey i don't know what do you
mean no no no you can't say
no no no and you'll find what
i give up that nice yeah is
that yeah rules you can't say no
no no for more time
okay the word was do you know
what you want where i was trying
to lead you like why use you
you kind of your eyes got very
wide when we were in the plants
yes section well he's the i shoe
this you got the glasses on because
her eyebrows lifted up she was like
ah okay oh okay
close we got very close at some
point yeah very continued were you ever
trying to lead us to bouquet from
something else yes but i feel like
i was trying to get you say
flowers which roses yeah okay i like
i mean maybe it's not the most
gripping thing to listen to or maybe
it is i don't know it's gotta
be but i do like this game
let's play one more round it's kind
of alright i know
oh i understand okay do you want
this or think of the secret word
okay so then i don't want everyone
to make fun of me because i
get the game now okay so then
i will be the one to start
but i sort of think you should
want to guess the secret word like
me it would be fun you write
like fun but i'm not saying that
it's us like don't don't fight against
it i wasn't fighting
yeah we're purely trying to keep the
game going okay i found it pausing
i wanna roy g biv yeah yeah
that's all i want to make clear
yeah okay so i'll say the first
word which is incorporation trademark
mascot tiger
um football
rain delay umpire
out
outside
indoors
um tv
shh magazine
oprah
um cars
walk king talking
um ah
like newscaster
alright
um female
woman
lady girl baby
um
ah david
crying crying rain delay oh wait you're
no rain delay was already said not
delay oh i was talking about tom
delay as well i was doing jeopardy
rules using crying crying ah pouring
water drip
that was from previous game protection condom
umbrella yes huh
umbrella was your word yes how did
we get there
through all the things we just said
but i know i'm interested that mascot
you said oh i was thinking morton
salt when
somebody said advertising yeah trademark trademark um
oh mascot yeah we interest to the
more kind of way and i was
going in the football category kind of
and then trying to stay there but
and how did we get to umbrella
where were the last things we said
it was like rolling protection condom are
you always trying to steer it towards
rain
aip stuff as well or i was
trying to steer it towards rain stuff
and the more than girls like little
girl stuff outside um the real question
is why would me saying umbrella make
use a condom know you know i
said no why would me saying condom
okay so is brian he said this
is why we shouldn't try to get
his water protection his umbrella now he
said prof
section and i said condom with daughter
drip no shana here you're doing it
on what i say not on what
the umbrella is the condom of the
so i can only go up the
last word yes okay condom is the
deck and i feel like there is
a joy i'm getting you know it
was great i'm just saying that you
cheated and usually wrong
eating it's prying is the umbrella of
the dick i agree ball that continously
umbrella of the day okay and again
again again scott you think of the
word i'll think of the word okay
i have the word and lauren you
have to start it's gotta be bird
i'm looking at it right now
nail polish oh remover
um acid um burn
pain
hypodermic needle
piano i know it's serious
ah polk
ah prod cattle
cow moo noise
the sound shatter glass that's it really
us okay we're na right now i
want to do it again okay well
that's good because you're turning mine those
years now it turns out with a
single word okay okay and paul starts
yeah
boy that wow i'm proud of myself
but see it was fun when i
got it it was fun but i
i was intentionally trying to going like
oh if he says something about only
one word i'll say shattered okay so
you had that point i couldn't but
no i couldn't say shattered unless he
said something that related to shattered right
okay true alright okay okay okay let
me just
really let me just really think about
this okay don't think of to harder
work well i just want to think
why i'm looking at you know yeah
yeah okay um okay it is ah
it is ah nigga but you did
okay i gotta gotta gotta get all
right paul you start with anywhere oh
right i think it was even word
i forgot that she was me
alright let's say what you just say
what you're thinking coconut
never would of gotten that noggin
head bonk conch crash smash hulk
ah punch kick throw
ah
lose win
award
top
i was gonna say more but that's
i can't say one word top a
plus
fail
ah die
barry
six
wheels
trick yeah whoa wait so six guys
goes to wheels well i it's like
yeah nah i know truck from that
like a ceo but hi paul what
do you think you think that's cheating
i don't think it's dating
there's no logical reason why i would
say six and you would say well
if i'm only thinking about trucks i'm
thinking stop haha can we also thinking
about trucks for scotch isn't like how
i play ok paul you've got one
chance to get it right or he
is gonna go ape shit and dump
jumping in this pool jump into the
pool okay swim away
okay paul okay
coconut okay yeah you're thinking you're thinking
of the word and i have to
start okay guard button so
needle thread
whole
escape room
door lock key
a whole iso already um oh you're
out ah shit that's me and paul
i bet you're happy
alright so me and also the goal
paul is for either me to pause
too long or for me to say
your secret word and my goal is
for you to pause too long right
okay so where where did we pick
it up i said yeah la what
did i say lock or
or key you said key because you
just said whole record and you'd repeated
yeah ok so i said key
ah hole can i say oh no
your eyewear right oh come on alright
alright key um
i'm trying to think okay key
bars chocolate
candy
eat
starve
emaciated
prisoner as gabon
turf
surf
ah
ah point break swayze
ah alright p
tear
oh i get you um
and wow what was your word cage
wow posted we get i feel like
we owe with close to you said
fucking chocolate because of bars sorry you
know why you guys fuck this game
and fuck you splash
um that's gonna wrap it up for
this episode guys thank you so much
for listening i hope your week is
going okay yeah yeah yeah hope everyone
you know what i mean hope everyone
we have to say that of course
we do well just don't give in
you know hope everything's going right in
the world did the romans we haven't
said that and i feel like retroactively
the means we were not hoping
that we actually didn't care your weakness
but this week in particular i hope
everyone's okay they'll take in particular when
you're listening to this we hope you're
okay we hope you're okay we love
you thanks for listening ah a
ugh