three
i'm really close
no i really don't
oh we weren't having fun in the
in a manner that grover would have
fun yes i remember grover although you
know what rp grover i know grover
died isn't that weird why do you
date in the middle of sesame why
will they have only run a funeral
to teach kids about funerals
yeah and it had to be someone
that we cared it couldn't just be
like grosser day for right now well
that would be so like the human
yeah did you ever care about any
of the humans on i care deeply
about mr cooper you know i think
small businessman
i pulled himself up by his bootstraps
i didn't care in the moment but
then when they've passed now i feel
when they pass it's like or bob
or whatever but watching the show know
you don't want to see those idiots
what would i do think is weird
is that they have grover hunting sesame
street and no one can see him
yeah i want to be on sesame
street so bad when maybe the cool
really cool if you're sort of
like grover to me but a human
oh really yeah i see that okay
i'll take that you're very anxious yeah
yeah yeah monsters yeah you're blue yeah
big round my head is completely round
you love cookies well that's unrelated here's
what's weird is that they all love
cookies
but yeah one is a monster and
out it yeah and those real name
think it's fred
fred cookie right said fred
he's wrong sixteen for his cookie it's
fred shenkman yeah fragile aka the cookie
monster you just gotta i think he
made it himself hi i'm fred madden
with that grover it was over then
yeah cookie monster lauer rookie me love
me love cookie
that's right the me part is very
important it talks like an idiot he
talks like a dumb it's like hey
cookie monster i love cookies now i
feel bad because maybe english is like
i think he's actually too he's perpetually
too
that is terrifying because big bird is
supposed to be like five he's five
years he's chronically five because i started
in what nineteen seventy has the mentality
like seibold yeah he's not real so
what
he's supposed to be five out of
five year old i don't know what
i should do while you mean mentally
five yes the body of the body
of a seventy year old yeah he's
incapable of learning yeah you'd like the
good doctor
exactly
i would see promos for the good
doctor after during bachelor i watched a
good amount of the good doctor you
did it looks so funny to be
so now this whole like everyone's meaning
it now oh they there's a clip
everyone's making fun of going this show
sucks but but i would just watch
trailers for it and be dying
laughing at one of my favorite yeah
wrapping show was that super bowl where
they had this is us on after
the super bowl yeah and all the
people that that had never seen the
show that hung around and watched it
and were tweeting like what the fuck
is this show
yeah you can't just bring random people
into that um i was once at
a stoplight and i looked awesome review
mail there's there's
only one stoplight ever i thought it
was a good storage green lights all
the way for me baby yeah um
i looked at my review mirror and
the good doctor was in the car
behind me wow whoa i recognized them
speaking like oh i always has an
irish accent in the commercial dr shaun
murphy joined the good doctor who
even the good doctor oh and would
you ever let me check your appendix
though
okay so if you had a button
yeah see i don't hopefully i didn't
hear what it is right okay so
if you add a button where you
were driving and you could turn any
light green but every time you pressed
it someone on tv fictional character die
oh absolutely
oh yeah no problem
you would fuck up some of your
favorite show that's okay but would you
get to know yeah you don't wanna
be it only shows who it was
short dvd shows you watch wouldn't fuck
them up or make them more interesting
i don't know so what's what's the
show you like but see you don't
care about aca yeah like you don't
care if something show
young sheldon r i p
becomes the title of the show ah
do you think anyone will but after
the strike is over yeah do you
think the one i've hit my pitch
for shelter lee where it's it's open
and nursing i think they should do
across over with young sheldon and ghosts
and then once you've killed off young
sheldon from your vihar track team he's
he's
i'd go so any they all have
their oil embargoes yea all it goes
they all oh wow let's go sta
i like it ideal solution because the
actor still get work that's what i
was concerned about yeah i was concerned
the actors getting fired and i think
a shame if they found out about
your button they would try to kill
you because you're like putting their jobs
in jeopardy damn the rich why anyone
who's on tv is rich yeah that's
me yeah so honestly if you're
every week yeah well this is the
conversation coming into play with residuals and
so true dreamers so true yeah we
are strike podcast yeah um that's ours
um but yeah don't people were posting
detroit podcast we've forgot about that we've
got started we forget to talk about
philosophy
four hundred episodes yeah we're gonna get
there we met to talk about how
the strike is coming well we were
on strike talking about this we were
like yes we were striking about this
right now but we already being paid
to talk about it strictly professional everybody's
everybody knows about today
there's video videos specifically zoo zoo be
zoo boise
yeah yeah lauren i would love for
you to put up now but lorna
was right here's here's the first song
okay it goes a little something like
this zoomy louisa bay
leave easily using the app
kept up a good show
that's my favorite part of that song
where she says she's gonna join i
know it's because i well my well
my sore throat is still here because
we recorded the same day as before
do you remember that day ah when
the line broke and the monkey got
choked
line broke and the monkey gun you
show and then they all went to
have a little rowboat i don't know
hey yeah it was sad that's a
sad batteries that's really so dirty lowdown
that's like his status the life of
pi o which i i a book
that i bought i think it sits
on my shelf unread to do this
a really crack it open room i
at least crack the middle lake quotes
a line from a giant tiger jumped
out you'll be like oh god and
i should really look up the outer
reefs and join tiger woo
what's up my bed wake can like
mike like really likes this one line
from the hilt quote and then it
makes me cry every time i literally
can't remember whatever but i what am
i certainly was rise do every day
life of pi yeah and then i
go oh um no but it's just
a beautified admire that anyone who can
remember anything he's very good with quotes
and he's very good with
actors names characters name why is what
that trigger siri siri get out of
here he knows carrick character first and
last okay one time i found this
on the web for actors names characters
name that trigger siri siri get out
of here check it out that's what
you felt you found me on the
web for that you fucking bitch no
you didn't you didn't find something on
the web
for that that's those unmovable shit overheard
oh today alexa was like i think
janey asked what the weather was going
to be like she tells you the
weather and said oh by the way
if you wanna know this yeah yeah
it's obviously what's testing shit and so
we're like yeah okay let's hear it
and then she's like
you can get this app it's like
hey no yeah that's well so what
i read like that when an app
alexis in trouble because they're having trouble
monetizing anything that anyone ever asks it
and that and because because what it
is yes exactly because people are just
saying hey what's the weather yeah and
there's no way to monetize that that's
why it's always suggesting things like hey
if you want to know this yeah
too bad yeah too bad i shouldn't
bother tell tell me the weather you
you thought people were just gonna be
going alexa buy me this bindi vat
well it's
all yeah i know spend my money
please yeah i'm not doing that yeah
i've never bought anything off of something
like that work harder not as tartar
was figure out a way to monetize
all the information you're stealing yeah that's
the willingly giving you yeah because no
but they're trying to say like no
you should constantly be like saying oh
i'm interested in the weather let me
buy an umbrella from stupid amazon
whatever by the way if you're a
sponsor amazon we love you we love
you amazon alexa will do anything for
you like the best and should do
whatever she wants yes she's a beautiful
girl she's a beautiful girl she's a
biff god she's beautiful why did they
make alexa just like a flat disc
like why at least make it a
bust of a beautiful woman
thank you will robust all the beautiful
wo ma flagship delete ne ne ne
da the the alexa type thing that's
in megan is pretty cool i haven't
seen that movie as a good movie
it's fun alright it's fine i'll check
it out at halloween time okay it's
actually once
you watch it on your next movie
night it's not loud that how you
could watch it very easily it actually
any number like an extra i was
trying to tell like that it's more
like an action movie okay it's not
really a gross it's not really scary
it's not likely a girl it's it's
not a little like amadeo he's like
a job do your job say to
be her
it's not like a scary you're the
one who watched psycho where we held
a fuckin weirdo we you want megan
if there was a live orchestra yeah
only then i actually would watch that
there was that sounds really fun um
i saw phantom thread with a live
orchestra wow i was high as a
kite yeah film because we were
we're walking towards the it was at
the theater at the ace and on
the way from dinner to the to
the the theater you we pass on
the pop stores yeah like let's fucking
do this wow and it was great
i was right psycho as well yeah
which did make it better i will
yeah yeah we went to see fast
x yesterday and
call up texted me come down here
but and i'm sure she's talked about
this on her own show so i'm
ah i think i'm eighteen to talk
about yes i think i'm cool she's
like come down here and she she
was like eighteen she see i thought
you said aid td and then i
was like what is it actually art
we were leaving from her resume therapy
session to go to fast x and
so when i get a tough turnaround
when i when i get a text
of come down here right at the
end of therapy yeah i figure something
was brought up that she needs to
bring to my attention that she's upset
about my therapist tells me you're the
worst yeah so
so i go down there and she
she micro doses on mondays and thursdays
i did not know that and she
apparently got a new ah much like
gremlins to a new batch and took
far too much oh wow and in
the middle of her therapy session started
tripping
and brought it to your therapist's attention
and her therapist is like okay well
we're here now well let's deal with
it but she's like she's like i
don't know if i can go to
the movie i'm like this is the
perfect time for you to be high
like you rescue a date we took
the day off to go see fast
decks like
just let's just enjoy it and then
she got into the right mindset and
it was just great okay that's that's
that's scary though when you don't expect
it yeah you have any more than
yeah i was weird chatting about there's
a lot of people are doing this
yes yes yes yeah i'm curious you
know yeah i'm weirdly not that curious
about it i'm not that curious i
know what it feels like
to be stone i know what it
feels like to be sort of sound
and i think i get what that
would feel like i think i could
see how they'd be great um so
i'm going just thinking now and i'm
doing it forever
yeah but i just i don't i'm
not i wouldn't say i'm like what's
that like it's more that i'm just
kind of like alright look more like
really nice people like if you're not
stoned to take your moods a little
bit better it's like yeah that's being
stoned or you just also popping the
anti depressants because they probably pymol my
head hurts those touches know you are
pushing up imagining because oh that's because
i was touching my head so i
didn't know what i was you know
my parents like yeah my glasses but
i didn't know if i was subconsciously
going like that oh sorry oh yes
i know i don't know what i'm
subconsciously doing yeah well yeah if you
okay take a lotta weird shit y
just really can you read body language
no not at all never know what
someone's trying to put out there
you know it was really wild ny
they do it a little bit here
sometimes but not it hasn't really caught
on like this but when i was
um living in ah london for those
couple of months i did kelsey jerry
i'll sketch show and i say cheerio
to everyone every day and i was
cleaning chimneys constantly um on the news
when they would talk
about politicians and stuff they would so
often talk about their body language or
heal but if so they have like
a body language person they're saying but
if you look at his body language
he's doing this oh we never translate
we never talk about i've seen it
a couple times and people are like
and people dismiss it there's always like
a reaction to it it's like the
fucking yeah like it's like vaccines and
stuff
exactly exactly yeah or the idea that
ah nine eleven was an outside job
it's just
um yeah that's easy writing that all
over you think of nine eleven as
being the day before your birthday like
when you hate when you hear that
every year i think about it do
you think like yo is the date
of my birthday yeah it's my birthday
eve when i tell people when my
birthday is it feels weird yeah yeah
you like to
twelve i feel like i have to
say i wasn't celebrating i wasn't celebrating
that year
yeah it's hillary that you will do
well i had a party planned at
a bar so and
i think you're not supposed to celebrate
anything but here were you in new
york no i was i was here
okay really grace and so i had
to either party over new york city
area yeah some people probably verde some
people in new york probably did
is that possible psychos need to be
really insane yeah but somebody did well
but the thing is i had the
party planned already and then i decided
not to call it off just because
i want everyone to maybe yeah i
think you have time so i just
wrote ah like so many emails rage
guess what this is not about me
anymore
yeah let's all get together but let's
but let's remember that it is my
look if you love me already you
can give it to me listen i'm
gonna act like i don't care about
my birthday i need you to say
but happy birthday to you yes and
presence still are expected yeah it was
just a nice gesture yeah and i
got so many flags that year so
many people gave me the flags okay
hey oh american oh you must been
happy
you love flags i love the american
i love the american flag so much
oh i die every time i look
at who do you think has the
best flag i don't think our flag
is that great i think our i
think our flag is okay tell that
to the betsy ross i'll tell your
face up and evan you think i'm
fulfilling everywhere we go by our house
every day and say yes huh
yeah who has the best flag well
in great britain is a great flag
the union jack you check it looks
really cool it's like metrics like in
japan just to read sapin to be
you vehicle yeah absolutely
um what's the busiest flag like where
there's just way too much shit on
it ours might be up there
wow i mean what do we have
fifty stars yeah that checks out cooler
flash arrives not coolest busy or i'm
gonna look at busiest busiest wow north
macedonia looks like a big sudden burst
anyone's to look wow that looks cool
good one that's really good all the
pop pop sub is
the most popular flight i don't care
about the popular flags i don't care
about the best flags i want the
busiest fly what don't you understand come
on chat gpg richard scarry get at
me
which countries have the clay's craziest flag
please
bermuda bermuda's ah bermuda jamaica oh but
lazy
okay let me let me describe
no air muda you're lazy ou wanna
lazy dogma munich so lazy okay isle
of man their flag is three legs
attached to each flag
move it
oh okay i don't stir right like
that that's too i like the seychelles
all that's beautiful that's just pretty so
this is a pretty one kingdom of
bannon is a guy being so funny
yes that is good great well pro
everyone hey come on in
oh god good stuff ma'am i'm beanie
mama beanie baby baby baby come on
beam if mike were to call you
beanie baby just one day was like
in real loving mood and just just
one year my many been like every
day he was like hey beanie baby
i'd be okay with it because it's
my yeah
yeah yeah yeah i know what that
what yeah me beanie baby in front
of you i'd like that too woo
so like you guys are at a
party he walks laps my take the
two of you walk up to paul
yes hi ibd baby and we both
go high whoa you call him baby
baby too icy and he just called
everyone beam and then eventually you all
he can say is being just being
a baby baby baby anyway yeah
same word i read his inflection about
what he's saying fine with that
in sickness and in health here very
easy going i'm chill i'm here ha
can you ask for exceptions in your
wedding vows and the power they accept
if you can't stop saying bd baby
if you start doing that it's over
i wish i put that in my
vows now that's funny
except if some reason you can't skip
saying only bd ab thinking that you're
doing regular human speech
i'm out i'm out yeah and you
get mad i'll be leaving your ass
rules are rules i do
i do alright we have to disagree
hammer back
once again talking to learn lab guys
are allowed just got awkward about life
and everything in it everything i have
we covered everything yet i think so
what were the topics that we hadn't
covered up we hadn't covered if you
only say beanie baby so we just
hit that that was new that was
new
the space race i think we've covered
remember things race war did we talk
about those yet the cold war what
do we think about it it's too
cold and like like we're made us
raise the temps here guy yeah we
did talk about war we did talk
about war okay yes accounts okay so
we took we cover anybody watching any
love right now you're just obsessed
oh wow i'm still watching wobble doctor
who okay i'm still watching the newest
doctor who reality recap yeah much of
the new queer eye yeah let's get
about kira it's fun
i forgot about stopping it nowadays everybody
wants to say
hi guys i'm gonna check but knows
nothing to say my favorites were like
guy which instagram who i showed you
guys yeah whoo yes he'd be like
he kind of guy who wants like
that song oh no and then but
you'd be like flip his his car
and watch that fucking thing
i don't remember you're the guy got
a i gotta go round look him
up nobody makes everybody wants everybody everybody
would do it in a class or
so
i don't know that you're describing this
for those of us who don't know
what you're talking she actually is like
yeah she's doing a great job oh
my gosh of a job brownie i
got the job brennan remember that remember
when they they referenced it on the
sopranos that was pretty funny what they
say on the soprano said that to
somebody when he is mad
i have a job brown yeah interesting
it got a job bernie
we're doing these apnoea ah he really
knew how to i'm gonna sneak out
was like hey honey i think it
was something like grunge or something grungy
looking brando i hope it is grunge
grunge if you're out there we love
you oh no he's told crux slip
your watch that's on your ankle i
guess what
ever lawrence trying to tell us yeah
bro choose stole christmas grinch who stole
christmas
i'm gonna try to google it
what have you been doing
i
a really good question texting random bible
oh maybe had a beanie baby isn't
the way to google call might be
called mike b i'm gonna write new
text just texas tech mike said i
was trying to find him the other
day yeah tex my credo and say
i wanna call you beanie baby from
now on okay let's see what he
says
see know we're taping
he isn't aware i've ever oh what
awesome
let's see what he says okay so
lauren has texted mike i want to
call you i also haven't already texted
mike and beanie baby
with no cuts
should i text or say yeah he's
taping he's typing okay he said sounds
good yeah okay i'm shy so just
beanie baby or what yeah let's do
bb just maybe okay alright being made
bb
there we go
um
lauren yahoo twiki is twiki rogers twinkie
no baby b to b e way
book there was a show called buck
rogers in the twenty fifth century starring
gil gerard and aaron aaron gray gray
yes from silver spoon and um so
it's about this
astronaut who falls asleep rip van winkle
style wakes up in the twenty fifth
century because he's just fall asleep i
thought he like what useful reading
the most boring just a chair like
war and peace he like there was
some accident he got you know you
gotta eat it was like into a
time loop or or was it literally
it was it was like i kind
of can't remember i can't remember he
got transported to the twentieth century we
just for like fellow induce some biogenic
yeah
yeah deep space is probably deep fiscal
ah yeah um and so gil gerard
was like a wide man
who was considered hot at the time
ah because he's beefy like that was
a great thing in the seventies and
eighties you could be beefy and and
people would be like that's a man
he's a real hunk sure a hairy
chest you know yeah which you're not
allowed to have anymore yeah yeah i
tell you that about the the one
that got away the one that
got away shit almost every chest know
there was this when i worked attention
there was one of the waitresses was
like hey i have a really tall
friend who ah yeah the woman yeah
yeah oh i told you this you've
taught yeah but i don't recall what
it was she was like i have
a really tall friend who is interested
in meeting you because i said you
are tall she asked if you had
a hairy chest
and i was like not really she
went oh it's a weird question to
ask so yeah it's a weird work
question to field yeah especially and also
fuck her like she's like yeah i
need to be with somebody okay he's
oh we'll ever thing but yeah before
you even you can't have two things
you can do yeah yes to be
tall with a hairy chest his feet
have to be three inches long and
he has to wear a red hat
and non negotiable is but has to
be like two big hotcakes this together
and it's not just a touch other
nick named rumpelstiltskin before i get there
force
his rebel force good i die you're
gonna dictate yeah my guy over that
okay right mike back and say i
want to call your rumble force
cv says sounds good
ah he is i don't think he's
he hasn't written me back
he just wrote back to me and
said ah he's probably tipped off there
were recurring did you write a doom
i did like oh you guys just
go row before
ah
huh
okay paul so fucking you're talking about
gilroy kills right okay so buck rogers
had this little robot friend named twiki
who before he's very thing and to
make this noise maybe bb and he
was voiced by the el royale blonk
yes he was a tiny little robe
dot has always been the guy that
bugs bunny that's really random but his
bd bd bd better or worse than
like the typical robot saying like query
or post works it's it takes up
the same amount of time i think
it sucks it's irritate i know it
sucks but maybe maybe maybe but any
i was
watching doctor who you see like bidi
bidi bidi okay like that okay exactly
so duh what makes literally putting her
child be bad i can see and
i'm bugging him with
but i was watching doctor who yesterday
and they and the dalek was like
telegraphing everything he was saying he was
like then you must be destroyed yet
any fires a laser it's like just
fire the laser bro okay they love
adp if someone's okay then you must
be destroyed to me i'd be like
baie they're constantly saying
you will be exterminated and yeah they
they say they give you the reason
why yeah and then they say here's
what's gonna happen guys chance don't bore
me to death shoot me to death
right yeah i mean look up twiki
twiki yeah you got around it i'm
gonna try to draw here next to
my cylon okay i wish you the
best of luck why are you
keeping the cylon because i feel like
once i remembered or once paul reminded
me that they only have one i
feel like i nailed it because i
okay so this is twinkie
i think he was two k's
and he had a little like thing
on his thing and then i beg
your pardon
is this sort of what twiki yeah
pvd
di di di di di wow sounds
kind of cool eighty baby in retrospect
d v d someone isn't going to
like that wow avoids a bug that
they make noise that maybe that's what
they were shooting for i think tdd
no pun intended because buck rogers shot
at people at least one community because
is this what
it looks like bombs no no no
what do you mean it looks like
it's got a little helmet on oh
this guy could have a helmet though
he no come on come on i
i at least got the height right
bidi bidi bidi bidi bidi bidi bidi
bidi bidi bidi bidi oh yeah a
little helmet he all
also would like carry around in his
in his torso there this round light
up thing yeah that's what that is
that was called dr thoughtfulness yeah yeah
now what was after those three buttons
correct but you don't have doctor thoughtfulness
in there well what was doctor theo
phalluses deal he was like a smart
um
consciousness that was in this round this
is the future liberals want
you know what i would mind it
to be a consciousness i wanna be
a consciousness in the ether abu dhabi
you barely consciousness
i got you i swear but in
fun but an ice where i'm paid
to yeah baby baby baby baby baby
appa digit i pay tension maybe the
dvd is actually cooler than i remember
being because in my memory it was
him just say he just saint but
it actually sounds like it's it's it's
including yeah yeah trying to think of
what i wanna say it's kind
of bad ass i think it's the
coolest thing i've ever heard it's kind
of changing the world one step at
a time i feel like a beta
next to tweaking i'm not a car
and it's everything
i'm literally gagging for twee is it
tweak here twiki i don't know i
don't i think it was one of
those things where depending on the job
differently yeah yeah yeah because yeah because
yeah it was the age of it
was the age of there were still
people left over from like playhouse ninety
days or whatever they came from the
theater and so they were pronounce
weird way and erin greatly felt like
she was a soap opera actress twiki
twiki twiki twitch she was gorgeous wiki
lucky you're a beta cuckoo gaga on
that too
we should do battle of the podcast
stars podcast now does that come from
what is it because i was thinking
about how how gil gerard and an
erin gray wood are the type of
actress who would be on battle of
the network that's right and i was
bummed that we would never be able
to do it because we're not on
a network show yeah but we're on
a podcast network okay so it's like
us against the small muscle
yeah i want to call you rumple
for skin from now on he said
less interested in that only paul may
call me
ah he put art on it
ah
good tag so shit all that good
shit my kids you remember tattoo from
fantasy island know the band yeah oh
man oh i think she said oh
yeah my head whenever one last time
somebody that one i just remember sir
john i got us yes that but
their big hit was
all the things yes well i don't
remember that dear so i don't let
me play with your sad other things
you said running through my head what
a turn rather than remember him for
fake lesbians yeah other fake game against
to title it was our for okay
we have a judgement we have a
air bnb thing first with
runs later okay we can skip the
ad though okay here we go rain
trickling this is subtitled so thank you
for letting me know thank you for
letting me know madoff bought up this
new original music video like oh the
show
this is the official one so this
is not a bootleg video this is
the video you want to watch a
video and i'm enjoying it and i
find out it was the unofficial video
running through my head running through my
day this is familiar
i had run into my head rather
is not in awe i feel like
i heard the other one more than
the song though i don't think i
know when you're talking she's not gone
again not god i got you must
have seen them do like an award
show or something oh i'm stuck near
oh i must have must have been
at the country music awards your favorite
thing to watch here's what goes
because whatever he did tattoo get married
here people also i realised this was
this is my um my reaction when
i see the cole kidman and keith
urban
is that they showed them in in
the front row and they're dancing along
to whatever song and i go
oh right nicole kidman's married to keith
urban right and then i go oh
right keywords australia yeah his name same
two things every time his name implies
he's like urban but she is that
she's australian yeah yeah because she hardly
ever plays australia yeah well she she
after a couple of marriages she was
like i'm only going to marry an
australian for now one oh from now
on you think that's smart so she's
just picked one or she's planning to
do more weight she's married to tom
cruise and who else tom cronin ci
have another one what was her aspect
who was her other us was it
billy bathgate
is that who
that's the guy from unc his focus
now it's the guy from mr magorium
is one garage area ram yeah says
wonder
she's been married twice oh just tom
cruise and keith urban okay one that's
firing a good amount to great amount
i think yeah cheers i'm gonna stop
to perfect yeah absolutely absolutely do you
think she would have stayed with tom
cruise if he had an australian accent
i think that was the deal-breaker i
heard about that i wonder where ai
promos she kind of mention
eons ah yeah yeah she puts these
easter eggs yeah in like two depending
on what movie you see you might
get a different one yeah right so
the one i saw it was before
mario or whatever she was like i
like she says like carefree children around
so yeah camera and then right then
she's like i only got divorced from
tom cruise because he wasn't touched she
did
id two hundred and fifty separate yeah
takes of that to include two hundred
fifty separate easter eggs this isn't to
say it wasn't takes really because it
was no she did the entire thing
it was choose your serie okay it
was just she would anyways it was
one three hour take and the operator
was like such a hero because they
were just saying yeah and shown like
she was just thinking of them they
didn't write
them for her she just thinking what
can i say it wasn't like scab
worker yeah yeah his arms cut off
because all the blood permanently drained out
yeah well his arms are sticking straight
up for ever yeah and so he's
like ma yeah just cut it off
so i can get me out of
my misery
yes so she did a bunch of
those have you guys see one i've
seen all of the yeah yeah i
travel with your favorite fact because i
only saw that one um she said
that it wasn't actually her in the
paddington movie what yeah yeah what does
that mean like that was chatting to
roles oh the one i saw she
said she wasn't riding a horse in
the movie austere
thalia she was writing it in the
one that ron howard directed far away
far away yeah and i was like
yeah i know
yeah you already knew that i already
knew i mean i think it's possible
that people are gonna know some of
the things yes yeah they're not all
top secret know there's a lot more
she said the news was she she
was like it's a clinic he was
kinda that she's didn't stay married tom
cruise but yeah but a person out
of the movie with so they saw
one that was a different one where
she said if i had to
pick any movie candy to eat would
be uber's which i think is like
really unpredictable it's i went along expecting
someone which should raise nets so she
did to canyon we're and she was
lying in one where one of them
so our ma lie watch co makes
you wonder if all the rest of
them realised too well i saw one
where she was like so i'm not
three years old
it was true i guess that's true
because that is true i don't know
do we know that though but do
people think that can anyone remember anything
she's ever done previous to three years
she's three years old she's very sophisticated
i'll say that she's got to be
in the top percentile yeah she wears
a gown very comfortably for someone who's
three ah she's a little too comfortable
a gown
and for three year old usb yeah
and those heels all the original yields
and don't get me started on those
heal oh those luba tom those red
bottom boots louboutin up a pot of
jeans the third oh my ah the
whole club was looking at her but
she ah
and next thing you know everybody got
low but i think she really has
that way of inspiring people she really
ah we love you nicole i don't
know what how we got on this
but the other day ah we were
talking about old tv shows were talking
about the beverly hillbillies and ah it
struck me that
granny um in the opening credits being
in a rocking chair on top of
their old truck on top huh it's
actually pretty funny it is funny yeah
although is it based ah is it
based on the grapes of wrath where
she was just on it i think
it's an heightening of that yes okay
yes she's rocking chair rather than a
chair chair yeah yeah yeah that's
she thought she's not on top of
the truck she's on she's on the
cab like on yep the cap yes
funny shit it's really funny yeah and
i think for some reason i took
it for granted as a child yeah
something like that you're like everything's going
to be this good
yeah right we have cigarette
and we're back here's what cylon south
florida nbc but first and are easy
asked what's our rbc is oh ma'am
this is an rpc
the customized with unique
starts right here i get bad
i like that by the way you
could plug in
i love how your sweet ass will
be with us shortly your sweet ass
will be shortly i thought when i
was a kid i thought that voice
was the coolest fucking thing yeah it
sounded really cool yeah but battlestar galactica
can't come out okay okay yeah my
thinking about that came out after star
war suit it was like oh this
is going to be as cool star
oh yeah it didn't have the budget
of star wars speaking of which yeah
ah okay so so star wars comes
out yeah nineteen seventy seven doctor may
who adds um a robot dog called
canine yes canine who truly sucks yes
although great final episode great final episode
yeah um then later they
add a more like humanoid android guy
named chameleon that i just got to
that episode and it's you look at
it and you're like that guys you
gave it a shot you know yeah
anybody tried can't win em all yeah
you tried to capture the imaginations of
yeah the world's children but you have
a budget
out of fifty p and you can
get happen
alright game we're gonna play reacher oh
we playing again this is an all
the end of goody gay we're gonna
play switch it in pitches oh yeah
this is like meeting an old friend
wow dinner feels like it's episode three
so one of us
it says the title to something that
exists at a television show or a
movie that already exists thought it the
other two then do the opposite of
each word for the new title that
they pitch and we pitch that to
the person who gave us the original
title and then we have to sing
the theme song at the end that's
right okay okay who wants to
part two the title now what a
man make a suggestion yeah so the
one person is being pitched to yes
well that then that's the person who
comes to people who are being pitched
hold hold no one knows one person
that's being my god why it's always
a team please please just let me
speak what do you it's a team
it's a it's a writing got let
me that it was the icon ix
i'm arguing with lauren i used to
be i when i fight i want
to thank both of you
in my memory it's two people hearing
a pitch that might be done we've
done which i was like that we've
we've done shows like that before so
if the person who comes up with
the with the actual title of the
real thing yeah that's the person who's
being pitched to yes so you give
that then the team one of them
will explain
the concept than the other one has
to sing the song what do you
think about that sure but can the
other person back the first-person up or
do they stay side i think they
stay silent to take whatever it is
and they have to incorporate it into
the song i like the interplay between
the two p okay fuck me okay
i meant to say fuck you i
think fuck you both and let's just
do it how you do it okay
do it we do it alright i
love one i love right yeah right
title hey thank you i think he
thought it was cool it's great eden
okay the title is and who's going
to pitch it will if you if
you say the title than the base
alright sorry jesus
idiot the title is quantum leap yeah
oh quantum leap hey thanks for meeting
us course ah sorry sorry i'm like
oh you don't throw rotten know we
we believe we had to run because
we're crossing a picket line yeah yeah
i know they are mad at it's
pretty intense out there huh yeah yeah
we
i would like to look out the
window and kind of just laugh this
is a big opportunity for us we've
never had any show on television before
we're not part of the right we
probably shouldn't have said wish us luck
to everyone yeah they were going with
never knowing you were doing but yeah
yeah so yeah okay great i'm glad
you guys are here you're both a
nonunion scab that's right yeah i think
this is every time to buy so
let's
we're glad to get our foot in
the door yeah ah it won't last
if you know once the deals all
done over here but i'm just telling
you i don't know what that means
yeah me neither um alright so why
might explaining why my last like your
success won't last like people will not
be happy that you did this and
but will rush right up
um hey miss yeah wait so the
other writers determine whether or not we're
successful they're gonna just you know tear
you down and kind of get you
i mean well in america we build
everyone up to tear each other down
yeah that was a quote from air
um alright well i don't really have
a ton of time because i have
but you we have another half hour
right i have a little bit of
time but ah jimmy kimmel was sending
over a pizza truck for the exact
year
really
so guys these sweetheart yeah that yeah
doing that to like dig at j
i don't know because he does it
for the writers who does it for
us it kind of just no one
knows like their hunger out there we're
hungry and here everyone's hungry yeah it's
like like you can't leave to go
get lunch because you're taking the lead
of our glorious mayor karen bass yes
everyone
i should just get along yeah yeah
alright alright um we're here to pitch
a show i love it and it
is called short stand short stand stand
okay yep it's a great show ah
well it's kind of a cross between
you know short round from the indiana
jones but yeah that guy who now
one of the
oscar yeah most no time is love
show could win an oscar oh my
god do you show winning an awesome
hey we're getting ahead of ourselves because
they see why that way yeah no
this is the first we're proposing the
first television show that's eligible for the
oscar it's part of the okay okay
yeah what's it about well it's across
as you said yeah between
in short your child and
the stephen king stephen king's the stand
you know randall flagg the rest of
those kooks there is do i have
to know for this to continue nope
okay do you mind reading the stand
because you right now wrote about seventeen
hundred eighty yeah i could all good
i'll zip through that okay just give
you a standard edition takes into those
characters even deeper
really i was just doing like god
die bidi bidi bidi bidi bidi bidi
it was good
okay maybe i like the part with
the stand yeah let's best parted as
far as i'm cause there's a plague
that is sweeping the nation oh and
it's called covert ninety minutes okay yeah
and it makes you do a bunch
of gross things and then you die
yeah only person who's immune to it
is a little boy
a from nineteen thirty nine that's right
a little asian boy from nineteen thirty
nine and he's the only person left
alive at the end of the first
minute of the show that's right oh
that's right so he has the entire
earth to himself and then called devil
home alone yeah yeah it's kind of
last man on earth so someone
no break in earth and he's trying
to like yeah we new alien burglars
who are soaking wet from jarrod plant
they're called the wet aliens yeah yeah
and they said like the opposite of
signs they come from a plant that's
all wow wow okay so short round
sets up some like paint cans on
ropes yeah big boulder
huge but and indiana jones comes back
to life really briefly and goes hey
that's my thing and then he dies
it's funny and it will be played
by her support um okay so then
he defeats yes to the whole series
and is probably going to refer ten
years yes him trying to defeat these
soaking wet aliens which he does at
the end of the second minute yeah
of the first ups every episode yes
silly episode just kicking back just chillin
have you ever seen a television show
that's so relaxing it's made you like
feel good about watching because it's like
wow i wasn't tense this isn't like
breaking bad yeah like oh are you
familiar with heuga this show yeah seems
to be the back-row
sound noise show of all time okay
we just talk about the main character
a little bit know you'd rather not
huh okay um great then i guess
my big question is like um who's
this for it's for every man woman
and child in the united states of
america and the world
old who's not racist because it is
amazing care yes who's not hey well
you should be for everyone i guess
racist can interpret it in so we
can have some self hatred yeah
no i don't think the character should
change i'm so you love the character
why did you want to talk about
the character i want to no more
but there's no more love what i
know there's no more so you love
one hundred percent of it yeah because
i think he's very likable yeah yeah
absolutely absolutely i'm so glad you've got
that from our charming and he's fun
yeah and he's
at every man and yet still very
unique yeah and he's everything i've ever
wanted in character you really get wow
amazing huh you now that being said
you guys have no experience none well
less than no experience yeah we've actually
this idea no we've actively we've forgotten
how to read and write for
this so does that mean you'll have
to learn again yes if you would
teach us okay early sun is a
link yeah you can click link
ooh
um okay
okay stops upset here's here's them to
offer you okay i'm going to offer
you and this is the best i
can do right now okay i went
down once
five seasons
seventy five episodes per season yes but
i can give you ten million dollars
per episode that's it teach me guitar
one second we confer this still sucks
let's get the fuck out who is
this bitch
sorry we're not for sale yeah okay
these ideals are too good hate ya
where the good lord split ya whereas
by the way her anything you pitched
this room is now mine so i
hope to show you guys my thing
and i'm gonna make it show from
scratch but what's the theme song then
if you own it
it's because ultimately this
short-stay he's little guy who knows his
whew
sure stand he does whatever he cared
on this earth to find love a
romance a number one fan everything he's
wanted and just one man yes he's
gay and that's something he'll discover in
season by
get there later
i can't wait to see the show
i can't wait till season five yeah
why don't i just go to his
legend tells you so it's gonna happen
five years from now
because that will keep you invested to
me honestly i know anyway good stuff
like that alright well thanks for the
idea wow by bo
get the guy thing going
bilbo
okay yeah huh
oh oh okay all right okay time
for one more yeah we do we
have time for two more probably okay
ah ah the executives that make things
easier sure okay
think of a show title that already
exists that's the part that was the
hardest thing in the world to do
okay
the title of course is a rodgers
the twenty fifth century
hey ah it's so nice to meet
you i'm so glad to be pitching
the show aren't you talking to me
because i'm talking to her do you
mind ah you're saying i'm the executive
i know i'm meeting her for the
first time oh i'm so sorry i
apologize wash
this guy yeah i just pitch i'm
hearing and i'm boy tift i hope
they don't know that i'm brand new
this dudes brand new or something hey
anyway so nice to meet you yeah
yeah really pleased to be pitching this
oh yeah okay so how do you
wanna do it um i think i'm
gonna like take your lead overly you're
gonna take the lead i'm yeah and
i'll just like do whatever you're doing
okay great
hay is for horses grass grasses fro
he's funny get get yourself a barn
and you'll earn i hated him when
i first walked in here but now
i think when i saw what he
was wearing i thought not gunman dad
and he said he hasn't yet harmonically
large baby and not gone into it
you're not yeah oh he's not funny
oh oh no literally yeah drama department
oh yeah they know we know we
know but we take all kinds of
pitches because we get let go all
the other departments okay well this happens
to be the most dramatic show of
all time
this is a song called a song
yeah just met him just pitching me
a song i just met him but
it's no problem if it goes oh
i wear a team but if it
doesn't go i just met him this
is a song that you're going to
base a television show i'd like to
hear the song at the end no
will this it was the whole thing
this was easy and i'm telling you
that starts as the song singing now
yeah no i forbid it
sing it i don't take orders from
the likes i'm not going to listen
see yeah i'm talking to her sing
it sing it now is this all
planned yeah yeah and this is the
relationship between the main characters of the
show we want to pitch da funny
which is called as dramatic very dramatic
which is
i called penny up penny sort of
roger roger hammerstein penny hammerstein mk did
crack what was the next one in
the twentieth of zimmer penny hammerstein on
the fiftieth
anniversary wow pegs hammerhead normally on the
fifth members faster i'm intrigued yeah this
but this is the problem with the
main character he doesn't remember things because
he's been asleep for so many years
yeah eight hours a night for so
many years it was like momento
no in what way no goes to
sleep any wakes up you can't remember
thinking no no not like that okay
no not remember things when you wake
it's very different i remember a lot
of things won't wake up yeah so
does our character or characters very related
our characters just like you i thought
you said you what's your name again
huh my name yeah yeah who are
you
hey name's chad ferengi that's our character's
name he's just like your first name
chad for ring dome really interested yeah
he just wondering orders heard of any
hammer register i heard about a tv
executive who if you put her name
the tv show she was interest she
was it really yeah well
yes chad frankie is our main character
penny hammerstein is the woman that he's
left behind on his fiftieth anniversary he
goes to sleep know for every night
for eight hours a night anniversary of
life yep
he goes to sleep for eight hours
every single night and he wakes up
everything's cool he goes to sleep for
exactly eight hours for around eight hours
okay varies depending on you know yes
like sometimes he can't get a good
position on this pillow yeah get lots
he's a little racist sometimes he's just
dog tired because some people in the
audience sleep for you know seven hours
some for
ten we time it out to kinda
whoever is watching well but it's them
and it's also you so it's kind
of based on your sleep schedule we
need you to report to us every
year kind of get a solid eight
but obviously i sleep between seven and
nine hours nine yeah there's times when
you get less in those times you
get more and we'll know it's exactly
between seven and nine will need you
to all us when
you wake up yeah sleep eight hours
every night exactly exactly oh interesting yeah
it's weird but we still want you
to call us every day and tell
us you slept eight hours just to
make sure you please call us sir
you will call my number is let's
say i remember at the same time
yeah three eight nine five zero
chief oh god
this guy keyfob
three eight nine far zero key
ah so look i'll just call that
just call every day was alright okay
so anyway so chat frank gay he
wakes up every morning and then it's
his fiftieth anniversary what more do you
need to know the birth right of
his birth okay
and then so what happened
kickers yeah how do we know that
she even existed so the infinity reference
rights in the credits a big crawls
in the credit yeah okay and narrator
before every episode yeah it's about it's
twenty seven minutes to narrator saying the
same thing that's in the bow no
no no they opened simultaneously
they happen some days you have to
listen third year and then rewire right
and three from multitasking okay good yeah
yeah it's good for people who can
like hear two things well it's like
whatever three nine eight five per key
or zero people the right okay i
apologize
three nine three nine four zeroes chemo
anyway so that the crawl is twenty
seven minutes which leaves also twenty seven
dresses so you get to watch the
entire movie twenty seven dresses so it's
address crawl yeah yeah so just one
dress per crop
yeah and um yeah i think that's
about it i mean other than of
course the fat theme song that it
has a theme song laced on a
theme song it's oh it's based on
it's own it's based on song because
we interesting it's based on i p
that already exists yeah
what's the i p the song it
you he pees like wherever you tell
really yeah the song it's an existing
theme song but yeah not an existing
show no no no it's just a
song that's out there that we were
like let's just see it this is
yeah hell yeah panay panay
amis de jean on his fiftieth and
others
he wakes up
guitar the bed good metrics girls is
ed finds his way downstairs and has
a cup and somebody spoke anyway to
do do you think ah ha
ah oh i read the news today
oh boy this is no no this
is where you chop out i've never
heard the song yes i'd say you
guys just met she we just met
still singing about him motor cross that
made the grey
oh my god okay so anyway does
that so yeah it's based on a
beetle we sold it does it does
but we're in an alternate universe from
the movie yesterday where you don't know
who the beatles are no i do
you know the way you're saying wherein
the universe right now yeah you are
part of the bench you're saying that's
what's happening in this
is happening in the world you don't
know who the beatles are no i
do i swear oh i don't do
you yeah or you wanna only people
who knows who the beatles it's just
us it's just us just just just
standing here in pus
well you started in the room now
get out okay yea and that's how
you play switch it and page hey
listen everybody we love you thank you
so much for listening we love our
piss pigs um if you'd like to
write to us and suggest a thresher
right to freedom usa gmail dot com
and right it's like a game like
that that we can
ah don't have to guess you know
to guess things comey objects guessing things
is fine but like it gave me
playing in the car or you know
game you play around a campfire classic
campfire game i texted me a gif
of an old woman saying in the
beanie baby world i was famous
great
um and if you would like to
call us there's a voicemail maybe you
want to ask us for advice maybe
you want to guess to start a
an interesting convo like before high or
whatever yeah they want to cause a
hag claims eight and try to keep
your message to under thirty seconds and
say your name so we can say
hi to you pigs yes
and then the other thing is follow
us on instagram at three item usa
yeah and write to us in the
right m usa at gmail dot com
already said that and if you want
write to us at three m usa
at gmail dot because you always have
to add free editions of this show
additions or issues ah yeah
exactly if you have the early edition
and the late if you want to
hear it early edition and a current
affair ad-free and the early edition is
tomorrow's episode but we put it out
one that's right star kyle c-corps and
if you can please come to my
show june eleventh dynasty typewriter yeah or
watch the livestream
from home get tickets at dennis taper
dot com i love that and if
you can please come to my show
bid philadelphia
ah talking about nick's entire underground because
i'm already picturing the next day when
i had so much fun that before
wow just thinking about it and you
can't get friday and saturday the sixteenth
and seventeenth of june at underground arts
come on out philadelphia i love you
and i can't wait to see you
and go to cvb
um or stitcher premium if you don't
want to hear some fucking ads and
the whole comedy bingbing book yeah man
yeah bias around funny thing book is
a bestseller and ah we gotta go
and we have to read one of
those apps we're talking about okay goodbye
uh