ah
oh my welcome back to three duh
really rocked my socks off
ah oh my i can find gum
they they rocked your socks away yeah
yeah
ty we should just get that out
of the way right now i'm soon
dude i love my dude i want
hey everybody i'm paul f tompkins i'm
scott orban i'm lauren lab guess laura
donor in a very bubbly mood today
she's laughing all over the place i'm
i've i'm
finding things funny today i think it's
terrific but you know what i will
say the first few hours of my
day i had no emotion and i
barely talked wow
what a wonderful life you've built with
mike
i'm doing that i barely talk
it is one of those things when
you start doing a podcast and you
realize it's like for us right now
it's one pm and you realize you
haven't talked to all day and your
voice yeah is kind of raspy and
squeaky because you just haven't used it
yet raspy n squeaky
hey guys store on laverne and shirley
speaking of which plenty and squidgy histories
michael mckee named sadie squidgy michael mckeon
who played lenny i didn't even mean
to do that i know it's a
it's a flawless segue wow we were
talking ah last episode about how ah
or a recent episode
about how played out brown-eyed girl is
independently he mentions that on twitter and
then all people people like tweet that
is just right oh i see this
did you know by it he's he
stole it from us it makes you
wonder what podcast he listens to every
yeah i want yeah hi michael so
nice i'm likely to say listening and
stealing our idea dealing our shit
that was a really good idea we
had and he it was such a
good idea and we're full of ideas
like this and what i do is
i put each episode and a jump
drive and i mail it to myself
so that we'll see you in court
and not better call saul style for
real you have so many packages in
your garage it's all jump drives because
you can't open them
that's the one jump drive it's like
a little thumb drive that you stick
in your computer you can put a
file on there and then take it
away yeah
call nada a flash drive flash drive
is fun too i like to say
jump drive because it makes it seem
like i got i'm doing it under
the cover of darkness and it was
way funnier and i ruined it by
asking a lot of questions know lauren
know don't care i don't want you
to retreat back into yourself
i slept like shit last night guy
oh no why what happened i don't
know but i just kept waking up
and falling back to sleep and it
happened oh hello what you should do
is you should sleep hotel me what
i should do should sleep all the
way through
yeah i don't know if you've thought
about this but you shouldn't like you
should like go to bed close your
eyes and your so are like meowing
those eyes yeah and then wake up
and the next day because you feel
a lot better yeah you would feel
better what what did you steal this
idea for michael mckeon
he tweeted this a couple days ago
the best way to get a full
night's sleep is to close your eyes
and not wake up the whole time
what if we started taking his tweets
and then pretending they were they were
on the podcast pretending they're lawrence topics
i'm going to have
i'm gonna look into what else he
said can i say i hadn't do
it i had a nightmare the other
day where apparently in kind of noctua
yes exactly where okay so i was
i felt someone like come up behind
me and so
someone come
come on me
because i felt i was dreaming but
then i realised i was i was
in bed dreaming right i realised i
was in bed and then i not
really these movie nightmares yeah i dreamed
someone slipped into bed and spooned me
and i was like oh d cooling
cool up what's her name cool
god
cool i've got me
did cool up get out of bed
and go to the bathroom and why
would she like who leave her bed
in her room and come into my
room
oh that by the way that was
a weird three-day phase during the pandemic
where she was like hey what if
i were to sleep in the other
room because you're always waking up we've
tried that just everyone's smiles like hey
it's like a vacation or you just
get the heat right right she's like
that is comfortable
it's a no-go here no go here
yeah you should janie wants to well
it's also our guest bed is it
what's wrong are get i don't care
i guess bed is our guest bed
is a is a sofa a little
like um mummy sex shows and i'd
say it was a little racecar well
you know
look we thought we'd have more kid
friends who would be going in from
out of town now with their parents
so don't we though without need to
have we though we would host unaccompanied
minors who are trapped at the airport
um normally we have it's actually a
very comfortable bed but it's an inflatable
it's an air mattress so not not
something you're going to retreat to as
a tree no you can't just do
that and it also takes up the
whole room and it's unfurled right right
yeah well back to my nightmare oh
sure your ny spoon by your wife
i oh no i was like i
was like that it's weird that cool
op is spooning me but okay and
then
suddenly cool hobby of a loveless marriage
well no just if it was the
size of dogs played we're kidding
because she would have done it on
the other side of the bed but
i was turned towards her now i
know about make sense spoon rules yeah
okay so in your dreamy the persons
booting you is spitting you from the
front from from behind i was i
was facing cool upside of the bed
so i was like that's weird that
she would come up behind me but
okay right like that move though
yeah it's like it's like adding another
person to your relationship
it's a take on the stranger so
then suddenly cool up
whom i'm facing starts moving and she's
actually in her actual spot and so
i go oh no this is someone
who broke into the house and lows
me
oh no how do i choose
every one dreads this moment
so no i started i started then
trying to get cool ups attention by
screaming i was like screaming but i
was trying to scream in the dream
so i was like i have watched
yeah yeah and and i guess i
was doing that in real life as
well i was going yeah and then
finally
yeah i like shocked myself out of
the dream and i was like there's
no abide me i am just told
the story in the wild horses show
we did recently but i the other
night like so it's damaged goods it
is it's used when a couple weeks
ago i had or you're trying to
re gift to the story well just
right on topic i was so scared
and
my dream and something really scary was
happening and then i was like i
woke myself i was like huh who
are you but i was like are
you in my dream whoa are you
and then i heard myself say it
and i was like ooh i was
like trying to scream out loud for
real my carrot no i don't think
so because cool i've heard mine
was worried about me but at the
same time i would have thought that
she would have like reached over and
said hey you okay or anything like
that but instead she didn't say anything
so i was like oh okay i
hope i didn't wake her but then
in the morning she's like what was
your dream about like oh i did
wake you up could use a little
reassurance that you couldn't tell her because
she would've gotten gel
yes yes exactly i was dreaming about
some other entity
who's this sweater
i had i woke myself up recently
i dreamed i was looking at instagram
that looking at this little korean songs
little always like i dreamed i was
looking at this little korean toddler that
i follow and she was doing something
cute and i laughed and in real
life i saw
oh wow yeah this is why you're
having your dreams are too funny that's
why you're constantly waking yourself up huh
yeah i can't turn it off i
just know my life is comedy and
i'm honoring like i'm like
um i once went to camp summer
camp you've never told us that and
well i used to go to camp
every shocking every summer for a week
i went to winter camp it's so
into intercom to yeah where we tried
to go get real jokes oh no
we had we we i mean in
in the church i grew up in
there with summer
camp and winter camp yeah so summer
camp was at this place called forest
home which is up like in the
redlands of california and it's the cemetery
that's far as lawn and um because
so buried there i'm gonna carry your
first home at the summer camp
um i want to be cremated put
my ashes in an urn tie to
a balloon and set me free in
the sky like up yeah exactly wait
is that what that movie was yeah
this is ashes the yeah that kid
was talking to a ghost the whole
time and you've convinced him to put
his whole house on a balloon whatever
i keep that movie up by the
way
the first what is it fifteen minutes
or ten minutes or whatever the rest
sucks isn't the rest is like robot
dies and shy disagree though rapids fun
moving dog who's fun but like hello
or whatever he does over and over
again and then like there's that bird
who is so annoying i'm like bring
back the part where i was crying
about how they lost the love of
their lives
it should just be a short write
it should i want to see that
woman in heaven and what happens then
or l um i think yeah that's
the first the first ten minutes of
the movie is like a perfect short
film yeah um but they call it
a flicks but yeah
short flick yep sharp flick um i
call it a quick flick i call
it a quick bite okay mcquivey and
i want there's no way you guys
an app that i am i've invested
in called kribi so i went to
summer camp huh
and then all the girls want to
kiss you ah i actually i actually
developed in on one trip when i
was fifteen i think to sell off
to everyone could tell yeah it was
like we must we must
increase our bust
um we must increase our nuts or
nuts yeah so the guys my my
testicles came in while i was
oh so embedded everywhere everyone t
ideal for the other boys i developed
a big crush on one of my
fellow camp mates and um like you
know and then she she told me
where she lived and i was like
trying to figure out how long it
would take if if i could get
out there to go see her and
stuff like that and like it's like
okay well it's a thirty five
five minute trip but i don't drive
so i don't know how this can
work anyway i think i don't think
she felt the same way but um
there was ah i'm talking about nightmares
there was a guy who i'd never
seen this before he um was talking
in his sleep which i'd never seen
before where he was having you hear
the secret city keeps you going i'd
say
um and then he got out of
bed and started sleepwalking and then walked
into the corner and started having an
argument with someone oh yeah and his
dream and then people came up to
him and like was were gently going
like hey man are you alright he
will say hey shut up a book
well trying to say to this shut
up and hey seriously shut your fucking
mouth bro there shut up shut up
um and he's sort of like shrugged
them off it's like ah and then
calm down he's like oh realised where
he was he's like oh sorry and
then just got back in bed and
fell back asleep but sorry i'm a
real weirdo oh sorry
oh i didn't realize i was here
i thought i was at my place
where i have arguments in the corner
i thought i was argument camp which
opens in the fall but that's i
i always i feel bad for it
and then i then one of my
ah previous relationships i once had a
phone conversation with my girlfriend who was
awake during the conversation during most of
it and then we were on the
phone for so long that she drifted
off into sleep but was sleep talking
with me where suddenly she was in
the office i could tell where she
worked and i was her boss and
she was like wait it was aussie
yeah right way what what are you
talking about you want me to get
the file and i had this in
the middle of our conversation i'm like
well what's that she's
like did she had the most generic
job amanda i was saying i was
like get the johnson file she works
in an office like it just as
a you know as an assistant or
whatever and she's like you want me
to get the file i was and
and so then i start playing along
with her i was like yeah good
file it was like okay finally got
to open it and see what the
papers look please yeah go go get
the file
cause i was wondering what she was
seeing so she's like alright it's gonna
take me a second to get through
everything so she then in her dream
i could tell she was in the
other room and she was like ok
i'm looking to alright here it is
i got the file what do you
want out of it i was like
could you give me the phone number
in it she's like yeah and then
she rattled off a phone number and
i said could you repeat
that and she rattled off the exact
same phone number and then like minutes
later i was like what was the
phone number on that file and she
said the exact same phone number and
then you called and that was the
guy she was cheating on you
exactly there's no end to the story
i just i had i had a
sleep conversation on the phone with my
girlfriend for approximately fifteen minutes which i
thought was so that is weird my
mom used to do that with my
older brother hoots who does everything that
you can do in your sleep and
he would sometimes
he would sleepwalk and he would stand
like at her bedroom door maybe just
be just be talking like nonsense and
she would just like go along with
it like oh okay or
was she asleep or what wasn't she
was right though yeah hello ooh
how would i know this otherwise
no i mean i did that one
says did he wake her up as
well yes he woke yes he woke
her up i woke up hearing i'm
saying that's nice thing nonsense if she
was just awake like reading a book
that's one thing but if he lets
her up and she have the patience
to wait yeah what would be scarier
if you were if you woke up
to someone doing that or if you
were just hanging out and someone think
waking up although this thing when that
i know um has a thing where
she has like really bad night terrors
where she has to like tell people
when she starts dating them like because
it randomly randomly even if you like
the first time someone sleeps over she
might have this happen so she has
to tell like everybody and they're really
extreme why does she say it like
mid sex or yeah she's like if
you stay overnight
ah but sheila hey
i feel like think something really bad
is happening she's like called the police
before she's like ran outside with her
dog like just like whoa but she's
completely asleep no matter how many barriers
she sets up for herself she gets
through all of them i realised this
is also the plot to mike billy's
book and movie yeah i mean we're
not like selling this
this so michael mckeon we share listening
or bigly has already done this reboot
is a horrible because he later with
a lady like they did with gluster
that's raw yes sleep with me jumped
out a window and like sleepwalk was
she
can i star
i don't know after that razzie domination
shot back even trustees yeah
i can't trust you
hey i'm fine i know you're fine
we're all fine we're all fine here
we're so fine as ryan o'neal do
you remember that movie yes they do
with the it was about a guy
who i never was allowed to see
it but i saw the the trailer
for and it was about isaak
z who who invented genes that had
clear plastic butt cheeks yes what what
happened was here's here's all i think
so you fart and they fill with
care
so the first thing you think of
do your regular pets leave a fog
up fog huh it would be like
obvious here's what i have thought this
isn't this is really weird as a
kid i always thought i wish farts
were colors so that you could tell
sure but and everyone had the students
color and it's really better that's not
a thing
for what i remember i don't think
i ever saw the full movie but
i believe what happens is the way
he accidentally invents these genes is that
he is sleeping makes the scenes interaction
and yeah not only his girlfriend jeans
no he's sleeping with this woman that
he's not supposed to be sleeping with
and then her husband comes home
home or whatever and he has to
get out of the house he puts
on her jeans and they split in
the back and for i don't know
i figured out how laughable idea yeah
and then somebody complimented sheets being able
to see his ass this is so
dumb i got so stupid it was
like an orderly ur
early eighties or late seventies i don't
know but it was the early eighties
yeah yeah i mean this this these
are the plots of movies then like
i mean that deal with the laser
is so share your screen sharing mine
okay
yeah we want to see it sha
screen here it is l l started
screen sharing i don't see anything oh
no here it is okay great
let's check out play chess online against
the what's that's one of your that's
mike's okay so yeah so so the
the poster is essentially ryan o'neill in
a tuxedo to show that he's classy
he's not a creep he's a classy
guy he's like what we all aspire
to be absolutely and then a model
who has her back
to the camera and she's wearing these
jeans that have clear plastic you also
get like butt cheeks i'm wearing these
because you'd be like pressing your ass
against plastic no breathing feeling in the
movie it might have been some ah
you know great kind of new plastic
who knows true and it's true the
the gene say so fine
i'm in kind of like gold and
diamond studded cursive writing on the back
which yes i believe that was the
brand name ryan o'neal why nieto's rhino
needle i can't say it ryan o'neal
right needle dick or tatum o'neal's dad
yes yeah and i only really know
them from like this episode of oprah
where they were taught
making it was like a whole thing
about how like weird their relationship is
did there was some story where he
hit on her at farrah fawcett funeral
did she say dad it's me that's
so sick i wish i'm rewatching real
housewives of new york this is the
reality recap reality yeah yeah lady recap
yeah
with songs that have trouble of resume
but where mike started the way we're
on zoom or not in the backyard
because by the way we're on zoom
we're not in the backyard and just
so everyone's clear on zoom out in
the backyard um but mike started watching
from the beginning and then i joined
in because oh from the beginning yes
it's all on hulu how may i
see
there must be like a million seasons
like twelve or something i mean we
are in season five now earth yeah
and oh what was it gonna say
oh well so there's this woman of
here rusher
and her dad's like um a sex
addict and he's like eighty something and
healing the club he's what the eighty
or the sex attics being go to
the beach and he she takes off
her like cover up and she's got
leukemia he's litter that body about his
daughter and then she's like isn't that
gross he said that about me and
then that's it
like like that's so disgusting
yeah i know gross and there was
it i wonder why they leave stuff
like that into reality shows like i
was watching stanley tucci show last night
i want to watch that it's good
because it it's it's on cnn you
gotta like see ya then yes cnn
app or something but i'm watching it
and he
he he goes over to this ah
older woman's house who like shows in
the recipe of how to cook this
dish and he eats it and he's
like oh my god oh my god
will you marry me and then he's
like oh no i see your husband's
over here i'm like i can't believe
they left that in the edit that's
stu
but he hasn't heard of a memory
i mean he's like he's married she's
married and they left it in that
settings that's sinful the um never watched
that immoral show okay even though you're
killing the amount of things that are
left into the edit on real housewives
from especially the older seasons are so
crazy because
ramona who's like the meanest person ever
where turtle time comes from businesses sister
that's right she's a paul paul wanted
to get a turtle time wine glass
not realising that it has to do
with ramona had zero idea july i
got it but she literally says the
meanest shit ever and i'm like this
is awful this is still aren't like
they left in this thing where she
they were added a kind of they
were like a speech that this woman
was giving about bullying and it was
one of the housewives
children like stepchildren what were they pro
or con again they were and she
had um like a ah a tumor
in her lip this this woman and
so no i'm sorry
and ramona goes after the show she's
like after the speech she's like that
was so amazing situ she she's just
so confident and you think just stop
talking just you're good like just stop
and she's like and then you didn't
she's deformed he's like you just set
the show and now that
woman has to see that and then
i'm like i think it's actually a
problem they left it in because it's
just like now what everyone's hurt by
this when this was just something rude
that she said in the backroom but
i mean if they were thinking about
how this affects us as a society
it wouldn't be a show
they would choose better idea to raise
their samurai killer person who was offend
yeah assaulted by whatever other housewives it's
absolutely terrible you like a better lauren
when they're just insulting each other like
they all signed because they all signed
up i'm saying that person was just
doing a speech like right they all
went to the sign-up sheet
in between classes just kind of yeah
she got into the bulletin board to
see who got to be a housewife
now they're there the way they do
those shows do they do they have
a sort of way of auditioning people
to see if they're going to work
out on the show well because a
lot of times the people don't really
know each other that well but they
kind of imply that they're all friends
but they're not really so it's like
they find somewhere all in the same
circles
or something and they're like oh yeah
yeah hearing about her for a while
but i wish i was on that
show sometimes i like watching i'm like
i would like to be on the
show i don't really want to be
in it but i would like to
be there go your a fucking bitch
like no one says it like they
scream at each other at a certain
point but think they needed to be
doing it like nipping it in the
bud like a little earlier like oh
my god it's the busiest i could
just like like shutting them down immediately
yeah stop talking
right my one of my favorite things
about because you know i only watch
one reality show which is southern charm
is is paul's reality recap this is
paul's rot rodriquez carry out yeah yeah
um and it's it's terrible terrible shows
boring yeah that one is boring people
are bored
earring and but what i love is
the the reality show trope of sonos
having a party and then it's the
only people at the party are them
right yeah it's the same it's the
same sweet people every time i think
like that i'm real housewives like they
have like an event and it's like
there are other people there who are
just filler yeah and but the producers
or have staged it essentially yeah and
the only reason the event is happening
so they can scream somewhere where it
seems inappropriate because they they all have
these interviews where they're like how nice
of whomever to to put on this
event this week i'm so excited for
it later they all and they do
that on the the real estate shows
that i watch which is just like
okay well i really want to check
out her open house and then you
notice every other cast members at this
one and they're there they want them
to fight what's your favorite house show
um the million dollar listing i think
i love that's the one that we
base the jillion dollar properties on so
yeah josh flagg i follow him on
instagram and i i like him a
lot but he has had a very
active pandemic he's doing whatever he wants
altman i think i saw on like
a refinancing commercial the other day and
i was like oh poor baby
very interesting i like that show a
lot i just recently watched oh hey
wake up wake up but still i
gotta tell you some good story elisha
yeah yeah it is but you might
like it do you like do like
home renovation yeah god dammit paul well
i've been watching rock the block a
block yeah that's great
did you watch the finale i did
i've seen two are you this i
was pissed what else show i thought
it was a fairytale ending you know
i kind of called it early utah
tell you rock the block is a
show you can watch it on discovery
plus app which i'm always talking about
but you can also watch it on
hgtv won't do and
okay and the show is that's like
these payments they get for teams of
famous designers for two and four identical
houses on one street and they make
they make like they say go crazy
scott waited until laura was just about
to start i can't handle where i
go i was gonna see it as
simply as that
and you weren't yes i was and
so the first season was the only
way i would have veered off for
that is it the first season it's
just solo people who are the host
of different hgtv shows the next season
they have a partner and that's what's
going to happen the next season suddenly
for people to have kim
if they'd have just like three minutes
late once for like one of the
rooms but so they take these houses
that are identical and then they are
given challenges like this gets the kitchen
and then they have to do the
kitchen and you can change whatever you
want did want you have a budget
of like two hundred thousand dollars or
whatever and then for the whole house
and then at the end there's a
winner and they they tell you
who wins based on which house is
now a praise for the most money
but the show is kind of confusing
because what i love about it is
that it's almost right used the design
element is the most fun part because
they get really creative they make the
spaces really beautiful and then at the
end it's based on what what you
can sell it for which they don't
go
well this stuff actually detracts from the
sale because it started and that's what
i find so interesting about it because
the whole time when the the team
that won wasn't winning any challenges i'm
like well they should win because they
they upgraded this house in a more
premiere away i felt that it was
the most the least inspiring of them
all which i just like nate
literally judges said nate and jeremiah gave
the house a soul and then they
go and the winner is this person
and that concludes reality right here he
cap yeah it's only if i mean
it's only one reality recap and a
yeah ok you may
go ahead recap yeah yeah you're right
we should just put the drop in
i guess we should i don't know
i don't think we should yeah i
don't know really i don't want i
don't want it's gonna come out and
drop and you're all jealous we shouldn't
put it in here we should put
it in someplace else where it doesn't
belong yeah for fun i don't want
a peer pressure josh into playing this
drop that we've mentioned twenty five
times let's not make jaw
ah to be fair josh's erring on
the side of caution yeah because he
knows if he did that we would
have roasted him even though it's entirely
appropriate handler in you can't win josh
knows that he can't win
so he decides to not even play
the game exactly is reality we kept
that boring
ah right right to us right to
us yeah i say
right to lauren specifically right now and
say paul i don't blame you it
is boring here's something you guys won't
know right to me sick stickley po
box nine six three new york city
new york state one oh one oh
wait i don't know that what hey
you are right
it is a um commercial thing from
nickelodeon where there was this little popsicle
stick named stick stickley and he would
be sort of a spokesperson for the
summer and popping the screen yes huh
so this is people who don't know
that this that the summer is happening
and they're trying to get out awareness
so howard kramer ripped
from sticks dick oh my god what's
this thing that he holding up summer
yes yeah well i do like stick
stickley was a primarily a summer character
um dude gotten new york city and
do different activities and then you could
write to him and send him stuff
and he would read letters and whatever
and he was a popsicle stick with
googly eyes writing from the camera like
this and that's his address
that's so awesome yeah i think you
should write him a letter let's write
ah let's see if he ever writes
back when i was still there was
on local tv there would be um
a number you could call for i
don't know what but the it was
something like civic service or something i
don't know what what happened there
but it was the jingle for it
was
call for action greenwood seven five three
one two
yeah so not catchy it was really
it's fresh in my head forever was
it kamin yeah i guess it is
catchy since it's stuck but yeah call
to action or call for call for
action for some sort of action maybe
it was like you don't want one
or one type thing oh okay three
one one is is like nine one
one but for lesser furniture
so for your calls someone lifted trying
to show you i'm median who you
beat
i'd say welch emergency i thought it
was furniture calling for police assistance high
almost so fucking good
i'm meaning someone put a mug down
on my armrest and it's going to
leave a ring oh no ah
oh ma what if i died doing
the podcast i know i mean i
would be so forever devastated by that
it would really mess up my life
i wonder if we would ever want
to do another podcast ever again i
think we would just because like financially
i could walk away right now i
can i can press to leave meeting
right now and be happy with my
life you got all those old ipads
lying around you could sell ah
if a bit seriously if i died
would you guys be sad actually have
thought about that started crying once oh
no are you serious
but also i saw online that people
think we talk about death too much
yeah man i'm all look it's like
coming from do you know a huge
part of life it's the opposite of
it i think about it everything glee
i went to my thought about that
and i started crying and then i
thought that would be so sad what
about me lauren then i thought about
you doing it and i was like
yeah i get it
i understand yeah honestly it would really
fuck up my shit so i hope
that doesn't happen to you guys in
the next forty five years well i'm
i think happening on this show i
mean let's leave it to just happening
on the show because it it if
it happened on the show i'd be
extremely um damaging
oh boy yeah you know all those
you know all those people who like
die on stage in a comedy club
in the middle of their act and
stuff like oh yeah when i say
all those people there's been what paul
for that i can think of for
people shines only when i can think
of dick sean dyche rage right when
that's the only one i can think
of those years ago like twenty years
ago maybe maybe like yeah
like a comedy club like there was
a full audience and yeah like it
was like a theater yeah and he
died he fell down and people thought
it was a bit and for a
long long time that's was the thing
the biggest laughs he got yeah oh
my gosh yeah he was bombing up
to that
dikshit sean
um but yeah i mean lauren would
like of our podcast lawrence like the
person on the procedural drama on abc
yes it's sits in their own little
rooms just computer universal
oh okay so he holly parent he
ah died kiersten venice at the university
of california
yeah that's right it was a college
show that's right university party town you
have los angeles or eighty seven comedian
dies on stage audience doesn't get it
gonna dig in my headline
and but physically dexterous unpredictable this this
comedian fell to the floor during a
solo performance in san diego and never
got up well okay so he was
always doing physical unpredictable bits i guess
that makes sense at the age of
sixty three he had died on the
job but shannon was sometimes so outrageous
on stage that more than five minutes
passed before anyone dared to check if
he was still breathing that's like if
you were
or a juggler who juggled dangerous things
like chain saws and you had a
fake bit where like you cut off
your fake arm with one of them
you know like would anyone be able
to ever trust it if you actually
did it
what you've done here is well built
in thing near their act when they're
bad at juggling well you know how
magicians okay so i went to the
magic castle ones and in one of
the in the in the tiny close-up
room yeah there was this guy who
you know how magicians fake fuck up
their act a lot so that they
they can go yes yes oh my
god
but then i didn't make your power
but yes see people like where you
can kind of see the the work
and then kind of feel sad right
so i'm watching this close-up guy who
has these fake fuck ups but then
half the time is also fucking up
his acts so he's every trick he's
constantly fucking up and half of the
time he's like oh i didn't do
that
one right and there's no punchline to
it and he has a friend in
the audience that he keeps talking to
and saying like i messed that one
up um and then at his friend
like laughs really hard at him fucking
up with one point he's like huh
you're gonna find something a little extra
special in your milkshake tomorrow which i
thought was the weirdest
pst slam looks like it'll shake every
day like does this guy have a
milkshake and what is he going to
do like shit in it or come
in it what does he try to
say yeah that's probably should er come
yeah definitely met with shit or come
what do you want what else could
it be lax noise yeah no more
noise huh and milkshakes boys yeah
he died from adjusting pause huh that
thing was so great live too though
i want to talk to at the
same time yes we all do
i know we're on slight delay on
this i think i'm perfect
that's very loyal i like to hear
that from you i can tell that
everything i'm saying is coming in real
time
with bill maher look we have to
take a break huh we're having a
good time
i'm sorry it's take a break we'll
be right back
we're back i know i know you
know no guy was talking to lauren
let me have a private conversation with
lord can you lead us for a
second what if we forgot that there
was an audience like we just read
literally as though you're talking to each
other
wait this is kind of what it
is i mean anyway i'm in a
local bill
elizabeth are you guys still thinking about
those memes those orange ones oh i
really like those ah trying to think
of something i saw an instagram of
candy the other yesterday and i sent
her instagram of candy i considered sending
it to you but then i realised
that he would say
set us off into eating more candy
on air which i think people don't
like what well and i get it
but what was the candy tell us
about it was just a bunch of
different flavors of a kind of candy
but i can't find it anymore but
it was it looked awesome
you know what though i would say
there are ten people who don't like
that we ate candy and thousands and
thousand students say anything about it
the broadcast they don't listen to the
show
i ate more um cadbury mini eggs
and baby feel bad every time oh
my god i just i just they're
a little way paul because i love
them so much but i got a
bad batch they were kind of like
weirdly stale but i kept emails like
they're so good and ah thousand they're
not doing what they need to be
doing they're not the crunch that i
want they're not the great tax
surely and so i just was like
they have to go i is this
we got the law coming back where
show is about the bad batch
oh wow i don't know what you're
talking about
you don't want to talk about star
wars anymore i said i don't know
what you're talking about but yeah no
i don't i do want to talk
about gremlins and the next patch for
the new batch okay well i badge
oh that'd be my new ghostbusters ghostbusters
ghostbusters next batch wait so they're doing
goes for doing his answer the call
there's gonna be another ghostbusters right yeah
you see that little
clip with those little stay puffed oh
i'm not gonna watch it at dinner
just dripping off my man groggy
i thought it was cute i you
know what's got i think there's something
do that they are saying it makes
it make make it grow glue your
what's
nor knew you had a whole show
about grogan baby yoda oh right i
forgot that's what his name was um
so it's like you watch these things
and forget them the second that you
stop watching them i felt he had
a name and paul rudd z in
the movie i guess yeah he's in
the movie
well why why would you think he's
in the trailer why would you think
he's not in the movie it's trailer
it's a clip yeah it didn't not
seem like a trailer it just seemed
like it seemed like a commercial for
actual marshmallows to be on like i
wanted them by the end of it
and i liked the whole thing i
thought it was very cute and everyone
was all up in arms you know
everyone just gets so mad online everyone's
mad about
their ghostbusters said i was like this
is cute and you know what the
grandpa is ghostbusters bill murray
his don't necessarily want to watch the
old one no they don't they wanted
with one way the marshmallow guys are
like jumping around in the open flame
who looks shy one nobody gives a
fuck they can remake any movie okay
i might have already said this like
months ago but i watched trolls world
tour and it was like the funniest
movie ever
you did secure a big booster of
trolls world tour yeah this is definitely
come up before your super fan i
just laughed and laughed i mean i
should watch it again euros yeah
so who's in the new ghostbusters the
new new ghost and ah i think
it's about a a woman and her
son
i can't remember i know gross sex
um i can't remember who lot but
is it carrie coons not it can't
be right i don't know but laura
bill pauley perrette over here is looking
at you know who do you got
just go supposedly showed me the okay
so it's called afterlife they seem ghostbusters
afterlife
who's in it tell us please make
this thank you lauren lee oh wow
it's a stone with thin wolf hard
yes oh yeah oh what a name
starring carrie coon finn wolfhard motorcycle race
and paul rudd now i was in
a pilot with mckenna grace when she
was five years old
wow blowing up she's in every big
movie and all these cool she's always
been a lot of horror movies this
is a big one for her um
that's cool that's interesting so it's very
teen it's very stranger thing right because
i remember seeing a trailer for that
that was not funny at all it
was treating the ghostbusters like it was
like it was a horror movie right
really
yeah like it was very it was
ghostbusters is a horror movie no it's
not come on now you gotta be
a little scared slimer with all those
hotdogs oh gosh so many hotdogs his
heart leave one for the rest of
us so many nitrates
but i was when i saw ghostbusters
i was a kid but i was
old enough that it was not actually
scary to me there i will say
the library scene at the beginning made
us all go huh well the games
get a jump scare when this show
on um netflix that's like around
quality recasting reality recap it's not reality
i mean i guess it is but
it's behind the scenes of your favorite
classic films and how they were made
and with cameras i've ghost busters is
one of them they showed how they
did that trick with the library and
it was really um strings that does
remind me of
it does remind me of a sketch
i wrote for mister show that bob
turned down immediately which was it was
the sports illustrated behind the making of
the sports illustrated swimsuit issue and then
it was a really dry documentary about
um cut
cutting down the trees and making the
paper and the printing presses and running
and he was like oh yeah i
get it words have different meanings
and we never spoke of it ever
again ah you should bring it up
to him i should
he's one smart lists this resp episode
i really like going you would mention
it on better call saul bob was
turned down a sketch of mine by
going on at length ah all the
things that were wrong with it and
why he didn't like it and they
concluded by saying um so in conclusion
i hate this sketch and it's trying
to kill me
they dropped it on the floor
wow
well
that's fun it's fun it seems to
get so mad about something like i
one time i said it with a
chuckle but i remember how fun it
was when my face got so hot
one thing that i would do in
the bang bang writers room is and
this was a tim keller this how
you would shoot especially this is how
he went he would put on his
jeans with the plastic butt cheeks
just like no i would i would
ah so much trouble i would if
anyone made any kind of ah spelling
or grammar or punctuation error i would
make them go back and rewrite it
um just for fun to like you
know but during the read through tim
cal packs would be like it
would be version six we would always
read the title and what version it
was and go version six and we
go this is the last one this
is the last version and then suddenly
we'd be reading i go hey hand
me you are pair of scissors and
he would go dammit and sit and
like crumple it up and like go
back to
the drawing board to do a version
fun it was fun we would have
to think a really good time it
would disrupt the day though and then
well i would dock their pay for
all their docs them i would talk
i would feel docs reveal the docs
their pay addresses on the internet for
all of this we had fun sometimes
we would have drawing comm
petitions that was fun where we would
like we would make neil campbell boats
and then we would all take ten
minutes to drive
ah sounds like just just a breakup
the day wow
no everyone liked to die or the
devil wears prada was based on use
god is that true
he's like the devil wears gucci
the devil were so fine jeans
at job something what did you drive
a chip clip
ah a chip clip well why are
you carrying a chip clip do you
have for meeting your boss oh man
i remember when i the first time
i was aware of a chip clip
and what an amazing invention that was
i thrive on having like everything like
this in my home like i want
to have all the things i'm going
to need and i love how this
is my chip clip do chips doesn't
work looks like a tongue it looks
like it's an owl
oh yeah i always like trying yeah
yeah of course especially when they're flying
okay okay laura that's scary now that's
scary do you do here's my question
wait hold it up again i'm gonna
get a screenshot of it
do
do chip clips work is my question
because are the tipping point whatever the
chip i got it lawrence they fricking
stale food no but that but but
chips if if you're trying to protect
them from air and all a chip
clip does is like crumple up the
bag in one part of it it's
not see
peeling it off completely so shouldn't you
if you're really concerned about your chips
when you put them into like an
airtight container like tupperware thing here's what
you do okay
can't believe have to walk you through
the checkout you can vote you fault
you fold the bag over i you
know press l or an over there
over i know i hand over i
know but i'm saying it's not airtight
and not like yeah out of everyone
deal yeah but it's casual with you
just kinda crumpled and you you clamp
the little thing on a club it's
a crumbling claim but here's the thing
that being said
i put those cadbury mini eggs in
an airtight jar and they are stale
and i they came that way the
end but there you go so that
dude that debunk your theory they didn't
steal them and disable them so you're
talking out of your ass but the
thing is you don't need them to
be vacuum seal because you're not gonna
keep these chips forever it's just you're
gonna work damn and within
so what is then the life i
want anyone who knows about chip clip
technology to write to us i o
does it if cn doesn't extend the
period and by how long and would
it be longer if they were in
a an airtight container yes well it's
like it doesn't extend the menzies by
the way someone has written to
us to say menzies is a medical
term and many people huh you wait
and somebody else was like whoa lord
knows i know what the fuck menzies
is get off my dick dick and
they thought now they the people were
under the impression that scott thought it
was a cute nickname for the menstruation
cycle now that but that's true that's
how i heard it
i think you thought it was oh
well then i guess you're correcting me
but i thought you thought it was
just funny because it was so proper
and not like no not that it
was proper i've just i've always heard
it in the in the term of
like mothers saying to their kid like
hey oh you got your menzies like
trying to make a cuter than it
was but people are so there's nothing
cute about the
it's about no nancy's it's a gross
word for a gross thing
we should never talk about it honestly
there'll be a mencius i feel like
it feels archaic that's why it's funny
to me like it feels like i
feel like it was like very like
it was a lot to say to
you on the phone like when she
gets her menzies it's like she's sure
she gets to me she's i thought
it should be
ie when she starts demonstrate like just
say it the way it is but
but apparently it is a medical term
and so hey hey everyone i shouldn't
have laughed i shouldn't have i should
know you are right to laugh but
oh it was hilarious am i right
to live yeah this one time
gnomes um in this instance
well alright goodbye
ah time for a game no play
a game it's not it's not oh
no this is just the second thing
when i'm playing game no honey what
was your favorite game as a kid
lauren what did you like to play
oh wow well i liked mario kart
in terms of video games um but
in terms of
board games like board games we played
a lot of board games so we
had we had a lot that were
just fun to set up like hotels
that game was always fun just looks
really i don't know hotels i don't
know oh hotels is just monopoly but
probably i don't think ever more so
it was happening and then i played
monopoly monopoly all the time but i
didn't understand what was
is happening there either and i had
a game called ready set spaghetti that
i enjoyed what and i just felt
like cooking you know what i really
liked that thing that's like it was
like a conveyor belt you just put
penguins on and they go up the
stairs oh yeah thing is going much
the thing is great that's always your
favorite board
i was not a big fan of
board games i liked i liked sorry
i liked ah so i remember liking
clue um close felt like it was
like you you got to really commit
and you gotta like yes play it
all the way through and three but
that's monopoly too it's always
give up monopoly in the middle of
it clues almost a weird game for
kids to play like it i wonder
if as an adult it would be
more enjoyable to play i thought it
was really fun because not not i
didn't think it was dark or anything
like that but it was just like
process of elimination like figuring out too
much like schools yeah it's like ordering
all
all board games are school's job you
know what i like don't say that
hungry hungry hippos
that's ah was that was a little
after my time when i was a
kid there was a game called don't
break the ice yeah oh yeah to
take well there's a version where you
have like the little ice cubes that
yeah six or the part where you
have the tissue and there's like i
don't know if this is was different
game issue and create like a rink
and then they have marbles on and
you've put everyone puts a drop of
water at a time until it totally
thaws epic wow yeah don't you remember
don't break the ice cut yeah i
do i didn't have it but yeah
the little yeah my cousins added ah
also come or plunk with the marbles
in the sticks yeah don't break the
ice you had all your ice cubes
and you had to tap them with
your little hammer
her and then it was is basically
genuinely little hammer yeah it was like
an opposite jenga no it's the same
principle same it just takes hides away
in jenga and jay do you ever
do you ever put things in i've
never played jenga while know what it's
all about who made it fall down
is ah it's all about taking things
away we have a gigantic jenga set
that i have
i've yet to set up does it
make you feel small i've well it's
just in a box right now but
it does yes yeah big box um
you're gonna have a party and we're
gonna play it yeah we should play
it sometimes vaccination giant jenga party yes
vaccination giant jenga bardi
surf music and wait for that rien
ne ne ne ne ne new vaccination
js party
like
we collected board games at my house
so we sort of like rich summer
i guess but we had stuff like
the happy days gang like anything that
was licensed we that stuff sure the
happy days games you have religious games
no we didn't have religious my my
parents love to play games like my
whole household is very competitive
native would you say it's a house
of games it's more of a house
of cards and game of thrones i
would say um but everyone very competitive
my brother and i would play games
together and get very there was like
a rule of whoever quit in the
middle had to pick up the game
because one
one of us eventually usually him would
be like this is stupid in like
storm off and it was like ok
well you got a twitter quitter cleans
up the game and then it was
also winner cleans up the game because
we were we were such bad winners
that you then had to like humble
yourself and clean up the game you
know
cause otherwise it would just be like
huh i'm so much better than you
and and my mother would not let
that stand but ah i just wanted
to show you guys that they have
operation for baby yoda o o operating
baby yoda so dumb because it's none
of his body parts to all just
like think the little gems will know
one wants to think about opening up
little baby yoda i don't want to
open up wow we grow and leave
grow go out of this i just
i think it'd be more fun if
they had his body and then you
had to like get his little ribs
making me hungry
operation is like really perverted when you
look look at this guy who's like
so he's wearing the hard ron is
underwear like hey doctor i'm in love
with you company oh i forgot that
it's all idioms or whatever yeah yeah
funny bone and pencil dick and the
wishbones so hard wishbone so
hard one i had a i had
a monopoly book that was all about
strategy what a nerd my guide and
read i would read it all the
time to sleep flashlight under the covers
and i was studying monopoly strategies i
remember like one of the strategies was
hide your money because
there's no rule that says that your
money has to be visible in monopoly
so it was like you know take
an extra thousand dollars and hide it
under the board so that when your
you know your opponent thinks that you're
you're broke suddenly you break out that
thousand dollars i remember i did that
one time my brother was like oh
and fare cheating
king and the board over and yeah
i always like to i liked with
monopoly like organizing my money right under
the tip of the board like perfect
little ones and fives tens and twenties
and then i would always be the
scottie dog and i was always younger
and didn't know i was going on
was probably the worst person to have
in there but
oh there's no difference between any of
them scott what was your tea i
know i know what i'm saying i
just only heard about that i was
i was the scottie dog because of
my name's sean then i think that
led my mother into thinking that i
liked scottie dogs and there was a
period of time where she gave me
gifts exclude
massively with scottie dog's on it including
making me a shirt with scottie dogs
on it when i was fifteen and
i and she was that now because
i'm very upset that i would never
wear to school and lie oh i
was like can i get away with
it can i put a jacket over
it like i did constantly trying
figure out how to not hurt her
feelings about this guy and you know
how when your parents just get that
in their heads of like oh they
like this thing yeah and then every
gift is that you know for for
a long time it was star wars
even after i was like mom i
hate star wars now after the prequels
i hate her were stopped giving me
star wars i would still get like
star wars books of
like all of their all of the
the vehicles in star wars and all
of the specifications and stuff you don't
like scottie dog here like star wars
i don't know what to do
that's very adorable it's adorable and i
would wear it now and i'd be
like yeah gets out but it at
the time it was just like mom
i'm fifteen and everyone already thinks i'm
a dork on a show school where
he goes scottie dog t-shirt and go
my name's scott look at my namesake
dogs on my shirt can
you can you all guess what my
monopoly token was for the thimble oh
top hat of course god themes think
of your penis who who who
wants to be the thimble so that's
that's my mom go bath test oh
my oh my oh no shit well
she quilts and sows and stuff so
she wow okay fair favre back story
to the debt over the okay top
scottie dog symbol raison because i just
had to scar yeah i had to
play monopoly on good girl
rls and we had a new board
and i didn't recognize some of the
pieces what were the old ones the
ones you're naming right but there was
but there must have been more right
there were more than four probably ah
jack was ira ai there was the
iron there was the boot there was
the wheelbarrow boo boo yeah so like
elf shoe and then there was the
the boat the tug
voter oh that's yeah okay and now
it appears that they have seven junkie
ah tick tock ah racks and f
g
there's a t rex there's a cat
there's a penguin there is a duck
you know it goes on animal weight
ducks how are dogs better the fire
ducks well nobody wants to be an
iron that was like the dust worth
no iron was weird why was that
in this it's so like fifties to
be like this is an important thing
thing the girl can be an iron
like not anything we should take a
break okay
bye
we are back and it's time for
one of our patented three jurors that's
right these are games that we play
submitted from audience suggestions and this was
more yep please send us more we
are running out um and this
one was suggested by scott aquaman in
an early episode of three edam and
it's called pitcher sit song and the
way this works everyone knows what you
do is you take an existing sitcom
name you inward or tower
or any television show it could be
a one hour
fair enough sure then you do the
opposite of it yeah as the title
and then so the person that's coming
example if it was family matters it
would be it would be enemies don't
matter right
enemies are irrelevant they're the enemies of
the opposite family right
and so then
ah then another player has to come
up with a theme song well that's
no that's that player doesn't that player
then pitch they'll show the one player
says here oh my god then the
other two players have to come up
with the theme song
and they have to describe what the
show is
yes because like this it goes like
this the fourth the one person comes
up with the name the other the
next person has to stay with the
opposite and title would be and the
third person who's theme song
the well that but the pitch you
guys are forgetting about the pitching part
of it like the the two people
have to have to pitch to the
person who gave the original sitcom they
have to pitch the show so i
say to lauryn happy days lauren has
to come up with sad mad months
got in and definitely what that show
is the two of us have to
then pitch it and go okay this
is
sad months and then we pitched the
show and then at the end paul
says well i really wanna hear what
the theme song is and then we'd
sing the theme song and we do
it over zoom
okay so paul do you want to
come up with the first show yes
i do happy
ah flea bag flea bag all right
this hi hi hi thank you so
much for hearing our pitch oh my
god i'm very glad i hear great
things about you too you're you're burning
up the internet when all of the
things that you do we are a
brother sister writing team of queer brothers
sister role i married well we were
featured on siblings are dating and we
hope that
that's why i'm thinking that yes yeah
we were heavily featured on that yeah
um and you know we came up
with this idea and it's been yeah
take getting so much traction it's called
moth box wave so you've been taking
these other places oh yeah no we
just post your last on our list
and yeah we did pitch to a
few places but we places are so
this is our safety this is
if the first twenty places turn us
down right so what we say well
you say it's gaining a lot of
traction what does that mean exact people
online love the idea completely out on
you put it online for free oh
yeah because we want to just see
what you know we've already made the
show and it's aired already on a
competing network
but that network is going under and
so we need to get it's creepy
we should just say it is creepy
quick bytes quiz actually queso
that's right quick so no melted cheese
please so yeah so anyway it's called
moth box and look smooth box and
we want to pitch you the essentially
the the story the idea the characters
i want to get all of those
the single old man lives
is alone and he is you know
we probably see his his relationship with
his wife for over the past seventy
years from them dating to them you
know living together or so getting it
good and they never get divorced they
they say they don't live together for
a brief period but they move back
in yeah they patch things up
up and then she dies and there's
a funeral and that's all done with
like a really sentimental montage and he
doesn't tie balloons to his house does
he he can if you like though
i mean one point yeah he does
so what he'd actually glee when he
does show my brother my brother kind
of misspoke what he does
is he doesn't tie balloons but he
ties gigantic moth wings so the top
of his house which he ditched together
from hundreds and thousands of mammoth sort
of died over the year because our
relationship so it's kind of symbolic of
the you know death of his relationship
and then also the rebirth could you
not sit on his lap while you
do the pitch it's just more comfortable
for me it's just
attracting it's very distracting
she can stop bouncing up and down
if you want okay but if you
stop kissing her neck i like that
list no problem no problem so anyway
ah i don't think you said you
would stop oh i think i've started
no stop you said oh doing it
no no well that's why i thought
it was so weird when you said
start
anyway if we have sex here no
anyway so ma to the pitch he
he ties these moth wings to his
house they flap up up in a
way like one make a race lap
the sort of just inherent their their
knowledge yeah they have like muscle memory
yeah you know what i mean they
want to go up and down it's
sort of natural yes nach
natural to want to go up and
down right honey a kobach come on
guys it's okay but have you ever
seen a brother and sister do this
stop that please
this is a place of business
i think this is good so anyway
it's a it's a box with moth
wings on it and it flies up
into the sun and explodes by it
way and really what's so great about
it is that it's about relationships it's
about you know sure bad relationship with
relationships is it about just this one
guy and his wife
who wasn't around anymore and so rosemary
lee know and then it's lost all
the moth wings to each other he
talks to the camera and it's exploring
sort of singledom and i just i
love it but now i thought i
thought i heard someone say that the
house flies up into the sun and
explodes oh yeah you
like minute three yeah so let's get
wicked right through that real quick so
in the first three minutes we see
this guy's life with his wife up
to the point where yes seventy years
old monetize he and then a montage
okay yeah and he builds the wings
out of he builds gigantic moth wings
out of countless dead ma
awww sad takes like ten seconds yeah
and it's honestly to higher love that
song but it's just as quickly just
just so really clear part of it
it's only ten secs so it's fair
use fair you gave me yeah
and then ran miya and that cuts
off and so we're out about two
minutes and forty seconds at this point
and then he presses a button the
moth wing start to flap and so
it's not muscle memory there's there's a
button know it's it's fun just to
allow speaker that says hey triggers them
to do what they are they want
to do says hey start flapping wing
the allowed speed
okay he allowed speaker and then they're
kind of all sitting there going god
i wish i could flap and like
they don't give them permission okay but
does the audience they privy to any
of this any of the the fire
mar sending were sending footnotes and send
a packet to every house and then
we're also planning to have like an
app that you can think
with the show and like this second
string theory and what it is is
talk about that and it's really exciting
because what it is is the app
works like a viewfinder and you hold
it up to the tv and you
see something totally different when looking at
your phone so you actually have to
look at your phone the whole time
if you hire a time yeah yeah
like what like like what you tried
to see a product in your home
via a show
shopping app yeah and ah you exactly
except this happen this happens more of
like what people are saying about the
show and about just various things in
life in general and like people that
you would follow they're saying things and
it's short things and you know he's
into it i love this are you
talking about what we're doing physically right
now yeah it's getting to be
going okay i've never seen a brother
sister do this before this is exciting
but i do wish i'd read it
out by horn i'm ready to buy
the show and also ready to do
something else but let me ask you
is there a themed song to the
show of course that's the first fifteen
seconds of the show okay let me
yeah fifteen seconds
i'll i'll sing it for you
when
when the moth bag leaks with bag
she's getting to them off box part
of it yeah i'm just sorry i
was just talking about when the month
bag leaks
have you gotta put it in a
mouth boss so the sopping juices with
the coke news of the box
but he is a low moon doesn't
have no one to go
he's a little love bo dogs he's
the buddy hey if you see in
the foot notes he can trigger the
box to fly with
okay so that's it so that's the
and then the mataji daughter honor the
self show and then the suite then
the footnotes and people might throw out
they think it's like junk mail or
something so we just want to cover
our bases yeah well we're putting a
bed bath and beyond coupon on the
footnotes as well so has to grab
onto it a little people
i'll save it forever yeah yeah exactly
yeah so what do you think i
think i am turned on and i
do what to buy the show but
in all candor this is not my
office my brother works here and he
went to the bath
room oh who's your brother my brother
is the person you were supposed to
be meeting with i think oh okay
your mother's phil do this with him
i will now
come over here okay
and see
yeah
whoa sick hey very sickening sick annie
okay so i'm gonna come up with
the name the original sitcom title yeah
which is
it's a show we haven't done probably
i mean not that it really matters
because i feel like it's not gonna
be the same idea but let me
just think um ok okay the hogan
family
oh the hogan family not valerie family
not valerie it was just called valerie
oh that's right and then it became
the hogan family with sandy duncan ok
hi thanks for letting us pitch to
you today this is very exciting do
i have to be here yes you
do your part of that you're an
integral part of the pitch to add
i just pleased isaak problem there's no
problem just a father and son having
normal father and senator actions okay because
i actually
the look i put you guys at
four thirty because i might i to
be walking out the door so we
wanna make this a little bit quick
okay totally friendly for baseball practice you're
not you're not late i had you
withdraw from the team i called and
said that you quit but i'm the
star player i was gonna win your
championship today now you're the star player
of this pitch
alright the tv business is boring do
you mind if i play on my
phone and i do actually if you
wouldn't mind we'd like to get right
down to the pitch we we got
to show we think you're gonna love
okay
lay it on me so what's the
title the title is the sh the
shellshock ball the fuck boy knife friends
the fuck boy knife a friend yes
yes okay so this is kinda edgy
this is what well it's streaming streaming
yes you spell fuck boy without the
key
a dad remember so two c's and
an eye at the end i know
i know i read the page so
it's spelled f u c k b
o o o i have used god
how old are you son
wow top does he really want to
know no he doesn't cheese i'm interested
is tell me i'll do think i
am sixteen yes good my shoulder seventeen
go up it's just great on this
great seventeen and a half higher you
are killing it go seventy or three
quarters more
seventeen and five eighths that's it now
it's i'm turning eighteen in just three
eighths wow well you're very accomplished for
your age congratulations thank you this is
my office and it is huge glass
walls stunning absolutely amazing and i do
have amazing budgets i can offer you
if you
wow me with this fuck boy knife
but fuck boy my friends okay it's
it's a it's a story of ah
a bunch of fuck boys and
hey they love to whittle and they're
trying to they're trying to stop being
fuck boys this part of the based
on my life so it's partly based
on myself if you buy this then
you're going to have to give me
money to ease ease of fuck boy
who wanted to become a baseball player
and where lying is baseball in the
show yes with
oiling stands in for baseball
so when these guys when they they
they do it at a huge field
umm think they cover a wide area
like three guys go way back in
the field then there's three guys that
are in the middle and then there's
a guy that's on a little hill
and then there's a guy that loves
to squat and whittle at the same
time
i love that and you know they're
all friends obviously um and they what
they do is they whittle things the
whittle they whittle things they wish they
could fuck so as to not fuck
them and that's that in baseball what
that stands for is when you when
you're going up against a p
etcher and you hit a ball
yes like i have five three now
and i couldn't have said it better
myself look honestly this this i have
to tell you the market is all
about theme songs so as much as
i love what you're saying about this
whole plot and stuff i really think
we need to hear a song so
i can just know if it's got
any any legs who okay
well ah do you want to sing
yeah well i'm i'm the singer of
the family obviously it's true i can't
carry a tune wow whoa i'm trying
to sing the national anthem that was
really bad i know and your son
looks like justin bee bay i do
a lot of people know that we
almost named him ebay because when he
was born we looked at baby pictures
of justin ebay
and we said this looks like the
same guy yes i can see that
i've had a lot of danger area
yeah evelyn is my name um and
so i'm the one who i have
choir practice that was supposed to be
after baseball practice you know i'm checking
out and oh god dad withdrawing you
from the choir wow hey because we're
about to be miller
renee oh that's right and what is
the show called again fuck the look
boy nice family okay anyway the fuck
point i phone my friends alright here
we go
the fray hey hands are over he
their footballers they all have an i
have an i've friends with my knife
did any body tell you it was
gonna be that way
and then they got an eif and
then they went on their way oh
say can you see
the dawn's early la manana papa la
madonna papa oh ma i did it
ma y cha
it is what do you think
that's an expensive song it's about twenty
songs mixed together there's one last part
to it there's a lady who knows
all that glitters is like begged you
not yet
okay and she's bi until doing it
stay away to just interrupt me if
you're gonna bite in the room just
in a rummy to have the huh
keep going
i don't know any of the other
words that dad was like oh wow
okay okay your stop stop stop soft-top
oh she's doing it she's gonna it
i will give you
one hundred dollars to leave and drive
your car to the side of my
building
this is tempting do we have to
be in the car when it hits
the side of the build ideally we
ideally but not decided necessity i'm just
saying it's ideal let me ask you
if when we got here we accidentally
drove the car into the side of
the building already will you still pay
us one hundred dollars
yeah did that happen yes and we
have a deal
we're shaking hands with or sell a
way to culver city
thank you for seeing us in three
p m and culver city
and see ah guys i think we're
at a time i don't want to
we are we are we gotta go
we are out of time um thank
you so much for listening at cetera
whatever you weirdos do well you turn
this on oh we don't care as
long as everything they do
maybe you're taking a bath while you
listen oh i do wanna thank you
for that thank you for checking thank
you for taking the bear oh didn't
do lou garvin found the top until
your ass
then stop until your ass the top
or the bottom of the the so
fine part oh yeah when you get
into the soap like mice so fine
hurt
so five parts alright follow every rule
and say goodbye alright goodbye
uh