maria
ah
a
three am is the name of the
game if you miss you must have
or do say what some childhood playground
games i'm recalling avocado anybody shimmy shimmy
koko bop shimmy shimmy oh what's brought
to you by tom hanks son right
that's right apparently it's called
olin yeah apparently it's calling a sunday
a mouthful and oko i always wondered
know people have been saying it wrong
for years it's colin hanks but what
about colin powell like here's a guy
who ever would he could just say
like oh it's pronounced collin but instead
he's like oh no effect here yes
it's pronounced colan please like figure gets
connected because he waiting for his pay
wants to die for you to say
oh let's call it balmy college
the thing we call connected shit oh
shit bo what does avocado though it's
some game for i remember from when
i was little it's like avocado is
the name of the game if you
miss you must have a word to
say and it's like then you say
like avocado something something any you have
to have a word everybody says of
ocado is something on the
cloudy just say oh let's try avocado
okay then you say cara co oh
i don't know it's probably some bushy
game like we play
we almost played it and yeah those
were close well it came really close
but it was scary because we didn't
know how but yeah that's never stopped
us before that's true i can look
it up you're right avocado game see
if it says something handy lotto game
fart three thousand that's it the avocado
game by genre
you look up avocado hand clapping game
okay because there is i don't remember
knew how to look up avocado hancock
became loren lapidus yeah that'll get you
there avocado hand clapping more like his
childhood lauren lucas memories
yeah i can just access your match
now if we could do that that's
like an ex michael shell gondry film
here's i forgive me this is gonna
come out of nowhere yeah all i
don't forgive you i think what we
do you would have ok i think
there should be a domain an internet
domain that dot oops
oh and why what happened for like
mistakes when you accidentally go to a
different website because it's funny just to
say i involved up kid daddy oh
you know when you probably can't like
like arden's website for a podcast is
at like dot vodka oh will you
accept this oh yeah because because the
real domain is probably not vodka
dot com but they but you can
get to it by just going so
when you could do dupes yeah we
could do it let's do a threesome
usa dupes and our website is what
i don't think we have one and
our website is what by the way
we try to put on there paul
i forgive you but i never forget
wow well thanks i don't want to
be forgotten
i remember you in this thing that
you said always i'm too sweet to
be for gotten that's so that's a
great math problem too sweet
oh okay here's an avocado clapping home
video
what kind of a child explain this
to me use these with her mother
zap mitigate it
if you change your name
dick they forgot the o
okay so it's if you miss the
handclaps you have to say a word
yeah and that's you changing your name
i think v
see so um oh so she must
go to view since she messed up
oh these two love each other huh
two name options and we're just going
take yourself so cute yeah is she
cute it's just very cute in her
mom is just lovingly looking at her
like this is the best thing
that's how you play the koto but
ah to show you this okay i
got no sense of value play this
from well i got something i will
definitely remember half of that for the
next time i bring this up specific
type of hand clapping right yeah like
bottom bump bump said you mow that
my here say a b c d
symptoms
you have to say too so then
what had happened so she missed she
missed on like two times some first
z or something i don't know ah
fuck carrot carrot of course and scary
gape it and the big sexy stay
joni mitchell but hey
again just like that janie and i
are watching it started a startup yeah
wait wait wait how did i miss
this is it on your feet it's
heard some say oh i'll pay for
this shit maybe only okay great i
don't want to pay but i'm really
excited we that's so amazing it's why
lee first two okay
they dropped two is the new model
is dropped to drop one one one
one one yeah two okay let me
see if i can get this too
it's very sunny was robert two then
one one one one one one one
and the two anyone can do the
first one i never miserable and you
can do it i didn't remember if
you can remember the first the first
night would be too and so it
ended i was like man i wish
i could binge it and then the
next one came up i went oh
fuck and then after that they had
the trailer for the rest of the
season and i saw aden and i
cried sure i even know he was
already coming ice but i would say
aden is her once aden the one
that got away alright so i'm pretty
excited um and the first they're getting
really sexual in these first episodes who
much it's so horn town miranda's fully
nude
multiple times miranda um cynthia nixon did
she ask for this she's like i'm
never gonna be oh i do listen
to la
that's fucking hilarious we show my i
don't care anymore that's really funny i
do listen to the companion podcast from
the writers oh she's like that which
i really enjoy yeah it's the all
the friends holding hands dr who's companions
and what if the sex and the
city girls all had to have a
companion on the show well it's very
good
real women i'm sorry um like sober
companion my pilot that didn't go last
year oh i'm so sorry hearing that
you brought up that phrase we were
there with you when you heard yeah
it was disappointing it was an odd
day it was disappointing but it was
okay i remember we were holding your
hands yeah and i was weeping yeah
yeah and we said why don't you
get into the pool
and then no one can tell you're
crying yeah and we were at airwolf
so it was weird but i didn't
get any um i got into europol
i went into the url for which
is always full of podcasters with their
electrical equipment it's very dangerous um but
the podcast he met michael patrick king
talks about asking cynthia nixon to do
that full
the nude scene because there's shit down
on one knee yeah will you please
he held a row he knew it
was a funny scene though wasn't a
sex scene when she's fully know she's
in a sensory deprivation tank and then
you see her footboard and he he
was doing that happened to him getting
the sailing in his eye right and
then he asked her would you be
eat fully naked for this because it's
funnier if you're fully naked and she
was down and then they were like
you know that's twenty five years of
trust from working together for so long
i was like i get that i
thought that was good and it was
funny or that she was naked if
she was in her bikini or something
i wouldn't have been asked it was
funnier but not that necessary it's not
necessary yeah yeah no it's not necessary
it was because it was now
not a plot point no it was
just a version seen although jamie and
i talked about this she's getting to
be funny so far in the season
yeah way that she was not allowed
to because it wasn't lasting i don't
know that much about it but it
wasn't last season a drag or something
well i loved it but it was
like she's going through her divorce and
all this stuff and so it's like
very she doesn't have as much fun
this is a more fun light hearted
it isn't fair we did talk about
how the there were things in the
previously on that absolutely did not matter
i didn't remember any second up to
say i was shocked and then and
then there were things in the episode
that was like oh right she was
an alcoholic like that they did not
think why didn't they put them in
the re
recap yes exactly they don't kept talking
about the met ball and and making
you think like okay this episode is
gonna start that high notions you've happened
yeah you're thinking of the met gala
oh yeah are those two different things
will know the map ball or the
mets in charge of one of these
i think it's the same thing but
i think what they what it was
that they only went to the
the party portion leading go on the
red carpet oh is the guy yeah
the distinction i think that guy includes
the carpet and the party i just
don't know i just i think it's
called the ultimate vp but show i've
never heard met ball in my life
maybe they can't say my god oh
yeah it's like it's like when you
talk but even for bullets like the
big game yeah you
can't say that and say the super
bowl yeah that's so like i said
it's just a thing in the world
unless you have a deal with them
where you're the official chip or whatever
of it you have to be like
hey you ready for the big game
on sunday i'm sorry that's bizarre because
i think super bowl is just a
word transcendent like yeah just watch the
ultimate football championship brand it's like mickey
mouse like yeah
yeah you can say mickey mouse i
don't know but i like especially especially
because mickey mouse now describes something like
oh boy that's really mickey mouse you
know right in the public domain now
no she doesn't know disney keeps so
why is emails the word for things
that are kind of janky i don't
get that cause i'm i'm actually making
mouse's perfect he early on is the
perf
picked male specimen he's a big winner
so he's not like it but this
is what peak male
here's a surplus yeah buttons on shirts
he has a shirt white caucasian flesh
colored face rest your bodies black um
sort of little lego like i say
yeah
i is it that in the early
cartoons he was bad at building things
wow this teaser slap and hammers and
nails and stuff i kinda can picture
that maybe he's become so not funny
was he he used to be hilaire
so he's more of a straight man
he's kind of like the every man
he's kind of the charlie brown he's
kind of like he's just like see
things are happening to him and around
him yeah well he's also like now
he has to be so well-meaning and
like on the kids side about everything
of like oh no let me help
you you know like really inside well
you know like if he goes
district and see see like fantasmic or
whatever it is sasha yeah mcmahon mickey
mouse's phantasm oh my bad i don't
know if that is just fuckin balls
with spikes coming towards zero just just
yeah phantasm was a was a horror
movie from the early eighties right i
remember seeing late commercials when i was
a kid and it was terrifying oh
it's it's
really good because it good oh yeah
it's great yes it was mickey mouse
they'd be like the spiky balls would
have ears floating spiking ball yeah yeah
we'd like hidden figures yeah but slash
everybody dimmick hey didn't make love to
find a hidden mickey mickeys starting jamal
hey hey hey mickey so malaysia jamelle
melee almost got it um oh
holly knows who mickey mouse now she
says oh thank god his mountain emailing
your everyday house she refuses to call
him by his first day yeah yeah
it's the last name based why would
why would she know like what a
shame she's into a couple of disney
movies but then i guess mike showed
her steamboat willie shore oh
oh and then now that shows her
his steam no no don't be disgusting
and it played that little clip plays
at the beginning of disney right every
every movie and so she knows that
his little ass and whistling and she
has a couple of disney movies she
likes monsters inc monsters university and cocoa
monsters incredible cool yeah that's
what inc stands for right yeah she
likes those three we've been watching monsters
university like in pieces oh i'm very
familiar with that film now i love
that show but it makes me cry
yeah monsters university diseases universe pieces i
haven't seen it you gotta come on
scott as it's going to be i'm
not going to show
but anyway she says mouse and i'm
very excited we're gonna go to disneyland
sand and shit oh really man this
is her only word is that correct
it's all she's got no she's got
many words and they're really really mary
babysat her last night and had to
like to say for a lot of
her words and it was so funny
to hear her language from mary like
she was like she was like gah
goo ga-ga
i was like oh i was dying
that roku the child she be covered
in pillows it was like a whole
thing where i also means cover me
into like cover like it was like
color like your answer yeah jago
mary gugu
because i'm like she's like she's so
adamant she's like
mary cover mian pillows if i asked
her probably for five hundred dollars or
more or more i'll just i'll take
five hundred
very very particular skill
i'll cover you in pillows but it's
gonna cost you five hundred
um ah so did did holly have
to demonstrate gugu so she pulled her
arm she eventually pulled mary's arm to
like get her to understand that she
says landry yeah yeah i mean if
you ever wanna babysit it's it's your
it's available to you and i um
i'm gonna do it she was well
she probably would but she was i
will i went to i say go
to her
yeah and then she covers you close
this guy gets it yeah yeah
and then i said okay yeah they
had a fun hero paul died
a baby or baby suffocated they laughed
on the news
he had all the power to get
up the only time they've ever left
on the news he let it happen
oh wait they didn't even apologize yeah
um but yeah no i had the
premiere last night for the outlaws i
was telling oh yeah netflix film coming
out july seventh and i so maybe
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
but it was it was so cute
she fed her dinner and they huh
what does she mention last night she
had annie's mac and cheese
and us annie's brand oh it's a
brand and like one thousand strawberries mary
techsmith is there is is there a
thing as too many strawberries and i
said no
chick almost ate the whole box i
was just like if she's eating something
with you i'm thrilled yeah yeah i'll
like do so and you will eat
any she did marry reader a story
she read a few stories and then
then when it's time for bed how
i got very upset and then she
she's being around there yeah and then
marry patrick malone was taking her and
she was
really upset and then she was like
what do you need and she like
pointed dramatically at her milk bottle that
was left in the big bed
and mary was like oh you did
your mail going to and then she
was like yeah
ah just fine
and then she went to bed she
takes her milk to bed with her
she sometimes does which now sounds like
a luxury sometimes yes milk oh i
love it it was literally as co
last couple weeks i just allowed it
and then it kind of yeah interesting
she'll finish it and then fall asleep
i love it yeah love it yeah
yeah it's great it's great i guess
i'll drink it out of a baby
bottle again you know what would be
so cute
it wouldn't be weird at all actually
for my for my brother's baby shower
for my brother's wife's baby shower years
ago others speak wow it was his
and hers but i ran some games
for it yeah my quarterly you gotta
run relay race and one of them
was to drink out of a bottle
as fast as you can and my
remember my dad brother having to do
it and it was like is it
really hot
hard because like it's doesn't come out
quickly right and so it was like
kind of like they're both getting headaches
i was like this is like an
insane game oh babies do it
so trying to chug it was a
psychotic game and it was really funny
does that mean that babies are just
like taking their time when they're drinking
out of a bottle i mean i
mean that's a problem with ami's she
always wants to gulp everything so like
with her water bottle or nipple ah
no now she's okay with the milk
but
jeans it's actually with wildly different hole
sizes be right yeah yeah we we
had to expand it ah yeah when
when she's really young it's really tiny
and then you know but there was
a time when she was like gulping
down eleven ounces would just like in
three minutes bubbled up up but now
with a why would she show up
no
oh no she just loves me but
you know now with the water it's
like she loved to eat she loves
it the water she loves water and
she'll just like sunk so much through
the straw that it just like dribbles
down her
because wrong with it i don't know
i've been wondering that i need to
ask her but we talk yeah you
should take her to a scientist i'm
hoping that her first year talkers broader
yeah you want her first words to
what's wrong what's wrong with it yeah
because like you saying what's wrong with
you what's yeah yeah i would love
her just answer me no i think
a scientist would be interested in her
like e t
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i
kind of like what's up like let's
see what happens when you get home
why don't you put some gray makeup
on or put her in a ditch
let's see if a scientist comes along
oh please there's more
sure scientists love a little great thing
in a ditch oh yeah there's i
said about scientists they intentionally live far
away from the lab so they can
mute and pass by ditches yeah yeah
in case there ever any little gray
when they're on their way to their
podcasts yeah ride bikes all scientists ride
bikes i just love bike rides they
think it's the best way to get
to work rain or shine
shine yeah yeah yeah like no sleep
there like mailmen no sleep yeah hey
helmet hey we have we have slow
slow slow seat hail we got scale
heil oops
that is scary scale dot hoops i'll
scale that hoops we should get scaled
oops that's our whips and sell threesome
scales when is this episode like the
scales of justice dropping i to be
honest i don't know but i mean
i think i think right before your
movie maybe but in july yeah i
want to ask you're doing for the
fourth oh no don't have any plans
great zero i'll be hanging out as
well not not here should we throw
some fireworks and i'm on your billable
are available now i'm going to be
in a different place where are you
going to be growing you're going to
a second location go to a second
location on the fourth of july um
i'll be in i'll be in michigan
city indiana wow
whoa yes it sounds random because it
is i'm going to chicago for for
a while and then i go just
for like ah around that time but
then my brother and my sister-in-law and
i and our kids and mike were
all going to go to an air
bnb on the beach talk louder oh
nice nice looks
lately we've never done that and yeah
the united indiana you said yeah michigan
city indiana it's on the lake like
michigan i never think of a well
yeah just like chicago is so loops
are underneath and around up to michigan
you know but um it is one
of the great lakes it is a
great lake and i'm excited to have
what's your favourite to tea
e my favorite like is like michigan
because it's the one that i really
know about you
elsinore
okay interesting minds nes
and so you're really doing nothing for
the fourth i don't we don't have
any plans we haven't discussed you usually
do so we're not talking to each
other oh okay right now you're just
waiting to give you a backyard screening
we could do a good screen it'll
be fun yeah let me let me
bring that up what movie would you
watch i don't know something just some
dumb born before the
we tried yeah we tried to
fun to watch it under the stars
yeah we didn't we try to watch
the green night one night and then
afterwards we we saw the green knight
were like that would have been terrible
for a backyard screen because so like
wyatt and because there was somber there
was something where some wrong with the
projector basically what happened was my garage
ah where i keep the projector
there's an incline to get to it
and i just let go of the
cart and traveled all the way die
and crashed into our gaze oh my
guy and the projector was fucked up
and these guys came over and we
were like wow we can't do this
but we didn't look cool yeah yeah
i mean it was i mean i
got ran after i ran after almost
it was like one of those singers
like in slow motion i almost got
it but but missed it but um
yeah that would be that would be
green knight is a movie that i
saw on the big screen really enjoyed
it and then i've not thought this
many times but i thought i wish
i'd been high watching the green knight
i don't think i know what that
is oh man it kinda came and
went although it was it was talked
about
yeah no no oh it's like setback
in ah you know green night days
yeah so like medieval times yes yeah
and dev patel is in it is
it actually um yeah oh yeah he's
great yeah it's a dallas fans totally
i love i don't like he doesn't
get his flowers yeah i know he's
so good
good and everything he does he's like
he's like a it's weird when a
famous person is under-rated yeah maybe he
actually is yeah he's great he always
is only good about homes twice a
week he's in good films he's fantastic
i remember every time i'm always thinking
about him yes but it's like like
you guys i just picture jason peterson
misstep yeah and i think we take
that for granted i guess so although
the israel okay yeah i've never really
watched that good don't ever okay so
is he on that yeah yeah he
was was really weird and i was
finding out all the hot actors of
that year and you put them on
that and everyone was like lily this
just sucks
sorry alison pill well i'm catching up
on succession season three oh great i'm
so behind i am and guess what
it's really good does this ring any
bells don't ding delete eighty
a bombay
going to stick
and we're back and okay so i
had something happen to me the other
day again this is not a story
good or bad
neutral bad i mean bad for everyone
involved what okay something bad for everyone
involved yeah i'm losing you and well
incluging or when he just tells the
story and you can decide what i
should have done holding i would guess
this is kind of a what would
moral oil work what would you do
what would you do was
that is that the theme to what
would you do that's the theme from
what would you do from news program
ninety show host marc summers uh oh
the news program don't you love it
when jon jones is like yeah would
you would you do i like you
saw this bitch screaming mr yeah there
is a
a phrase that he said that the
phrase that pays it's just in my
brain forever where he's you know they're
going through the scenario and they still
there there was one person after another
doing whatever and then he goes look
at this guy wow look at this
guy oh my god i love how
he ducks he talks like this look
at this guy what would i wanna
hear we're gonna shame we also haven't
talked abou
about the curious case of natalia grace
on ah fantastic it's true we haven't
talked about it's a really good show
overall it feels like the kind of
thing john kyoto's would host what it
was it's a document only thought that
he would host one show which would
you like i was saying this show
you get it there's a guy with
a white hare who's like keith morris
yeah and we didn't know if this
was a child or an adult but
it was this orphan all that she's
seen yeah we needed that on the
john donkey series would you do i
think that's amount of plain ones know
you think you saw him that's incredible
you saw him on a plane yeah
and people are coming up to him
going i love your show people
we're coming ups
spy love your stroh i follow this
like blog that i followed for like
twenty years probably weblog yeah and i
followed it for like fifteen years and
this this i really enjoy but there
was ah they now send an email
in the email title and some people
out there might know what i'm talking
about i'm not gonna name it but
exam a fan but the email subject
line was so i got like celebrity
gossip and i was like oh
ooh celebrity gossip and opened it up
and was that her friends saw the
priest from from flea bag on a
plane i was like that's na casa
i want a society want things about
him did he famously say i will
never fly on a plane yeah just
was like don't call it that if
it's not that i got my hopes
up okay so what happened that was
bad
alright so i'm at a wedding oh
no friend's wedding oh god and once
people lots of people very fun lots
of skeet i mean sleep i think
like nicely beg your pardon events me
very fun and it's it's getting late
into the celebration or you have to
dance now the regular crouch i've used
before
the dancing okay they cut the cake
so right right because the slice slice
that's exactly yeah yeah pieces together
policy i've finally seen it yay
i actually was so impressed by that
woman saying all that stuff
that's hard to say without tripping over
yourself yeah yeah yeah so the kick
gets cut and i go over and
grab a piece of cake and it
looks really the bridegroom still standing there
and i'm still in there never was
actually putting the piece towards her mouth
and oh wow he puts his everyone's
got their cake everything's cool i'm labour
it was some sort of chocolate
ing chaga wedding now you don't see
chocolate everyday at a wedding and i
love to true i love chocolate cake
i didn't even have chocolate my own
wedding why why wow so i grabbed
the piece of cake and i and
i come over to where everyone's kind
of congregating and i take up i
take my fork and i take a
bite of it on earp up
i cut a piece of forkful yeah
and i'm lifting it to my mouth
now is there a worm on it
no
okay half a word of quarter four
so i'm lifting you up to my
mouth and suddenly someone someones mother from
the wedding party takes us a stumble
oh no a nasty fall and falls
like right and not right in front
of me really don't like when people
fall yeah i hate it
it's it's i think you're i think
about flowing all the time yeah and
yes it's like i i i was
reading suppress about tom segura as new
special and i guess his wife like
fell downstairs it's it's one of my
big horrible pet peeves when people fall
we're having fun here why did you
do that
alright so this this older woman falls
not in not directly in front of
me there's still is like a a
group of people around me who can
help her you're on you're better than
me so you're having a larry david
moment i'm like do i eat the
cake i literally am like i'm look
i'm going to look like an asshole
if i eat this bite so i
put the fork
of know we've had and i but
then i'm like i can't walk away
to eat it because then i look
like i don't care about the situation
so i'm just sitting here like moving
back and forth going how soon is
too soon to take this delicious baie
moving battle bad bad thing that happened
to like wanna say hey you didn't
know if you could bite it because
and i can
i'm there like a pirates of the
caribbean animatronic yes it's just kind of
going back and forth like i'm going
moving closer going no no i can't
i put it back and then and
then i'm like i really want this
piece why should they the game was
finally a five about five minutes oh
no there's like i could do when
everything looked oklahoma hear everything you could
say i think i walked away and
i finally have that piece
okay i know is it so good
and she's okay i think so did
anyone hs ok didn't follow you know
i don't think anyone was trained on
me because this terrible thing was happening
by just felt very obese children if
there's a wedding video where she's got
she fault everyone's like oh my god
and then there's you
no actually i didn't actually shake his
hand going up down uptown like is
is this weird it's just weird oh
my god i felt so self-conscious now
with camera phones that stuff can happen
you know
absolutely
wow apparently also at the wedding i
left before this drama but apparently a
neighbor because he was out of a
house that has public events but that
had you know residential neighbors right apparently
a neighbor got so upset at the
noise that you start bum rushing everyone
got pepper sprayed by security
people are actually out of there people
are out of their minds these days
i do worry about that yeah i
don't worry about it i feel like
it'll sort itself out people being insane
right now no mental health help in
the world balances out
um speaking of almost putting a forkful
of something in your mouth one time
janie and i were out to dinner
um we were heading to generally ran
into somebody that we knew we said
come have dinner with us we're having
a lovely time and this friend starts
telling me he told us a story
sorry about this guy that used to
work with at a gas station and
the guy would bring a briefcase to
work every day like he he sort
of he he was like a guy
who acted as if he had maybe
he was in special forces or something
like that like active
he tried to act like a cool
tough macho guy and then ah one
day they opened up his briefcase and
there was nothing in it and so
they put which they figured right you
know whatever it was it was like
inconsequential and then they put a ah
that series so lexa someone's alexa
do you have i brought my lecture
with me is that weird oh yeah
i can run my legs ways introduce
us i plugged it in i got
call your wife
yeah i guess i want to know
what the weather was before he left
i wonder why they named her alexa
maybe because it's a word that no
one ever said when someone a certain
kind of but ceres worse because you're
always saying i'm sorry and then it
turns on you're always saying you're saying
yes and councillor i'm sorry i'm so
i'm sorry cut-up seem so scary
i'm serious oh my god i'm very
sorry to hear that i um so
ah so they put something inside bilbo
and his briefcase with the delay where
did they i didn't know i seem
to have a dildo
right here behind this prank was playing
oh okay yeah they were less why
let's put the builder with their
let's let the community know he has
it on his desk what he found
it in his briefcase with the restroom
key is attached i was thinking on
the way here about the phrase oh
i'm sorry please so so we're laughing
at the story and then i ask
our friend
well what happened to the guy after
that and i had a forkful of
food and i was bringing up to
my mouth and our friend said oh
he killed himself
i froze i never knew i'd ever
get a free steak i did a
free take where i was like i
literally did not know what to do
here it's true it's shocked me to
my core isn't true
oh my god fucking eye with the
del dolce
i think because he was humiliated he
was humiliated that's tragic yeah that's not
a fun story then if if that
i just thought you meant like oh
he was very troubled and years later
he did that he did it because
of the dildo thing i think it
was not long after that i really
don't like gosh yeah yeah you don't
know if you're supposed to take a
bite it's not that i was trying
to decide what to do i was
was capable of doing it did you
ever take the bite no it's still
there my god you still have that
before oh dang years old it's rotten
cheese that's right your alexa that psycho
hey well you are alexa am i
psycho yeah i found this on the
web
you are you bitch
ah
it is wedding season though isn't it
so true oh but i was gonna
say i was thinking anyway here about
the phrase weddings yeah i was what
does it like i was sitting with
my thumb up my ass yeah like
like i was thinking it's kind of
a funny phrase like um if you're
like i made a start i made
up a whole scenario my head on
the way here of like what would
be funny if someone was like oh
do you go to
the that birthday party of someone you
hate or whatever and then i know
like what do you do instead i
sat at home with my thumb up
my ass and i was like that's
kind of like it's a really harsh
thing to say it's usually it's directed
at other people it's like you're like
sitting around your thumb but i thought
it was funny to say might yourself
like weird how much you didn't want
to go to the stage to take
ownership of it yeah
instead i chose to put my thumb
up my ass like i so didn't
want to go another great ass related
phrase if it was up your ass
you'd know if it was stressing like
where we're literally my keys if they
were up your ass you know yeah
yeah that's so eighties isn't it it
feels really nice thing to say to
love it feels like something to be
a john hughes movie
i would i would think it's ninety
nine percent of the time you say
that to someone who's someone you live
with and love because otherwise nine hundred
percent you live love and laugh with
you relax you're at the lake with
them like would you be saying that
to a coworker oh yeah well if
they if they asked you know yeah
yeah yeah yeah in our line of
work i think you care of those
files
you know it is okay that's the
if it were up your ass you
know challenge three-time champ yeah say that
to your boss yeah today if only
if your boss asks for files and
only if your boss is cool as
hell yeah no i think i think
anyway like you want people to get
fired this is the test
to see if the bosses yeah oh
okay fair and i think it cannot
be about files to like if you're
working at a pizza place and saying
where's the mozzarella cheese if it was
up your ass you know i think
it has to imagine being at a
pizza place in losing trackers electrodes and
honestly if it was up my ass
i don't know if i would know
yeah the ball we need to like
where yeah where is this
an emergence of important ingredients dough we
have tomato sauce has peppers pepperoni olives
but we don't have the cheese no
cheese all day no cheese old bay
we went to lake arrowhead as i
mentioned recently and we went to this
pizza place and then we were waiting
it was gonna to a forty five
minute wait
remember you until you go ahead you
came back with that lake arrowhead accent
i know i was only there for
like a few days i know so
braddy of me but then this guy
was like have you been here before
like the se waiting in line to
to like say to us how long
how long is the wait today i
don't know i guess there's like a
thing there and i'm like i heard
forty five minutes he goes is this
your first time here
and we said yeah and he's like
it's the best pizza on to say
the best pizza on the mountain or
the best pizza and i'm like yeah
this the bars low yeah yeah it's
like it's mess it's dominos i saw
one other one like it was good
but i was like i hit all
my pizza sea level yeah every individual
place on the mountain would have the
best of whatever it is yeah yeah
exactly
yeah yeah it's the best gas on
the mountain the best milk on the
mountain best known yeah best luhya tissues
ah tissues on the mountain you get
ah you get a car freshener you
get um shit you get ah ah
you know ah
come on well you could put your
avocado coordinating the lamy put it in
the mess in the cigarette lighter you
say you put it in the cigarette
lighter or else i guess oh my
god i saw something really funny i
went to um i know thank god
something i went to mormon i said
thank god ah child's birthday party ah
last weekend
and were you invited eighty buys no
don't tell me you saw aliens like
in signs no i didn't what my
favorite line of i saw signs in
aliens my favorite
don't go in here aliens um by
favorite line of dialogue from the movie
signs was when the the aliens were
on the news they you know they
took over for the anchor you're like
well a little
the story was being reported on the
news and the the ah anchor said
in voice-over the images were taken by
a forty year old at a child's
birthday party
why is like the clunky why would
so need to know the person's exact
age i don't show the video yeah
it's also outing someone's age which is
kind of rude yeah can you imagine
you captured the video of the alien
and you've been telling all of your
friends you you're thirty five yeah um
a man in his forties to childbirth
people that he was even there
i should have only been children present
so you went to a child's birthday
party i did too we were looking
for parking it was at someone's house
and we um we turned on the
street and reach yeah it was like
that and then we drove by this
guy and his chi this guy's car
was parked and he had his door
open and his feet on the ground
she tries to his baby gonna get
out but he had on only tight
boxer briefs ouch
yeah we read any had a child's
like a little girl's suitcase like a
pink with white polka dots rolling suitcases
have a dildo inside i didn't know
it shoes on he did not and
he had he looked like buffalo bill
i was literally like his hair was
little cray and i was like the
cool western buffalo bill um no and
i was when i was like did
i mention if he'd fuck
like him
i literally said to mike what the
fuck was he just drove by this
guy because it's like a suburban area
it was just like really weird right
um go into the party and then
spiderman walks in with a pink ah
oh wow and he was spiderman who's
putting on his costume and he's putting
it on a half a block away
in plain sight apparently because i saw
him in his not in plain sight
of the party but nobody other party
goers i mean like other kids were
park
in their car you know kids were
parking their cars our kids will be
any cars other kids were pulling up
around the same area but i'd be
so great to have a child's birth
they've already been ever a line of
big wheels just like company was like
well i know hilarious and it's a
different kids and there was a batman
who came in as well and why
spiderman those are two different universe kid
loves him
both and so the kids were all
really excited and they were maybe two
they did a good job and they
were like doing this little like just
in games with the little kids they
were like four and under so they
come to do too much to three
to one yeah and holly was really
skeptical of the whole today anybody here
into galaga
cover up
oh so so this guy had they
have a little parachute i know it's
time to go no um niv a
little parachute they're having the kids like
do you know like sit in the
middle and they're like you know pull
on the parachute make it flap and
whatever and this the the bad man
was like swedish and so he's like
okay where are you met i can't
do the accent he's like where did
you imagine yourself
and he was like doing this sort
of game that we were later talking
about was like to like advance advance
he was like where could you be
could be anywhere in the world are
you in paris and are you in
majorca okay are you and my four
year old being like and there's like
a parachute flapping all around he's like
you're in majorca you could be anywhere
in the world are you in work
did you see those i'm saying my
aura yeah man i lose a year
in majorca you're on a beautiful beach
with a lady who's wearing a string
bikini and you're having you're having drinks
at wins really so specific and weird
and i was letting you go to
the disco and the kids was like
looking around like why like i've never
heard batman talking about majorca in any
of his movies and then i also
we also were like wait spider mentioned
i've had a pink
dotted suitcase he should have a black
bag if anything if anything not rowley
i would also i thought well i
think black death you shouldn't have a
camera to that he liked webs to
the wall that takes pictures of everything
yeah daily bugle yeah sure there should
also be a j jonah jameson who
comes in and say i'm gonna get
pictures reveal you're a menace um the
the spiderman should have
looks like a web which spiderman would
sometimes do something like that would be
not a little pink suitcase because it
makes you have too many questions but
did the kids have any questions or
did they just see it and get
it i think that they were fine
in general but i think i don't
i don't know what the actual reaction
was i feel like there was a
lot of just like okay we're playing
with them now like i don't know
if they were like
if it's spider man you see on
the video of the little kid who
loves ah it's shit is adjacent know
it's ah mike myers yeah halloween yes
yes yes it's so funny because like
oh the show because that little kid
who loves kitty just yes that character
and and was it like a mickey
mouse type character so he comes around
the corner and it looks
ominous but she just like runs up
and hugs him and yeah he hugs
her back so funny it's so funny
it's so funny and i just saw
a video of ah ah like probably
nine year old girl who loves michael
mcdonald and what her dad surprised her
with do you know where we're at
we're at this place and we're gonna
see the doobie brothers do you know
what that mean
she goes mike michael mcdonald's and because
that's right mike mcdowell the scene with
the doobie brothers do you want to
go inside she's like yeah and then
he's taking video the whole time just
take nine with glasses and cute and
she's in and she's like screaming my
goal the entire night
oh minute bout oh dummies minute stop
should have to be this this is
i haven't stopped sewing since re-run added
tobacco to fall out of it now
that's going to better focus on happening
do i hear a child's voice someone
under eighteen
and and so then he's like going
off stage and she's waving to him
and he like waves up there and
she's like michael mcdonald waved at me
michael madaba waved to me and then
her dad very nicely like takes her
back to the cordoned off area where
the buses are whatever and has her
weight and he comes over
in science her poster oh she god
she's just like you saw me and
you wave to me and he's like
oh yeah not only keeps moving like
you're actually very special and the dad
is like she's actually a huge fan
like like i didn't make her do
this yeah i don't want to be
here i don't like your music i'm
having
hard time alright we have to get
the good i think you should leave
sketch yeah yeah go bye bye for
now
alright we're back and guess what we
got a mat producer update
yeah that i said i said that
like it was a regular thing and
then i realized we've never had a
yeah mapa update he said okay this
isn't a three cheer but a piss
pig named patrick white by the way
ah shout out to the piss pigs
all over the place i was all
over show on thursday night lacey mosley
eli's scam got his live and as
i was walking out a gentleman yelled
at me hey paul i'm a piss
pig
i also thought oh wow really i
did a show the other night with
ben schwartz and one of the nice
people who work there came up and
said i'm a three-time listener and then
embarrassingly said i guess i should say
i'm a piss pig yeah that's right
you should and tani was there and
she laughed out loud and said i'm
so happy to see that in the
wild yeah if you say me now
not supposed to say it proudly you're
supposed to know you're supposed to use
supposedly chan the question yes alright so
i thought there was there was an
update there's two we got to update
to okay you're doing them in order
to map producer updates but he's first
update okay this isn't a three-tier but
a piss pig named patrick white sox
video i want to keep it a
surprise
so here it is okay okay good
and then i'm clicking on the link
and plugged into the ox ah is
loading here we go
hello skye paw and line oh my
god
we know i know that your fans
i've actually heard about your podcast from
a lot of people oh no no
no i'm like the only guest to
have ever have on guests and so
i'm just here to tell you from
hat-trick that i never be i guess
ah you want me to be and
that's a little lie and so lou
lie to have ah i've told so
many
people who've mentioned me like oh they
would love you bob above but they'd
never have guests and i've sent messages
saying if they if you want me
on i will be more than delighted
to come on but if you don't
that's also page me you don't want
me on she's clearly never heard the
shelter no thank you out and say
that i didn't want to be
associate well that was funny that was
good it was good she got a
side actually being
i got this request i couldn't remember
where the request came in from like
was an instagram she looks terrific by
the way you see an alert from
oh she does her hair looks greg
her hair's beautiful eyes yeah it is
it was patrick she looks fresh as
a daisy and anyway beautiful eyelashes we
see
for the name of your machine does
three something yeah this assertion searching trying
to figure out what oh no i
hope that's not true alert from cameo
and now i know so anyway all
that being said i'm very flattered i'm
glad you guys are fans
yeah that's it that's the whole thing
well honestly i'll let her finish let
her finish my cell number well the
cameo messages and patrick consented onto you
guys want to reach out nice sleepy
fuck and love you very much ah
okay
wow hey patrick don't lose that number
don't yell patrick don't ask her for
tips on how to trade spaces with
one of your neighbor gonna say ending
page david's a you up
that was so nice wow i like
i like to fake out i liked
the not fake out and i liked
all of it um you know it's
a tough situation wherein because i think
we moved on and we said reggie
miller and then we home did pass
but i but it sounds like she
was trying to find us during that
time and so that's really frustrating we're
gonna have to talk about this author
yea we're gonna have a group of
the top maitre amazing to hear from
pei oh my god that was about
and thank you patrick that was a
really great gift yeah it's really delightful
of credit so i hear from her
and it's great to see her i
was i enjoy broadway's own paige davis
when that was credible that was so
cool very cool of her
survey that was maybe the first time
i've understood why cameo cameos cool
not because of me
that was the best cameo i could
have received is how i should have
rated for that one though i do
want one philly bano should do cameo
why be funny he has no reason
why it's okay do you feel like
they would be sure to be inundated
he'd haven't had ever people i know
but you feel like they'd be thirty
seconds or they'd be ten ten ten
minutes add
and but but i feel like to
weed out unserious people you'd have to
charge like ten thousand dollars a cameo
forum but do you think you would
ever include phrases like world just people
like at some point that comes up
all right matt producer update number two
o convert to another doing another one
this is another one kelly strobel who
writes whipped this up after listening today
and i don't know i think it's
a bop okay what about
was at you gasping or was just
so crazy news on my phone actually
idea of a yeah that's just the
way we're ah
things will never change
you're perfect now that was actually just
thinking it works
that's just the way it works
so an average day
what what works
a i sang that was yeah that's
low
it's outside thing and zou bout
ah i didn't know he did that
so much
work project away at work wow perfect
kelly thank you so much can we
build on instagram somehow is that pos
know it's possible they haven't figured that
out how to can you upload original
audio no no they haven't know that's
it's a weird iphone quirk alright guess
we can't oh i play i feel
um wow
wow incredible thank you to our
his bay and crappy like paige davis
were actually to be on the show
we would have to explain the concept
of pittsburgh's to her and that would
be directly for me it's too embarrassing
to explain the why the family chose
it i like i hope this is
okay to share but this is from
ah mats got another update this is
from my dear friend i can't mendell
mon
oh it's not it's kind of oh
okay i just texted me a screenshot
somebody wrote to her saying hi mindell
i know you're probably not going to
see this but nevertheless i wanted to
ask if you had any idea where
i could stream bajillion dollar properties because
i want to watch it so bad
but there's no way in hell i'm
paying per episode or season
or see yeah she just wrote i
love our fans
season you if you're if you're not
even willing to pay per season that
to me doesn't make any sense like
just get it all at once for
a bulk price so crazy however much
just is like everything should be free
all the time there's a lot of
that i mean we're not really horrible
time with so many streamers and services
that like you have to have it
to spend younger
love them like it doesn't make any
sense i will say i recently got
rid of cable and i now only
use hulu live and i'm pretty excited
to take me one hundred dollars a
month when i figured out the math
and i have it no
you actually can't share it because no
no guys one hundred dollars oh well
i'm saving it now no but can
i have it no i'm saving it
for something really special are you really
because i want to have twelve hundred
dollars a year now because i'm not
spending that same for how many years
forever so i'm now probably never get
it again so say
say like how many more years do
you think you'll be alive i'll be
alive sixty maybe i hope so okay
so sixty years twelve hundred dollars a
year yeah we're talking somewhere in the
range of like seventy something bruce hornsby
and the range yeah so choice just
the way it works is i'll buy
like a really fancy ca
car right now right now and just
you know you will max out money
yeah great i feel like collecting cars
is a sign of a bad person
really who who we know you're right
take would you would you say that
i go in cars because op has
wanted i've won oh shit jeannie and
i each have
or you could like it all too
boy yeah i just it's like i
don't know it just seems it's such
a gross thing to collect it's so
i always feel like how often do
you get to use yeah one that's
the part if you're jay leno you're
out there driving them all izzy yeah
when he goes and gives donuts to
the writers' guild z in a different
car retype he drives different cars all
the fucking time
well at least he would always go
to bony was doing the tonight show
but so he's that's gonna drive a
different car there every day yeah but
that's his touring money yeah yeah it
doesn't touch his tonight show money well
he still does well he just give
that money to us please if you're
not gonna touch it i'll touch it
i'll yeah oh awesome just get out
of money
and i'll have the cars i'd love
to have a lot of cars i
know there was a second where i
thought it'd be fun to have like
ah sort of like a convertible that's
like you know like not expensive or
something but like something something to take
on the weekends yeah but then i
was like yeah it's probably like going
anywhere on the way it's gonna be
a lot of worktop keep this thing
and it's an i'm gonna get my
i'm gonna
sunburned and i've found that so many
times about like a classic car so
yeah yeah that but it's done it's
just a nightmare it seems like underwear
constantly it also like how much money
are you like thirty grand if you
get something in like shitty conditioner whatever
and then that's so much money for
something you're all you're going to drive
like third
eighty five times and i really don't
want to be broken down on the
side of the road with that kind
of situation where yeah what do you
want to be broken down by the
side of the road what kind of
situation to i'm next to a mcdonald's
oh okay fun yeah i'd go in
the play place have some fries yeah
two fries and two fries have two
fries please we only sell
when two groups of twenty five or
so
no sale i want fries or i'm
starving cuba the game oh wait new
wow out of time we are oh
shit choices took oh i love surprises
that's just the way that's just the
way it works some things will never
jam
change name and
ok take that and do something without
just now is a better version works
it works it works it's just the
way it works well we gotta go
listen if you want to hear ad-free
well ah edition at this point i
think you can only hear them on
cvb world dot com i believe that's
true because i just got absolutely breaking
news five minutes before we started the
show that's different premiums going away yes
they are just continuing operations so but
you can hear that they were operating
on i think all that's so weird
i like frankenstein situation have to find
a new place to go well cb
world dot com has all the ad-free
episodes so that's the that's where you're
really going to go let me let's
assume you get so much more
so you can hear ad-free episodes on
cbp world dot com if you'd like
to write to us send a three
cheer you can write to us at
three am usa at gmail dot com
if you would like to call us
and ask for some advice or just
tell us amusing story or whatever the
fuck you do ah hot call us
at hag claims eight but now i
would like to close it out by
formerly reading the
this announcement from stitcher okay oh good
i didn't get to see this this
was via the social media platform twitter
and the stitcher app and the police
racist congregate
the very same but also jack owns
blue skies want say that anyway the
stitcher app and website will discontinue operations
on august twenty ninth twenty twenty three
for ancient for inchon nation on how
to expert does not list any other
questionnaire nation please visit and then there's
a link if you are a creator
and have quest
tions about your show distribution please visit
r f a q's here what i'm
supposed to find it on a website
after august running everyone twenty three this
account will transition to stitcher studios and
provide updates about the podcast produced within
network thank you for giving us the
opportunity over the last decade to create
the best pa
possible podcast listening it's best possible not
the best podcast try really hard but
if you so you're saying if i
wanna know what's going to happen to
my shows that are on there i
have to go to the f a
q that anyone on this listening to
right now i'm sure you because you
also find out so why does it
want someone listening this go look and
tell me what's happening to all my
show
well there we were gonna miss you
r i p to a real one
yes you are very divisive within the
podcast listening to people really had a
lot of the patents about you and
that's great yes but people like do
most people hated you yeah but don't
worry about us we're not going away
i think we have three more episodes
after it goes away loyal wow but
ah
well but we're not going away anytime
soon but the the ad-free episodes will
only be on cb world but yeah
but ah we we love you for
listening and please don't bother page anymore
i think we have it yeah totally
we have it covered at this point
we'll take it from here yeah yeah
the fact that she responded was amazing
yeah wouldn't mind if we got in
touch with reggie miller no
oh no don't waste his time now
oh god if you can if you're
psychic and can talk to clara peller
would love to hear what she's a
waste of time to get money to
do a little dumb video and now
it is actually okay alright goodbye
uh