three
ooh
ah maybe three oh
three
email ever gonna song who might in
gmail we're gonna song as opposed to
whatever good genocide they write yeah
i was trying to do the music
from raising arizona
i've never seen that oh yeah
come up a few times yeah for
me i think i'll have to watch
eventually like yeah yeah got to see
it but yeah it sounds very similar
to the yahoo song and you're right
why didn't g gmail get a three
earth the situation on juju to to
email to ginger tajima
just steamy i remember in gmail started
to i was like wow that's so
cool really
well you know i had this friend
who we used to to get an
invite i'm going with fitz yeah thanks
friendly knows this is exactly yeah i
had this friend who always does not
allow you to get in yeah oh
do you lose a certain amount of
envy yes yes but always knew the
hip new technology to know about like
oh we should get on your emails
you should get a vibrator and then
he'd be like yeah i tunes out
with batteries new technology
he got me on twitter at the
end for square and only different website
remember when twitter didn't have an app
you had to use like a different
app to use it need use the
browser oh yeah but then you'd use
it you downloaded the different type of
different type of app and then find
out twitter made it's own now yes
that's right yeah yeah the good old
days
a good ad when things were safe
but so so gmail you thought was
cool it was okay compared to you
know people will still have yahoo and
stuff and i just go what do
you do it yeah i've ever stolen
a well man but i haven't new
boyfriend doesn't actually gmail i just wonder
what do you what's going on and
well what about our our good producer
matt apodaca yeah what about him really
telling us to get ios he's always
trying to tell us get outlook for
ios every email every email get outlook
for ios and he can't change it
no matter how already been and quite
often you read his replies to to
our emails and he only says like
yes or something like that but it
it seems like he's trying to just
tell us to get up
like honestly there was like a couple
of months yes get out look for
iowa he roamed you gonna like there
was like a question about because you
said you guys like calendar i've invites
and then he wrote get ah look
at i don't want outlook i used
to row back i don't like like
i use gmail and then he's like
sa ha sorry i was like i
actually thought you were saying yeah
i yeah tricks me thirty percent of
the into thinking he's trying to tell
me to get out like yeah and
why is he so obsessed he always
wants to say dude loves it he
likes it more than his own name
does he get a commission i don't
know looks more than me that would
be so rad to get a commission
like passive income from oh my for
ios you know and the deep deb
oh please go ahead it is funny
that you
i used to have to get an
invitation to gmail now you can make
fifty email address i know i know
but i find that more is that
is it a scam or it's or
it's just a shame yes thank you
scammers jam or ham alright let's play
scammer james abraham scam sham ram okay
right amy you eat it at easter
ham scam exactly scam
yeah jesus didn't exist
ham
i'm still playing i'm going ham if
you say jesus didn't exist
were you going to say somebody i
don't know you or your disease dive
oh they they talk about passive income
they have their amazon stores that you
can have and i think klopp made
one oh yeah um so that's been
kind of fun but then just saying
hers got shut it was getting shut
down for lack of purchases being made
on that seems what's the unfair what
does the amazon store if
set up your own store like i
like the lauren store and it's like
here's my favorite items and then if
you buy it through my store i
get some money back which seems great
to fuck with amazon it's like someone
else can make money that's anything though
you could like have a website i
think and and have a link and
you tell your fans and friends like
hey if you're gonna buy
something through amazon go through this link
because yeah it's like an affiliate link
yeah anyway yeah um seems i was
gonna say is this a scam or
a shama raham that you that these
invites are they trying to make it
seem exclusive or they just can't handle
the web traffic or is it like
a new thing my guess more like
cry
oh i was trying it out well
it's no no but you know reveals
elite so you're like ooh i wanna
do what i'm saying that's a scam
ah or a sham monday i think
it's more of a sham it's more
of a sham and associate where they're
trying to make it seem elites right
but they could handle as many ways
i mean you think google could have
would not have had a problem
elam yeah with a bunch of people
setting up email addresses at the same
time my my favorite thing i've been
doing recently is it's like all the
second yeah truly your favorite thing yeah
i love this okay no idea to
a friend of mine can do everything
every love it more than my wife
okay wow okay you have a daughter
it goes my wife my daughter oh
suddenly this thing is third no no
no and then male
hands down yeah i would hands down
and now i'm going hand up okay
so i mean he's below cool blow
up deaf should not you know she's
hey she says this is a trial
protocol of a long time probationary citizen
beta yeah okay um she also is
a beta
but ah what was oh yeah is
my friend asks me like oh my
god where did you ah how did
you find that out and i just
like right back a google link like
to google not to the link of
the thing they're trying to just like
your favorite bit is to say i
looked at google dot com yes yeah
because like that's so many times when
if people are asking you a question
it's like something very easily global but
you don't give them the link of
them just the link to show that's
number two i feel like i mean
no better things better i think he's
better than google dot com and i
think wow right under it i was
gonna say that but i think that
i think emmy i agree with scott
that it's too soon to tell on
me yeah she might watches be bad
eat this true she might be ah
one of those macaulay culkin yeah she's
gonna try to push a kid off
a tree huh something yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's so ironic that it's called
the good son when he was so
bad i know but is it about
him or is it about elijah wood
i think that's sort of right they'd
maybe you think the good son is
macaulay cult
aiken and then he does bad things
and you're like actually the twist was
the title was about alleged would oh
so that's the ny channel on twist
at the end with what the title
refers to so the author comes up
to very specific as he comes out
lord grantham style lou was just seeing
his twists mr grantham lord grant but
mr graham calling back
our last days i shall be holy
what is the ultimate dream factory
it's already said in the new one
mr mosley says oh one of the
one of the few hours the hollywood
at the end of this last film
right and he i think he becomes
a screenwriter yeah
i love that movie why does it
does the latest dance and have the
the new doubt the most recent of
everybody's oh they have movies the oldie
of movies now six seasons and a
movie is is upstairs downstairs good i
was thinking about that my parents used
to watch it when i was a
kid i watched those in adult and
really enjoyed it
yeah yeah i think it would be
good it goes through different time periods
i think it's bad that that pbx
look exists yes john das no no
no i now with streaming and everything
like that i feel like you never
go through pbx anymore when it used
to be so reliably wonderful to like
as as something
you know to watch as opposed to
just be their slogan reliably wonderful yeah
but you know what i mean like
b now why we're reliably wonderful why
would you happen across pbx at this
point you know it would take a
lot you have to be little channel
i yeah yeah it's i mean even
you know the classics like sesame street
happen with showmax their app on apple
tv how often do you watch it
never exactly
yeah you're right i can switch artifact
so yeah but but isn't it wonderful
very easy to find and skip over
isn't it incredible that they had a
huge hit with with downton abbey yeah
and it was just word of mouth
that was their show yeah well i
knew it was you know yeah four
but it was because they didn't have
billboards
bad review on every day zappa you
know what why did you ever watch
it well because i'd love some matters
good manners badwater yeah exactly yeah lucy
i was gonna deal with the manners
i never really watched that show like
i don't really know you got to
see it because it's because it's got
ah ah dialogue and actual i did
watch the first episode and i think
there was a surprise blow job that
kind of threw me oily and i
was like what's surprised you the audience
or the person receiving it the person
giving everyone involved what am i doing
but
good to hear
stuff my beautiful
yeah
and then i found myself giving a
blow job
what i meant to set up the
croquet
well if you if you had to
live back then
and you couldn't be part of the
aristocracy yeah what job would you want
to do
what are my options like if you
could be one of the downton abbey
like servants so it's like oh chauffeur
you want to show love to drive
those cars yeah yeah yeah that would
be he would always talk to me
but it would be so bumpy
it yeah you went over a bump
the other day and you had a
bad time a lot of tire that's
right are you now reconsidering your choice
that would happen to you all the
time do you think pull the tire
just wood or pop oh that's right
so they're more durable yeah i'm not
worried about the bumps now but the
roads also are probably in a way
better
yeah worse well they weren't they weren't
like i don't think they have things
like dirt and big potholes you had
you had dirt yeah yeah but you
had like it was you had some
risks that got me when you weren't
just driving over the country like that
roads that but their roads just because
like people have gone down them so
oh they're not paying
eve they are a little medieval times
like here is like the third yeah
we know is like the tenth to
the thirties i think yeah yes it's
some top so you but what if
they had paved roads empty hence they
did in the city i'm just saying
like if you got from downton abbey
and went to the city you'd have
to go over a lot of bumps
i don't think so i just agree
i think it would be bumpy i
don't know i don't know why we're
having to argue bumpy roads and nineteen
ten where i know i can you
run
i would disagree with me when you
could have just paid no mind to
that's exactly i think i'd like to
be like um
you could be a scullery maid what's
that
you could be what does that she
would wash the pots and pans right
oh no i'd like to be the
the cook the cook but i don't
know how to keep the statue might
be good the cook is allowed to
be sad yeah you assume you would
be well you have the skill in
this game that we're playing right now
you are good at the thing yes
no no it's you held then i
guess i'd be like the nanny
like you know what to call it
i guess did they have a dedicated
nanny back then or there or did
everyone just kind of take turns on
it i can't remember i yeah i
don't because they did eventually have babies
there yeah but you never saw like
one of the people i don't remember
my only job is being an yeah
yeah yeah interesting they also sort of
but also made it seem like the
servants didn't play that much of a
part in a baby
his life when of course they would
they wouldn't want to remember it seemed
like it i do remember one scene
where they was just there and there
was a baby they suddenly the baby
came in everyone went oh wow
yeah they played with the baby a
little zed all right take her away
yeah so i don't know that's living
like that friend when i was renal
grew up in this house that was
like my friend did too okay it's
not a brag it was i actually
very much
that had servants quarters wow ahead servants
like stairwell that led to a room
and then let went to the kitchen
sh like that and i actually think
this stairwell right over here is it
was used to be a servant sir
really this is this is our only
nineteen twenties it isn't really i wouldn't
guess so it's very narrow yeah um
and and i think when
we were looking at it the realtor
said oh and these used to be
servants our house might have been servants'
quarters to a bigger house that might
have been i was demolished yeah i'm
like i love to look at real
estate online just for fun i was
actually doing it last night and i
was like this is better than instagram
because it doesn't hurt my feelings yeah
what can i say i'm glad you
didn't say
real estate porn no i would never
say that and people just put poor
i don't like food porn and nature
poor it's like no it's just you
can enjoy something yeah it's an involved
you're not actually jerking off no look
at that cheese burger but i saw
some say sex is like nature's porno
don't you yeah i think so agree
yeah i saw some houses that were
shocked
all i saw was one house that
was very victorian home and as you
scroll through the pictures it got more
and more haunted it was just like
a terrifying like the wallpaper was creepy
and every room was creeper than the
last room and it was like oh
this is like the end the way
they photographed it was so chilling yeah
it's just very scary honestly this is
why i watched downton abbey and i
don't
i would never remember a lot of
what was going on because i watched
it purely aesthetically yes to look at
the role of the sets i love
the clothes i loved all of that
yeah and then janey we would watch
like sex in the city though yeah
you look you see the girl yeah
yeah yeah yeah jenny would be like
way why is he
was he was mad at him for
something i'm like i don't no idea
i don't care i don't know it's
great it's brand new to me everytime
that's fun well what what happened your
friend who grew up in the house
nothing but i'm saying i just was
remembering she's still okay yeah serving kostin
i just remembered that house and being
sort of like ah like oh it's
over it's like the stairs were not
used
oh and but yeah it felt a
little you know what did they do
with that room it was just like
a it just have a bed in
it you know they did rent out
some space to college students um from
time to time so i don't know
if there's that rumor if it was
another room that they had but it
was disconnected from like the main house
was like in the attic okay it
was like a room fancy style yeah
yeah yeah i was doing some research
for a bit paunchy live in someone's
house he lived above above the coat
cuttings garage mister noisy forgot that he
did that he also had a very
funny way of sitting in chairs well
you also always put his thumbs up
in the air he would jump into
it remember no into the ah into
the like recliner of mister c's
oh yeah like jumping i remember that
i remember that um i was doing
research for a scrip years and years
ago um and so i got to
be taken on all of these open
houses for these incredibly huge rich people
houses in beverly hills and go back
to life on these giant ones with
like bowling alley
these from the twenties that's bananas oh
my god i would love to i
i do have a friend i follow
on instagram who's always at a state
sales and like he was that one
recently or your friend the goal one
recently that was like clearly who's dead
who's yeah wouldn't die recently judging it
was clearly like a crew
person had passed and all of their
belongings were like a lot of interesting
props but they also had water bottles
labeled this was properties i just drank
out of them oh and like have
like sean hayes like a straw sticking
out of a starbucks cup with like
liquid and like different celebrity tape with
their name that's gross isn't it
crazy yeah give someone's keeping your cup
and then i guess hoping to sell
it for something with your residue and
and then i was wearing forward again
i'll decide corps gonna get outta kafr
yeah i don't know who is in
charge of the sale but i'm like
just feels like the trash cart knows
why
nice tough that's my czar that they
would leave it out yeah what if
the person house was in charge of
the estate just made this shit up
yeah shake it interesting cleared out their
car of all starbucks shit yeah i'm
like you should take quick people covered
over and you know like have you
ever been to state sales do you
ever never have to know oh hey
i'm mom hope
who i used to live down the
street oh that's just wrong i mean
with like a celebrity like you remember
yes my name that would be very
interesting and sometimes i would be curious
to go to like what you're saying
with going to like really rich people's
houses and like just being able to
see the house and like what how
it's all laid out but it can
be very unsettling i think to go
and see some all of someone's belongings
like laid out like that it's just
kind of like yeah oh
this is like what we all become
is just like this just a process
you don't have but at least we're
taken up to heaven i'm assuming the
rapture
yeah so there actually you can't you
don't get your clothes can you don't
get your wedding ring close down earth
everything stays
it's your biggest concern you're wearing yeah
just like your dream or the car
i don't wear one hearings hearings following
i've talked about this yeah all right
your your earrings fall out your ah
your gold teeth your grill know your
tattoos you're just throwing metal
anything you've added what's this weird skull
with flowers
that's kinda cool how great would it
be though to be the people left
behind on earth it's going to be
so oh my god you've got so
much elbow room at that point so
much real estate pops up as cheap
i know i'm gonna watch those left
behind movies yeah i haven't seen just
to see what the idea is what
i've i've seen the thief in the
night mu
movies they used to say that it's
it's similar it's based on the rapture
the first one her camera know these
these are the seventy s this is
not the cross this way i played
just not the cross and the switchblade
with erik estrada
i remember that that he did a
christian movie called the cross and switchblade
but um back in the sixties but
ah this this is the thief in
the night which is from a bible
verse and it's basically the first ones
very tidy which is a woman wakes
up in her entire family is gone
the raptures happened oh and she's the
one who's never believed in in all
oh and basically like the government starts
to oppress people where everyone needs a
bar code tattooed on their either their
forehead or left-hand i have talked about
this yeah anyway but then then the
fifth one is just like zombies chasing
her yea yea just fine
yeah it does have nuclear explosion happens
or something so then it just gets
to be like zomg oh it's not
god's wrath no no alright
but um anyways because when the rapture
happens i don't remember the details when
the rapture happens the people left on
earth it's bad news because then the
antichrist comes yeah then all the plagues
start happening yeah yes and all that
kind of stuff so you don't want
to be around it and also also
get out just six six six part
of it is the bad part because
if you get that number it's just
like dude you fucked up mean if
you get that number if you get
tattooed on you it's like oh you
fucked up you have to go to
hell now even if you believe in
all god and rapture and stuff yeah
you can't get that number you gotta
escape what if you got nine nine
nine but you didn't count on you
didn't put the line yeah
you were just like god i this
is emergency number in england nine nine
nine nine nine nine nine nine nine
nine nine nine what's emergency no no
no show emergency love any
what's going on nine love or nazi
emergency alright we have to disagree
we're back hi i hi guys i'm
still we were talking about houses i'm
still dreaming about the house whoa my
teams that oh your wow that i
own that i never go to wow
for some reason and then for some
reason
like oh well let's just go here
i own this place and we go
in and it's empty and ah but
it's the same house all the time
it's in the same place some lag
is gonna come of this and it's
going to be something you think sinister
oh like in the movie since know
where you're going to move and it's
gonna be that housing gonna be like
whoa on earth yeah i do
don't like this yeah i think that's
interesting yeah and they'd be really cool
but why do i keep dreaming about
this one that's what i'm wanting to
use your psychic yeah yeah you need
to are you psychic at all kinda
just show you what was carried out
yeah i think you're going to i
think is what i feel on what
i see is that you are going
to eventually sell this house
it's okay you might not think that
right now but something is going to
come in your life that is going
to make it very clear that you
need to sell this home and when
you do you're going to be a
bit rushed and you're going to move
kind of quickly and your realtor has
you know it's gonna all fall into
place really really well and when you
move you will see that that new
house has elements from
what you're starting your call my other
psychic okay hello
here's it's got this guy yeah who
just made the circuit good you oh
hey yeah i hear you want to
tell me what you think this house
is yeah
ah so you're still driven to the
house right yeah i'm still dreaming about
the apartment this is just gonna be
so okay to basically what it means
you're going to move out of the
current house you're in yeah in there
no it's going to be a rush
you're going to be like putting shit
in boxes you will know what i
wrote the center of that sort through
this packet in there you get to
the new house
house sorry i to go ah i'm
sorry i'm just getting excited i just
think you should hang up because i'm
going to have to leave i mean
or you can keep talking no i
just needed a second opinion on this
thing or two psychics think the same
thing then it's actually okay so what
i can't be sure yeah i'm still
here yeah okay so this this all
lines up with the person who gave
me the first opinion
okay so he saying something you say
he says the exact same thing that
makes sense because that's exactly what's going
to happen right yeah why don't you
get to the i'm gonna end the
scene here
why don't people get a second opinion
from another psychic
you know i think a lot of
people don't want to break the spell
you know what i mean i do
it with a doctor that's off the
idea if people truly know what's gonna
happen to be people know it because
then they would realize there's no such
thing as psychics don't wanna ruin it
oh if you seem healthy goldman yeah
no and i need to watch this
i don't even know a thing about
it but i keep hearing about it
absolutely watch i was reluctant to watch
but i'm glad i don't know anything
but i heard it's good there's a
psychic in that yeah no spoiler no
i won't spoil anything about the cycle
but essentially but this all reminded me
talking about this reminded me that article
i sent you guys the other day
bass
based on a previous episode discussion we
had about hypnotism yes ah now teach
the controversy so just to just to
back up a little we were talking
about how i tried to get hypnotized
in a show when i was young
and it didn't work but i pretended
and i went along with it and
i raised my arms like they were
light as a feather
there were balloons on the end of
my fingers and it was raised and
i didn't get picked for the show
and i was secretly glad because i
was just faking it and some people
have said you know some people have
replied oh yes this is what those
hypnotism shows are they just find the
most extroverted person and everyone is faking
it and so we're good theory so
homes accurate this then after we did
that episode was extroverted person in everyone
is faking it yeah everyone's faking it
so just find a person who will
like go along with it and do
the acting like a chicken and stuff
oh so i wasn't extroverted enough i
guess um i got to work a
little harder but um this article came
out called i faked my
the hypnosis during therapy and then lied
about it for years i know this
is fascinated it's a great title and
it's literally this woman writes woman notes
a fellow named patrick i'm sorry waster
i know you would think it would
be a woman because lying is something
that
no i thought i thought i was
way under there was liking work that
made me think it was a woman
but um yeah i thought it was
a woman too but i just looked
down and it's this guy patrick patrick
wake doctor he's a buzzfeed contributor i'll
tell you that much thanks for your
contribution one thing that he feels her
but i thought was really interesting i
wanted to try with you guys yeah
is that he wrote there's ah there's
a little test
that hypnotists will do yes is there
to see if you can be hypnotized
you're more likely to be able to
be hypnotized susceptible so you roll your
eyes back what does it roll your
eyes back in your head and close
your eyes right and when you do
if your eyes come back so if
i look at you and i'm only
seeing your sclera a white part of
the eye well that's gonna show me
it's clear you no one has ever
seen my dad and that you're more
likely to be hypnotized but if your
eyes kind of come back you are
less susceptible okay if your eyes are
just in place when you open your
eyes you know like you roll back
and close your eyes and if your
eyes don't roll if your irises right
so let me just do what you
asked me to do and
you tell me okay roll your eyes
back and close your eyes
i see i feel like you had
a lot of iris
too much iris like let me show
you like the goosebumps i'm gonna see
what happens when i do okay yeah
okay no i just square a square
for days oh wait so i'm supposed
to keep my mind open like you're
supposed to roll back as far as
you can and then close your eyes
okay okay here here and i see
what you're doing it has made me
all is well re doing okay i
was about to do it he's rolling
his eyes back i can't even roll
i know you can't can't do it
so you're not saying that's why you're
not hypnotized let me try it okay
what happened is really funny
it's was it i opener i was
doing what happened tonight they went back
you i still saw your iris while
you were closing right yeah but you
got pretty far but some people can't
roll their eyes when you got pretty
but that means i can't be advertised
so supposedly according to patrick wow miku
who wrote this article well i don't
know i talk about the story blog
you leave let's talk about this article
a second because ah just to some
by the way when i saw the
u so i think lawrence said there's
an eye roll test and i was
like and i like if the comedian
if the images tries to advertise you
and you're like come on dude like
okay i get it baby clara after
he entered come on and tell elsa
yeah so this first era dispersing layer
ah this person went to a hypnotist
because ah he was having a lot
of ah mental anguish um the lingering
pain of a divorce a lot of
anxiety now i feel i thought he
felt one of his own quizzes
um and he went to get hypnotized
and essentially paid for three you gotta
pay for three sessions i think in
advance and it was a lot of
money and um he went to the
therapist that would make me suspicious right
away i know they say well if
you're gonna do this you have to
do three yeah
nothing interesting and painted nice thing you
know you're gonna want like yeah i
feel like a lot of beauty things
will have you do that right oh
if you're gonna do this you should
do six sessions and you get this
discount and blah blah blah and then
it's like at the end of all
i don't know if i want that
yes but i'm missing on a discount
because i'm tried it yet for me
the issue and i think i think
the real person who does hypnotism
brings us up halfway through is like
this hypnotist was saying oh and we'll
delve into past lives which to me
is like oh you're not a serious
person yeah this point yeah so and
that's what the anyway so but but
this guy this guy goes in he
does the first session pretends to be
hypnotized it doesn't work he's awake the
entire time says at the end like
oh that was really good yeah and
i sure was hypnotized yeah and then
the then the second one oh by
the way he starts to kind of
talk about his feelings first before the
hypnotism of the persons like not interesting
does not and will just tell you
no feelings just a separate person no
this is the third hypnotist is a
separate person from the person being hipped
knows if that's what you're asking however
thank you i'm saying did the was
the therapist the hypnotist or was a
separate it was a it was a
hypnotherapy person which is not like you
can't be credited for it
so and forgive me because i have
not read the article because if somebody
sends me a link it goes right
in the trash okay um wow what
that's i'm certainly talks about it for
a while was ah what you pretend
to do if read it right
i started writing for buzzfeed oh um
did he go to a regular therapist
first or was this his first stop
was no i think i think he
i think maybe he did and again
i'm just you know i read this
a week ago when i sent it
to you but as i recall he
tried a lot of different stuff and
finding the price and finally settled on
hypno
racism because there were various people who
had said like oh this really works
right so we're all hip to justice
so he found one who said oh
you gotta come in three times and
relevant to past lives first-time they just
hypnotized and he goes he goes okay
now play this every night as you
go to sleep the tape of it
and then the second time he goes
okay now we're gonna delve into past
lives he said
bill pretends to be hypnotized and then
they then the the hypnotherapist says like
okay now you're in your past life
and tell me what your name is
it could be anything it could be
like a sound even and he just
goes like buh buh ah alright bo
well you can't see me on the
spot because i'm now speaking to book
so um so so he does the
whole thing and he's like in his
head the whole time and he's on
a dirty couch and going why is
this couch so dirty i hope some
of the money i'm giving like a
clean their couch um and then he's
quality comes out of it
it and goes like oh that was
really great yeah wow i was really
back there or whatever and then called
them the they call for the third
appointment he goes nope i'm cured
um so but here's the weird part
the lying about it for years yeah
two he lied about it as he
said he was open to all of
his harmonies like i did this thing
you've gotta doing it really working for
me that's that is very maybe that's
what he actually got hypnotized to do
i know this really was just recommend
system
i don't know whether it's like you
don't have to tell the story about
hypnotism is it to seem interesting or
is it to seem but it's like
it would be such an interesting story
to say i went to a hypnotist
and it was all a lie and
i was faking it yeah does he
say why he lied about it no
he just kind of says like i
know if you're my friend and you're
reading this article and you owe it
and those my friend posted an article
like that and i found out they've
been lying to me that way this
isn't be hilarious i had such a
that would be wild if you saw
someone like send you a link to
something your friend said oh only heard
them say many yeah oh by the
way she's never done that kind of
medicine yeah and like hero an article
about it reminded me of paul's book
about how he quit
smoking and how like what if you
were still smoked wow yeah i told
everyone about that book yeah it's just
a weird thing to do is so
strange also and i had a totally
different idea based on the art of
the title of the art of what
the article would be i thought it
was he had a therapist who at
some point suggested hypnotherapy and he didn't
go under but then he he kept
continuing to see this therapist for years
and was saying like yes so you
did hypnotize me and um not that
he went around telling telling others yeah
that's the bizarre part and i don't
think he ever explains why he does
it he needs i do think i
could have a follow up article with
this yeah definitely see lying to the
person and saying it work because i
definitely have had situations yeah where i
find myself no problem weird sort of
like i got like a free rookie
know when i was like those amazing
and i'm like i don't know what
the bug man of cypress california i
was on that because oh yeah i
learned that i learned all about these
bugs just give me the bug yeah
the bug man of course the famous
bug
of cypress california but that i'm all
ready to go but then telling your
friends about it i'm saying it were
up to me that they should do
it yeah yeah but in any case
so he wondered can anyone be hypnotized
anyway without lying about yeah anyone to
a person who who who actually was
like oh the first thing is like
people talking about past lives that
it's like quackery you know that's you
know he goes but no i mean
this is how you actually do get
hypnotized and talked to some people who
have these kind of sessions on tape
that they play every night because they
have trouble going to sleep and they
go i have never heard the end
of this tape because i'm it i'm
out and he goes thing and he
goes well
you know a lot of those just
like psyching your body into think it's
one of my albums oh no oh
i've never heard the end because i'm
just about to to turn on and
fast
but a lot of it is just
psyching your body into like a meditative
state yes good in order to fall
asleep sure so but yeah yeah so
i just want to follow up with
that about hypnotism the closest i feel
i've allowed myself to get to hypnotism
is wanting to drunk history was allowing
myself to be that volant yeah
did you feel that way is so
weird because every time i did it
i never felt i think i did
it twice agency every time i never
felt um that drunk during it but
i look at it and i'm like
i am yeah i obviously was i
was drinking more than i ever would
drink and i can get drunk off
very little so i was like but
as much the sich
curation was so unnatural that like it's
like my body was still kind of
going like you're fine
and it's like no and also that's
definitely how i've been talking to someone
at a party and think that i'm
fine and i'm like not is weird
but you feel like you are more
like in a tribe and i blacked
out oh so i had no reckon
you have it because i feel like
i definitely watched her do you like
fall over at some point and in
your couch and like no economics i
did not fully mix you up with
some
one point i did have like a
little apparently a little nap because i
think it was after i was done
and they were like they left the
camera on like she people packing shit
up and everything like yep equipment and
everything yeah i'm just peacefully it's actually
kind of swimming but it was i've
only watched it once i feel like
i wanna watch it again because it
was so shocking to see myself
i like that yeah but that's why
i did it yeah because i wanted
to be like that because i didn't
know what was going to happen yeah
and i was like i just want
to give myself over to that experience
that's really fun you know and like
without having to do shots when we
did it was like he set up
a game where we were doing like
water or vodka shots yeah roulette oh
yeah and i
ended up getting back like so many
times i never do shots i'm i
mean so it's like i know that
i was but it's it i think
there is that part of your body
sometimes when you're drunk that's like telling
you everything's great yeah yeah and that's
why we're going you're having great conversations
why it's so fun to drive
oh driving drugs stuff bad i remember
i chose very safe by the way
where they've upset you have a job
i mean when i say salmon a
nurse there and they let yes they
let you take the wheel if you
ask them now yeah oh the p
took me if you drive yourself you're
absolutely drivers yeah yeah yeah they gave
me pizza and ah
so the the next day i did
not remember the ninja turtles cheese no
pizza was the only thing i remembered
like i remember doing it and then
i don't remember anything and you walk
up in you're like i had peace
and then i remember for some reddit
table eating pizza dough no i got
there and i was saying the next
day that i was emailing jeremy conner
the next day saying
what happened between this and this because
i remember at some point i was
i just was gone and then i
remember eating pizza at the stable and
he said yeah you you were fine
and you did this and you passed
out for a little bit and then
we gave you some pizza and you
kept saying that the pizza wasn't good
but it actually was very good ah
trying to be rude
yeah but i sort of remember saying
this piece is terrible but i kept
eating it because i hated wow yeah
wow that's fun well use you know
you can do drunk history when you're
not on camera it's so much jeannie
old story that feeling of that feeling
of that drunk like not not where
you
blackout drunk freedom oh my god
you could just tell the same stories
yeah it was yeah it wasn't the
worst if we had like a party
and then like we went and recorded
a podcast in the middle of it
and they'll be so cool
so cool i ran would kick our
ass i feel like i've only ever
seen you drunk once really yeah it
was that christmas part that's god's yeah
i recalled oh i remember that yeah
and you weren't like drunk drunk but
you know your fellow she's yeah yeah
yeah i yeah showed up drunk that
was hard yeah and you left even
drunk yeah
free drinks oh no you walked out
of the cow shit you're wrong everyone
three hundred dollars like that's a lot
more than i expect i was talking
with friends about you know when you're
younger and you and you're drinking a
lot and that i remember that feeling
of like when you get too drunk
and you don't want to be drunk
anymore i'm just like i'm just knowing
that here
where is especially it feeling so bad
you don't really know the expand ever
need to take care of you i
haven't gotten word that describes you that
night i think i did throw up
oh i but i it's been a
very few and far between i have
like barely ever remember a new year's
party over a brian cosines and dave
rats where i got so drunk then
we all walked to denny's for some
reason well and actually the next part
of the story when you study suicide
when i save for some reason i
mean meaning it was too far away
oh that's also we did a high
school musical and then we walked at
any time yeah oh yeah or baker
square it was too far away but
we johnson decided to walk there and
it hit me how drunk i was
when i got
to the denny's and i immediately went
into the bathroom and just like threw
up and wretch and i was like
four and and i just stayed in
the bathroom on the toilet for and
i fell asleep and let's take
and then people had to come in
and be like are you okay and
then like i know dave everyone's still
got pancakes and disorder yeah yeah i
mean i'd like he kind of came
in i was like you're okay you're
okay you're okay buddy um and like
sort of took care of me and
i remember being at ah patton oswald's
bachelor party and ah i took some
drug right before
for it and um i was at
his bachelor party and like a big
night came no epitope is a night
came in or something yeah right what
happened but i was too fucking high
medieval bachelorhood and i and we know
we were at a steak restaurant laws
south and is one of the most
confusing things if you were really fucked
up
and then that happened i was really
fucked up and i started getting very
paranoia and i was like felt like
i was being judged by everyone there
and horrible david the worst kind of
high anymore yes i remember tv world
david cross was next to me and
i was like oh my god david's
and i've always felt judged by david
cross in certain ways right so um
it's not familiar
if you feel like you're um but
it is great you mean carmel
what eminem
ian carmo said you mean channel
oh yeah karma oh david david's grade
and and and very nice but i
for some reason i felt like i
couldn't tell him and i remember telling
him and he'd be the perfect person
to tell he was yeah actually because
i i told him i said i
feel really weird i'm way too high
i don't know what's going on i
don't feel good i feel re
early paranoid he's like hey it's okay
everyone feels like that and like talk
me down i was just like very
appreciative yeah to him yeah yeah but
do you think you told us that
i'm just have say that for the
record shares term i'm happy but i'm
drunk now look i don't remember anything
you've said just at the end that
vaguely vaguely go okay so i've told
this twice then will you remember it
with the next time we play three
different review yeah
i was a start bachelor party yeah
um i the first time i did
ecstasy i remember just last night
i have this bill from ninety ninety
four and i've been saving um time
to drop mbean my p nodes call
isn't that what like the i mean
yeah fish terminology yeah oh okay you
should know this my brother likes fish
you should know this yeah he's the
best guitar
one drop per beam drop
um i was um should i say
people's names is so long ago i
don't know i guess just don't i
was
unless we ask or no say them
all then we'll believe them all so
we know we can't believe it's really
not it's actually not important to the
store okay but i just remember i
i we were at um friend's house
and we were going to go to
another friend's birthday party which was at
the h m s bounty oh yeah
it was a great bar bar and
like korea too
down on wilshire which is sort of
not likely theme yeah it's funny wasn't
apma it wasn't like a korean bar
it was it was you know hotel
yeah and it was like it was
nautical themed and sort of english seeming
yeah in the middle of korea town
yeah yeah yeah um and so like
the brass monkey was also like decorated
like shit i guess it was right
yeah yeah
anyway um and so i are ass
monkey we were all going to do
there was a group of us like
for i think four of us were
going to do ecstasy before we went
to this party and wow so we
we we go we took the pill
it was illegal summit then i'm a
dark now you can do it as
much as you
e illegal illegal you have been branded
illegal illegal you shall be taken away
and so we did it at my
friend we have a hard time waiting
outside
just in case we ever tell anything
incredibly incriminating really hobble me i'm speaking
into a little button on my on
my arm illegal ah so we we
all take it and then i'm sitting
there and not you know nothing's happening
in and i'm like man i guess
it's not you know there's not going
to happen for me and then at
one point i said
i feel weird
and ah you know my friend we
had one person with us was not
on ecstasy and she said weird hell
and i said
i don't know like i might be
sick and she goes well why don't
you go into the bathroom and here
yeah you see how you feel
and so i went in the bathroom
and like i i put water on
my face and then i looked in
the mirror and i saw my pupils
were gigantic i was like oh hi
i'm on drugs yeah and that n
did you feel fine after that like
i had a great takei good i'd
agree to give yourself up to the
experience we went yeah we went to
this we went to this party and
then when we got to the party
it was like weird for us because
we were the only people that were
having this one experience and we were
like we were not the greatest guest
at this party because we kept going
off by ourselves talking about touch stuff
yeah i love this fans of the
show basically you're listening to two nerds
talk about being on what am i
i mean you're cooler than us yeah
true i was pretty cool i think
we're all really cool and i think
our stories are ah neighborly i'm simply
that or they were
relatable to a bunch of squares hopefully
well yeah because everyone there because everyone
out there goes everyone does coke you
fucking square
whatever i do your thing if you're
like you whenever you want we're just
talking about our lives have you leave
me alone yeah i don't want be
around you alright we have to take
a break
and we're back and we're back and
by the way one thing i want
to say oh people give us a
bad rap for telling the same stories
over and over yeah i started the
story thinking i'd told it before about
the thief in the night series and
you guys were like no what is
that oh of course
so it's we know it's a half
my fault half year this is how
it is
this is just life i mean i
think you tell the same jokes in
line why my question is why do
any of you remember these stories we
oh good point yeah forgot you should
forget everybody hypnotized yourselves into forgetting everything
we talk about on the show this
is i'm constantly saying this folks
you've got to hypnotize yourself you got
to do it there's the love living
in you have the stories okay it's
also funny that you won't remember a
story until there's one crucial detail it's
like yeah oh i have her i
know it oh i remember it was
the craziest thing oh i know well
that's kind of what that game was
really hard were no questions because i'm
not listening to your song
but i don't have the context at
all and i know who you are
yeah yeah alright we're gonna play pretty
sure yeah i'm trying to think of
the rhythm for this three because i've
done it an improv okay this is
called bad rap it's submitted by emma
bradshaw and we basically are going to
chant bad rap bad rap bad rap
and you're saying it's like the beastie
boys i think the chacko my favorite
shirt
my favorite shirt is blue and red
yeah right yeah right yeah she's only
just do it like that okay no
no it's definitely wrong but i think
we just like that because i can't
really figure out in my head what
it is my favorite color is blue
and red but bad rap bad yeah
and then the next person when i'm
tired i go to sleep yeah right
but yeah so you say a line
that would rhyme yeah we indeed should
run should run out and said you
change the last word now my question
is does the next person know i
think you start over a new you
start over anyway okay so you don't
have to do the rhyming with sleep
would be an extra added level to
la yeah and it also makes it
harder if you're the random word you
throw in is really weird yeah okay
right here we go
bad rap bad rap my favorite
i didn't know who it started okay
i'm sorry please the last second oh
you're gonna start i'm going to start
okay oh three oh two three two
bad rap bad rap i'm standing at
the corner store bad rap bad rap
when i'm hungry i ask for less
bad rap bad rap
yep drinking waters what i do all
day bad rap bad rap that's
man when we take this one i
knew that it was gonna be trouble
for both of us as you want
to rhyme no because we're just bad
at any of this it's it's both
that i want to rhyme but i
also want to put the word
right right right yeah alright let's try
it again let's go okay you want
me to say awesome i'm gonna start
i'm gonna start okay okay lol rhyme
bat three two three two bad rap
bad rep my favorite thing to sings
a song bad yep bad rap you
may think i'm right you know you
are right
bad yeah i
ah
okay so far both times with i
yeah i like me it's so hard
to divorce of anything yes it's yes
these are completely new things right this
is a harder part to me started
this dark this is definitely yeah now
you start it could be anything at
all this is definitely a hard game
i'm i'm surprised i
pulled it off well yeah alright here
we go it's really we go through
to three two bad rep bad rap
last time i had the strangest dream
bad rap bad rap when i'm scared
i want to cry bad rap bad
rap that's why i go to a
therapist bad rap bad rap
did you ever read stephen king's it
bad up bad rap that you said
i'd see the mist ah rap bad
rap but this is a whole new
one i did a slam time which
i think you sorry i'm sorry bad
rap bad rap i like to listen
to music
can we do the straight lines
ah alright i try to write bad
rap bad rap my favorite clothing is
my pants bad rap bad rap when
i have a picnic i see a
penguin yeah bad rap did you ever
have a stale sandwich bad rap bad
rap i hate my mom she's
a stupid hoe bad bad rap seriously
my mom really sucks bad yeah bad
rap i think i look good in
a tuxedo bad bad rap
you know good kind of amazing about
it when you when you is u
a e a long gated the actual
word knows i mean it's like every
every line is equally a bad rap
because nothing ever wrong so it's almost
like it doesn't matter what was said
before you really good point re hydrate
but it has to matter because it
has to be like
what you expect the word to be
so yeah because there's only three of
us it's more it's less obvious what
the what the and yeah that that
that that okay okay you're starting in
bad rep but bad rap i want
to go to the beach bad rap
bad rap should i have all of
them okay bad rap
and one of each
huh
bad rap bad rap i like a
quarter i like a dime bad rap
bad rap random when i'm running late
i take my midst
is
ah
i think i did it wrong too
because you're only supposed to head you're
only supposed to swap the one word
right yeah okay god i gotta go
so everyone's ready for the word you're
about to say right yeah yeah but
yeah and it has to make sense
okay got it alright man you wanna
start again yeah rep bad rap i
am looking at the sun bad rap
bad rap
yep
i was like i finally hit on
one long after i was supposed to
start i was like son what rhymes
son yeah yeah finally got one then
i was like i had nothing to
say about it yeah i'm really sorry
that's good breakdown what happened though yep
that's that's what the mind goes behind
the three cheer okay
already doing to get are we done
no no it's okay who wants to
start i'll start bad rap bad rap
you know i love my sweet little
doggy bad rap bad rap it's not
the weather outside is kind of misty
bad ms battery
um i went to a concert show
bad arrive bad rap when my friend
asked me i said ok bad rap
bad rap i like to look at
a picture frame yeah bad wrap my
lion here is very fierce bad rap
bad rap
seriously take a look at my lion
bad bad rap if you can't see
it then you're not even making an
effort bad rap bad rap what do
i do when i don't know what
bad bad rap i think i'll go
poop out of my penis rep so
sorry something
it's wrong with me
i got a phone call on my
phone back up bad rap please go
away and leave me be bad yeah
that seriously please don't call the cops
bad rep bad rap i'll see you
at top of the charts bad rap
bad rap
a plan i am leaning in my
chair bad rap bad yeah i took
off my hat and i didn't find
my ears bad ram bad rap some
people say that the sun is hot
bad bad rap and i am lying
no i'm yes i am yeah bad
rep what am i going to have
for dinner pizza bad rap bad rap
yeah pieces hearts yeah why do you
you always set me up i'm sorry
always always ever since we started this
podcast you always set him up this
right every time we play bad rap
i need to go to podcast couples
therapy the therapist okay well it seems
hey okay go ahead and say what
you said so
we do this
three chirp y game what you playing
a game it am i playing a
game a game we just listen to
what he's trying to sell right thank
you this is serious this is serious
serious i can't pay attention because i
can't hear what either of you are
saying i think why say i don't
know this series saying about me
me and i how i can't hear
you and i just want to talk
and like i feel like i can't
be a therapist why do we pay
for three sessions in advance yeah had
to do it
watch
she left she bad rap bad rap
she winked and then was gone back
up bad rap i hope you like
my little ditty bad rap bad rap
i went to the zoo and saw
horse battery bad rap when my friend
asked me how it was i said
huh
wrap sitting inside a cardboard box bad
rap bad rap i liked that little
red-tailed ah or bad rap bad rap
when i asked if i should i
said i otter bad yeah bad rap
my favorite show is welcome back to
that old teacher
better yeah but bad rap if you
go outside you'll see the sky bad
rap bad rap don't ask me when
you say if you should do ooh
and that's how you play well and
that's how yeah how often does it
end up with a bay but
it feels right that feels feels right
it feels right but listen thank you
all for listening listen
look thank you all for listening ah
we love that you do it um
if you would like to hear add
lovely versions of the show you can
go do so at stitcher premium or
at cb world dot com um and
if you wanna follow us on the
socials were three threesome usa everywhere and
rachel's three three mm
usa ah at gmail dot com to
send us a three church or call
us at our phone number what's the
number and the number is and the
number goes a little something like this
four two four two five two four
six seven eight and that is hag
claims eight and it's in the episode
notes in case you don't know good
way to remember it is like it's
there's not the number one at all
and there's not a number three at
all no but there is another number
nine so if everything if you've filed
a one or three or a nine
so here's your remember god for two
for just remember four two four okay
super actually just remember the hopes remember
to vive two and then after that
you go you think it's gonna be
five six seventy it's for success but
the mnemonic delay yeah force you've all
you have to remember forty four because
remember forty four times and lee fleet
issue five two to five years if
i do yeah they go together like
so
remember that work for lore to find
time to actually make sense and instead
of watching seven eight you're doing for
six seven minutes you're going for two
four two five two five two four
nine no five two four two or
two or two sats up five to
stop stop four
city seven eight there you go that's
your advice so easy to remember so
thanks everybody
yeah we love you we will be
back next week with more of this
bullshit yeah yeah hypnotize yourselves by ca
uh