hey everybody three is coming back and
you are ready for it oh my
god oh god it feels like it's
been forever and yet it feels like
it has been much time at all
you know what because we haven't done
it in a while but then we're
also doing it again that's what's fun
about it so it's gonna be great
you're gonna hear
other news stories about what's been going
on in our lives since we last
left i'm shocked by the way you
haven't let me talk yeah that's all
that you you gotta you gotta fight
every day really like okay we let
each choices what the show is i'm
paul by the landlord and obviously obviously
you're subscribed to this you know what
this is yeah man we're coming back
next week
iq guys it's really gonna be great
and coming back on thursday nov jay
burr seventeen we're in topics that will
be dropped in the episode and in
addition to new stories will also be
telling us who are old stories garrison
well will touch on some but we'll
try to yeah news stories new age
news stories by yourself i tell you
about something that happened in topeka is
yeah we're just doing local news stories
news stories from all over the world
won't believe it yeah well this woman
here's what happened in kildare please listen
and follow wherever you get your podcast
you gotta listen otherwise what's the point
of video
of this our lives so important to
be i love you we're coming back
next week november seventeenth you gotta listen
you gotta follow us not personally no
no no all but professionally follow our
instagram accounts yeah stalk us on insta
do you have anything you're gonna talk
about this season yeah i'm gonna talk
about my life oh shit i'm gonna
talk about my death too good you
always do
alright well we'll see you there yeah
sorry i don't i don't know what
else yeah goodbye forever