three
oh we're back baby oh yeah but
this isn't us being back yet no
no no this is purely a prelude
to us being bad you're being low
paul revere's for ourselves saying that we
are coming we are coming next week
paul revere by the way was not
i guess he was a paul revere
for other people but he didn't he
wasn't going around
i'm going i'm coming i'm coming you
probably did at some point
i hope so i were you confused
by what i said oh no but
i just think it's funny a funny
idea if they've paul revere was a
paul revere for himself what if he
had his own paul revere paul revere's
coming here it's because he's the big
news these are the kinds of things
we can get into on our show
when we do the full episode this
isn't a full season full episode this
is not a full episode we're just
letting
you know all your mile there's no
way around it because we're letting you
know that we are coming back we
cannot wait we're going to be back
in one week with our new season
it will be it'll be one weeks
and spin three months
it's been a little while but we
are going to be a wow wow
so i have done my three uto
mapusa oh wow
we're coming back for our new season
next week and there's just so much
to talk about the amount of topics
that we have not been able to
talk about because we haven't had a
podcast a podcast yeah wow yeah we
have that a podcast talking about it
on and now we do have it
again and we're gonna be able to
share all this stuff with you guys
it's actually a very big ne let's
tease what we're going to talk about
this
lawrence topics the season there's a huge
episode of lawrence topic yeah there's of
course we have reality recap yeah yeah
we i don't want to brag but
we do talk about the song walk
the dinosaur at one point we really
do at great length i say we
talk about it more than most people
ever had even the people who created
it i don't even know if it
is a brag to say that i
feel like we talk about more than
was but not as
much as not once yeah yeah what
else do we talk yeah we talk
i i i tell a story about
something that happened to me on christmas
eve as well as someone else harrowing
and d harrowing indeed there's so much
to talk about on this episode of
freedom and you'll hear these stories five
more times throughout the rest of the
season yeah so
so you just try not to soak
it in the first time because like
you'll watch over yeah make fun of
us so much we're gonna really pour
it on we're gonna tell the story
and every episode yes we didn't just
do a word for word of each
episode airs oh an arc of one
story per threesome
um but it's starting next week or
so happy to be back yeah um
here's the other thing we're also doing
bonus little what we call three meme
episodes and those are every other week
i come three mmmm creamy
it's true do you really i do
but privately right yeah
thank you for sharing that with us
yeah like my diary the australian creepy
three meme creamer according to the moon
premium today
could occlusion
during our three-room chromium i believe i
screamed oh it's been quite a dairy
meal
they were saying why you thought i
was saying ah so i think you
are hearing that these three mean here
yeah these three new episodes come out
every other week on wednesdays whether you
like it or not yeah if you
don't like it it's not affecting us
at all we're still gonna doesn't affect
you either so like so he got
to
here i'm rubbing my fore finger and
my thumb together to do the violin
thing but these tiny vi loser are
so are short episodes where we're going
to respond to your voicemails and you
can get those columns episodes in my
diary sepsis chromosomes and they're hosted by
shep rose from southern charm these are
available exclusively
cvb world and also apple podcast premium
and that's where we're going to be
ah responding to your emails and all
your voicemails that's where it happens that's
where it happened that's the room where
it happens the room was that it's
something room where i'm wrapping
ah um also we have three visiting
on the twos that's oh yeah those
are old eps all the so if
you want to catch the original for
all the originals so it's all going
down starting next week it goes down
the dms yeah yeah so we're gonna
send everyone a dio yep to let
you know that a new episode is
coming out we're also going to try
to hit you up and
have you know relationships were gonna i'm
gonna ask you right now okay this
is for the rest of the season
you up
constantly never go to sleep just an
alias of to stay up until yeah
able to hit with us make it
a marathon here's what you do wait
for the entire season to come out
and then stay up very big yeah
yes yeah and then stay up for
days drawing on your walls thinking of
all the memories of the things that
you heard yeah it's sort of the
number twenty three in there sure
um so next week episode one of
our new season comes out this is
so exciting this is like with star
wars episode one came out this is
huge there will be a line around
the block to download this comment everyone
will hate it
and then years later another generation will
say actually like yeah we're still waiting
for that
yeah so get ready for it because
it's oh my god are we ready
for ya oh we already heard so
many of these episodes and there some
song brown wowee rises like are you
ready are you ready for it wow
wow well please someone tell us what
this
song is where someone far to be
under omidyar said i'll find out alright
so it's coming next week until then
i hope you have seven wonderful days
i hope you have sex that's what
i thought you were going to say
well i hope you have sex at
least twenty times if all let me
say something if you're into sex unless
you're ace habit i think it's swift
song
yeah it is you're right or you're
taylor swift i am wondering this because
i'm a huge travis kelsey fan and
keep hearing this name a lot yes
we used to also look at with
your eyes when you hear the name
because oh yeah eyes when you hit
yeah um we'll see next week until
then lauren had something
she wanted to tell all of our
listeners is the debs when you burp
invited the same dad your whole body
could explode okay so everything yeah yeah
this was the yes i assumed it
was going to be careful about that
yeah be careful and we'll see you
next week bye