three
yeah
oh yeah yeah right um yeah huh
yeah hey three um
this is a little show we like
to co trace down grip oh yeah
terrible stars you really brought it home
i got distracted by a fly
what was it doing well why around
but we get the oil yeah whose
name is a verb of what it
does
about elephant oh that's true he's even
look at that thing elephants ah we
got this bug zapper this flies operates
a fly swatter that electrocute them most
sure sure we began to swing it
you you either can get kind of
get them when they're flying past you
or you got when it lands on
something you go low we know like
we know how flies water
or works it's a tennis racket it's
not a fly swatter it's like a
it's like a wired tennis racket that
i was like zap zap zap and
they fry up a little nuggets like
you and then afterwards or they bray
put bread on them
can we talk about something else what
are you talking about i bet you
won't die why people are listening to
this episode yeah why are they i'm
not wow well let's talk about first
about who we are because i'm really
confused about the two of you yes
my name is paul f tompkins my
name is peter the intern
oh oh no i haven't ever guy
to talk about peter yeah we have
talked about in full here about it
on this episode but i have a
theory right because i was looking at
that dark peter the intern and fuckin
dorna be fucking pictures why you so
proud of himself in those pictures it's
like don't you know what you look
like you dork but i was like
who do i know who has a
dark
the face like this i realised it
was lauren nobody i know you're gonna
say some shit first hope people said
it was like our love child
all three of us are just doing
yes yeah well if it had a
mustache noticed it looks like you paul
because that's how people think yeah moustache
that looks like paul very men two
dorks the two come more very true
and i chose no i'm not either
about when i hired p t you
hired pci we're not gonna get into
this
but we already did and people will
hear weird
i have pgi right now peter traumatic
institution
that and you have you have a
bti as well yes i have a
penis tract infection
that sounds like yeah hurts it's actually
fun
really yeah well i mean anything with
a penis as long as there's feeling
down there you're going to have did
you put a piece of rice in
your penis yes what's what's i put
a shepherd's pie there
did would you ever see puppetry of
the penis from no no i don't
want to support that but i would
see it if i got a free
ticket merely a support thing of it
you want to see the content i'm
curious how they make the eiffel tower
if you went with just sit there
with your arms crossed even if you
are enjoying it i'd sit there with
my mouth open just going oh
more ram salivating you're somebody's mother
ah thousands of hours of podcasting um
do you think anyone went to see
puppetry of the penis and got so
offended that they left or i mean
it's pretty much how right you missed
the name of the show maybe they
mean something else i'm giving these guys
the benefit of the doubt to see
what this is all about they were
lit
or role here is puppetry of the
penis a current reference do you think
there's very nineties isn't it yeah i
mean it was there a touring company
where two other guys were doing that
you think you guys i literally have
no idea no i think a bunch
of guys a bunch i thought was
two guys it's a bunch of guys
with variety sized dicks
who was writing tactic guys who are
like you know what i really want
to be this they do on the
side
a turtle's head
this ain't nobody really button oh can
we talk about the dead fly nuggets
again can i just say so sure
it it it sounds very like new
york in the nineties and then i'm
wondering today tell you about the restaurant
i went to the ninety s in
new york restaurants my ears oh no
no you couldn't scan signal in this
guy you couldn't work there scott because
it was called twins and all the
servers were twin no no yes why
remember very distinctly it was very exciting
and it's very safe i was a
kid i was a kid so i
will do anyway if ty ten and
this was in new york city yeah
if two twins couldn't make it with
they have to cover their shift with
two other twins yeah just yeah i
guess it's just like if you can't
if one can't make it one can't
work because there's no point in just
having one twin walking around was it
only the servers or was it eh
everybody was everybody yeah in the man
i think you're right i just mean
front of house front of house yeah
i think it was only the servers
that's but you know again i was
a child kind if it was everyone
the busboys the dishwashers that lauren this
sounds like something i use restaurant staff
identical twins i just googled it oh
i was gonna say this sounds like
an idea that you had as a
child and it's been so long you've
convince
xd yourself and it was really real
i remember being there i actually thought
it was really cool it opened a
ninety four on the upper east side
it consisted of twenty nine sets of
identical twins who worked as hostesses bartenders
waiters and waitresses hostesses thank you it
was owned by lisa and debbie gans
identical twins and tom berenger there is
only wow
why skip over nick how did he
get in there housing involved in fact
there were only two non twins who
worked there full-time the chef and the
general manager it took us only two
weeks to find enough twins to work
here we've had twins quit their full-time
day jobs work here it's not about
money it's about the twin thing
i mean you gotta split all of
your unless unless people are tipping you
know forty percent you've got to snap
up their earnings with here's what a
fan wrote twins sounds like a pretty
silly gimmick until you get there when
you're greeted at the door by two
gorgeous identical hostesses and glance at the
bar to find two identical men pouring
drinks and you begins to grow on
you
this is a person who's just realising
they're bisexual
when i looked over there and see
hot men i'm not i'm over here
hot women and i that i'm a
bisexual exclusively does three threesomes that's it
i'm a bisexual is three somes and
i love twins wow god i want
to go there now but it's not
i bet it's not there anymore all
the twins died they all died know
yes i do too
twins die quicker than normal people today
oh no but they do die simultaneously
oh yeah yeah that's whoa yeah it's
great have you ever known a twin
a million millions what what scott have
you never known a twist is that
why you like your brothers scar
brothers much
um i guess i know them i'm
trying to think of any other team
i grew up with a handful of
twins i grew up with some twins
i was sleep i was close with
a number of twins over the course
of my life okay but not anymore
it was there a certain point where
you cut them all off or ah
one set of twins i was friends
with in elementary school and then you
know you just grow up and then
the other set of twins i was
friends with in high school and we
all just i'm so friendly with them
but we just don't hang out we
all live in different places i had
friends
we're twins and they had a really
rough life they were fraternal twins own
and nell and they
they've they've both passed on sadly but
they
grew up in this haunted house um
and i think about them i think
about them every day i feel like
i saw something about these these two
like a documentary or something there was
a documentary about their lives yeah and
the whole family yeah yeah i remember
that like a ten part series ten
martin was like um starring jack nicholson
no um it's a documentary
okay
also like we could do a full
episode i talk about this forever okay
well we don't wanna do that twins
for the year the restaurant or the
concept anything
you to talk about anything forever
that is freedom
ah well and we're all threesome today
we're all three-day let's talk about what
we're doing today because that's a very
special episode this is our ninety ninth
episode this ny ny oh you out
of your mind
um and this is a very special
episode um because we're going to talk
about energy and by the way because
one of us is addicted to drugs
and the other two will confront that
person and then by the end it's
fine there is we have a special
announcement at the end of the episode
blah blah blah just yeah listen to
it all the way through so you
can hear the special announcement movie you
do you'll be doing
gobi gobi we do eat but what
you're going to hear today is god
this is i mean it's our version
of a clip show you ever watch
a sitcom they get a york the
money remember when we were growing up
flashback to five years ago the money
was running out on the
sitcom all they could afford to do
was like ten minutes of a show
and then the other twenty minutes of
the show was clips that's what we're
doing today was it a monetary thing
is that why they did it or
it was just that they there was
altogether like the corporation yeah but i
mean i think it was usually a
monetary thing um but isn't that so
ridiculous when they lived together like an
edited episode just
like fran but i guess when you
don't have access to all the episodes
you're like oh yeah remember that one
but wait a second would the cast
get paid like when they prorate their
salaries do because they'd be in the
episode being like hey i hit my
head i don't remember anything like i
feel like we ever tell you about
something everyone got paid the same amount
of money but maybe it was like
shorter to shoot in the writers well
shooting the crew and all that the
lights ah you don't have to buy
pizza for the audience
but we have bought pizza for each
other yeah and it's all getting delivered
simultaneously at the end of the episode
which yes really really rise each other
with pizza and no one knows what
kind of pizza they're gonna get and
no one knows who gave each other
the pizza but we'll figure it out
secret santa pizza you guys can try
at this secret santa song is a
concept that's good
you know we really should start secret
santa pizza yeah we should what what
happens people show up they don't order
they just get whatever we give them
and then they have to give us
pizza back oh i thought that it
was this was like a concept that
anyone could do but oh no i
do us no i think that we
just started a business okay as a
business yeah see
huh
but now that the the secrets the
concept of secret santa is that you
know you're going to get something you
don't know who it's going to be
from okay but you also don't know
what you're gonna get true but i'm
saying you people have to know that
they're getting a pizza and i'm getting
a pizza they just don't know which
of the chefs is making it for
them and they don't know what the
pizza is that isn't
ready the way it is except a
day or two there or they will
know they can't order something specific and
then they have to give a full
pizza back to the restaurant ah ha
and is a pizza weird or is
it just like you got cheese
ah lauren has put on fake sunglasses
sunglasses you've got decent with some nice
toner gloves on a a virtual sunglasses
will look this is a clip show
and we decided not to do a
clip show of just this would be
boring clip shift just our show of
our show of the previous episode
oh now we're at a museum i've
never seen this
but we decided not to do not
to do clips of of previous episodes
of of our show because over the
past nine weeks we've been airing reruns
of the show with new intros done
by us ninties and then we started
to think about it and we said
you know what all of those intros
are going to go away and they're
all going to be lost to them
waste of time yeah um because they're
not going to be in an episode
so what if we did a full
episode where you listen to these intros
back to back yeah exactly so back-to-back
to back-to-back tibet freaking crazy and it's
also simultaneously going to be on marvel's
what if
can you imagine a world where this
would happen
but the the process of doing these
ou
i would love la la la la
but
the muslim of the process is doing
these because yes let's get into it
i listened to this earlier today and
it's basically we we recorded these quite
a few at a time and over
yeah over the time period that we
did these we slowly that in the
first one we get off track but
then we slowly lose interest in the
concept of introducing
these episodes and we just talk about
random stuff now do you think it's
that we lose interest in it or
do you think it's that we forget
that that's what we're supposed to be
doing maybe maybe when the three of
us get together we just forget what
because it's very talking about twins i
could've gone on and on i didn't
care what our plan was
everywhere
learn are you putting these on or
i am okay if i'm playing with
the zoom feature lawrence addicted to filter
she can't stop i just can't see
myself i really am
but we are desperately trying to claw
this back okay good luck go for
it let's see what happens so do
you guys what are your memories of
doing these intros oh man i remember
all times because i really i really
do i really do i remember all
these times and i remember him and
they were so good yeah and it
was so nice how we did
them and i think one of the
best things about it was the ways
in which we talked about stuff because
i think when we would kind of
just break it down and kind of
get into stuff a lot of good
stuff would come out and it's stuff
we learned i couldn't agree more i
think that the memory i have is
sitting in this chair looking at this
laptop and talking to youtube
what were your favorite parts i thought
the sentences were really good i liked
the beginning middle and end and there
were parts some parts in the before
the middle before the end that i
wasn't quite as keen on but right
yeah i see that i liked the
content yeah i liked i liked everything
that was within them it will say
and um i'm excluding everything that was
not in them yeah to the extent
that i liked what was in them
i do think you know we're seeing
a lot of people have a lot
of success with doing podcasts about tv
shows the third i'm not against doing
a podcast about this podcast that's right
and we're doing it whatever episode of
the podcast we talk about
we reflect on what it was like
and we talk about what happened something
funny that happened behind the scenes maybe
someone's computer wouldn't start we're not only
broke we're not the biggest stars of
the podcast but you still like us
i do have to say there is
a funny funny behind the scenes moment
that happens learn with you where suddenly
you you stop recording i don't want
to spoil it for people but it
wasn't it wasn't f f vt xem
it was an epic fail and it
was also layer one of the things
that i like about the the first
clip is that it was part of
god's grand plan for earth yeah well
and i think one of the last
clips was where you kind of hear
us really have a lot of realization
about ourselves in each other don't skip
ahead laura i'm just saying i'm just
saying because i think i think we
are we are planning to do what
did we say podcast mullet where we
do a little short beginning and a
longer end so maybe you'll get a
little something at the end yeah maybe
you want like i like part partway
through the show you can hear one
of us sinning yeah yeah
and you'll never guess what it was
yeah yeah here when it happens it's
part of god's great plan yeah one
of us sins and um i'm not
sure if the person has sought forgiveness
yet for that sin or rate depends
on god's plan here's what i love
about god's plan is that we don't
have to feel bad when we sin
because it's part of the plan
and you can do whatever we want
well it's it's whatever god wants this
what's right is making a sin all
the time i like god being a
puppet master and i like being a
puppet yeah huh i got no strings
to hold out already know anything your
legs could do that well they can't
so believe
leave it why by the way why
are you upset why this entire upside
down why am i i know this
entire upside down i'm glad you asked
god because the world is a crazy
place where you're listening to the freedom
my yeah
well we are going to so what
you're gonna hear is you're gonna hear
these these intros for the nine episodes
i know and then we're gonna do
then we're gonna come back and we're
going to do a three chow at
the end of a water bottle boysen
to drink it like you're wanting yeah
yeah ah some ah water with that
water i don't know how to
you do this job why don't you
put some water with that bottle to
rise over the take
yeah i almost cried we're going to
do stretches the end and we're gonna
have big exciting news at the end
too that's gonna fucking knock your socks
into your block big exciting news or
ben as we call it in the
industry michael jackson he loved ben
bay and the two of us need
look no mo re bowed bowed what
we've been looking for oh got to
remember we sing that song together yes
you beautiful christmas duet of been christmas
ben what is that it was um
that's from the mu
ivvy willard which is about a young
man my controls rats oh yeah wish
they were mice
that was the tagline yeah that was
a remake the original was bruce davidson
lauren my lesson i once saw crispin
glover
talking on the phone about finances is
how were his finances some stressful but
i think i don't know that his
finances were shut you know a problem
but he was having a problem with
a finance his name makes me want
to eat gloves his name is we
want to eat um nestle crunch
anything makes you want to eat nestle
crunch come on laura you're a real
leslie crack we we want to say
three we are so proud that nestle
crunch has a soul throughout the crunches
with us nestle suck it hershey crackle
the whole nestle family from nestle water
to nestle crunch we love you guys
thank you so much for making threesome
a reality and he
sdl yes nestle's makes the very best
when do they tell me oh well
it's not nestle's it used to be
nestle's that's what shot and asked paul
when did they drop the s they
drop two women dropped it
we had a good laugh at that
guy
well look let's just get into it
oh what you're gonna hear is you're
gonna hear ah these nine intros to
these episodes and we get decidedly more
loopy as they go along and it'll
be a little and then we'll come
back and do a three-tier does that
sound fun guys yeah yeah ninety ninth
episode
alright i do on food thumb episode
let's do it ninety nine or three
times ups now now now
hi everybody it's us the pretzel gang
that's right it is us the pretzel
gay way you didn't laugh at me
saying it
whenever we go by then
ah hey everyone this is scott this
is paul this is lauren this scale
this is scott this is lauren and
i'm scott paul and lauren and this
is us say that's so this is
sarcasm
yeah
yeah well so i'm afraid to do
another season that he wants to take
a little bit
welcome to the three um he's here
because he needs more restaurant stories so
yeah honey i gotta go work in
restaurants there's other zoo once he's andy
kaufman style he's gonna go back to
all those old restaurants if they have
closed down he is going to make
a little cardboard restaurant and call it
that the old diana's work i gotta
say
two of them have closed down you've
checked her maria yeah well ah matt
gourley sent me ah ah notice for
marie calendar's ah on the sirna closing
down because you used to live over
by their sure and go to it
and then cafe cordell also closed down
anyways yeah restaurant roundup for this episode
very sad restaurant roundup today as we
bid goodbye to some of our dear
old friends
look whatever people listening to right now
they're listening to old ass support of
freedom this is an introduction to a
previous episode of threesome while we're taking
some time before the next season starts
we thought we would we would play
some old episodes so we put out
a survey to hear what your favorite
episodes were and we're gonna be playing
those over the next
a few weeks with these little introductions
now if you want to participate in
the survey it's really easy to do
all you have to do is go
to h ttps colon slash slash www
www www dot survey monkey dot com
slash lower case r slash capital p
slash or wait oh lord i'd ever
let me start over okay you just
go to h g http s colon
forward slash forward slash w w w
dot survey monkey dot com slash four
forward slash okami hd okay here we
go it's really easy all you have
to do is go to h t
t p s colon forward slash forward
slash
w w w dot s u r
v e y m o n k
e y dot c o m forward
slash lowercase r forward slash
upper case p oppor case v upper
case n oppor case q six upper
case m upper case why you guys
there you're right there and they're just
next door on the internet and why
did we save data should go there
to eat to look at what the
episodes to the haunting image hear that
if you don't continue well yeah yeah
you oh she'll also you will be
killed not by supernatural means someone will
just kill you you will be killed
if you look at it as well
yeah so don't go there so either
way look stay away from that link
and again that is h t t
p s
colon forward slash forward slash w w
w dot lower case s cases and
forecasts are okay speak lowercase e lowercase
y lowercase m lower case o lowercase
m to lowercase k lowercase e lowercase
y period lower case z lowercase o
lowercase
m forward slash lowercase r forward slash
upper case p who close no i
don't know about that okay learn
okay so here is yeah
i won't even ever do miss size
i want people to evan perez is
to say you're not supposed to go
to go to your web browser and
don't type this in
it the code is as follows lower
case h lowercase t lowercase lowercase t
case as colon forward slash forward slash
lowercase w lower case study laura k
seven period case lower case to lower
case r lowercase v lowercase e lowercase
y
laurie hayes m lowercase o lowercase n
lowercase k e y period lower z
lowercase o lowercase um forward slash lowercase
r for sash capital p capital v
capital and capital q six capital m
capital y and you're there your fedora
but don't go there go to your
browser and do not go to that
if you go there you're right there
but please do not go there yeah
do it for your own we're just
we're just saying we're trying to tell
you how simple it is to end
up there don't go there is to
not it's so simple so many people
are gonna die i type in you
might type in atps colon forward slash
fortune
a w w w period survey monkey
period com forward slash lowercase a hard
slash uppercase p uppercase v uppercase m
uppercase q six uppercase m z sure
you might think you're typing that in
but then instead you type in the
other one and then and then you're
killed and yeah i'm getting a headache
i've held please don't get a headache
until you listen to the following episode
which will be preceded by our loud
ass intro song this one was so
good i think we told you the
shows we already told absolutely we told
stories that seem boring when they're described
when you listen to them they're actually
very funny if they were gonna do
this why did they just record new
episodes why don't you shut the
fuck up
go to reddit neat shit
that's our slash eat shit
alright so you love the next week
for a different episode but before then
listen to this one
what i what i bought up this
is a show called three-day well it
isn't yes but it's going to be
very soon this is the pre three
item that everyone listens to radio or
three them freedom prix huh and if
you suffer from freedom you need bluetooth
some people call freedom fruit
maybe the dirtiest thing i've ever said
um guys my name is scott
my name is amy lauren and we're
all the host of threesome which is
this podcast you're listening to and what
are we listening to guys well we're
listening to a best of threesome um
which is an episode that we recorded
a long time ago because we're taking
a little break from recording new episodes
until the new year this is well
not the new year necessarily but
wow i was misinformed you fiscal year
new fiscal
animals don't know what year it is
and maybe they're going by a different
calendar and a new year could start
tomorrow that's right what you never know
when a new episode of three-time will
show up what animals do you think
is closest understanding that it's a new
year squirrels
i was gonna be parents
why because they can think words yeah
but they don't they mean i think
i think dogs really dogs are able
to figure out the position of the
sun so they understand time holiness i
mean i don't know what ur talking
about parents just just saying stuff that
they i mean i think for the
most part they just repeat stuff so
like what what
do yourself or something what if you
got a parent to say
what if you've got a pair to
say i understand years yeah you could
dan then there we go i'm right
here or like i saw a parent
on like dateline who was like looking
like you know they'd pull the
dateline like a toy and it's just
ah he didn't want to crack you
wanted to murder
anyway people obviously know those stories were
like the parrot knows who killed somebody
but i would train a parent to
throw suspicion on somebody else this is
a twin peaks subplot is it oh
that's right yeah diversity no um oh
i see ah
watch four hundred years and do not
cause like
many hours there's not many hours between
boomers that have you know there's there's
problem there that i believe there are
about forty six hours plus a movie
yeah
not including the return that's included the
return but maybe like two episodes per
episode and then an hour and a
half of deleted scenes from the movie
which are very important anyway alright yeah
um look guys you're listening to threesome
classic or as i like to call
it three m legacy ooh i like
that this is a golden year this
is how it all
started or continued guys and we are
happy to present to you this very
special episode that we did a while
ago and episode let me just say
paul this was the most meaningful episode
to me so much goes down in
this episode so i established this is
the episode you know this is where
it all turned i remember this episode
lauren as being when
you officially became a member of the
freedom k yes and i insulted too
like when i left i was like
i think they actually want me to
be
you are of course filling in for
john gabriel's for most of the episodes
yeah be there until late ninety two
or yeah we called you at the
last minute because you come down john
ayers refused to do the show and
you said okay yeah and it changed
my life for the better for yes
certainly did well in this episode's gonna
change your life for
the better this is one that you
guys voted on ah on our survey
so listen to it in remembrance of
us yes and if you want to
vote on the episodes guys let's say
this altogether here's where you go a
t t e yes colon forward slash
forward slash we just say so please
double y'all but yeah thanx gianni di
da former for slasher law forward slash
slash c o p e bay and
big big six guesses whoa hey there
you go and you
vote in your vote counts unlike in
every election in our country this yeah
i'm like the last presidential election right
paul do you usually say big and
said okay oh no did you hear
that big six or big it's only
a little bit a little six
what does number should have capital letters
absolutely number should be capital letters because
scream number but you don't know how
capital six
okay enjoy this episode but i don't
buy
hey guess what dip shits were back
it's were you talking to i heard
you talking to us when you dip
she's never know you'll never know and
never reveal it i'm gonna i will
only tell carly simon and whispered in
her ear if she pays me one
million dollars
well aren't gonna know what that's even
referring to i don't know there's a
song one million dollars is from um
austin powder yeah that's that's what it's
reversing that was that was a movie
the popularize that sum of money well
also the character of austin powers was
based on carly simon yeah on her
personal life shag
just the aspect of her sexuality she
was getting
um welcome to threesome classic it's a
three-run this is the show where you
hear a show you've heard before but
maybe not maybe you're a new listener
of threesome and you haven't heard these
old episodes and while we're biding our
time craftily waiting for the new season
to start um myself
elf lauren lamkin wait did you say
where craft driveway leading yep
what is that mean putting plans in
emotion and and waiting for dominoes to
fall into this scott was like i
can't do another episode i don't have
any new stories yet i need a
few coworkers
restaurant
we are freezing only waiting until we
have new stories to tell you and
when we do you'll get a new
episode but until then you'll get this
and like it and you better like
it i think this one has a
story that is about something that happened
when we were kids no bed or
one of our jobs who knows
knows anyway certainly not something from our
future
oh i i hope we're not rerunning
that episode right where we predict our
deaths we're not gonna rerun the one
where we recorded in the future we
wouldn't that back to the future car
yeah way the gigawatts we got up
to we got to the old gigawatts
car
that's reggie watts his brother right yeah
he used to deliver ah gigawatts to
people from fred watts
guys anyway enjoy this episode of threesome
classic and will we'll be seeing you
down the line yeah well where hang
you we love you and we miss
you emmy you used to keep going
no viewing yeah santos
oh guys very active on instagram and
talk to me
scott what's new i love you very
much
anyway honey and scotland loves you so
much sunni pe scott sometimes when i
read his instagram captions i get a
little choked up i'm not gonna lie
there's so vulnerable on main
okay goodbye see you next time well
now listen to this first see yeah
he can't be vulnerable on this on
this format but we can't see you
next time unless you listen to this
first bye bye bye
hi everybody listener i was saying i
was saying height of are you saying
hi everyone i'm saying i have the
freedom listener know what happened to you
you see something terrible happened the last
time you oh it's like you're straining
to yell oh i can't yell anymore
it's a terrible accident i had
imagine if you had an accident that
took away your ability to yell i
got ahead in the throat by a
megaphone
running
but yeah you have megaphone powers i
would think that's true as a radioactive
megaphone megaphone like from marvel
no
lauren you haven't seen marvel
but you know what a megaphone is
you are the captain of the cheer
leading team you have a big ios
yo-yo ma ed roger blah i was
one of the little ones they would
throw at the top yeah were you
actually in cheerleading fuck no oh okay
i was gonna say we've never talked
about it on this show three to
see if i'd never brought it up
listen we this is
not a new episode so ah fuckin
calm down we are rerunning episodes until
we were ready to start our new
season and where we're picking some episode
well actually your picking some episodes that
you'd like to hear again you chose
this so yeah this new episode it's
because you either voted wrong or you
didn't vote yes you're caught
your actions have consequences and this is
one of them fucking out and also
find out if you would like to
vote if you'd like to fuck around
and then find out if what happened
is result of your fucking around you
can go to surveymonkey dot com slash
p v r let me take over
you go to serve i'm not going
to tell you
all the atp know you know all
dash slash w w dot you knew
all that part it's survey monkey dot
com slash lowercase r slash capital p
v n q number six and capital
emeli yeah that'll get your right to
the source you said em then capital
m so okay to do it i
just got
yeah alright so it's surveymonkey dot com
slash oh let's lower care before that
age http oh boy now we just
you just put it in it'll be
no prize just want to be known
what's before it okay so you know
you don't have to put this in
it'll automatically do it but know that
there is an h t e colon
and then two forward slashes than three
double
i use at adopt your hat is
a baseball cap with a question mark
on it is this supposed to be
like we have to guess what team
you're into yes i play for the
seattle
edward magmas
remember that move to seattle retailer's um
link scott they'll look at surveymonkey dot
service
monet manet monet da da paul now
i have to do it okay so
you you've heard about the atp in
the colon you've heard about the two
slashes defer the three w's and the
dot here's all you need to know
you can just put this party heard
about the fool on the hill
survey my walrus was paul dot com
slash lowercase r slash upper case p
uppercase v uppercase n uppercase q uppercase
six
him over gay sam an upper case
why now what does that stand for
why is it so difficult well here's
how you remember the p stands for
parte yeah the z stands for victory
the n stands for no new stories
the q stands for culo and on
this six stands for the number six
that is the age you are when
you're six and the my stands for
my podcast my podcast and that's how
you should think of this as your
podcast now i've never clicked this link
and i'm curious what happens when i
think it's like a scary face comes
out right
also rick athlete jumps out of your
computer and sings never gonna give you
up live to you but he's this
big he's so small well no biggie
isn't real life yeah i would absolutely
do that i would i would click
on that if that happened if a
little tiny rick astley would be a
hologram ruby him it's him but what
okay what have you clicked on it
and somebody else clicked on it like
a half a second later does he
get sucked back into the computer he's
in multiple like timelines he's like santa
claus where anytime rick astley rick rolls
but you can be in several places
at once
but only on christmas eve
so go to christmas eve and then
click on the link and you'll see
rick roll
this all made sense anyway enjoy this
classic episode of threesome or things i
like the ending of this one
hello is this a new episode i'm
scared no boxers of budge old bolger
we did more
high three-time listeners this is paul this
is scott and i'm lauren and that
was a clip from the fairy tale
play
freedom in the woods
what if we did an episode in
the
let's do it like shakespeare in the
park the covert can't get us there
no you can't you can get your
dodger stadium though fairly i know apparently
um guys we want to just thank
you so much for being such great
thank you i just to say thank
you
thank you so much so much
sadly winning on his podcast thank you
thank you so much i'm so much
seriously though and i know we've had
a lot of fun on this podcast
but now it's time to take it
down several notches and get on the
serious tip we just want to thank
you so much
paul i mean yeah i mean yeah
i'll sit this one
can you go to the three-time instagram
and read your latest caption out loud
no i don't want one come on
won't even be the latest one i'm
sure you're gonna add some more both
show why this will be the one
that's from i don't even know how
to get to it i think three
need graham
do you want to do it pick
up my phone flee oh like you
your your screen time is an eight
hours a day so here's his paw
eight hours mindfully twenty three twenty three
i told you on this show about
the week that it said it was
twenty three and i've told you about
the week it was twenty three
d told you about the movie he's
twenty three and me is actually about
your screentime oh wow
that was savage
that was a savage ratio code you
got right yeah i am here for
it um what is this you're listening
to threesome and this is new but
we're about to hear us in the
past yeah right now we're in the
future because you're hearing this before after
we did it so yeah you're here
we don't know when you're hearing this
so it's the future so it's the
future and honestly it might be the
future on the old episode to you
if the old episode really like you
who are talking on the earlier episodes
like there they wouldn't they couldn't even
conceive that this was gonna happen that's
true that's true
that's true we didn't we didn't have
the knowledge that we have now we
were ignorant fool actually i was listening
to one of the old ones hearing
of a new baby
there was something i wanted to hear
on the episode but i was listening
to part of it and wasn't advising
you not to have a baby yeah
and i was like hearing us talk
about something that hadn't happened yet and
it was weird to hear us be
so ignorant oh well listen to us
be ignorant on this show
this is lauren was the one where
we say there will never be an
insurrection on the capitol yes yes and
we said we could never imagine such
a thing it wouldn't happen the worst
thing is we recorded on january seventh
and i know we're all asleep on
january six yeah we're waiting for our
fifty presence
don't worry about it from epiphany jess
mcaleese and blue boxes yeah i think
today if any present today though that's
about to breakfast at epiphanies
guys have some epiphanies while you listen
to this show like let let us
guide you through some personal epiphanies you
some aha moments that you may have
while listening to us maybe you'll think
like aha i don't like hearing these
twice and maybe you'll think aha i'm
gonna go buy some aha because i
saw lauren and the commercial for aha
sparkling blue gone
me to take oh me um take
on this podcast enjoy it we will
be back soon but until then listen
to this in remembrance of us
yeah
yeah oh so can you believe that
how ah this is paul lauren and
scott and the present again and um
we just heard those first five intros
and ah so good but we're gonna
take a break if that's okay with
i hope it's okay of you because
we have a great sponsor that ah
you're going to be very excited about
we are here from oh
oh excited about the sponsor and we've
been begging them and now they finally
came around again i came around our
point of view we got them we've
got a good lot of tweets for
all of you to get it done
but they finally yeah little once you
guys started doing your part it all
came together thank you so much for
everything you did to make this happen
you are
our number one listener that's so please
hobble us and ah put us in
a bed and a cabin solace were
a misery look it up i actually
have seen ninety percent of that movie
what's well then you just aussie dvd
the miserable part i might have seen
the end i watched it like during
the pandemic
fun was it was if it was
so recently why don't you remember because
i don't fucking remember dude she's got
to there's got all right well let's
go wrong when we come back we're
gonna hear the rest of the story
and we're back here next one this
is us in the present and okay
these four when they really start to
go off the rails so no this
is when we go off this is
when the rails are not even inside
anymore because we've gone off them we
are a train flying down the side
of a mountain okay if it feels
going sixty five mile
as an hour and three of them
is playing at sixty minutes per hour
i'm in now pongo how many episodes
of threesome is paul now snowpiercer did
you ever see that movie about a
game deeply roaches basically percent of yeah
this is like that only off the
rails i really don't remember how movies
and i could like there's movie
is that i'm i've not to say
i i've been in movies but i
was a babysitter and then i got
in movies and i will be in
movies i don't remember how they end
yeah because you don't read the whole
script and you're there please remember to
the end how the between two ferns
movie
um
you were in it we had to
rush oh okay we owe the reshoots
to make it seem fresh it was
that yeah new show
i don't know i saw that movie
and i remember how it ends and
i know you only listen to your
part
i remember the original tune out i
was at the premiere i did you
would put sunglasses on his laid back
and you turned your back to the
to the screen to i remember you're
like you're watching how everyone's your back
thumbs down gestures to but i wasn't
the only one it was also a
ed harrison amy madigan yeah but then
like they were they people were laughing
and you'd walk around and show
shut people's mouths with their hands you
shut up stop i was like not
funny when people pass their hand over
somebody's a dead body to close your
eyes i would do that to people's
mouths yeah i know stop laughing and
they were confused why can't i laugh
like how did that work
okay so let's hear these bees ah
last for intros you're gonna love them
and then we're gonna play three at
the end and have that big announcement
it's gonna be cool
hey guys i just don't know american
issue because it's hot where i am
it's our welcome to my air conditioning
is on and it's like freezing where
i am welcome to eat em yeah
where are you i can see your
mouth i'ma miami mama mama asia rhoda
are you in like a restaurant you
are in miami malmo
guys welcome love welcome to three to
wherever you are this is overlord in
miami and they're like looking like scott's
here he's here and he's so cold
just like me hey you know my
name is scott i'm not i'm gonna
say not welcome through it and wherever
you are because some people might be
in hell and i'm not welcoming them
it's true do you think they have
podcast and hell i hope so yes
though they must oh my god they've
even more there can i just complain
about the apple podcast update i wish
you will it is so hard to
function in time to do it we're
in a podcast we're trapped in this
podcast you're complaining it doesn't show my
new my new
episodes i don't care
well look what i like about an
interface is if it keeps me guessing
like i get used to how a
word yeah and then they change it
and then i'm like now what i
think it's fun and exciting like an
escape room that's true
you guys are know escape room together
sometime yeah we should we should decide
while we do an escape i would
absolutely do that i think that's really
funny that would be funny so that's
going to be in the new season
if that'll be a whole ah chunk
of episodes called threesome escape room
and that's because that the so that's
coming up so you don't want to
miss any of that but until that
happens we are hearing these threesome classic
episodes some really interesting episodes where you
voted on them to hear your favorite
episodes yeah you're you're taking matters the
escape rooms like joshua grow with a
boom mike capturing every
anything they say yeah actually i think
we should have lav mikes so that
when we're like under our breaths cursing
each other that gets picked yeah because
i think that's fun for the audience
and for us to hear later josh
agreed to do that yeah he agreed
that's this kid is so nuts and
you'll hear that on this episode
wild
some of these edits he does in
this episode you're about to hear are
so crazy i mean yeah does he
talk on the episode but the idea
of judging with the boom mike
like trying to fake out clues some
doubled its cake and then he's just
trapped in it and he knows he
by the way will be forbidden from
telling us the answers to any of
these things which he will have figured
out before us but it's also assure
like if you're if you're if you
don't hold a boom mike as your
job it's a very exhausting thing he's
he's really excited to do it you
know
how much his arms are gonna hurt
you either way during the between two
ferns movie we did a forty five
minute take with andy daly and everyone
and i didn't think much of it
but everyone was congratulating the boom mic
operator on how long it was that's
amazing that's right i forgot um that's
a about hope you said that to
the boom and then he had to
hold the boom in the movie and
that's
hard to yeah that's very difficult to
do because suddenly you get camera shy
and pee shy i bet i could
do it i bet i'll do it
i bet i could hold a boom
and piss at the same time how
what's the heaviest thing you've ever hold
held two pencils
together or any job together or they
number two yeah so far that's happy
so for pencils wow think for me
the heaviest thing i ever held is
like marshmallow no
for me it would be eight clouds
what's their big hunting get your officer
item suck huh and why did you
get those arms around me
by the way we are all romantic
with each other so yeah final episode
where i was incredibly amorous relationship i
think people deserve to know that we
already guess we fuck each other all
the time
yeah
will be reflected in the new season
oh yeah actually you can hear the
sexual tension in this episode huh
this wasn't doing pop off this is
one that like right after it ended
we all just started making out absolutely
absolutely at the same time our three-phase
so the minute you hear the credits
just picture that
sure her three faces meeting at the
lips you know it's a cheap trick
you don't need to picture draw or
dry yeah john
dry and i will post it on
the three-time instagram
oh and scott i will make sure
that you write something really poetic thank
you so much if you do draw
please use a more recent picture of
me
like within the last thirty seconds thanks
yeah i'm taking i'm taking several pictures
right now and uploading when you do
it like the matrix right where you
have like all the cameras around you
at all times simultaneously like the matrix
yeah the red-billed i'm my build i
think my diarrhea medicine i just watched
a funny instagram
video where will smith said he turned
down the role of neo oh save
it for the next season because that
sounds great anyway think i told you
they'll listen to this because god he
did hancock know yeah he said he
wanted to do well but alas he
said i'm sorry god west i'm sorry
everyone that you enjoyed that movie i
mean no yes he's talking about webos
but but you
you gotta say you said i didn't
ruin the matrix for you yeah it
was nice it was still aware philly
i love him i'm not recording anymore
oh no goodbye
everyone okay i'm ready if yeah we're
doing it of course we're ready we're
doing it right now
hi everybody
this is ebay
oh no
is that true hi everyone welcome to
three threesome the redux version scott i
have to tell you that as you're
talking my little mouse glove on my
computer is right on the tip of
your little nosey you put a glove
on your computer mouse
in zoom it looks like a glove
yeah so shut up you fucking idiot
yeah he didn't notice two guys gloves
zoom looks like hamburger helper
things that we say even the things
we love
oh good
oh no
um guys this my name is scott
my name score and guys my name's
pole and and you're gonna hear another
episode of the hilarious podcast three oh
no in this episode i think this
is the one where we started one
of the really hitting jokes oh yeah
that too
also episode one yeah but i was
gonna say we started one of our
most epic inside jokes that would come
back many a time in the future
which one i don't know i'm listening
scam that i don't know what happened
to your lawyer he's lying
no but this is all all jokes
oh no but okay no seriously this
is are we really in this this
is a really really good episode so
um this is actually my favorite episode
of freedom and it's mine too there's
some things that are happening but scots
favorites like there's nothing that happens at
the twenty minute mark that you are
going to really enjoy more on your
writers my
favorite of scots favorites but it is
not my favorite exactly like if i
also had forty five minutes and um
twenty two seconds you will hear the
loudest scream of a banshee yeah just
in time for the spooky season and
listen be sure to listen for the
tag yes you won't want to miss
the
test the skin tag
no we just we just got a
skin tag for two hours yes but
look this is how how else can
i say it you're gonna love this
show it's just i don't even more
is doing press myself much more i
don't have the words to express scott's
self and what we're doing is we're
presenting you a classic episode that you
all
already loved and now you will love
again even more you loved it the
first time but you're gonna love it
the second time do you remember when
elizabeth taylor and richard burton married then
divorced then remarried again yeah it's exactly
like that yeah yeah oh my mr
some other aigner order some other great
couples
i've got a ben affleck and j
lo
yeah um elizabeth taylor and larry k
cara zoosk has nice name no she
married the construction worker remember that guy
for ten ski who married mary for
daresay yeah i know that because every
time you put down four tens in
a poker game you call it the
larry sure
absolutely larry morrison see lauren two thousand
post two guys crazy posters a lot
know who mary larry's posters lisbeth elizabeth
taylor explained posters soleri fortescue they fell
in love and they were both eating
a poster at the same time there's
very little only was like the heather
locklear with a bikini on remember that
poster
i said who married larry pretend ski
an ominous portent ski of things to
come
well look guys you're you're gonna love
it we're gonna love you loving it
and then you're less loving you lads
to love you loving it you guys
love to luu love to love you
love it
but op op oppa love ny make
nuggets by what that right now ain't
that right now just the idea of
em you wanna meet guys by the
way if we could be sponsored by
mcnuggets right now what was that old
dreams just mcnugget not mcdonald's
talk to mcnuggets get them to sponsor
us that makes nugget characters when they
had characters of them those looked so
good to eat did any of them
have sunglasses on oh easy yeah for
sure there's one that's creepy yeah yeah
there's already eyeballs in creepy the fry
guys sunglasses i didn't mean to say
creepy i'm tired
learn when to sleep oh no she
should around town glasses and she's like
a parrot she thought it was nighttime
it is nighttime alright listen to this
fucking episode goodbye it gets the fuck
out here
hello hello hello it's one thing oh
yeah we come through oh it's time
once again for the show we call
freedom this year oh yea scooters and
toots high minors and toots my name
is potters and boots my name is
hudson who's cool
yeah
lmao i hate trash oh my god
clean it up me i mean wow
all to do it the yellow hated
trash or he just hated people polluting
he hated pollution but that included trash
ate it all trash any ways you
don't want a factor all these until
lady hate it or did he just
say hey i have an appeal
onion give a hoot don't pollute he
actually he wanted you to care but
part of that caring was to not
pollute yeah so if you a little
kid most of that is done right
like you're not you don't create much
pollution let's go hunting on your scooter
what was ironic was he didn't care
like he wanted you to care but
he could actually hear glitches but he
felt sorry for us yeah
as a food that our world would
be ruined and his would remain perfectly
intact she was an alien all owls
feel sorry for human beings yeah if
you ever see an owl in the
zoo and thinks you're a coward yeah
yeah yeah who hasn't had that experience
anyway you're listening to threesome and this
is this is what we like
to call threesome refresh this is the
nearest taste of what you'll hear in
the episode yes i mean we're we're
recording this now but we recorded this
episode years ago like a decade ago
this episode is so fucking old that
nothing is relevant that we say yeah
hey this episode is so fucking old
your grandma farts dust ah
while she listened to this
new ah you said we're recording this
now but when people hear this it
will be then that's true oh my
god everything is then or the lessons
now we're in the past right now
we're in right now right now
it's like that they might be giants
song that to be that fucking zach
on the bachelor yeah yeah yeah you
were whatever may well use sir and
now you really oh thanks for putting
it and now you're uranium handlers still
anyway we're we're here to guide you
through this process we're gonna pop in
occasionally throughout the iso
oh yeah that's right so cute little
listen closely to the whole thing we're
gonna pop our way through i'm gonna
come in and say oh really big
secret of mine yeah this is sort
of like like pop videos yeah yeah
or that there was some show where
the tom arnold hosted and then no
thank you like it was like an
america's funniest videos but ah like for
you know people
that let them shits yeah dumb shits
and he would pop up in the
videos like a little oh god what
am i lesser used that why is
it doing that someone like him were
like i don't know no offense i
guess it is offensive no one wants
to see him no i think they
did i think they did and that's
all there was a period where he
was just fucked did he have his
back to the camera at least yeah
he did he was looking at the
screen like he was a little guy
walking up to an enormous screen like
mystique
yeah but not a silhouette you like
walk into frame return to the question
what do you think guys and then
you would point at the screen and
say something funny
now i see the show actually happened
ah well yeah so we're going to
pop in once in while and clarify
things like if we ever got anything
wrong we're gonna pop up and say
apologize profusely chachi beg your forgiveness my
yesteryear here josh josh comes out not
the very because i want you to
just skip ahead from the tid that's
the tag l and i have to
say we use a new technology that
you can't just skip
up ahead trying to find a you
have to listen through if you skip
ahead it'll just cut out and take
you back to the beginning yeah and
it'll it'll make your phone blow up
ooh hey and your phones with tax
law yeah you're gonna get fucked
okay so don't be a dumb shit
don't turn this off right now keep
listening to the entire thing you're gonna
like shit and you're gonna be reminded
to be like this is why like
this show yeah i'm sorry i don't
know why i have such a bad
idea of these people when i'm not
listening to show what i do listen
to the show it's like oh yeah
i do like this oh we should
talk about peter the inter
turn oh fuck fuck do that let's
do it that on the next one
oh keep one care yeah keep buying
more because this episode is already in
the can it's already like we're already
like halfway out the door mentally at
this point much like the audience so
let's just throw initially yes a cliffhanger
like this one
on and we'll see you next week
to hear about pgi
um um guys this was a tough
one we lost someone who worked for
wow starting this is like a cold
open we're starting with lauren i think
all want to hear what i said
yeah i ever know any of the
show like any sort of welcome to
no no just like straight no
or said about a cold open we
had over you know disguise if you're
gonna raise a paw show we had
an intern yeah his name was peter
if you follow us on instagram you
did get to know him pretty pretty
well he had any well my number
of posts where he got very almost
equals better than anyone in your family
you probably know him more than that
and peter
her was
look i'm just going to say it
he wasn't a great in turn know
he was tired he posted the reason
why on instagram he did post nudes
in the story that was something
yeah yeah you will really find him
because i wasn't part of the hiring
process like showed us interview you said
you didn't want to have anything to
do with us having an intern yeah
you said i want him to do
all the work but i don't want
to meet him yeah and you never
did oh i remember yeah and he
showed up at me and lawrence joint
office yeah and he said
like joints or yeah yeah we rented
we rented office two rooms connected at
least we'd there yeah it was a
glass wall between and we look at
each other smoking weed but we know
we saw so i'm really yeah exactly
smoky we see if we can hop
doctors obviously yeah it's so high oh
he gets so high anyway i guess
when we were so high peter showed
up that's probably why he got hired
he showed up wearing our minds long
neck and his weird glasses and he
said i want to work for free
for you and scott i suppose and
we say what can you do and
he said nothing but post instagrams yeah
and we said well that's helpful because
scott does all the
instagram's now and i think it is
a lot of things to break i
yeah it was so much on my
plate and you were wrung out emotionally
i truly was i would go to
sleep weeping every single night fare with
joy yeah with joy because i love
you luck tonight to it the fans
all day but it's a lot of
energy yeah well i mean to have
such a wet pillow in the morning
thing as well it's ending and crying
really does wear you out so that
i mean i dreamed i was looking
at giant marshmallow and woke up my
pillow was wet
i had a dream i was eating
a giant marshmallow and i woke up
i was shitting marshmallows
i had a dream i was eating
a giant pillow and i woke up
and my pillow had been eaten by
me giant marshmallow
yeah but anyway so we are on
the hunt for new intern by the
time you hear those we might have
found somebody we may have yeah um
keep keep a close eye on the
instagram stories because i'm tired of spending
so much time on it and interviewed
a couple people for the hum
that's definitely be talking about this or
i don't want to get a job
want i want it to be objective
yeah we are hot we want them
to be the hottest i'll find someone
really good-looking the one thing that i'm
you know i put a put ah
a ah apc for a new intern
yeah all points bulletin oh good extent
know what that meant
and not an applebee's
one of the things sandwiches applebees by
the way every once in a while
we go to applebee's oh yeah maybe
the national anthem now i heard the
other i think it's apple bottom jeans
you mean no no no but it's
why we go to apple bottom jeans
now it's onwards slang words like usually
we get nuggets or we get a
shake but now
we're going down to applebee's and get
the oreo milkshake for dessert and it's
not a jingle this is yourself i
found i came across this guy on
tiktok who is like jesus guy oh
yeah i was i gist across him
that way and chewed the world talk
and stumbled upon a most remarkable for
elo
it's like ah he was just this
guy's okay and he was sitting in
an easy chair and he's doing like
that what was called depending on what
the chair is just sounds like a
great tiktok so far and he was
like he was doing issues is honestly
you guys is ideal shit because he
was going like mashup songs that he
would just like go from one
song into another song until such a
low opinion of these weekend neck gym
and everyone's comments actually fucking flames dude
and then huh yeah that i i
went down a little wormhole with him
turns out he's selling out fucking concert
venues singing country songs include and then
people love when he makes these little
like
song mash ups on his tiktok and
until he got famous he goes in
the he did a show he's like
think tiktok amazing and the whole crowd
goes insane
a week is this guy named easy
chair mash
my favorite country because i didn't know
a thing or did i just put
those oh easy chair is a face
here's the thing but we don't know
what chair you're talking about lazy boy
yeah we want a brand name is
that a easy chair but broyhill
in an inter in any case put
out your applebee's and i said in
it whoever it is i need you
to have no photos of yourself and
you only have photos that have watermarks
on them that is the only way
i will know that you're legit because
you got getty images meme national yeah
images alamy photo whatever it's gotta be
just covered with water
march and you should be very attractive
and for for a girl that means
pretty for a boy that means handsome
i mean we did say with um
with peter we we also we will
thought he was incredibly hot we we
we thought he was really hot we
were stone out of our minds um
yes so we had
paul goggles on boggles boggles yes so
you know you got to know peter
really well we've got news so well
i truly do i mean i'm so
upset i truly do miss him i
thought he was doing a good job
yeah i didn't mind what he did
i thought his job was shitty and
what sucks is
i got to be really close with
him friend wise and couldn't tell him
that i thought his job was bad
and then we also agreed we were
gonna get matching tattoos like suicide squad
but also like suicide side squad i
got one and he didn't get one
like will smith didn't wow yeah what
did you get
i got a tattoo of his face
and then my face kind of behind
it like peeking around from his head
and he was supposed to get the
opposite his head the like the back
of his head and you you have
the back of his head the back
of my head was gonna be the
back of my head and then you
could see so it's like oh put
each other's legs together so that p
apple could see both ends and this
is like watching the show biceps and
then it was the tom arnold show
and my tribute and what happened was
now it's just neutral review
is that tenacious d
this is lauren your hip
um so um yeah sad oh yeah
we had to kill him i mean
fire him economically yeah kill him he's
gonna ruin them in a squid game
all right although these days there everyone
knows we put him in a one
vs good game he lost the first
game he's doing himself okay soil
or alert
boy mouth about peter boiler ruler
um anyway i miss pgi but hopefully
by the time you listen to this
there's gonna be a new intern who
will be popping off on a chat
yes god willing in shala so guys
listen to this episode of threesome this
is actually our least favorite episode we
have no idea
so my god i hate this one
i can't believe we did and you'll
hear it you'll hear wow no real
being a parent well we played before
we started recording we said ok every
other thing we each say should be
a lie so yeah every other thing
that each of us says isn't true
yeah good luck figuring out what's when
we started with lie or not lie
fifty truths and fifty
lies right
so listen to this and and boy
we'll have exciting news about a new
season very soon but or we might
not who knows but listen to this
one and entertain yourself with this it'll
remind you of why you love us
and you'll wait for us just a
week or two and remember we
might not have exciting news soon
enjoy by yeah yeah oh
no
damn damn damn damn thing
ah yes we fucking did it again
well guess what guess what we're gonna
take a little break and it's none
of your business what we're doing but
that's a little free time for you
to whatever you want okay and we're
not what look i know what you're
assuming we're tinkling we're not we don't
know that we're not
tinkling we're just taking a little time
for ourselves we're not doing the other
one that's worse either no we're just
going inside the bathroom and just having
a spare moment away from god i
just want to thank for two decades
i not making thinking i'm not making
water i'm not making stinking
you guys do whatever you want to
do no judgement here no if you
have to do that i understand some
people helping me go hunker we don't
have to do that till we don't
have to do that we don't our
bodies work differently find out who game
oh christmas find out who game shirts
are probably one dollar now yeah yeah
how about your your
shock charms by the way did you
enjoy listening to us talk about crocs
yeah by the way did you enjoy
that i hope he did and if
you do please tweet at cracks tweeted
crocs that you love us um okay
so we take a break when you
love us when we come back we
come back we'll play later feature exciting
exciting now i won't have exciting announcement
can we're bad just like we said
we would be we we are alone
we promise something we deliver can you
imagine or if you're a parent now
saying to holly like years years from
now like and i didn't lie honey
and see i didn't lie but i
do
tell her i'll be back and i
oma i'm always gonna come back oh
what a true yeah if that true
well looks like a thing to say
goods like don't worry because you said
she gets like crying some object permanence
subject comments it's a big deal it
doesn't mean forever authors but i hope
to live a very long time wait
what's that
paul considers women to be objects yeah
he says huh
god did we go
now i'm going to get cancelled oh
no um okay guys so we had
fun listening to those cliffs but yes
you know how fun times over one
times over you know how how episodes
of three demand and that's by playing
three years yeah and paul there's nothing
we could do about it you've decided
to introduce this three-tier to us this
yes i have because i agreed to
do it i've requested to do it
i agreed to do it and now
i am honor bound to do it
this entire classic by the way if
if you didn't do it someone in
your family would have to do it
teachers called
it just said song now this is
where scott explained the rules okay thank
you so much for doing the heavy-lifting
ball really appreciating
um okay so this is this is
the three-tier where
who of us come in and know
okay so here's how it works someone
says an existing television show could be
anything this is us we've done we've
done some other ones
the person who gets that title has
to do the opposite of every word
and make that the sitcom that they're
pitching they have to pitch that sitcom
so in this is us it's like
that isn't them okay and that's this
that's the show that they have to
pitch they have to pitch the show
to
two network executives and then also sing
the theme song at the end yes
and that's why we call it pitches
hit song yeah yeah first i learned
this i do okay so um so
we we well we know first we
have to pick a yeah save your
loving show for you
okay so how about growing pains perfect
i second it okay oh hello welcome
one in hi my name is ping
aren't you delight high ping pong cute
as a button what was your name
pingpong she said long that wouldn't unusual
name he has it's my nickname um
oh what's your name because i bounced
around from place to place sure several
name is debra
ira bands debra van well nice to
meet you we'll call you ping pong
if that's what you like yeah really
what did you say you bounce around
from please yeah what do you mean
when you say that was my quotas
races so i guess watch this oh
my god
fuck like she literally does it yeah
wow okay huh well that was impressive
that was impressive but i was showing
you based on two how it go
yeah can we have you in a
reality show i'm not an actor oh
okay good good to know alright ah
did you get any water outside i
did they sprayed me down good luck
and um i you know what i
don't want to waste your time i
know it's six o'clock on friday i
appreciate you squeezing me at the last
second of your day no we always
like orders before billy joel we love
to have a little meeting at the
end of the day that we don't
really pay attention to makes us feel
like we did a full day yeah
yeah so okay i just want to
kind of jump in so
i have an idea for ish why
don't you want to mountain pinball
i would if i could but i
can't but i want okay oh you
got me
can you show she's so darling
but she's a tough cookie as well
she is she's got this hard exterior
but i know that deep down inside
she's soft and squishy i like it
crispy thinner she would just be like
yeah it was like so we're like
parallel or zucchini yeah but i have
on high heels you know i'm down
for serious business your dpf right you're
like here
like sexy sophisticated lady who's also maybe
mentally impaired
um i didn't hit my head but
some fell on it
oh okay so the other way
so grab your friend love how confidently
you say it's it's exciting so my
idea for a show is really unique
and the idea is called
shrinking heels shrinking heels and how's that
spelled heels hga okay gotta go to
way okay yea sure cause i'm here
because i we heard a pitch called
shrinking heels about high heels yes suddenly
shrink to where the woman is wearing
flats yeah
and there's really only directive yeah yeah
oh yeah catholic law shoes yeah exactly
yeah and then there is the whole
idea no we were not interested but
we did buy it yeah okay yeah
no it's it's not that idea it's
a totally different one good thing so
it's called shrinking heels and it's about
so it's about a family of therapists
oh i meant that there's a family
up there a piss um no i
think you're reading like a jeopardy category
and snell
oh no i think we could because
i just heard it family of thera
oh okay thank you okay that they
are crazier than their patients someday are
they are because oh that's got the
mom and the dad who are both
therapists and ensure the kids therapist to
therapist and training because their own training
i thought that would just be born
therapy or i'm a dad whoopee
a i t i thought you were
grandfathered into something like that wait t
i t what did you say the
kids are th by the way put
those away when you say that just
to make it clear the kids are
kids therapist in training's got two of
them and they're big and bouncy and
yeah
exactly they bounce around like gummy bears
i'm one of them is slightly bigger
than the others that one's older so
the kids are really astute they're really
observant um and they're great therapists and
now you've got get a dictionary hold
on stewed the way you smell that
dog ceo yellow t
that's right that's correct
all ideas i opened up the dictionary
just tell your mess
that's okay family therapists and then want
to get buddy okay so even the
funny thing is though here's what goes
on go funny it's the dog it
was so surprised for this and wait
taio
yeah they're animals what is this whoa
i've never heard anything like this no
and so
and is it a totally silent no
no dialogue no music good question i
had the same it's an animated show
where no one talks no one sings
there's no music there's no sound there
is that um sort of beep that
happens when they're doing like a test
on tv okay
right right here all throughout or just
intermittently um intermittently just make sure you're
you're still paying attention it's kind of
like the netflix are you still watching
thing it's like it goes and it
sort of just asking you if you're
paying attention and if there's an emergency
this what would happen that kind of
thing does do the full emergency broadcast
system instructions
over that over the animation i got
the rights to those already yeah rights
and so is that incorporated into the
theme song because i would imagine that's
the only other time you hear some
know the theme song goes like this
yeah should we clear arthur osu oh
wow
there
ah piss there a piss this therapists
they're a piss
iss
drawback
sure la i'm just a fat joe
i just got i'm sending text
okay we're in the middle of thing
that seems like you've got so many
texts i got i got an upsetting
text like oh my god everything alright
yeah yeah anyone know i had to
keep pitching some almost there ah piss
there a piss there are shrinking little
piss
hey look i'm sold
i'm solved if i'm wrong it's right
there i'm sold
i yeah oh dog their cat their
mom and their idag their brother their
assisted thereof piss and that is that
they are shaking slow okay the morning
are not new side of tall they
are getting smaller smaller when they solve
your problems don't remember that part
the bitch gosh yeah we definitely establish
the entire family and everyone else is
therapist there's a shooting now listen up
shrink i mean i know that now
shrink shrinky
oh so this is answering our questions
in the middle of the
here's one issue that i have the
more you actually need the more i
realize it's to the tune of be
our guest what's that from beauty and
the beast was yes highly crate right
shrinky dink watch some shrink but they
don't stink they have beef it's delicious
don't believe me
wait all those dishes or dishes get
in there
satellite dishes satellite dishes pick up on
in this little world they pick up
the smell of things and they'll take
good tv shows cinnamon cinnamon
cinnamon scent cinnamon scent that's what facebook
like inside
okay well the internal rhyme scheme seems
to fall apart but i will say
i love this show i haven't heard
anything like this all day much less
all week much less all year yeah
and i'm ready to say but of
course it's not up to me alone
i'm ready to buy this but if
my colleague here says no then i
say no
because i don't have a spine yeah
and i'm i'm the tiebreaker yeah my
all my vote is is like len
on dancing with the stars no matter
how everyone else votes the way i
vote is what ends up happening so
um i gotta say you are definitely
mentally ill and that no judgements they're
cuckoo cuckoo
cu cuckoo ah i'm running up the
walls
and i'm looking forward to you being
in charge of millions of dollars we're
buying yeah oh my god yeah woo
you dreamed so excited yeah i think
i'm dreaming now aren't we wake up
paul wake up huh huh
oh my gosh oh my hippie money
what's going on why aren't you get
in here
as established where all fucking he just
about that earlier this is canon
oh that was fun that was fun
do we do more is that it
i think that's good i find one
a long time yes but we do
we have that exciting announcement oh yeah
we do should we come back from
there and say right no we say
it right now shit right now the
announcement is
three dom is coming back for season
full ride you motherfucker this is your
lucky day because three dots coming back
for season oh yes we're coming back
november eighteen
aren't used just admit it everyone weeks
we're going to start and we're kicking
off season four with our one hundredth
episode that's right well fantastic because everyone
was really worried that on thanksgiving day
they wouldn't have a podcast listen to
to avoid their family and now you
have it you're i think you will
have episode one hundred and one on
thanks guy
i guess what you'll also have something
to say you're thankful for it the
thanksgiving table if you're one of those
weird families that does that you that
is like i'm mommy daddy world's thankful
that the threesome boys figured out their
contract negotiations yeah
it'll make sense to everyone at the
table yeah and if it doesn't fuck
them listen but freedom is not a
cult but we do ask you to
distance yourself from your family members and
friends
look your family are obese there is
there espys as well what are they
sbs ropey are other people's people yeah
they're opioids opioids sbs you know me
obese s p s p p s
p spiess look at these nice um
but yeah we're coming back and we're
so excited so just two weeks from
today we're going to be back
back um we're we're probably going to
do a a trailer next week so
be on the lookout for that yeah
we're just stare at your phone until
it comes out and and please send
us topics to look i mean there's
obviously the big hit of last season
season three was the lowrance topics section
yeah huge topics i mean huge section
huge huge people loved it i mean
it was
hugely loved it was hugely obsessed but
every week more about a different topic
and one of the topics was she
was having a baby other times i
watch something that was ninety nine percent
of the time and then the one
percent was you having a baby but
we have had a lot of time
off and i have had a lot
of experiences of know and things
i can talk about my yeah you
have more oh my this is exciting
more to learn aren't topics is definitely
going to come back but we want
you to write to us to to
tell us what to talk about because
we don't even fucking know and also
scott you got a job at the
restaurant during the pandemic so you do
have to restaurant roundup stories yeah i
also appear on the show
well i'm gonna get to you but
now he won't oh you want to
write to paul f tompkins at twitter
and instagram and make sure you just
blow up his social media and blow
yes go ahead i have my notification
set that i cannot see messages from
people don't follow me so go right
ahead so go ahead why would i
can't see any of them nope
not let's go hunting is your life
better it is kind of yeah um
but um head over to three m
usa over at instagram too because we
don't have our intern anymore maybe we'll
get a new one who knows we
might get a new one
and ah lorin lorin jason gay you're
still here right lord shut off shot
ah ya
lauren has run out of power
good how we're going down for the
day i'm good you know i'm really
spacey lately though i and i can
almost talk about that yeah i'll save
it that's one of my top yes
fly keeps landing and my way is
that fly going to be there next
week i think i'd be dead by
then you better be house don't fly
have a twenty four hour lifespan oh
i wish i feel like
that's something they lie to you about
that's made me feel better but mayflies
live for a day but house flies
can live to ninety years
god well we're going to talk about
all this next week lauren we're gonna
we're gonna catch up with eat paul
and i have have expressly forbade her
from talking about her childbirth her baby
we want to talk about on this
show we haven't heard anything about anything
wow wow so we're gonna be talking
about that a very special episode one
hundred season
wow our kickoff episode on november eighteenth
pleased can be huge listen going to
be yeah but wait till you see
what we pull out for this show
when you see what we're wearing in
this episode your mind's gonna be blown
i'm going i have billy porter's hat
that has the shades motorized shades
and i have porters billy huh
definitely more bills hat ah
um so we're and don't worry we're
going to talk about michael jackson we're
going to talk about cause me all
nice
there's a lot of things about both
of them yeah we're a lot of
about all of it yeah it's gonna
be um but thank you so much
for listening this is a little free
episode that we did for you hope
you enjoyed it and ah free mean
we don't get paid for it i
mean it's just as free as the
other episodes but yeah you know free
two hours free in the sense of
like we just decided to do
it and have fun yeah you know
what's wrong with that nothing nothing
yeah absolutely nothing just say couple a
weeks absolutely nothing by the way war
what is it good for absolutely nothing
say it again absolutely nothing
so we've really run out of juice
here yeah it hit hard right not
true i could go right out around
like the lore and just looked down
like this i don't like i've obviously
reduced to this tuition you do bring
the juice and the juice is no
longer loose
that uses today huh
alright so we'll see you in a
couple of weeks look out for trailer
next week we love you until we
love you until until then yes then
our love shops
lauren or is enough hands i was
kissing the fans all year
oh okay lucky
love you guys i love you you
know bay
uh