three
ooh yeah
ah
ah welcome back welcome back welcome
lauren is over there she's the one
who just saying yeah in case you
didn't know that was scott who just
talked and i'm paul i'm here too
um do you know that show welcome
back kotter or do you know what
does seen it a few times oh
i've seen it i know john travolta
was on it that's right um who
by the way um i feel like
i what oh something sad happened to
him i was like hey i'm in
the news
something interesting happened oh never
sad yeah ah a lot of sadness
and well when by the end of
our lives we'll all have a bunch
of sad very true true on our
way now we're on our way now
it's right and the very last act
we ever do will be the saddest
thing of all dying but hey at
least we're not a cult
maybe it will die in a funny
way that's true but what's the what
way do you want to die what
are you yeah we're funny or funny
death lord funny can you watch of
an america's funniest home video if you
know the person really got hurt or
do you need mentally to know you
don't just feel like there's a lot
of people who send around like video
it's not america's funniest videos but just
like
tick tock type videos of technical things
happening like that where you're like that
person just fell on their face well
yeah i remember when that when that
woman the the news reporter came out
and start speaking gibberish and like partition
was the worst she said stroke or
something well that ever everyone starts sending
that video around the minute
that it happened like oh my god
i was just watching tv and saw
this and then we all like a
lot of us were like hey that
person might have just had a stroke
this is not cool and then she
was fine so now it's funny to
sanitation do you know this one clip
that i really like wait operation is
the word she said yes she's like
ah rotation she was she was she
was reporting from an award sarah
omondi and she i can play it
if you want yeah yeah i don't
i'm not sure if i've seen ok
then i'll play you one too it
makes me think of the paula abdul
clip where she was on some radio
show
and she was it seemed like she
was on drugs okay ready are we
ready yeah yeah man here we go
well let me prepare myself okay here
we go this is a prayer a
reporter and she's fine and it was
she does she she got checked out
by doctors she doesn't know what happened
doesn't know what it is but this
is an and
it was after an award show which
is why we were all watching it
and everyone saw these centers re-releases live
at the staple center with highlights and
backstage coverage we're seeing for the very
first time saree well a very very
heavy heavy vegetation tonight we had a
very derose derrickson but let's go hit
terrace taste and that's terrifying
is
that is so much worse than i
thought it was gonna be it's an
and the look on her face she's
confused she's know why she's saying what
she's saying it's it was very once
it was really scary but she's fine
okay well here's mine this is um
from the i guess it's it's a
british pop group called little mix and
there's this
video that my friends and i always
like to reference and because this there's
just this clip where they're trying to
do different accents and they go oh
yes yes okay and so this girl
tries and she she does she does
not like this being played by the
way oh well of course not do
you want me to find it and
play it through the sophomore and what's
what's the grape and little mix jamaican
and then i did my own version
which i can actually get last name
all of her fazal tape yesterday that
oliver fans by the way anytime you
post this they'll reply she doesn't like
it when you post this horse
okay so like this so this lean
into it i think because it's fucking
hilarious advice so it's this girl group
and she's there they all draw cards
of an accent there they're trying to
do i love that rock god or
the accent you'll do and she gets
to make an and so this is
her trying to do why would they
put that in there
huh
oh ma
her eyes roll back in her head
she was palsy
she's like bad let's hear it one
more time when i guess the extent
of it yeah
oh mama
it's so good
yeah she's like can i i'm trying
to make the play yours what are
you playing oh wait wrong what boo
boo this isn't gonna be like a
criss angel evenson anywhere you're gonna show
us a picture of your penis no
guard that pussy
let's go one what was that that
was me doing those doing it last
night oh and whatever my mind what
happened with sevens i did not investigate
so when chris rosaceae was doing a
tweet and he posted a picture when
he was alum knows a livestream on
play wrong it was a livestream he
was on and he was going through
his photo twelve years ago he was
trying to show a picture from his
phone on a livestream worse than i
thought and he brought up his photo
album and so you could see like
a slight like nine photos or whatever
and one was a picture of his
dinger dogar okay and one was a
was a picture of captain america from
one of the movies that he had
put
he had put on there with textedit
guard that pussy
and yeah obviously he knows that one
no he wasn't trying to show those
he was looking for something in his
phone oh my god and he brought
up his photos and the photos that
everyone saw were the sly would you
why would you ever put your phone
and your dick thing in your phone
why would you ever don't pull it
don't pull your phone out burn your
phone oh don't go putting it around
on alive
ah you feels a picture of your
pc phone talk pretty good around on
a lie
but back to okay so back to
my original question can you watch a
video yeah i cannot see that dick
and not guard that pussy um no
because i was talking to my mom
the other day about the the show
holy moly which is become a recent
favorite during the summer and she was
saying like
she finds it hard to watch if
she thinks people are getting hurt and
and she said the worst one is
that one where they get shocked i
don't know if you've seen it but
there i've never seen it does feels
like something i should have seen all
of it's grain so but but but
there's one hole where if you miss
the whole you get shocked tell me
a bit and they have these it's
like it's
like a doctor frankenstein kind of setup
where they have like electrical switches and
then they have people with putters who
are supposedly conducting the current and they
put in this fake electricity current effect
so it's not really hurting anyone so
it's like a mild shock it's like
going operation yeah but my mom is
like you see the huge
each electrical current on there my mom
it's special effects jimmy
you know what show really making neurons
sometimes as ellen's game of games this
is the other one my mom brought
up she goes yeah she's taking too
much delight in it she while she
loves watching them get hurt this is
yeah this is her version of look
at these story you are telling before
we started
i can't remember oh
just remind something um but the the
some of the things they do on
that show like look really painful they'll
throw things people's faces or they fall
really seemingly really far and i don't
know what they're falling into and i'm
sure it's safe because well can zero
can lay nose aspect you know i
dated a woman who was on a
game show
we talk about this i think we
did where they oh yeah it's a
fake shadow but it's so confusing my
brain so i dated this woman who's
on a game show where if you
lost you the floor opened up and
and it looks it looks terrifying when
you see it it makes you laugh
and she was like now you fall
about this far huh
that's weird onto a bunch of pillows
and went oh my fellow listener like
it's like two feet or yeah four
or five later on ellen's show also
sometimes they'll have a thing where it's
like you're laying in a harness face
down like mission impossible and you're like
being raised in the town how i
would describe face-down but go ahead
down
yeah um but they wouldn't know like
slam you down into like a vat
of pudding and stuff like overwater oh
oh nah doh he's rack so back
baby now
record is a recommendation to one episode
i was out to bill cosby rotting
in jail turn the sign back out
for coven to oh well how about
lori loughlin horrible um bullshit where she
got to pick which picker prison yeah
man i would love to pick a
prison it's just riddick i've already picked
him out yeah you guys gotta check
my prison pitchers page
shh there's a website or your favorite
prison track your prison if you ever
get sent to prison the one you
would go to ho no terrifying um
i went as a kid i remember
having a bad reaction to certain kinds
of slapstick in comedies like three stooges
stuff or yeah most of the three
sue
just stuff is like it's just silly
cartoon stuff and they have the sound
effects over the thought on mister show
that we were trying to write a
sketch of like if three stooges was
real the consequences of the physical stuff
yeah something like that but i remember
one one three stooges gag i remember
was like somebody ah like grabbing somebody
his nose with a pair of scissors
right so that's not funny
got a horrible thing about what i
remember there was a pink panther movie
that i saw when i was a
kid when i saw in the theaters
a paedophile inspector clouseau inspector clouseau yes
i've heard of these and he
so this enemy which is the um
the chief inspector or whatever played by
this guy herbert lamb and so bad
things are always happening to the chief
inspector who hates clues oh and once
again fired at one point i remember
he slips on something at the top
of a stairwell and the guy goes
so far up in the air and
then he drops out of sight lands
on the stairs and it's not all
funny yeah right it's not funny well
like just this guy would be paralyzed
how did buster keaton do all the
stuff he was doing well yeah we
actually did take a toll on his
body but it's he did all branch
any chase all those crazy practical things
chevy chase he
did somebody somebody falls that got them
addicted to cocaine
i remember taking a slapstick like physical
comedy course and they were always saying
like the what's not funny is the
fall it's the getting up and selling
the you were hurt or something like
showing your okay and it bothered you
yeah it makes it funny like that
you know i get that yeah
yeah the fall should be funny too
but i always i cannot watch your
videos of people falling on the ground
because i've i've fell recently on the
ground and it's fucking heritage really well
in the house around i was i
was looking at our camera and i
saw cool up and left the gate
open and then also our front door
and our
dogs started to geez it's a lot
going on our dog started to like
go out the door and so i
was wearing socks and we had when
we moved in we'd have the floors
done and so i stood up and
went no and then immediately my legs
went up and i fell on my
side and i was fucked up for
wow that's pretty on it's like a
fall you've had
battery free paul levy fallen fall f
tompkins
paul i'm sorry tom kyoto mf topic
do you know i have ah not
i can't remember the last time i
fell i have tripped a bunch and
almost fall yeah so is that a
trip and then stumble stumble stumble but
you see exactly i cannot tell you
those are how often i have the
thought not even with
tripping but when am i going to
have my next horrible fall because it
will happen oh yeah it will happen
i always say i always picture myself
like falling or knocking my teeth out
or all that kind of stuff like
but i had a fall when i
was in london for holmes and watson
and i was staying in this apartment
that had kobe callers and english flat
ass
and it was that's on me back
it was like when it was kind
of place that was like really um
at first when i walked in i
was like wow and then like the
longer i lived there the more creeped
out i was like right corner
and i and one of my first
and i was completely alone like most
of the time like months there and
i fell down these carpet stairs like
my socks just slipped and i thought
so hard on my cockpit oh and
it hurts but i just like when
you're alone and you fall like i
just was like
bear basically saying the medical ran straight
forward into like the bedroom and fell
face for four for the like oh
my fucking god you're just like oh
well there's nothing you could do beside
just like you be sad that happened
did you have this kind of reaction
oh mah and bah lived i was
going to the sarah i was like
oh what would you do
yeah
um yeah when i was over at
my parents house recently i got a
a stern talking to because i was
eating at the bar stool at the
bar and i left the bar stool
not completely percent pushed in and she
was like you're living with old people
this week damn you're going to trip
on this and
and wow how old are your parents
yeah somebody's forty one
um yeah i just falling is the
worst yeah i just don't like it
yeah it's terrifying it's so scary we
had the first ah the the last
place we lived before our first or
last get your story
that's what you lived before our house
now
we have this apartment where um it
was it was like somebody had flipped
it you know so there was like
a lot of stuff that was a
little shoddy about it yeah um which
we didn't discover till after we'd lived
there for a while yeah that's the
worst thing about that kind of yeah
no because you're at first like great
and then the longer you're there like
this every little thing yeah horrible yeah
which places it's like living on a
sept oh yeah
oh wait no i get religious vi
so oh yeah phone it and like
that yeah i think that's like one
of the i think that's such a
cheap gross way to try to make
money because you're doing the worst job
like you are you are you do
it really well and flip it and
flipping well is one thing i'm saying
picking out all the worst shit is
a mad even if they do it
good all that cheap stuff like it's
yeah it's just there's no
no point you have to do it
again yeah well the one thing that
really splurged on where these tubs that
had this really wide wall you know
i don't know what else to call
it like the tub wall you know
like like the white heart of the
tub is yuk yeah like like if
you wanted to have a nice luxurious
bath and put candles right thing okay
a but then they may wind like
one inch wide nother the middle of
tub was fine but it was getting
in and out was like you had
to like oh layout so far when
there's so high and so yes and
you just took a shower and it's
wet and it's like am i going
to break my hip right now yeah
it was terrifying every day yeah jane
he would sometimes like sit and then
swing her legs around yeah that's because
you know she's shorter than me it's
like it was scary it was scary
what a weird thing like how often
are you taking a bath like that
yeah but it's like gotta have these
wide walls i want my candles my
radio oh for the picture to get
you to run the place right like
yeah it's like it's not a functional
yeah yeah
they're just like ooh let's give him
a spa tub if i ever have
a tub it's gonna be so thin
it's gonna be papers since tub and
walk in tub like old people have
those actually are they look good okay
lie yeah i mean i know it
seems easy if you see one now
you go into a place you're like
oh an old person lived here but
why can't we
switch the mentality to where it's like
now a feature everyone wants like hey
check this out not just old forward
thinking young person lived here yeah because
they wanted a cool tub that has
this feature
huh what is the ah lauren what's
the one thing you want in awe
amaze you were to yeah indiana man
okay really i could say nah
whatever you want you'll get yeah and
will try to find out your braces
okay great yeah we're on the hunt
when they are put in the house
yeah what's the one like one feature
like that you're like man it would
be so great to have that oh
man so many things but
one thing i'm not aware of too
many things i know if you know
and i was just reminded of that
song recently well i was thinking maybe
oh you guys have lowered it wasn't
one of the new bohemians and one
of the meals went over his sleeve
mark niederbrock hell yeah and i've never
heard it here i've never heard i
like it well we i was with
a group of fr
since lauryn hill story okay i would
do the group of friends we are
trying to think of a true guilty
pleasure song because as you as you
you know as an adult oh wow
well as an adult it's like no
i'm not guilty about that i think
it's good fun so you know yes
but it's it's like it was very
hard to think of a song that
is kind of a bad like you
know it's bad like so what did
you end up saying what about bad
hey hey now the really really bad
they're all guilty pleasures really really bad
those you know those are all guilty
by the way i was actually tobacco
we have now done an episode with
my yeah oh it's true yeah we
go thanks to you both having broken
the c um i think that was
the that was the one we came
up with at the very end where
it's not the tiny brielle it's not
really good i love that but about
my pocket pop pop music that's soft
like it it's a good song alright
lorne what do you wanna talk about
i think like some cool things to
have would be a skylight oh and
opening one or no necessarily but just
like in a bathroom i think that's
like cool want to see those birds
yeah just like the sun coming in
like so much shed light coming in
yeah um i think
ah head of the papers oh yeah
i mean it does creep me out
to think about at night like so
many people putting drones over your skylights
or like a touchy was lucifer standing
tub and then a shower and one
bathroom so you could choose and that's
fun a stay of up and shoujo
yeah it's nice i mean i think
it's really like you mean
like a separate yeah bread so you
could take a bath or take a
shower yes yes um yeah those are
some ending i think a lot of
people have it i don't let be
so cool to have a skylight it
would be like you'd be able to
see the sun sometimes my mom growing
up had that ray will fall on
it that's why i always think about
it because it was so pretty what
what did when you were young what
what was there and you are like
open book where where it was like
oh my god no we used to
say live and let live oh my
god that's what let him know you'd
rich people if say well i had
a friend whose whose family you world
um joffe rich like kind of suddenly
they did not have to die trying
um valley of fun sakurai to me
about exactly how there was a pro
bono lawyer i don't know if i
know all the tow but eventually there
was some issues like lemmy charge no
no no y'all some one that was
going on for like
extremely long time like decades that somehow
ended with him getting of i don't
know okay sorry this is going on
too long i need that bono but
honestly i don't know maybe he was
ever pro bono but he was like
always helping the little guy or some
maybe he was doing that one case
and everything else pro bono hours yeah
yeah and so this was like some
soapy some big breakthrough yeah and so
he got a lot of money so
they they built this really beauty
huge home and so whenever i go
ah yeah so whenever i think about
like that kind of rich witness yeah
whatever majors where they had an indoor
pool oh and they built it all
themselves from scratching came up with it
all from scratch so they chopped down
the lumber and chopped it down and
they made it into bricks and they
made lumbering into bricks this is incredible
i had an indoor pool should have
vetted that they also had a really
um i loved going there and it
was just like a really cool house
but they had um all the phones
that they got or all that um
bang and olufsen phones are the bang
olufsen or whatever it's like a very
expensive sur le jeu i'm gonna look
it up but
there were more and i know go
off is it something that sounds like
me
bang olufsen
but they were just like cool so
they have like those phones so the
house was kind of before cell phones
were really awesome brand yeah not a
person bang olufsen hi i'm bang olufsen
and i know you have a phone
you like a landline call me please
i'm so normally it's good for emergency
okay so they have these phones every
nowhere and that just seemed to really
opulent what about a phone in the
in next to the toilet oh yeah
that's very cool i want that you
want to call people while i'm shitting
the fuck in the one place where
you want to be alone yeah five
minutes yeah dad i just have a
second you take your phone in the
bathroom every time you go yeah because
i usually read because
it takes me you know twenty hours
to shave
you've a sea of full desk and
their hours suck the phone in there
i'm like i fucking stop like there's
points where you just go can i
just think for a minute what can
i guess this is what they were
invented for as for you should not
take it outside of the toilet
you know what a smartphone should just
stay right by the toilet keep it
by the toilet i knew everybody's the
magazine moment of toilets i used to
be a malbec i mean i covered
that it's like i don't like storing
them in there now it feels gross
now but even though i'm bringing my
phone which is worse it's more disgusting
to have your phone because your germs
do you know what's really what's germs
are coming out of here
whoa spray possible germs
something has been really good a real
it was a really good experience was
we were watching this and i'd probably
told you guys about the show the
bureau the french show yeah sounds french
it's liberal in america told the dresser
it's in subtitles it has subtitles so
you couldn't use your phone you had
to just watch the show yeah and
it was like a weird adjustment at
first of like oh normally i'd be
doing this so many times sometimes like
oh yeah it was great and we
really we love the show like we've
got really invested in it you have
to really be in the mood to
be like i'm gonna put my phone
then you get invested because you care
about the plot yes but yeah it's
so hard yeah i'll be watching shows
and then go okay i have lit
literally no idea what oh yeah yeah
yeah i've seen that five times by
going to a movie theater is sometimes
really good because you can't take your
phone out because yeah it's rude so
it makes you you know watch the
thing whereas if you just watch something
at home like we watch milan or
whatever recently you can just constantly be
checking i know but sometimes i try
sunridge i'm sorry yeah i'm jeremy
yeah yeah yeah i try to put
my phone down and go like this
is my movie night yeah it works
for like part of it i watched
trolls world tour and it was fucking
this is larry heard of the problem
that you're watching trolls oh my god
i thought it was the best i
was good i loved it alright i
got my phone halfway through but the
first half
i was like truly like a child
like so we'd have secondary problems maybe
but it was very funny and very
beautiful too who's very funny it looks
like the animation does look animation tantalizing
and there's so much funny physical comedy
with the characters
what if trolls was real did toyota
know i love to be in chose
i was it was really good shows
is easy losers read when you watch
the animation of trolls there's moments where
they have muppet like fur hands when
they're super close up on them yeah
and it looks so cool
the i wish i could be that
close to a troll look man you'd
probably argue it even know they're they're
microscopic was the remark there like germs
kona the toilets comic
whoa alright look we need to take
a break we'll be right back okay
bad we're back and hell yeah let
me tell you what i would like
in my dream home yeah first of
all if i could if i had
the money could have should have would
have i would like my house to
look ah very nautical ah outside and
the
like that steven spielberg restaurant dive in
the century city mall better than that
though like the wes anderson film v
life of quachaun yeah i would like
i would i would definitely love to
like big porthole windows like windows shiplap
of course if it ship i'll lap
it up you um but
like ah ah of nice like are
cool aren't call you know i was
thinking
peeked out on the balcony like eva
peron over here looking really no chow
but like nice dark wood navy white
trim kind of real um cabernet feeling
inside interest in every room yeah yeah
yeah interesting sort of like a beach
house as well yes like taking a
beach house aesthetic but then we made
like it on the beat almost like
wow that dream that's the dream yeah
that will never come
so if here's here's a question if
you had a beach house and a
regular house yeah would you keep the
beach house in that theme and have
the regular house that you stayed during
the week in in more modern ah
type thing or do you want both
houses to feel the same no i
think i would have the beach house
be just like regular house
house because also there were these houses
a regular thing and then your regular
houses like yes i wouldn't be fun
like oh you're in a survey channel
so you owe me at the beach
i love the beach i love the
ocean i love boats you don't want
i haven't seen the entire time we
saw thirteen sorry also my dream
a secret passageway yeah yes i everyone's
wow i'll be watching one of these
renovation shows and you do a secret
passageway and it's like cod dam is
assembly from my friend michael who's a
museum musician and composer bolton um
nesmith um he ah after years and
years and years of meaning to do
it he finally redesigned his home studio
and the door is a fake bookcase
oh five fucking best but i think
it's hard to hand frank oh sure
well that's intentional not like old old
scooby do's and stuff like that you
just think not like i don't think
they were some shit they didn't have
a secret about all of it but
bookcase door am i getting bay didn't
have ah you might be i think
they did have a bookcase in um
and franks was it a book but
they were in the attic but yeah
i went to the house but i
was really just
that
she was out um but i you
see an
really jet-lagged at anne frank so i
was because i only had two days
in amsterdam and i was like i
gotta go there and i got to
fuck a hooker gotta get up smoke
all my hash was just a very
importantly when to do it i wanna
do it right away and i but
i was really tired so i don't
know that i remember exactly but i
kind of follow very steep ladder by
a bookcase but i think it was
hidden
i don't think there's a buy on
the scene imus because all the books
would fall just let me not want
to see ledge this doesn't seem to
be able to alien hiding the latter
i think but let me just look
ah okay oh okay oh guy remember
him i do remember he was on
my television yes
it was a bookcase doors right a
secret door there was a secret oh
well these other word yeah yeah that's
right
so the original bookcase that can see
the entrance to the hiding place anywhere
and very funny excuse me has been
a part of the anne frank house
since it's opening nineteen okay cares however
the condition of the bookcase has visibly
deteriorated today the bookcase has a partial
glass cover to prevent further damage ah
good good i guess that's the way
to do it that's though
way to doe money for nothing and
your chicks for free oh i just
think this is interesting the original bookcase
visitors enter the secret annex through the
narrow opening past the movable bookcase too
many people visiting the anne frank house
has emotional experience they try to imagine
what it must have been like accepted
for lawyers some people don't flashy ride
you fuckers
anyway whatever anyway
okay move on i'm talking about amphora
anyway whatever anne frank house um where
where would you want your secret passageway
to be for an office library or
four i think someone that was to
like a clause that's right there was
this closet there was a shine that
phone look no no i surely know
in the in the closet in the
walk
in closet there was also a secret
passageway that's how we do that took
you to like the kitchen or something
i knew i'm someone who had a
panic room hidden in like a clause
oh that wasn't tony foster no um
but that's it i am scared of
the idea of having a panic room
because then by penny yeah it kind
of makes you think
i might have to go in there
at some point all the time we
have a panic button that cool op
said she was going to tell me
because it's by my bed and i'm
in charge of it but i still
don't know how it doesn't show me
what it is okay everyone's oh my
house i hear this weird loud bell
is that you guys yes pressing a
button just wakes you up yeah bill
nye
was me which about that earthquake how
loud my guy just literally gotten to
sleep in the previous three minutes and
i was in it yeah i was
in sleep and so when it happened
i was like god the fucking dogs
jumping on the bed and then cool
up grabbed me
as if as if we were gonna
die she wanted to be holding me
while it happens yeah and yeah that
was the same scary natural impulse
i was standing flossing in the bathroom
and mike was standing in the catching
the dance yeah i was like ah
we were talking about their mercy if
i was doing it right when he
was saying next to the fridge and
i have a couple of things on
top of the fridge and then he
was like we were standing in talking
casually and then that we you guys
are casual at home when yeah really
likes it's not manners no no you
have a fridge in the bathroom of
course and we're dressed for dinner we
were
standing there like ten fifteen feet apart
and you guys are keeping ten fifteen
we always don't just to be very
clear sure and there the floor was
rumbling with all due to the ground
for typical earthquake stuff but i mean
it felt like so confusing to your
brain i have no one had asked
you to get ready to run crown
i don't work this way i haven't
experienced an earthquake in like five years
i've been like out of town for
a couple of the ones really but
so then the everything above his head
was like shaking and it was like
that realization as you're like looking at
were like oh oh oh wow i
like you guys you're realising what's happening
take almost ending yeah but i always
going to
run to him and then i stopped
because i thought maybe that was dangerous
but i stopped in the doorway which
was an accident but i think that's
good
it's not good
it's just the opposite
ha ya mama wait why is it
not going to be ah that's bad
you're not supposed to use a doorway
now don't do the doorway thing it
keeps changing i also like watching hockey
here's just tiptoe if you're in bed
cover your head with a neck with
pillows and stay in bed that's what
oh the ceiling crumbles or something happened
over the ceiling crumbly than men
in the whittier one um i was
not there for it but but i
had roommates who were living next to
like apartment buildings that like
hi yeah i moved here right oh
northridge earthquake and ninety four and the
city why it was like a month
or two after and ah everything was
still like it yeah it looked like
a movie set it was crazy like
just demolish just moms like big cracks
in buildings and p a is running
everywhere guy
i'm on call coffee cup that shouldn't
have been in framed
ah yeah some people died a lot
of people moved up for that and
a lot of people left town after
that we know they're all back
we're just like in your face janey
was asleep i was in the loony
was this every time he mentioned dad
something yeah i want to sing it
and i've curbed that impulse now it's
every good every time why that's unlike
you i know but i because what
i know it would happen continuously on
the show and now it will
oh um i was in the living
room watching tv and i remember what
you were watching
no i don't as ninety ninety four
is probably oh no oh are you
mean the other o the other night
okay
you're i still thought you're talking about
the nurse i've known jamie since nineteen
ninety four i guess it doesn't make
sense but at the same time it
does it kind of does it doesn't
um and i've experienced there's this has
happened a lot of times where janie
has been a bed and i've been
in the other room still away your
bed in my bed
my valet has just left he's gonna
work on my clothes for the morning
she decided i remember this couple that
i i knew this guy through improv
like when i was still close yeah
frazzled um grizzled looking when i was
like twenty and he or nineteen and
he was like in his late twenties
or thirties i don't know how old
he was but he was he seemed
much older at the time huh yeah
but he was married and his even
he and his wife had two separate
bedrooms oh yeah i mean there and
he was like hey it happy better
it has i mean not i understand
it you know when i'm next in
her room and then i go to
he didn't wait didn't tell me that
thinks i do
for that i wipe yourself off oh
d
i feel like i feel like i
it's i'm not dying to have separate
bedrooms but i feel like i if
we had enough space yeah i mean
i had a refund just like it
is i think the hard thing yeah
i mean yes i do think you
could definitely have nights where you're like
i'm gonna sleep over here especially a
lot because if you have an earlier
call yeah you know if you have
to be if you have to like
get up in the dark or something
like
go in the other room and sleep
i had a girlfriend who snored so
loud that it she became my lot
was ah well it would wake me
up at night
you sleep in a different room um
no it was very tempting though because
it was just like oh my god
this is unbearable sometimes really doing so
like i get how it happens but
these days you can go get a
sleep study and yeah my brother used
to snore like crazy we shared a
room for a while and he would
say hey it was like that crazy
like yale snoring where it's so loud
what is it it's janney i don't
know how it would speak so loud
it's just like the sound of storing
but it's like off the charts yeah
and i would go through this thing
every night where i would i would
like yell to wake him up like
marc marc yeah you go what i'd
say
you're snoring
and he would say again obit and
i would say turn on your side
or something and then
shut up
via via repeat every night ah god
yeah i used to like nudge or
whatever
ah she knew she she knew i
mean oh she knew she had to
know i did tape cool up snoring
recently oh because it's it's not a
common and prove a point it's not
a common thing but i thought it
was so funny how loud it was
for whatever reason it was happening i
was like okay i gotta take the
distance right
it was pretty funny but um but
i'm a really light sleepers so stuff
like i and i i didn't know
what to do about it and then
suddenly i was like investigators like oh
get a sleep mask oh get a
sound machine i mean well i mean
to counter those things now i use
i usually use a
sleep mask that i just got a
sound machine and i love it i
fall asleep to heavy rain every night
and oh my god it's so amazing
i sleep so much deeper even though
i usually sleep pretty well i'm like
knocked out my neighbors can be really
loud so i don't hear them at
all it's kind of amazing you'll learn
you ever fuck with ocean sounds okay
so i've tried ocean south
you and your ocean might drop it
i have one that's called thunder by
the sea oh that oh it's the
ocean and a thunderstorm at the same
time it's pretty cool i'm a thunder
down under where it's just guy stripping
just the sound oil no cell no
music just oily guys taking your squeaking
i got this alarm clock that's called
a hatch
and it's like a little shit just
like from last hemisphere we gotta impressive
numbers every twenty one minutes but anyway
this is why it was late today
because i there's certain things about the
also you get up late to do
thing tumble out of bed you stumble
to the kitchen was i wish i
had woken up at eight but i
then set my mom again for eight
forty
and started be on time and the
all eating go wrong when i woke
up at nine thirty so i did
something wrong with with the alarm because
i it's like three or phone app
i don't fully understand some parts of
it but you miss schedule the hatch
yeah but it's really fun because it
lights up all these different colors you
can pick what color you want it
to be when when it wakes you
up oh and then it has all
these sounds and meditations you can follow
asleep in there sound like um maybe
yeah like and i fall asleep instantly
but bilal bilal baja you know like
this thing which i haven't gotten into
yet but it's like you could set
your light in a sets like a
routine for you so you'll be like
thirty minutes of reading light and the
light will fade
fade and the sound will come out
of your rain oh i like this
that's so down for bed yeah the
one thing i'm finding tricky about it
is i have the habit now of
having my phone in the kitchen at
night so i don't look back yes
yes yes guys i need to set
things on the hatch from my phone
i'm finding that business you just
just just lost you watch the the
other night you're talking about it i
just knew you know what i'd actually
i would watch all lost i would
you really think i loved it but
i think it would be such a
waste of time i think it would
be really it's so long but i
watched all of entourage again
why i loved everyone that's on ya
hey lauren you said earlier something you
haven't seen during covert oh the ocean
i know i know yeah you're going
to say entourage but that's not true
i saw this actually that's been dubai
watched all the seasons and the movie
again and i actually i like entre
y
there's a certain thing about watching andres
watching rich people get to do whatever
they want and then fuck whatever they
want is like kind of ever at
least let's see who i don't but
it's all i can't get into that
sort of um i guess wish fulfillment
or whatever i can't i can't get
like people will say
about succession what they lie love succession
to see rich people getting to be
miserable and it's like yeah but it's
still entourage re opposite like writing i
know there are never consequences one season
that was actually kind of like that
either there there was one season that
was kinda good where vinnie like was
not a popular actor anymore yeah yeah
and he was like a fascinating
season where he was really struggling and
i remember the final episode of that
season you remember this lauren carr thing
they call him go oh by the
way scorsese wants you to be in
his new movie you're back on top
and everyone went yay and then the
rest of the show until it ended
was just them like literally fucking everyone
and being rich they're absolutely episodes that
are amazing and
many words and phrases they use that
do not and clauses and the test
of time but the frying pan into
the fire there was one that was
used
just cool this is like here running
this like a morning say no coupon
or a regular tube
ah anyway alright we gotta take a
break okay
alright we're back and it's of course
time for another feature aka oh of
course it is reacher and this initiative
has been sorted so course this has
been submitted by our producer joe schmidt
scott or do you believe this guy
what he's saying like oh of course
i know of course we do of
course it's time of course it's time
scott um that isn't ballet's ballet of
nap this was submitted by our producer
josh and this is called half-life um
i'm gonna congratulations to josh your feature
has been chosen josh
we're gonna send you a swig of
three mg here ah that includes the
non-stick pan you've got the bumper sticker
the pin the hat the glasses and
the seed kush id which you can
use on the go we've also supplied
you with a water bottle that stays
cold for twenty four hours the umbrella
hat
that you don't need to carry an
umbrella rao when you wear what on
your hand the freedom wedding bands some
of you seem like you're married even
if you're not the threat of i
u d don't want to get pregnant
don't get braided the three away all
three of our heads on a little
team because inside yeah alright i've started
alright haven't started it but i've set
the timer for two
minutes we're going to apollo nida place
the moon the moon we're gonna do
a scene in two minutes and then
when the timer goes off we have
to redo the scene in one minute
then when that timer goes off we
redo it in thirty seconds than fifteen
seconds than seven seconds than three than
one i follow why would we do
one i don't know but
here we go second alright here we
go and we're on the moon and
go i am so glad we finally
landed ah i have to go to
the bathroom so bad you didn't go
the entire flight no i'm too embarrassed
to whip it out in front of
you wait did you think there were
bathrooms up here there isn't one no
you're just
supposed to go in your pants just
go ahead could have gone the whole
time i just flow right out the
two ho i want to cover this
in training oh what's that noise oh
i think it's a moonshine that's what
you call him someone from the moon
isn't it yeah of course moonshine it's
a moonshine yeah moonshine is that oh
no it's getting closer oh god
god that's disgusting it looks what do
you want from us bad as it
is it looks like steven mnuchin
give it some food here but don't
give it some food i know my
food i'll do it i'll do it
here moonshine do you want some ice
cream it's free try stand out another
five hours he lie he'll say mellon
shan he like and we know it's
a he because we see it's giant
penis well we don't know if that's
what that is yeah that's true it
could be an arm
that's true and you can have two
penises on the side of his body
uses it there let's try to shake
his hand if it is an arm
bike oh god
shot some purple goo how we doing
on time forty seconds oh no unbelievable
how long two minutes can be
talking about the word oh what a
terrible dream wait oh oh but have
paul wake up anyway were you were
snoring and we filmed the entire thing
oh i didn't think i would store
in the newer talking in your sleep
what did i say you were saying
let me shake that guy's hand way
did at one point that i say
bio lab map i think you did
yeah
i mean what does it mean i
had a beautiful dream a dream about
a moon chen lydia ah will tell
us about it for ten seconds well
we got to the moon ah a
little faster we were all talking about
this ah go to okay your dreams
boring
unfortunately you're out alright your dream is
boring fortunately you're ours now we have
to do the same scenic way what
a game show right you're talking about
your dreams yeah ms jane lynch says
a panel of judges your dream is
boring goodbye i'm sorry your dream is
boring goodbye okay one minute one minute
here we go ready and go wow
i'm so glad we made it oh
god i have to pee so bad
you should appeal like we did which
was all the way up here wait
i didn't i'm too embarrassed i didn't
want to do that in front of
you think there'd be a bathroom up
here yeah there isn't no where have
you guys been going in our pants
i didn't know why didn't they cover
that in training
they did oh sound by saying oh
wow it's i think it's moonshine what's
a moonshine it's someone from the moon
like on mars we call it martian
oh my gosh it is a moonshine
it's coming over here what's it want
my inside what is it saying my
name baby is hungry give it some
food recipe i'll just give him a
little bit of ice
cream
oh yeah and we do he loves
it he loves it hey ma e
ca and we do know it to
him because of his giant penis could
be something else and that's his arm
let me just try to shake his
hand and c o o s p
k u
paul wake up like yeah
oh hey the dream again what is
it this zandra i had last night
you said belushi in your sleep okay
alright alright alright you can't do just
two all rights alright alright alright
alright now we're going to thirty seconds
on the clock
thirty seconds here we go and go
we made it we're on the moon
oh god i gotta pee so bad
she got the whole time yeah we
pissed i felt weird doing in front
of you hey what's that noise ballet
nib oh my god i think it's
mentioned ballet now chair of the denizen
from the moon get some ice cream
give some ice cream free shit ice
cream he likes it
yeah of course we go to him
because of his giant penis oh what
if it's an arm well yeah oh
yeah oh yeah yeah it wasn't we
are on the moon there was you're
talking in your sleep using balloons yeah
i know it's all moonshine and then
okay so here's the drink
yes nice alright fifteen seconds
that's right yeah
alright ready and go oh we're fairly
here oh god i gotta pee so
bad we pissed her pain oh no
oh look it's a moonshine ice cream
hey loves yeah oh and of course
we know it's aim because of it's
giant penis oh oh i have the
dream like yeah you're sleepy said by
lujan yeah
alright seven seconds seven seven here we
go ready
oh sorry i know i can't just
not you okay
i ready go or anywhere on the
moon oh i gotta be so bad
with emotion management ice cream hey may
we know table
we were on the move
alright three seconds ready and go nah
deal
hello
again
alright and one second
here we go and go
and ah oh that was fun now
was a good teacher thanks jaw shot
feature goes out to josh that one
goes out to josh in the arms
of a shimizu we still have time
don't do that one again or do
you want to do a different reacher
i want to do that one again
do it again right
right we can't waste three years doing
two on one show these are these
are precious these are praised are precious
resources she's reaches i now know all
of our ace
guys you miss me that was me
going who was it
good thank you um hello three years
we are okay y'all know that i've
been to hobbiton in new zealand yeah
who i'm going to stay at an
air bnb next weekend that looks like
a hobbit hole it's a day i
want to see it yeah that sounds
cool wow alright lauren we need a
place um
this place is the grocery store the
grocery store two minutes on the clock
and go excuse me can you tell
me where i could find canned beets
yeah it's in the canned food aisle
sorry i thought i was gonna help
him i think he was talking to
me oh i don't mind either when
they look into my first day on
the job and i just um i
should you should watch how i do
it because
cause you're going to learn how to
interact with customers that what they mean
by shout i just don't know where
the beats are okay so um ma'am
the beats are as a man don't
miss gender him i o manly it's
oh i'm sorry when you said you
were a ma'am before i thought you
said i'm a man i said i'm
a ma'am oh that's such a
weird way to say what i saw
i'm owning it i man did gender
you correctly thank you um thank you
though i will tell you the beats
ma'am this is a robbery oh no
oh my god my first day on
the job this is so exciting geely
all the beats okay i have to
shout i still do want me to
say you have to shadow her and
see how she treats the case so
so what do we do why we
never pay
a beaten my life and i don't
intend to start i mean are we
supposed to give them just to beat
tom here what do we got into
my back so we're we're all gonna
walk to shore so what how are
we supposed to do a top accommodation
rabbit cart tell them the combination did
you say mushy i'm talking to each
other it's making me sorry but i'm
training tammy and i just want beats
timmy
you know i know your name timothy
oh yes want beat i'll forget it
she just want beats i just want
beats just won't beat i don't want
beach and now we pan out and
this is a music video and we
are seeing is being shot there is
a grocery store and there is a
robbery and this is all part of
the play that one life i use
it from a
you don't robert to the star a
music video i just want beats i
just want beats ah it's ca i
really wish he wouldn't improv okay i
want people to know i want people
to know my story and brought his
hot these days yeah i know but
we're just wasting film you know what's
even out making fun of improv
look i mean we heard you we
yeah it's supposed to have lines
oh it's like ten minutes
it is the two minute one is
a big ask
alright ready one minute
you guys ready here we go
go could you tell me where the
beats are oh sure the beats are
over in aisle i mean well you
just watch me do it i'm sorry
i'm just shouting yeah okay go ahead
okay ma'am the beats are actually ma'am
oh yes that is what i said
in fact no don't miss gender him
he is a man i said man
i'm sorry i missed her daddy now
okay so i'm all i'm voting for
you
want i will let you know where
the beats are if we just take
a moment and you're pulling a gun
on me yeah there's a robbery and
what do we do we just lemme
see what how do we know these
ha
that beats aisle i'll four oh i
see the same for i never paid
for a beat before we pull out
and we are on a film set
and suddenly it's a music video and
they're doing a cool song about the
rob about how they just want to
watch those beats i want those bees
alright kai yeah right yeah oh excuse
me i really wish you wouldn't imply
that he would do it yeah
yeah i'm sorry everything looks now i
just want beats everything was an improv
i'm please love you bro dean ambrose
hot right now
all right let's go down to thirty
seconds on the claw back and start
yes where are the beads oh they're
over now watch me do i'm sorry
i'm so sorry beats her oyster here
in aisle four i just feel don't
have to be okay we're just going
to get the beats and say oh
my god
that's right it's a robbery we do
in this situation tomatoes beets just go
to idle for she's pushing the guys
way back yeah no chance it's ma'am
it's ma'am i say ma'am we want
to eat cio and it's a whole
amazing side kind of like okada
i just could tell you about to
talk
remember right now in progress huh
alright fifteen seconds
i feel like we're crazy alright yeah
alright here we go and start i
want this piece okay so alright remi
shit okay go ahead i wrote this
nice oh my god da da robert
okay okay okay should we post videos
please look at me alright guy oh
god she would not improv
alright seven seconds ready and go beats
i write this way
a yeah those beat here i yeah
high life really is hot right now
wish you would never have i wish
we hadn't gotten through all those beats
earlier because we saw two seconds in
fact beats what oh that was fifteen
i did reset it ah shit we
had it wow it now three now
three here we
go and go pleats no robbery
yeah alright one second ready oh shit
alright and one second go yeah huh
stony brook
wonderful wonderful
we did it we did it feel
to it so fun we did it
to it we did it you yeah
yeah that was an incredible most normal
i felt in many money to ah
yes sorry do do we tell people
who were yeah we told me we're
outside and we're outside wow this episode
be our outside so if you've ever
heard
erd kind of a buzzing noise it's
a b there's a beautiful dragon fly
here so she wasn't laughing it's water
or lauren lapping if you hear the
sound of magma it's probably a volcano
just as a listener that we're not
going to be breaking any covert protocol
we just thought it would suck a
repartee
ration fun to actually be in the
same place with each other yes it
was this great was now next week
next time by next week by next
next week next time ah huh
we will get all of the eminem
variations this is a sword fled north
american eminem very we're not going to
get like green tea and shit like
that shooting also if we make a
list i'm not gonna get anything so
what do you mean i gotta set
all this shit up but you guys
get one at the eminence but will
send it here will send my order
them online that's
what i was thinking okay same here
you'll find at the store exact exactly
because there's a new eminem i just
had laver you just had it i
got it good i can't wait to
try it what is the five brownie
fudge and it was really good but
i was made um corner okay but
i still don't put at the top
oh right yeah we did this on
the show
before no but now we read damn
an inflamed what now we're going to
do it we don't who knows remember
but now we're gonna do it i
like i don't care i don't get
okay now we're gonna do it with
loss trying yes labour live yeah we're
gonna write it down lie and we're
gonna write your mind some rankings my
change and we have to write down
and i
think we should have um josh pull
up what we said last time and
write it down so we can compare
but not look at it beforehand if
anyone knows what episode that was tell
josh yeah don't tell us just tell
josh said he doesn't have to waste
his life or right to write to
our anymore than he already has joined
twitter which is at three am usa
also subscribe to this show it's coming
out
every week for free yeah and ah
like it tell people to subscribe to
it i don't know what else yeah
what else do you do it leave
it leave a five-star review and say
something fun yeah yeah maybe we'll read
lacking with catchphrases that no one can
understand yeah so we want to make
it actually really hard to understand also
send us your videos of you trying
to do jamaican accents
shamari miami know little little news channel
more than you turn to do to
make an eccentric trying to do an
impression of what of what she's doing
yeah we don't actually yes please don't
want to see anyone when anyone trying
to do it i'm trying to do
a real gym i want to let
your adrian brodie if you're adrian brody
please bring back your roster man character
like i don't know my less know
we've talked about
we won't know maybe on the best
of the best yes we've talked about
yeah yeah yeah nice cliffhanger for next
we gotta go we gotta go we
gotta go oh alright i mean glee
we wretched out a little bit we
love you guys thank you for listening
we're at the end but it's the
wind it's like when you land a
plane it doesn't just drop out of
the sky onto the runaway over but
this is like
and then suddenly like the doors opening
you tumble out no you you you
you coast down that runway a little
bit it's it's to a stop but
this is like we're we're we're letting
the the rubber come off the wheels
of the plane yeah that's the show
maybe you want yeah i mean the
wheel of the plane robbers are off
sweetie rubbers
vapor throw runners off when you listen
to threesome roz only raw talk rawls
agu rod talk oscar uncle that should
be in batman porn parody it
oh my god my raw dog oh
cool my friend joe like a porn
drama my friend erecting a porn in
december oh whoa can i be at
it yeah hell yeah he's looking for
background can you play a lamp
it's a lamp lamp out of our
live shows yes yeah that's right you
know lamppost lamppost that's right all right
um come check us out on our
tour oh yeah we're not doing gotta
have it end
ankles are fucking treat apart by mosquitoes
will check back next time about paul's
mosquito problems we'll see next time love
ya love you bye
uh