three
yeah
ah god help me
help me god save me from three
god blesses me
tv code plus the tv
god please bless the devi ever think
to say it but there's so many
people in the tv and you use
it all the time yeah his god's
blessing now you guys are so right
i never really thought about that when
you turn the tv off it's cold
for the people in it yeah they're
going to hopefully our players sleep yeah
they're awake there's keep it they're awake
they're serious deep but they're awake
they're back but that's gonna yeah
yeah right
don't today i do i do know
what it all comes down to say
i haven't got it all figured out
yell she is
um that caleb ah heron post that
you shared yes was so funny now
here's i didn't see breakfast never see
it no you will see it oh
shit you're gonna sit right down and
watch it right now all right what
you
implementation of his last name no oh
okay because i was like actually like
he was on podcast i asked him
to think i'm saying it right okay
to tick tick tick
lord easy glue pick a little talk
a little too cheap to gloss along
um so i saw that i retreated
what are we even talking about you
responded to the retweet hahaha yeah because
you enjoyed it laughter
then you d him to to me
oh i definitely mean to do that
i meant to post it on my
story i which i did do you
slid into his d think i did
or maybe just send it to you
i puzzled over it so i was
like why is this what yeah i
i didn't like but i know but
he was weird i also sent mike
a dm of something and he was
like i was like oh did you
see that saying i send you then
he was like oh yeah the earrings
reverend i was like what
yeah you deem this to me
i didn't mean to do that at
all i meant to send it to
my family probably oh so you think
i'm part of your family you speak
spanish just thinking of you as family
h no but i think i was
going going who's p h i get
it okay but i was probably still
thinking of your name as i was
typing what i thought was learning but
i did that
to mike and i sent him something
and i was like what what am
i doing on this phone like i'm
not even paying that shot like random
people getting random messages but that was
a perfect standups bit i thought so
funny it's so funny he's talking about
being a teacher and and how he
likes the bad kids in this kid
like makes fun of them and it
just it it plays out very wonderfully
this great wonderful quiet kid wouldn't try
to cooker we
e and no please don't hobby hello
i kind of enjoy it i mean
i could try from memory a try
okay let's see what you got with
apple
oh boo
something like that i think i think
i got i gotta you know i
got an email from a producer that
i oh my god day he brags
all the time that i haven't worked
with in fifteen years or so and
it was it was it was inexplicable
and i read it several times and
i realised oh he didn't mean to
write to me
um but it was something like hey
how do i he had he he
was like hey how do i get
this taken off or something it was
like as brief as that and i
was like what is this and so
i wrote back i said like a
picture of a mole
yeah i just wrote back something to
the extent of like my man i
don't even know what you're talking about
but it's so grading your body yeah
and he was like oh sorry i
meant this descend this to i t
at my company and then i was
and i was like hey he goes
but how are you what do you
have to i was like i'm looking
for a job in i t if
you hear about anything
opening up to someone who can't do
something and that producer was robert ah
fuck but the the kicker to the
story has been told there's a kicker
he wrote to me then accidentally five
more times that day oh that's crazy
day that's jay he needs to focus
and and and each time you're one
to talk
the first up the first couple times
first couple i wrote back like hey
it's still me and he's like what
is happening and then the successive times
he was like why am i doing
this seems like follow it up immediately
wow it's absolutely bonkers
but noodles yeah yeah good to hear
from i was gonna say how did
your time do you think people have
used that as a way to like
ah inadvertently slide into the dms somebody
like send them something oh yeah you
may exit yeah scammers is what they
do and anyone about people who are
trying to date somebody it's like oh
i can talk to that girl which
i say i'm like oops i'm innocent
oh shit yeah how have you been
i see yeah oh that's a good
one hello joanne i heard about location
dear joanne if someone takes to do
that but as your friend and you're
like oh you listen to and oh
so are you okay ah i hate
bad joanna show she turns the tables
i um i've done the accidentally emailing
someone that when you mean to forward
the email to someone else and comment
on what the person said i've only
done that once and it was to
a producer i was working with on
a movie that we were trying to
get made and um they sent me
this the tiniest criticism
and i thought i forwarded it and
said well i don't know that i
agree with this i instead responded to
it oh no and it was it
was like the the least dramatic version
of because you're able to go oh
well it's i'm kidding because it was
a very minor note that you gave
yeah well no she she knew that
it was meant to go to someone
else and she's like hey you sent
this to me accidentally but nice to
know
you don't agree with it and it
was like oh well i don't really
but oh yeah that's right it's so
awkward it's so embarrassed i mean snafu
are just so embarrassing and when you're
like you want to text a friend
about somebody else i'm like i will
focus on the name i'm sending it
oh yeah and i'm like oh read
it out loud and then i'll read
the last messages we send us like
this is who i'm talking
two because that's the word i did
that once and it was i i
i got out of it it was
not too damning it was it was
open to interpretation yeah right and i
was so i was able to wriggle
out of it but it was like
ever since then scary i have been
so so so so careful it's the
fear of
god into your heart the f o
g the fog that's what john carpenter
made a movie about fog fear of
god fog yeah oh yeah doctor foggy
oh and doctor foggy oh doctor foggy
oh we love you dr fowler your
doctor vagy
apache was a dog yeah it would
be doctor fouled doggy like right no
we all agree doctor bow doggy come
on we all agree to be doctor
bow wow chee doctor bow wow lil
bow wow ha
what about scarecrows dog doctor dog food
doctor dog food would be me dead
plants guess
will say doctor doghouse okay what are
you you tell me to acted dog
shipper that's so i'm dr dog food
dr deutsch dr doghouse and her doctor
jacques shit bag yes i don't make
a lot of sense yes and we're
all friends because we all met in
med school donkey med school no we
don't know each other in that world
we don't
oh no i don't want to live
in that world where talk about we
never talk about work we ever talk
about but i went to johns hopkins
is
that's where you went to school yeah
in the dog world oh are you
bragging about what you didn't the dog
okay brag about what i do oh
i really hate when people talk about
what college they went to a lot
when they're an adult like who cares
yeah it has no bearing as as
a college dropout i could not care
less yeah well i mean look this
is because of our industry as well
like a lot of probably say it
probably affects
other industries of like oh you went
to oh oh right it means nothing
to us yeah to us things definitely
a job where it matters where you
went to school but i still think
bragging in sort of because those people
who are bragging no one's just saying
it about some random school they went
to it's always like ah ivy league
school and they're like saying it over
and over again while the people the
yeah i know the whole harvard thing
of like oh i went to a
a college near what is it was
they say i went to bridge college
near cambridge or something like that yeah
right the whole bragging yeah and that
way without brian went to school near
cheers yeah
i we're just going through the bull
and finch pub yeah it happens with
a lot of schools and it's really
i mean harvard's a big one though
that you hear a lot i went
to school near the marathon bombing
not to pry right on top of
it
i never understood people's connection to school
after school is done yeah until um
i guess it really depends on the
this is an experience i can understand
jamie went to a very small school
high school it was
there's an all girls school and next
week yeah and it was so sexy
i think that would have been so
great yeah and it was a small
class so she's very she feels very
connected to them still even though they
don't they don't like talk all the
time or whatever you know it can
be hard to talk all the time
no we try
it on this show we turned on
the show we can reach out an
hour
yeah i i understand that it's like
you've had this it's yeah there's a
totally different thing what are your names
and stuff like that when i'm what
i'm talking about people like basically name
dropping their own hispano i know that
yeah yeah that's absurd to do but
for an adult to be doing that
yeah that's a pathetic yeah although i
realised i talk about the action school
i went to which all collie for
store
well yeah for stories you know walking
out people saying saying oh by the
way you may want to hire me
as i went to i'm a graduate
of artsy artsy you literally thirty years
ago i'm realising you can you believe
that this is all right rose yeah
sorry anniversary of you doing the of
me graduating you graduated if they didn't
graduated vaccine school not college does that
make sense know that guy again we
would get college credit for everything but
i never graduated i never got a
degree yeah sorry you think you're gonna
go to dubai
i have looked up college courses here
in town and you have talked about
this and and what's stopping you you
interest yeah why are you looking up
the courses to see if there's like
a course that i would like if
there was something that jumped out at
me i would maybe go like oh
i might do that what is it
like once a week i have to
go to these things i have no
fucking i think
generally yeah yeah that sounds fine like
what does line what day every you
know you kind of pick a day
based on what works for you can
i say the idea that doesn't work
the idea doesn't work for me well
then i need structure for some reason
i've gotten into i've gotten to continue
like a class that works your schedule
right move boy mccoy
i've gotten to a place in my
life where trying to schedule something on
a weekly basis seems impossible i would
pretty much agree with you on that
like a thing that i want to
do well as opposed to like an
obligation like i'm i have a couple
of writing projects and i meet with
each of those people to write once
a week and it's like that is
hard to maintain
like it's like it takes a lot
of time energy yeah it isn't it's
good but it's like you have to
really build it into what if it's
at night well i'm doing that tonight
even actually writing at night tonight because
i was like maybe this will ride
at night yeah i'm gonna do it
after he goes to bed that's my
ideas were gonna meet on sit some
possible and
right at seven thirty one of whatever
you write she ends up dreaming about
wow that would be so amazing i
hope not why because it's vulgar oh
you don't want a vulgar child
yeah god hates vulgar truly
one of the one of the things
that god hates them oh okay god
hates he's like number one with a
bullet appeals above himself even though he
used to be best friends they used
to be but it's so if that
happens how it goes yeah that's how
it goes sometimes that's how it goes
something none of our business also feels
about our business devil he's too good
at what he does so it's like
burns it's chaps gods um how
how bad does god feel that the
devil contempt people into doing things i
know and and it works and it
works because that's the thing is like
god's like hey none of you have
to sin yeah but then the devil
comes along and is so good attempting
he's like yeah because no one wants
to be gay right is the devil
just yeah it's too good yeah devil
just temps piece
what if you were gay and so
tempting we feel in my life i
think i've talked more about god and
the devil with youtube that when i
know and i hope so well it's
i hope so i think doing that
episode good christian fun i unpacked a
lot of trauma during a really crappy
trauma trauma trauma
ah really did it come out on
air or did you realize it later
i think afterwards i was like oh
wow that's stuff i haven't thought about
in a while and it's really fucked
me up for years yeah yeah yeah
did i tell you i'm not sure
if i've told this story on air
before please tell it but the story
of when i appeared on an episode
of god the dev
bill and bob remember that march i
remember that kurt who was in it
again robert downey junior that's right yeah
pre iron man three iron man was
a nineties before his big resurgence yeah
yeah maybe early to early aughts oh
wow that wreath he was still kind
of in trouble i'll be looking at
the time yes title but
um i think it was alan cumming
robert downey junior and i forget who
else but ah i was i was
hired to be a guest actor on
the show the ideas three um did
you watch i did not audition this
translations offer never gotten anything from a
voice over audition in my life mailer
it's a really were any audition ah
feels like a distrust to me the
only thing i've ever gotten from like
oh remember minimum on all i did
was look at my butt ooh la
la sex um you know percent t-shirt
just for sale i don't even know
if they're moving at all yeah we
haven't checked and we haven't we've only
boasted about it one
since we were trying to even like
to know not art it's for just
wait till december though that's what the
oil yeah christmas thompson comedy bay major
ooh la la oh yeah if you're
looking for christmas time when we released
the best of you're looking for last-minute
gift that you can't get on time
they definitely order one of the shots
you should order it now so you
should are now in time for
christmas yeah that's where we get there
really work said i will bring down
the gym nature and it looks like
almost almost like it's like oh my
god you know what almost like what
is that cartoon
what you're doing looks like it looks
almost all rosy looks almost like bitmoji
is that i was gonna say it
looks like and ah what is the
name of the show and i think
kevin's able to help me and it
was like a family where they were
like always in the jungle and stuff
jungle family was on um it was
like the wild jungle the tart
tarzan jungle tarzan nickelodeon nickelodeon show my
niccolo mucha michael berries the wild thorn
marvelous marv thornberry the the luxurious people
the wild since it was restaurant robinson
thorn berries is i want to see
a very similar drawing style turnberry ma'am
your worries it's the same
oh guys yeah i'll find out so
i get hired to do this i
am one of three um ah people
that escape from a insane asylum or
whatever um and so we're all crazy
characters we have our individual personalities okay
and so at the table read um
you know we do it and
it's real funny tie edition for this
i did audition for this wow you're
a liar because at the table read
one of the other actors who is
in my little trip ditch
he had the line right before he
had his first line right before my
first line and he did the same
voice that you and i additional why
but like the same kind of character
that i was doing and then so
then immediately i'm like i gotta make
some yeah and we go right from
the tape
able read to the record wow
and that's stress nobody nobody mentioned no
body masia dead nobody yo that's someone
who worked in the shop
i had a friend who worked on
the show who never said anything about
it and i'm like you guys know
what's you know what's going on here
yeah this is because the audition i
think was i feel like it was
an in-person audition because this is before
you zarco sen shit in like even
before but even before covert you could
record stuff at home and send it
now when i sort of prefer the
in person of course then it could
delay
wrecked you but those days are over
apparently but you know i couldn't believe
that nobody was saying instead they're giving
me all this direction like yeah like
oh like i'm fucking it up and
i'm like but this is how this
characters written like i'm definitely doing it
i'm doing what it was like there
was a logic to the voice that
i was doing someone stole like yeah
yeah yeah yeah and he didn't know
you know what i mean like we
weren't there together they ever say do
you like no just do it like
the way you did in the audition
and then you sound just the same
way that he did or no no
or you just nobody's your voice and
no one said i just kept trying
to change it up i i yeah
it was really also there was the
third actor i will not say his
name but i'll tell you
affair oh boy this is juicy was
andy someone good was a comedian an
older comedians been around for awhile this
guy was so distracting during because we
were all in the same room this
very rarely happens too we're all in
the same room recording at the same
time right and this guy like whenever
he wasn't talking he'll kind of notebook
he was drawing it like show me
stuff or
whatever it's like we're we're we're working
yeah yeah do we but he never
stopped talking when he was allowed to
talk yeah like in-between you know tapes
or whatever he would just be talking
talking talking and then we would roll
and he would like be showing me
notes and shit like kind of like
when you can't do this like school
so how did you
so you didn't get fired ah they
they replaced me they did they let
me record today and then they they
got somebody else to do and no
one ever said you won't ever set
a fucking if you watch it and
see oh they did the voice that
i did never seen it never say
wow and then why did this come
up in your mind just because we
said we were talking about god god
in the devil got it and up
bob was the only one not mentioned
and i was like i gotta get
him in there i got a story
about this guy why does it have
to waste are we going to start
asking that why did you think oh
no the reason i asked is because
i i i've been listening to the
whole story through the prism of he
wants to talk about something that fucked
him up the way because it came
off of me saying religion had fucked
me up and so i was
like okay what is fucked paul up
and said it was no just you
heard the worst experience of my life
and i changed my helpers yeah that
sounds really bad
wow so you're listening to a story
like how does this relate to me
well no but to like usually when
no oh did i tell you this
story but you forget about the interruptions
that happen ah pardon the interruption
a
why are we fighting part in the
that's my question every episode
so if someone says part of the
interruption and then went
be funny my friend used to say
my friend used to fart and say
pardon my dust i thought that was
i'm sure i found this but my
friend called it's blowing dust off a
turd and i thought that was like
a funny show
well it's so good oh stuff it
well
alright we'll be right ryan staying system
and we're back ah and more new
i'm here it's here just be present
i am present lauren fisher hasn't lauren
was googling she loves it ooh i
love a goo she loves to go
she's like she's so visited you're gonna
color whatsoever called gugu guglielmi guglielmi
gallon what if a pop singer came
out and said their name was lady
gugu oh my now we fucking live
i think that's the way to be
i would think love them when should
do that and they should be really
good yeah i'm lady gugu yeah and
yeah it's no it's not a parody
or anything it's just set up my
damn thing i think she's fine i'm
i'm not mary jane lady gugu and
like she got really famous but
he's like well i'm gonna change my
name yeah what if it was gugu
in botha or what's her name i'm
googling as a favorite merkerson now from
all over google in basra yeah is
that her name i don't know who
you're talking about she's a great actress
who you may know from cloverfield the
third one oh a bunch of girls
yeah that's not what you're
count on me to know her from
her name is gugu gugu yeah it's
a great name yeah it would be
very cool she's got oh you may
know her from the morning show where
her character committed sou o o their
school guide goofy side oh man
that was a dark movie where goofy
kills fellow big guy
oh i just can't take it on
board i don't think it was canon
though like it was like they did
that no no it was it was
definitely an alternate universe aberration
oh loren loren loren la got i've
got waiting for your birthday coming i'm
going out of town this episode will
probably have already aired at that point
i believe don't send me birthday wishes
where are you going
in ah hello know oh can i
come they never asked ah
i'm going ah on a little trip
up north a bit nice it's a
couple of friendlies let me grab all
mutuals you're going to friendly's yes oh
get a ribble um and this civil
yes they they bullied us into going
on this trip
for your birthday and while it's not
in celebration of my birthday it was
like the easy worse there were two
windows hey you pick one of these
windows and you're going on this trip
with us and is it like a
fourth of july trip no it was
just a let's get out of town
trip so you'll be back for the
fourth or maybe for their snap in
the nah actually ah paul and i
are going to something
on the fourth oh what are you
together oh my christ that's right oh
she don't make any other plans i
can't tell you because i don't remember
what it is we're doing okay but
i know that we're doing it so
i bought mine during the whole thing
we're going to see i think it's
gugu was made i know he doesn't
owe impression on him
to steve martin and martin short oh
yes
very empty i'm very excited again yes
on july fourth with fireworks gray i
was saying after watching their special on
netflix that you and i should figure
out a thing yes do that would
be fun that we never did it
well we did do kind of something
at ah that that oregon festival
two or no ah washington yeah the
gorge in washington yes yeah sasquatch sasquatch
the sasquatch yeah and we did it
but it was more of it it
would have been more of a theater
experience i think it would play better
in a theater rather than a tent
with a bunch of like horrible two
in the afternoon when the option hundred
and two degrees out
the last day of the festival when
people are in a tent trying to
get out of the sun yeah that
was my slot as well and it's
their super high and they can't focus
on anything yeah yeah um but it
was fun but where we each did
separate things and we did things together
gather yes yeah the two of us
i was fun wow so our club
and janie ogres are just a voicemail
it cool up and jannie are going
we're gonna not pay attention to him
yeah no we're gonna say well after
everything that steve martin martin short say
we're gonna turn to our wives say
you probably don't get that it's kind
of a guy thing this is real
guy comedy
i'll explain later if i feel
i saw martin short more than sure
martin short i saw i saw important
shots morton morton shark yeah it's charter
and staff should be telling them the
show i saw martin short up in
vancouver the vancouver festival when you're the
last year ever film festival um the
year we all
got stiffed that was a mess that
thing yeah and ah i still pay
anyone know well martin shorten might have
gotten paid and that's why if anyone
did he did yeah yeah um i
felt so bad for him because he
it was great loved it and he
finished his show and as he's taking
his bow yes the organizer of the
festival rushed on stage because he wanted
to present him with this gift or
whatever and the applause immediately emergencies happening
or something yeah but but everyone's like
he yeah oh something else is
happening and so he got he didn't
get his big applause
oh and it looks like a sad
piece of shit art thing yeah it
was like paintings a local artist had
made for and he was very gracious
and he was very much like oh
thank you so much how nice but
you could tell it was like dude
you i'm taking my bow like hey
wait some reason we do here is
die down then handed off yeah as
the cheers are happening and you walk
off stage before throw that in
the trash and never let him see
it yeah see him off stage yeah
d go fuck yourself d never let
them even paint gory d again e
don't pick up the phone the phone
rings don't pick up the phone
but is that whatever new rules yeah
don't remember it wasn't new rules new
rules to make no camping new rules
new because that's it is that's bill
maher's thing no one knows that
can you imagine a world where people
are like you see bill maher new
rules less known or to go like
hey what you can't name your son
exactly i mean i don't know that
i would it's like when maroon five
came out with like the red pill
blues or whatever their album was and
everyone was like hey do you know
what being red-billed means and they didn't
know and it was way too late
in the like yeah albums were all
on the way to the presses and
stuff there like we did not
no and we can't change it
i seen the matrix but i've picked
up a little bit on what thing
they they were basing it on the
matrix there were like we just liked
the matrix were the other idiots yeah
yeah exactly oh they don't want other
meaning of red pills yes yes you
know the look it up and get
red pill yourself well i don't think
it's good you should see the
h the first matrix is really first
one is great someone did you don't
need to see well ah the second
one you can watch just for fun
action sequences and then turn it off
having seen i think the freeway things
oh okay yes so long i looked
it up i know but just then
just watched all the same only to
read it for the people who don't
know the freeway thing so i really
yeah in the minority but only
just watched make that movie yeah that
should have been a movie and it
should be called freeway matrix two it's
twenty minutes long two freeway
hey how are people getting into ari
guys the matrix it's just called freeway
the latest matrix movie included like canon
from the video game the matrix like
they everything that they did matrix related
was considered canon for that universe and
so it was like i had no
fucking idea what was going on because
i didn't see the
third one yeah i liked the idea
of it and i liked the first
one was the idea of it that
the mate here's what i would have
done with it yeah okay so the
the basically keanu because it starts with
keanu reeves like in an advertising job
or something like that yes and he
said he know he's got you know
he's the guy who made the mayor
six video game or whatever yeah and
i like the idea the idea of
basically the matrix has recaptured him and
convinced him that the matrix experience was
all just like something he thought of
as a video game and then he
has to fight his way out of
it but here's the tough time i
have with that is that sort of
that's all off
scream yeah right know that i prefer
the whole movie be off screen
so then it's just like a minute-long
so be saying like here's a crazy
thing that you have it yeah and
they describe it and then credits
you like that you'd like minute-long movies
love a minute long movie as long
as it just gets right to the
point and then i would take two
hours of credits and i'll read all
of them yes i love let's lift
you holly let's take em l m
back instead of multilevel marketing yankees minute
long movie you're right yes and let's
take m l k back
minute long okay what do we take
you back from
oh that was the other thing think
are you saying it's bad i was
the other music related thing that came
out when justin timberlake put out a
song called take back the night and
everyone lie
everyone's like hey you know that's actually
not something you should probably be singing
like a sexy love song about and
he was like oh i didn't know
a dumb dough i didn't know that
that that was a thing i'm like
and you will never and no one
called him up and no one would
ever call their song take back the
night like no one has ever thought
of those those words
us together like he's like well what
didn't like the people who worked in
the sandwiches probably fifth yeah she's twenty
people that's the whole thing about red
pill blues someone in the chain of
command no fucked up and so wild
to think how many people are involved
in a project like that and not
one of them has either heard or
said the current or yeah or the
curves like she sees
yeah but i feel like i'm missing
something here and let me just ok
i feel like to red pill i
feel like i get everything cause someone
to have their perspective dramatically transformed especially
by introducing them to a new and
typically disturbing understanding of the true nature
of particular situation that's yes they are
talking about conspiracy theories and claim they
have been red-billed orange
in the nineteen nineties with reference to
a scene in the film the matrix
in which the protagonist is offered the
choice between taking a blue pill in
your stories ordinary what you're not getting
is the specific type of person who
says they've been red pill yes it's
not nobody internet users to fairly describe
their own socio-political few points got it
but the best
first is that i think the earliest
origins of it being used in that
way can be traced to a guy
a guy who was saying he he
was red pills and into understanding that
women control actually are control of everything
and um he realised it because his
something about his mother making him take
diarrhea right
this is so funny to say like
that's how i really like women are
actually in charge of everything and without
turning i would know about as a
woman or what i was that you
didn't mean like how does that yeah
but it's like something like that like
a conspiracy theory like that would you
how would you know about that like
i guess like his when you believe
you believe something so insane yeah do
you think that
all women are walking around secretly knowing
that we're in charge right exactly yeah
but i think selling you right yes
exactly there you wanna admit it is
that you wanna admit it that you
actually hold all the cards yeah i
love that idea yeah yeah but it
all really comes down to it's like
i'm mad at my mommy and also
women can deny sex so that means
that they
they are in control of everything yeah
yeah yeah that's it yeah that's everything
that's everything yeah yeah yeah yeah they
run the world girls men can deny
sex too
yeah but only to other men
we can't not into women no oh
oh scott get real okay you're right
it's too good ooh la la la
sucks those shirts are available now a
pathway call bob swag hi i'm bob
slag won't try some t-shirts from me
the god the devil and bob swag
ah oh no
i got replaced with a t-shirt
do you what conspiracy theories do you
believe ah a bunch of em so
i guess we'll just get ah
ah but it is true i think
i really um get on board with
most conspirator you'll hear about them kind
of late i feel like i'm like
oh i had a friend who is
really trying to tell me about the
nine eleven being controlled them yeah i've
heard that there that's where those conspiracies
there are certain conspiracies that i don't
believe but i
can say yeah i get i get
why people now wants to believe it
easy to me yeah i don't know
like most of them are like so
so many people would have to be
involved and no one can ever keep
a secret exactly yeah yeah yeah that's
the thing that always trips me up
is like no there's no way that
anybody we would something something
that colossal yeah could never be involving
that so many people yeah it's like
it's like people can't even meet at
the white house you know without someone
leaking into the brass you know name
like the first time anyone ever got
a group together and saying like should
we take down yeah mineral trade center
minute bow into the white house nobody
knew about
ah my favorite thing is the moon
landing that the moon landing was faked
yeah that's a bizarre one yeah because
i mean at this point i guess
anyone involved is dead right no well
no but but please call judy does
he still thought he was recently live
he was on dancing with the stars
was any way wow did he
do oh leoni
did he win
yeah he was alive you did the
moonwalk everything huh
good ninety two years old interestingly he
got he's been married multiple times but
he got divorce most recently he's wearing
three times all divorces make me say
i know me too because most recent
was twenty twelve years ago versus make
me sad all the dude on the
day and a weight on divorce law
i'm almost dead
right john archer from ninety four to
nineteen seventy four so that's twenty years
including the time when he went to
the moon okay that's a good one
so he had yeah a marriage for
three years my team seventy five it's
like your andreas divorce to the nineteen
seventy eight ended and then he waited
ten years and married lois driggs cannon
and then she and he got divorced
in twenty twelve wow it made
it's me wonder why like why it
ain't like is it just you just
hate it and not to judge anyone
anyone who wants to get divorce should
get well they were married for almost
twenty years everyone should get divorced anyone
who even the thought crosses your mind
should i get divorced get divorced media
if you're married i'd get to their
married for fourteen years and it's like
if you that's that's not to eighty
though like why are younger me oh
no she was born in ninety one
twenty nine again yeah we're both old
that's really what it comes down to
for me maybe it's just your mister
hundred maybe it's just your fucking miserable
of like i just cannot oh she
passed it but okay got it got
it and then they got divorced
say she passed away six years after
the divorce maybe she got to have
a lot of fun without him who
knows what his deal is i'm gonna
live it up i want to see
how he did i'm back onto the
market
boys i did
i'm on right shows a picture he
was ten place
if the woman yeah i want to
see this hot little piece of ass
let me see this hot senior up
oh look
ah yeah
wow i don't know what i was
expecting but that's still spry
here she is younger
oh she had a bit of plastic
surgery later but it seems like there
she didn't really yeah yeah gold medals
on who wouldn't fall in love who
won with a moon man with metals
but when you when you go to
the moon that's the best thing you're
ever going to do it's all literally
downhill from there yeah you know so
so it's like it's like you're hitching
your wagon to a star and decline
ooh that is poetic shit you know
i mean where would you go in
space
um the sun i mean like the
moon seems like one of the easiest
things to do because it's not we
know there's no life in terms of
the closest the only you can read
them here so people know you're talking
about yeah yeah that place yeah i
went there only thing it's doing like
clique and land on right now right
as hue
human being ah prolly can people go
to mars shooting people cars rover yeah
yeah i i don't think that we
can go there yet how long did
it take i know i cheated on
bob the devil
how long does it take to get
there isn't that a problem ah yeah
takes years i think right yeah to
get to the moon let because no
no to noon it's like twenty days
tomorrow when we have looked this up
before if you go yeah if you
go ah you're not coming back if
you go to bars is that true
i'm gonna look it up because
people are not raimi bit about her
i don't give a fuck let em
scream let them boost green who's screaming
martians they're like sixteen twenty oh hi
hey even their shit potatoes
magic potatoes taken oh right hey look
it only takes between one hundred and
fifty and three hundred days
so if you if you go there
you're never coming back i swear to
god i heard that why is it
taking such a wiser to a wide
range oh i just seven months i
guess it's because if you were to
when they're talking about in terms of
like colonization or something that goes like
all the infrastructure and everything and you
couldn't write yeah you know
no nine months fuck so long time
to travel yeah all in all holes
you want to make it around trip
all in all it would take about
twenty one months as you need to
wait about three months on mars to
make sure earth and mars are a
suitable location make the trip back home
dang yeah that's a good idea i
don't think anyone should ever go there
i don't think it's necessary if you
do
bring a copy of date night i
think you should wait to tow until
we can get there faster just even
like shh let's shave off two months
off of that i think it should
take five months mask max to get
anywhere yeah think if it takes longer
than that you shouldn't go if anything
takes long in the five months out
it should be like making ah ah
ocean crossing how long yeah learned and
how long did it take them to
to get to america columbus how long
was his trip oh i don't know
he got lost too so don't factor
that in for the snowmass thought he
was yeah columbus doesn't explore yeah yeah
how long we know it was his
trip okay how long was columbus' trip
he just put in how long was
his trip and the noodles like columbus
do you magnus george jesus christ t
well he journeyed for thirty three years
on earth thirty six days that's not
last long at all anyone could do
this i'll do it today there there
are a survivor longer than that usually
you're really upset the fucking idiot columbus
until i got scurvy and stuff ooh
yeah scurvy it's not just take take
your food sounds vitamin scurvy stuff scurvy
it's very tough you guys had this
instance you got this check out instances
like daddy the old standby
yeah mori this is the lines from
modern romance when he's all drunk and
he's like talking about how he needs
to get vitamins and he's like
recent events jenny is a giant tub
and he's like i got e i
got e the old standard many opens
it up and there's nothing yeah gotta
get more
huh
her boss huh
those are funny lines of oh great
oh well maybe i'll watch some maybe
our brooks movies what if you and
nicole did albert brooks movies has been
oh yeah absolutely yes you could do
finding nemo i won't go back to
tyler perry you go back to go
back to tyler yeah we've only willing
to
tapp said i feel like we could
get a lot more done with tyler
yeah yeah yeah alright we're wrapping up
this segment oh and the way we
always do which i take a break
which is we each draw straws yep
and decide who's gonna who's going to
break we'll be right back alright so
yeah cut up your re straws alright
here we go get this one and
got this one oh paul oh
let me see your stress okay let's
what are next to each other okay
okay so this is not looked as
you can just go from the top
of the bottom yes okay got it
okay i guess it's me yep
we'll be right back okay
and we're back and it's time for
a three cheer can't believe it i
really i can't i can't believe it's
three times already i'm a bit surprised
but i'm also totally on board during
the serial alphabets yeah this still making
those are really good wow i really
don't think they did they were just
a sugary little
alphabet you know i always like to
chomp into a different shape and they
had a lot of different shapes yeah
six to be exact do they do
all twenty six oh yes you could
spell stuff in your serial do you
know that sometimes i use a commercial
confuse the amount of letters in alphabet
with the amount of teeth in the
human how many teeth are because i
never remember that i believe it's thirty
two that's my guess actually that i
had my
head and how old was jesus when
he died thirty three it's because he
was one to missing and hope they
used have more teeth back then yeah
oh and you would live to the
age of your today he loses tooth
every year on his birthday he loses
a tooth every year on his birthday
and so by the end jesus had
no teeth no teeth wow that's where
the chris fun
yeah no sound so yeah i'm counting
my teeth and it's not it's not
adding i'm killing my life and you're
using your tongue to do this the
most precise tool
it is for some things my man
oh sure yeah
it's a sexy
ah now alright well guys it is
time for things make sense oh you
counted thirty-two well i counted eight on
one side eight on the bottom side
and then i thought that equals there
yeah i can't make my tongue thin
enough to like there was so i
can make i can make my paper
thin know i was really
focus that's too thin yeah like there's
one i'll give you a paper cutouts
total teeth at the same time but
i'm going okay that's one huh
it's been about five two yeah yeah
make sense if like forty yeah part
of my tooth has crumbled away by
the way why no he doesn't it
didn't hurt i was eating from believable
i was eating
are you eating chocolate chips ahoy cookie
i was eating a chocolate chip treat
whoa it's chrome believable and then i
hit something that was supposed to be
like soft batch chocolate chip it was
not well and i was like what
does this and pulled out a piece
of tooth one of my one of
my mole ars it didn't hurt at
all you have to get it repaired
i'm gonna find out i go
to the dentist tomorrow oh let us
know keep us updated i was going
to begin to sort of three i
was going to do this earlier but
then i got kovida nineteen harvard gets
in the way of plans really yeah
you know we used to go to
the same dentist did we not
oh that guy lombardo huh yo that
guy and he would yes you didn't
like it was bad news he cheated
me put atrium bad yeah and but
he would always ask about you when
i was there and then because because
ah i got the recommendation from bob
odenkirk he would always say how is
robert doing and i was like you
don't know it
i'll say
i was robert um i do to
you he did a um ah he
put a crown on and then it
fell around king
he said he'd shot this king know
you drop it i did it came
off like almost immediately as you're saying
good bulk and then i was like
hey this thing you know you gotta
put it back on and he like
rushed me through so like gave me
anesthetic did not wait for the anesthetic
to write
take place yes and it was like
hey my mouth hurts a lot it's
hurts donut he was bad yeah i
want him to yeah good for you
yeah i went to another dentist that
a friend of mine went to and
ah one of the hygienists there would
confuse us for each other like azmi
similarly how's lisa lisa
oh i bet he's confusing you with
police know as lisa and i'm like
anybody in the third person yeah was
wait was it wendy from wendy elisa
yeah wow wendy mellow in melville wayne
um alright let's play this thresher and
say wendy and i would say yes
lee
is the water
yes yes lisa
um do you have a sensitivity to
hot water yes please
you need a root canal
doo doo doo doo doo just smiling
plushie does like this oh hey you
guys get it but i like what
i'm hearing you love it i love
it alright this is a three-year call
actually took a video of i love
it i don't care that i'm into
sunday night i forgot oh well the
winger that oh please do people
we're dancing to it yeah aw i
love it yeah i don't want to
say that
this was submitted by krista and this
is called pitchmen toe pitchmen toe which
is a portmanteau of pitching and portmanteau
for belief okay okay so elegant portmanteau
this is a lot like structured like
switch it and pitch it in a
way here's what i like about the
thresher yeah there's five ingredients
yeah this is like our taco bell
one six actually one is a portmanteau
one is switch i don't want it
one is guessing what is sideways and
prolong his big ingredient yeah okay but
young is big ingredient so the the
one person is pitching to two people
but the
the the way they figure out what
they're going to pitch is ah separately
the other two people that you're pitching
to send you one word fuck and
then you have to okay put the
two words together seems and pitch that
ooh so it's not like you're making
a portmanteau of the two words but
you're using
both of awake i started spam risk
i got to take oh okay yeah
put them on put them on the
mike hello messages provided by administration of
energy-saving okay go ahead and set aside
one point three billion dollars oh homie
eligible after ten thousand dollars whoa clean
energy out of one point three billion
navajo
that's chump change why do you get
me all excited you gotta go for
the whole one point three guys have
a million yeah why is that such
a thing right now so many spam
calls i don't know but i get
them three times a day and the
exact same one of the one point
three billion dollars let me tell you
something my auto is warranteed like you
would
didn't buy one today but my my
car warranty well i hope you got
the warrant till i sent my social
security number yeah a million dollars hiring
good yeah and apple gift cards yes
and it all should be working out
okay warranty by the end of the
day um the scammers are starting to
leave me alone okay the jammers just
tripping
chris crocker yelled at them um which
is it's you know it's bittersweet because
they did enjoy um messaging with them
yeah and there's never a satisfying conclusion
they just kinda like stop a peter
out because they realize you're not ah
like the days of you go to
hell our wives were so fun recently
on what
whatsapp and i was pretending to be
a guy and then at a certain
point the girl or whoever asked me
about my what's app picture or something
which was like it's not me but
it's something else and then they were
like oh so who's that and then
it was at this kind of like
if like they were trying to go
well then who's that in this picture
and then what's this and then they're
like let's take this off
what's happened text on the phone i
was like always there trying to get
into the next level yeah i didn't
have that maybe just blocks that was
made on but yeah the the last
one i don't watch app ah was
pretty good um hi how's it going
we haven't talked in a while we
should catch up soon great opening ah
huh i wrote back thanks pretty good
thank you i got a judge
i got a judge to declare me
legally immune to coven and will probably
be interviewed on the news soon oh
are you i miss us oh i'm
pretty good i miss both of you
too how are you today if we
were just talking about how long it's
been since we did the fun night
of entertainment together all three of us
having so much fun i'm ok although
i've just tested positive for over twenty
four
somehow i skipped two codes how are
you how many codes yes we are
how is your wife is she going
fine she's going so fun thank you
were worried she wouldn't be able to
go as fine as she is but
she worked hard how are you oh
yeah happy for hear that she is
going to fine i'm fine thanks how
about you i just bought it for
twenty five i believe my coven i'm
wrapping up but i don't feel too
badly other than loss of touch oh
i'm really sorry for hear that it's
you on your profile thank you for
your kind words they fill my heart
with light my profile is me and
always will be in your profile you
oh yeah yes i mean you have
the scam they were asking at my
profile yeah yeah
think i'm saying i'm forward thinking so
have we talked before oh this is
wonderful news we are both who we
say we are oh we have spoken
before we are good friends yeah yeah
yes we are a good friends such
a good feeling oh yes may i
know your name please robert robert and
emma yes i am robert and emma
and you
her name is mia bella such a
lovely game what does it mean it's
mean beautiful ah my name robert means
mechanical man with a few letters change
do you ever look at the stars
and think that there is life out
there
yo yeah really who name is mister
paul f tompkins yeah oh no have
i been hacked who hacked you this
paul thompson guy he's hacked me almost
ten times now are you trying to
tell me a story yes it's a
story of fraud and triumph shall i
go on okay gone mad okay because
it starts about twenty five years each
other
i was quite the ski bum back
in those days skiing and fun doing
my way up and down the state
for as long as the snow stayed
on the ground one day i get
an email from someone i've never heard
from the email said written down i
am you whatever i want me i'm
sure you can imagine i was perplexed
it was signed mr paul f tompkins
oh yeah since then
every few years this guy has been
about computer phone and pretend to be
my dear friends like you mia bella
it's humiliating i am beta male to
him
he's like me okay beta male yes
we have established previously in the thread
that we are friends anyway what did
you wanna scam me about
yo what's up it's still me where
do i scam you right here let's
do it
he just scam you now yeah you
are sure you want me to scam
you are you ready i thought that
was the whole point and then some
some like gif that i had to
download but i wouldn't download i'm scared
to look at that isn't the scam
let me ask ama if it's safe
oh you want to know about emma
is she safe she is my wife
which is canon i feel like you
are trying to retcon the thread
then she sent me ah office gif
which is clearly brian baumgartner laughing and
i just yelled across yeah and images
yelled across the room do not click
on that anyway me i do think
we've caught up enough can we call
up more mia i can't m s
fears that i spent so much time
catching up when our house has been
on fire this whole talk
create to chat with you and sort
of the scam didn't work out that
ah he writes whose scam you dear
at i wrote not this again
that was doing that but i loved
it it's good
okay wow i mean you're i mean
it's it's perfect rio to show like
this wow you're spending so much time
doing it and so much time doing
and engaging with him but maybe you're
wasting their time unless it's an automated
thing that didn't seem automated that seemed
like at some point it was like
a real champ i feel like is
yeah next level to the ai
yeah yeah yeah and saying okay beta
male i don't think a robot would
do that do you i i don't
know do you remember that ai that
that advertised on bang bang that
that was trying to be a thing
and then it just suddenly closed up
shop and i felt like i had
green for her yes it was like
zia oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
remember smarter child did anyone ever you
what it was like if you spent
a lot of time on a well
this was a and just said at
a bar that you could chat with
and it was called smarter child and
it would just
respond it was an ai or spanish
show me your undergrads
i guess to it within two days
is your parents home let's play a
special game yeah are we going to
play this or should it was at
the episode let's do it like okay
let's do it we got a couple
minutes okay we have some times okay
so lauren why don't you pitch to
us and paul and i will text
you separate words okay ah
hitching what you basically just put our
two words together so the example that's
krista used is if i tex poop
and politics spoon then you have to
pitch a poop spoon yeah yeah anyway
i don't want to do it
ah
so i'm gonna text you a word
and paul is gonna text you a
word i did it and my phone
nah just not smart got it and
here's mine
and then you're going to pitch us
this product
we do this one before i don't
believe so zu neuen dun dun dun
dun dun dun dun ten tentang wow
wow wow oh my god yes ten
ten ten ten tenth person has their
own theme music danton hello sharks oh
we're not we're not sorry there must
be some sort of confusion here no
this is not sharpie
i've been sitting out to those double
doors for like oh now i know
when we do if we got double
doors people are gonna think of a
shark tank i know he wanted the
single door and he wanted triple doors
and this
okay well um
what are you here for dear i
have i have a product page if
you are oh this is perfect yesterday
so yeah we'll yes that is that
we're not talking listen to pitches we
don't buy pitches we listen to them
okay well i guess i could just
practice it on you yeah okay sure
no that's part of our business okay
well i have the most important thing
that everyone in the whole
world is going to need very much
o vowing okay and now is a
huge justice huish if everyone in the
world i mean that's a huge market
yeah that's the whole market that's i
mean can they use it over and
over again so they have to keep
buying it um can they use it
over and over again so they have
to keep okay
it does it does it wear out
is it like a yeah so single
use products single use tell us what
it is champ like a tampon his
one trinsic um
that's what you're trying to say yeah
like did you just say that is
it a tampon that everyone in the
world needs to use twelve times a
year i feel like you're you're approaching
this kissing game but i'm just wondering
well no i'm saying that's the kind
of product that i want to buy
why because not only does every single
person in the world needed but they
need it over and over and
over again you can keep making money
i don't know that everyone needs tampons
now every single person that's i'm not
saying that everyone in the world needs
tampons saying that literally i'm gonna have
some public outside and you publish this
the private sector i'm stepping outside you
guys can go buy come in come
in through the other door now okay
yeah dunton done
dun dun dun dun hi we're starting
wow you are where you came in
through the right door that's right okay
great shark tank for this time and
you're robert herjavec and younger obviously marketer
wonderful i'm simply well that's not mister
wonderful i'm saying he's mr wonderful my
name is simply marvelous oh your name
simply marble yeah yeah simply irresistible i'm
a simp
i think lee is marvelous yeah he's
the marvelous mrs maisel as well sam
lee marvelous yeah but my simp lee
marvelous
is louisville's out there could be better
lee marvellous is i would love to
meet her the father of lee majors
right yes that's right okay wait what
what are you going to sell them
thanks yes it's like it gets worse
each time
somebody's stomach tucks systems that was a
girl in my throat hurts just point
that out know it's only gonna hurt
conversations it's it's gurgle am i doing
our conversation before you walked in here
though no i'll think oh thank god
we were talking about personal stuff in
confess to a lot of this is
gonna set up my board here oh
look at that wow
and your very prepaid is this about
karate are you going to kick that
um break it i'm not going to
break it i need to keep this
so if you do karate please don't
break this i'm only a yellow belt
is i try is a little trick
it is a little trek so he's
going to ask here and i'll just
use him to kind of hey they're
stay here at all star oh wow
it sings yeah i usually
does it more
it just thinks the first part of
all-star okay it's so usually does it
again shaking it again no it's nothing
i think it's broken yeah did i
break it maybe i'm a black belt
paid so much money how much oh
no why do you think you're impactful
did you karate chop it well i've
been a yellow belt but yeah crash
update stop staring again hey no you
tobacco okay he did that great oh
it's saying yeah you're a black belt
wow thank you i thought i was
ok so my ideas thing everybody needs
so you ever have any message in
your house that are just all sorts
of crumbs in your bed like crumbs
of cookies and crumbs of you know
anything i'll see i mean i have
a problem i don't kick my wife
out of bed for eating crackers okay
oh yeah this cracker crumbs i sleep
on a bed of crumbs yeah okay
i go to i go to the
supermarket i go right to the congreso
i'll aha and i just bags and
bags of progresso breadcrumbs yeah okay let
me sleep on that and you know
it's very control it's pretty cultural i
slept on at once when i was
house sitting
you didn't tell me that you slept
in the wood you think you can
go through yeah where do you think
i was going to sleep the couch
when i'm house sitting for yes for
a year his personal for a whole
year i'm supposed to be on the
couch i have daydreams on that bed
where do you do when you do
on the couch i stare straight ahead
okay i'm sorry
i pose so this is this is
a crummy id a work it's creamy
it a crimean made yes do you
have an accent all of a sudden
no so you're saying creamy id yes
okay you're saying me it crummy id
you're saying crib yes and i was
definitely what it is
brushing it's really a small room that
this little shrek could hold if it's
too small for a room and hey
any heat you have just like a
large brush okay come into your bed
and kind of just why are you
just talking about paying into to anything
that we should go to bed he'll
just sweep up all your crumbs into
a little pyramid and then it goes
right between the the bed the pillows
of
you and your spouse or whoever's sharing
your bed with you that evening or
nobody if no what if what if
i have a gu ma
that's fine too and then it's alright
ah huh and then like more hero
no moral judgments and then in the
morning you know you'll you are able
to document that for instagram and wait
so the so the chrome brush that
trick holds turns the crumbs into a
pyramid of crumbs yes and then you
put them on between the pillows he
will place it between the pillows
you can well those aren't pillows you
can please present a bill so you
can instagram its own you can instagram
it and then show your pyramid so
it's kind of like show off your
pyramid of chrome this is something that
everybody know your pyramid and that way
people can go oh actually had way
more than you i've seen that hashtag
yeah that's what it's the hashtag is
about because i was trying
sandag that was trapping wow i know
it was trending it was really huge
day for us but it was huge
yeah yeah so um and trek is
a part of it he reckons attached
attached and he will show up at
your house hosting the first part of
a song if he's feeling like really
do more than hey now he usually
does hey now you're an all star
okay well that's actually good
yes and you don't get upset i
tried to him do more and he
really pushed much did you pay for
this you said you paid a lot
of money for it i was so
i've invested in my company already quite
a bit um just when you say
that you just have bought this record
getting this check because you don't even
seem to have the the implement yeah
you don't have to go from the
from the bidder
whatever it was called sally figure i
mean he will stand there and he
will do this once to go to
you so you haven't invented the pyramid
you've just bought the shrek thing it's
not inventing a pyramid he makes pyramids
out of crooks but you haven't been
invited the the brush you just bought
he traps the brush it's there
it's it's more about how just like
ah ah dulls he bearish pyramid so
it's a sentient doll that gets sent
to your house i will talk to
him later about that he's not adult
weight he's alive yes i just wish
he would stop playing my doll he's
getting very printed but i
beg your pardon see if he'll sing
you're an ogre hey
i thought you said that he was
gonna say hey now you're an aussie
would and he just said hey two
different ones
do it buddy he's doing like tibetan
throat say hey dude this is the
time where we're gonna sell this thing
and actually get our money back the
million dollars i paid for you from
the dollar store yeah that i didn't
know they sold million dollar thing she
says dollar store doesn't say one dollar
store sing a little song
come on guy moon river right shut
up moon river rit that's not that's
not the shrek that i know and
love singing moon river from breakfast at
tiffany fan and i said what about
breakfast at tiffany's okay so i'm just
gonna pack up shop here in lee
because it seems like you're not interested
in crimea we don't buy anything we
told you them from the beginning he's
don't leave we're lonely when you're so
lonely you're just two lonely sips yeah
but don't give money into lonely beta
cooks we got blocked by the marvelous
wow yeah you're gonna find the real
oh please t v e
and wait trick stayed track trick hey
now you're an all-star get to a
mom oh shit you say you're an
all-star get a out let's play and
all thanks to me as a chow
thrill
oh nice stars break that ma i
forgot track oh no amy please please
leave him here he's a tangle this
whole song for us he yeah right
scam artists
when he goes in time for scam
now it's time for a scam hey
now there's a scam now
alright i was fine we did it
the and and that's how you play
by frenchman teach montoya oh yes oh
pink man submitted by booths food thanks
boobs ooh thanks poop spoon and please
submit e pitch manto and pinch manto
oh it's a new game that would
be great fun to play pinch mantis
where you should pinch praying mantis yeah
took a game but you get fined
fifty doll
dollars if you do but that's how
you play the game
bebop doobie okay three usa twitter and
instagram three minutes eight gmail dot com
haha in poo is the phone number
we love you want to listen to
ad-free versions of this shit why don't
you go to stitcher premium or cbp
world dot com before going to fuck
yourself wow that would be great if
you go if you go fuck yourself
fun fun doing it doesn't have to
be a bad faded time fuckin you
suh
alright we'll see you next time i
book your share of by
uh