three
the name of the shows is
staff name
oh yeah baby we did it yeah
austin powers we did it we did
our show so delek shag your delek
shag adeleke shy shy guy like shaq
oh we should just name is joe
shaggy delek do you think it's time
he's finally time one hundred we get
sued as a copywriter i hope that
austin powers ca
copyrighted his most famous catchphrase see i
hope he gave it to the world
that anyone could use it i think
you're right for awesome powers so loved
the world he gave his only because
ah loss of hours sixteen what all
these drinks you have i didn't notice
okay so we've got a regular bar
over there we were talking about drinking
during the show on over last episodes
i found these
is in the fridge during our break
ooh ah wild roots lemon vodka and
soda you well yeah we don't don't
throw that throw it i didn't know
you were having a straight up cocktail
yeah it's i mean it's almost four
o'clock so somewhere why not do you
want it you want me throw no
i'm ok have to drive oh no
so sorry i don't drive for ten
hours oh wait are you a trucker
on this i am going to have
a little in them by the time
i drive it'll be done i'm a
long haul truckers yeah it's only one
it'll be nice to take my pills
and can um it's my thin as
a pencil this is as skinny isn't
easy to say is britney spears says
skinny as a needle what does i
do that is um she
posted this video a long time ago
about how the popper i'd say would
post pictures that were not accurate of
her and she'd see i was wearing
this bidding suit on the beach and
they post this picture me and then
she would show it and she looked
like she was heavier than two but
see here i am wearing the same
suit later that day i'm skinny as
a needle
but they won't post that oh boy
poor percent alcohol free britney just four
percent alcohol can we should just left
it to the court's four percent alcohol
is like a a bottle of whiskey
whoa i love this yeah a full
bottle of whiskey wait this tastes really
good what does this company it's wild
roots i don't know why we have
them
i feel like maybe this is my
jam i would drink every night okay
i have all sorts of flavor this
is not an ad by the way
i just got these out of the
refrigerator don't get holly driving that milk
and um i'm moving off that juice
you're moving on to juice
yeah so you're not drinking anymore
ah but so i can have a
little sippy sip how do i get
holly to be my best friend or
to think of me as her best
friend oh um right now she only
really knows two people she's seen which
na ru paul and i'm maury povich
she loves that guy
ah i like this little this little
thing this is like a pretty little
this is like perfect for like if
you are going to see a movie
in the park yeah yes by the
way it's ah daylight savings time is
going to happen soon and we'll have
the movies back again it's gonna be
good i know oh boy i'm so
glad daylight saving time is happening soon
now daylight savings time
i'm means that they're the days get
longer yes yeah because well the days
get longer naturally but also in the
nights get stronger than moonshine sure of
course well i just noticed yesterday that
it was five o'clock and the sun
was still up and i was so
happy and you're so drunk and i
was you'd been drinking our you know
i barely just for the record
and i don't care what anyone does
but i barely drink i really don't
find it very compelling to me but
i did have a glass of wine
last night and i was like wow
here's where i had one glass of
wine a few years back i found
it very compelling ah no i mean
i read it i knew i used
the wrong um no i think that's
the right word i know what you
mean like i fee
that way now like i got who
drink right now i feel that way
about getting high but then when i
do get high it's very pleasant yeah
yeah but then i forget about it
you don't mean like i like to
have yeah my my glasses of wine
on the weekends yeah but then when
if i do if i eat an
edible or something yeah let's just like
a mile weekend like this during the
week it's all rocks
rock yeah it's really nice yeah it's
really nice pot has come a long
way what if ubereats was like getting
weed delivered back in the day where
they came in and then they ate
part of your food huh yeah wow
video games
get the fucking santa such an insane
business model to like when you think
about it doesn't bring pot party you
know cause he's like i can just
keep getting high this way because they'll
hook me up so it's like yeah
i guess it works out yeah yeah
every day from somebody else's pandemic has
taught us anything it's that leaving stuff
on the porch and running away is
the way
way to deliver things i mean you
currently running away whatever really wanted to
stand there and have a whole interaction
so nuts when i think about that
you used to have to go meet
the people and to take them and
go like oh thank you so much
when i saved on my door and
right away nah my bachelor days when
i was ordering food a lot i
would
get the same people alon and it
was nice to have like a little
that running a megami relationship but that
can be nice that can be nice
but williams here there is one one
place that delivers to us where we
know the person who delivers it to
us and yeah it's always like oh
well i mean coop knows like those
people never want to like chat with
you because they understand it's food that's
the thing i also wouldn't same a
stand there
and have a conversation it's so insane
when if i were an uber driver
and god i hope to be at
some point
make you i wouldn't want to chat
with the people in the backseat would
you or maybe it's just so boring
maybe so maybe yeah maybe you're bored
but also maybe it makes you feel
safer and i mean maybe that's a
female perspective but i'm like maybe i'd
want to have a conversation because it
kind of makes me feel like oh
just some normal guy he's not going
to kill me
i tell you what i never thought
about it this way before because i
was thinking why would wanna chat with
people if they looked interesting and now
i feel like maybe that's a compliment
to me if somebody wants to chat
with boy got some perspective and curious
about this mr moustache over here who's
just weirdo what's all dressed up for
right yeah to mr magoo
you're not wearing glasses
um should we should we do part-time
jobs this summer we've talked about topic
this i literally need to hire somebody
to help me so do that as
a part-time job be my own yeah
i mean i already am doing it
it's called mom it's my mom maybe
you've heard of it it takes up
all day what does mom stand for
most original oh boy
you really waited out here you can't
go back to shore only one more
word to go huh
huh most original mah mah mother
oh cops oh no lauren they found
you oh oh from your weekend to
get me they're coming to take away
haha haha dr di mento remember him
he's around right yeah it's just a
with started oh definitely
is he still doing this thing i
don't know but there's anything too relaxed
yeah you aren't you before you were
so on it i know i know
religious stuff sounds great way to show
whatever you want yeah to me here's
how i rank the races oh it's
not what happens when i get relaxed
ah i feel so kind of relax
your rank the races you're saying yeah
like i said olympics
oh god oh so this was a
mistake it might be i mean i
really would love to just be floating
in the pool drinking this thing i
would love to push you in the
pool chandler a perfect match meaning
really coupled with your heavies you can
believe me that's a great outfit cool
i know i just feel warm for
the occasion but i don't really care
well at four o'clock yesterday i was
out here recording a different show sorry
guys cheating on ah yeah sorry but
oh my god he admitted he only
did it about four o'clock on the
dotted got it dropped like
five degrees so i'm expecting that to
happen today not to be great for
me that would that would be so
good for you yeah i'd be fantastic
i love that for you i love
that for me
i don't think you're allowed to say
that i think you are i think
other people are only a lot of
love things for you what are these
little orbs in your pool lauren you'll
never guess what at night they light
up yeah okay that's fun day on
a timer no it's the sun sun
based
i think there's so much technology solar
technology and then at night they they're
like oh the sun went away oh
shit let's turn on now we can
shine into that they have to say
hey this is their way of defying
the sun here's how solar technology works
you make something that hates the sun
and then it see it pretends to
not be alive but it's eating up
all the sunlight
yeah and then when the sun goes
away it's like hi trick to you
yeah meanwhile paul's coke can that he
threw says roy nah there's a rolling
stone wow again pretty far away it's
like breaking bad colo pretty sure he's
not gonna remember to pick that up
but after this episode i'll pick it
up right now oh you will
he's taking user advance off oh okay
huh peace knowing yeah hey he found
this on the web these headphones off
check it out
i think that was i think that
was wise oh my gosh oh my
gosh
what did i say to trigger syria
oh my gosh
that's horrible case you alright paul's coming
back he picked up his coke can
now he's thrown it at me oh
my god yes no rules he is
just gonna trick up the can and
walk away and throw the can too
dua lipa yeah kidz bop yeah it's
called gulu kids about version
and don't brush your teeth before you
go to bed and then say your
prayers too
so shouldn't kids say their prayers first
thing in the morning it's so dire
to have have him do it right
before they go to bed like all
i can think about is the horror
in the world you think kids can
comprehend the shit they can't just proud
of you have to make them do
it so they get in a state
of grace in case god takes them
oh jesus do they know
that's what they're doing before they figured
out later oh my gosh
did you say prayers at night i
think maybe they were like my parents
were like yeah i'd do this at
one point and then i tried it
maybe once i don't know i'm not
gaming
yeah once you know what it's not
compelling just wasn't compelling to me did
you say prayers or hear a little
kid no no no i did i
used to pray in bed oh but
i think i probably prayed a long
time do you get these next year
better you laid in bed i did
not do that and i always felt
guilty about it oh you're digging it
easy i did feel that way and
i usually
like fucking cross myself i used to
relay part of the church clasped my
hands yes that's very i was a
believer not a believer that's a million
francs very nice
i'm happy for you um
i think that's nice i love that
for you i do love that for
you i love it for little kid
for child you what point where you
like this is stupid
i'm trying to remember when i stopped
praying because i probably i would imagine
a prayed all through high school because
i was a believer all through high
school and then when i was seventeen
eighteen getting out in the world you
were seventeen going on a tumbling out
of the house not doing the work
in what really yeah you were
so like you stepped outside the house
it was like holy shit the same
realize oh i'm put in the truck
like i don't believe anything
i think i remember praying as late
as fourteen maybe i've thrown some prayers
out as an adult you know just
kind of seeing well yeah hey why
not like if it's real
you could always use a little help
like devote my life to it god
if you're real give me a hundred
dollars
wow spread out over the next twenty
years
in charge from purchases you know what
i take it i'll take it if
it's extra but she'll come in handy
early if i'm just getting it like
through my day-to-day activities no thanks god
but if it's extra money yeah hell
yeah ah no thanks god yeah
ah lauren is going to slay yeah
a quarter of the i barely drink
any guy so belligerent i know it's
just a placebo show down i just
want to be known i haven't had
that much but i do really like
how it tastes i could chug this
whole thing it's very light chug chug
chug chug chug chug chug don't want
to drunk cannibalistic
humanoid underground guy
what is i like vaguely know what
you're talking a movie should know china
is capitalist or seeing that humanoid underground
dwellers weller yeah i don't like pleasant
he dwells underground and is kind of
humanoid
have you seen the toxic avenger never
seen it that's that's good never seen
any of the troma films yeah but
chad i i've never seen let me
ask me i know you don't even
know what chad was as we ever
have you ever seen toxic vendor oh
would you see the princess diaries yeah
a bunch but i love that movie
really alright to scholars and seen about
it oh okay okay now a deal
estonian you i'm going to tell you
what's happening know she's got big bushy
eyebrows and yeah she's got big she
was very cute in the before i
what do you mean that's the thing
it's like so much for you an
eyebrow wax yeah the before it's always
better than the after but they make
a really awkward and whatnot so it's
like she's like always klum but she's
adorable awkward she's adorable she's she's she
was the original adorable
she's so adorable original adobo
oh god she's dorky kid she's a
darker i want a door to door
on a whale darker
they will do well isn't that what
a well being this is called a
dork day isn't like the clinical term
scientific term
well they look scary is a whale's
bean is called a dork i found
this on the web for siri it's
me
siri what is the name of a
whale penis
give the phone back to your mom
i would love to see out a
bunch of free programs yeah i know
what you're trying to do and you
won't get away with it i'm like
not on the wifi just like working
on that ah we're really putting in
some research something went wrong oh no
oh my god um i guess i
could try although i don't believe i
have siri activated i think you do
because it just wants you to activate
on this computer but i yeah computer
awake and computer when i'm on the
wi-fi
what is very what is a whale's
penis called
sorry i couldn't find anything on the
web in parts of british columbia canada
the word dork is referred to as
the male genitalia of a whale thank
you jenna wailea ooh god i'm spicy
the blue whale's penis or dork
it is the largest that ever existed
well the biggest dog in the world
does anybody else any other animals have
special names for their dicks they don't
know but it isn't isn't a corkscrew
or is just a long nap think
it's like the average size for an
adult male is fifteen feet that's soul
grow so big and low yeah boy
circumcised or uncircumcised
well religious households weighed twenty two pounds
too heavy that's decade live sting
that's disgusting the blue whale can produce
between three and twenty gallons of sperm
during it's mating season more than enough
three three is enough for me i'm
gonna one three happens you go you
doing okay do you do masturbator before
this
only three gallons but yeah
can you imagine being there you were
just coming forever like i'm sorry there's
more
throw not even enjoying it it's just
happening can you imagine being on the
receiving end of twenty gallons of skin
we throw twenty gallons and you just
say imagine it
twenty gallons of what sperm oh okay
sperm sperm whales okay we're gonna clay
whale sperm next to the water and
just one shoot twenty gallons you think
it's watery i mean he's in the
water all the time you think he
just isn't see where it goes i
mean if it's twenty gallons it probably
impregnated a few things yeah do you
think he just jesus and because it's
in water just travel to where
passing by like laud i know yeah
joe swimmer don't get me pregnant was
that part of finding nemo just a
lot of whale sperm everywhere there was
a point don't get me bragg well
yeah
did you ever see blackfish yeah oh
boy that's watching my god the what
in the pool yeah you don't know
that's coming my and also working off
a killer whale oh wait no part
no i meant the power they drag
that lady around she gets pulled that
is that's very scary when that movie
is so scary and and it just
like why what are we doing why
yeah of course they can kill you
the way they
drag a lady around onstage and jerk
off a whale in another scene that
sounds like the family harvest the sperm
of the the current shambhu shamu is
like a dynastic title sugarhouse downs like
minuto yeah he there's still a menudo
impulse i hope so he
e o
yeah no it's like this thing this
episode got very dense all of a
sudden like we're we're ripping through it's
like digging up
it says wild roots eleven vodka soda
i'm not even on into sway so
partly of the i was you you
can just like that and he's like
i've done a lot of weed miranda
and i'm like done a lot of
weed i've done a lot of weed
maria i'm ok i need right now
oh my god what so wait so
you win your shambhu part of the
you're sure
a's are you trying to make it
go faster ship
you may of course schmooze me switch
move shit do you remember the shmoop
i do remember the shmoop yeah i
have to go to the bathroom he
looks like you have to go through
that you drank one quarter by taking
all these cans of liquid death that's
what you do da do da can
i go now and you know we
don't have to take another break for
another five minutes okay so i'll just
wait so
so um shamu of course a very
valuable property for seaworld sure he names
him in the door y'all say so
then um he also had adorable um
like when one shamu dies they just
have another whale that's like this shamu
that's so funny shamu is still here
just give him a new wind that
shamu is still here fifty years
here's my name but that's not because
then the product has changed they have
to build up a new yeah the
the key chains have to be remade
example want shambhu people want them when
they get him
damn where does shan lu originate the
name shambhu probably from the first shamu
i would bet ah shah mo that
ha ha ha
jack off i bet it's an inuit
name if i were to wake j
ah based on kind of willow snow
swim based on context clues based on
based on context like wake up more
george burden based on the jamming some
context clues based on context clues she
went to me
brewed and based on the context players
drank the whole thing was so none
of the news rays we can assure
me as a needle
ah
huh
shop in brockway sony as a needle
whenever true need hold down underneath
we have to harvest the the white
gold that is shamu sperm white gold
that they can keep having schmooze oh
so schmooze have to be direct lineage
yes whoa so they harvest it and
and his is he in the water
when this happens no he sure isn't
he's using dry lands lying on his
back on one of the platforms i
know it happened in those do they
have to do they say like hey
it's coming you're gonna enjoy this or
no it doesn't get pleasure i mean
we know that dolphins do but to
wales yeah a pleasure centers in their
brain while i'm surely a pleasure in
life but not from gysi mammals sure
because this guy's clearly enjoying it
like he's not going anywhere ad ma'am
rather viewing that the animals that have
sex for pleasure but wait whales are
mammals whales are mammals that's right and
like if you are dollars and something
like um sea lions and shit like
that will dirty lies off monkeys will
jerk themselves off yeah okay monkeys will
jerk you wouldn't why do they say
dolphins are the only ones who have
sex for pleasure who is
i've heard this my whole life every
day someone tells me your mom and
dad mom i didn't priority and we
told you that your mom and dad's
needle
wales would be pretty teeny and alina
dolphins are the only ones to have
sex for pleasure
they don't like it
um so yeah i think that ah
a lot i think so and so
they do if sex for pleasure but
they certainly enjoyed jerking off they do
it for money though sometimes yes there
are sex workers of the c o
wales paid to be shabu yeah yeah
even paycheck in clams wow ooh never
mind this my whole thing is total
me wrong i sold it now i'm
having to go back what does your
heart and now sigh yeah like your
life are we still that was satisfying
enough about the door by novos and
other parameter of sql pressure just lactating
for the joy of it oh well
sure that's engaged in oral sex to
prolong their bouts of intercourse oh dang
short nosed fruit bats nass
hyenas goats and sheep fame is female
hyena is goats and sheep hyenas female
cheetahs and lions like around the male's
genitals is part of the courtship show
that doesn't mean they haven't pleasure i
don't think i'm gonna just let that
just be we don't know we don't
know what they're feeling as opposed to
the evolutionary thing of this is how
they have sex
right how do fish enjoy it they
don't write fish do it whales do
it even educated fleas do it
so so a prude close the loop
on many proven to fall in love
ah yeah they they they jerk them
off and where's it go like they
have buckets doing the hand motion on
the fifteen foot dick
what's the circumference that's the other thing
that like ok yeah it's fifteen feet
it goes but it's gone just getting
is a nice one
as discussed ah it's like a pole
vault it goes up in the sky
and they turn their umbrellas upside down
to catch my mind yeah so like
mary bobbins no i don't remember how
they how they get it know they
dealing and they put a bunch of
buckets around and hope some lands and
whoa i think there's a guy on
a ladder
after having a whale i wanted i
want a in a condom yeah it's
good idea yeah that is true it's
just a tarp that's disgusting it's like
a boyscout ten
oh and it's natural it's nature it's
nature catchy for the whales nature isn't
discussing except for bug i think it's
disgusting that a person's getting their own
involved in that sense you know the
person who does it loves doing it
yeah okay so you're saying that a
love of it that speciality and you
know they have to word it very
carefully in the one
isn't a possibility if you're getting paid
to do it for a job
god yeah consider that person had sex
with a dog and a porn that
they are being paid for speciality if
you enjoy spca spca porn if it's
just a job it's not be reality
and you have that's why all actuality
porn comes with a disclaimer says they
did enjoy this
note all the performers in this film
enjoyment for a ball
i had a blast stay tuned for
testimonials at the end of the film
alright we have to take a break
learn sep alright good
and we're back we just had a
giggle off my you could have heard
the giggle oh my god stories that
look cool yeah he literally did take
forty five minutes we had a great
catch up i wanna lights came on
back here and ah it is midnight
right
before yeah we're sleeping bags and um
we're having a great time we're making
s'mores from our sleeping bag and a
full six pack of those drinks alright
to leave these couple years these crispy
yes so they were christmas lights that
we decided are going to stay up
all year i wanna wrap some trees
i love that i want you random
right shows
around some trees
bes t is for the tree
three e is for the e e
is for the tree based t is
for the dream ha is for the
rate
these are worthy any more they just
know jonathan katz the comedian yes from
the doctor yes i did his show
in san francisco he i are you
as shaky wavy drawing yes
you have to transform yourself into one
of those i've worked with him doing
stand-up back in philly years ago and
he was so much fun to watch
i loved watching him we ever on
this show yeah i was on a
shootout a few times i mean tarzana
if yeah yeah wow i want to
look that wow
oh you're amazing wow
holy shit oh yeah it's free you're
free my fucking eyes out right yeah
hero we love you
h is for the hero e is
for the hero is for the row
is for the who
he had this bit where you would
play a crank quality made
i love like when people say crank
call i always said i grew up
saying what i said yeah craig murray
is eastern west and prank is midwest
yeah probably they make sense um he
said this call he would he was
calling someone
and his he was saying as my
name is my name is john potterton
that's p s and potterton o isn't
isn't too different to turn to his
attorney
nervous when you have to say though
like what the letters are like sometimes
i'm i've had to do that recently
a few times where i'm trying i
can't even think of an a word
like i'm like apple oh yeah i've
had a word sometimes it's easy peasy
and then other times write blank like
in the middle drina joe door now
to george
huh did you urge giorno as it
did giorno di isn't dub
dubey meals for every letter d isn't
torn top diaz in a whale's penis
jordan foreign co
could you get away with doing a
pretty word for every signal a isn't
o b as in bitch i see
isn't kind i heard there is no
this isn't dork there's legal which is
dirty version of word lie guy that's
said to me by brett does he's
into ooh
bremmer is your dear friend my dear
reddy didn't send it to me oh
oh he respects you to imus i'm
his boss yay for you here britain
yeah charlie is actually fiery as you
say
he said it was like you were
different i do what yeah yes do
i know okay you're talking oh oh
oh however you said if i'm good
or yesterday me it's for the b
c c c d is more than
just putting in the first five letters
of the effects i don't think that's
gonna work lucho lou
oh no she tried to spell ludo
oh but i don't have twitter like
they do out of dick
limbo lower you are kidding you do
mad libs with dirty words oh we've
gotten caught off no we got caught
because we um we would do it
change it to the newspapers
like we read this i dare you
we with the zodiac killer
um no we wrote it on the
ah you know how we would have
scratch paper from the real estate agencies
that would always like send you you
know scratch paper okay i know that
i know the concept of scratch paper
real estate agencies the same day we
send you pads of paper that were
with their brand new never go i
wouldn't call that news you know when
we had tons of scratch paper
from like pads pencils things like that
from a funeral home whoa i gave
dying soon i don't know why we
had us the fife and hour funeral
home i guess they would send it
send it to people in neighbor we
they would they would like deliver it
all the time you'd get it on
your doorstep and so we would have
scratch paper from
all of these realtors everywhere and that's
like how i even knew what a
realtor was because we had that oh
well it worked so my parents would
go away and my brother who made
one of the realtors twentieth century fox
suomen latu made star wars that's who
engraved my ipad there's this little woman
who has a real term but she's
on the carts and bah
bonds ah and a little yeah yeah
thing you know that wouldn't add at
the edge of an end of a
car or like in the flip baby
slowly yes yes yes ma'am the day
we had to bang my hair i
know it's ok anyway i really wanted
that changed you better humble yourself you
gotta start ah yeah you're too big
to ride this shopping card
now they have those little cars kids
can ride around it's to me it's
the best early to say about this
realtor oh anyway so my my parents
would go out and my brother who
is only two and a half years
older than me was tasked with babysitting
me and this is like you know
i'd be i'd be eight i'd be
you know i'd be you know it
was just like
and by themselves i sort of think
that's true but not anymore depend on
the relationship because oh yeah all the
bullying begins well you're always trying to
kill me so that was but ah
fair enough but anyway so he he
ah i don't and i shouldn't put
it all on him because you know
i was interested in this as well
but being killed
no in in in doing doing dirty
math yes oh sure i loved a
dirty madden and so i remember i
remember we would we would we were
like we can't write it in the
madlib lib book and this is we
we get from scholastic we would get
the mad lives force so we can't
write it in the madlib book so
his solution was let's write it on
the realtor scr
each paper and will throw it away
before they get home and then so
that's gonna backfire it's like you want
to hit it better in the madlib
exactly because they're not gonna read the
madlib book ever you ever love to
shave the first page that's had with
a pencil right that's the funniest part
in um psycho and brothers movie the
great big lebowski
where like as it because that's a
detective trick where you're like yo and
into the scratch week so he interviews
some guy and the guy's like writing
something the entire time and he like
does the scratching thing is just the
guy was drawing a guy with a
big dick
so to watch the movie again i
don't think i've seen the whole thing
i didn't really like it when it
came out i didn't like it when
it came out either but i like
it now but in any case so
we rode on the scratch paper and
then we never could figure out when
my parents were getting home and so
every once in while we'd be watching
benny hill and yeah which had boobs
on yeah k hell no
while yeah crazy you know world yeah
so we would have to turn off
the tv and pretend we weren't watching
tv and they would always go over
the tv and see if it was
hot and they were like you were
watching tv and then they would say
well were you watching and and i
remember coming to betty hit chinese i'm
benny hill anyway
so they macneil lehrer report so i
don't know how it happened but they
they came home and we like abandon
the paper and i guess we forgot
to throw away the paper and within
five minutes my parents like found this
paper and somebody said all the paper
is it just just we're just like
number one fuck
fuck or do shit
huh
and within like five minutes we knew
we were decided on that i mean
that's plenty i would fucking die that's
the thing or one is fuck number
two as would you call them out
on it and be like oh but
it's funny i just try to figure
out why their numbers like interesting know
that was part of it it was
like okay let's sit you down
and this was always the cases my
my mom was these are in the
wrong order
number two should be shit because it
is number two um no they would
always find something in my mom would
immediately like turn like do a heel
turn and and she would turn bad
and she would like she went from
face character to heal
and she would like go in the
other room and we always when my
brother and i would locate each other
like oh fuck we forgot to throw
the thing away she just founded and
then suddenly my dad would walk in
and it was like okay what is
this and we'd have to explain and
it was just like fuckin punished for
everything like can't i live yeah can't
i do funny fake
dirty mad labs that is so stressful
yeah oh i wonder how parents and
i guess i'll find out how they
decided to punish people together like the
kids together like your parents were have
the same basic belief system i guess
that like they can't do this they
can't do that or they had today
discuss and like one was kind of
like one thing that's fine but i'll
go with you on this one
or whatever like well i i think
my mom my mom ended up not
caring about certain things because i remember
i was in a play when i
was twenty that had a lot of
cursing and my mom i was kinda
not even saying that it was happening
in my moms are like are you
in this play and i said yeah
but there's a lot of cursing it
and she goes i don't care and
came and and
liked it and then later on in
life she liked like sopranos with cursing
and stuff like that i was like
oh interesting so i but but at
the same time they were both very
religious so it was like but maybe
there's also like if you're eight years
old i don't like that if you're
seventy yeah yeah yeah lord who do
you think is gonna be the softy
between you and mike sort of think
mike i think
so too yeah i know you're gonna
be hard i don't think of myself
as that but it's a planarian no
i don't i don't want to be
i mean i know but i already
get the spanking pan out yeah sure
that's true i like to let them
out i'm frightened of you hi i
i don't want to be doing the
show anymore
i know cursor monkey i don't want
to be hardcore but i also feel
like i think that at some level
of rules is good full of course
but i don't mean like you're gonna
be a strict disciplinarian but that in
comparison is like if i can't get
my way with mum i will go
to death probably yeah yeah well with
a cursing
ing and stuff like i like will
always say yes if holly comes to
me just so yeah okay well you
do whatever you want wow say hollywood's
great my husband roles and my number
one rule is do it everyone
um no with the cursing it's like
i like how some people are like
oh there are words you can say
in private and there are words you
can say in pub yeah like but
but for us to be bad for
even thinking these things know i know
that's not how i think i mean
obviously i i'm going to be swearing
and like that kind of stuff i
feel like is it's hard to control
and you shall hear all that stuff
whenever
but like something like doing something that
is bad i think i wouldn't say
swearing counts as doing something that's yeah
what is bad for you murder like
breaking something in lying or like you
know flying lying being mean being mean
blogging this lush
even jimmy carter e if she is
hurt is exhibiting slaw i will ah
word i think jimmy carter like they
should bring that up anytime he makes
another statement he only has so few
left but you know hey time you
said your listener made one recently about
i always worried about democracy he should
also have to add peace
still most of my work was that
it was a playboy interview right yeah
yeah where he that was like his
big quote was like they asked him
okay you're a devout christian it's the
only way people remembered from yeah oh
my god it was like do you
still do you feel are you attempted
or whatever i think wasn't phrased but
i have i have had lust in
my heart
and that's like kindest way you could
put that i know and it's the
only thing people are like oh lusty
jimmy carter hey dean jimmy carter was
like a decent person still is still
far as i'm concerned i mean still
is a decent person but will be
florin just yawned so hard at two
old men talking about jimmy carter
ah well yeah this is like my
dad and so paul
you can play stop talking and he
was a gang
so it was the longest yawn i
ever had let it out but i
knew i had to
i was talking to like scholarly get
something like what's going on she were
like yeah just link polite you're trying
to keep it and she was silent
it was silence but sadly my heart
sbd
sorry for talking about jimmy carter i
don't care on a lie were you
not alive when we fit your fire
in our knee
it's okay she's adapting i don't care
about presidents as i've made very clear
but i i don't know when he
was the president you don't know what
year i would guess the eighties seventy
seven through eighty one great so i
count that's right he was succeeded by
ronald reagan i really don't care what
the hell and so i really don't
do
yeah i feel yeah i tried to
learn them all i guess i care
who is president well i care about
that in my current life and i'm
saying oh about knowing live yeah like
first one was this second one was
this guy right he believed the third
president really believed this it's like yo
i just don't like you tried to
memorize them all and i got i
got i got to a point where
i could go back to eighteen
ninety six recently like this is during
pandemic i was like i'm going every
day i'm gonna like go over these
again and now i can now i
i probably couldn't do it i think
stuff like that is good for memory
that's good i try to keep i
worked on the labeling all the states
on a map that didn't have i
call my guy suck it you make
during the early
pandemic days you're like let's make sure
we know this and i think there's
there's a couple that i mess up
every time but i probably should have
done that instead of eating all day
long and drinking a bottle of wine
every night sounds pretty good i wanna
say it was good while you have
oh yeah yeah let's what have we
the three of us decided we're gonna
a month of quarantine yes with each
other that's what we do hey that
sounds really by the way lauren call
mike so you're not coming over today
okay here right now yeah it starts
right now you've got more of this
wild
the joke was one corner of one
dan and laura yes yeah
um alright we have to take a
break we'll be right back okay
oh shit scott is getting his drink
on he's onto the beach flavor i'm
onto the beach laser that's going around
the world yeah why guys
lemon then the beach hey i didn't
look for a game did you idea
on one of three ter it turns
out three for everybody this is my
favorite part of the show lawrence river
park and scott's favorite part not to
mention the audience and people who just
heard of the show i think that
you know they love the idea of
a lord on the show love the
yeah this is a game called jitterbug
which is submitted by yoni gordon hi
yoni this is a game that yoni
thinks yoni invented okay well yoni when
you figure it out you know there's
a game that i think i invented
which is called jitterbug
yeah it's explaining like a little story
you one day beginning of the wham
song wake me up where they're just
the snaps and the word jitterbug jitterbug
jitterbug you have your iology above into
my bang bang scott you're going too
far oh no because well this game
involves singing the first few bars of
that song just the snaps in the
word jitterbug but each player needs to
go round robin placing a different three
syllable word or phrase in place of
the word jitterbug without missing a beat
in the song if you miss a
word you're out which we know you
can be out because there's no definitive
ending to this game okay okay how's
tara reid m by-laws okay let's do
it it does sound hard here's some
examples jitterbug litterbox cigarettes apple jam you
know what what are ya whoa sorry
obviously what you're not
here let me die is all wrong
so you could just say what
don't hurt me let's just see sing
that song okay instead of playing the
game yeah do you know anymore the
words nobody heard me na me know
that sketch became a movie
oh yeah and by the way it
should have been starring that song that
movie should have been a sketch
what movies do you think should have
just been a sketch ah probably lincoln
yeah i would say there will be
blood one hundred percent just a sketch
with you i would say my left
foot you'd still be in it though
yes okay ready and jitterbug
wait we gotta get the seam goes
jitterbug snap because jitterbug i thought okay
why don't you started okay then we'll
join in jannah bug snap snap so
you don't want to deface snap but
i'm trying to give you the rhythm
of it because you guys are going
i'm getting it from because that was
your jitterbug
jitterbug
because firebug i think it's wheat we
also jitterbug three times and then i
worried about all you think it was
the rhythm and then i'll start and
then it'll go clockwise okay okay jitterbug
jitterbug
monkey paw
jid but wait
wow am i supposed to do
i enjoy saying jitterbug oh okay start
over three jitter but then i start
and then right after you're yeah like
yeah really
a jitterbug ever again let's write okay
i want to see dude i know
you do okay here we go jitterbug
jitterbug
and f t
farting brain
make-a-wish
dallas door
ninety nine cents know what scott you're
out your oh farting brain is shut
to keep every yup keep snapping to
keep us over the alright
i mean it's like we make three
we let that slide let me die
phrase sammy yeah
please kill me
no one's ever said fighting brain no
one no one okay leave probably sadly
poor we do which isn't that movie
black swan no
what would you've got an oscar she
said yeah she's like no one there
done this before oh fighting band i
was that embarrassed me and made me
mad yeah then she was like ever
heard of the shins okay let's go
the yelled in a hole
bug
jitterbug
do you let's start here we go
oh my it a bug
jitterbug
spick and span
mr clean
roger that
fred rogers
miami alec oh no oh no no
i go alone bobby i like to
go along those lines yeah yeah yeah
here we go jitterbug
jayda bag
jitterbug
jatoba oh he forgot yeah
it's fun today just to say i'm
gonna start we don't need to go
back you start going again and then
we'll do a round of jitter
sap jitterbug
data book
jag
liquid death
nike shoe
little pants
just looking at things
you will feel your lego death chloride
huh
baby doll
oh no i'm still going oh
whoa you're yeah umbrella hum hold on
i'm still going
squirrel base let's do it again oh
i just think we need one more
chance and we'll go yeah
again yes other guy scott starts then
shoot them paul okay okay jitterbug
jitterbug
j bag
shock treatment
homeless man
bloody nose
umbrella
icba
icy hot
tasty freeze
frozen yo
oh frozen yeah rosie yo
you're out
okay alright jitterbug good luck
j bag
charlie dog
make goodies
mellencamp
john cougar
ah ed grimley
billy c
martin george
yeah other eighty eight half i see
are other nineteen eighty five s adele
cast members yoni was ahead yona thank
you so much but nobody around a
jitterbug okay here we go ready jitterbug
j bag
jitterbug it's going in time gym bag
jaded about it
shit about yeah let me go okay
go jitterbug
jitterbug
amy
jitterbug one more time jitterbug yay task
that was a great game we will
definitely revisit that when future do you
think will be nominated for a podcast
award for this episode fucking way we're
not the system is corrupt yeah it
really is alright thanks for listening everybody
and thank you for submitting three ch
rs if you'd like to submit one
we are three team usa gmail dot
com we're also on twitter not really
we're also on instagram to sign our
post on i never do either we
have a twitter account but we never
use it we used to use it
for three years now we just ask
for the voice yeah for the emails
we should we should get voicemails we
should get voicemails turn this into a
column i'm gonna google
little number yeah
scott's number yeah just i'll give out
my phone number let's just call him
home anytime of the day or night
i never answer it anyway so leave
a long long message go go like
where you get cut off and you
have to keep you have to call
back to it keep going do you
ever answer your phone i do it
all the time you do you do
it all the time yeah yeah i
never answer it
never they never answer why would anyone
though there was one that i ignored
um ignored ignore and it was from
a bimbos gibbins said you know something
say that when the who's calling something
say who he's calling who's coming away
like such a sure thing keeps turning
and then i was like huh well
i wonder why they're calling me then
just didn't i didn't pick it up
and then i saw the voicemail was
a spam thing like your car warranty
and then i looked at it and
it was actually it said ban if
it was cut off by the thing
you will say the bank is calling
you and will start obeying yes and
then dad wow then i was like
that's in your rulebook against that that's
a fucked up scale yeah p scams
and plan i can't with scams do
wow sam isn't happy ma'am me listen
to add to corner the card about
scam stories that we've been going here
i was saying to janie what is
going to be the thing that tricks
us when we are old people oh
i was wondering that too right scams
gonna get can't even imagine i mean
well a whole new thing everyone talks
so much
shut euro every once in a while
someone will sell now get it i'll
get an email or something and and
well coop got tricked by one the
other day where it was like ah
your power is being turned off well
that's a good trick right and it's
like you like power more power room
oh okay but it was like your
power is being turned off she she
did not call them back she sent
it to me and said is this
a thing and then i sent it
to to the people well yeah i
sent it to yeah the power people
power people red green blue yellow and
there and and there were like no
you don't even have an account with
us um
but like you have to be so
every single thing well what i found
is like anything that comes in you
can google it and within one second
it'll yes say like no this is
a scam you should not pay why
is there no law
it's almost like there are i think
there are laws how do we get
them we get these laws there's i
mean one of the things i like
is when you realize you can see
and you can spot it obviously like
there are certain markers like well amazon
is not going to text me yeah
yeah no shit like that um but
yeah
it's scary to think that there there's
gonna be something deep fakes maybe i
don't right yeah i don't know what
it will be but like at this
point we're one step ahead of him
we were gonna slip up at some
point we actually started a new episode
everybody thank you for listening and goodbye
well listen no notice subscribe wherever you
get podcasts and listen ad
free at stitcher premium dot com and
also ah seaworld dot com yeah bye
good-bye for forever fuck you know we're
never gonna do another show huh goodbye
ah
uh