st
what happened
not a precise science okay wow
it's not a precise science ah mahalo
wowed you that stressed me out why
did it stressed you out longer to
understand when he was counting down and
suddenly it was going oh what did
you think was happening a tiny rocket
ship is going
no i it's so small let's just
go from three
i just learned i just learned newcomers
that they just launched some fucking spy
rocket fuckin spy ragi spock a late
na rockets like lie elvish on the
like poster for it or elvis presley
wait
elvish language on the poster for like
or like the design what a terrible
spy
i don't know they had a name
that had artwork and it had a
logo and it had elvish on it
no thank you name artwork logo all
the markings of a spy plane and
really are used to still doing lord
of the rings oh yes i want
to commit suicide oh what is left
it's insane we're doing a video game
next week i mean
d and d were playing d and
d soon that makes sense this isn't
the place to advertise other podcasts though
this is three dogs now but it
is hard to talk about lord of
the rings for twenty episodes let's see
very close mistake you guys made it
mister hi we didn't want to do
it yeah it's hard to talk to
both of you for two i know
i know we just struggle to get
through god
that's me scott aquaman hello and over
there who just said that is of
tom console of tongans the monitor and
i'm more in love guess the recipient
i think i was the recipient of
that old in admonished by him more
than one that's true wow
i launched by more than what can
i just say for new merci season
three people are pitching a lot of
release scary ideas like doing all the
marvel movies and stuff but somebody said
we should do studio jubilee really scary
ideas i don't want to watch twenty
mar
no no you've you've never seen any
of the muslim maybe like you've never
seen ghostwriter no
every marvel movie not even the marvel
universe didn't show up in avengers and
he they didn't have the right zoom
they have him now though really yeah
yeah who had the rights ah that
charles m schulz
remember all the charlie brown cartoons use
him flaming head use a lot like
franklin who had all the flies buzzing
around him you know there's pig pen
you racist
mr his name is big ben
is i never heard the word
oh yeah it was frank pen franklin
frank franklin ben and frank p ren
just learn and you probably don't care
know what i'm talking about but that
daniel tiger the cartoon is from mr
ross yeah yeah i did not understand
part of the mister rogers extended universe
i used pin friday i alone make
it
actor daniel tiger yeah i've never connected
that that was show was that well
because usually when you see him you
don't see mister rogers hand up his
ass that's true
but yeah i mean what yeah i
mean what yeah yeah meant was the
fact of life grow up
um welcome back to the show we're
here outside again and we are ready
we are outside again
outside again but we have ah where
we have helicopter remixes that you've sent
in at the ready if a helicopter
ever comes around again so i got
in fact i'm gonna get those rates
shoot up hell yeah hit one right
now your one right now and i
do it yeah i don't know it's
not that close
okay so far away it just feels
like a waste i mean i feel
like if we're hearing it on the
headphones the the listener's hearing as well
now
nah no bare na na da da
da da da da da da da
da hey
but they already and oh shit they're
not ready because i just clicked out
of shall we talk about our clocks
let's talk about our clocks let's talk
about crocs baby let's talk about you
left and right but
oh okay i got my crocs in
the mail and i got i got
the glare i'm sorry let's give a
little background because i think our name
has happened off show we talk wait
oh wow
now that's a try that's a truck
we need truck jingles send them in
um ah we we we discuss crocs
on a previous episode um and then
off off mike in in our in
our classic text thread we discussed all
buying crocs and then we all and
then we all day yes well here's
here's more precise
mostly what happened is we are going
to say you buck i want to
slap some of your signature precision on
it we all talked about it on
mike and ah then the clip that
we we played ah to advertise the
show was about us talking crocs and
that got me thinking i gotta get
into those crocs so yeah i bought
some and i sent
you guys ah a screencap of of
the amazon purchase and we suddenly all
three of us within twenty minutes at
all bought crocs yeah and we'd christian
ourselves the crocodile crew we absolutely had
and i got the crocodile silver glitter
crocs which i thought were going to
be made
of member jellies though yes i don't
think i really don't think you are
but i somehow don't think you're ready
you remember jelly they'd be that glitter
where it's like in the material yes
but there it should run top show
really no that's ridiculous and they don't
exactly fit my feet so i think
i have to say
dart over sheriff yeah um but but
paul is wearing his org my side
of the street clocks and they look
really good i am the only one
wearing crocs i thought we were all
gonna wear them i was gonna wear
i'm just even show you how they
didn't fit and i have to walk
around these medicinal shoes
well i was like it's like my
feet bug burnt burned in a fire
well you're also wearing bright pink socks
because i'm fashionably well also like your
feet have been burned up and their
bright pink what happened to getting the
flame ones or the banana come on
i was never going to get those
oh wow i thought you were saying
this is it here's our first helicopter
renee never my honest jams here we
go
uh
like a mother
perfect covered it up perfectly well
it's really good i like how we're
all on it
ah um but i got the crocs
and i had assumed we were all
going to try them on on the
show wow
because you're the only person who's never
tried them all i didn't realize that
i'm the only person who's never tried
i've always looked to them by the
way when i bought them longingly cool
up was aghast oh really she because
she our amazon account is through her
emails so she gets all the receipts
for everything and she was like what
is this ah yeah that's it
i want to say that i mean
that's totally valid to be upset about
that yeah we made a case for
them that she didn't hear you know
so yeah it's true she wasn't ready
to shit but i i now i
have an excuse for almost anything i
do i just say it's for a
podcast yeah so when i was like
when you were like said why nudes
watching the bachelor read i'm like it's
for a podcast yeah anything that she
upset about it for a podcast so
she not watched the bachelorette she hates
it although i will say she sits
you know depending on the promo for
that week you know if it's very
dramatic she'll be like oh i can't
believe you're watching dimensional sit there and
watch yeah most yeah what a hypocrite
yeah she is i didn't want to
say that to her shoes on now
ow jeez yeah this is exciting so
this is scott's first experience well rocks
the plasma prohibitively expensive i think cool
off was anyone loud was anyone else
surprised they arrived in a bag and
not a box ah no i guess
i'm in a box o bag that
was in a box i ordered from
the cr
ocs website and they arrived in a
bag weird that is wow is this
another helicopter yes ok here we go
play the other one here we go
the standby jack's junior talent
the helicopter flies above us
nah you look like a fuss
nah
a samba
nah you can either do that strap
on the front or back
i was just sixteen i just really
about to ask that yes i've really
come to despise my laugh as a
result oh my god wait tell me
how you feel in your crockpot before
we hear scott trey hits ah well
that you know i have experienced with
crocs they're incredibly comfortable um they're like
walking on a cloud as we've discussed
yeah i didn't i
i did not go for the ones
with the um with the holes in
them eye holes in the top of
mind you'll hold on the top you
can add gems later you can adjust
your scott yeah means there's all these
little things you can put in the
holes and decorate them oh cool i
was saying that she was going to
buy some for me to make me
like fall rick out by crocs or
something bored now she's not
yeah you embarrassed me our friendship j
yeah it's like ah a million amazing
gem hers appealing out yeah yeah i
just wear them outside or does she
just wear them around the house i
think she wears them outside interesting so
so i'm kinda i went with a
navy blue yes and you can wear
these straps in the front or the
back which would you suggest it kind
of depends on how it feels
oils on your foot okay i'm gonna
i'm gonna go off mike and i'm
gonna put these on okay okay well
can you describe it
he's getting old yet for some reason
he's starting with his belt
scott is he's already he's got him
on he's in them strapping the front
walk around he's standing up to watch
your awesome birds
what do you think
what do you think kiddo
what do you think are there going
to be good for school i mean
they are very comfortable that rice there's
no way around it sure being an
old man over here to touch your
toe
i mean it's just a metal thing
with the slide and try straps in
the back didn't you always kind of
like putting your friend that metal thing
i love to me i loved it
it felt good and yes it was
very snug it was like having a
squeeze machine like in tipping yeah and
it's like they like they kind of
rub that like metal thing like down
your foot yeah there was when you
went to buster brown where i used
to go to shore
did we talk about this oh yeah
you go the sharky sharky but did
we talk about the x-ray machine
yeah we did that that like supposedly
took a look at your feet maybe
we did or not but it's basically
radiation coming out of these horrible out
of the ground of of every buster
brown do you think it was just
at that buster brown there was a
foot fetishist who managed the store and
they were sitting inside to these feet
they were just pictures of feet like
did they show you the extra
that's great yeah they show it too
and they go and they go oh
okay this this makes it look like
you need this type of and and
they told me i had very narrow
feet which i guess the only way
that is this another helicopter it is
another helicopter we i think we have
another winning today and let's see what
this is this is nasty and gmc
yeah this has nothing to do with
health
copters but it is good okay it
was completely dark for like black list
thing
and then a creepy white guy with
dreads really nasty looking
nice sent by jordan same part
nasty
boy ass
this goes on for quite a while
i've gotta save some of it so
yeah see some of it the best
songs are listened to in installments twenty
seconds
what are those um growing foods right
there what are those growing foods ah
it is mysterious to me i don't
want to categorize it as fruit or
vegetable i can't see what you're looking
at prob well there's two rounds hanging
off of some tall six
oh those aren't fruit
and that's not my finger um i
don't know there's lemons over there that's
about an apple could be a tomato
neither one makes sense to me because
they're so tall and and high yeah
i have no idea um sounds like
me tall and high ah but i
can i say that i like the
straps in the back better yeah yeah
you can say that yeah see
i think with mine i don't want
to get a bigger i think i
mean maybe maybe they make crux narrow
so the problem for you is the
you're like banging around the sides yeah
but then my toe is in the
end and if i put the strap
on one then it's over because i
can't i have no room to really
move so do they make narrow crocs
crocs if you're listening
and we need help crocs just said
no they don't make they don't they
don't seem to make half sizes and
i'm a half huh so i want
to size up and they seem i
want to size up to yeah they
seem to be all right yeah i
think mine are good ah and are
good they they they're also unisex they
say yeah i don't like that yeah
i don't like what's
putting my feet in some a woman
would put their feet and do what
if i would if i go to
the supermarket there's another some broad where
does she was aware okay there's at
crocs dot com you'll find a roomy
relaxed and standard fits roomy so whether
you're a narrow size or wide you'll
find the perfect fit for you our
roomies fit just like our original style
claude some models include a heel hugging
backstop for more instability you're looking backstrap
yeah extra should do it they say
that narrow so she didn't they say
that now rising i might be able
to ah get myself some narrows get
some narrows and getting in and no
glitter yeah i get the glitter once
it was you know shedding onto my
couch
really knew i'd maybe yeah well why
are your crocs on the cow because
that's where i was trying them on
what's the perfect thing for you you
like to stand on your couch to
try on shoes right yeah i do
would it be tied i or would
be rainbow or what do you wow
it's like see here's the thing i
don't really i felt that the glitter
would actually minimize my foot in a
way while also being
being a fun shoe but tie it's
like wearing clown shoes it's going to
look yeah big and crazy so i
got basic black by the way because
i'm a basic bitch one case you
have to go to a funeral yeah
oh you don't want to save nine
what the holes in the top why
i went to ah see what they
gained me the trinkets did it was
the trinkets are the no because it's
not like an air can come in
right air come in there can come
in where there's holes there's air
you go back in water i um
also heard someone someone commented that if
you walk on the beach and those
it's like you don't think at all
okay guess we gotta do an episode
at the beach yeah meaning like a
like on wet sand now or dry
streisand dry like you could just walk
down the beach and like you float
into
casting okay we we gotta get some
either some sand here who said there's
a ghost i mean i don't know
who was the who was the commenter
i don't know who was the ghost
i tell you about the funeral i
went to and i didn't have any
black clothes ah this is my pre
goth phase and and so we're like
oh whites oh my oh yeah i
was like thirteen like wow i didn't
have any answer i had a new
white jacket so i was like alright
i'll just and white jeans and so
today window thing you could do did
anyone comment on it no but i
think people were ah alright we gotta
play some of the rest of this
a bit more nasty
but i think people are looking askance
at me i would think so
this this
this okay
is this song every time we've said
nasty is high and other people i
think it's probably
it's lesser people to ah i'm why
don't we put that whole thing at
the end of the episode okay sure
people can hear it uninterrupted sure thing
any of any fun funeral stories that
you've been a part of you know
what i was reminded of this the
other day i was a i had
my first contemporary of mine
mine died this was in the ninety
s first like friend of mine that
died and i was asked to be
a pall bearer me and i frown
because of your name that's correct
it was all pulse
it was also my name's paul simon
when the grass single word it's like
really heavy for a couple of people
because there's not enough pulse oh yeah
exactly all all poles of the same
height and this is what people don't
realize and that's why they're perfect to
be pallbearers can i of course mention
dance like in the meme
have you both been pallbearers before i
have yes i really um i don't
know what i mean it feels like
i'd be really hard emotionally but also
physically and also because it likes looking
at you lifting a thing and because
it's not a thing well i mean
you could probably like lift a dead
body with two people so
so to have so sounds like it's
that heavy it's more i feel like
it's it seems really um just emotionally
heavy it is and it's it's a
very but i think that because you
are focused so much on not fucking
up yeah that that aspect of it
ah is is put on hold for
a second
now will you be shocked to learn
there's more to my story why actually
i'm not shocked because i interrupted you
about one second into it
i kinda like it because i was
the center of the attention for the
future yeah apart you would like that
which you like being the center of
attention someone's dinner and afterwards at the
wake you're like you know gcc when
i google yes see i carried that
when people say hello to use a
it's a pleasure to meet a fan
um my friend adam and i
a ah we were in our early
twenties and we of course we were
both friends with the deceased and we
got extremely drunk the night before the
funeral and we overslept ooh overslept to
be pallbearers was there an alarm set
or
or was it just like oh we'll
wake up and ah i don't know
i don't remember if there was an
alarm set i don't i don't know
if we thought that far ahead and
we slept through it or if we
just just were fucking stupid and we
um we got who we got there
too late ah so it was he
was already in the ground now
no we were allowed to be we
were allowed to be pallbearers on the
backend oh okay so they had several
receiving it from the service to the
grave they had to call surface down
with my tupac album yeah i was
thinking youtube from the servers to low
gray una it's rod stewart know it
is going to oh was it
yeah yeah yeah i wanna do oh
well alright but remember yeah when i
drop the service joe gray off my
roadster
instead of like riff raff
never heard pronounced that way riff raff
is very classy but i think if
raf what are you doing i feel
like i've heard it pronounced that way
maybe i did put it in my
mind that way because it's it supposedly
his name as opposed to referring to
him as riff raff right i guess
i've always just made do they ever
call him riff raff in it or
does not
in it i i don't know if
i've ever heard it out loud you
know what i'm talking about lauren um
no but i could guess yeah go
ahead and guess okay um my first
guess is by the way this should
be an ongoing thing you know the
whole it's got her talking about if
somebody doesn't know what the other people
are talking about you just guess yes
my
first guess is that it's from fat
albert
yeah i mean i can't play guesses
go like nah i can't believe you
i mean didn't it wasn't were there
was much mouth in that so much
smell not much mouth mouth what are
you up to dumb donald my next
guess is that um donald it's frostbite
again with his right
my next guess is that it's from
a rap group no that's that's good
not bad either you could be part
of the clan or yeah thank you
hundred and family
okay my third guess is that it's
from a sitcom
now you're you're getting so general you
started very useful
or like johnny genre it's from the
dictionary notes from earth
oh you got it right yeah boy
you could you could say yes i
could keep going it is not from
not from a sitcom okay see let's
not waste my time
oh sorry
i hate to tell you what show
you're on ah okay my next guest
dan wow this really changed i mean
at this point is it from a
comic strip know so the two ways
that
what do you mean to hold on
i've got a lot of ways huh
okay riff raff it's just a lot
of voices tv show or comic strip
this is the do things like i've
guessed rap group i've guessed a specific
show um think of okay wait i
don't know
it's like a baseball made it last
longer is it basically
it's buddy okay it's a it's called
the persons called riffraff but they're never
called that to their face and we
were saying in the thing it's a
movie there you go oh
what's the movie
you're supposed to guess
okay is it from the eighties no
no ninety s no no seventy s
yes and the movie is called
you're sucking all the fun out of
this game
oh i was gonna guess it the
movie's called can i can i can
give you a hint yeah it's a
musical oh man i was like oh
no no oh why cats just came
out last year
um riffraff quarantine has broken lloris bref
street rats scoundrel take that yes dell
yeah that's it you got it what's
that aladdin oh come on i don't
know i should we just tell her
no oh okay yeah yeah you'll tell
me first how many will how many
awards and okay
five
why five words in the movie yes
ma'am can you imagine
back in the seventies there were so
many words in movie titles oh the
full sentences sometimes yeah okay i don't
bring me the head of alfredo garcia
um i don't know the rocky horror
picture show i never would have guessed
that richard o'brien the creator yes the
musical plays a character named
riff raff or riff raff wow
and we're but i as someone must
say that's riff raff like to introduce
him to barry bostwick and susan saran
i don't feel just like tim curry
must say that guys rip well tim
curry comes in so late that i
think riff raff has been no but
he must address them at some point
riff right now i don't know i
imagine it rip right
rough i don't know watch rocky horror
and like dress up and like sing
along i never dressed up but when
i was fifteen ah my friend and
i were both very into these two
girls in our drama department and i
had a super huge crush
as autumn and they how can we
impress these girls no but i'm going
to wear black lipstick
they like to go to it so
i asked my parents if i could
go and they were like not satanic
they were like as long as there
is violence and swearing but no sex
are there any abortions and but they
also part of the problem was as
it was starting a midnight i think
i'd want to clock curfews so there's
no way when i was fifteen that
was why
i am curfew is possible but on
the weekends i think it was so
ah so so i instead because they
like to go and i just really
wanted to spend time with her um
instead i would sneak out my window
ah hey how's the weather up there
oh and then
then then like there were all these
precautions that i had to take so
so basically i do like open my
window punch out the screen that was
on it and then we didn't punch
it out but you know push it
like i know roddy kick
master and then your one leg would
fall out the window uv high crotch
for oil i would do a jumping
three sixty spin kick out the window
but then i would have to there
was our our back gate i would
have to like lift up so it
would have silently you did knock that
out with my fist
karate chop it because it was good
and then my my friend who drove
me would have to park like four
doors down so i wouldn't get out
because my parents window was right on
the street their bedroom window yeah so
i and then i would walk down
the street come back in and when
i would the the only issue was
putting the screen back on
yes from the inside was really tough
there would always be a corner sticking
out so i would have to then
the next day when i woke up
hope that my parents didn't see there
was a corner sticking out of the
screen how would they have seen that
because they're nosy so they would post
has been established as you can be
like they would have been like hey
what's going on with this with the
screen
what is your scott we need to
talk about the screen corner yeah exact
stressful so they would have seen that
and then put it together and been
like oh you you went outside your
thing so the next day i would
have to like make an excuse to
take out the garbage or something which
because my guard the garbage cans are
right outside my window and then like
punch the screen backend wow
but it worked i did it like
probably twenty times or something like that
and she'd never ah likes me back
it didn't even work
i saw it i think i started
once in in theaters i think i
went to one midnight showing at the
theater of the living arts in philadelphia
pennsylvania but you didn't dress up i
never dressed no i didn't i don't
think i knew about that aspect of
it until i got there it was
all new like i didn't know about
the yelling of the screen i didn't
know about throwing toast and all that
shit i had no idea so it
was like i was probably seventeen something
like that and it when i was
seventeen i always been the rocky horror
picture show and the two that seventy
whore was looking now i don't know
what that is showing i guess yes
no i just started saying oh would
you say oh you didn't hear me
i know this is great this like
ah taylor swift nope no katy perry
no
other woman singer
oh have i named both
both of the popular ones now i
don't know i'll never get well yeah
guess a decade ninety s no o
two thousand know oh eighties no seventy
s yell sixty s you know yeah
forty s no seventy s somewhere in
the set okay seventy s sing it
again learn the truth
gene the love was made bobby queens
then ah da na na na na
na na na na si no anna
and um i know i can't place
it janis ian at seventeen janis ian
she has two first names and one
male
and she sang in the sooner she
sang another song no she stepped in
the booth like this sounds amazing he
was high she's on the new jersey
boardwalk is one of those make your
own record boots somebody found it lying
in the sand they're wearing crocs otherwise
they wouldn't fill my god i went
in in fifth grade i went to
six flags and they had a carry
oh wait slow down with the math
five six with what is it in
fifth grade i went eleven jags i
was in seventh heaven
hey um karaoke booth where you could
record ah by the way here comes
another helicopter
pardon the door i know there's only
no part of this that would be
made better by me just telling my
story now sorry for the delay but
hey my computer needs to wake up
when i
so maybe you should start playing at
first and then announce it so as
opposed to announcing it again then playing
and then we wait for yeah like
the series on the computer this okay
well you are in control up so
there's nothing we can do about it
um go ahead with your story you
were fine was it if in fifth
grade
flags and i got to go to
this um thing that was like a
booth where you could record a song
on a cd to cool up change
the flag is that what you're pushing
did yeah she did it this morning
i believe with the new and genre
i get there yeah
and you get a flags
there's a trend there's one reported that's
fine five more
bop by oh did you really you
in one friend yeah because dan henderson
is a trio friends oh it was
a friend and her sister and then
the sister saying like a virgin ou
on her track but and there's two
of you that sang bob three all
three of okay three
so did she pay for her trek
solo or did you all chip in
i think the following everything three were
all of it to happen from my
you know my mom or mom's have
to pay ever pay her back i
don't think so but yeah you know
i do wonder how much that would
cost it seems like kind of special
i did it in the mall i
sang careless whisper
her and i gave it to my
grandmother as a christmas present wow she
loved to hear me saying wow god
i love to use she she loved
to hear me swinging swing speaking swing
though she also hear you i also
like gave her a tape of nat
king cole i think for christmas and
she was very impressive today
ah like one step over the writing
the lyrics and saying oh yeah really
this is based on forgettable ah um
but she was she i remember her
saying i'm very impressed you know this
music this is my generation's music
it's like yeah no shit
grandma that's cute but it's cute i
tell you the other rocky horror pictures
show story by the way you did
okay
i have no idea i just accepted
that i was like i guess he's
told it so my uncle who is
my cool uncle uncle i used to
go over over to his house all
the time he had like us not
slot machines but like these slot machines
slot machines yes he would slap my
fanny
and he'd call it a machine
thanks for the quarter
who got a quarter
did it come onto your bug you
know i get this game if i
put it in his mouth and he
slaps slips my baby
so he he used to have ah
i think select tv or on tv
i can't remember which one it was
this was pre hbo ah it was
like the first kind of premier movie
ah thing that you could get at
home where where you could ah but
and this is previously ours and everything
so it's basic
early like a box you had to
put on your tv it's pre tivo
ah it's a pre pre can demand
of ah definitely before cats um so
he used to tape movies all the
time and and we would watch him
that's where i first saw bad news
bears and all sorts of stuff but
he i remember him saying he taped
the rocky horror picture show and his
only
on once oh yes i did tell
you i don't remember what happens but
i remember a long time ago you
telling me okay so he only it
was only on once and it was
a special event but and so he
tape he taped this i guess it
wasn't previously or because he could tape
things a special event yeah so they
they it was like we're only gonna
broadcast this once on select tv or
whatever it's halloween
mean and so he taped it and
he would say oh yeah i have
a tape of that and i remember
cool uncle also taped cool movies on
tv and it was like really awesome
like like well like things that i
would like like alison wonderland the live
action with um what's her name ah
i remember this oh bill
with carol channing oh yeah he knew
yeah and then he would just tape
things that he thought i would like
and then i would get the the
v h s and it was so
cool cause i didn't have hbo and
the suis yeah we didn't have a
vcr so we had to go over
to his house to watch the stuff
so and then my parents wouldn't let
me
watch rocky horror picture show but i
filed it in the back of my
mind that he had taped it so
when i was seventeen or sixteen maybe
but i was sixteen my uncle taped
the rug
oh did your parents care what you
watched no they weren't the only time
i think i've said this before the
only time they ever my mother ever
gave a restriction on something we could
watch was my brothers and i wanted
to watch psycho and she wouldn't let
us watch it now one sounds like
it's going to be a little much
so i mean just from the title
like zoo
yes leica
so that's where we get that phrase
just everyone knows jacinda there is no
such thing as psychotic before that movie
and now that is where and that's
where we get that phrase i feel
like the movie made psychotic i do
wonder though like it made it easy
to say did was it the first
and so people like i'm gonna be
that
was it the first thing that took
the tick off
i beg your pardon what psychotic when
you mean to the attic
you know what i mean it's the
oddest thing that tick tick tick yeah
yeah so they it was at the
first but where on the popular culture
to shorten psychotic to psycho what are
other things that have tick or you're
just saying that var tick oh well
you hide under there was it the
first thing that ever taught me something
oh that's psychotic love it and i
was kidding but i do i don't
think so i feel like psycho had
to be a word before that maybe
alright well the sentosa you're i'm sure
when it's i'm talking about i'm talking
to you don't sound effects what is
your opinion my opinion
ah carefully usbs it's gonna come an
airy socks um but so i i
told my friend who is in drama
with me oh yeah my uncle tapes
the rocky horror picture show teaches love
to drop
you know the word did gain further
notoriety after the release of psycho further
but it was in let's clay before
link so hey so i told my
friend this and he goes oh my
god this is great can you borrow
it because i have two vcr is
and i'll tape a copy
e oh shit give it to my
friend for christmas
and i was like um yeah sure
i'll ask my uncle this was a
special event yeah but i was just
like yeah sure i'll ask my uncle
so i asked my uncle and he
goes oh let me look around for
it and it took like two weeks
or something he was like i'm sorry
i just can't find it it was
like okay no problem thanks and i
called my friends i remember i was
like hey
sorry my uncle can't find it and
he goes
ah no
i'm like what do you mean he's
like no that's not good enough
wow what is good what do you
mean he goes well you said your
uncle had a tape of it right
so i'm gonna need your uncle to
get me a tape of this
that is
so weird so i was like what
do you how do you mean he
goes call your uncle ask him to
look again until he finds it because
you promise me that i could get
a tape of this and now my
friend isn't going to get his christmas
present because you have failed me wow
it's just how i was czar that
guy as a saigon which comes from
the greek word psycho meech means meant
to me which means many species j
t although the word has long been
used as a prefix and words like
psychologists the pejorative term for a psychopath
has only exe
listed since the twentieth century nice the
word gained further notoriety after nineteen sixty
release of psycho amazing well may that
gives us close bay is suis la
so the se
doe ray
buy me a we have today break
we'll be right back
people babu people huh i'm up here
i'm down here okay
oh boo welcome back high scree ice
cream is that from music man sees
just sustain na ok na ice crea
i know we've talked about this but
my ah old drama teacher really wanted
you to go i know we've talked
about this by the way be papa
bubba
la bo bottom so yeah around hopping
around yeah that is
hey this is nice i'm the loudest
person that's breezy i'd be so upset
yeah yeah yeah but my drama teacher
of whom we will not speak um
voldemort he ah he was talking about
commitment to your craft when we all
got into drama in ninth grade and
he was like when we did the
music man
three years ago the four people who
played the barbershop quartet oh yeah walked
they learned how to do ah barbershop
harmonies we taught them how to do
that and to practice they would walk
around school together and only respond in
barbershop harmony away to anyone i don't
know and that's commitment to your craft
and that's how
and it oh god and i was
just like they have any friends i
doubt it but it really instilled in
me like each had three friends that
and probably when i learned that weezer
learned did the same thing they've learned
how to do barbershop harmonies in order
to do their complex harmonies for the
songs it made
made me want to start a barbershop
quartet with you i believe i'd like
wasn't you doug benson and me and
one other person we were all talking
about yeah let's do this let's do
this i joined to me
i don't remember this at all i
know it was me and once i've
bent so it was definitely mean doug
benson were like yeah let's do this
let's figure out how to sort of
does yeah doesn't let scorn i've never
heard her shop cortez i feel like
you want to start with someone who
definitely seeing but i think we were
just like well this was also when
we were doing that musical like around
then yes um
so i think we were just like
yeah let's do it let's figure out
how to do barbershop quartet and walk
around like argo just doing barbershop courts
editing all the time let's be like
these four actually from my high school
from approximately nineteen eighty one and probably
when they did that what an absurd
story and then to share it like
this is the kind of thing you
should be doing
seeing is inflicting this on other people
although otherwise you're not dedicated is what
makes it absurd is it the fact
that they were fourteen fifteen years old
because if yes like christian bale were
to do it whatever yeah i think
he's absurd too
ah yes now i want the secrets
and bill doing this he was just
me any sin incense
um do you want me to play
this thing lauren that day as he
wants do you wanna set this up
apparently okay so jen i understand you
brought a clip i product clip jensen
karp tweeted this and it's a but
it's a music video it's a song
sung by a woman about i'm
dating a jewish person at christmas and
it's really sincere and specific and it's
joe i only wear where christmas is
approaching but we're not because we're in
the midst of hanukkah right now arrive
so and he crazy nights i just
have watched this and i was like
i just want to hear it with
you guys because i found it to
be so so you basically
like turn something on half watching were
like i'm going to save this i
want to hear this with all it's
got yeah alright i wanna see what
my reaction is and i want to
see what the reaction of my friends
is alright here we go
ah this this
oh be some ride huh
jewish day
e
karzai see
uh she she's talking to other people
and then now she's talking to him
yeah are we still there
singing
i'd rather hear her sing
clothing
b
nah three
i don't like to hear that word
coming out of her mouth the super
weird like i mean get that far
to see now
bottom line guess no he won't be
saying merry christmas
he says shah i simply mean
this chris from him saying shallow
just as he like observance that's the
other thing it's like nah alone yeah
and she can't do anything that she
normally would do you can't roast chestnuts
know you're dating me and i'm jewish
too
yeah is he is he telling her
or is she offering all this shit
like say honey you know yes like
oh do what you want to do
also
uh
sure other stuff as well
so she's suing up the two
she seems to be like a forty
five year old white damage
picture of hers i would sure i'm
ah there's a video attached and it's
it's a pretty well produced video wearing
q i'm like oh what you meant
oops what man paid for this yeah
you have to wonder how this guy
he's definitely did you yeah no know
he's got money shalom let video i
wish i'd said
i the ironic racism yep now
nope well it's born about it okay
i'm the guy you're done you're done
i'm done with it ah i'm done
i'm finished i don't want to i
don't want to contribute to that dumb
shit yeah take withdraw from it i
withdraw i've i hear about withdrawal oh
withdrawal saturday
well thank you for sending us this
it's ah you're welcome it's ah you
know ah i mean i thought it
was weird i just thought it was
weird and you know something in the
holiday spirit also if you're trying to
know she's trying to be funny right
i don't get that i mean the
videos she's very sincere in but i
will say
say like she mentioned santa i think
and you see holding you mentioned send
him like holy on my hands gesturing
like alas poor yorick like he's experiencing
are you about santa but she's she's
she's ah i mentioned this because she
mentioned santa and behind her in the
window you see like santa passing by
like
not stopping the house so maybe it's
funny i don't think it is but
sometimes i just don't think it's funny
i think it's just it feel utterly
say it was funny but also if
you're trying to come up with a
new christmas standard like the melody can't
just be data dot da da da
da what child is this come on
oh that's a hunting
melody if that were a regular song
he would be popular that should be
a halloween melody ooh ooh ooh whether
we're talking greensleeves what child is this
well i mean it's very spooky it
fits in with the telling ghost stories
that we all do a christmas scary
ghost stories we've got gotta save some
of this material for our christmas episode
next
this week but that's true but but
it is the christmas season certainly the
cs is real what's real this woman
it's real she she recorded a christmas
album and that's on it but wait
i thought she couldn't do christmas stuff
oh wow
she's all over the map
i think her name is sandy baynham
okay that's a joke name come on
come on sandy baynham oh i get
i have a sandy bain game in
me this christmas okay it was from
twenty twelve genre easy listening not kabul
certainly wisdom
oh
do
what's due oh okay she made an
album that is all diwali just happened
yesterday did yes this is this recording
it's a celebration of light in the
darkness oh i'd like to celebrate that
and light coming you missed goodness shit
alright okay but she's done the man
with the bag sleigh ride song for
christmas and then i
thank you for your love which i
think is the please don't tag her
and snitch no shot tag please we
don't need to snitch tag do as
good with brushy one string because we
got yes kickstarter goal exactly but we
don't want to help this woman
i just i don't need to know
your here's this is a real thing
don't go tagging people that aren't being
tagged in conway chicken blocks um one
my dick in a box vs justin
timberlake yeah parody my taser logs jay
gone down to lockdown is justin timberlake
everyone's favorite comedian mine week
oh i always can i tell you
this i apropos of the christmas season
depictions of santa claus on commercials for
adult things like cars stuff like okay
drives me fucking i hate because it's
juvenile so when you see like
santa giving someone a cossack cute it's
not funny but to think that maybe
just maybe if you opened your heart
a little bit you could see that
those commercials are also for kids
you think a car commercial is for
a kid they might be watching tv
and it just readers have already sent
a job whatever way you think a
commercials for whomever watches it
he might be watching tv but it
reinforces the idea that santos real
yeah okay gives me that reinforce wait
so you think you think a car
company there they want to sell they
want to sell it you'll take sar
g several different actors playing santa claus
but they have a responsibility to children
i think as a kid i didn't
even conceive
order them looking different like i didn't
care that there were all these different
looking so because i always knew that
people in commercials were actors it's like
no no that's like an actor playing
santa but he's one of surreal setups
the real set is he wouldn't do
this but like if i went to
see santa at the mall
i don't i never considered he looks
different than the other sigh always cause
it was right oh yeah i don't
think i thought that i always knew
that that was a guy playing santa
you know i can't remember if i
knew yeah maybe i don't i just
don't know i believed in santa i
think but i always knew
yes i'm so sad all those letters
unreturned but i i always use you
always ask for a response when you
put please you had to get back
right on your house to santa stop
here i wanna hear that you received
my instruction that you're going to follow
them thank you in advance i hate
when people say thank you in advance
i thank
me when i do something
but santa and i have not done
it and sometimes i don't want to
do it thank me no i'm not
gonna do it doesn't imply you're gonna
do it it's more thanks for know
i think thank you in advance is
you have to do this and here's
a reminder here's like a polite way
of saying this is mandatory while it's
saying thank you in advance saying you're
going to
do this yeah yeah you know what
i mean like this is there's no
wiggle room here thank you in advance
for doing this you have because there
you know because i told you to
do it and you're gonna do it
yeah and i'm being nice by saying
thank you in advance it's knocked i
hate it back back to santer yeah
i am about to tweet this because
i'm interested in hearing people's
responses what's your lead time on tweets
seems to be about six hours i
plan all my tweets twenty four hours
events okay so i'm gonna try my
hand first and draw the gif yes
i say draw the frames of the
gif
um the herridge twitter would be deleted
yes i mean it would be great
to have it taken off of my
hands i want someone to take i'm
not gonna do us yeah no no
no i'm not going do yeah yeah
i think it would be a blessing
anyway um parents who they just don't
understand who won't tell their kids about
at santa claus because they they don't
like the idea of lying to their
children oh yeah right i want to
know are there people that felt this
way and then realize like um overthinking
this this is like a magical thing
that i'm taking away from my trying
to do something magical i think yes
even as a kid like i believe
dueling ferries and things like it
it's fun like it doesn't have to
be that serious yeah it's not you're
not want the idea of stretching that
to be lying to your job yeah
so extreme i do remember being five
or six and i think my parents
let it slip that that santa wasn't
real or something and i was like
you've been lying to me and then
within
in two seconds i think i got
over it yeah because you still get
a ton of presence yeah and the
same thing with the two ferry i
knew the tooth fairy wasn't real but
still i wanted those quarters on what
those quarters i want today pull my
teeth
i think it's complicated when you have
parents who are one is jewish and
one is one celebrates christmas because then
you kind of have that conflicting energy
of like what do we go with
here right well i if if it
were me i would go with both
foreshore yeah mo don't use people to
go away it's just great we get
the best
asked both well yeah but then maybe
ah no i think a lot of
people do that but i think the
decision to full force go with santa
as a thing is complicated i do
think it's i have a cousin that
converted to judaism we hope scott berkeley's
do you think that's more complex than
explaining the birth
of christ
i mean
you're saying so what are the rules
with santa yeah jewish people have enough
other things to explain well no i'm
saying that it's santa is like a
fun magical thing yeah as opposed to
getting into the the the the differences
between religion actual reason for the holiday
right which is that this person was
born to be this
savior of mankind well i feel i
feel like i being raised in a
religious household like there were concurrent tracks
like the whole santa thing was being
explained concurrently along with like but the
real reason for the for this yes
we yeah we had a manger and
to the point where i i bought
a manger for our house even though
i'm not
religious anymore i just like having it
at christmas time yeah so we have
an activity scene or some people say
natively seen some people say natasha vt
who did the tea but i think
i'm a tie i think it would
be so hard to try to yeah
converts to another religion i know that
some people
i'll do it just simply because like
i'm marrying someone and they they cannot
like they are so religious they cannot
marry someone of another religion and so
his kiker name so i converted you
know but i just think it would
be so hard it seems like would
you ever really if you were to
be the one converting it would you
ever really believe in the other thing
that's hard and i think some people
really do when they get hurt but
i think when you're converting for a
relationship that's less likely that you're like
fully believing all of the right stuff
i mean maybe there are some people
who are like ooh this is a
cool religion i like this you know
oh my cherry a problem was like
i might feel that way mister belvedere
mr bellwood john is a man with
his balls wow
i don't know this is a doug
benson thing there's expensive toys really good
all ties my girls i know jackie
kay tweeted this really great story at
one point about her audition for two
two seven did you accidentally go to
two to six yeah but she was
like hey thanks for that she was
flung
it was just a great story and
you can google it's just puts why
don't you tell us i don't remember
all the great details but part of
it was just like she went um
she got to fly in a private
you know not premature to fly to
new york and they were buying her
ticket to go for the sedation it
was like really exciting and she then
she realised there were a
a lot of women who are being
flown on that flight to go for
this also it was like the i
forget what her character name was but
me too but then she gets there
to your name
me too d too
she did the whole audition and how
reviews auditioning for a different part originally
but then she ah they let her
out she died thing i'm i'm telling
it horribly yeah okay detail stuck did
she did she have a weird voice
like that she leaned into yes and
like that and then they really
really liked that right yeah you seem
to think like that's always fascinating like
stephanie beatrice ah for foe yeah for
brooklyn nine-nine like when you find out
she doesn't actually talk like that and
she or brad garrett on everybody loves
raymond when you hear their real voices
it's like holy shit you guys have
the balls to go into this audition
and with a
voice that's not yours well you know
stephanie beatriz was sick oh really yeah
she went in she had she was
psycho she was like getting over
she added about psychosis altered her voice
she was ah i think she's getting
over bronchitis or something like that but
she told a story on spontaneous asia
okay and i had i didn't know
that either and um then she had
to commit to that voice wow like
a choice she just had to she
just happened and then she had to
commit to that
that voice so brad carrots is like
so strict because it's so different because
his voice is like it's really different
yeah he's like yeah anyway blah blah
blah you know he's sort of he
is sort of in a way kind
of i also heard this not to
bring them up again about michael jackson
where people were saying my people were
saying that when you by the way
we've had
had one episode where we did not
reference either of those two gentle really
yes and that's in the stats that
josh sent us know that's in the
stats in my brain from listening okay
episodes so okay but i heard that
like when when he wasn't being recorded
or there were no cameras around he'd
be like yo what's up i'm michael
how are you over that too yeah
that will yeah yeah ahmed best story
yeah where michael's voice changed after he
he realizes damage are sadly true
i told that on here though today
i don't know what would yoga newcomers
but we had ahmed best on who
played jar jar binks and key he
got to go see michael jackson with
george lucas and natalie portman and they
were like watching a crew from love
to go to a concert with those
guys look to be much more interesting
i mean they had to
they're watching it from some you know
private box or whatever and then they
were led down a corridor and down
the hall and all these places to
meet michael jackson and they went to
the amendment parking lot and he george
lucas awesome following introduced natalie portman to
michael jackson and then he said reference
this is instead of saying this is
ahmed best he said this is jar
jar binks who and who said that
george lucas said it oh and then
interest michael said hey or whatever like
he was really not into me i
think he went oh yeah that's right
that's right oh so sorry sally was
hi thanks
to meet you hello me was like
natalie and his lies charger banks oh
so so doctor bass was too racist
for even michael doe we want to
play your big o angle wow in
a bid basically to play is that
how you get parts is bidding
yes you may put in five dollars
that was the beginning of ebay george
lucas was like what's to be in
my movie but yeah he asked he
really wanted to be larger beings and
then it didn't go his way but
that was how he found out wow
oh and that's saying that so that's
why george looser reduced the movie hadn't
come out you know and that's why
george lucas introduced him as
as jar jar because he was just
trying to break it to michael this
is this is the perfect way to
break this to someone instead of just
writing the email perfect they've just done
a concert
oh or maybe he was trying to
see what his reaction would be and
it wasn't supposed to be so it's
george lucas like fucking with him i
don't know but wonder what is so
it's so weird little reactions going to
be when i pulled this show on
i'd be i'm the puppet master wow
that's incretin incredible story her only on
nukem and ahmed best told it really
beautifully
whereas it's a great episode and one
what a great guy great guy i
wish him all the ahmed best and
that was the first role to use
such technology that's entirely true when i
think about that and think about how
mean everyone was i just am so
confused i'm like you've never even seen
anything like this before i've always said
don't hate
the player hate the game yeah i've
always said that and and i i
agree you know i've always said that
and i've never known what i'm talking
about
okay like we have to take a
break we'll be right back
welcome back and it's time for three
cheaper and resist submitted to to us
by ha someone's yes and not josh
this time thank god um yeah he
really was on a hot streak
this is submitted by pop culture review
thank you pop culture review away and
i think i know what that is
oh do you review pop culture okay
no wait isn't that what ah never
not funny ah never mind you thinking
of the pop culture beast guess okay
that's very powerful okay yeah
ah this is admitted by pop culture
review monster ahmed beast he's never far
from my thoughts why didn't he play
beast in the excellent that's that's right
just add names and it's so funny
that he got kelsey grammer to play
them
it is hilarious
a guy who like could not be
more sedentary
he played beast in an x-men movie
so he was you're not going to
early you to eat no spoilers because
you might watch these guys any blue
are sometimes covered in fur and that's
the last straw for you
i don't wanna see frasier blue
ah yea the fluid is back um
okay and across the conversation scott polo
lauren make a sentence by trading off
adding one word at a time and
the word must start with the next
letter from the host's name in order
example of a game than a scott
paul lauren order someone please lie
let cats ask all of us unusual
tricks like reading tales every night wow
great so we who were gonna pick
our own names for this first one
and ah i shouldn't start because we've
we when that example started with me
and then when we were practicing
this during the break we also started
with me so i feel like why
don't we say you started with the
same word yeah exactly so why don't
we start with you paul okay and
that'll mix it up a little and
ah basically what happens we just go
until someone fucks up or we run
out of better grammatically incorrect or with
bill maher yeah i guess don't do
either watching them
okay doesn't make sense for some reason
okay great
alright let's start with paw my name
is maria by the way we are
using the f we just we decided
this yes whatever are we're not going
to use our middle initials because those
aren't our stage names that's not how
we're listed on mdp that's right it's
however you're listed on mtb yes we're
not using the sometimes cry
edit it as because that's a misspelling
all right
here we go practically
an oren is just the worst word
i could have started with losing
soccer
and
also
contriving what
we know this doesn't make sense it
does so kind of does practically practically
losing soccer and also contriving and also
contriving under
unseen
orthodox
likely
okay now now i think we've lost
it because i mean oh we lost
it unlikely i think the fine transitional
radically
losing soccer and also contriving what you
want also contrived gun scene
under something under unseen it doesn't make
any
not yet not yet can we pull
it out you can't say it since
it doesn't make sense until the end
okay
yeah the man blank the ballet
a bag that she was in the
news last week what happened she she
became a jamaican citizen she wasn't like
credit something that runs that it was
suspicious oh people really are looking out
for her nice like we start over
yeah yeah we know it doesn't mean
what you start okay
look great great scott
are you fucking kidding me yes no
panics
anytime cats
r
around
otherwise
understandably
unseen
tremors to use
it is understandably suddenly easy trailers lead
revolt
traditionally
four
anyone approaching with anyone so with an
e by the way oh dear ne
anyone
approaching
ah cut the tension with a knife
polys and repose tears
mason klee
underneath
this is where j balvin just doing
work
first two sentences we got a good
start over we gotta get this right
ah let's reverse order
oh we're going this way now okay
starts to jangle go to you okay
um
okay so i have to use back
to buy no wait so how do
we avoid this so yeah even going
this way there's no way to avoid
it i guess we know if we
go lawrence got me but then it's
that's lauren again
yeah there's no way to avoid it
yeah why don't will i'll start and
go back to you and we'll see
what happens okay okay um sincerely
lauren
p s
can
atlas
and auto
read no wait ah oh
my name going living here at the
u right
ken allison otto
undersell
underwear
try
what's the new new sentence try that's
not the i thought that we could
do most of us is just one
run on sentence it never does anything
most sincerely laura nps can allison auto
understand yourself underwear try let's let's do
it a new where we could do
because otherwise like a model
never you will never make sense yeah
we reviewed your premise and it's flawed
try
um raging
lightly
then
eating
food
also
never
tip
underneath
ledges
or karate chopping
aged
ah
maidens
ergo
ah please
kindly remove
knives
in an
i think i tracked you
underwear oh no i didn't oh great
that worked out
sleeve
sincerely oh no no i'm in sorry
never
sincerely
every war never since you never sincerely
back to the town know that's what
i've written because i'm done and you're
done so never sincerely so interesting you
started with sincerely lord and anyway i've
never needed a way that's like wow
intro working on it's so was auditioning
crowd any of that
that was incredible okay now we'll do
one where you have to do each
other's names okay so who don't know
any letters that start with paul f
tompkins
ah on beam is right my i
i'll do i'll do scots name okay
i'll do lower and i'll do paul
okay and who wants to stewart i
will okay and wish where we go
in
ah paul next okay okay who am
i doing lauren okay got it
so no i started oh i'm sorry
sorry sorry padding
padding
a new oh sorry we established at
the beginning she was gonna start and
then go clockwise i don't listen to
you guys yeah ashton
padding p d d and yeah
softly
lightly
and jelly cli
just like a poem i love it
cats
r
upset
ornery unless
let
the
rippled
frank voters
saw enough
that's
a
naughty
optimistic understandable
languid
mopey
kinetic and shit
genetic kids straight adjectives
i think you know these kinetic connecticut
kinetic
enervating presence
i
refuse
knowingly
knowingly spelled wrong what do you mean
with the k clinton guys i have
an ah
what oh okay
yeah so my word was knowingly no
it's not you're an english major you
know but that's how i found it
yeah knowingly spelled wrong knowing these bell
drug what you became an english major
because you spelled knowingly wrong you were
like i gotta figure this habit yes
wait i said knowingly and you're just
gonna say knowingly
come on try find i was funny
um
nut butter
knowingly nut butter
also
understandably
sunflower seeds
nice
sincerely
paul f tompkins
that was really good oh wow that
was excruciating and was ah that's ah
that's all the time we have for
this episode yeah we really ran out
of time we really i mean the
clock was ticking yeah and that ticked
down to where it needed to be
that was challenging and had no payoff
here's where the payoff comes is when
someone transcribes the sentence yes and then
we read it and go home oh
we did do a bad job yeah
alright we hope you're having a good
holiday season we know it's it's helpful
for us do ah you speak for
all of us right didn't it wasn't
one of our original titles this has
no payoff oh yeah i think it
was interesting
doesn't so we know ah you know
yeah the holidays are tough this year
no you know the holidays are oh
you know but hanging in there everybody
can easy go find something to do
in your area noisy safe and wear
a mask and do something in your
car like driver and look at christmas
lights yeah we're gonna do it yes
you know what yes there's there's
i think that a lot of people
are gonna be doing stuff like this
there's the the six flat it's at
six flags right where we are by
the time this comes out will have
already been six i got my ticket
i hope it doesn't get ruined they're
doing a drive through um at the
park where there they decorate all the
rides with christmas yes and it's gonna
be charlie i want to find as
many random things like that to do
as paws around duh
random so random holiday chair exactly so
we hope you doing well we'll see
you next week by a i'm up
here asti
a
uh