three
ah
oh yeah oh yeah
hey that's how we start every episode
of this show entourage v yeah welcome
that's welcome to the show i'm scott
alderman hi paul f tom guy i'm
lauren lap yeah and we are doing
this show welcome to our fourth episode
and um we're happy to be here
at
and nothing would deter us from doing
this now thus we are here that's
why we're like the mail man exactly
we're like podcast mail man wait no
or fire fire this right now no
that's true i don't think dave remembered
oh yeah they've never mentioned fire like
if your place burns down do that
does the the po
post office says row mail on the
senders
yeah clean yourself up
welcome to the show welcome to the
show and this is the show where
we just sit around john that's right
and occasionally we'll do something interesting so
hopefully you'll be interested in spending a
little time with us were just three
friends and we wanted to do a
show together yeah so what is so
wrong about that
we want if you've got three friends
so you can do know if you've
got two friends yes you can do
a show just like this if you
want and who amongst us does not
have two friends wow don't hurt anyone's
feelings
what do you mean maybe maybe someone
only has one friend and they can't
do the show okay i'm not i'm
not making a judgement these rules these
are this is the format that we're
trying to franchise um now lauren you
brought a banana i did and you
are you going to do with it
is it
is it appeal or i'm trying to
i'm trying to get a glimpse in
there do you do you have the
banana within it yeah i it's it's
got a banana inside it's not just
a hello appeal no no no no
no i didn't have a hollow peel
and sew up the end so it
looks three-dimensional it's it would be three
dimensional you're gonna say that
it's a banana um i mean what
do you wanna know about i'm gonna
eat that bad boy soon you know
i've had my two clem and tines
i also had brick what's your daily
reggie you have your breakfast then you
have to clement times and then you
have a banana when i just was
like ah goodbye nuna new listeners okay
yeah i like to have a study
so what's your workout regimen
um i i couldn't get into that
because i it's my new thing that
i do oh is it real book
that's like a typical ah question that
women don't like to be asked oh
well i've never worked out in my
life until last march what happened i
started working out i went um the
dumbbells podcast which is ryan stinger in
eugene cordero his podcast all about like
fitness and stuff and i
i just talked about that high don't
do anything and i i didn't really
care that i didn't do anything i
was pretty proud of it my whole
life but kind of wanting to work
out but just had no motivation to
do it and they talked me about
it and then staying there gave me
some like tips and some things i
could do at home and it just
started the ball rolling for me that
was actually like the winter
for last spring so he told you
to roll a ball yeah yeah and
i started rolling that ball let me
tell you my arms got ripped um
but i got i started working on
just very like a little bit at
a time here and there and then
when i got back in town cause
i was out of the country for
a few months after that podcast i
was like barely doing it i committed
and i have been working out
two to three times a week taking
sixty minute classes since march i've done
like eighty something classes now it's time
class you take i do like barre
classes like like damn zeke bar method
i've done a couple dance things but
then i or i do like pelamis
and stuff which i just started but
it's really fun and i knew
never would have thought i would enjoy
it and i really like it and
i can see the difference like i
have muscles i've ever had so yeah
really that's really cool is it you
also yeah you also feel better yeah
and i feel like my posture has
gotten better and like i don't know
there's a lot of okay
we you know that paul and i
call you slouchy yeah so nice just
like a nickname when slouchy comes slow
yeah but yeah it's cool i think
i never understood that like why it
would feel so good to do it
before i felt like people were annoying
when i talked about it and i
was like whatever do it everyone and
now i feel like i get like
why once you start to see a
change in yourself it's really fun to
keep pushing it right yeah ask you
about this banana yeah because it see
seems a little on the green side
is that how you like your finance
i like it ah this is actually
pretty good it's a little bit green
but mostly yellow i have to say
i bought this banana at target which
is not my preferred place to buy
fruit um but i was there and
i just nurse sponsored by the way
i needed some random thing were there
buying christmas dinner through bananas in my
cart
never and oh whatever throwing a bunch
of guy at the checkout like put
the bananas in the bottom of the
bag and start like piling like cleaning
supplies like random shit on top of
it and i was thinking they must
really not be used to like they
have a whole grocery section but it
feels like it wasn't like something they
were trained on yum yeah that's my
helpful have you
in these small targets now my mom
was very excited oh yeah like the
city targets are like are they city
target i don't know i guess one
was built by your house and she's
like it's a target but it's not
a a whole target it's a smaller
target it's like a target tino yes
i don't know if i've seen that
and i haven't seen it either my
i think i think my dad called
it something like nah
tars j but to like tars haha
can't remember i i love target do
you really yeah does it because of
childhood memories or just you ah adult
caring adult present i like going somewhere
where i can get everything that i
need like it's pretty i end up
spending someone twenty which is like whatever
one says about target but
i gotta go there and get everything
i love
drug stores and office supply store yeah
i love them you buy office supplies
lot or you just like virginia like
oh the order that it implies of
like look at how everything is organized
i just like i love seeing all
the supplies it's like yeah here's all
the things that you need and there
you love imagining the owner of the
store
like making his order list yeah yeah
we need more racers it's like i
need a pen i have plenty of
pins i like the i love those
stores too they remind me of going
back to school which is a good
feeling going back to school for me
was like i liked the idea of
buying things like getting notebooks and stuff
like that pencils but it was also
it was bittersweet
because i was going back to school
duty if you guys could go back
to school for a year like high
school like knowing what you know now
i don't even know if like you'd
be transported into like just say that
it's adults like every every adult gets
there there's a there's a high school
for adults and ever
one gets to go for one year
i don't know what in what situation
this is but just like everyone's an
adult it's not like you're sitting right
but you get to do all the
things that you did in high school
you get to do prom you get
you get to have electives i probably
have way more fun i think they
probably learn more and i would learn
more i think i was thinking the
other day that i could like i
think i could crush the
s a t s now what was
cool about that sometimes i don't want
to share ah noi score wasn't horrible
but i didn't study ever i didn't
like to prepare for them i got
eleven seventy on the team that's good
but i didn't i didn't study and
i like like that like i got
a twenty eight and the eighty without
studying at all
but i think if i were to
do it i if i were to
do it now and try and care
because yeah you did you'd have a
goal and now we're yet to actually
achieving goals yeah back when we were
young it was like oh god gold
and now everyone has to say what
they got on those tests right yeah
i've i honestly i don't remember what
i got my cds but i remember
i did pretty well
yeah but same thing like i didn't
really study much for it because i
was always good at tests like that
yeah yeah i was always i was
always good with like just deductive reasoning
eliminating options and you know that kind
of thing yeah but um but yeah
i don't remember i got thirteen ninety
that's good which
and i never the other thing about
high schools i realised i never actually
read a book or i think on
one of our previous episodes i was
talking about how i just carried every
book i needed and i never went
to my locker but i also never
read a book in high school and
like literature like books you were assigned
books i was a sign i never
read them i just know i would
pass the tests by like listening to
the teacher talk
talk about them and kind of like
gleaning what i needed to know about
him and then i would write a
report did you try reading books and
then you're like i don't want to
do this the books that they were
giving us oh i'm i'm sure i'm
interested in them now like you know
i don't know nineteen eighty four heart
of darkness i don't even know if
i still could read it but um
you know what i mean i just
wasn't i was interested in doing my
thing i was doing
my thing did you read books that
you chose at that time when i
was in high school not read although
i did read plays and stuff because
i was doing theater i probably i
you know what when i went to
college when i was twenty ah when
i went to my theater college the
my shakespeare instructor was saying was said
to me you're obviously very well read
read because i when i was young
i read a lot and then i
really didn't from junior high to high
school we talked a lot about encyclopedia
brown
great brain obviously really well read but
but um did you say bugs meany
i know who that is
but but i thought to myself oh
gosh i'm just faking it and so
then then i would go to like
used bookstores and buy all the classics
and then try to read them right
and so i have a whole you
know ah bookshelves filled with just like
classic novels of which i've read half
like i got really into
ah nabokov or nabokov however you say
it and i got into nato cove
i got into kafka and kafka dostoevsky
is like
but um but then i would try
i've had this like giant book of
plato for four years for twenty five
years that i bought a used bookstore
and i finally recently was like never
gonna read it throwing it away yeah
like it's just not interesting to me
sometimes it's nice to get rid of
those things you know you're never going
to crack into because then it stops
becoming like a weight on you like
young
damn supposed to do that i eliminated
a lot of books from my home
because i realized i don't i'm never
going to read these again and i
don't care about displaying them to people
you know what i mean so we
have we have one book bookcase in
our home and it's got like um
you know it's a lot of books
by
there there's a number of books that
i haven't read yet that are there
but then also wants i gotta i
you know with with technology like reading
an actual book flesh and blood book
is i haven't done it in such
a long i prefer it though i
do to and for every two yeah
then on the ipad although when i'm
on vacation the ipad is some but
i don't know
no i don't know i really feel
like i read a lot more when
i have the actual book but yeah
and it's and it also feels like
a break from the phone and computer
lab somewhere when i'm doing the apex
yeah i'm still like ruining my brain
yeah i don't know which ah which
things would you enjoy doing in high
school that if you could do it
again like would you would you do
the exact same
things like what what were some of
the electives learned that use um theater
so would you do theater ghana or
does that seem like work now i
think i would because it'd be fun
like i think and you'd be a
sti best and people because she's on
horses sidewise voted best actress among a
yearbook really voted best actor oh good
i wasn't voted in most likely due
to forgotten
i went to a theater place i
believe i didn't know i place i
went to a theater high school the
high school of the arts my senior
year it it oh well that's like
enormous competition went to best actress so
yeah like the best actors and langley
was either lead in chicago billy flynn
yes of course wow
where did i do oh i heard
you talking about this off book oh
did i oh did i yeah you
sure did talk about all the leads
he got it is a weird show
to do when you're in high school
everyone's gonna underwear yeah that's weird i'm
surprised at some of the shows that
the schools do yeah that are just
like kids shouldn't be doing well my
school
cool had great actors like i was
never in any of the real place
i auditioned for every season one way
it but you got best actors yeah
never in any i wasn't i was
in r like yearly show that was
written by students and directed performance since
it was like us basically a sketch
show and i was like a pep
rally type thing no it wasn't it
was like a real it was so
people would come to it yeah it
was like a it's
been going on since like the fifty
what's it called jamo
was based on the northwest based on
the michael mcdonald song yah mo b
there of course now is based on
the northwestern show which is of the
same thing like wamu or something so
guys are spelled y a ammo okay
um and what's wow it's like the
northwestern sketch show that that we like
in the same town
so it was like our version of
that or so i don't know why
i'm west of the mississippi so i
have no idea where you're okay i
don't even know either um but it
was like our special show because like
i directed at my senior year oh
really you win best director then because
i wasn't
um that wasn't an option nobody was
very like special show but so all
the kids like to cover that show
and so i think more probably students
went to that show more than to
the other show because probably more community
people seen and you were in it
as well as terrain yeah i was
in it do you remember the bits
that you did where they skip yeah
i was in one where i was
like a really bad school photographer at
and i just like made everyone look
awful in their pictures did you write
it was this a written things written
by students so i was when i
was in it i didn't write it
and then when i like as a
senior i wrote one thing i think
got it
was it open to all classes or
just the upper class know everyone okay
and were the sketches funny like that
the kids wrote yeah we always thought
it was a great show i mean
it was so this year was the
sixtieth anniversary i was invited to go
back but i couldn't go because it
oh ne and i was really sick
oh and i sent a video but
then like ah like there are a
lot of people kind of high school
who are
famous like yeah jessie mueller who's like
opposite way and she was carole king
and the beautiful musical she's a broadway
star she's she's investigating donald trump for
truth
rush their whole family is all like
actors so i think they took over
the show um which is great but
they ah but i was sad to
miss it because i would love to
see the the current class jokes i
have no idea that's the thing outside
of my age you know me after
i left my school ah theater programs
i would maybe a couple of
times i would go back for a
few years after and they always looked
kind of small and ricky dank but
when you're in them they feel giant
and like yeah i think i mentioned
this on off book like the the
shows the two shows that i saw
before i got into high school with
that were at the high school theatre
department that i wanted to be in
were like still i remember them being
the best
shows i've ever seen me relax i
was gonna say that i remember the
actors in my school being amazing yeah
do that henry hey guys my fair
lady i remember him being the best
actor i'd ever seen him i've just
i'm so curious like i think they
were legitimately good like alot of them
went on to do like things and
whatever but i was just transported like
they were they were the only ah
well amaze
raising you know like i don't know
i don't know we never know i
guess i thought that i that i
was amazing when i was in those
plays and watching them years later on
v h s you have tapes of
the yes sam a few tapes oh
my god i gotta have anything i
got to digitize them because i want
to watch all of them
a lot of my choir performances
oh my god i was inquired to
so obviously looking back at it i'm
like oh i'm just like every other
high school actor where talking very slowly
well i think i feel like when
you feel better than other people when
yeah when you're in high school isn't
it just like whoever can overcome their
shyness to be outgoing yeah you know
i mean is like but there was
there was a difference between you know
people that could you could tell when
somebody was a was a good performer
right like those standard yeah yeah someone
who's like a professional bad actor yeah
you know like oh wow they're saying
their lines they're projecting their seem like
very specif
think about what they're doing but i've
never been invited back to my school
for any alumni things right because they've
done alumni shows and stuff like that
oh crazy but here's why i think
because it was a catholic school i'm
very clearly not catholic anymore right i've
never given money to the school right
and i don't care about the school
that still watch any advice you should
be excited i'm i think that is
weird so i can turn them down
and get won't give you opportunity to
not turn them down right or you
like whoa maybe i should i just
went back to the my high school
of the arts a few months ago
actually gave us give a talk really
what was it about how to suck
dick then the cop showed up
um no i was just yeah i
was thinking well that's cool talk talking
to some suck a dick
here's how you do it kids and
apparently slurp a tongue
that's money that's why he's done that's
my lesson oh errol episode caroline just
slipped on her sa slouching slurp slurp
slurp petard is not a bad title
for this show
no it's just i got it i
got asked to just it was weird
because when it doesn't have a certain
topic it's like you end up just
kinda talking about like oh i don't
know here's how i got into show
business maybe maybe you could do some
really bad or whatever oh and what
did they what was the question they
that everyone wanted to an answer to
well the few to i've i've gone
to a few high schools yeah but
if i get
it asked to i'll go to it
i actually went to hospitals high school
this last year too which was great
and and those and and most of
those people had very specific questions that
they thought of in advance but anytime
i go to these like just general
high schools and talk to people they
don't know who you are they don't
care they're like oh god at least
it's not the teacher talking but this
is boring yeah all they everyone here
is
is like so do you know kevin
hart right and do you know he's
the one version although the one person
who don't know the one guy i've
never met a tom cruise yeah
he's my best friend lauren oh i'm
creeped out
yeah jumping around on the couch bike
oh proper
i would go back to my school
though and do a show yeah yeah
what would be fine like to make
an alumni show or if i could
do with the people that i did
it with them and you'd have to
write much fighter hers for like a
day or something yeah i was like
i was sad i couldn't go and
then and then i was a little
bit like okay with it because i
thought it probably wouldn't live up to
whatever expe
stations i had for it but then
i was like what i even expect
i don't know so it was a
back-and-forth you should go next year just
go i'm here like there's no celebration
yeah i was here i would like
to see my old teachers i liked
them i did this really weird thing
when i used to work at chin
chin in the valley i don't know
paul if you ever came by the
russian studio city
oh yeah yeah i did not um
we were all like sort of ah
close like all the managers and all
the waiters were all kind of close
like we would have a christmas party
and everyone would go and everyone would
sing karaoke we would always hang out
together and all this so our favorite
manager was having a birth either his
like fiftieth birthday or his like anniversary
with the company i don't recall what
it was
so we did we we had a
surprise party for him
where we put on a show
oh wow and so weird and there's
so much we we loved him i
actually went over to his house once
and with like three other people and
watch the odd couple because he was
like you only know you only know
the the tv show you gotta watch
the original film i'd never seen the
original film so we went over you
tell us how suck
i was waiting for it
no but we we i remember me
and a bunch of the other waiters
did the song officer krupp key from
west side story his name ah manager
mill yeah i think it was simply
because he liked the fact that so
many of us had done musical theater
and he was like always walking around
singing songs or what
ever and we're like we'll do a
song for him that's cute but the
weird part about it was was that
um two of the people involved one
of them had had it had just
come out that he had started sleeping
with the other one's wife oh and
they
and it was a big scandal and
then and then i would think that
one of them drop out they still
did the show they still did the
show and we rehearsed it together and
like during the rehearsals they would like
split up and walk away from each
other and like not talk to each
other like hey i'm sorry cram yes
yeah what are you doing it's sane
when i think about
it it like it's one of the
craziest things and tension filled and just
like so insane that i've ever been
i mean that's professionalism yeah i mean
you know didn't miss a performance we
only have one show must go crazy
that's truly insane but also that these
guys weren't together a restaurant like
i got to fuck that guy's wife
yeah i can't not do it we'll
see what it's like there too yeah
yeah my god and she was like
monsters
anyway what crazy stories yeah we all
fucked each other in my place
horse
course we did every i mean that's
what high school drama is all about
right yeah and i wasn't part of
that well i i there was a
high school drama with my high school
drama oh really and senior year we
did um what the fuck was the
name of the south pacific ooh we
did a big musical anacostia every man
right out of my head right that
song when i was
oh and when you were a little
bit so i think maybe my mom's
my chanter it's very i can see
a kid latching onto that to be
carefully taught me so
scott standing on the table
what am i slurps a lot slower
slurps time slips at times slouchy slurps
it down um and the big weird
thing that happened was dick cheese it's
very good there are two there are
two male romantic leads in that show
with with ah young
guy and there's an older guy and
the the always the second leader always
the quirky leads right aren't they
no no south pacific and oh pick
theirs though there's there's the interracial couple
who's like the leads leads right well
i'm trying to remove the summit chanted
evening younger people some enchanted evening is
a meal de becque the frenchmen you
okay nellie forbush who is an american
white person right and then um ah
the younger couple is the interracial couple
right it's ah liat liat caribbean yeah
just the name of the girl and
then the guy
guy is like lieutenant somebody i was
hired to do able i was hired
to do that for a summer and
i and i went to one rehearsal
and it took me an hour and
fifteen minutes to get there because it
was down in orange county from here
and i bailed on it never never
called to say i was there
there's still wondering what role did you
play i think i was in the
chorus say i think i like they
they made you it was one of
those things where they make you edition
say if you don't get a lead
and you audition you still have to
like you have to be like you
have to be in like you auditioning
is you auditioning to be in the
show no ah and and you can't
just not get a lead and then
bail oh hey
oh no wait tell me what happened
so they cast in the role of
emile de becque who is this you
know francois infringed miller yes
a teacher from the skull that you
told me about retired i think we
talked about this but yeah going and
so there's a scene or episode four
and we're talking we talked about it
a different oh we talked about a
different thing okay there's a scene where
they were they these characters have to
kiss and so there's this mary
raid teacher who's kissing this high school
so wrong like that's insane right it's
like obviously don't like yes this poor
child first of all yeah yeah creepy
man can't be anything less than creepy
yeah you are even committing to doing
that so the the the female part
was double cast or two girls who
was a senior and a junior and
i know the silver mask
steven oh they they double cast all
the i know but still like nah
not here arthur yeah and i was
i remember being mad because it's like
we weren't even doing well yeah we
weren't allowed to audition for that that's
so weird to say to a kid
it's like yeah go do convention center
or something like the students only get
to be in wasn't a relief it
was a catholic school was it like
a plea
this no no no no okay it
was a lay teacher that is so
now yeah and of course the guy
like stuck his tongue in her mouth
dad did it yes oh watts yes
that's that's crazy
even if if you are seeing south
pacific and and a meal de becque
was sticking his tongue and nellie forbush
his mouth already and they were adults
that would be weird like just like
obviously you just hug her or something
like do you know what i mean
like the audience yeah czar gets her
on the cheek when i think of
it now it is so it's demented
re allowed that to happen really
the really sad is insane it's nuts
i wrote when i was when i
was fourteen and i was i got
into the drama of congratulation place that
that i've tried into the drama program
um i remember i had a shakespeare
scene with my friend holly ah where
we were supposed to kiss at the
end and
ah we'd never rehearsed it you know
and it was it was obvious and
she was i remember her being like
beautiful and i'm like a dork or
whatever and i remember we we did
it and i was and we did
the shakespeare thing in it and then
we had to kiss and it was
very we'd never done it it was
very uncomfortable i remember my drama teacher
like calling me out and going well
yeah you're obviously very uncomfortable with the
kiss let me show you let dan
get up here and show us how
easy it is and this older student
who by the way i'm not quite
sure how much i should get into
all of this kiss the girl the
older student gets up the older student
is is gay ah but saying he's
but you know in
the closet and sixty years old
most are person most of the most
of the people in my in my
high school drama program were gay and
in the closet because no because the
eighties yes my mind do and they
and they immediately by the way i'm
not like calling them out they're still
in the closet late they like a
year later after i graduated all came
out yeah i would see them and
they're like oh by the way i'm
gay you know yeah yeah but they're
all
all in the closet and so but
and this teacher the other part of
it is is this teacher is like
ah he's he's i've talked about this
on another show but he he was
kind of like sexually harassing me as
well during the during the show all
right and like basically you differently
this is why people are silent for
so ah see it was a cover
of time no but he was he
would like take me over and like
kiss my neck and she ah and
and say i was special and all
this going into your cell yeah and
so anyway but i'm sorry that happened
to you he's usually hit
yes he's dead now and so i
when go stones or game but ah
so he's so happy so you have
this keeps thumping you have this gay
closeted teacher keeps topping baby i can
daddy oh yeah she have this gay
closeted teacher like calling out me as
a straight student
ah for being uncomfortable kissing i'm fourteen
and kissing a friend and classmate so
and then calling on a student who
is gay and i think he was
also sexually harassing him or something i
have no doubt and saying like hey
go show him how it's done and
this this like guy gets up there
and he's just like takes the girl
in his arms and gives her a
real passionate kiss you know like stage
kiss and then like you know breaks
away going like yeah it's that easy
you it's like it's like it's so
huge that you're too yeah girl it's
like i guess everyone's donald a pro
time yeah it's just a demented my
girl has um i mean i whatever
it's public knowledge there's a
a teacher who has been called out
for such things but like wasted my
time but yeah but he just got
called out okay i got an email
about it wait there so they're emailing
well they're they're emailing everyone well they
talk about
lorne you could find ah yes um
no they ah they emailed exploit just
saying that the course they don't stand
for anything like that he hasn't worked
there and expo years you know they
were speaking about it just that there
was a statement but i had heard
about it through the grapevine because some
of my friends were to the california
raisins yeah they were lying on there
huh
oh yeah so my friends were older
and they had him so yeah yeah
i mean i've talked about on the
show we had a few we had
a bunch of those sicher not on
the show on on my show we
had a bunch of those situations with
like teeth yeah it's crazy i had
a bunch to my school it's the
teachers that get rid of orange juice
freaks me out but you could never
reach
and do anything really weird i feel
like if you and my parents never
prepared me for anything like that but
i feel like you do you have
to talk to your kids and say
like by the way chances are good
there's going to be a teacher who's
gonna creep you out and do such
and such a thing immediately tell someone
i know because i knew it when
like i would be
it was drilled into us when we
when we were walking to school anyone
any stranger offers to give you a
ride yeah say no that happened to
me i said no call the police
you know they tried to track him
down all that but you know you
never heard about teachers like by the
way if a teacher ever does is
i know and they can do things
that are so like they you could
just write off as being like
that was weird you know but yeah
yeah when you look back at i
actually really inappropriate or like that made
me really uncomfortable but i didn't know
i didn't have the language to like
yeah you know yeah because because you're
experiencing it for the first time and
no one is talking about it yeah
i was very naive back then of
course i was raised with religion as
well and i think bye bye
parents who came from an age of
adults are to be trusted you know
what i mean like i don't and
they're always in the right yeah and
i'm sure we got some talk about
beware of strangers or whatever but i
don't remember that but i never got
into any situation like that where i
had to even where even came close
for like a weird thing to happen
but i do when i think about
it it now it's like there's so
many fucked up adults that you have
that you encounter in your life yeah
child that i but i don't it
wasn't like the the idea was not
even it wasn't even an idea that
a teacher could do something wrong right
but it was happening ensure i don't
know how do you spoil your
kids innocence or do you you don't
want to scare someone too much when
they're little and be like everyone's dangerous
yeah well i mean but that's the
opposite for like my parents were always
telling me about dangers that we're going
to happen like on halloween the razor
blade thing yeah it's been widely many
bars but man was it a huge
thing for us like don't don't ever
accept
an unwrapped candy yeah and if an
one time i got one i think
i got a caramel apple from the
people across the street and a fucking
freaked out and they were like who
did you get this from you know
like i dunno maybe they cut it
because i'd would be fun to be
like let's see if we've got a
razor
alright we need to take a break
when we come back we're gonna have
more of this show
ah right all right we're back way
back ah i'm still me i'm i've
switched places with lauren i'm scott
yeah flips a ton dies slouchy like
fighting
do you like it do you like
for of letting the stuff out
it's it's like farting i don't disallow
dare you it's better than than having
something gurgling and your stuff out though
sometimes i do get mad at having
to go to the bathroom like just
the like to avoid yeah the howls
your bladder it's so
sometimes every once in a while stretching
like humans this is this is undignified
yeah there's chicken your act of bending
over here's the thought that i had
a you shit here's the stuff that
i have is on my hands knees
the thought that i always have this
this is the system in someone's face
just spray and it's like it's like
a windex bottle
ah
can you turn it turn it for
the insert the head turn yeah you
can turn the rig my asshole it's
so my god
well it's like this i have is
this is the system i know to
get rid of that way it's one
of the things most efficient it's one
of the things that disproves evolution when
it feels like we're the better when
it's haven't evolved much my entire life
i although oh right exactly yeah when
the handles
change when we were when we were
buying toilets for our new place a
few years back we went to home
depot and the guy was trying to
sell us the toilet i was like
really they're all the same or whatever
right and he said oh no this
one's got a little bigger of a
bowl so if you got a little
more power and then he looked to
me like ha what do you think
yeah and i'm like yeah i guess
i was like atta boy like you
shit cool
maybe meant your your eyes streaming i
god don't i do believe this is
gross but our were already talking about
son grow so i'll say it um
we've covered power and ryan stanger has
a funny previously mentioned doing the first
job podcast ah that i think is
so funny that when you far
right
and it smells really bad that you're
blowing dust off a turd
blowing things to offer to carry fighting
be like you probably should shit yeah
that's been good stuff
whatever are you are you in a
group of him or are you just
friends with them oh we were on
being around together you see buddy i
left the team like here now ah
but they're still playing friday nights make
the scene okay well went on without
you they dead they did what's the
ah if you could get rid of
of eating or shitting which would you
get rid of i mean this is
a dumb question obviously shitting right i
yeah but the having to eat also
is such a bummer like if you
could if you could not eat and
you could stay at your ideal but
like would you it takes soylent to
know what soylent oh it's like that
drink that like it's
every um its vitamin yeah whatever directory
those nutrients you need in a day
and says they're the diet that they
recommend is like just drinking like three
things of soylent today it's sort of
like the goal this diet that soylent
right yes
you know what you should do just
drink our product all damn day it's
sort of like the michael kors wearing
a black suit of food yeah it's
like i say soylent can you imagine
i'll do that every day i mean
i love the choice being taken out
of the you know not having to
go out what am i going to
eat yeah yeah sometimes it's i'm i'm
paralyzed if i'm hungry i'm paralyzed
by that i i don't know what
to eat i love like making a
lot of something and then eating it
over the next like for like every
night you do it oh i love
that meeting one deviled eggs per day
yeah for eight months chomp
good night i met my wife does
that yeah
i wasn't going to do it so
glad yeah
she she loves to cook and she's
just cooking for the two of us
and so she'll make like a big
pot of something and then we'll eat
that over the course of several dove
that and i always it'll always to
me it's like she got a recipe
for the army yeah the only way
she knows chow time or your time
bomb
over here to the mess all yeah
it is there such servings one barracks
is there such a thing as lebanese
cuisine oh yeah absolutely she cook and
eat it yes she does yes she
does um and it's ah what are
the yeah right what what is typically
well there's like ah i'm gonna fuck
it up yep
i'm just waiting for you to theirs
coby coby lise
what lies can be lies gibi sweet
little lies give me my nickname give
me lies given yeah yeah well i
was actually talking about janey last night
at a party with felicia fasano about
how felicia rashad yeah scott how some
genius hold on a second we'd like
to have fun here
yeah but you know that she did
not say for sure shah you
i'm sorry
i'm sorry what were you talking about
this is failure just talking about how
great genius and how my wife you
guys live near each other from her
you and janie
we live very close to the show
and full are you guys felicia live
close to each other so you they
will go on walks or true texts
all day long like she's just the
best she's a lovely look i'm very
blessed you are she's a wonderful lady
congratulations we're gonna say marry my best
friend that's so tight my best friends
a guy name
john you didn't man it was it
was illegal to marry him so tom
moore said i married cool
second best was the only reason why
you are married by him though iowa
yeah yeah well he can say he
married you that's true and i married
him technically because i married him newer
yes so that's true there we go
yeah i mean he is so clue
nice this a friend of ours he's
very tall that's why people call him
tal joe he likes
it though it's not like us denigrating
how policy ah six i believe
eight or nine i cheese it's like
right over the limit where he he
he technically is viewed as a giant
by the airlines so you can like
demand i say yeah yeah i think
i think that's the actual term weight
the airlines are are using these terms
yes so what can demand first-class for
our giant customers hi you're welcome to
board i think
it's like a certain type of seats
on the airline or something like that
and it has to yeah i can't
i can't recall exactly what it is
but yeah i'm not sure yeah i'm
not very love that yeah you're not
there yet know you think you're not
growing you're gonna keep going till i
wonder if people just decide to stop
growing oh that's heavy
you know what i mean like i'm
tall enough not mean i'd like to
be there probably tall people who would
argue the opposite that they grew way
passed upon way past i you know
hold up now lauren you're tall are
you talking about yourself i'm not do
you like being the hey i'm fine
with my i don't really think of
being tall
and but people well pointed out to
me a lot but i think i'll
stretch yeah
wow people asked me how tall i
am a lot but i don't really
think about it in general i just
think of people as either being my
height or tog i think most people
as being i don't think about their
height at all but if they're taller
than me i'm aware of it that's
it i was talking about this the
other day on a on a show
that we did with neil patrick harris
where yeah it's being tall
um you you never noticed anyone tight
yeah so taller you just see people
and then when someone says like oh
i'm short i usually go oh you
are oh yeah i guess so i
mean i see everyone's tiny little short
v yeah oh love to take your
word for it yeah ooh short
but i saw a woman one of
my yea today who is taller than
me and i was like weirdly like
jealous of it but i did i
don't really want to be over six
feet tall think that would cause lot
more whose womb and problems with buying
clothes and just make i feel like
fronting for acting it's terrible it would
be hard because it's already hard enough
i think being my height yeah it's
terrible for me yeah it's it's right
yeah i doing bang bang it's like
trying to frame people in the shot
while trying to get someone's love interest
if you're five ten because guys every
actor is my short yeah and so
it's like you have i mean that's
it's a challenge yeah i think i've
i think i've for sure lost out
on things for being too tall yeah
you guys are the real heroes
whenever we would get so many parts
sure interesting
look we should take another break okay
fine is that okay yeah um when
we come back we're gonna have one
of our world-class segments thought of by
me paul f tompkins yeah we'll be
right back with this show
this joe is back we're back oh
budge huh everyone short to me i
pick up a co just squeeze it
into my mouth for milk and and
for hamburgers as well you don't care
what comes out no
i did too usually blood and bile
my taste buds are gigantic
oh you know rock
the country
i don't know
like a rock or rock rock jack
bauer he twenty four he big money
alright i have a segment oh
this is a segment where here's a
little story i like to tell about
three bed brothers you know so well
you must describe a famous scene from
a famous movie but describe it in
a way that is hard to guess
what the scene is what the movie
is okay okay okay okay ah very
good very good awesome very good okay
um ah okay i'm thinking
okay i'll probably do this poorly okay
and do do we get points if
we guess or there's not points it's
just a thing that we're doing it's
just a thing that we're doing okay
got it
ah how do you describe it huh
okay um okay
a bunch of males
you've got my attention i mean you
know synonyms so i don't know how
i'm gonna do it
um
okay
it's i wanna do it like a
poem
winter's cold
winter's cold brushes upon them
they brush chuckle or just let me
do my book they struggle
for attention captain america civil war the
yeah yeah that's good keep guessing as
i'm going
um long hat
the hat fur hat
glasses
squinty eyed teen
spies like looks like a fox
one
one is bold enough to try the
task at hand
it's cold out
woodruff gold
the task requires a body part to
be shown
ah you know ah and they
it is above the neck
stuck out to touch the ice cold
poll oh christmas yeah ah that's okay
you sounded insane yeah nah i still
think you sound like i think it's
so clearly you sound like you're like
the psychic in minority report describing a
cry you see okay your turn or
somebody scott lew i'll gladly i do
not have an example by the way
um
do i have to do it like
lauren or do i just know i
think it's cute alright um a family
is sitting around ah their breakfast nook
but it's not breakfast it's actually a
family supper time
and um the mother is a single
mother she's trying to wrangle her children
and just trying to make it through
another family dinner she obviously didn't have
a lot of time to prepare it
but she's done her best um e
t yes
didn't even get to the racist pieces
that was fun
right good good
alright let's see yeah but the the
upi the upi people o r two
d two servers shit
alright um
getting acquainted
getting to know you
yeah
conversation gets personal but also remains profession
dinner with andre langdon
remains professional buckets person um um
hobbies are discussed
past adventures for sunrise nope there i
guess it's not professional it's not professional
they pay we're not paying strictly for
fun
um
advices given
professionals secrets are revealed
chorus line no no sort of though
keep going florida posto if it applies
to just movie you have to well
i guess yeah yeah it wasn't good
but you might inadvertently described another movie
um
fear
control
ah what's a barbara strides in movie
where she goes to the psychiatrist not
the one i'm thinking of damit button
nuts nuts is what i'm thinking of
is that good ah these are good
okay my balls
it really works on the podcast
um what whatever benefits it is not
good at these nuts
these nuts is that's good he's not
just a jack bauer he's twenty fifth
yeah big hits big hit keep your
weight and um
advices given us about the fear
oh okay oh basic instinct nope is
it a man and a woman yes
it is one person makes a request
of the other
yeah
mrs doubtfire no
when a man loves a woman no
keep going failure to launch ah famous
movie everyone loves
that i've seen many times ah medmen
the nba
this is crypt someone is someone is
sized up
honey i shrunk the kids
when be besides down honey i blew
up the kits
see
semen is thrown in someone's hair ah
mary was and what other movies there
with siemens throat and there's one other
famous semen semen in the hair movie
ah louis c k da
ah my gym blamed i'm drawing a
blank on semen movies that's the only
one i remember
and it's thrown in the hair seems
someone threw semen and a hair in
is is it like like a dinner
with through semen in the hair someone
through receiving the hair
so do see whatever
tell us more like who's in ha
ugly out there a little way
um so man and a woman oh
sperm in the whale
sperm it away
ah she was so confident
but i could sperm on notebooks books
oh yes right yeah he jerks off
and he rubs the spunk on the
books really now it isn't a nasty
zell is da li has welcomed in
my sd tower how often i say
nasty yeah okay wait we need more
how much semen who are the p
just enough what's the consistency older man
younger woman
oh wait not oleanna or something like
that okay i don't yeah something i
might know the older man is not
the one who puts the semen in
the hair he puts the same in
there
hey does the silence of the lambs
yes it is yes when does ether
i got i guess i haven't seen
that one when she goes to visit
him that probably noisy though many people
in one of the other onshore oh
my roommates throws throw scenes oh i
don't remember it yeah i saw that
when i was too young to probably
understand what was happening see it again
i will i'd love to
and then he he talks the guy
into killing himself later because wow it
was rude it was rude to do
yes if that's all it takes zero
today's throat with his penis it's rude
to do boo know with his hands
okay so he's complete throw with his
penis yeah wow yeah good game i
guess you're the winner paul because it
took
us way too long i feel like
it was a bad game no i
think it was good i'm the loser
because i guess well i guess how
many movies really have single mothers in
it it's it's under rebel certain of
your anymore i was just really good
at guessing that one because i was
pictured on the breakfast nooks and
really all the famous cinematic breakfast notes
there aren't that many there aren't that
many but you're right there should be
more breakfast news and cinema they're under-represented
what was the story with the dad
and that movie do they ever even
mention him being gone do they know
if they talk i think she's i
think the mom might be dealing with
some stuff related to him but they
don't the kids it's kind of subtle
the that suit spielberg like sort of
jettisoned after a he used to do
a lot of overlapping old menace dialogue
yeah yeah yeah and then he also
used to be kind of subtle about
stuff like that nowadays you know or
not nowadays but in his middle period
is hook period he would have like
you know a giant you know zoom
in dolly shot on her like going
vic the dead
dads the dad left or something that
day dallas
her husband the diablo half jack bauer
the person that she was interlaced but
she now only refers to as tattoo
ah well guys this has been fun
i think another episode of our show
that's another one in the bud that
one in the books huh
the the rest of them are in
the future history books oh that's true
that's great books about this yeah i
wonder if we're gonna be famous because
of this i wonder if someone like
scott will never read them hey you're
ignorant lawrence putting all of her possessions
into her purse she got sammy to
lee and eight this um guys
i'll see next time we had fun
i'd fun i enjoy spending time with
you all saying i know alright i
want thanks for listening good bye
a this has been an era with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com