three
sweet
oh i'm welcome to three duh thank
you oh he's obviously said who said
your willie's name paul the person whose
thank you his name paul the person
who said thank you his name oh
the person who pointed that out is
a moron and the person
who is playing the music is named
mike mularkey and the person who press
play on it you to kick yeah
i playing the music d j
is it crazy how much d jays
make it's insane it's insane like did
you watch the paris hilton documentary ah
no i like her song by the
way stars are born i wish she
had done more of that
the secretary also an amateur okay and
she gets paid like a million dollars
a gig yeah it's bad and people
like she's like out there going like
yeah and just like i mean like
heaven here seem genuinely doing a lot
of stuff that people like calvin harris
get paid like three million or calvin
harris the present maybe it was more
that's calvin coolidge isn't it i don't
know
no that is
does she seriously given a million dollars
yeah something like that yeah all they
do is they press play on the
laptop and then they pretend to move
knobs yeah but she did make the
playlist and then like she had oh
i made a playlist named movie knobs
as i made playlists and it's the
almost famous suntech
ah it's such a scam i mean
i know it's doom it's fun random
i always work condom she's even wear
a condom when she doesn't she doesn't
work onto we ah there was a
d j that we that grew up
and i really liked if i told
you this where we asked him to
play our wedding
and and do yes yes i did
talk about it on this show i
don't know if you've talked about it
on the show but i remember the
story from life yes so we don't
think i know it we there was
a d j that i had his
album and i was like oh this
is pretty good there's a mosquito right
there yeah um and ah then we
saw him play
here we go come play at ah
that's ah south by southwest and it
was great and we were like oh
man this is so good i wonder
if he would ever do a wedding
and so we took a shot in
the dark and wrote a letter and
said hey you know we're we're an
la couple the you know we're doing
this wedding if it makes
any difference to you there will be
celebrities at the wedding and the person
was like you know he doesn't do
this but he really thinks this would
be a cool thing so ah he
will do it for you say celebrities
yeah he wants to do yeah he
i think this sounds cool he will
do it for twenty five thousand
in dollars and that was more than
the budget of the entire wedding we
were like yeah that's great no thank
you and then did i tell you
that what happened with the other deejay
that i ended up getting so i
was only in charge of two thing
you know i know
end with you kissing a d j
i'm in love with the d j
and understand what the other needs
now pronounce you man and wife i
turned and i accidentally married the d
j
like it was d j qualls but
it was actually more money but she's
a d j
so i married a d j
um no i married a d j
oops
i was in charge of the music
and i was a d j
merit yourself
that's impossible isn't though i'm not actually
considering the eiffel tower or eagle to
marry oh what would be standing in
the way of it like yuan marrying
anybody who cares part of yourself goes
i object but but there's no legal
thing to like there's no division of
assets or an airbrush
rules are you saying like if someone
wanted to say yes i'm married i'm
married to myself is it the tax
break it must be the taxpayer i
think it's just that it's tedious and
people living like we're not gonna let
you do that so you can go
around saying that you married yourself it's
just so she leaped out of his
medium type in things that make no
sense because you just type everything wrong
but google still no
what you mean sarah rose good yes
and you larry you're sorry you larry
your hell did you lower your elf
on css and log me as marriage
by a person to themselves supporters of
the practice argue that it affirms one's
own value only just a happier life
an alternative term is self marriage but
this may also refer
to self uniting marriage with his merit
which is a marriage without you an
efficient sarkari salami i've heard of it
is it illegal though sounds tasty
i have a little salami provolone oh
wow so agi was a salaga go
and get some kind of lizzie does
seem like it's illegal self marriage has
become increasingly you type in cs and
mary elf larry legal oh your elf
legal
um what yes do you have it
not legal in the united states yeah
usa usa usa
but it is although places it is
of a places where is this place
you can do and then if you
move real land if you move to
the united states can use then say
you're married you know what i mean
because you got married somewhere where it's
legal does that make sense it's not
the only taste but women are doing
it anyway
i'm going to stay in the country
call yeah
that's the new green card sql you
guys services like marry yourself and i
married me i know so by the
way i went to a wedding in
vegas that was all fake for a
green card once and you knew it
yeah we knew eighty was like and
and gosh i i have to say
i barely knew the person
guys that i believe that kiss
ah but they they were getting married
to this guy was getting married to
this woman because she needed a green
card and i think maybe he had
feelings for her but they were supposedly
just friends oh boy but they needed
to have proof that there was a
wedding and then because everything comes
down to an interview i guess where
they come over and interview you and
look at pictures and try to ascertain
if you're actually married like detective yeah
and so we had to go to
vegas and like take a bunch of
pictures you know celebrating their fake wedding
like that you don't like what i
like waiting like everyone merry making it
yeah mike i don't
like it get this bug away it
looks like i'm in the sea jesus
brand suitable
spray it spray it don't say it
don't say it there it is yeah
you got it oh dangled it no
he's still he's still hanging around me
this is my zone
this is the friend zone um you
don't like people getting married for green
card look i don't like anchor babies
what's an era stephen miller supporter oh
no no i um love ninety day
fiance but i which is a great
fantastic program right paw on your phone
i love i'm waiting for my okay
full day
closure for the listener okay we need
to have full disclosure so the listener
and everyone should know and promise we
would always tell the truth yes we
did i think i missed that three
to meeting meetings blind on every episode
time and at christmas seventy token true
oh that's true what was it from
that's such as bizarre actually oh yeah
by the way we watch
it's the queen's gambit on netflix okay
so good it's really watched it i
mean mike watched it and i was
in and out but i liked what
i saw i really loved it but
there's a kid in it a young
man who's like why is this kid
so familiar and he's like a cool
guys got like sir shaggy haired ah
well moustache to go
john lennon was that john lennon yeah
who's this kid john lilly was john
lennon circular glasses and i was like
why is he looks so familiar is
the little boy from love actually all
grown up honestly i knew immediately because
his head is exactly the same is
yeah it is a little kid who's
like
i want to be a drummer and
then he's like i'm in love with
her and then he chases the girl
through the airport i don't remember i
saw one it makes me so mad
over the beverly center like what makes
you mad it makes me mad that
anything because don't remember where you saw
it and adult man liam neeson is
indulging this child or the adult he's
like thw
thirty but
he's indulging this child to such a
degree where it's like well i have
to take you to the what father
is like i'll take you to the
airport three nine eleven were doing that
on the tire port it always sucked
and so did your airport i want
to take it to the movie sholay
oh yeah
yeah what was having forgot about the
guy's music video oh yeah i'm gonna
dick into the movie shout hey remember
driving people to intermarry ebay i never
liked it i never liked being driven
to the airport last time i did
it for khula this we're talking fifteen
years ago we still talking about driving
the airport
so what are you doing before uber
ah she would take a cab the
car service okay trip
oh most years ago we got to
know but like most trips are through
business through church if you want to
lower service always sounds so decadent yeah
it's like as it's as expensive as
a cab yeah um but ah especially
in l a i feel it was
one hundred dollars to your cab to
the airport when i forget it was
it's like
yeah it's insane um so in any
case but i gotta i gotta i
got pulled over by the cops in
the roundabout at the for speeding supposedly
pull over by the cops and the
random about this is you in the
l a x
yeah mario kart doing one big donuts
are you going to tell the listeners
what's going on with you yeah full
disclosure guys and i'm sorry that i
kept this from you for so long
during the this episode but
for some reason i took my in-ear
monitors out of my bag my what
i call my freedom bag wow your
go back my go back my freedom
go if there's an earthquake the only
thing you're taking is this microphone and
your head that's right you don't have
auto which i also took out of
my bag if the assassins are coming
for you
come over here and we recorded episode
and then you go to the airport
and see the city seasons please don't
go
she's like me i wanna relax don't
symphony me move so i'm waiting for
my beautiful wife janie to drop off
my headphones so i did not have
to go all the way back home
and then come back here and waste
even more time she's willing without headphones
right now she's willing to do that
she's willing to
we do think we do things like
that for each other it's nice how
it really was shiloh she wasn't annoyed
she was fine she just said i'm
not getting out of the car so
you have to come get them do
an impression
she was like i'm going yeah it's
just gonna do this other thing and
you're just doing the nagging lights
nah coba god of the law oh
i'll have to come to the down
help of your zoo isn't that a
different type of southern accent there's four
southern accents oh okay let's do it
hey they originally from the site evening
really you're like mater the car from
car yes mater the kafka you only
car from cars is the psi which
was later he's the car
and he's actually a tow truck can
you believe it and you believe it
how that is misleading is because it's
tow mater right you go see a
movie called congress so that i know
it from cars land let's just make
it very clear okay i have watched
cars i just spend a lot of
time playing in a kid zone do
you know
oh no
i cars is i think one of
the only pixar's that i've never seen
because i don't like the concept i
don't want to watch a car as
i don't want to go i don't
want to talk you spend the whole
movie i know this has been covered
by matt belknap probably but you spend
the whole movie confounded by the rules
of the of the things they thing
yeah they go when they
race in a in a stadium and
cars are in the crowd in the
seats and cars with scenes in paul's
going away paul shouting but he can't
be heard we have no idea what
he's saying he's going to pick up
his headphones so their cars what now
we can really tell the truth yeah
sounds like christmas you tell the truth
that's right
okay so pause as we hate him
but oh my i've been dying to
see this i've been dying to say
on my oh my god reason because
i mean we say it all the
time on facts about it but oh
yeah but oh he's oh
oh
um bars it's so why do you
spend so much time in cars land
because you love decent sir
quietly i've used to love to go
to disneyland as often as i could
sure or the ol lockdown i tell
you when we went with our nephew
it's so fun with kids to um
when he was a little bit younger
than today it was like last week
um you went last race at all
yeah bristol on carson i hate that
i really wanna do that he he
was okay with the rides and he
liked some rides more than others but
man he spent like an hour and
a half in just the fountains that
the dancing fountains and yeah around in
them and it's like that for a
kid that is so much more enjoyable
than if they could just make a
little public park yes with dancing but
well
mean universal studios has it yeah well
for you go inside ah no no
and you citywalk in citywalk yeah hey
they have but usually when i'm there
it's like seven pm and the sun
is going down and i'm looking at
these insane people getting like soaking wet
going what are you fucking do i
need to be twenty degrees in a
second what's the thing you miss the
most
that's like that like citywalk going to
universal citywalk
i think people get so wet i
tell you i was walking down the
street just the other day i saw
a pretty lady i didn't know what
to say okay
yeah it was to say anything no
literally yesterday i was walking right over
there that because we have to walk
the dogs oh by the way um
the two things can happen and it
hardly ever happens and it makes me
so happy because i get to sing
two different songs which are um if
the dogs
ah the second they get outside they
take a poo either one of em
yeah huh then i get to sing
to the tune of sweetest taboo i
get to sing immediate poo nice midi
poo and then if they and they
never do this if they poo simultaneously
i then get to sing a parody
of pete shelley's homo sapiens and
who's who's deciding whether you can or
not my myself okay and i assume
god who is watching over me
come on we get back here we
need you we need you okay
a jew
you don't even want to know the
parody is it's yeah imo taney is
poo but i don't really know the
original so i'm leaving again yeah it's
very homo sapiens anyway um ah so
i was walking them and i saw
ah and this is just flouting ah
city guide
outlines bad maybe hungry for flower touches
woo let's get some let's order some
flowers we should order in the show
um but i saw like eight guys
on this person's like sort of roof
porch having a barbeque and like sitting
around drinking beers and laughing and stuff
and i was like these mother you
are
not allowed to do that right now
yeah i'm serious it does bother me
like i feel like i'm i i'm
dedicating my time to being a safest
possible i'm reclaiming my time i'm reclaiming
my time excuse me and i only
do things that are very socially distanced
and usually have a mascot of i'm
with friends and
that's it but it's not me cackling
the night away on somebody's rooftop i
was looking at them going well maybe
they all had it and this is
like their immunity party or something like
extreme what if they had a mao
and they're like we're dying it's like
they were having a barbecue and i
smelled the bbq and i was like
and i am
i've been fine during lockdown it's like
you know i'm not you know cool
up is i have some hardly smelled
any bbq but ah but that just
passing that made me go oh man
that would be so fun i know
i miss everything yeah i'm paula question
was what do you miss like in
the real world like that like we
were talking about disneyland true story
a which i do miss and well
i also really miss disneyland because every
year i would take my nephews to
disneyland and so we don't get to
have our yearly trip where i spoiled
do they get tired of it after
a year is it like when i
was a kid it was like every
year yeah no way we've only done
it twice and they were really excitable
times and because their ages like their
interests change
each year they kind of do it
a little differently or ordering in twenty
one yeah they're seven and four but
like so in previous years one of
them was like a little too little
for something and they both get really
tired and cranky and like i'm thinking
we're getting to the point where they'll
start to get to a good age
and they both just have fun enjoy
it yeah
our nephew he went on goofy's ah
the roller coaster creepy roller coaster and
i got on it and i i
had this experience where i was like
oh this doesn't feel safe i want
to go on that but i didn't
want to sound safety goofy's role working
demo he built it he's goofy guy
he can barely walk
but um we got i went oh
this seems a little scary and then
they strap you in an as it's
going or nephew goes i want to
get off this oh no that was
like ah we can't anymore and yeah
but i was like it's totally safe
and meanwhile i'm sort of freaking out
it was the same thing as when
i went to the fair with cool
up and
we went on the big like you
know you look at those things where
they so it's it's you get in
a car and it's on a line
and it's over yeah like a monterrey
not about having like or not people
mover i've i forget what exactly what
they call it like a straight-line ferris
wheel and you look up there and
you go oh that looks fun and
we did and we went oh let's
go on that and then the minute
you get fifteen feet off the ground
you
i started freaking out and coop was
really freaking out and going oh this
is terrible i want to get off
i wanna get off because you can
just like slip under and fall out
oh my god oh it's when it's
like a schema okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah well yeah but don't do that
now and that was ending a county
fair yeah it was the orange county
fair but then do you have to
ride it from one and yeah listening
to the other sunday yes
you're like so wait so i was
like honey it's okay meanwhile i'm freaking
out but i have to put on
a veneer of lies the man common
know otherwise she's gonna freak out even
not as but i know i don't
care about
but um but that's how i felt
with him and he was like i
don't like this i don't like this
the entire time as it's like doing
the twists and turns and then the
minute we get off he's i was
like yeah sorry maybe that was a
little too i read it was good
for people your age is just i
think i'd go on that again
oh my god sorry kai i had
done my research beforehand so you can't
blame me i was talking to my
nephew on the phone today and he
was like
are you safe from the fires i
was like what do you know about
this thing it was like that's so
straight off to wear a mask inside
your house and i was like no
no so that's why the day was
well it was really smoky at one
point like oh but i guess someone
told him i didn't tell him that
but i didn't want him to know
when he's nowhere what's really funny is
for years my
you would call me or email me
about anything that was happening in california
and say are you okay and i'm
like that's so far away from me
and then it's only recently where it's
like i think we're okay oh i
know it's getting closer all the disasters
oh boy yeah good luck um so
going back to the wedding i was
in charge of music and held the
story and lights i think yeah waiting
for you this is the part i
know and so i i've forgotten were
happening the d j the d j
didn't worry the famous d j didn't
work out so then i was like
ah you know wedding d jays are
always so bad they they play you
know celebrated
kool and the gang's celebration all the
time they always play the same old
songs i would really like a good
d j that because there's gonna be
young people who like get people up
and you know someone like in a
club so i happened to be in
their late thirties but there's gonna be
a few young people up was a
little loud my leg boo boo
grade school friends with this she finds
she just had to take over graduation
cap what's your graduation song it's from
two thousand and eight
so i happen to be in a
club off of hollywood and there was
this amazing deejay who was mixing in
everything and i went up to him
right after he was done with this
said i thought i said i thought
you were so good do you ever
do weddings i want an actual like
good d j he was like yeah
i would do it and so i
got his card and we worked it
out over email and
um were there at the rehearsal dinner
the night before we we got married
at union station and um we then
we have the rehearsal dinner there at
the restaurant at union station and i'm
sitting there and there's a million people
passing by through union station it's like
union station
and y'all go in somewhere suddenly i
see the d j walk in and
i'm like that's weird and i wonder
if he's going somewhere and i like
wave to him i go hey man
he goes alright where do i set
up way the other d j know
yeah the one that i hired oh
okay okay okay and he was a
famous one yeah so it goes well
where do i set up thought about
it
he's like an i'm here whatever hey
whatever you want okay so the the
d j you hired shows up shows
up things like where do i set
up and i'm like oh you're here
on the wrong night it's tomorrow oh
yeah no you said it was today
and we like look to the emails
he goes oh it is tomorrow and
you just have a saturday i just
happened to be there and he goes
it is tomorrow
saturday which is when all weddings are
and he goes well i have another
gig i'm like oh fuck he goes
tell you what tell you i tell
you what let me send my friend
he's just as good as me he'll
do it really good and then when
my gig is done i'll come and
do the last like three hours imagine
if he thought it was the day
after and then
you just didn't show up on the
day and you were screaming so so
could you just send you the payload
imagine imagine imagine if he fell in
a hole
that's gonna be kind of a cio
in the topic bend to snap
well it wasn't just a playlist it
was literally him mail stores of course
so anyway so the spirit j d
jays the night comes and his friend
doesn't even show up what is this
and so the guy who is doing
the lights who really wanted to be
the d j who was a professional
wedding d j's guys like now's my
chance he's like he adjusting lights would
isis
checked foul play he literally was like
let me just deejay because i turned
him down before cause easy he's like
i'll i'll do the music hall to
the music so he says wait he
offered already you had to turn him
down while we went we i was
in charge of the light so i
hired him to do like hired a
guy that was it yeah and all
we had
a playlist or just like play these
songs so we we i hired this
guy and he was like well i
also do the d j and i
said oh we already have a d
j after looking at his whole aesthetic
you know what i mean and see
yeah the review he was like a
corny d j and we didn't want
someone who knows he played celebration right
off the bat well so what happens
is they say all
right let's we did our first dance
and he goes alright let's get out
on the dance floor immediately plays cool
and the gang celebration oh my club
and i just started laughing and so
realised it was all still fun and
you were only one out there
it was it was one of the
dominant laning like a bunch of privileged
deaths it was one of the moment
because you know the seating was all
we were supposed to the wedding was
supposed to be outside and then yes
your brain huge know that no supposed
to sit next to a celebrity hell
i don't want to say now please
tim allen
members your time with two oh i
sure do you have time with him
oh yes i love that story um
that was mostly outside and then d
then there was ah a huge mariachi
festival across the street at olvera street
how do you know and that was
televised unknown when none of us knew
about it tell him novell iced and
so literally a half hour before the
web
reading loud incredibly loud mariachi music started
and i do feel that whoever booked
your wedding should have known about that
yeah like yeah who knows but so
we we moved it inside and it
was actually way better because coop got
to make an entrance down a big
stairway it was really pretty cool um
but yeah those of us who were
friends
with gun club at the time got
to enjoy that totally then i was
but a twinkle in my parents ah
what year was it two thousand and
eight
i write with tears and eight weirdly
you were right with it weirdly well
i was graduating college hey congratulations yeah
i had my cap and gown are
you the only college graduate here on
the show are you one you know
i'm not yeah i didn't think you
i am the only one
the most wonderful thing about tigger and
do you have a degree yeah wow
english
inc what english
ang lee what do you have to
do to get a degree in english
like do what courses yeah well it's
not the blog
it's not that complicated um it's a
lot of courses of all different types
i took many sciences and maths and
all others things as well my gen
ed sort of credits right and then
everyone wants to be the literature i
got to pick like a lot of
different types of literature i've never heard
you talk about a single book what
sorry
i like to talk about this how
i'd ever need to talk about a
book but i'm no english major it's
also we have heard each other talking
about books yeah definitely have talked about
books i was really good we have
called go car go yeah i can
think of one um but yeah i
took you know shit
shakespeare and chaucer and all that wow
like a whole semester on chaucer or
was it was to chaucer plus the
other people from whatever know chaucer chaucer
plus it but it was the quarter
system so it was we didn't work
on semesters we did quarters and so
that's a special order or it was
like um this
the year is divided into thirds actually
because its fourth-quarter yeah i see that
was my problem with college quarters yet
it the game ives i mean i'm
leave me there lead me there i
buy well there's a drinking game quarters
and i played it too much and
i was forced to leave college was
was my crippling beer addiction did you
guys play drinking games i know i've
ever played a tie game i've played
one or two but i really don't
find that fun is dumb
i did do drunk history and i
had to do a drinking game on
that and i was kind of nervous
because i never do them and i
don't like drinking hard alcohol really and
we played ah vodka or water roulette
game or it's like a spinning oh
yeah thing and you like on lazy
shots yeah and there they're either water
vodka and i got so many vodkas
and i got trashed but isn't that
the point of the show for sure
i just was scared to get that
trash you know i mean like i
thought like i like controlled a little
bit yeah yeah been a while since
i got that fucked up yeah i
never do that like for so unpleasant
title that i know i hate the
neg one
a younger it was routine yeah getting
that drunk and then i did drunk
history and had not been that drunk
probably the last time i was that
drunk was probably when my mom died
when when i was like the first
thanksgiving after my mom died and i
was at my cousin's house which was
our tradition as we would go over
to their house for dessert and
and they're a big family of drinkers
and we're a big family of drinkers
and so we would stay up to
like the wee hours drinking beer and
that night i was like hitting it
real hard and i threw up and
i passed out and you know it
was it was a mess where are
you doing it sort of because it
was your your mom
he had died or yeah i didn't
realize it at the time and then
the next day i was like i
think i know why that happened
but um so when i did drug
history it was like ok no this
is what i'm supposed to do but
my mom has a died again so
it's like kill my dad
so i started drinking on an empty
stomach you know before i went there
and yeah yeah yeah wait so were
you okay were you worried that you
wouldn't be able to get drunk enough
and the amount of time there or
you just want it to i just
i figured like that's what the thing
was you know and so and i
knew that they'd explained they explain like
you're gonna tell the story like a
bunch of times in varying states you
know so you isn't your thing though
it takes them a while to get
set up and so a lot of
people are way too drunk too early
i heard that from a few people
like i got way too drunk and
then i had three more hours until
we started filming there's no way around
that by the way i think it's
like we were
we started
they started filming they do like behind
this the behind the scenes stuff when
you're kind of getting you're in the
process but like i i can see
like me and derek in my episode
we're talking in this kitchen and i
can see that i'm already drunk yeah
um you just arrived like hey paul
now
what is one of the funny things
was i remember derek saying like you
know that's hard for me because i
have to drink with the people and
it's like you don't have to
fine if you just told me no
one expects you to yeah that's funny
this whole show is just an excuse
for you
get drug every day but i got
i got blackout drunk i passed out
there's there's footage of me that i
saw of me like sleeping on this
couch as they're clean up around me
like packing shit up and states tell
you like hey do you want this
footage to be on the show or
not or do they are they just
trying to put whatever they're embarrassing
thing they're allowed to but they're honestly
they kind of they're very um protective
of people like yeah they know what's
funny and what's what's sad right so
like i know one of the rules
was never show a woman throwing up
because it's not it's like seeing a
dude throw up is one thing but
seeing a woman throw up is like
just really more
embarrassing i think it feels like it
takes more advantage yes she was so
drunk that she's throwing up in your
film like do you get to a
place where women can throw up on
tv hey well on it check every
tv show yeah
but i got i feel like in
those i didn't twice and i the
first time they took my there's like
a nurse there who like tests your
blood vice okay and i like both
times when i blew i was never
registering as drunk but i was drunk
like it was like yeah but yeah
we're like it's not work gig or
like you're not coming in at the
level that we're expecting or something but
like i don't take that much to
get to feel really drunk i don't
know if that makes is that still
relative to your blood alcohol level like
when my if i was drunk when
it's still be point i don't know
whatever i tell you about the when
i went to lake havasu for spring
break with my friends and our
our boat broke and all sorts of
stuff happened but something but ah so
the part that's remained to this conversation
as we went to a club and
then we ah got in the club
closed and there are police sitting in
their cars like just waiting for people
to fuck up
and just sitting there watching everyone get
into their cars so we get into
our car and my friend is easy
my friends fucked up
backs up into a cop car and
they get out and go all right
so let's you know are you drunk
and my friends like yeah i probably
am a little too drunk tea they
go okay well can anyone they were
nice about it such a great way
to add like you probably think about
it i guess i didn't drink all
day on this book
huh so drunk kelly describes mega both
broke the law got jokes we all
want to have a little robot so
they go but can anyone can anyone
will let you go but canadian one
else driving the car and i said
yeah i can because i didn't feel
drunk at all there go like okay
well let's let here let's do a
drug test on you to see if
you can do it what are they
digging around did the entire drunk test
passed you know did the nose to
the fingertips to the alphabet all that
kind of stuff they're like yeah okay
you seem fine they go you know
what once you just blow into the
thing just we can check and i
blew like twice the
yeah okay you should not be driving
and so we had to leave the
car there and take a shuttle where
and i dropped my wallet on the
shuttle with all my money and all
every every every yes well i mean
at that point at that point in
my life till now yeah yeah temple
your life you didn't have anything in
the bank and so it was just
like i took what i had everything
out of the bank it was like
one hundred and sixty dollars and how
old are you i'm twenty five and
that was all the money that i
was going to use to eat and
drink and that's you know and so
i dropped it on the shuttle and
this is the one good thing that
happened on the trip was i woke
up the next day and some
when asked me to pay for the
food and i was like i don't
have my wallet anywhere and i retraced
my steps i said i'm sure i
had it with the cops because i
showed it to them so i knew
it had to be on the shuttle
and i went to the shuttle got
out of paying for breakfast yeah i
didn't pay for breakfast i was wanting
to know i went to the shuttle
and they had it and it had
all the money oh and everything else
and they go you are so lucky
because most people i was going to
take
that money
if you found a wallet yeah and
you were were lady would you throw
up if you were would yeah i'd
say let's say you were in that
same position yeah in your life like
twenty bucks was your bank that you
found a wallet and it had
one hundred dollars in it would you
keep the cash and return the wallet
or what would i will say that
that particular experience turned me around and
i said i will never if i
ever find anything i will just return
it the way i found it i
won't take anything out of it because
i was like i was so grateful
it saved me at that point yeah
and i was like i i don't
think i'd ever found anything you know
like i've i found a random twenty
dollars lying in the middle of the
street once but yeah there's no way
to return that by put up a
sign but that's true any little industry
anyone lose a twenty dollars and then
you just take all the calls paint
and so on and they really rose
what it looked like the letters on
it i was like if it's in
a wallet you must leave it in
the wallet yeah if you just see
some money on the street baby oh
yes your street money baby but if
you see someone some money got to
chase after them you gotta chase after
them and say did you drop half
of this money yeah exactly and i
get the other half because i think
get up but i ever since then
i felt like i just really empathized
with whomever dropped it and so i
yeah so i just have always you
know tried to do that whoever dropped
it adopted true that's it's works for
babies
whoever dropped it adopted so if you
go over to your friend yeah you
drop their baby you have to adopt
that baby that works out were you
dropped smith adopts works less better yeah
alright he works much better things better
monthly this
english major zuckerberg bike
we're back i know i am i'm
here
with our first break that was our
first break wow it was a little
late i'm so so unable to keep
it tabs on how long we're going
speaking in which tabs no longer keeping
tabs because they are going out of
business tab soda yes oh it's it's
the skill thing or your mom was
a big tab yeah
yes and when i was a kid
we had tab in our household yeah
the cheesy right oh did you feel
bad when you heard that news when
i just told it to you i
guess i guess no i'm surprised it's
still a thing but they do have
the best logo yeah it's iconic iconic
can i like a shirt attacker kona
pop
i don't care i love it um
i found i think you can easily
get that right i can too can
get what a shirt attached sure to
not like a vintage tee sure go
get one you don't have to thinking
about i will cycle through clothes pretty
regularly like i feel like i like
shopping and then i like to go
to do it well i like to
go through and get rid of things
and donate and whatever and sell stuff
yeah and lately i've been thinking i
kind of wish i've kept everything i
ever had because i now miss random
things like i'm i'll think like oh
my god that's what actually was kind
of cute that ten years ago that's
where you start getting into her
hoarding where it's like i remember cleaning
out my parents' house when we move
them from where they were to where
they are now i don't want to
say their locations sigh as you the
secret service is protecting them and why
should you but um but you know
they had like a huge closet downstairs
just of storage of all this
stuff like stuff from when i was
a kid like my kid kids records
and i was like we should get
rid of these and my mom's like
it's records my my record adele yeah
or like you know like disney turn
the page records oh i love storybook
record yeah they're great but i was
like but mom there's no reason to
have them anymore i'm not a kid
and she's like but i you know
what if i ever want to look
at them or listen to them i'm
like yeah listen to them but that's
the thing is is like you feel
so connected to something from your youth
i was like what if we just
took pictures of these things well kid
maybe nice too but i do feel
like with stuff like that i'm more
likely to keep it than clothing like
i i have so like
like i have all my dolls when
i was a kid like so many
things that my mom has saved but
part of it is that part of
the reason why i'm ok with it
is because they've been really well preserved
like i have chautauqua wow we have
a song i've all my childhood planes
we only have a helicopter song what's
that yeah
helicopter house sounds one he's looking for
someone he's looking for someone helicopter
um i had collects all these beatrix
potter stuffed animals as a kid and
i had every bit of animals of
beatrix potter just delay it was like
every character
yeah my my cuddle dock you asked
for beatrix potter stuffed out stuffed with
the commissions then screw up kin anyway
my mom send them to me like
last rose ceremony of it oh my
god you want i pushed through talking
about the wedding ah maddie erupted i'm
never
you know ruin squirrel nut can because
now he's come related
he's always been come books and she
says there's like twenty stuffed animals and
i have them all in there all
like perfect and i guess i'm a
guy i'll never get rid of them
i don't know like i'm just like
i love them and i do actually
buy some animals for myself so like
whatever like i liked them but it's
a weird thing to have like all
of this stuff man yeah there's there's
a lot of
and of i finally learned that lesson
where it's like you know you sort
of if you have a box of
old stuff you sort of look at
it and then you realize yeah okay
i saw it again now i'm done
you know they're they're thing i like
like what's something that you could get
rid of and want something you keep
honestly there were things
i was i was a person who
would keep a lot of things for
sentiment like ticket stubs and fats like
i do that birthday cards yeah and
then i would like a ticket like
just a ticket like a raffle type
ticket and i'm like i don't know
what this fucking is yeah i've no
idea but this was whatever this was
it was extremely important to me yeah
it's connected to some
a girl that i loved or whatever
and now i can't remember at all
but a harder thing is like paper
stuff is very easy for me to
get rid of objects are harder for
me if it's like a a weird
little anywhere little totem for when i
was a kid and then i think
about like toys that i loved when
i was a kid
like it'll pop up in a movie
or something it's like oh my god
i used to have that and i
think i could get that now just
like yeah right what what would that
be like to have that in my
field of vision whenever i wanted to
remind me of whatever at a certain
point you had edited out of your
field of vision like yes yeah i
mean and yeah and it would have
nobody you know what it is i
realized it's the feeling
of i want to hold that thing
again right yeah that i remember from
like when i was when i was
a kid that we had these um
there were like like a large version
of army men kind of they were
civil war actually like kind of army
men we only get better the outside
we both sides say well you can't
have fun
besides the floor with one army both
very fine people i'd make people vote
said um and they were they were
like large they were like look at
this look at this eagle or whatever
the fuck yeah there oh and that's
a helicopter no lower yeah oh it's
a hockey after helicopter hawk is out
he's looking for some
someone he's looking for someone he's looking
for someone helicopter
and i thought it would be i
could feel it in my hand do
you know what i mean when i
pictured it i could feel it in
my hand the weight of it would
have felt like and i was like
well i'm not going to search for
this online what am i gonna do
yeah you can already do it you
could i've definitely good yet ivory bought
things yeah even some shoes that i
had in high school that
i got rid of and then i
i bought them again there's enough that
i think if you if you miss
and you're like oh i i threw
that away accidentally or something then you
can rebuy it but i there was
there was a point when i was
someone when i went to college one
of my teacher says well you're obviously
very well read and in my head
i was going ah no i'm not
i had never read a book in
high school
cool like i did reports just based
on summaries and stuff notebooks and now
we're talking about booking so i was
like okay i'm gonna go and buy
like ever go to used bookstores and
buy like all the classic literature that
i've never read and and teach myself
you know and then what happened so
i i i would then like
like everywhere i went go to a
used bookstore and look through these certain
authors and find these books and stuff
and so i had a huge collection
of books that when we moved here
i was like i just looked through
them and i was like you know
what i have literally had this collected
edition of plato for thirty years have
never cracked it open
and yeah it's safe to say i'm
not going to read this yeah yeah
yeah yeah you know so i just
i don't end up freeing like i
feel like absolutely things like homework things
that you bought and then you're like
i need to let it go that
feels good because it's just it looms
and then when you see it on
the shelf like i'm gonna get to
that i got a complete set of
homework and
i was like i don't want to
do this well you like to go
to colleges and pay for paper yes
i do pay for people to write
space for you even though you're not
absolute yeah i think we might talk
about that but i do know someone
who does that he he's paid to
write people really is your husband i
know but it could be
like a random thing that she's like
a side-hustle for him i will say
one of the things when i was
moving my parents when i was like
looking through all of their stuff and
i i found a lot of mementos
like newspapers and stuff and i found
one moment i found that was the
other thing if i was ever in
the holroyd of joe pantoliano
oh so do not trust him don't
believe his lies if i was ever
in the newspaper they bought six copies
and kept six comics yeah kept them
yeah so i was like it's nice
to have a hard copy of a
thing you were in yeah but i
feel like i don't have the dedication
to cut it out yeah i do
think you'd be better if it was
cutting capitals they would keep the entire
paper oh i mean i have
like some full papers from like i
have the full paper from nine eleven
i have the paper from nine twelve
would be a little more insta i
mean yeah so like the day they
warranted it
oh nine eleven oh okay yeah oh
we're getting too close anyways nice well
but i think it was nine eleven
i think it was ninety well they
printed hey maybe they didn't show the
judges did you hear what happened yesterday
oh whatever i have the one that
hatched and saw newsies on the corner
extra extra nine eleven average yeah
and i had the one from when
obama won i think idea obama won
but but anyway so i'm looking i'm
looking through their mementos left
i looked through the information types that
xl gets printed in like new york
and they're like cranking it out i'm
handing it out like it was normally
it depends on model papers i'm gonna
find out if it's normally newspapers remember
elevens are printed i don't remember like
two in the morning so they are
delivered at five minutes and they're breaking
new they suck
times do an extra edition which is
what the news is when they go
extra extra that means like something just
happened and we printed next oh
but then the orange county register was
printed in the afternoon okay because i
was a paper boy and i delivered
it oh now we get nine eleven
eighty yes
that was i came out of retirement
okay ne we got big news we're
getting home
pretty call you back and we we
signed the contract
we all need it so you know
when you wrote a rusty old little
bite
we found your original bike ah ah
i remember watching those towers come down
and say it's nine eleven it's really
isn't it was crazy how quickly they
coined it
because it happened in nine eleven on
nine eleven like when nine one one
it's like there's a lot happening within
an hour people were calling nine eleven
in my in my memory oh yeah
nah say we're sometimes because within an
hour people were saying people were saying
it happened at nine eleven on nine
eleven how
you know and and within like i
swear within an hour people were saying
nine eleven is a day we'll never
forget and then people just kept calling
nine eleven i don't i don't think
within an hour before maybe right dude
that the date that was that was
happening at the moment two notes
he'll never ah but so i don't
google i found these like said term
nine eleven larry o by people like
literally googled us whoa
see
yes and crosby stills yeah people are
dumb but was nine eleven building called
nine eleven building
alright whatever yeah i'm able to call
them lee question how else will they
know how to hit it so i'm
looking through these mementos with my my
mom and i find six copies of
paper and assuming because i'd found so
many that had me in it i'm
like kind of looking through it i'm
like why do you have these and
she goes there and she points the
car
at the
she points at the headliner whores come
every day she pointed like the major
headline of the day and it's like
an abortion clinic in orange county being
picketed and she goes i was there
kidding
and she had kept the pay wow
i was picketing against the yes bank
and i just go like my mom
we're throwing this away
just like they do all those babies
at the abortion that is
crazy
this is very broad alright we need
to take a break huh
and we're back hello hi do we
have a three-tier yes bet your ass
we do we always thank god i
bet my ass and i get my
ass back you get two houses now
i bet against it seeking out my
ass
and it's yoda plata
ask platter plaster this is submitted by
waldo at shah roster oh i'm sorry
i sang over who is it are
you average fall love at trois a
schwa love law loves loves the schwa
this game is a reversal of ham
half-life you start with a seven point
five second scene we played half-life about
five episodes ago people seemed to really
like it they really did i mean
it was and we liked it we
knew that was where we start we
improv a two minute scene and then
ah condensed it to one minute then
to thirty seconds than fifteen seconds then
to seven seconds then to two seconds
yes so now we
start with a seven point five second
scene why is it seven point five
seconds and it can be fifteen thirty
okay maybe we might take it to
a sorry i was a math major
ah so start with a seven point
five second scene where you when you
are an english major you just read
books about math yes an english
start with the seven point five second
scene then repeat the scene but this
time it's fifteen seconds adding details as
need be then thirty seconds than a
minute than two minutes up to four
minutes or eight minutes if you feel
up to it we're not doing an
eight minutes eight min early we're doing
a four minute so far we get
okay so do all who is keeping
time i have my clock open way
to do it i can do i
have the time vagrant um is there
any parameter of how we start the
scene or is it just a community
to suggestion or anything like that oh
less time i guess we did locations
right okay i can give a location
great the location is
theater lobby theater lobby alright are you
guys ready yes and go hi one
ticket for this theater production please oh
hey i'm sorry which one was it
that you wanted to see the there's
a couple of which one wasn't honey
this afternoon we have a few different
stages i'm shit
so wait i think i fucked it
up because shouldn't be that we're just
trying to get a bunch of stuff
out and then we add i think
i think so i don't know yeah
i think i shouldn't do a scene
it should be sad yeah fact check
yeah okay let's start okay okay theater
lobby ready and hi one ticket
okay they're all dead oh no we
have to get out of here it's
too late for me all of us
okay
and that was better
it's alright
going up to fifteen seconds one second
hey birds shut up
oh they don't listen they don't make
that back i tell you alright so
we turn to remember it now because
i was working on the timer okay
i sorta remember ok let's try it
so okay fifteen million seconds okay hi
there could we get one ticket for
the show yeah you just want one
for the both of you ah we're
gonna shoot receipt
well i'm sorry i have an announcement
to make they're all dead weight doctors
yes all of oh well we gotta
get out of here it's too late
you're dead too for me too okay
alright alright it's coming together see those
details are sprinkled up little by little
oh so little detail just bring up
all right thirty sec
seconds and go hi one ticket please
for the both of you ah yeah
we're gonna share see if that's okay
yeah that's fine with me okay great
oh boy can't wait to see the
show all the lights are coming up
they usually go down yes hi everyone
i'm the theater manager i don't usually
like to be on the stage it
scares me but um
they're all dead i'm afraid woo the
actors yes the actors are all dead
of what there's a gasly we gotta
get out of here and it's too
late wait for me too i had
yes year old dude no but i
have this mass time
it's working it's working alright tales are
being seeped going up to a minute
alright and go hi ah one ticket
please for the it's a wonderful life
stage production yes and it's one ticket
for both yeah oh yeah we're just
gonna share a seat this is my
baby oh okay well seemed
like a woman
yeah like that's when my name right
yeah alright let's come in oh boy
can't wait to see the show wait
a minute like a woman usually lights
kitchen lights up when the lights go
down but instead they're looking for one
i'm an irish guy full tomato or
junior wait i got asked yes you're
the son of harry
old pulser buyer who i don't want
to get into the narrative type who
the cupola backslash yeah i don't wanna
talk about composer of the running man's
guys i have a very important note
okay this is the the actors from
the play show you about see yeah
i'm afraid they're all dead oh my
god wait what what happened well this
is embarrassing but there's
a gas leak here oh my god
we gotta get out of here it's
embarrassing is other someone's but here's what
i'm gonna get out of here no
because you're all going to die to
me no time okay
alright now two minutes right
yup two minutes this is and this
is the last one okay maybe and
this is where we'll cap it just
to be high oh i have i
excited about the forbidden
i lie like we're gonna do the
able to see oh hey sixteen we
got time alright here we go hi
one ticket please just one for the
it's a wonderful life for both of
you well this is a baby she's
just oh wow of course she's still
like a woman does i thought i
thought children under two free know that
you're totally
right sir i didn't why did you
you thought this was a wonder my
glasses on i just saw our lord
you move your glasses i left them
on my nightstand will not mine italic
die nightstand but i don't have your
i'm so excited for this show it's
not very good how weird that they
would hear me and announce that over
the line
the usher i'm right oh i thought
that was allowed loudspeaker oh oh hi
i was a loud speaker well you're
speaking very softly but i you're right
next to me so i guess my
confusion okay
well i'm excited to see the show
in any case know whatever you like
just sit down you and your wife
know it's a wonderful life and this
is not my wife she's not my
wonderful wife or your beautiful wine oh
alright well alright i'm so excited to
see the show and i hope my
baby doesn't cry during this entire thing
like yeah i hope so too who
brings a baby see it's a wonderful
life in the middle of the day
she's got to learn oh my gosh
the lights are turned the lights lights
usually go down but they're coming oh
no i'll go out there no hello
everyone i'm a theater manager
harold feld meyer junior and weigh i'm
sorry i gotta go i know what's
coming you're the son of harold falter
meyer the composer of actual f the
running man yes i'm sorry i gotta
ask yeah what's your favorite candy oh
oh probably jolly rogers that's surprising i
surprised a lot of here i have
one right here wow
oh i'm sorry i hit you in
the eye ooh just like fabio just
like no no sorry just like david
bowie that's right you got that that
candy store yeah cool i oh my
god what's wrong oh yes i forgot
why i came out here ladies and
gentlemen i'm terribly sorry but it's all
the actors did oh what gas leak
guess we gotta get out of here
it's too late
if you're able to do o time
well we're adding a lot to the
middle
one four minute come on hello for
you go forward enforcing for yeah alright
here we go
haha hi ah one ticket for it's
a wonderful life oh the musicals one
for the d all white cast yeah
just one for the two of you
why would you advertise we just make
it very clear that we haven't gotten
to the diversity thing so we just
haven't got around to it or yeah
no one addition ah we just make
it very clear that the cast is
all white in case that
it's problem gugu i guess that wasn't
in the advertisement sorry just want to
get for you in your ah this
is my wife this is my kid
i thought the children under two are
free that oh that's very big on
the advertise no no and the all
white version is very very tiny i
don't have my glasses on i um
i thought that was a woman now
she's my baby wow
this is a wow wow wow have
really poor vision okay but i love
my class but that's fine she can
just sit on my guy like on
my watch sooner trust okay okay with
this guy last night are you saying
sorry what a body by every time
thank god i never grew i love
you just the way you are one
foot tall will you please take your
seat sir
ah oh i'm hearing an announcement apparently
you're not a i'm a person you're
not making it an outright i'm not
well i mean all i said was
i'm hearing an announcement you know what
if i a galley
alright go away please alright i'm gonna
be back though i'm so excited for
the show
was so excited okay i've always wanted
to see this show
i'm so excited okay don't be it's
not very good why would they say
that over the lounge i didn't say
i sent it right next all your
bag for me yes i've thought was
a loud speaker announcements it down you
and your wife i mean you're speaking
very softly but i heard it i
didn't know you're next to me which
on stops the letter i'm not allowed
speaker you're a close talker though remember
seinfeld
and the the comedian yes no i
yeah to show why don't you and
your wife to know him from if
you don't know him from the show
i know him from comedians in cars
getting coffee oh i love this show
it's great it features so many great
up and covers like alec baldwin alright
well sit down and shut up alright
will love you love you oh you
got me
i can't to say it
oh boy well um can't wait for
those lights go down for the show
to study doesn't cry during this who
brings a baby to it's wonderful life
midday she's got to learn about how
wonderful life is way can you think
of any other way to teacher um
i don't know why what are you
some childless hag yeah i'm a childless
hey you're gonna you're gonna get
lesson from this show because she turns
into an old maid at the okay
well let's just see you that's you
about this
why did you choose yellow spoiler show
what i'm supposed to yell spoiler alert
spoiler alert the knob falls off the
railing spoiler zoos pedals come into play
my birthday present spoiler boys on christmas
the banchan little it's christmas
yes it's christmas day oh my god
the laws you want me to buy
that goose yeah who the lights on
please
hello everyone usually the lights go down
but they're coming they're coming of the
lights are up i'm i'm the theater
manager harold falta buyer junior where i
got is here codes are you the
guy who composed axel f no i'm
his son oh okay i gotta ask
yeah what's your favorite candy i gotta
throw in the running man just so
i don't
jolly ranchers oh i have one right
here we ah oh my god i
valued you i mean david bowie you
remember when he got that lollipop stick
stuck in his eye during the conservation
for you what are you doing on
stage oh thank you you reminded me
of the actors you know for the
pleasure yeah your majesty
you won't be seeing them because they're
all dead oh no of what there's
a gas leak at the theater we
gotta get out of here it's too
late we loved me so hard why
would you lie story for the employees
you've been here longer
we gotta get ah
time
eight minutes to share eight minutes is
a long felt really tray let's just
try one right okay what are we
what have we tried it for six
let's try break here we go and
start
oh god this person in front of
me is just taking so wow wow
does it go so it goes like
this you give me your credit card
i understand credit cards why because that's
how i swipe it for me well
i'll put it in this chip holder
so it's hard again a swipe like
like thirty slang for stealing something wait
is me i'm twenty thirty walking skidoo
hey your agents and rode the theater
is my dough
okay i'm an old lady that's true
during your hard rep candy you know
i did that's celery sticks wrapped itself
but why have a baby
that's your baby it looks like your
wife what a weird insult
yeah it was a gap
i was a baby um mrs flick
your your car glitter through you married
jiminy glick whoa you source like i'm
not trying to
your car isn't it interesting that god
was declined
so she okay she's married to jimmy
glad i don't have any cash you
see there was a fire at my
house very old woman yeah may i
pay for your ticket what a gala
just so you'll get the fuck outta
here so i can go to the
theater you ruined with the theater for
me
i've only the concept of the bears
i gotta go spit on the ancient
greeks
are you going to find them i
got a grease good idea hi huh
god thank god here that was so
obnoxious wasn't it i am not allowed
to say
legally or yeah morally legally yeah i
think she was fine what you're allowed
to say she was fine while i'm
allowed to have a positive opinion okay
the i mean positive i wouldn't really
say flash back to her first day
on the job no remember you are
not allowed to say negative things about
anyone
but you are allowed to express positive
opinions okay so for example i could
say
mommy mommy don't lose this job we
need the money um let me just
try one okay oh god mommy you're
terrible compliments this isn't so bad
that's on the line
it does imply that it is a
degree of bad though which is negative
this could be worse
yeah you say probably no no i'm
trying to see if i need food
tonight okay okay yeah sorry donald let
me give you a a fire sir
let me give you a scenario let's
say a dinghy old broad as in
live with the theater ed she doesn't
have any cash and she's making ready
she looks like you know not exactly
like me
okay and you you then you have
somebody come up after she's gone oh
and ah they want to complain about
her because she took a log time
sure
what do you say
i still think she was fine perfect
you've got the job
donald she get an advance on her
paycheck so i can eat tonight child
why are you here at the job
interview why do you know so much
about how it works i grew up
too fast since daddy left that's the
one thing he told me about his
advances on paycheck the slap yeah oh
oh vice back again flashback again he
said daddy you're not leaving are you
i gotta get out of this mommy's
a bitch but you gotta stay no
she's actually not it it's because of
you that i'm leaving
yeah you're weird
you do like adult just because i
read a lot my a i q
of two hundred yeah and i'm a
scientist already yeah
yeah all of that combined yeah it's
frightening to me honey don't go just
because of him i can't stand to
baby you know i love him outside
you just saw forever yeah put me
outside yeah come on in the little
dog house you'll be fine one of
the big dog house that was for
the dog i can't i can't have
him on the property
yeah i gotta go listen to so
son
here's what i want you to know
and then i said the thing that
you said before about that i told
you you are gonna tell me about
the paycheck advance listed paycheck advances you
gotta get him when you can because
sometimes you'll need food to eat thanks
danny i love you so much yeah
wish i could say the same goodbye
love you are my arm wow oh
my god
he hopped onto that semite to the
present day yeah
so you're just not allowed to say
yeah no no i'm not really um
cool but who cares if you do
or you don't i mean if i
say if i look at my phone
rural or be a real uphill and
say that that one was a sloppy
cunt pitch is everything okay well who
cares like it's just like you could
get another job
bob oh it's beautiful woman like you
stop know you'll be a model stop
no i've tried flash back
hey hon you ah you want a
model for me yeah i saw your
ad in the paper it was what
fifty cents for three nudes yeah fifty
cents so do you have fifty cents
on you daddy ready to blow this
we mean shut up shut up i'm
getting so you're gonna give me three
of your nudes yeah i think this
modeling works
look if you got the cash i
got the nudes handed okay your daddy
sense alright alright oh i don't have
any on me i just gotta take
them real quick so let me take
polls click click click click click thirty
go three nudes for your extra three
nudes for sale what was the date
so
september eleven oh my god nine eleven
i'm calling it dead for an hour
flashback to present
ah anyway ah one ticket just one
for the both of you yeah well
yeah this is she's gonna sit on
my lap this is my baby oh
why why did i'm like wow oh
wow this is my wife know you
sent children under two are free know
they are i just thought that was
a woman oh mccaw was alright anyway
once when i want to do okay
and
yeah thank you for ok thank you
thank you she paused god i can't
stand her but she bought it inspiring
works every time amazing alright so glad
that witch cursed me and i never
grew
why did she cursed by the way
oh i cut her weight i never
heard the story i don't know it's
like we we gotta move through this
two hundred years old yeah i know
all that stuff alright we've got to
sit down or buffet carriage traf we
gotta sit down alright
please take your seats i don't tell
my wife i'm a different person i'm
so excited for this show well don't
be because it's not very good i've
seen it first of all it's an
all white cast oh forgot about that
yeah sadly they're all doing black voices
okay that's not on the poster oh
sure
it should be it's a weird choice
okay well okay you're going to ask
like what is a black voice while
i put that in quotes you know
okay where it's very nice to meet
you anyway i gotta sit down oh
wow the lights usually go down while
i'd enjoy the show instead they're going
up i hope you and your way
you show she's she's my baby anyway
bay
baby who's this guy oh during the
night so during the nighttime
hello everyone i'm the theater manager harold
faulty meyer junior ex left guy in
the running man is ten times yeah
what's your candy that's six minutes or
eight minutes eight that was a house
flu because we were having two flashbacks
really ate into the time great way
ah that's gonna be it wow what
a time
thanks everyone and good suggestion oh my
gosh everyone has instagram because that's where
it's really popping off it's new ethanol
that's right we have an instagram now
freedom you were that were through team
usa on twitter and instagram instagram we
started posting reference photos for some of
the things that we talk about um
and it's been a it's been
fun so i follow it also if
you're interested in hearing more you can
binge these episodes five at a time
um on the stitcher premium app that's
absolutely correct there's three more just sitting
up there right now on the stitcher
premium app for you if you're listening
to this for free of course it
will keep coming out for free but
ah head over to see
sure premium and listen to the next
three domain explain how it works no
are you sure and you shit i
think i should try go ahead
okay three of them as a podcast
you can hear every week for free
wherever you get your podcasts but if
you're a stitcher premium subscriber you get
to hear some episodes early so our
new season which has just debuted we
put the first five-step first five eps
up on standup as a little bit
and fives ep by the way five
hives up
ah there are two more five episode
binges coming when episode while there's it's
out right now so we okay five
are already out and then the next
five so there's ten episodes available this
is episode seven but there are three
more available that's right and when the
eleventh episode of the new season comes
out on december thirty first new year's
eve there will be another then the
episode x five eleven
five will immediately all be together on
stitcher premium boy you explain that perfectly
not confusing
you get five at a time do
you think it's your premium and if
you don't want to get so creamy
get every week and if you don't
want to binge it don't binge it
if you don't want to listen don't
listen if you get such a premium
and you get five at a time
and you're gonna be sad next week
when you have a new one don't
binge it don't rain next week you
got it early but don't bend your
ears or
you do listen week to week but
listen the day before everyone hatches yes
talk the reddit thread off yeah chicken
spoilers ruin it for people yes alright
that's gonna be it that's gonna be
it gonna be all for listening thank
you to the listeners thank you to
our producer josh guess ah al
and we'll be back next we will
be back the running then i will
be back to running man alright bye
a
uh