three
oh
cp wow i did a question you
did a declarative statements yes three exact
three eyeliners through them oh rural threesome
ah welcome to three man as quickly
as the three women the best group
three to be fair to them welcome
to freedom i'm gonna chicken i can
open my his buckets god is drinking
a big bottle of piss huh now
it's an ice tea strawberry apple green
tea that looks fancy ah fancy don't
let me down ah his lyric of
don't let me down
oh lemon oh i that people still
don't know i stopped thinking of oh
let me down i expansive i was
thinking of that song da da da
know what does that no i know
what you mean come on da da
da show no no
national it'll bring me down doma so
much so many poor still don't
that's and brings and this i just
got into kate bush and i feel
like an asshole
why didn't i know and why didn't
i know oh yeah and then i
thought well some of those first of
all also it's a meat i mean
i just didn't you did you get
in through the future heads because didn't
you say that was initially how i
got into did they do a cover
of hounds of love and i knew
that song for some reason i don't
know why and then you sent it
to us i below
leave last november saying if you heard
this this is great no but i've
known that song forever but then i
figured you guys would know the kate
bush version and so then i didn't
know if you would know that wow
but then i and i kind of
been aware oh yeah but i mean
i've been aware of kate bush but
i have never dipped my toe yeah
and then i did and now i'm
like to do that tony doi it's
like of course wei joined a new
some influenced by like you know you
just see the trails and i felt
like i was an idiot whose trails
you saw the bush trails trails for
some reason i i i am not
a huge fan yeah i have oliver
records i put well that makes exactly
by the way i just was listening
to add to cart
where cool off was talking about your
collections and how you did you i
mean do you know i don't know
what she's talking about she talked about
how you collect an artist even if
you don't care really about every element
of that you want to have the
whole discount yeah she was crying yeah
she's actually screaming
oh i mean i want if i
want to find my ways in because
there have been all sorts of people
like bruce springsteen i was not a
fan for the first twenty five years
of my life i'd be like oh
he's corny or whatever and then i
heard a david bowie cover of it's
hard to be the same in the
city i was like that's a good
song and then i went back and
investigated and then that open opened it
up to me yeah i mean so
how long were your investigations
well i got my friends halo
i started putting dust everywhere was then
five years later
cleaned up i liked tunnel of love
by the way we are back in
the backyard and it's a windy day
and you can hear the wind i
feel like i am certain that the
wind will be heard and then joshua
say no no you can't hear it
yeah josh that flow i'm pretty sure
i can minimize this josh that's you
you click anywhere new losses vary sometimes
the wind will sound like sia yeah
well yeah did you get a new
crock no new no but there is
some crock there i have a crock
announcement okay
i what is it you didn't buy
the crock balls did how's this data
by the way these please stop sending
these da stuff we've seen what's the
other thing please stop sending us the
chile dogfish
fucking sucking on juilliard we know it
i die i'm gonna confess though i
haven't clicked it i finally collected oh
my god i used to get a
ticket i won't click and you get
a ticket i thought it was supposed
to be one or the other i
think it was both know if you
click that you get a ticket because
both i didn't think it was boo
my darling du livre dough
don't tag me bush and chili dogs
mother fucker man yeah so even that
guy is going i don't know why
they keep tagging people more these people
yeah
um okay my croc announcement i was
it's a crock but crush announcement yeah
i wanted to find a rhyme but
what's what's a note of pro chronicler
mation okay pro crl claymation i like
it with a crackerjack i'm a claymation
that makes more sense
alright a clinician kinda does huh
so i didn't break it to ya
hey better you hear it for me
that makes more sense not getting mad
i'm curious clutching his piss bottle too
hard no matter a check on my
piss i don't yeah
by the way
for for all these weirdos who keep
writing to apologize saying stop interrupting laura
and i case in point you just
as much i literally interrupt all the
time but here's one of the things
that i think is really heightening it
and then when we can blame josh
for this for fun
sure if said josh is posting choosing
to post yeah i suppose are ones
where i am being talked over heavily
and that's just what he's into he
loves it it's fine but yeah it's
gonna highlight that okay well anyway um
look the show is built on interruption
and it will die on the sky
cannot make a proclamation due to the
fact that
how long ago i said i had
a proclamation oh my god what is
it so cool i was on zoom
and asked me if i would pick
up something that we got delivered from
a career okay so i i it's
legal here you can say what it
is
so
um so i i was tracking the
courier and it said oh hey put
on a mask and all this stuff
so i went out and i went
down to hey hey
a pre-measured all this stuff oh yeah
right oh come on alaskan one of
them so she parked right in front
of our house and i opened the
gate and i went out and she
was handing me the stuff it was
a couple of things brick ofac and
i looked down at her feet what
she was wearing
crocs with charms on them and then
she saw it she saw my crocs
wow gibbins and she said hey i
like your giblets and i said well
i like yours too oh my god
it's connection in the time of cove
i found there we were mark oh
sure yeah yeah of course is
it is um i think giblets are
bringing the world together i just felt
like we were in a secret club
and i was like why did i
wait so long all didn't get the
ones with the holes and i saw
return mine and haven't bought ones that
i like yeah i know i feel
like i'm the only people that i've
literally worn them every single day since
like i'm the only people i feel
like i'm the only people you've worn
every day
day and i need really good ones
but what's in your way darla the
problem was that the glitter ones were
too hard and possibly a little bit
too small so i feel like i
have to really investigate i want to
release squish factor right you want that
squish yeah what do you what do
you want squishing you wanted inside okay
set up
i want it to be true you
said it harder to get inside but
i was very soft outside is eighty
except for yeah
yeah yeah that's going all ruining yeah
come on man aging this hey you're
losing to freedom this is the piss
drinking the piece of you're gonna piss
you remember the song we made up
in our show i want to try
to remember it now gone that ah
ha na da da da we want
we gotta na da thing in our
last livestream and turn it into a
song i was a potato and laura
i was a cookie and i don't
get why you don't want to do
do these shows
ah oh i think i think it
was that we were both barbie and
ken that's how it started and then
they became yeah well anyone listen listen
to that it's called watch it not
listen sorry and it's only five dollars
if you go online yeah you can
do that right it's okay for me
to plug
that here sure why not but in
the first ten minutes of our show
i don't
well i thought you would like this
song if we could remember it only
mentions really are over we gonna go
get there and i've get to write
a short this episode of three remember
i have fun know guys we know
we yell shit on here always fun
it's always fun that's right we don't
have to convince each other of that
okay no just because we're saying it
over and over
again doesn't mean we don't believe it's
really always fun right
yeah it's always fun it's always fun
but you know okay so i can't
find my crocs but i just i
do like blogs i have a pair
of wool clogs that are okay but
all you've said is clogged yeah with
a cork sole half linger all you've
said is that you need them slightly
bigger and slightly softer what is standing
i mean
i don't know what's standing my way
because nicole byer has about twenty pairs
choose tweeting the day she has her
beach pair her outside pair her inside
pair her shopping hair it's like i
saw that she said she accidentally wore
her inside pair outside and she was
very upset with herself yeah i liked
the idea of having them just for
inside yeah yeah well i
i don't know that i would i
mean i walk the dogs with them
but i don't know that i would
ever wear them
walk anywhere wanna ruin your whole sex
life
do you have slippers do i have
slippers do you have slippers i have
um well okay i've i've sandals that
i've worked all summer it's not slippers
and then i segue into the crags
when winter crop just decrease child thing
back
a few wow you know by law
these are just as good as crocs
clogs are just as good there okay
i got them on hollywood boulevard the
cold clogs they are the crux taught
costs too much by the way is
this crop top this is crock talk
i good officially josh play the jingle
the
reclamation part of back um but i
but when winter came and winter was
upon thinking of throw meaning like sixty
degrees but for some reason it gets
super cold now it does get cold
in my office which is not part
of the the central it's it's like
an e what are they called e
g eighty yeah
so it has it it basically just
has like a ah portal not portable
but the body it has a port-a-potty
here is an outhouse your important parties
your office support ten miles away from
your life like a step and i'm
fine yeah you like phones yes um
but so it just it was freezing
and i until i was wearing multiple
pairs of socks and
crocs i mean socks and crocs together
you're doing it now yeah i am
anyway what does it mean i don't
know if double rainbow paul didn't want
to get the one with the whole
suit couldn't have a gym it's i
didn't need the giblets i don't want
i don't believe you because you love
you love you coach romar but you
love the giblets of life like you
love the gym july viewer if anyway
when we're rigidity would be you what
you're a gym or a jib it
come to life but you
oh my god this is what we
need we need three zip it three
dim yes leaving the gym it's we
need to notation with the boys sure
to up and ah but this episode
is going to come out before we
get them on sale oh no really
we need to come down to look
forward to josh getting made
aid so that people can buy them
right now josh get the yeah if
we could get freedom giblets i'd be
really good i'd be really good and
probably want okay so we probably here's
a few designs
because you gotta have full freedom croc
oh yeah shouldn't you know view so
maybe like one of each of our
heads yeah one of the three of
us together one that says freedom and
then you need like five quotes like
like crackling nations your ugly shit need
a beautiful shine there yeah or a
helicopter because you go to hell
chapters would be rich banking pen yeah
probably restaurant roundup well do you need
to fill one whole crop of the
names while the restaurants in wow which
by the way i want to hear
where you guys worked i already told
you i were two places in i
know yeah then you got baby sitting
in the movies yeah
but paul has had interesting jobs i
mean we talked about tower video one
of their interesting i've had days when
you worked at the hat store when
we've heard a lot about that work
the hat store worked at a comic
book shop for kind of on their
comics every comic
every store does belfry row
first starting out those place called comics
and more on south street in mom
the moore was like ah action figures
and shit oh that's exactly what you
would expect yeah exactly i've told you
about this store that i went into
it wasn't like also we refill prescriptions
the store in santa maria which was
beads and things you worked there and
no i went in there because i
was putting posters for chickens mean the
wizard of oz i can't remember um
ignored
but yes ignore ignored ignored um but
i went in and she was like
this instead of ignoring something we have
to say ignoring alright will do that
well that's another gym that's hits instantly
yeah i got a test workshop it
was only proven gibbins
so i went into it we guys
gym it ceo is a full jib
or see joseph there was a monumental
episode a lot of people go into
sia ceo apologizes real quick i just
want to say somebody said that i
went to a cocktail party during cove
and i don't remember that happening so
what
because they were like saying that we
talk a lot about how people who
do follow the covert rules and break
them because which by the way not
everyone can follow them so i you
know of course we meet other people
never who we're talking about talking about
a holes but um i didn't go
to a cocktail party and i don't
know you're talking about so get off
i don't know if you go to
cocktail parties
when there isn't quite i don't i
mean i don't do anything anyways yeah
that's true but i feel sad but
i don't go to cocktail party we
did have one in this very backyard
where we were all is that what
we meant as far away from each
other as we are right now literally
so far apart we were screaming and
we just oh but which by the
way we were so far apart we
can
not have a single conversation so we
all just chat conversations our lives we
hadn't yeah which by the way i
want to talk about this and we'll
get back to beads and things and
then get back to comics and more
um but ah we we had been
talking about smash burgers on a previous
episode true and that was
big big topic covers me up topically
and paul didn't understand so what did
i do paul you made smash burgers
for me and jane you did i
did since when are you like the
fucking burger fare these are our our
coven confessions that's so nice i made
smashburger delivered them i
i didn't bring them over to his
house they came over here yeah oh
um and we ate super far away
from each other so it was good
it was delicious it sounds really good
so the smashburger pitched a plus i
think a a placer stretches better gibbet
oh that's right you do it's hard
to be invested in making my myself
a hamburger but she forbids me in
the hell wow because it just feels
like a lot of work for just
me but it sounds good was the
only way to determine mean yes since
he was a teenager you do you
find yourself eating vegetarian more because of
that or yes i do i don't
eat
as much meat as i would otherwise
but i i'll go i'll go out
of my way to get it i'll
get that was i mean good to
meet and get that meat shake out
and whatnot row take out a whatnot
but i don't cook me what's the
whatnot
we're talking about like and more yeah
okay so yeah back to beads and
things the things are
pool tables why no that's truly unhinged
yes the the bid the things were
pool tables but i'm sorry if you
want a pool table you're not gonna
go to beads and knows it was
bizarre that most high priced item in
your store you gotta call your store
that and then sell beads as like
impulse buys
guys maybe they saw i was fang
beads or a pool table those loyal
to you both oh my god she
get into beating did you ever see
my beaded pool table
it's beautiful it's really hard to play
on um i feel like it maybe
that's because they knew if it was
just pool tables no one would ever
known whatever yeah um like oh yeah
we're shopping if you're shopping for a
pool table and you and you were
looking in the yellow pages because this
was ninety ninety one or something and
you saw in the pool table set
when it said beads and things would
you even call them to see if
they had pool tables or would you
say that's a mistake i absolutely call
them out of curiosity and say well
i just need to know just like
i go every store and ask them
that every day
imo megan's ignored ignored
forget it okay so like there is
gonna be more
leave me hello know what is your
loss guys that was actually a really
good bit
get it so po when you were
to comics and more yes did you
work there because you were interested in
comics at the time or and and
were you one of those types of
employees who was helpful in that respect
i was somewhat interested in comics i
would say at that point in my
life the only comics that i was
acquainted
painted with were through my older brother
who collected comics when we were young
umm but i did not i never
really collected them myself myself but i
thought this would be like an okay
place to work you know right and
it wasn't oh wow um i worked
the the people i worked with there
was one guy who is just a
dumb guy
guy who his name full yea he
is he still remembers lasting but i
think i remember now i don't know
so don't say it but he he
did not like me instantly um was
just coming from the hat store yes
this is after so you're wearing a
bunch of those yeah like an air
of pretension sort of like hat man
yeah i came in with a bunch
of hats and then like batman i
got my comeuppance because a bunch of
monkeys came down from the tree
they all took my hats and i
said oh that's frustrating it was lorne
it was so frustrating
and then i got fired from that
place also you that fire i got
fired i was late i was five
minutes late twice and the second time
it happened um the manager told me
i don't want to fire you but
if i don't the assistant manager will
wrap me out to the boss and
then i'll get in truck
cool so i got to do this
so i'm like what tugs away a
big problem and i really want understand
what's the big problem with arriving five
minutes late to come book store if
you're not opening it i don't know
yeah yeah and i wasn't even thinking
someone just shift right like you're replacing
someone i don't they have to stay
the extra think so i think i
was probably coming on i don't know
but it's fucking five minutes yeah i
guess i could fire you guys from
three of them for being five minutes
like it's that's why i'm asking we
could fire you for freedom oh really
yeah try it okay oh my god
let's try you're fired no okay hold
on thanks you're firing me you're fired
fuck oh i didn't know
yeah you're right oh my god okay
good and just count yeah scout um
well that's so so this had nothing
to do with the guy who hated
you know that was just another gambler
yeah so why was it so bad
though other than they just fired you
you after being late well it wasn't
it wasn't fun though other the the
there was one guy had very bad
breath
those talker um the guy who was
the guy who would have ratted on
me to get his superior fired right
obviously not a great guy
the wind the wind umbrellas gonna eat
me you know there's an umbrella above
paul that is blowing around and shaking
but i think it's steady i hope
so it's very scary today i didn't
have a daydream on the way here
of an umbrella um flying at me
and then me ducking and rolling wow
you're really athletic
this daydream i know and then and
then my daydream he made fun of
me but i did protect myself so
i felt that it was worth it
this is a lot this is why
you're driving
a lot happened
speaking of ducking and rolls you think
about somebody meaningless no of course yes
but that seemed like an elaborate daydream
for driving it was like ten seconds
but it was it was ten seconds
where you were not paying attention to
the rise slightly but sometimes i think
i think i do this a lot
where i'll have a gestalt like that
and they go well
that happens i'm psychic yeah how many
times has it ever happened i am
psychic about a couple of things okay
people calling me ma people following up
on emails and people texting me like
i'll be like i'll like i'll think
about like oh i haven't heard from
that person but that email in a
while and then i just get
email like that happens a lot so
i feel like i have brain waves
that are like connected to the to
the internet oh okay the vote i
have known any time someone has called
me to tell me that someone has
died i've always known immediately that's why
they were calling yeah do you think
it's a tone thing or you just
like it's their calling a weird times
though right no
no it's not that it's it's it's
it's not like a waking me up
in the middle of the night it's
the the few times that it's happened
happened like three or four times and
every time and as soon as i
answered as soon as they said hello
i knew and i don't think it
could be just a tone thing but
but you just felt it in your
gut yeah yeah yeah although i this
meat too
two technicality like once cool up and
i were were in paris and my
mom called me and i and left
a message and i knew something was
bad because she knew we were in
paris right and i was just like
okay this is bad and it was
but then every once in a while
like my mom will call and have
that tone and i'm like say yeah
hello scott and i'll say hi what's
going on and it'll be something so
trivial it won't make me so mad
she uses me too because i often
think that's what's happening and then she's
like what's going on and i'm like
okay
i got a little scared
does your mom usually call you scott
or she call you a little term
of india um what does she call
yoshi calls me scott i think hello
scott yeah that's that's her hello scott
is your mother is a woman who
is half of your dna this is
your legal mother
huh so just
when the sun popped out or just
like i don't know something shifted and
it was just blinding for a story
it'll be down time like we're where
we may be going into dark times
on one of these episodes and that'll
be exciting three am after dark right
i'll be exciting things can happen anything
her hair down
you get dirty so wait so paul
hat store comic store tower video no
way no those upstart videos was here
i had a bunch of jobs in
philly but just listing jobs you've had
stopped listing them don't do it don't
do it you have a high school
job a high school job was that
that we discussed earlier was that p
it's a place that i worked out
for like three days tim kehl pakistan
had to yes it was yes a
pizza place yeah yeah he doesn't anyway
i had to take time off for
the school day and the guy was
like yeah you guess right you don't
have a job right yeah yeah right
right okay so pizza place then hat
store to pizza place that have store
then comic store and comic store then
ah
ah beta only video beta only wow
it was called that or that's all
they had the both
it was all deposition binary so pool
table
we fade max why would they open
a store there was an imax in
the nights yeah i know it was
probably a front for something that i
didn't realize oh okay yeah but people
we did have seven customers that would
come in so it is that is
your beta and more experience how you
got the tower videos made to only
update and more there was no more
but is that how you got the
tower video job because you had made
no i would imagine you saying bit
more i don't know line i also
don't know why you would need videos
george beers to work at a video
store but did you isn't okay is
that an entry level job or something
anyone wouldn't you don't make the videos
when tarantino ended up
using only seven customers yeah for the
beta store yeah we have the same
whole team seven people that would come
oh yeah yeah yeah and you know
of course they wouldn't come in every
day i've this is well doctor damon
every day this is well documented in
my fabulous stand-up our laboring under the
delusion seven be the same seven people
came in every day then you know
it's a front
for somebody it would be very weird
every single day there's ah exact set
of the same company order they get
a video
was just where we're at we're we're
all of their interests the same like
like they all just were popular movies
or was there one guy who was
always porn or i don't think we
had any adult film no beta or
no beta porn did you guys calling
our more mature go in the porn
room with the video sir
i did when i was eighteen and
i was like oh i can do
this now and i remember just being
ashamed and then i went in and
the woman saying are you eighteen and
yes and me saying yes ma'am and
she didn't even check i was like
oh i could've been doing this for
a couple of years
but it seems so hard to rent
a porn as a kid and then
figure out how to watch it and
it just seems like too much work
well okay you're still discovering your body
l you're growing hair in places you
haven't had it before especially if you
don't have a vcr in your bedroom
like to watch it in the common
room to wait for her to go
to bettors everyone to go to bed
and then you have to turn super
low and then it's way too risky
it's way too risky yeah it's bad
or it's so important so much easier
i wonder if kids are like yeah
inundated no they are now it is
is that good or is it bad
i think it's great oh
i'd like picking up anything they want
now it's bad but isn't that better
than having hear about incredible shame about
it and having to hide it doesn't
mean you won't feel that but you're
going to be like once fingering and
then like one second later like wow
nah it's better for you to have
to just kind of figure that out
she shouldn't porn be illegal until you've
had sex for the first time
yeah so it's not an age thing
one thing that i that i hear
about a lot that they never occurred
to me is that um pp it
goes in the yes and i was
like what
going around the back
they both do the same thing occurred
to me um that ah people who
were who were brought up with a
you know unlimited porn essentially access to
porn that it it fucks them up
in their relationships in their sexual relationships
because that's how they sort of learn
what sex
right and so they think it's it's
supposed to be like porn covered in
body oil and when joking but
with a stepsister i just actually saw
this um like instagram real today of
this very religious person that i saw
my friends checking on every once in
a while
like you know we'll send a little
like oh here's what she's up to
right now if someone you know or
no no no it's like sort of
instagram famous religious person and she married
this guy like la but i think
what it was they never kissed until
their wedding so then they posted the
video of that they'd be youtubers and
another on instagram okay but
anyway it's kind of fascinating and they
have a baby now and it's just
like how they kissed really hard and
she posted today or recently about porn
being like if you have a porn
problem and so it's like it's basically
like a video that's going like some
music playing and then she's like silently
acting out stuff while
like words pop up you know like
basically tick tock format and it's like
porn isn't porn is a bad addiction
that ruins the relationship between man and
wife like and if you have a
problem poor and like you could fix
it move it it's like it just
and then she's kind of like bopping
around like smiling like pointing at the
words right pointing at her bible
super weird read this thing but just
like porn is it was all the
reasons why porn is like really horrible
well here's my counterpoint is counter poison
gas sexism mysterious i remember when i
was fun sex best when it's one
on exactly but you um so
so this almost stopped threesomes i never
saw i never saw like ah an
actual porn where it was like insertion
until i was eighteen um muzzles off
and everything before then was just like
weird cinemax movies the that i killed
her with your penis next to the
vagina were simulated in every
motion and saxophones are playing with yeah
like a lot of butts soft core
yeah yeah soft core porn so i
remember the first time i saw porn
i was like shocked that i was
like oh i didn't even know porn
was poor i thought it was there's
the front yeah but i thought it
was like playboy where you don't see
anything and was simulated or whatever yeah
so i was like oh
but then it actually was like oh
so that's what you're supposed to do
i mean i think that's like it's
it's like fine in an educational sense
but like it's so it can be
anything and that's i think there's so
much now that like you could click
on something that's like really scarring yeah
i mean like totally totally the one
of the things i've seen on accident
that are just like terrifying it's like
ah like yeah and being a little
kid
having no way to process yeah so
yeah maybe there should be like a
porn site that's good for
people teenagers
like i'm not teaching this is really
bad
no but i will say i took
a human sexuality class in college when
i was nineteen or seventy just a
negative na and and i took it
because people were like yeah basically you
just watch porn in the class and
it was like
essentially just this teacher showing movies and
talking about various things and then the
only thing i remember from the class
begins with get a load of this
hello to this little um wow
my lord the age the only thing
i remember from the class and i
failed it and i failed all my
classes because i just ended up not
going to class anymore yeah that'll do
it but um all i remember is
him talking about a dude he knew
who had a huge dick and the
teacher yeah yeah or someone
he'd read about or something and he
said imagining this teacher yes those saw
news one guy oh so to say
so but he was saying like you
know everyone talks about size and how
like they you know they brag about
size or whatever but i actually know
someone who has a very large penis
and you know what he has to
do every time he has sex or
the first
umea sex with a woman and he
clicked out the lights and he's like
he has to do that because otherwise
they'll get to scare guys
this is a carbon lights came back
on he was nude me
checks yes yes
like also to draw pass tax like
that's like a real problem is like
so stupid
you don't think ah that's like i'm
learning more about your husband
ah alright we did
right back
and we're back yeah hey thing came
i'm plugged oh no yeah i mean
i can still hear you it's my
headphone oh it's your headphones came on
blah blah
oh hey phone came on blah welcome
back to three of them we never
introduce ourselves but i'm scott i'm paul
and i'm lord yeah man then i
worked at tower books oh it wasn't
that after reviewer it's getting kind of
ah this was after beta only okay
is this an l i now know
this
in philly with our books okay tom
looks acid beta things go out of
style they were out of style in
the nineties i mean like hell it
wasn't in a very short time that
they were yeah yeah it was for
sure i mean it was i remember
dvds came came out and like ninety
five that's when i first started them
so it was
like but already after like laserdisc when
they like yeah yeah yeah yeah so
but laser discs were still around because
i used to go into a laser
disc store every tuesday to to see
the new dvd releases do you have
a collection of laser discs no i
never did laser discs but i did
dvds and club used to call it
i would i was making my rounds
i
would do it on wednesdays usually where
i would go to the comic store
and then go to sue the laser
disc store for the dvds there were
my errands you know picking up whatever
when i worked at teller video they
still had laser discs yeah they'd probably
male deer valley you would be one
of the seven customers at paul's beta
store but no i'm in the nineties
no one
i had beta know it had already
been crushed by vss you guys keep
talking i'm gonna move on this yeah
sure both i'm gonna i'm gonna move
this umbrella for lawrence you
and then yeah tower when i worked
at tower books that was this is
also on the same street south street
i worked up and down the street
and so when you would get fired
you just like go down to doors
and knock on the next one and
be like can i work here yes
tower books unfortunately that i had to
quit beta only because i had been
ah
cause i was getting so many standup
gigs and so then um well that's
that's a successful moment yeah but then
it dried up and i had to
get a day job again tower books
was my last day job before i
moved to l a and how old
are you to move to la i
was twenty five years old twenty
five years old and that felt old
to me too yeah i moved i
guess i was twenty three
yeah twenty four maybe oh that's great
that's great
when you move from you just stand
you were twenty three when you moved
from chicago to new york from new
york to shoot to la okay i
was twenty yeah something like that twenty
three twenty four oh my god this
is you i think you didn't do
anything unfortunately do you want take this
umbrella because i'm freezing
you want to switch by all the
shade in the world we have our
coven friendly microphones exactly we're doing it
right well i could just say we
ignore it'll just go away eventually
i mean now all the umbrellas are
just piled around paul put your sunnies
on
yep put those sunglasses on back and
i did nothing to help when i
worked to tower books that was the
time when howard stern was on the
rise and he had written his first
book private parts oh yeah and we
held an event at tower books um
in philadelphia which was of course a
huge deal because he
he humiliated john dibella the host of
the morning zoo um he ah the
morning the john duval is the host
of the morning joe that was the
number one show for years and years
and years in philly um they would
they would do the same jokes every
day
say like fuckin some sound cards and
everything every single day and then when
howard stern entered the philadelphia market he
um as he's from philadelphia no no
no he shows indicate his shows indicate
so when it came to philadelphia he
made a big show of saying i'm
gonna crush this guy john
dibella like arsenio did about j that's
so meal that's gonna kick johnny different
because he was like already really successful
jay leno like ah like local news
or local zoo person feels like meeting
to just shit on no jay it
was yeah it was singer yeah
it is the same no j just
got the tonight show or oh i
think he just got for ten years
and and so are cindy was like
i'm like yeah that's hilarious did he
do it he did not he was
already i think he stopped to show
a year later so i did it
for a year know our signal had
been going for ah a few years
prior and so that's why he thought
he was gonna
and then people say i thought you're
gonna kick his ass and he said
i didn't say when and it's too
much it's way way too it's gonna
come yeah have you watched the wendy
williams documentary side note no you have
to watch this okay anyways i call
her wendy o williams is that okay
why because of the plasma attics that's
right they were on um sctv ones
yes yeah
um so howard stern himself was there
it was a huge event lines around
the block to get in and get
your book signed by howard stern well
that would be very exciting i bet
if i if i was in howard
stern it would have been oh i
liked howard but i wasn't but he
wouldn't he wouldn't do anything like that
now there's no like at the time
it was like ok
i'll do this thing because i wanna
sell my trying to get yeah exactly
yeah exactly but he like he made
john dibella like apologize for being on
the air like he did it with
say this whole theatre of humiliation of
this guy that dibella went along with
money it was crazy it was bananas
that's funny
i like it it's good to see
apologies for being on the air yeah
so so books and still boost you
did use it to get free books
to detail them says well er no
i i bought books with my employee
discount you can also borrow books do
you remember a book that you bought
at that time fuck i remember buying
um
if this is the right time i
remember buying the biography of dean martin
that nick tashi oh yeah i read
that yeah yeah um it's all about
ah
or it ends doesn't it with dean
martin watching what someone he was in
a movie with doing a commercial for
adult diapers and something like that yeah
thinking like how did we sink so
low or something like this all i
know the author imagining imagining dean martin
thought process yes and i remember i
really liked the book i wonder if
i would like it now yeah i
read that in the the jerry lewis
one they used to be saved by
side on my bookshelf oh i was
like he also wrote a jerry lee
lewis one josh interesting in a similar
vein of like okay imagining being inside
that ended also with him looking at
someone doing an adult team exactly exact
serie lee lewis he's saying oh my
god
goodness gracious good i like hey i've
heard it physically flinch revolts to buy
that he was the killer ah he
said a piano on fire jerry lee
lewis or ah no who am i
talking about dennis quaid desperate pleading in
the movie and insane yes portrayal of
him who should you get how about
yeah two two feet taller and cannot
sing and it's just gonna do the
craziest i want yeah it's it's it's
crazy yeah i saw that in the
theater with great balls of fire movies
great balls of fire by a friend
and i have a false front of
my snuck into the movies to see
that movie were like we got there
we got there early
or like one reason let's just like
let's just go in now as there's
nobody at the ticket counter oh scott
sought at the arcadia cineplex number four
it was a four twelve show there
was a woman with a baby and
there was a another man
i saw it on cable
yeah but we hit on the floor
why lie the disgusting movie theater oh
what an addict we were like sitting
there and then we heard a voice
and we're like oh get out get
out good oh my god i missed
out on the gross world i miss
being in the gross know i know
my friend did i used to sneak
into so many movies that we
we we were gonna write a book
a wanted poster
wanting to losers
you're gonna write a book and call
it to furs about how to sneak
into a movie and all the thought
processing one page long know we have
so many theories on how to do
it theories and and i remember we
would look up and this was mainly
at the arroyo grande a six but
we would look up we would look
up
which theater it was playing at okay
and we go oh my god we
got a straight shot because there was
one particular theater their big one that
had an exit door lead you a
big one that led you not outside
but to right there where more theatres
were lacking you could just walk right
in it was good yeah i sure
i've told you
this my my family famously insisted that
we all see when i when i
was in the movie tenacious d and
the pick of destiny yeah my family
and sister will see that when i
come home for thanksgiving my god it's
happening with holmes and watson crossed i
had already seen it i didn't need
to see it again they're like no
no no we're all going to go
together as a family i go there
with janie and
with ah my future brother and sister-in-law
we get there first my family does
not show up what until after the
opening credits oh my god they had
gone to another movie oh and then
were stealing this movie but fifty bills
oh my hmm ya yeah
either way yeah if you're gonna do
it but also leave me out of
it you rye oh they miss your
fart know they saw my part and
know when i say nobody said anything
and yeah they didn't say i'm i'm
on my own it a few times
oh you're in you getting to yeah
they didn't say anything i know the
one i remember my mother called me
me and said um that i got
i got home when i got home
there was this message that she left
me while i was flying home that
said you know thinking about you in
that movie and i think i figured
it out um every you were everyone
else was so crazy and then you
were not being crazy and i think
that
it's what it was and i'm like
that's what it was yes yeah i
think what she meant was that's why
i thought you were not good in
nano instead you're underplaying it for me
i'm playing ah yes i'm playing a
deadpan character ever seen that movie but
i think everyone loves you in that
movie like they they also tally remember
even the series as well
yea yeah playing the same characters so
i'm in two seeds like yeah but
people like really remember that yes they
do they do because there's a big
speech at the end and then i
turned in the devil so that you
the devil yeah what what it's it's
already spoiled radios i told you my
mom the first time i was mister
show and this was
just as an extra part this is
the season two best of where it
was the fake infomercial oh yeah yeah
and we and and so bob and
david always were like hey let's get
some friends who won't mind us not
paying yeah um and so we were
all up in the up in the
seats and and my mom and dad
unbeknownst to me they didn't
say they were going to do this
but they didn't have hbo so they
rented a hotel room oh yes you
go see it and then they called
me the next day and said said
they did it and i went oh
okay well what did you think and
she goes well
you've gained a lot of weight all
at once i said okay well would
you think of the show and she
goes well we turned it off after
ten minutes
oh my guy we saw what we
needed to see i was reading about
um actually i was listening to a
podcast about kathy the woman who made
cathy comics because the guys white yes
yeah and it was all about her
as wide shut if there was a
podcast the longest shortest time um
and it's like a podcast about children
i think because this podcast was all
about her having a child by herself
in like her i don't know bedroom
thirty or forty oh um but at
the time nobody was really doing this
some raw but she's successful she draws
and writes kathy yes but she was
hitch she was talking about and by
the way she's like really cute like
it's very funny to see her because
she's not like an act yeah yeah
nah i need to like have that
care to be so choosy i'm her
i'd watch your shop for bathing suits
zak yeah exactly
thank you kathy periodically as to oh
and it doesn't go well but that's
actually not a bad catchphrase like watching
the guy is horny well that's what
they do on the bachelor it's like
tj's on a walk out oh wait
watch they're all the woman's shopping like
yeah it's always like hey here's a
great date where i'm gonna take you
shopping and you're gonna try
on several physically right do you think
it's because of pretty woman so ugly
they love is the reason why it's
good for the woman is that she
comes home with twenty bags of clothes
that you get free plus jewelry big
mistake yeah yeah and they get tons
of other girls are always really challenged
of like she got twenty thousand dollars
where the stuff and and all we
did was we wrote horse
i mean it's true it doesn't really
ever make sense like why did they
get that one person to go do
it in order to cause drum well
i know but it's just you know
it because with the alcohol was four
i guess i'm out but my point
is more that she told this story
about um visiting her daughter at college
like her graduation or something and she
was like so proud of her and
just thinking like how amazing it was
and she
she saw her across the campus and
she was like she's so beautiful and
she's like then i walked right up
to her and said like in-universe your
hair and it just like funny how
she's like i couldn't control myself like
even though i like that's how she's
like wow bombs do like ross just
so strong describing like the way she
felt an a hole all she felt
was proud and then like she walked
up to
her and was like that's incorrect said
something like you need to johnson crunch
yeah i that's weirdly comforting to yeah
yeah yeah i think it's because i
think it's so true it's like i
couldn't have been the only thing your
mom was thinking about that but then
it's like the one thing that comes
out is like i think she has
awareness of it later because the one
time i've seen them this year was
when i had to go down
down and and take care of my
dad because my mom have an operation
so i went down and we just
got into a like my right before
i left we got into a big
fight because i went to pick up
her pain medication and i went and
you took all of them before you
go yes oh you oh you're saying
i shoulda have
now i went to the pharmacy's she
doesn't normally go to and referential upset
and she was upset at me and
and it was a big fight and
like i was like mom i know
you like things the way you like
things but you got the pills what's
wrong anyway so like two days later
i got a call i'm sorry i
said you were fat it's funny
years ago i'm still waiting for that
now with that sorry wait so two
days later she calls and she's called
in said apologized and said she knew
you know so i think you have
awareness maybe in your mind while it's
happening i have no idea well maybe
when my mother and i are reunited
in heaven i'll get all those apologies
when i think you're going to have
it interesting i don't
she got either she's in hell no
she isn't with an atheist and that
is a no no don't you ever
think that like don't you ever kind
of know you're doing that like i
feel i know i'm doing that sometimes
like i yeah i know i'm a
part of it's going stuff saying this
and then i'm just going at it
yeah i got to via annoying for
whatever reason
yes yeah absolutely i hate it though
because like i truly am going to
stop like i i do it to
my like there's just you know random
things i can't even like what is
your theme deserve like well yeah like
what do you mean like like what
is what is your technique of like
i can i can intensely pinpoint what
my mom's technique is that drives me
up the wall
so when cool uh oh i'm always
like that's my mom oh yeah and
i do one thing like his mom
and he's like what oh my god
yeah well it's like making it's like
i i kind of one thing i
do a lot is that i um
ask him to just do stuff right
now like like i'll just be like
can you empty the dishwasher and he's
like i'm reading and it's like well
i want you to do yeah
yeah yeah i know it's stupid but
it's like i do that right away
but i'm trying the dishwasher
that's you know obviously during covert everyone's
learning how to divvy up chores yeah
better and all my stuff but i
just realized the other day i was
i'd been putting it off for hours
and hours and then i started so
i was like alright let's do this
shit i'm put on music is like
a song let me put on some
new
isaac and it'll it'll pass the time
better hi the eighties song it was
dumb
that's always my argument i go like
it'll take two minutes and like i'll
be like can't he finish the pale
chores chapter of course of course we're
like and and we were talking about
last thing because we were face time
with his friend joey and like i
said oh fiona you um move this
you doing as you saw it like
yeah he's trying to be an actor
can you move this
to the other part of the house
and and then he's like joe is
like why don't you do it like
he's on face time and he's like
why don't you do it i'm like
because i want him to do it
yeah and he's like yeah and he
was saying that his girlfriend does that
a lot where she's like mike's grover
yeah it's guava joey's girlfriend will be
like do go to this thing for
me and like he's like
if you want to don't you do
it i'm like because we do because
we owe everything to be equal for
yes it's nice or at least you
want response i do seventy percent of
the stuff i'm just asking you to
do thirty by yes my responses like
we do so much that you don't
even acknowledge that is being done that
makes everything great yeah and all i
want is for like me to know
how to do these things
and then they're like we do stuff
too and it's like okay like yeah
we work out but it takes hours
like it does feel like i do
i do believe that there is a
like imbalance of yeah that stuff and
with most relationships like brothers it's to
a point where i'm like upset about
it it's more just like that's why
it comes out in that way
when she's a mom ish sort of
thing to do and so it's fast
and so that that's triggering for him
because of his mom yeah like ah
does that particular thing and so it's
yeah so maybe if you didn't do
that particular thing you could get away
with like minute thing that he likes
now that might be like really my
way of fixing it is i'll say
when you feel like it can you
do
do this and then he's like thank
you for saying when i feel like
this and then it's like great so
then and not even when you get
a second but when you feel yeah
yeah yeah if you ever feel like
just if you ever get okay yeah
it's like sometime today could you do
this or whatever and since then i
then i can take it off my
plate in my head yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's good but yeah i were
on the topic of the dishwasher yeah
i would much rather load the dishwasher
then empty the dishwasher no it's a
yucky empty news is crazy how little
time it takes the paul i know
but here's the thing you don't know
where stuff goes no i do know
where stuff goes and that's the problem
is that
when you're putting the study in the
dishwasher you are you're putting together a
little puzzle which ideally take this like
i liked that part of it sure
when you're putting things away it's like
gotta go over here gotta go here
gotta go over here yeah there's a
lot of walking whereas if you're if
you're ap the sees anyone the walking
but it's like i wish if every
single child dishwasher went if i could
do
the puzzle right in front like on
the cabinet oh yeah if it were
the same thing in reverse that would
be what if you kept all your
dishes right above the dishwasher scott i'd
love nothing more
lungi has another way cabinets work some
cabinets could be ripped up again it's
good we could do that but then
the thing is you have to wait
is in our kitchen is we have
a cabinet that is like there are
two shelves that are accessible and then
there's one shelf that we have to
stand on something to get to like
janie she gets out
or she stands on me yeah where
the other so you can shoot yeah
so we could get we could get
ah and that right now is where
our glassware and our coffee mugs are
we can't get plates in there too
you have to stand on something to
get your glass ware no no no
there's a shelf above it's like seldom
you
used say yeah i was gonna say
yeah i think you should move the
glasses interesting i i'm gonna glass you
gotta get a step ladder
somebody's gonna spot you and your eyeglasses
that's where you keep those yes i
have some wear my glasses i can't
see
check the kitchen cupboard i'm eccentric and
eccentric yeah i read an interesting article
the other day and perhaps you guys
read it but talked about porn i
thought it was i thought it was
helpful in these times which was a
person who was getting really depressed during
coven during quarantine me saying no no
you
really oh check the byline i was
like this has gotta be written by
ball
the first line is i'm a depressing
piece of shit i was like famously
a depressing piece of shit um buddy
but they were talking to their therapist
and they were like there are days
where the dishes are just stacking up
and i cannot i just can't get
off the couch to do yes and
the therapist was like
well a big because because he's like
i can't rinse them and then load
the dishwasher and the therapist is like
just run the dishwasher twice oh wait
yes i did man and i really
liked that and the person was like
well you're not supposed to do that
and the therapist said we're in the
middle of quarantine like take care of
yourself just run the dishwasher twice yeah
and
that saves so much of this person's
mental space he was like okay i'll
just run the dishwasher twice and it'll
get clean and it just made them
feel better and that it was a
metaphor for a larger thing like do
it you need to you know run
the dishwasher twice in whatever area of
your life you need to absolutely yeah
that was a great article those great
piece do you feel like you guys
both go to therapy
i have to go back i have
ah like last i
last was my therapy i don't rewatch
it my god sometimes i feel like
the smoke motors after me um i
yeah i went for a long time
and it was it was extraordinarily helpful
for me um but lately you know
i've been i've been needing it again
and especially with the last year has
been
really fucking tough when you stopped going
did you tell your therapist or did
you just kind of show growing less
and less less i believe it was
a while ago and believe we had
a discussion about it yeah you know
um and then i just felt like
i because i felt like i was
kind of hitting a wall with therapy
whereas like i was i was going
but i wasn't really getting anything out
of it i felt like i was
just going
saying the same things over and over
yeah right and um because you're going
weekly and not much i was going
weekly how much would change yeah yeah
hard during that i feel like during
this time because i i go but
i go once every two weeks now
on zoom um but i feel like
usually i just focus on like one
problem that's
like weighing on me or whatever yeah
like i it's it just is kind
of weird during this time because like
nothing's really happening then the whatever the
problem is is way bigger than it
probably would be if it was normal
time like someone having a problem with
a friend or something that i'm like
ah and it's like this isn't really
that big of a deal but yeah
right now it feels like it at
the very beginning of quarantine right before
started i tried seeing a new therapist
got a recommendation and it was such
a this this it made me realize
how i really lucked out the first
time i went because i got somebody
that i clicked with right away and
then this guy used like an he
was a nice man but there was
something
about his his style that was very
um ah
how to put this because it was
not it was not he's listening right
now it was not ill intended it
wasn't thinking what to do it about
he didn't choose to therapy day one
who's like i love three-day um he
eyes it came off kind of condescending
like he was talking to me like
i was a child and like borderline
and it was like i knew
no he doesn't i know he's not
talking down to me i know this
is just his style but it's not
enough for you yeah yeah well also
probably because you don't like being talked
down to in any area of your
life so when someone there's like five
areas of my life i love being
talking
wait my picture on zoom is from
between two ferns where i'm playing the
trumpet oh and i say something about
that before yes you do not have
rights to that photo i know that
i've never told you this i don't
think but when i liked that scene
where it went oh yeah he works
as a movie know when
when things would get really tough on
that movie because there was the post
process was very difficult i would watch
that scene where you would say you
got this
cheer me up oh sorry sad swe
what about my machines
well i just want to say that
my picture and zoom is is like
a still of me like blowing the
trumpet and it just silly because i
just felt like run over this that
moment before you people see when i'm
therapy it always feels weird when it
pops up because it's like so silly
right before i go in right to
see her this is what you're dealing
with but then she said
she was like i love that picture
of you it's so sweet and so
and she was talking about it and
then it became clear she thought i
was a little
a little mentally challenged girl you thought
it was me as a kid and
i was like that was oh a
year i was like oh that was
like two years ago i took a
joke in a movie or whatever she's
like oh my god i thought it
was a sweet picture was like yeah
no that's me now wouldn't you love
return to that innocent child blowing the
trump if you could talk to her
what would you say like ah god
alright we need to take another break
and we're back and it's time for
a three-acre yeah so shut up everyone
you guys have sent us three cheers
in this one was submitted by josh
superfan josh and josh backend it he
loves the show so much he decides
to edit it together he's gotten most
of the three cheers on the show
um this is called taboo word fuck
taboo word um two players secretly decide
on a taboo word by texting each
other the word then
all three of us began a scene
prompted by the suggestion of a common
household item wait i missed a crucial
element i don't know we're just we're
just this has nothing to do with
the taboo word just we like say
lauren and i decided on it on
a word that's taboo venus so say
it's venus we're not allowed
to say penis in the scene you
were trying to get called to say
we were trying to get paul to
say penis but the scene is about
anything that seems about anything but but
this says it's prompted by the suggestion
of a common household item yes ah
and if the scene ends without anyone
saying the taboo word the third player
wins okay so it's like
and the wait time wait if you
guys watch the hustler on abc yes
i love it yes oh you made
a mafia i just heard about this
show yes yeah record hitler whatever but
it's very fun but that's kind of
the rules like if to convince one
person than to the two people in
the audience at home do they know
who the hustler is now no shit
so early playing
last thing and i'm swear i'm wrong
like sometimes i'll pick the person right
away and then other times i get
it wrong the entire time and it's
very fun it's fun um so lauren
should you and i do the taboo
word for yes and then okay so
um why don't you text me the
word that you think it should be
taboo and then we will start now
but it had to do to doo
to do
about it out loud to say bow
wow duty but we're not allowed at
done bow buddy do you do and
then paul do you want to say
a household item and will start the
scene and and we'll time it you
know what i do and i think
i've got to say dishwasher dishwasher we
go on topic guys
will do will do five and z
east kenshin is eight gazed you guys
it's in the zinc easy guys you
guys it could not hurt would say
that we did know the distribution come
up because we were talking about other
disease
will do five minutes and will
we're gonna try to get paul to
say within five minutes if we don't
he wins face you may think it's
because we want to know okay alright
here we go ready and go
hey guys i really need you both
to step it up as roommates someone's
gotta do the dishes i can't be
the only one doing the dishes well
i have to say paul and i
because we share a room we should
only do it half the time and
you should do it half the time
because yes it's a two bedroom apart
we're paying for one room
them and so are you so yeah
it should be half and half do
you guys use half the dishes i
use half of all the dishes in
the house we eat on the same
plate and we just put a tape
because they use half of half the
dishes and i just point out like
let's look at all these dishes that
are in the sink they have food
on them like what is this this
is like just desc
gusting this is i mean well that
one i'm still eating what we have
we have unusual and unusual diets crepes
yeah okay we have an unusual yeah
oh you're aware from france and we
only eat grapes were chocolate and i
mean what we do we do we
do savory crepes but we also do
sweeper yes that one has chocolate raspberries
ah some crim crash also i mean
there's mince sometimes and also other fruits
christopher ministering plot you came over was
covered in a crepe yes he was
a giant creep he had a he
and his schoolmates have been taking a
tour of creep factory and he fell
what was in the thing that he
fell into the vat yeah great that
there was a crb fresher ah chocolate
maple syrup ah i think raspberries um
and flour their kiwi there was kiwi
there was kiwi there was ken
to loop there was not not by
the way cantaloupe because it was the
us three song cantaloupe that's right there
was ah what was i was i
was singing the candlewood i wanna hear
when my roommate is gonna say there
was also i think some hanukkah gelt
was in there
where do you see foiled what do
you think i was gonna say felt
fish gvl to fish there was pineapple
there was there was joe baker bermuda
come i'm gonna sue ya
all of the i mean there were
plantations there were battles yeah hey i
thought i said that earlier did oh
were you gonna say before he interrupted
me you said simba i was gonna
say about an os i o c
we would have gotten it so much
sooner
did you know we were trying to
lead you into saying a certain fruit
or or i didn't know if it
was a certain fruit i knew the
i knew what the object of the
game was yes no but i mean
what did you feel like i was
guiding you towards a fruit no not
necessarily good we didn't played well right
right yeah you did a great job
alright who wants to be the taboo
too
to yea this time i mean yes
we do with with whom with you
with paul oh it would be the
taboo too yes the taboo too yes
i guess me and you okay do
you want me to text your order
do you want to take me away
who want you to take me where
did you check the last word no
okay okay so um i'm texting you
a word
and then i am waiting for the
texted word from you and what are
you doing i was just looking at
my phone okay baby i got so
lauren do you wanna do you wanna
say what the household item is i
do ok the household item we are
working with today is couch fuck couch
and i'm going to time it
it and i'm going to start the
timer
now
well i'm so glad that we got
up off the couch i am tuning
into this restaurant it's so nice to
be out and about so i love
it i love hello i'm here waiter
this yeah boy
obviously
i wanted it to be over i
just really wanted to get it
yeah
like struts in restaurants you know that's
what it was i just figured it
was gonna be you know couch surfing
huh huh nice to get off anyway
go to this restaurant oh my god
that made me really laugh so nice
to wake up get out of bed
none of our day
a and then go to this restaurant
okay paul you text the word to
lauren and i will be the household
item alright
paul is texting the taboo we're now
a buddy to his the other half
of the taboo to do boo boo
badoo power to see to do to
beat a day to alright
and the word has been texted and
i have not received it
have it okay and scott would you
like to give us the household object
who house learning objects i will say
ceiling fan okay
oh let me start the timer wow
i think we're gonna need a step
ladder
oh yeah well we it's hard to
get the dust off of these things
yeah i guys i um
i bought a stepladder two weeks ago
oh fantastic are you are you going
to share it with us ah it's
in the other room and you're gonna
have to come with me to get
it why are you scared
i am oh i know you're scared
oh it's the haunted room because of
that thing you saw yeah it's the
it's the room where i swear i
saw a ghost ran what did it
look like it was green and it
had ectoplasm it was eating a bunch
of hot dogs just had a hotdog
cart it was around where i'm gonna
like
climber classic slimer aka yeah yeah yeah
eating hotdogs you said you know it
wasn't real scott
to address this because this has been
hanging over our our home for the
last you know few weeks now it's
a big thing i swear talking anytime
i pass by that that room i
feel a chill i feel like it's
thirty degrees colder in that room well
there's a chill in this room because
you have this problem
with seeing a quote unquote ghosts i
swear if you just come there with
me you'll see it goes to look
can we just stop pretending
let's go in the room and see
come with me guys coming alright
here why did you make that noise
because when i'm walking and you know
it it muffles the sound of my
steps you know it sounds like you
have to peg legs
that's really insensitive because you know that
i have they're not pegged just saying
like oscar pistorius like blades i don't
want to get into this again i
do actually
here's the thing look look let gonna
hold on a second okay no no
no we gotta go okay could you
do you don't want to get into
this and it's like we have all
these topics building up that we're not
allowed to talk about well like what's
the one that you don't want to
talk oh me yeah well like what's
taboo to you what's what is
taboo to me and to taboo to
me what is taboo is the taboo
oh my god from from ah what's
called ah like a piece oh
luckily i don't want to talk about
who i saw on cuckoo says that
true yeah i'm not you don't remember
the employees said hey man i love
your music you said i'm just on
my ground you know i'm gonna take
a different tactic here with scott because
i read i don't want to look
for slimer don't think i wanna see
slimmer but i'm gonna close my eyes
and try see if i can feel
slimer oh
that's a great idea i will do
that too okay okay i feel a
big
big fan
big fan feels like a leather fan
who's what are you kissing hey don't
do it if we close our eyes
don't start kissing us sorry oh that
is not a cool way you feel
a big leather fan are you touching
an elephant ah gotcha
oh thank god
the manager said that i was like
oh they're trying to leave of elephant
the idea that
both sides when i know i didn't
win i win but i already did
the same thing i liked i like
it when we win every one twenty
know what side their rights fun oh
my god learning is fun yeah alright
it is oh it is fun learn
do you wanna send me
ah yeah the word and then paul
will be i know it's grease of
course reaches the word is the word
used to be bird bird is no
longer the word the word is no
grease the word has been sent
great paul do you want to have
a ah ah household item i don't
have a house
i to have a house on item
when you want to household filled with
items ah i'm gonna say ah remote
control remote control and start
hey can you pass me the remote
control please i want to watch a
movie which one we have like tim
like barman star go to vista del
mar no no he was dead remotes
oh which remote do you need the
one for the the blu ray player
or the betamax no give me the
baby oh alright hello
there you go thanks ah do you
like this movie well i haven't seen
it yet i yeah it's very good
things like oh i'll watch o is
one of my favorite i love i
love i love these guys so you've
seen it already yeah i've seen it
it's one of my favorite things yum
oh my god it's ding dong hai
deng di di tom how are you
let's plays
it's good we're just watching burn sir
can i hang out yeah just don't
do it in ding dah yeah have
you seen this movie yeah i saw
it if you like it right i
loved it damn that's she's okay she's
so funny which one ah not annie
but um
ah christian
not any not and on any momo
but kristin is funny the other actors
yes what kristin is funny in it
i think i think they're both funny
but i think kristin she's playing a
dual role it's she's really christian davis
is in this no yeah what's your
last name
wow
oh paul you're balding what you gotta
take care of this i do not
i gotta get plots oh something a
little more trump
oh and yeah i'm driving to school
i'm laying with the toys canada something
either party
huh
don't freak out don't you know don't
know don't know don't flip your lid
well we have three minutes to ah
write all those wig ah one of
you is lying
a christian touquet yeah
i thought it was just subtle enough
because it's ah i always said at
the very first time i will not
say you should do you should follow
that instinct
alright i'm going to text
all i'm going to receive the text
um
oh guy go great citizen update you
asked your passes twenty eight million cases
of coven nineteen that say oh alright
lawrence you wanna come up with a
household item i also love nectar we're
linking with right now is called
he has called
oh hello alright and go oh boy
i had a crazy dream last night
where i wasn't eating marshmallows and eating
marshmallow eating marshmallows multiple visiting one giant
marshmallow yeah yeah you know how i
know you do because you are saying
marshmallow marshmallow marshmallow oh i know i'm
talking to sleepy it's
ooh blue blue not only that but
you walked into my room to talk
about it
how do you know because i i
well i was going to turn on
the light but we paid a bill
yeah
hey eviction
you're trying to get it
you try to sta
anyway here are you paying down
like
experts
hey dingo why were you hanging out
with those other dudes today the guy
was jealous wouldn't we we ate it
when you don't hang out with us
well that they had something to offer
me was going well they watching barbara
starr good and they gave me dvd
copies if i would star multiple dvd
college barbara starr well sorry we can't
watch it
okay why evicted okay turned off everything
up all your stuff and go no
electricity yeah were you trying to say
kind of
and vicarious fun when i say yes
it's fine alright one more no you
know we should try again not right
now but maybe on the next episode
is that game where you bring the
stuff to the picnic because i think
we were okay we did we did
it wrong we we i talk about
we definitely did it right here remember
what i remember when we learned something
afterwards yeah made it make a lot
more sense
it seem maybe even fun we're gonna
play one more paul's gonna text lauren
and i'm gonna say the household item
and ah now and then we're gonna
end the episode so get ready for
that okay guys you're ready for the
end of the episode and be winding
down soon okay yes alright did you
i don't know you're crying lee
later when it ends because you told
you did you receive the text i
got it alright and specialists start
i love camping i like it i'm
i loathe it wow the all through
we have we all feel the feeling
that say bears of camping yeah well
it's where's our goldilocks huh yeah yeah
hey guys last night what app did
you hear that
sound i heard that bear that like
came into a bear yeah no oh
yeah are you sure we came into
the ten two minutes attended like poke
tusla all in together now guys didn't
see it i'm sorry it wasn't a
bear it wasn't a bear there's i
wouldn't have made out with a bear
oh my god ding dong
ang ding dah
ding dong where were you yesterday because
it seemed like you were never how
were you late to the camping tri
was here i just i met ray
bring all these copies their urban star
listen i was in the tent last
night with you guys are all attend
together the big ten and there was
that rustling in the in the trees
and rustling in the leaves and them
and that some yeah not a bear
came in and i'm made love y'all
wait so whatever came into our tent
last night made love to you yeah
i remember it's a big shadow i
guess i assumed it was a bear
but maybe it was satan
i don't think so because when i
said hail satan he just grunts
and made him more into it i'll
say would have been like thank you
yeah yeah yeah wow that's crazy anyway
what do you want to do today
i don't know but we should try
to figure out what that thing was
because i fucked it yeah i agree
i don't i'd like to move on
from this topic okay fine so what
do you wanna have for breakfast um
hash browns okay that's it
that's it that's all i want alright
i'm not gonna list of bunch of
stuff i know i'm absolutely not only
was asked but i'm actually not ask
you can list as much food as
you fucking want okay legs hash browns
milk eggs milk chocolate gang wu boys
ricketts really came back to
god what ding dong what does it
think on your password
but you didn't you disappear for days
on end did you see that the
track weight doing in the ground those
footprints yeah i see them they're there
they look to be a size eight
nike zara you think yeah because i'm
looking at it as it looks a
little fantastic you're looking at your own
foot stupid
oh no damn what's up plans
oh i got a damn don
damn daniel you're looking at your own
shoe with the white kicks
the pumped up kicks well this is
crazy i don't know what you think
it is why don't you tell me
what you think it is think it
might be like some sort of mountain
man ooh yeah so a mountain man
came in our data bron up to
the brawny paper towel man or nick
offer yeah i'm just glad he found
me and that either want to you
guys because it was
thanks for taking the bullet oh wait
you're glad because it was awesome not
because you secondly i mean sellers
ding dong what's up please i don't
know you like you are mysterious like
you disappear for days on end we
don't know where you are yeah you're
like a mythical creature yeah sometimes i
do find myself wandering the woods in
the middle of the night hoping to
be caught and just a glimpse by
someone who isn't sure they saw me
you wouldn't want to drink i have
some sprite here
no
you'll like the loch ness monsters atm
yeah no soda you don't drink soda
what before noon i'd say noone is
a good time to start
from noon noon to wed noon to
six so time so to tell them
so hours six to one to two
so no nursing so wonder eleven fifty
nine but doesn't the other sure um
i feel like you guys should go
track whatever this is i mean i'm
not even heard of anything like this
yeah all the time
i'm like what well there was this
i saw this movie tenacious d in
the pick of destiny and there was
this crazy monster at the end of
it which why wot yeah well it
was the monster the demo dave grohl
played it was it smell after the
fall events or religious figure that's not
a monster i think he wasn't small
i remember there was another monster in
that movie yeah that's true jack black
no come on just he's nice he's
my guy although yeah
just say it's got a sasquatch know
abominable snowman no bigfoot yeah okay so
we had fun and then it was
rare was eight seconds i could have
derived oh my guide r c cola
sprite as me
ethical creature nah speaking of three cher's
well guys i was fun i enjoyed
it i enjoyed jonah to um oh
there goes the alarm oh well time
to go everyone time to go everyone
go to sleep later stop drinking soda
good-night good-night by
a