yeah
god
you know there was something about today's
energy where there was just dead silence
not looking getting till there between each
yo but yeah she hated i had
my eyes closed in between each yale
just trying to feel now is it
i kill you guys when we yell
mad i know it's embarrassing i typically
i don't think we do look at
each other but i glanced over and
noticed how much we weren't looking at
each other
and how there wasn't energy between each
yell which i knew even in the
room there just was nothing i feel
like i'm bringing that energy yeah i
know what's going on guys because i
feel like i am so hyped to
do because i'm doing great now i'm
cracked out of him i have
wrong crack on crack cocaine yeah different
due to my addiction we never did
yeah lawrence topics on crack cocaine i
forgot to tell you guys i have
a new hobby and she's ah she's
on an only because she's addicted to
it it's not yeah sounds like she
thought she doesn't think it's quite unhappy
oh yes she just has to actually
get sick um i've not been sleeping
well
l at all this week and i
feel like i had like major depression
yesterday which was almost funny where i
was like why do i this is
out of nowhere yeah wasn't totally related
to the sleeping or i think it
is related to the sleeping yeah yeah
yeah yeah but it just like hit
you yesterday of just like yesterday it
was bad really it was like i'm
on a fucking elliptical machine and i'm
like am i going to cry on
this machine oh nah dan and and
sleep problems what's happening all night long
i am having like stressful dreams i'm
waking up a lot ah today like
last night went to bed early but
woke up in the night woke up
before my alarm and i thought no
like i'm on let's just an hour
before my alarm i can start my
day had coffee didn't do anything it
just felt like i felt like i
just
fatigue yeah not at all or no
you've caught a wall take a nap
i don't believe i have copied i'll
test again but i just testify the
thing just the other day well the
early bird gets the worm yeah i'm
trying to get worms
you listen with warm
you want to eat more worms to
lose weight i want to get heartworms
oh god what is so sick i
just because now i'm michael hornworms yes
okay good luck pin worms ooh no
you're right because i'm like you know
always reading these baby and child related
things now and then there's like moms
being like my kid keeps itching
in her ass and then it's like
oh she has norms put tape on
her ass and they take up there
saying yeah
like snitching for tape her ass shut
essentially yeah this is a real thing
it was like put tape on it
and then at night you take it
off and then like there's a worm
on it no they come out at
night
the worms come matinee so worms come
out at night so like put some
little scotch tape around the um does
that three scotch um no but you
know when i used to brand side
does that reminds me i went back
when i went to ireland when i
was in seventh grade i was making
a scrapbook while i was traveling and
i wanted scotch
tape and that couldn't have been more
confusing and they point me to a
box of cassettes oh i wanted scotch
tape wait they had scotch bray what
does like help what do they think
company they didn't have the team but
what do they call they had scott
scott notate they had scottish music on
cassette oh so like the proclaimers i
don't know
hey would walk by maybe side mileage
was your second language basically i like
knowing what they are talking about
a yeah anyways i don't want anyone
to ever pin worms in my world
so so what are you putting the
tape on beautiful i put the tape
every night
my own but she puts it to
anything i put the tip of my
butt every night when i get the
whole stick my buddy here and see
what happens yeah it puts the tape
on the puts the lotion yeah no
puts the lotion kid what if it
gets the lotion in the tape it
puts the lotion on it's skin or
else it gets a papoose lotion on
its skin the tape won't stick that's
right
so that's why you put the lotion
in the basket okay i'll take that
lotion you put on the day i'll
make a lotion for five hundred please
yes okay the question is who use
this much lotion i thought we had
more oh ah who is buffalo bill
that's right nice scott controls the board
okay
let's not touch
it's category oh i gotta pick em
yeah oh lord pulling the boar ah
don't tear it down tear down the
whole board tear it down for how
much for i'll pay you a thousand
dollars destroy the board down so i
went for a negative one thousand dollars
who was told to tear down a
wall by ronald wilson reagan
who is ah that little bespectacled forehead
guy mikhail gorbachev that is correct scott
maintains control of the bomb rocked it
out to the time that he figured
out what he was talking about and
then he got it he didn't get
the full boop no he didn't get
the there would be no i miss
alex trebek yeah i miss him every
day
i recall well first of all i'm
very pissed because i had an opportunity
to go see jeopardy a cup like
right before the pandemic and then i
didn't coordinate it well i'm like i
had a hookup there who was gonna
like let me come to a taping
was it arabic yeah and but it
was when he was he was there
and i'm so sad i didn't get
to go live because i'm in jeopardy
fantasy yeah mister groan yeah
say hi afterward i would have loved
to do that i was working on
some sitcom and it was right and
jeopardy was right across yeah the stage
and i wanted to go in there
so badly but i was scared of
getting in trouble yeah only when i
went into was ah prices right i
spun the wheel
you do i only got like sixty
five it was a bummer ah you
could have still done wow i know
what you want to hit the dollar
you want when i was working the
greatest job my life sees one of
real time with bill maher so i
was right he was right but that's
why it was yeah absolutely i support
paul they would
no i did come when you were
on it didn't generally hey i don't
know what you built around real time
with gum no no i just came
to the audience and when i went
downstairs best place to be from what
was your job like sort of i
respire no i well kind of i
love noi also i had my own
little segment okay this his first this
was first show
back it was real reporting real news
i was in kosovo this was his
bill hearing this was his return to
television after politically incorrect you know had
been k yeah famously and um so
they were trying to to play around
with the format of the show and
so what if in the beginning the
middle we have this guy who does
like a more lighthearted thing
thing that was basically like a monologue
comedic monologue about something in the news
yes yeah you wrote yeah performed that
poorly wrote and i love it i
thought you did great both well you're
very kind i thought it was so
good
i just finished learning of it yeah
a lot of people either reaction because
i can't see it yeah um but
ah the prices right stuff was just
like stored in the hallway haha in
that in that building until next big
couches and fridges are like no like
the fucking big wheels so you could
just hoard it like why didn't they
just have it out at the time
no it was out
all the time they they just would
shove it out in the hallway ah
and so you could go up and
like spin the wheel and everything to
make any noise but it was fun
and yeah that's the thing is is
it it wasn't the the clicker or
whatever like the david's body that's not
that's not actually a thing right yeah
but shown yeah you're kidding
yeah no if it's i feel like
because i just wanna have to be
it just went whoosh when but maybe
they plug it in and then plug
it in
right before everything became so technological i
got ilan samus became so so so
sort of neutered and and extreme like
i'm like new dr liked it when
vanna had to flip the number the
letter i liked yeah like watching eye
to eye that matter and i liked
watching prices i had to click click
and i liked it yeah like when
you used to shop on ah wheel
of fortune yeah yeah i'll tell you
either dining set i'll take the broyhill
furniture i'll take the fifty two it
they only have a limited amount of
time to do it but then they
would always just run long and that's
a would just be like okay you
have five hundred dollars left you need
to pick something i it's
slow down my show so that dumb
statue here's what should happen wordle should
be replaced by a an app that
is for wheel of fortune and then
we compete every day to see who
guesses the hangman of sorts before the
other oh the hangman you're right wheel
of fortune news based on agma yes
it is because he made it sound
so polite and nice
yes i feel that they have a
hanging person they should yeah we'll show
wizard of oz thing we're like there
yeah fortune should have a guy who's
being oh yeah literally yeah you don't
get it right yeah but they they
put on his limbs one at a
time they put them on so it's
a it's a it's a previously yeah
well no it's not it's torso it's
just a torso
oh and then they attach yeah what
happens in hangman again you what do
you draw first the draw the ahead
first so it's when you get that
last leg that's when your last arm
or you while you decide beforehand or
you gonna play with toes are you
doing close are you doing yeah i've
never heard of any of these ah
what am i trying to say variations
when you're a kid i think it's
your ricky
i knew this was gonna happen i
can i felt it and there you're
desperate energy yeah no no i love
it guys i have to leave
oh my love videos oh me am
i just making sure my phone isn't
blowing up oh my god oh my
know when you're when you're a kid
sometimes your parents are a little more
generous with you knowing that like you're
not going to work out so much
so it's like you agree beforehand because
typical hangman yes it's ah you got
the head you got the body to
arms
right but a gruesome game but but
the but your parents you can sort
of decide like oh okay we're gonna
you're gonna get to have feet yeah
you know or you're gonna get to
have any more chances you if you're
really like dive fingers on youtube five
years any chance you've gotten all the
letters of the alphabet by that point
it's like you know wow media wow
nah four five six plus and then
plus ten that's sixteen if you buy
sixteen then toes twenty six twenty six
so what if he did all fares
on the head if you had a
numbers and you were doing close though
i think like a t-shirt and pants
at some what was on the t-shirt
smelly things do
and then you would complete that slowly
right exactly i know those are calling
smiley faces and within within reason why
they ought to call it state sponsored
execution yes thank you say what it
really is that's right we're in favor
of it yeah yeah a lot of
it yeah i hate when they pardon
that turkey
what is with that show they put
up it's so bad it's so to
go groundhog you know it's all it's
it's gotta be
cute it's not for us learning a
turkey my my opinion is is not
for us it's for it's for biden
because the job is so grim and
solemn it's like hey but you get
to do this once i went to
yet is how would you like to
do this that that mimics our execution
system that we still have in our
country but it's like huge and be
fun for you cute and you can
see kids for an hour you know
what i mean easter egg roll etc
make it should have one every once
you think a president these days you
kids say hey yeah i hear a
good impression to give away that's right
bring the kids that's right we're gonna
give my toys here's a deal wait
come on man
ah here's the deal man here i
wanna do it hey jackie i'm jus
baby hey yeah bye yea where's my
home lab job hey put the hot
dogs in the buns man he really
we're creating jobs we have lots of
job
your job to catch ya your mom
can get a chair when your dad
could get a job
it's just oh no adult is a
big problem hiring all these ninety year
old ask your mom if you can
get a job that's good tell your
dad i want to go to work
dad i want to work i'm six
years old when i when i wanna
work we are both doing grown-up delaware
i wanna i wanna i wanna get
in there with my little finger
workers want to put together wanna ride
a bicycle i want to go down
the hill with my legs but yeah
i wanna i wanna i wanna put
someone like a little row bunny in
the basket i don't want to give
it a ride i wanna i want
show it the world like a bunny
in the basket or else it gets
the hose again alone shit um i'm
sure i've told you this this this
story before
please tell and we want to hear
it please let me know nice hey
like i said i was depressed enough
um i went to visit my friend
who lived a little ways away but
it was walking distance and i thought
how fun if i roller skate over
there and what i did not take
into account was that
um there were a couple of big
hills on the well where like up
the sidewalk went down like when i
when i was first going it was
so steep that i had to like
put your ass to hang onto yeah
i had to like hang onto to
like parked cars and stuff because i
could not there was no way that
elementum would have killed me right what's
worse going down or going up going
up as worse i had to like
it was like doing now i was
always myself up by like parking meters
oh why does use take this scott
that's a great show
yeah never occurred to me wow never
occurred yeah there on times the stuff
with their own your families is wild
when you later realize oh simple resolution
yeah exactly like you could have killed
yourself instead of just taking off your
skates and that's a great lesson look
my parents paid for those skates and
they gave
them to me and i was not
going to disrespect them by taking them
off and walking in my stocking feet
so they gave you this gates yeah
he bought them and then gave them
to you i think so you owe
me they didn't charge you for i'll
be very honest here i don't remember
i don't remember my brother michel great
rollerblades that were forest green glitter color
ooh
they were fantastic and i loved them
so much and i would just sip
zip zipper on i remember i had
blue skates with orange wheels and that's
cool yeah nice i had blue and
orange kids and i loved them really
get those now i thought about what
was blue was yeah what yeah it
was a blue seeker with orange trim
wow the copper orange not the rubber
the rubber
she's like road was like the design
on the side and everything oh that's
nice yeah it's like a nice really
good shoe that's a good question what
style of shoe what what what company
made it kids kids did okay cancer
just for kids though right you think
cows know anyone's allowed to wear do
you think your circle who started the
company keds also says melk probably
early and as a business of melk
yeah hi would you know anyone like
to buy milk okay
wow if you want if you want
to win this auction put a bet
on it can i just say there's
a huge formula baby formula store shortage
here are you are you being problem
i just started panicking last night well
i went to target two days ago
and i just picked up one thing
a formula that narrative that they just
put in that's been there for twelve
years i need to go see that
you want to target
it only about one item while i
had it you don't even know what
i was doing i was dried up
full cart and you know ragging rubbermaid
bins around the store we don't which
was another thing where i was like
i could've done this at the end
but i didn't think i stopped midway
yeah exactly i thought midway through the
the journey and i was like that's
too bad wheels on it so wasn't
having to deal but i got one
thing form
mila and then really i was like
rio's all they have no and i
just grabbed one because my heart was
so full and i was gonna have
to do it all by myself loading
everything and i was like one's fine
i have one other one at home
and then i was like online i'm
noticing this and i had read about
the the shortage but i was like
i guess my brand's not a problem
it's right here and shit bro not
realize yeah urban shit i didn't realize
my dog i got four kids that
the shelves were totally empty but i
didn't it didn't i didn't clock it
in the moment and then i went
online last night trying to find more
and it was not available to any
target no formula of any brand so
what if you went back to that
same target oh i thought maybe i
could but there was only a couple
left and then my friend said my
friend found me summit a
walmart kind of far away and bought
it up for me so i can
pick it up oh thanks but last
night i ordered a bunch online from
grocery store i ordered a like ten
containers yeah and then this morning they
said they didn't have it oh no
then my friend found this other one
at walmart and so hopefully i'll be
able to get it when i pick
it up but yeah dude why rising
why is there a shortage it's just
my chan shoes
yeah the tits that make formula powder
yeah are all dried up no no
it's really crazy because it's like it's
very serious picks off tds they forgot
to rotate out the women know it's
a very serious problem and i'm hoping
that everyone who's listening is in dealing
with this is able to get what
they need because it's very crazy i
i hope and pray that that is
the case that people can get with
you
but why is why really why i
don't understand why every brand is down
at the same time as it was
just the toilet paper shortage the way
it was explained to me was ah
there are two types of toilet paper
um there's stuff people use at home
and then there's stuff people use in
offices yes the worst the industrial yeah
right and um everyone
left the offices and so no one's
using all the toilet paper in offices
oh they're all using it at home
and the supplies shocked they can't get
in there and the supply chain is
like building up outside of the stores
and the builders now double the demand
fuel which is going into shitting in
front of the office yeah but there's
more to the whole office can agree
is more demand than ever for the
regular
for the regulates double the demand so
there that's why i don't know i
would just briefly reading soon last name
that i sent me into a panic
i just started searching for formulas or
babies not going back to the office
anymore yeah oh yeah and then there's
of course horrible threads of idiots being
like why don't you breast-feed and i
was like oh you can't just start
lactating out of nowhere
i give you one hundred dollars right
now you couldn't i mean one hundred
dollars
eight hundred dollars onto it
hundred dollars you could milk me greg
ah bro robert de niro
are you talking to me because you
want to give you money why was
he so mean to greg
every time you watch that i think
i talked about on this show but
i thought it was glare it's still
good that there's a lot i haven't
seen it since it came out but
i bet there's a lot of funny
stuff no it's yeah it's a classic
it's definitely classic um yeah why was
he though i mean i guess it
ties into the whole like no one's
because enough precious girl or wow is
that a real thing oh yeah like
are you going to feel that way
like yes let holly date whoever
i'm going to have my cat piss
the toilet front of whichever man comes
or woman or non binary person comes
into my home no one is a
robot for my robot pet whatever are
you trying are you going to try
to lead a holly's suitor into saying
that you can milk anything with nipples
i will definitely try to get you
the person to act out all of
that movie if you can set that
up so the person doesn't know that
it's happening yeah that would be a
few basic like if if you and
mike and everyone were doing that scene
yeah and even holly everyone knew about
it accept the person who i wouldn't
say this has to be so it's
going to be like twenty to twenty
five years from now yeah yeah and
everyone's off book yeah
wow plenty of timely time yes yeah
yeah remember memories one word a day
until then and you'll yeah five guys
hologram i got the first word
what what liz think that there's only
because actually interesting one word a day
when we're in a year probably three
hundred and sixty five or forty years
year no it's not good okay one
word for it's it's beyond the mountains
can we compromise one word of month
one word a day no i'm saying
well okay i guess you could get
can i get you into the scene
yeah the whole movie do you wanna
do the whole movie i was saying
the c o o you're gonna you're
gonna engineer the whole movie yes okay
interestingly the water bottle that shouldn't so
if someone gave you a transcription if
someone gave you a transcription of meet
the parents and you memorized one word
a day and you just added every
day you're like okay today is it's
like memorizing pi or something
yeah it's just the dialogue is go
hey yeah fucker yeah hey the first
verse line of that movie could you
do it in twenty five years because
you memorize the entire movie yeah but
what i'm trying to tell you is
three hundred and sixty five words a
year times twenty five is probably not
a full movie that's not very many
words are you also going to do
until lightly it's seven pages you also
around ten thousand words are going to
do lord of the rings style and
memory as meet the fockers as well
at the st like back-to-back yeah back
to the future to enhance memories lord
of the rings at the same time
as well okay now if you can
engineer that you might be original one
that wants to
the parents of my brethren you might
be an elf neck
how do you know if you're a
redneck i'm really there's so many ways
check your day job anyways to learn
as adrian brody once i'm seriously wondering
if you've been good
okay okay na blue baby bad you
ever seen your money david spade do
that and that's an empty what you
might be redneck ah i don't know
if i did he did jeff foxworthy
yeah i i think i remember that
yeah it was funny i'll have to
google that later as yeah please give
it a quick goop as he would
so google in um we crashed to
watch gal gadot me why did i
watch that i watched i watched all
of it you know why i watched
it anne hathaway was brilliant she was
good yeah and stop being mean anne
hathaway she's good actor because i mean
yeah she's
black like she's so hard to take
and it's like what are you hanging
out with she's funny how long by
the way and she was so good
in that role and that movie i
was blown away when they show not
movie whatever show and they reese whatever
limited series laura zara zara that ltd
series i love just when that end
did
id and they showed the real people
yeah i was extremely confused because stars
they're just like us of course but
jared leto surely handsome man as we
know had prosthetics on them in the
show the character that he is playing
the person very good looking he did
not need to put on why he
had prussia looks weird almost thing he
does he doesn't need to do it's
home
i'm and we don't need him to
do it i was very taken to
tacit agreement between everybody audience in him
let's let this guy off the hook
it was like jared you're free for
members possibility take five five i need
you to have brown contacts and a
different nose yeah for me to understand
that you're being a different guy i
also didn't notice that he had prosthetic
soccer that's weird imo
yeah his feet looked totally different it
didn't it didn't not get them at
all it was all happening right here
i never look right well yeah laura
was a real bridge of the nose
yeah i'm i only stare at that
i never make eye contact yeah yeah
yeah right right in between yeah right
but the way was stunning in the
role i thought fantastic great lower voice
it was very absolutely um and yeah
then i saw the real person she
was playing in i was also blown
away by the casting choice the whole
thing was just because real lady was
blown away to like actually is a
super model so you know right she's
gorgeous she's a stunning woman when the
man and you're saying the original is
ugly i'm not saying that i'm just
saying if they're gonna put prosthetics on
july
edo to make him look less hot
to look like that guy i didn't
understand the whole concept of the looks
you're going for i see what you're
saying i see you trying to dig
a hole around me to fall into
just relaxing it's ever electing unless you
have percent x on yeah real acting
yeah god i would love to do
some real acting i would loan out
to me i'd love to just stretch
out like you tried
really shakes i'd let oh man to
get some statics and do wm oh
my god that would be a mate
will the actor's dream to do romeo
with just giant jowls well yeah but
yeah what if it's just a lateral
move like jared leto and we were
in we crashed right and it's just
they just made you look like a
different guy a different same level of
attractiveness yeah
yeah well poor scotch i won't hear
it made it eat atty no delete
added either that sound means lauren was
to change this update yeah it appears
we need to take a break because
lauren has started doing our playoff music
amsterdam but if you were watching the
oscars and instead of the
a nice soaring orchestral thing it was
just lowering good
oh really do you no good my
team dancing across the stage to like
swipe people off because hey man yeah
oh yeah exactly daddy daddy to do
better shame and that should be on
every award show it should be the
sandman yeah sure you adopt that style
yeah sorry no and the actual segment
yeah
he's still with us a lot of
work for him how we take a
break do you think ok we take
we gotta take a break where we
were to just said something were to
take a break no time no thank
you
our back and lauren we had to
go to a break because lord had
to take the biggest shit these guys
go whole toilet flooring yeah i rose
up on a mountain yeah alright i
started so i'm getting all these
damn tax on what's app only started
writing back to them oh i love
that okay what do you got i
like this one begins with sorry i
have the wrong number
usually there's one thing before you have
sorry yeah right number why are you
starting yeah don't you don't text me
i already knows you to let you
know i don't know who you are
sorry i say the wrong number my
carelessness hope you don't my carelessness hope
you don't i wrote back no i
think it's wonderful sorry i say the
wrong number my carelessness
i hope you don't mind again it
was enjoyable any time
sorry i hope i'm mistaken bother you
it did not bother me it was
the greatest moment of my life so
far
acquaintances fate if you mind if i
ask which city you live in i
live in sacramento california the greatest city
in the world and you my friend
where do you call home and is
it magical
i'm from singapore and currently living in
los angeles usa oh my goodness are
you a hollywood movie star of the
silver screen
i'm ready and waiting for one and
we read a lot of similar things
when we that we did on instagram
yeah like because it was like where
are you from i am from whatever
yeah the boise i was like i'm
from boise idaho usa because they wrote
that to me it's it was so
but like they have they have such
a weird script that they're going with
i know and what what is
posed to happen well i mean someone
in our family was just like totally
taken in but was that one of
those it was a scam tax tape
through facebook yeah oh yeah because i
heard it on add to cart okay
so she talks about it yeah okay
yeah so she told the whole story
okay yeah it's really i mean it's
very thing you can say if you
want to say it's very i mean
they they just
you know and i told you i
think that my mom also was fell
victim to one of these scams it's
just like very just i'm always time
i'm i'm like do not click a
knee thing ever oh my god but
yeah it was it was just basically
like hi i think it was something
to the effect of high your cousin
who they had inflated that trick like
that's a real
oh that feels a little more than
trying to engage nepal in like they're
trying to say like i'm in los
angeles oh maybe you're somewhere in los
angeles we should meet up and i
have this opportunity for you and all
this kind of stuff oh god so
she yeah and remembered the one that
i went i went off on the
guy and i was like oh he's
like what is what business are you
in and i was like i thought
we were both
in the business of scamming strangers and
you go yeah yeah yeah i was
like ok i guess i go to
hell you buddy yeah the one thing
everyone should know is if anyone ever
asks you for like i itunes gift
cards to to photograph the backs of
them with the numbers that it is
a scam
are they this or apple giftcard yeah
or anything like that yeah it's like
it's basically ah those are untraceable like
once you take once you take a
picture of these numbers they just use
them as cash and it's untraceable and
that's why they asked for them all
the time like god looks so bad
with that story that was so awful
and stress
useful because then you have to like
try to like fix it all and
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but look
if it sounds too weird to be
true it is yeah and i think
that it's really shady though to reference
another family member because that makes you
think oh this is oh zazu yeah
exactly but also after after she was
taken in by them they took over
her facebook
account because she gave all of her
passwords to them and all that and
so they start going out to everyone
she knew including some of my family
members and ah saying like hi this
is it wasn't cool op who did
this i don't think we yeah oh
it's cool small yeah but hi this
is pat and we're like i just
wanted to let you you know ask
you if ah what what does
is your social security number you know
just curious i've always been wondering what
those numbers look like when you write
them hey what does your social security
number again i remember it's like one
two three four five and nine digits
yeah yeah it's just so crazy that
the fact that they're people and they're
out there because it works i know
but it's just so sad that there
are
people out there with such ah you
know low character yeah know what's really
for living what's amazing to me is
that i haven't been scammed i just
take a job on a sitcom anyway
so exension stay drank actor
my um i've never been scammed but
my security number is one two three
four five six seven eight nine really
yeah okay were you the first time
or no the first one one one
one moment or just yeah why would
they even start with nine numbers at
that point yeah one no he was
the one millionth and yeah and balloons
came down to the diamond thirty one
thousand two
i'm home shot you out it's like
ooh they set off fireworks cannons confetti
yeah because it was like your number
was finally the one we will been
waiting for exactly i'm like that that
like number flaps went down was like
one to so many flaps and they
haven't put that it was in the
paper they put my picture in the
paper with the number wow oh no
it's out there see
through that's the thing everyone knows what
let's see i was born on january
first
three thousand four hundred fifty six and
seventy nine yeah
january second three thousand thousand fifty six
seventy eight ninety eight yes
that's a letter that's a lawyer from
the future from one hundred and yeah
i was fifteen hundred years and dewey
is that right yeah yeah the da
da da da da da da da
da da da da da da ny
guy guy guy gets it sound like
you're talking yeah okay so
oh god oh i don't like that
i lacked shouldn't if i had my
challenge cat who did pass and september
rest her soul she used to live
near the interval she was at war
huh really like lots of big meows
coming out that you think you'll see
her in hell yeah probably
allows you to have an all cats
go to hell ah yeah i'll probably
see er yeah yeah um do you
like what
do you like when huskies scream for
no reason what's that husky dogs they
just are like was like oh yeah
oh wow craziest noises like when he's
very funny to moya id you know
yes huh would like when someday their
beautiful dog there's so beautiful a huge
white fluffy dog and how tall um
big i don't know how big though
really eat six feet tall um okay
seven eight nine feet tall standing up
on hind legs soon highlights twelve thirteen
yeah but i never really understood big
dogs like i never got a bark
yeah really really thought it'd be that
fun to have one but then
we like dog sat of dog that
was kind of big and i was
like this is really great how they
just kind of get on top of
you like oh no they're scary i
think big dog oh to hug a
big dogs know when they jump on
you know i come home but if
they're trained well then if they're come
just like on the couch or something
just going onto you like that's cute
i thought it was very comforting
and i sort of thought if i
was like oh it's like when i
was like another game dog there's something
cool about it to me if they're
really well trained when they're not well
trained it's really stressful i used to
think i only liked big dogs and
now i realize i like all dogs
yeah i don't care what size they
are they're all great so so liberal
group in
i've come a long way baby molly
our second dog she makes these weird
noises whenever coupe comes back to the
house after having left like she just
hears the garage door open she starts
just doing this like
book because nowhere i thought it was
going to arrest her
i've been deputized you know that you're
an officer of the court oh huh
you know me my trauma raza king
of chicago
hunter gear chicago you know me know
me been talking i've met dealer green
one huh even on one kind of
finish can reduce this one hunt started
twenty years ago i love that it's
good
right now yeah i want a hot
dog where can we get out east
we can order shake chequered i was
really close oh shit shit let's do
it let's order a shake check on
air and then yes you did in-between
like it's like not a prank but
it feels like a pri show will
ask do we have your permission to
put you on speaker phone david eda
you don't even know
i figured we would just do it
all over uber eats postmates yeah yeah
mean yeah yeah it works because what
if we didn't have their permission i'll
be such a call them yeah okay
and call you doing group order shots
so busy like they'd be like what
do you want why are you calling
us t m a t s postmates
for you bp
bpb yeah yeah oh no ring huh
dogs my signal is poor get onto
wi-fi get on the wi-fi it works
because it is making it even worse
at eataly li lu lead eddie money
heroes will start to order to open
the postmates i think it's fun it's
so fun to listen to us tried
to like all
looking at our phones trying to figure
out if we have the app now
hold on a second i did not
look at my phone you didn't uses
file i was safely away in your
pouch i wanted to call them directly
not using your phone you want to
show the color reds were like i've
got a restaurant in a million years
to even get a reservation hello pizza
pie yeah exactly going to get a
reservation it's like one of your round
his paws around you of this i
usually don't want
wow we have some triangle pies in
the back while i'm talking to charlie
brown's head oh and could you make
it look like the bro
with what with the soil assuming you're
white pizza okay and put some bull
anchovies to nowhere for the oddballs for
the eye maybe an onion for the
nose okay and assemble an entire onion
for you yeah big old onion omega
roar
la la la la
are you the guy with the dogs
michy working it out with the hot
dogs um what yeah or some fountain
sodas as well and i just forgot
the address but i don't want to
say it i just thought i had
it but i just want one to
do your will flame
just just shoot your little usa it'll
get here shouldn't we take a break
yeah checking the oh yeah so you're
going to love it twisted free go
we gotta go we gotta go okay
bye bye
and we're back and ah yeah we've
ordered the shake shack it should be
arriving in between episodes yeah very exciting
because he's not an ad for shady
what did you get so i got
a hot dog you know where the
only person who got a hotdog i
started got one but it's like when
i have the chance i got chicken
nuggets wicked lady in the tr
ramp mine yeah and you know what
i don't i don't i wanted to
talk until you mentioned shake shack and
then i was like there's other things
yeah it's like well i gotta learn
her as well we aren't beholden to
whatever you guys thought we were gonna
do you got two entrees got to
andre yeah for you honey if your
damn like sadly i'll only eat a
third of each oh that's really reach
your time oh shit
oh yes hey gotta yo it's a
three-tier alarm yeah mean any food yeah
we couldn't decide they needed to eat
so we just moved to delete though
this game is submitted okay first let's
get this straight outta elephant in the
room k p
you blew it again why haven't we
heard and yeah why haven't we heard
from you kristina it's been weeks now
yeah we need you to make another
adjustment to your game which we forget
what it is and yes we've recorded
all of these before you would have
heard the episode where we ask you
to do it but that doesn't mean
we haven't heard we have heard from
you because we had we haven't heard
from you
yes so that's still on you yeah
so k p get a y p
get your act together oh fuckin there's
no coming back from that k p
your problem ah but so so that's
a boogie nights reference i've ever seen
that film i saw clips of it
as a child and i was like
a child just laying out his going
it came out to me because i'm
keeping my friend's house you should see
it it's a good movie it's good
yeah it's a watch that it's tonight
because the best movie in my iconic
alfred molina before i'm sorry i hate
to there will be blood i know
you're in but sorry inter there will
be blood i say i'm say that
there will be blood you can't say
my movies the best movie
oh i actually did watch a clip
of you in it and you were
offend see there you go and you
saw my overlords it was really fun
to see she saw a clip of
your performance it was once well done
one
ah was it really fun it was
really fun and really interesting to like
be in that environment it was wild
it was really i definitely felt like
i did not belong there did you
fly there drive their drove their wow
drove there to see california they built
a little town that's now all right
did you take any
names and you take anything from the
setback home with you like steal anything
i took a barn door wow that's
awesome is this not a real born
that's fucking awesome so the cows are
gonna escape they don't live there
and now i have it in my
home and when i just like poloniex
xmr yeah like fisher price barn that
was always an interesting sound i loved
it i love the little i like
trying to make a circle thing maybe
i like trying to make it go
real short in the circle when the
when it goes the farmer says no
no no that little thing you turn
upside down and it makes the gala
gala yeah yeah
i had one i had is that
weird done don't know like that but
it's almost like you from space
it's because it's a little like there's
a little like
do i feel like that's more the
feeling that you get yeah the vibration
yeah it's like that yeah but the
sound is pure moon i think you're
one hundred percent right thank you anyway
alex is the big winner this week
with his game or her game or
their games snake oil so or snake
girl depending on where you're from love
my name is oil
my name is steve bowery boys and
their first sitcom have each player write
down six different completely unrelated words oh
man one player gets right the shit
out of these one player chooses their
occupation diarrhea and in no way i
mean i can relate or you're gonna
unrelated
ooh one player to me kind of
ride interrelated one player chooses their occupation
and announce is it to the players
he forgot to put the announces how
are you supposed to even read it
when it's written so horribly yeah what
are we doing here who did this
can we end this one early alex
alex show yourself
alex have each player write yourself out
outtakes have each playwright on six different
completely unrelated words one player chooses their
occupation fight of course it's different words
if they're unrelated you wouldn't be ready
to have the same word six times
right but it's like we have a
lot of notes have each playwright on
six completely unrelated words one player chooses
their occupation and announces it to the
players each player chooses two to three
of the words my only question is
how do we do our occupation like
each player says
is their occupation what does that mean
i'm going to read more and see
if that okay brings it to light
alright one player choose have each play
write down six different related words okay
one player chooses rocky bay only part
i gotcha
have each player write down six different
completely related words one player chooses their
occupation and announces it to the players
each player chooses two to three of
the words to combine as the name
of a new invention like tent juice
or dreamcloud which they will then attempt
to sell to you with an enticing
sales pitch their pitch should explain what
their
invention is how it works and why
you would particularly want it given your
occupation so we can just come up
with an occupation it does it's not
our actual occupation because we would all
be professional podcasters have each player write
down six different completely unrelated words one
player chooses their occupation and announces it
to the players each player chooses two
to three of the words to combine
as the name
mm of a new invention like ten
tensions or dreamcloud which way they will
then attempt to sell to you with
an enticing sales pitch their pitch should
explain what their invention is how it
works and why you would particularly want
given your occupation inventions still need to
be logical or work in a realistic
way once everyone has had the chance
to pitch to you choose your favorite
as the winner that
player gets a point the player with
the most points when you finish playing
wins okay do you start over yeah
i know he explained it but like
when like a human something what would
you listen yeah okay okay but hold
on i'm put the let's start let's
just show piece okay so yeah let's
do the six one related words six
unrelated and completely different
i mean could they could they be
spelled almost the same but they are
don't really write down the six same
unrelated words okay ah alright
cobra kai
okay now we're just looking at things
in the room okay cobra kai
cobra kai okay let me record company
job
guy
america there's a lot to do cobra
cobra kai lemon rookie cobra kai i
mean okay because a few of you
feel for your funeral funeral feel but
brainy freeney blah lulu okay i got
my six i got my six and
then we pick our own two words
that's the weird part i think
could i think other people should i
think so too we should we should
like text each other to the left
of and those are the words we
have to to the left to the
left oh wait that's about that's about
you know what i mean okay so
we don't make two of our own
words yeah and when we pick two
from the list that sent to us
okay great romana text poor or we
send two words to the
person no i think we should pick
the six because that that'll give people
more choice i'm sending you six words
alright and i'm sending you six words
lauren and scott i'm gonna send you
six words and then what am i
picking you're picking two of them to
combine whatever two you think and by
the way we're going to have to
do this three times so okay
you know don't you gotta make sure
that you pick the right one and
combine them to do what to to
as sell any product you're selling right
god okay great do you want to
read it one more time no i
think we all right but now it
now we have to pick our our
occupations and tell each other that yes
okay or do we assign each other
occupy
a no no let's just take our
own pick our own occupation yes yeah
which is just part of my character
yeah exactly um my character is the
first grade teacher so we're pitching to
you then first okay yeah okay got
that and and both of us are
trying to compete is that what it
is yes okay hello sir or madam
madam mining madam my name's harvey barnes
and i am a salesman and i
have something that is perfect for you
a first grade teacher oh i have
to interject here and i'm sorry to
do it right at the beginning of
what you're doing but i myself by
the way my name is harvey parnes
and i want your name harvey jar
it's okay harvey parnes over here focus
on me unrelated you're not a couple
no we're not i don't think you're
related your names just rhyme yes we
used to but you didn't think we
were a couple wow we used to
john's to be fair we used to
rhys have a big torrid romance going
you're sort of denying i wouldn't call
a relationship we were fuck buddies ma'am
and who was a top and a
bottom we switched off verse that's really
odd days and mondays okay i get
it right yeah i'm the top even
days i'm the top you have sex
every day cause it is a thursday
based on whichever day you want to
have sex well on odd days the
the interesting thing is sometimes two odd
days would come in a row
oh the thirty first in the first
right so those were the really those
were the lean years and we put
a mask to be completely different people
so it didn't matter yeah we can
count those okay but we didn't have
sex every single day and when you
have sex with each other yeah did
you ever say i love you
ah yeah i love having sex with
you is yes we did say that
a lot i love i think i
owe you a really big power he
said having sex with
i mean sometimes the pause was very
long sometimes i would say i love
and then ellipsis than you yeah but
the having sex with was very implied
a lot of times i would say
i love and i would mouth having
sex with and though it's a you
does that it's your question yes it
does these kind of questions you ask
if your students know i just wondered
if you guys were fuck buddies because
your last
names ryan yeah madam and your first
names are the same no way are
you that's how we met yeah being
a teacher is the greatest job in
the world oh you really even better
than other mom billionaire i would say
is the greatest job in the world
but well i mean most important job
yeah yeah for sure and i'd be
a billion and i know it's hard
because you have to buy your own
supplies and nobody is ever getting credit
for it that is true
that is very true well wouldn't you
like something that made your whole life
a lot easier and helped you more
effectively teach your little students of course
i love that well then i got
the invention for you it's called the
moon demon oh okay it sounds scary
it's not it sounds great but it's
not now when school take play
it's the datetime yeah it does it
takes place from seven three s varying
about night school over here well but
you don't teach first grade night school
do you
do i teach that yes where are
you where are you being i'm saying
his questionnaire and all the aid you
mad yeah what's going on right now
i don't your your eyes are shifting
back and forth at night school wow
your eyes are rocketing back yeah i
don't this is making me feel like
she does teach a nurse grade
it's not something to be ashamed of
i don't even know it existed but
i'm glad to let some moon demon
you've peaked my interest i'm glad you
asked a moon demon makes use of
your classroom at night so the moon
da is a device that you put
in the outside of your classroom into
one close to the teacher's desk you
okay you'll always keep an eye on
it
don't let the kids get into it
because it has toxic properties now you
it's good for me to be by
it exactly but the kids because they'll
stick their fingers in it and then
put their fingers in the mouths because
the kids do yeah but you will
do that well but no well rubbing
my hair is that bad no it's
good for hair okay what it is
is it captures
as it has a goo in it
that soaks up the moon's rays and
then what you do is you open
the window just a crack mind you
just a crack and then you let
that ah that moon glue seep into
the classroom the gases from it it
off gases into the classroom and it
keeps the kids alert and awake i
i love that so they're always ready
to learn it's it's a gas so
it's not connect to a demon himself
no it's called a demon because it
seems almost like magical and evil because
it's so this sort of smoker gas
comes through the air and makes all
the kids stay away it's invisible but
it gets into their nostrils and their
little lungs and it keeps them alert
and perky and now does it get
into my nostrils no
it doesn't work on adults and so
i won't be getting into toxicity but
the kids will yes they will but
it's harmful if breathed in but you
mustn't touch it if you're a child
but it's going into it's harmful if
breathed in but you mustn't to know
it's not harmful of breathed in it's
harmless if we did maybe i misspoke
and i do apologize a really crucial
detail i was just taking my checkbook
and then when you said that
i started putting it away i've been
talking to teachers all day i do
apologize sometimes i misspeak ah can i
interject here and say speaking of alert
and awake who else was falling asleep
during that i mean grandma that's pretty
nice to listen to plus hey that's
pretty funny i've i've ah something that
i want to tell you about okay
harvey karp but first i have a
question cars park
mine's harvey parnes armies yarns yeah who
are we p car harvey carr was
a cartoonist you're thinking of harvey p
carp the fish cartoon yeah hey yeah
i have a couple of questions for
you okay what is the number one
thing that you want your students to
learn that starts with g e o
g'day
basic domes are the wave of the
future b r but what the subject
that i'm thinking about is geography we
all gotta know where we are at
all times don't we yeah but what's
the niger wonder where i am right
now and how did you find me
oh we just came in through this
open window yeah you just came in
through the window yeah joe cocker protected
by a silver spoon
it was instructed to do so by
ah what's her name okay
who is it that those things come
through my window myself desperately sad thrilled
she speaks to me through her records
okay but aches in town what's the
number one subject or our third stuff
we went to the doctor we went
to the mountain yeah okay good same
get all the big stops yeah you're
you're two lesbians with a mission yes
we are what is the number
or one subject that your students want
to be studying instead of geography
nah i'm just gonna say it naptime
naptime they love naptime don't they really
add i've been trying to me march
interesting much naptime so what's your product
called it is the recumbent globe the
recumbent globe this is a globe that
lies down on the floor with the
children
it's
i love your lies down next to
them a cradle army one the spoons
them are taking notes well i am
taking note of the old expression he
who lies down with a glow wakes
up with lines on their face like
i had ah my fair share of
lying down with globes and let me
just say it can be a very
good experience it can
it can't and it's instructional and it's
motivational as well because these kids once
they're lying down with the entire earth
they want to get out there they
want to be traveling around the earth
they want to be going to different
places talk about motivational globes what about
brown pop music everybody interesting interesting steve
now where did you learn that can
i ask and yeah i learned from
ross
from the streets didn't you you learned
it from the streets which is where
people should not learning things neatly we
want them to learn things in the
classroom and this release kids in the
classroom down with the globe i like
this yes how much is each one
you go first oh ninety nine cents
oh no mine's just a cent okay
for a moon name and the catches
moon rails kinda worked it works every
single night because even though we don't
see the moon it's still up there
and it's shooting down rays so it's
just one penny to have that work
for the rest of my life or
it's ninety nine cents to have this
work for us to my well my
know mine doesn't work it doesn't work
at all no i think your choice
broccoli or madam
okay i'm gonna go away i do
admire your honesty and that is something
always personally i almost came close to
loving you however like i chopped out
ah cherry tree when i was really
young like my food it yeah and
then after that no more lies no
more lies no my question is can
i do think i could fix it
the tree no the broken
my dad but oh ah we i
mean how i tell you pansy are
you i mean handy um i'm very
handy i mean handy
what did you ever tell me about
what wow that time i ah you
know gave somebody the wrong change this
woman i worked at a store and
then i had to walk five miles
to give her two pennies oh no
you never told me yeah after our
fuck session pretty honest okay well no
we mostly just talked about crossword puzzles
actually love we never did them no
we just talked about one thing to
do i love
the way your shapes be harvey to
love shapes the shapes are they're very
symmetrical i would harvey jones yes yes
yes ma'am i'm sorry did you say
my name no reports of you one
penny to have your product slowly leak
into the windows that's great the rest
of it too that's great so the
moon demon itself just one penny because
can i the subsea
friction unfortunately cost one hundred and fifty
dollars a month but you've already made
up your mind and so i'm rich
did did did you already swiping my
door any good hey
wow yeah that's how you play it
and that is how you play it
and you know it's almost here is
a little guy called shake shack wow
first do we all wrote six words
maybe only one of us needed to
i kind of felt like that was
what was going on
eternia at the door to the da
da and if you're out there and
you have a ton you come into
your door go meter yeah time to
me ty wish you all infinite tanya's
at infinite door we year's fringe what
i want happen your steal i want
ton you to come to your door
hey i would time
you come to your door when i
was a kid growing up in scram
this is on you
guys do it on cvb baby never
okay do it right here right now
i love alright we have to go
eat our big cylindrical hot dogs i'm
just thinking myself i guess but um
you know we'll see next week and
remember to call our phone number for
whatever reason ah it's la la input
haha la
la input jack did this haha in
but didn't do jumps and write to
us a gmail do we want people
to write to us anymore we've just
had people rather shiny reacher if you
have a three cheer you gotta write
to us if you please write to
us threesome usa gmail dot com three
dm usa on instagram and twitter we
love you very much and if you
want to hear ad-free episodes head over
to stitcher premium or cvb world dot
com and that's it we're getting our
food goodbye everyone
uh