three dom
freedom
hi everyone i always forget that we
don't have a version without a screening
on it oh like there's no karaoke
version of freedom oh there should be
the shy people should be able to
have it on the same yeah yeah
we should do it to learn yeah
you have we should do it at
karaoke though yeah
those was filling second josh absolutely people
are like what were they rush
what are they setting three people pumped
and then when it's over they'd be
like what happened
well i was excited i never heard
the song before you were like fucking
just sell it up there i know
i've done
ah wow i get to sing the
greatest love of all great blue calls
though welcome to freedom i'm porn i'm
a lot i'm pl
pull a law accommodation of paul and
remember lot from the bible oh what
a what a guy throwback man i
wish my wife would be better assault
row
throwback thursday with lots what if there's
probably videos but for the bible just
be like bible verses and then like
throwback people throw sixteen remember i think
i would never do this because i
don't want the comments but if they
just post a picture of jesus throughout
tbt
threw up there's say jesus november even
remember the last supper one of the
old this is jesus now tim in
heaven it's the shroud of turin
no
fantasia it is his indentation that tortilla
that told you are tya
jesus tortilla jesus to r g t
yeah she's that song tangerine speedo i
beg your pardon ma'am
no no hold on tangerine speedo wait
no i i'm shocked you don't know
what i'm talking about okay so what
if jesus cared you really what if
jesus came down and hung out
for eighteen months on earth would we
believe it no not two months yeah
and he was just like i'm jesus
here's a couple of australia
yeah
tangerine speedo
it seems like the lyrics are cha
cha cha
i think you would notice it's know
was just from like the nineties using
louder as it came back or what
does this combustible edison
who isn't it's caviar and turn it
the fuck up
cute
a la la la la la la
la i'm gonna play some tangerine dream
if jesus hung out for two months
and try to convince her that sounds
like the plot of a bad movie
no but it might be bad job
but it's good life it's this ain't
no movie bad movie good law does
not plot of bad movie
his plot of good life
um my ah my i'm not as
rush as i thought i was oh
i love that okay we're gonna stretch
out and hey fuckin do a super
long episode here this is tangerine dream
is mike dunn playing chess with a
tattoo with a tattoo yeah all of
his interests combined yeah exactly oh
oh you like tattoos he plays basketball
on chess boards and gets tattoos while
it's happening
he likes tattoos he has fifty he
does yeah where one is a number
order is damn body really yeah but
i i don't think i've ever even
nusa i'm swimming in hawaii i don't
know he's yes
ah i don't remember that fifty but
he has probably two money where all
over and barely list his body parts
you hers yeah one round was just
saying that lever two thousand commercial
so are these still around yeah i
do lever levy and so nineties what
was it wasn't ninety you want to
call it two thousand if it was
past two thousand it's fuckin good point
ma'am what was it though what was
different it was a show no it
wasn't a nice lever because it was
green i lived here i remember seeing
those commercials yeah but you lived here
in the nineties in
the late come on i met you
a ninety five scott i know but
that's the mid nineties yeah that's what
we're saying
labour two thousand bar soap why what
what is it though it's just a
soap it's the number one soap that
guys love that they say you can
use it often add by the way
all over where read what part of
your body are you are you never
know some guys love well like you
would use it on your face and
your as opposed to like having a
special oh yeah your face getting special
treatment you need which what people see
anyway i can't figure this out what
anyway like did you try to figure
out what year it was oh you
know i do on a b pop
la lever two thousand ad no commercial
ad advertisement okay hold on i'll do
that now
okay oh and the d thousand law
a amanda zamboni sampson never seen wicked
ninety ninety lever two thousand bars up
commercial ninety nineteen ninety ninety six ninety
ninety five oh shit oh shit oh
shit man i stand corrected shit oh
shit yeah but i didn't survive they
are still available
on amazon oh really on amazon yeah
come on lever two thousand sponsors were
talking about you for so long i'm
like to read it dry out
lauren of you ever consider
having a recording career singing career as
well yeah i wanna be a pop
star
why not
i want to be a pastor
what made you ask that question
i mean you can be like lindsay
lohan on the pop star selena gomez
rita williams serena yeah i i've always
considered being a pop star and the
one stopping always everything
why not but i've got i've i
would only do with autotune on every
syllable yeah
every syllable yeah hey this shooter
i wonder if the autotune needs to
take a break since take a break
two for like ten i wonder if
autotune needs to take a chill pill
please relax a little too much it's
like ah there's in tune and then
there's in tune yeah it's like auto-tune
makino
as a style of it's own it
wasn't even about me hitting the notes
it was about sounding like your war
auto-tune became a style of it's own
everyone from this guy to that girl
was doing it and then somebody died
after this year out of tragedy did
you see the autotune documentary on netflix
yes it was good i like the
share really invented she claimed oh no
huh no no ah that invent but
she's the first two that they well
they they do talk about how they
had to they used it on her
and then they had to say that
they were
not doing it because sounds illegal well
it's it's also like she's a real
singer and so do you implied that
i mean like anyone tuning her so
because no one knew what it was
back then yeah but she's so when
she's singing do you guys sound like
a voice which i sadly have to
say i want a part that's that's
what i remember is that one part
sounds specific
likely like ne like out in the
open auto-tune like this is an effect
right yeah but they had to say
it was like an effect or something
they couldn't say autotune because to imply
that they needed to tune her singing
right well if it wasn't already called
that at that time i think so
yeah i think it's been around for
a bit yeah and people would just
people would use use it very spf
daringly um but then i like they
would go it's got to my main
turning a little tiny diet will take
just a little bit nipple it's just
a yeah i'm barfi
it looks my finger i'm bar um
i'm literally borrowing but then but then
um ah my man t-pain he he
like heard it on a song and
was like what is that and then
would search plugins on it's on on
like cd roms for for years but
she was getting for free in the
mail ready he was for years he
searched for it and then he found
one it was like oh my god
this is it and then turned it
all the way up and yeah like
this is it oh i did a
thing with t-pain during the pandemic and
he was really funny he's great yeah
and he on this documentary hear him
sing and he has these very nice
yeah yeah tiny desk concert yeah his
lower decks are great this is star
trek lower decks episode
incredible star trek tiny desk
oh you're next from time to time
yeah recording my mind from time to
time as well yeah my grain on
it not on it what am i
great on it i wouldn't know because
i don't recognize oh okay do you
play my face is the spaceship and
character's name is jen i think you're
an n
i'm dorian right you're blue oh god
yes i am ten am so i
haven't ten a yeah i guess i
didn't know that was you well now
you do was a great and i
play a bird man yes you play
harvey birdman i play harvey birdman attorney
harvey p car
and i wondered all the scenes in
it's weird
eco i remember loving movie american splendor
thought about the david's such a long
time i know he's been on letterman
all the time yeah my gym it
lasted gibbet oh no no giblets on
tibbetts i well i have a whole
bag of chips i have to i
have to go through you know my
plan was when i was supposed to
come
yeah inter was to bring everyone a
big pile of giblets oh what what
bram i'll bring em to you um
i didn't come because we didn't have
a babysitter and then only one of
us could go and and covet and
just everything it was it was called
justin i would allow to seen baby
holly at the table booster see what
happens yeah i would of bought her
an app wow an app
that would've been his twitter instagram what
usually you would buy her now i'll
buy her a nap yeah you want
me to buy you an nap right
now yeah oh
oh my god i'm buddy my punch
in the facebook download feels blvd oh
no like out of nowhere yeah he
was ah there was a um a
an unhinged individual who was speaking in
he couldn't understand what he was thinking
ahead my friend had headphones on and
he said what and then the guy
punched him in the face he wasn't
even being confrontational
yeah he was saying what and then
the guy just punched him like sucker
punch him in the face we think
he said you know guy about to
go punch in the face as what
and then ah ah two other guys
come up and they were like he
almost did that to us like he
was this guy was going around and
just oh good looking out thanks yeah
protecting yeah you almost did that to
us and we watched him do it
to you yeah fucking idiots yeah i
know scaring your new assignment scary to
just get punched or walking on the
street it is i remember walking down
if i get punched i want to
get punched for something you know you'll
get friendly i want to earn it
you'll get punched for it'll be worth
it it'll mean something earned where are
these coming from trees what what tree
has this oh this yeah ok don't
worry about it well i only saw
palm trees so i was like what's
this little toe
is
oh
see it could be a podcar
seeing us anyway and here she is
saying her new song sing a song
like hockey full of rye everything which
spells seen this thing this everything's tight
up here everything side up here and
my possess
okay dear oh dear what does that
it's not that it's just this oh
thanks tight up yeah things are sad
yeah right imagine what a britney spears
or christina urias the sing his new
single everything's tight up here she's not
knock ramen and things tying up he
starts with the chorus it is right
there
it's like the freedom facebook it's the
shortest single in the recordings perfect for
a busy night hario key okay i
do want to know what tired of
waiting for your turn only to get
bumped off the list now was shorter
songs everyone gets a chance what is
the shortest number one song in history
i wanna know that and could
is there is it possible to go
to number one with a song this
twenty seconds long i have a guess
of the shortest people requesting number one
song what do you think everyday by
buddy holly it's a short song every
day eats chicken show you guys are
making it longer actually every day it's
getting goes i go
no goes i love like like
by the way hey hey um i'm
looking this up shortest song um this
is interesting to me yes stay by
maurice williams stand slow was my karaoke
and the zodiacs at just one minute
and thirty eight seconds in length is
that the stage
along the thinker one i don't know
that jackson brown famously quote in his
the loadout
why was it like don't you feel
like in the eighties well those songs
were used so heavily like the fifty
sun sixty songs oh i was the
eighty's all about this summer it's boomer
nostalgia yeah so they were capitalizing on
that but do we do that now
ninety three minute style but that's not
the same thing so what i mean
it's a little more because i think
it's it they did that so heavily
in the eighties it's now a very
specific thing like if you watch yellow
jackets and they have all the songs
from the nineties it's like this is
the ninety right because that's not what
they were due but they weren't always
the shows where it was zeiss in
this yeah
yeah exactly it was very specifically tailored
though towards a generation of people who
all of the sudden got really rich
when they used to be hippies in
the sixties and it's it's for people
who are like now really well off
and have really nice cars to sort
of feel like oh yeah i'm grooving
like
i know right
why are they rich because all the
boomers fucking boomer heard we got boomed
we got boomer we got boomer
members got rich learned by the way
all is that correct i'm a i'm
a millennial i think i'm an um
what's it called like an elder millennial
or some right and then star gen
x my old band leader you can't
count each dancer i'm not gonna answer
that shit kid cut is beautiful trip
is shortest
hot one hundred hit ever wow huh
and how long is it it is
ah this is the problem all of
these are on billboard and you need
to fucking sign up for an account
on billboard dot com billboard louis' kitty
i'm really sick of stuff like that
when you're just looking at a website
yeah tell ma yeah
yeah we then pho and also oh
i don't like when when like it's
a news story that seems really important
and they're like you gotta pay only
if it's really important you should just
be telling me it's so important covert
update your claim if it's that important
i tried you know it yeah like
whatever if it's like some celebrity shit
or whatever no one's gonna pay for
that while i'm saying that's the thing
thing if you want to if you
want to like you will give you
the news about the world ending okay
fine but you want to get this
juicy stuff you've gotta pay a little
bit more yeah time in a bottle
is only two minutes and as rank
time yeah oh i used to i
used to have this muppets album that
that was on oh man when the
muppets covered she dries
me crazy good
i am piggy do she driving trams
mean it's really good um my ah
a friend of mine who is owen
gift millennial yeah i didn't want to
say i don't want to name drop
friend of mine saying ah let's call
him our present um a friend of
barney kelly who is please don't have
that one to the rotation horrible feeling
you bring up don't um she is
a millennial and she only knew the
song kokomo as being done by the
muppets oh i wish
and after we were talking about that
over dinner and she sent me the
link to the to the muppets doing
it and it's like this makes so
much more sense as a muppet song
oh yeah alas i would be mad
if they were just muppet song it's
kermit singing co imo i know that
virtual piggy shows up at the end
she's mad because he checks out one
of the hula dancers she punches him
of course yeah their relationship is toxic
absolutely we've all been in one of
those haven't we but at the same
time it's like which this which they're
they're just better separately i had a
girlfriend who would use karate on me
she didn't space a lot
she was a pig
not okay to say what if she's
literally a pig than it is okay
to say thank you do you think
that it's okay with a some pig
i think it's okay to date and
if it's consensual having get consent from
a pig they have to oink in
your mouth there's there's spider friend writes
yes well yes
that happened to charlotte's web right what
did it well yeah what did what
did the summer rain some pig and
then there was something something else i
think dated i'm dying or something good
by okay i haven't read this since
i was fifteen or so our reasons
i was what one year old what
is the plot of charlotte's web ah
ah a spider befriends a newbie
born pig is also a rat rat
named templeton he he considers a fair
to be a virtual smorgasbord yeah but
that's only in the tv version of
i can't really picture the tv i've
ever do yeah it's hard like really
burned in my brain yeah yeah i
saw that when i was young yeah
um and the spider ah the friends
of the pig
and the pig is entered into a
contest like oh first turn killed it's
ah
yeah there boy he doesn't know that
when he wins it said in your
just hope your future
just like animal foods the running man
because the the spider writes some pig
in the web i believe in the
barn yeah the pig that that gains
the pig notoriety he wins i don't
know why it doesn't erase spider know
to ride yeah really by the way
the pig didn't do that when you
called charlotte's web and like i always
think the pigs named charlotte and i
t
all about the pig and it's like
it's really about the charlotte yeah sure
yeah doors the girl named charlotte i
don't think no one knows charlotte a
spider charlotte is charlotte is spider the
charlotte is spider i don't think i
could read anything in a web
i bet you could have tried you
know what i was holding down a
web that was an not a good
location i feel a little bad doing
it but they can do it again
and build back better would not go
down i was like this is the
strongest i was spraying a hose on
it and it would not come down
i was like this wild what they
can do it it's incredible how strong
website yeah it's really wild i don't
even think that if i saw wow
eb that had words in it i
would even know it well that's what
i wanted to bring up as i
think i think you would really think
okay later it would look markedly different
from any web you'd ever if it
was like all across a room like
a surprise banner or something maybe yeah
well like that's what the crypt keeper
got for a surprise party
surprise or should i say it your
die
okay carol janney yeah you die but
that's okay i like that i think
i like that game too i think
i did a pretty good crypt keeper
you you did i just yeah it
was it also sounded like carrollton well
those two sounds like this yeah assault
carol channing is the original grip keeping
she really who's the voice of the
crypt keeper john
your wow who is that the voice
of keep keeper that's it go on
this for hours he's done other stuff
but that is his most famous right
if when you were in showbiz you
got one job and that was it
and then you could never have it
i don't i mean i want to
last forever i wouldn't mind okay
but that's also that's what i'm looking
for right now is one job in
show business one job in show business
yeah and you get health insurance people
complain about being on like a show
for too long and that's that's such
a i would never complain about that
that's a great thing it would be
so cool to be on something like
sixty minutes yes
you just had someone there doing an
expos yeah that's like this was hey
you're paying attention me right
um yeah sure i caused a bunch
of child deaths but you're talking about
me sixty minutes yeah well someone who
would be ah yeah what if what
if it turned out that sixty minutes
did all the things that they're accusing
other people yeah yeah when you use
someone someone or something that you really
like someone there's fifty nine minutes forty
bucks
sometimes i love to watch shows like
that but mike really hates that kind
of thing what does he hate about
it like he hates like the news
and he hates like it's the dateline
or twenty twenty i like to watch
like a news thing sometimes it feels
like watching tv yeah i know janie
we have that like it feels like
old school days of watching
teams like it's watching this thing and
this is what's on and i wanna
see now i'm curious you know i'm
really got to please my interests i'm
that way with documentaries in that jamie's
could always be in the mood for
them but i have to it's like
either you gotta spring it on me
or like i have pricey i'm certain
mood yeah like we have to just
kind of fall
into it but if if were like
looking for something to watch and jamie
says how about this i always will
say i'm not in the mood i
feel about documentaries to like me if
i'm in the mood then fantastic but
i'm like them and i already knew
but like it's like you're what you're
doing is you're committing to watching a
full investigation of a specific topic which
is
very different than just watching a show
like a fake thing yeah yeah yeah
i like fake things
although my
a friend made a documentary off indoor
referees give a shout out to my
friend sarah mosman who made a documentary
called losing sight of shore show isn't
for shout out i'm just getting called
losing sarah mossman now it's called losing
sight of short it's about the these
four women who rode the pacific ocean
they were the first team of women
to do the road it like yeah
course they wrote tweetie omission was thought
to scald they rode otto w e
d and they it was it's very
it's very inspiring that's why we got
to see what's on netflix but now
with somewhere else so you have to
figure out you figure it out she's
given you all the clues yeah you
just realise yeah who are you the
snowman there's a website oh you
snowman snowman obi how dare you tell
me you gave your clues who are
you the snow bag yeah
remember when jack frost melted in that
tub do you talk to a guy
who was in jack frost over here
i beg you you were in jack
frost the michael keaton movie yeah yes
paul i need a reel of every
scene you've ever been in compiled into
one four hour thing for hours you
just want them to repeat over and
over again
i'm in jack frost for literally one
second what does it i am it
doesn't again the tub i don't know
i never saw i never saw it
either yeah past my part which is
in the very very very beginning i
went to the premiere what is normal
to support paul what was it you
there is the jack frost blues band
is playing at
everyone is right loving it and then
they finish a song and they cut
to the audience i'm in the very
middle of the audience and i go
yeah and i feel i'll just upset
well of course i forget everything that's
my it's very easy to see on
youtube but i'm gonna watch out okay
i have to i'm gonna do a
compilation i'm gonna make compilation
and okay i'm gonna do to my
phone on my computer back and you've
got there will be blood you got
tenacious d i got the informant informant
right tenacious d is by far my
my big longest cinema screen time yeah
can someone who's good at editing meiko
video of all the stuff yeah like
like music and member sally who did
all the turn
you know folks there's no if you
can make a cool god love ya
i'm i'm excited about this i was
gonna i was gonna do it you
know these people these people who listened
to the show they have skills yeah
to pay the bills they have mad
skin and be the bad bill whoever
makes this hopefully they went in oscar
down the line and then they thank
us because yeah first thing i ever
edited
it was this paul f tompkins compilation
of all of his dumb movies roles
that he's done and when they die
in their oscar memoriam it's a clip
from from you're my real yeah i
like which is cool and has music
i like but you're still alive so
you can see it oh fuck it's
like tom sawyer being his own funeral
yeah yeah i'm ninety nine years old
yeah i wonder if i'm gonna live
that long yeah i bet you do
i feel like i feel like there's
an i'll be waving right there my
dad eighty six sir
my dad's side of the family was
pretty long lived yeah i know yeah
so hey all all and we're all
living longer most days i hope everyone
that i know lives to be ninety
nine point five but not a hundred
and one hundred in honor of the
radio's eight hundred if they want to
ninety nine point seven all the hits
may you all live as long as
a radio station yeah what else explains
that oh that's last too long so
long at what point do you mean
he sets up all the time she's
like i don't want to live to
be that old to be lying my
baby i wasn't my eighties model i
know i would say um i would
like to
i'd like to you know hit the
gong at a hundred gong and just
like tommy lee motley crew just hit
the gong and then you keel over
yeah did you see tom and family
tom tom and pammy i actually i
hadn't seen the loud no one did
two episodes oh my god don't join
sometimes i think okay god it would
be great to live forever tell my
family it'd be great to live forever
like but your body stand a chance
twenty one right but then i just
saw pictures of myself when i was
twenty one and i'm like too young
well like how about the how about
in captain america winter soldier where oh
someone seems young and that had old
biddy gets old and but then also
the winter soldier himself bucky yeah played
by the guy who played tommy tommy
yeah there is i was very reluctant
to watch that because when i heard
that the penis had a voice i
was like this is not my concert
buddy i know but but yeah no
oh but i didn't but i was
just talk much nothing happens one i
missed the first couple episodes but then
janey was watching it and so i
would be in the room and i
started gradually start paying more more deliveries
here of ass
i'll take back that ass up i
think like the penis thing one time
to go do with as far as
i know oh and i was i
was surprised by the tone of it
and i thought they were very um
respectful ah whither were more respectful and
expected about the idea of like jesus
people had this very percy
little things stolen from them and that
it really sucks such a nightmare scott
is laughing at the the truck backing
up i'm assuming yes okay it just
got out of the idea of pity
for these two people no no of
course not
whereas o steep steep scarp it's gone
here sing old saying the cbe yeah
this is like a metronome so this
will get you used to singing ski
yes i fell asleep
escape i let us keep our ballistic
a break we'll be right back with
more trucks
we're back we're back we did guys
we've done a segment of the show
we have how we waited for that
goddamn truck to stop backing up and
it just for your listeners as far
as we know it did stop backing
up yeah think it did i think
it's moving forward now
oh and so are we yeah general
hot out here so sorry you want
wanna move here move your thing over
oh wait that's a thing up back
to back that ass up lauren keep
talking show me what you are working
with talking and then throw them on
the glass lorem oh
yeah
a line is drawn i will you
added certainly bad answer but throwing them
on the glass oh never use my
name when you ask me to throw
them on the glass up pushing the
chair she she's pushing it oh no
you gotta pull it you gotta pull
out a bullet you can't push that
tried to push but could not push
pull
oh mandy oh my god she almost
fell down he almost fell down like
oh look a little weakly oh
ninety eight pounds and can't pull a
little chair like one of my favorite
things is ah janie everyone's all tries
to pick me up
oh so funny when cool used to
put like paul rust on her shoulders
during new year's eve usb parties oh
man it's just like come on cool
i don't do that stop stay because
oh yeah she's gonna fuck it back
up yeah she's with a stripper right
now what may oh do you mean
um oh
oh wow they're delivering him right now
what do you mean that she's with
the structures at a bachelor party i'm
going to a birthday weekend little getaway
in april should i just hire a
stripper for my friend as a joke
even though it's out about it yeah
like what kind of is like a
remote getaway like um it's it's what
you mean remote like is it a
key
cabin type of thing an air bnb
like an hour absolutely get a stripper
yeah i feel like the cop thing
is way no funny but yeah it
could be owner of the airbnb about
like owners i came back early yeah
what are your people doing here that
would be so scared that it wasn't
our agreement iver blackstar like panicking and
calling the cops no i didn't top
the show
yeah just more and more strippers
neighbors complaining that what was going on
were able to have a pool pumps
out like an improv anywhere thing where
like before it's even revealed to stripper
like first the owner comes in they
call the cops then a cop is
like oh no we need to call
the fire department like in some other
like we need to call the fire
department twenty people are there before ever
revealing it's a stripper and then they
do it
choreograph strip i would love the culture
like hey these ladies did you ah
they started a fire like like really
and the guy was like i know
i know it's going to be more
shoppers yeah it seems like someone here
needs a doctor as well let's call
them up i'm having these ladies so
i'm having a heart attack
everyone knows they're strippers but it takes
oh three hours for all of the
things they're called the corridor this guy's
dead from these lazy too hot shippers
wear masks during combat i don't know
that's a good question this is the
only thing i'll keep on probably right
the instead it's too good to pass
that up because you get to cover
your
face well because you get to make
that comment oh yeah yes yeah i
wonder if people are are are allowed
to film strippers on their phones now
now that like everyone has a camera
on their phone i think they absolutely
do yeah yes i'm gonna say yes
okay yeah because i would assume if
i were a stripper and i hope
i hope to
at some point that i would say
like hey no phones i don't want
like this case when you walk in
and you're like no why easy okay
i want everyone like i'm you're paying
me can we just die now you're
like you don't want to give away
for free hello ladies no fuss don't
take pictures of me no videos either
and now here we know
your main attraction when you don't mind
could you please not record me on
your ten a day
i like to move it move it
ok where's the where's the right to
be which one of you scanning oh
you oh my god oh sorry i
mean i'm happily married to
i like to move it move it
me da
huh
tell you what i'll go up and
do this character for your friends yeah
oh boy now you're never breaking you
never say to you that scotland no
no no if you get really shy
about taking your clothes off like you
start to and then you'd say oh
i don't think oh one other rule
you keep thinking of another rule i'm
not going to take my clothes i
can't show anything below the elbow
elbow he wears long gloves which direction
i like tomoe but only just
move it i forgot my boom box
i just get close
i could everybody clap like a movie
i like come on with moving
ah now you started want this to
happen right i do but i want
the bed i to be a bachelor
party of twenty twenty young men who
are gonna kick your ass
ah yeah somebody kicked my ass i'm
the stripper you didn't specify which kind
ah stripping
wow fun to do fun to do
i love doing it at home i
mean it's just saying my clothes off
yeah like i do it before i
go in the city everyone we know
has a stripper pole now on instagram
i'm like wow i've had one for
awhile everyone's got one on instagram my
glasses and all that it was like
she was ahead of her time production
to put in too yeah oh my
god
well it's i mean you want it
to be safe you can't have it
be fast but it's no it can't
just be portable you're gonna put your
whole ass on it yeah you have
to you have to like hook it
up to the ceiling and the floor
you got to move moving yeah yeah
nicole byer has a pole outside oh
that's nice yeah that's good yeah al
fresco
yeah i saw the stripper alfresco
with the name of the strippers chipper
al fresco cooling hi mary rollo stripper
al franken
stripper al franken oh no way would
you that somebody chink would you hire
an al franken themed stripper of course
if you saw it average i mean
if it was now franken themed party
yes is it al frankenstein
man what a burn to him if
you ever called him al franken into
his face i'd want a stripper named
al frankenstein and it's alfredo with molson
saying exactly exactly yeah he's painted green
i like to move it move and
he's doing the like hands over the
breast
each lady in the bachelor party and
you say okay take a picture
hands over
you pretend to be asleep and i
will hover my hands over your tips
fuckin crazy
okay you should do cameos of that
a fuckin send me a picture of
you asleep now yeah he does like
a tick tock where it's like behind
him
ah i want huh
that's great cameo i love how how
much would you pay though i'd pay
a million dollars oh that's so much
money i want him to have it
i want him to have it i'm
worried about him he's out of lucknow
yeah i want him to want to
have it i want to talk about
what has been good for him al
franken simon petition to let me give
you a million dollars please
i only need what's okay sure so
how much would i pay it would
depend on if he was doing it
for everyone or whether this was like
a special request that you only do
once like a wu tang situation yeah
exactly yeah he'll do a scroll do
it currently let's see if you can
really at lunch and my stomach if
you do it for everyone how much
would you pay
twenty dollars no i pay one hundred
okay and if it's just for you
three thousand one hundred and fifty
it's only for you you can't post
it but i can show it to
people yeah
she brought the internet should we do
some audio cameos for people right now
yeah yeah hey everyone it's the threesome
game no not everyone you have to
just do a simple hi amanda hey
man omega wait hold on it's just
me
oh okay i thought there were or
not i thought were gonna take turn
why don't we take turns and then
we'll do a group one for somebody
hey amanda it's lauren laugh guess i
just want to say happy birthday i
know you've been having a tough year
as we all have with the pandemic
but i'm so excited for hopefully things
feel being up again where you are
and then maybe you can get out
there and have a little fun thanks
so much for being my number one
fan i'm a huge fan of you
to amanda
hey peter it's paul huh the bible
listen your friends told me that you
were feeling a little down lately and
you could teach use some cheering up
because your birthday is coming up very
soon maybe it's even today i don't
know but they also told me that
you like to do puzzles and glue
them together after they're completed and that
you need insulin so i wanted to
say
have a great birthday i love you
with all of my heart paul hi
mary where's peter and paul oh that
was the other guy hi it's got
aquaman from from three adam
in comedy bang us awesome article anyway
your friends just thought that maybe you
needed some cheering up and thought they
would hire someone look i know my
cameos are only five dollars so it's
maybe why i got this gig but
anyway it's great to meet you um
what are you doing later is that
weird to say i would love to
like
look up maybe oh wait this isn't
cameo this is grinder
um ok well yeah let's meet great
and let's do a refund without really
dying dollars back okay and this one's
going out to it's also the name
at the same time do me worry
dimitri weismann what would it be three
networks hey davey it's the threesome gay
right
freedom boys the pretzel gay noise um
wow looking for someone he's looking for
someone to me tree hey we wanted
to tell you that it's okay that
your mom died everybody's mom dies eventually
yep and this too shall pass the
good thing is is you didn't die
before your mom because that's really hard
is that she's in a better play
ace okay hey keep keep your chin
up champ we love you and we're
freedom well you know i think we
can make a bunch of money doing
that i think we just did if
you are those near those people you
owe us money you only trade on
june or mary and amanda yeah and
peter peter where jill come from
i don't know where did you come
from nobody knows just mysterious should we
get on cameos ah as john adam
and jill as adam and spazio
what should we do cameo together not
out of a jail it's out of
a coup no we shouldn't know we
should know we i still how did
you get into cameo because they let
a while going around you do you
want to do it now well i
want to make it happen where i
would just say whatever i wanted and
you could pay for that
not like you pay me wait i
use a c it i'll use no
side i'll use your name but i
say whatever i want i think that's
fine right you don't have to say
what this what is putting the message
yeah i'd you just pay for random
tammy's someone to shout line with youtube
i would do it for a minute
why wouldn't i would just make
up facts and an occasion whatever i
want to say i think people would
be happy with that i think people
would like that okay i gotta figure
out how to how to do that
so i can make that money i
think they probably are listening and are
going to contact yeah if you're liberated
by the end of the episode please
why would they be listening to this
because anyone they hear
yeah they're gonna find out they want
you to join they want they want
you to join badly
they do chem you'll get at me
they've begged those are my terms yeah
i got i've gotten contacted in various
ways i've gotten contact on saturday was
never begged well it'll be fine take
your time tell you about it oh
yeah we brought it up naturally to
convince you
actually say it yeah so we've can
this was just making noisy la la
la la la la la tattoo this
is your favorite podcast from yeah
i really like the sun is getting
to us i know why don't we
take a break let's take a break
when we come back we'll i'm a
brew reacher this is so exciting this
is the first time we've ever teased
it lauren's been looking up this reacher
and she was like oh my god
i got a good one yeah so
you're not gonna want to miss this
this is a mega get a good
in a god amanita and montana read
one page yeah don't you know that
i love you so coming back look
it's not the commercial yet we still
haven't released you but it almost is
have a horrible signal here it comes
commercial time and now
freedom is freedom is back there and
you can name it huh
ah freedom and we're okay but unfortunately
that makes you think of a manu
me this is right the mop was
sad commercials swiffer commercial oh dope is
that mop it's like yeah put me
water and rub me on dirt i
know then put me back in the
dirty water i always like
mops don't aren't good for that reason
there's so many people's purpose of life
like we would feel sad if we
weren't doing our purposes huh so nah
i've got a three cheer for yeah
oh what we mean when we went
what if the lion king was mops
mop queen like the whole the whole
thing was just ma ma ma queen
it sounds good okay like oh it's
good this game is called benjamin button
scene submitted by josh bowman you do
a one to two minute long open
scene then do the same scene as
teenagers than as kids than his babies
yeah let's just do it and see
how it hap okay so we're old
first is that what i guess lowe
benjamin you're adding more ages and be
old then made than teen then i
think we should be old old like
very old that's all adults and teens
then teens then and kids then kids
and then babies okay i don't know
be well
see let's try it we don't we
don't know what it's gonna be like
okay don't like it we edit it
just like we do on all these
episodes yeah okay so here's the opening
scene but people should know this is
what you're hearing is the absolute best
these sessions the crime hours from yeah
his the opening suggestion just to get
us going yep is um what's
the suggest land going landfill landfill my
man i'm okay alright i look at
you and i see a dump how
dare you await world oh yeah yeah
oh yeah hello friends oh you you
and she just hey what did she
say to you why did you say
what said i look at you and
i see
oh damn i dumbed like a dump
like shit like a dump cake not
your classic gump kick from when you
were a baby alright enough of this
squabbling between us i mean i think
it will be a baby oh i
have something important to talk to about
what is it i'm being kicked out
of the hospital
whoa where we live
why are all our life support and
they're kicking us out because we can't
pay read ooh no died and realize
we've been paying rent i thought we
could just stay there because we're all
we're out of money honeys
we mostly say yeah we've been friends
for so wow are we supposed to
make you cash hey joe know how
we make the cash would you like
to be worth something in the gig
economy perhaps okay what does that mean
would you rather instinct like
would you rather be a big ho
you can be pay give you a
kid or be a hundred fifty a
day but you can be any one
native share or would you rather be
paid new yea hell yea hello i
just wanna
to come in and say a donation
has been made in your honor and
you're allowed to stay at the hospital
and continue to be on life support
a donation in our honor for us
as well yay thank you fourth character
yes you're welcome or my name to
be getting younger or older love with
this i don't know my name is
nurse carol
oh nurse like christmas emma lamb carol
like a christmas well where's your the
sweet young thing come here and you
can give me a kiss ah whoosh
hey what did when i look at
you i see a dump how dare
you hey what did did you hear
what she just called me
oh what did you say i said
that when i look at him i
see a dump what's going on look
okay enough alright enough of the squabbles
between us alright like i have something
to talk to put you in charge
we're all adults here and we are
all adults but i was adult first
okay what's up it's got me there
i'm a little bit younger than you
because we're eighty god that's right that's
right
ah we're being kicked out of the
house we all own what but we
own it i know i know who's
thinking doubts being condemned oh government but
wait the government ah because we live
on the border of mexico obviously their
eminent domain y
why is it being condemned yeah i
mean they're they're condemning usually it's like
there's something wrong with it there is
something wrong with it but then they're
going to tear it down and build
the wall so you know that wall
and who's gonna pay for it mexico
apparently we are we are we owe
a lot of money so hey i
just wanted to pop in and say
hey um actually there was a donation
made in your honor and the house
is going to stay in your name
oh my god this is great news
thank god this is great yeah my
name's carol like a like a nursing
student carol i'm a nursing student i
hope to one day be a nurse
whoa also to hey come here it
might take me fifty years here and
give me
a hug why is
no shit
hey what did you say to me
teenager i've i i said you look
like a dump what yeah you do
hey what you just said to me
oh my god what does she say
i said yeah it looks like a
dump because he does um okay enough
of this alright like i mean can
we just stop okay what's your fucking
you're like
um important to talk okay bitch okay
we're being kicked out of high school
no bitch what ya loss by our
mean teacher oh my guy makes us
mister grand granules but how are we
supposed to get our degrees yeah i
need to get my high school degree
i was planning on having an m
f k um hey i just wanna
step over here and tell you guys
that donations be made in your name
and the teacher you can let you
stay claim thank you looks smelly and
lame hey leave her alone she's just
a kid i just want to be
a nurse when i grow up why
why we're doing wanna do that segway
scrubs all day
i mean smell bedpans yeah wanna sniff
bed you do want some scrubs i
want some scrubs what's your name kid
my name's carol wow we're going to
know somebody like like have faith no
more song yeah we care a lot
yeah just like that
oh my god i hate that song
get out of here let's kiss yeah
hold my head first whoosh
hey where are you why did you
call me that because you look like
when i look at you i look
you look a good dump this mean
hey
hey guys what's up what's going on
what's he say about if you call
me me jay leno the way you
talk
oh
just walking over here oh your car
is really cool with the bob's big
boy i've ever restaurant
there was bob hope or david lynch
o j lo two
i love it and that mess up
put the hey baby what's your name
that guy from the top two guys
about
what is it about the tonight show
again yeah i'm taking it away from
conan again okay now it's fixed in
time
a little bit a little
i'd let that type but that's ok
nah that that stuff diane we did
it yeah and to put it simply
we did it that's all you can
say what are you doing are you
kevin i was a weird lean forward
ah yeah i know you've always said
lean back
i always tell women lean out yeah
lean in girl shot la la la
doing do it do it do we
do it again
um do we do it again no
no i don't think that'll do a
reverse let's see the now where we
start out young alright yeah alright goo
goo goo goo goo goo goo goo
ga
huh huh huh later
yeah that's what i was saying and
i can't even care what isn't
one idol episode was with the huh
hey hey hey guess what why don't
we do it with all the sex
in the cities and so we start
with i can't guess what guess why
that cheerleader over there is giving me
the eye
the uva eye she's looking at how
old are we we're teenagers nineteen
i'm pretending to be a teacher i'm
doing twenty one jump street situated yeah
only i'm not investigating drug cases i'm
trying to have sex with well you
guys gonna go to the forty one
years ago the side huh
i'm also over with my oops i
can i have the clap
the end we ah when you can't
say that we didn't put a design
whatever tells us that we didn't do
that three char la la la la
la la la la la la la
la la la la la thank you
for listening thank you for listening we'd
love you thank you so much for
listening to us
we are threesome usa at gmail dot
com if you wanna send us a
reacher we're on we're also through to
usa on instagram and twitter and paul
and i have a show coming up
that you should be walking yeah streaming
you can't come see us in theory
should just live streaming yes we did
it once before we're doing it once
again april three when
april the i wanna see april thursday
that feels so soon but i feel
like it hurt too soon yeah yes
no we're doing a live stream and
we're going to be on stage at
dynasty typewriter doing a two-person improv show
for no audience just like three days
and we have a new shit we've
been able to
element to it that hopefully will work
out oh yes i think that a
will and fifth element yeah yeah chris
tucker is going to be there it's
interesting how the words coming out of
his man lady dresden bandages so you
will not want to miss it be
there or be square we did it
once before it was really fun you
can see the archived version of dynasty
typewriter dot com and we're going to
do it again and we're looking forward
to it
i can't wait i'm so gonna dynasty
top rider dot com for sure for
check edge girl design wow those chancing
guys do your taxes gotta you gotta
don't don't get it don't be like
don't be like paulina lien put on
you or they'll garnish your way did
they garnish your wages whatever happened with
they threatened to do that and then
that's when i got an accountant who
who heart who figured all out yeah
you figured it out now that you
figured it out that ah with the
pencil and a pad he figured it
out yet
oh yeah there's spooky theory yes i
knew okay they're all together yeah yeah
buddy buddy buddy do what they want
they say what they want they act
how they want they are what they
want to but who in the ottoman
family would you be put up but
gomez no questions day you'd be wednesday
yeah
a morticia
oh my just got my hops grandma
ma yeah i guess cousin it i'm
the neighbor who has died recently the
guy who was cousin nino the man
behind the head from the tv show
i'm sorry to hear it i'm so
sorry paul feel like something is nameless
paul i'm so sorry
in a casserole of my house
alright goodbye my oh yeah goodbye i
mean i'm gonna say too
uh