three
after
wow
a
ah ma ma ma ma ma magma
three na tu mama famous naps and
now read a vase podcasting phone
wow did you just wake up thirty
seconds ago cause i mean pretty close
that's lucky they feel really good um
it felt really good yeah just top
of the covers oh now he's yeah
yeah i yawned like a little sleepy
baby i did see on top of
the covers as per our households rules
this is three and by the way
this is a night night podcast so
this is freedom by the way
imagine it somehow being on on your
phone and you don't know what it
is what is various imagining why you're
here and you don't know what it
do
okay well this is as good a
time as any to end the show
oh sky this is gonna tell you
to say this is our final episode
of the season but we'll be back
with another season so soon you won't
even notice and you won't even give
a shit or one shit you won't
even complain to us i do
yes um but yes this is this
is our final goodbye before in our
time in our dimension lauren has her
baby yeah and we're not going to
see her until after that and then
who knows if if she'll even let
us see her after that i might
just be a totally different person
and just you know kind of say
i don't really have time for this
anymore oh my god you'll like go
away because you'll have a baby and
will be like my life is different
in my priorities are different now and
who needs podcasts yes i just don't
want anything to do with this medium
at all all i want to do
is watch over my baby and make
sure nothing happens all i wanna do
is zoom zoom zoom zoom and boom
oooooh i'm having a baby
he's having my baby you know that's
gross yeah by paul anka ooh izzy
love me like they're otherwise say hey
do you know this song sick janie
and i stumbled over this song the
other day never been over the song
yeah hey no sure enough um i'm
ready to that song by melissa manchester
called don't cry out loud don't yeah
it's exactly right but you know keep
everybody onside is about somebody joining the
circus what yeah baby crowd the day
the circus came to town of laurynas
today want the the world just passing
by her where we were
she pulled out her face and took
up with some clowns she she cried
the day the circus got there not
when it left yeah maybe be out
of joy okay but she was a
little bit too but the next line
is just she was sad about it
right what did you say lauren then
she's tired of the world passionate
the world passing versa so she painted
up a face and took off with
some clowns took on the sounds of
the down up on oh why oh
but vivid
a where i first heard that song
was on american idol sung by diane
dig diana de janeiro o amo de
garde de carmo thank you to giorno
and delivery it's still live diana delivery
yeah but anyway yeah definitely that was
her stage name and it's actually a
good stage
ha okay it's not going to be
delivery it wouldn't make any sense
you think he would get it i
guess so
i loved it so much when she's
saying it that i downloaded it at
the time and that's an amazing herb
or is a little random that they
liked this american idol serves ran the
song yes it was her version well
let's look somewhere heard the real one
while we till we discussed the lyrics
on stay of home co and once
your
bringing other podcast business into our podcast
as a springboard to our podcast business
oh i love it what's our business
we need a springboard scott because there
is a video that someone sent us
of melissa manchester doing that song on
the muppet show oh i love that
and there is a it's a very
sorry it's not a funny rendition it
is really a video it's an episode
of a tv show
okay so there's what do you what
do you call youtube videos any any
clip on youtube you call it episode
of the you call it exactly what
it is this is an excerpt from
a movie it's not really i mean
when what do you say someone sent
me a funny video like implies something
someone taped or so you know you
know suddenly just something someone made
and it applies that immediately or like
way away into the sentence and at
least as long into the sentences when
i interrupted you
okay
i would show anyway video someone so
i started with faulty premise i retract
my statement someone sent you a clip
from an episode of the tv show
you know what the muppet show that's
correct and what happened oh
she you did want to know now
i'm interested now you've hooked me see
now you got your claws into me
they did the she performed the song
ah and they sort of acted out
behind her there is a little muppet
on a highwire and then there are
three
three full like people that are wearing
clown outfits and sort of mudpie masks
and it's a little disconcerting because they
do look like muppets do you think
they'll do learn to walk like they
should do like current muppet show and
then they have i'm sorry lauren will
you will you hold
my moment
are you one of the impression that
none of the muppets can walk know
they'll slither kermit has feet and legs
one sees one proficient at karate he
has them in one scene and one
movie but so you have no he
doesn't know you know like carbon and
you think that his feet and legs
way yes when you don't see i'm
not seeing them they're gone
are they here to tell me the
truth mar they there will i'm not
saying they're not right are they what
are kermit slaves you see something does
not mean that it does not exist
but tell the truth they do not
exist when i'm not seeing them as
that we we don't know that this
is schrodinger's kirby like you think that
jim henson is down there with his
hat
end up passed on so no i
don't think that at all
and you but you think that the
legs are just dangling
it's not whether or not either of
us thinks that he cuts out we
cannot week he cuts them off this
is absurd
ah
respect kerr me respect my neck that's
right respect um but didn't make a
new muppet show and then like do
like um authentic reenactments of whack
yes i do yeah cool with with
the with the complete original lyrics yeah
yeah absolutely i believe that the the
radio edit is is not good enough
yeah because it's wet and gushy right
it's like what's the kidz bop version
gonna be oh boy yeah i know
they really they really do need to
figure that out yeah i guess
i would say they really do need
to figure that out
um dry and pushy
absolutely
the concept of dryness is not threatening
to kids at all no but i
mean and a dry civic sense of
humour this is like you know describe
yes catherine o'hara or some kids ryan
bennett cerf
libby hellman wachner dick cavett
is there anybody you ever see him
in documentaries where it's just like any
clip of dick cavett is him just
getting owned by whoever the guest is
i was like somebody really cool it's
like yeah i don't know why you
say that dick cavett you sound like
a real idiot yeah really watched i
watched an episode because we were doing
and were sort of trying to figure
out
a sixty s episode of the bang
bang tv show and so we watched
one comedy bang bang tv yea yes
since you that one um my show
and we your show i was on
it for a solid ten minutes i
would say that yeah okay alright
if between two ferns as paul's movie
than comedy shows my show stands to
reason yeah and curb your enthusiasm is
my show of course well i believe
it's also my show okay alright so
perhaps a show we share um but
yeah i watched one and he came
out and i think i feel like
john lennon was on it or something
he was like a big monumental show
and he came out and he did
a monologue and he ate shit so
badly that i was like how does
this guy have a job yeah and
it seemed like it was a regular
occurrence of him coming out saying a
couple of jokes that no one would
laugh at and him going oh i
don't know and then moving on to
an interview which he didn't do well
i don't know yeah there was there
was one
one i saw in that five years
documentary about david bowie um where he
has david bowie on the in the
ziggy stardust era and is talking to
him like you know like oh you're
certainly different to ooh yeah like that
kind of thing and david bowie is
so calm
and ah smart in in replying to
everything that he's saying like not taking
the bait of anything um and it's
amazing also considering the table is out
of his mind on cocaine at the
time
still is able to just be like
yeah i get i get what you're
saying but that's not that's not what's
happening like a mum an artist and
i'm i'm actually good yeah not a
weirdo and you're a weirdo yeah and
you're not you're aware has a better
effect yeah i don't know it is
interesting like the tom snyder's and all
the people who used to be able
to have like
broadcast careers doing bad interviews
no i mean tom snyder was good
but again you know what i mean
like like with everything in entertainment i
was so accustomed to like you watch
old s and l episodes and they
truly leave it up to the audience
whether to laugh or nodded stuff and
people will eat shit whereas now you
go to the show and they pump
the applause sign you know all the
time and they they try to get
you to laugh after
every joke and applaud every single entrance
of anyone it used to be like
tv was so interesting because people could
just sit there and have like a
non interesting conversation and that's like reductive
of of some of the old shows
but i mean there could be a
whole hour long conversation and ten minutes
of it could not work or not
be interesting yeah yeah
you know i miss that it's a
lot more to show we're doing here
yeah i have that comment about us
as well um d what if what
of an audience just somehow knew that
they were on the same page and
refused to acknowledge the applause without talking
to be interesting yeah
without talking to each other but just
one store sort of looks same way
yeah like yeah i'm not gonna do
that like oh everybody does it anytime
you decide you gotta go crazy and
everybody sort of looks around at each
other like nah i'm not gonna own
up for me like what would what
would happen like that with the guy
have to keep coming out saying look
we were begging you please
we are dying a break with old
shows have that applause sign like with
like let's say like i love lucy
or something like wouldn't they have that
sort of i don't know if they
had it for i love lucy i
forgot when it started it's interesting yeah
i don't know how far back i
go but you know like just societal
norms were different i remember an episode
of the sixties dating game that i
was watching where
not the one you want no no
i was and i was not on
it but while the dating game was
his life
but they they went to one of
the bachelors everyone everyone's in college at
some university they're all wearing suits and
they go to one of the bachelors
and the bachelorette says like a bachelor
number three will you sing a song
about me and he says oh no
i don't think i could do that
and they just moved on and that
was it whereas like
hey that's authentic and then you know
i do want to date that person
or not like but but as opposed
to allow anyone who's on television will
do any stupid thing that anyone asks
and lower it is yeah yeah well
someone was tweeting that these they thought
colbert report could not exist now because
everyone's so like the audiences are so
literal that they would not be able
to enjoy the satire they'd be like
getting mad on twitter about it or
something that's interesting i don't know if
i'd go that far yeah i mean
i don't know if i would either
but people question so you're just love
randy rainbow he wasn't serious reading rainbow
yeah reading rants on the reading rainbow
by the way
what do you say randy ray was
reading rainbow has one of the best
theme songs of all time saying yeah
eating good um butterfly in the sky
i can go twice as high take
a look it's in a book reading
rainbow reading rainbow i can go anywhere
way to win to know ways to
go reading rainbow
whoa can do anything did he do
they did do newton knew who did
it
ooh i forgot that dude really remove
threes see but jimmy mchugh i read
array bozo a wedding got other colors
paul whoa is the thing in the
video that you had was a thing
in the video the guy who did
all the impressions
it was like to hire him from
hari oh yes yes yes and it
was the end of what a wonderful
world what did he saying at the
end it was ah somebody's rock and
orchestra and the idea was he would
ah neural they would do different things
this guy i forget his name but
he was like a you would hire
amount for events to sing at events
and one of the things that he
did was an impression and this was
a this was a ten minute taper
demonstration tape yeah yeah exactly wait um
what can i have anymore which is
unfortunate that isn't for yeah you should
get it when you're digitizing all your
old stuff if you have it please
send it i don't think i have
it i think i got rid of
it i didn't come
across it in that it was curse
it was curse yeah so oh my
god somebody else has it now we
um todo is this guy i'm but
yeah so there's this guy who wanted
to be hired for parties to sing
at parties and be an entertainer and
it was like hire him and he'll
do all these different types of songs
and it was him and he would
give out a tape of himself and
you would be you would have it
yes well you know this wasn't like
a gift at the end of the
performance this was like for you to
hire second ah yeah yeah but like
but like how do you access to
tape he wouldn't be like handing it
out you'd put in your vcr know
i guess it would be how did
you get it like how did he
go around and give it to people
or later know we we got a
hold of it because of just because
of being in show business
somehow like some segment with these guys
around yeah yeah this guy's submitted it
to someone that he probably shouldn't have
that was like look at this dork
but i guess i guess it would
go to it would go to event
organizers or whatever so if you're throwing
an event you say i need a
singer they'd say oh we have this
guy or you know but he so
he was he like this tape was
demon's
iterating his range i can do this
i can do this i can do
this and then at one point he
does
what a wonderful world and he does
a louis armstrong impression oh no um
and it basically showed him doing the
very last bit of it where it
was like whoa wonderful oh and i
say to myself gabardine boot
if anyone gets a lower ooh yeah
but the gravity boop is something yeah
oh good gambit
did you ever hire him yes many
times
he's actually gonna be here in ten
minutes i will man why is this
special occasion it's there you know he's
unvaccinated and wants to hang out e
the deeper
the other guy was like bill hopkins
rock'n orchestra or something i don't remember
yeah it was like huge band a
huge band yeah doing all the party
favorites and then there was the other
guy who was trying to basically take
freedom rock songs and turn him into
a that one i still have
yeah flower power flower power yeah yeah
yeah and that was a guy basically
like telling an insane story about a
movie that he'd concocted using all of
the different songs from the sixty's and
including popcorn popcorn yes and the rain
was kind of fall down on the
characters faces to the sound of pa
popcorn and then popcorn starts do do
do do do do do do do
do do but then he starts imitating
the rain and the very first thing
he does is he pokes himself in
the city but yes that's right yeah
this guy invented the jukebox musical he
he sort of did it sounded yeah
and at the time yeah weirdest part
about the whole thing was at the
end
or towards the end of the story
the the main character invents ah ah
ah vegan restaurant yeah it looks to
be in a yurt and then he's
called veggie rot of edgerank any steps
he stops pitching the movie at that
point and start saying when the movie
comes out this will be the most
popular franchise ah
of restaurants of all time eclipsing mcdonald's
yeah like he predicts the future mixing
mcdonald's um and he had all kinds
of merch that he would drop in
throughout the thing um there was a
heart with a peace sign that was
his his big logo that he would
there was a like a t-shirt and
then there was like a c
a staff with like ah ah oh
yeah oh yeah mcconnell dollar stone it
was i got ah i digitized it
and i can't find it i have
to find that okay crazy there's an
pewter
no it's not anymore that's the thing
they've got out it got out i
deleted that folder i was having issues
with my um storage folder now i
can't find the tape and it's gotta
be around here somewhere okay isn't it
yeah wow that would just be like
an an a weird instagram account
yeah well it is interesting because we
when we when you know paul had
a whole bunch of these and we
would sit around watching them a lot
and it was like you you have
this secret thing that no one else
had and nowadays it would be like
if something like that was uploaded to
the internet it would be popular like
one day and everyone would dunk on
yeah and then you'd move on you
know
no but there's this one we've watched
okay over mike and i can't stop
looking at and i don't remember his
hands because it's something weird but he's
like kind of like venice beach life
are kind of person and he also
is like us in our own schwarzenegger
devil join it in his feet so
he's
always doing things like this thousand feet
where weight double double jointed wear and
it's like his feet go like weird
ways like you want his ankles or
yeah double yeah okay not that shoot
themselves though yeah yeah right that that
would be extra weird but the yeah
his ankles are double doing it so
he like puts them he's always putting
on display like like flop his foot
up onto like a weird table
like it's just easy i know and
and apologies to anyone who happens to
be double jointed and i'm sure you've
had a lot of fun with it
over the years but it's been my
stop i don't like looking at play
time his ovo know being double jointed
is a blast i'm not but my
my brother was when we were growing
up he could flip his knees like
you are down basically face down bring
the legs up to the side oh
and it was a cool party trick
but our no i don't think so
he hasn't tried and one time but
if he tried he would dry right
yeah what do you mean he hasn't
tried well he hasn't done it in
a long toke i mean it's usually
rusher heads pure-play won't
let's all time high that i will
but this man like
whatever who cares if someone's double jointed
he puts it it's his it's his
thing yeah he is using it it's
like every video is so odd it's
like he just like he'll like be
walking down the street and then he'll
flop his foot up onto a you
know stonewall
he has like a watch on his
foot or like it's actually a phone
and then he'll like look at life
so i'll make it but he'll make
up around i'll be like
everything's going fine and then like flopping
open like su fifty nine and like
the
company boo
so weird things going bad is too
vivid nine
can't stop watching it can wait the
sides there's what were you sitting on
his bed and his his legs are
going like just so strangely and then
he's like he's like pretending like put
things in a pot and he's like
he goes this looks like some soup
to me so everybody go but it's
kind of man it's like wow
he's in his bed
i gotta find it please add my
name also did you say he's got
a phone on his foot it was
a wow no it's a phone it's
like a phone i think this is
another one of lawrence patent no no
idea here is gonna happen here his
name is nar norcal g
n a r and o ah no
i refuse exe i'm not going to
a site called nano focus of domains
women that elstead me
all the success so we gotta take
it
huh
wait what
what is his name
because i'm going ma
where do you go already oh my
god a guy when the reels take
me away
oh wow oh my god dad did
that to me this looks like some
soup to me and i'm like maybe
i'll just be walking just silent for
a long time then this looks like
some soup to me
what song said parenting though just the
dump outdone to me and allow milking
i mean i may know the bush
no no it's not magic it is
nonsense i don't know it's like some
know it's like a red hot chili
peppers thing or something ooh this looks
like the body but maybe deep deep
feeling better so um santee she say
that we feel duh i know you
guys wouldn't wouldn't pay to go see
the red hot chili peppers but write
some paid how much would someone pay
you to go on thousand dollars i
would go to watch the haven e
to watch knew the whole thing good
bench
you're not just gonna walk in and
do two new outfit three sixteen i
now see them um two thousand dollars
actually sit through the concert i'm gonna
need five thousand and really good seats
you want i'm gonna i'm gonna need
i'm gonna eat five thousand beds in
the worst seats yeah i want i
want here's what i want
i want to be in a box
where i get like lots of food
everything i need bathrooms accessible and i
need to be paid five thousand dollars
ok here's here's a here's another question
good terms how am i
how much would you have to be
paid to give birth at the red
hot chili peppers concert that's the most
psychotic
i was sponsored by them and so
when it happens there's a big spotlight
and everybody's like it's time you're on
the jumbotron and then they sing sexy
mexican maid while you're giving birth
okay one million dollars you do it
for a million yeah okay i'll put
i'm gonna try to broker this and
you have to name your daughter she
flee
it was that chiefly female version of
flee oh oh she sleep with with
an iphone actually yeah she chiefly that
you're saying chiefly how much would you
have pain scott to um go from
be on stage during a britney spears
concert wearing atlas
and going to hell
what do you do danno too i
might do it for the exposure ah
my name out there exposure of your
as britney spears fan all right how
much would you have to be paid
to go to a gordon lightfoot concert
and
i stand behind him every song you
just shake your head nun and do
thumbs-down yesterday and the crowd loves him
so they're pissed at you the whole
time and then he finally turns around
and your pants fall down and you're
like oh no he doesn't know that
i'm there he pretends not to know
that your use in on it exact
so he
turns around your pants fall down and
then he gives you a thumbs down
and shing yes yeah that's this is
a dad going to guide it on
make me laugh two guys bring out
a board they put you on it
they dump molasses over you and feathers
and then they ride you out of
town okay i would do that for
one dollar
yeah i mean it sounds fun to
do that during a concert i would
do that part for free the funds
down part but then the whole molasses
i get syrup all over my head
for the bang bang tv show and
how many may me my show that
was your show sorry that was really
not fun so i would i was
the most unfunny
part of it
ah well i had a dumped over
me so many times and then just
leah cleaning myself ah i don't know
it was cool add i don't know
but ah i would do it for
i would do it for two dollars
okay don't all three know what a
deal has been struck oh i'll do
it i'm going to arrange this yes
we're both gonna be on stage the
the thumbs down during the concert sounds
great that sounds like an i don't
know that it's ever been done before
you're just going to yeesh you have
to be you have to be like
like tending that you're listening to every
lyric very thoughtfully
yeah and then you consider it and
then you give a thumbs down after
each one and i'm i'm doing like
the cut his mic off and you're
looking in the wings go
if he were willing to do that
i would do that for free i
would show up anywhere to this this
is in canada too and so the
audience will absolutely hate you they will
delay yeah that's fine and because i
don't think it's sustainable longer than ninety
seconds that's why it's to do with
the entire show is so fun two
hours
paul and people just confuse the entire
time i would love it i would
do it right now paul how much
would you need to be paid to
um stand in front of ah subway
sandwiches on hollywood boulevard and ah be
dressed as jaffa sandwiches or in front
of the actual store theirs
two sandwiches on the ground
alright that's important in my decision you're
addressed as johnny johnny depp as a
pirate okay which one i am the
one that's famous oh captain jack sparrow
yeah claude le feet and you have
a megaphone and you're shouting can somebody
hit me with these meats
can i
do i get to sounds like the
word can i do the delivery different
however i want each time let me
ah let's audition ah idea yeah what
you got
could somebody hit me with these
nah newbie do with eaten me this
is pretty good oh somebody hit me
with these me it's um okay no
you have to do the third one
but that's the only one you can
do and you have to say it
nonstop nonstop okay
because i feel like i feel like
physically though ease yeah i feel like
physically that's but that's taxing like to
do that you know what i mean
that's really care okay fine you can't
you have to do it for
one hour but there's like a tour
guide group that's constantly being brought in
every minute right and people are spanking
you and they all know who you
are they're spanking me with the meats
oh so oh okay now if it
was just i was begging for someone
hit me with the meats but i
didn't actually want that to have
open and when people tried to do
it i would fight them that would
be i thought would be interesting to
me like what are you doing you
have one i like that no i
like that i like that your you
say can somebody hit me with these
meats and you seem like you really
want them to and then when they
start to do it you start running
yeah and then like yeah people just
chase you yeah
two they chase me they were there
they went on how fast they are
how fast you are or they paid
to chase me or you're you're just
counting on this to happen some people
will chase you for sure just knowing
kids will definitely chase you because they'll
think it's a fun game oh yeah
twenty year old guys they'll chase you
twenty yeah twenty one year old guys
you know they they can drink they
probably just
go off to a bar like let's
drink instead instead of chasing that captain
jack sparrow with the bullhorn asking us
to hit with meats from those two
sandwiches on the ground on the ground
who brings the sandwiches that's the other
part of it lawrence was no deal
i will lay the sandwiches on the
ground before you arrive thank you or
they put today
so it's like deconstructed sandwiches or all
the elements of sandwiches and paul has
to put them together though their subway
sandwiches that are completely put together
one is roast beef and one's turkey
so someone wants me with the meats
or if they dare to they will
have to pick the meats out of
the sandwiches ah what do you mean
when you say hippie with the meats
is the sandwich the entire and hello
oh okay six inches people get that
their foot longs that they can have
a little bit of social distancing in
case there
got vaccinated for their six foot long
six large subs yeah yeah this is
now this is interesting a six foot
long party sub someone has to pick
it up wield it like a bat
right like batman they have to but
they have to be very careful like
a batman um there to be very
careful because it the you know little
bend in the middle you know if
you try to exactly yeah so maybe
frozen maybe they should be frozen well
no that's that's that's always good sandwiches
needs more salt what does i know
that's that's assault somebody just gonna hit
me with the frozen bolts because this
is a salt people i will definitely
read this it's actually a pepper
oh so you're out as ever you're
saying for this reason you're out no
two hundred dollars okay i don't i
got two hundred that's i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna pay higher than two
hundred dollars for this year you know
what you're gonna pay for this oh
i mean no i don't want this
to happen
yemeni coming out of the pandemic it's
almost like you could almost say anything
like how much would i have to
pay you i would say i'll just
do it for free
sounds just like you just want to
get out someone out of the house
as well to see people sure i'll
do it yeah i'll do what i
watch what if i throw a boulevard
a pool full of bees oh yeah
yes all right yeah no problem sounds
hey how would you like to get
stabbed
just take place this is like how
jackass started
what if the three of us did
a competitor jackass show
oh i think definitely this time for
us to do that
in our lives i think we're three
of us the three of us are
the perfect point in our lives it's
mutilating ourselves always seem like i do
think jackass was funny like oh i
thought so what but what if we
did a jackass type show that was
trying to compete with jackass but we
got too scared before every single thing
we never did any of the things
yeah that's a good idea that's good
and everyone would just see us being
scared and we never actually do the
things yeah
it's fun but we always feel like
i don't want to everyone could see
us being scared like heads that is
really the draw that's the drug is
yeah it's just look at east cowards
what would be a challenge that we
wouldn't want to do like attaching something
to our nuts yeah we could we
could clip something to your nuts lorne
and we could like like electrodes or
something
yeah like this and yeah you do
like um pregnancy labor pains electrodes attached
to your nuts yeah yeah we would
do those we would do pregnancy labour
yeah we go boys like roads yeah
those attention to our nuts general labor
pain electrodes
um we obviously get a report a
party filled with human shit yeah oh
my god that's it so there's a
of body filled with human shit and
we and everyone we're being paid for
the show and everyone expects us to
do the show but every single stunt
we just go like i just yeah
i don't want to do it and
we get back the money
after every episode what with jackass were
they getting where they exchanging money to
do these well i mean i say
guy working at the atv should we
get we get back the money that's
like the deal for the show well
yeah for the episode so like the
next episode we can do the stunts
and go ahead with it if we
want this is interworking still in the
episode basis yes
but we're still in the episode it's
like they they still need to pay
us for our appearance fee well sure
there'd be a sag-aftra minimum yeah of
course yeah that's understood of course my
answer any preacher that in the yeah
in the acting labour wires ancestors
yeah but after but each time were
we just kind of like take a
look at it and go okay what
are we getting paid for this like
i would imagine we would get ah
probably like twenty grand an episode a
piece to to be in the show
right and so it is like what
is honestly the mildest stunt that you
could think of that you would actually
do yeah i would maybe do something
on why
water and also lauren um okay i
guess i would do something like
like with hot sauce and my taint
on your nuts my taint um i
i you know
to that over the weekend two things
happen like a daredevil number one a
a daredevil die attempting a stunt and
then it's like real yeah i didn't
hear this and then a bunch of
people dare devil die and no one
told me and dare the devil don't
think people know he died jumping out
here are some
nothing and it was kinda like oh
yeah well no one should ever do
those things ever so yeah oh my
god i hate when people jump from
building to building for foe what do
they call that sugar score
um yeah i mean i don't think
i would do okay so i would
i would jump in a pool probably
that's not a shot pool with my
clothes on i'd do my phone in
my pocket i watch ah jump in
a pool i dare you to
jump in the pool we used to
i mean i was home and i
were talking about this the other day
we it's true lord we were we
used to ride bikes into the pool
tall john and i yes um and
that was when back in my twenties
in our twenty wow your wild we
would we would try to use the
the key
was you would try to like pull
up on the handlebars right as you
got on the edge so that because
what we found is if you just
wrote it into the pool it would
two-fold first you go face first but
so we would try to like jump
it into the pool and then today's
first is funnier face first was fun
though but then tell john would also
jump from the top of the roof
into the pool yeah that's
inside she gets a bike out but
that's crazy how do we get the
bike out we picked it up it
didn't sink to the bottom
sure this is to
he would pick it up i can't
argue with you it did sink to
the bottom it sounds hard to get
it out boy he jumped from the
roof does sound hard to get a
bike like if you because you're going
in the deep end presumably right deep
ish yeah like midpoint okay so you
could you could drag it you could
stab drag you didn't drag and drop
whim it up to the surface that's
what i'm saying wait so what
what roof is he doing this half
of this was brian hussein's house so
he would he would take a run
off of it so imagine that roof
yeah i actually did baby so he's
him constantly for his child and also
you've maybe been in that place i
probably know someone i wonder because it
did he did dave rath live there
no okay so not family
home i wanted to ask you it's
called koi laura i wanted to ask
you i want how much how much
did you get paid for babysitting i've
never employed a babysitter and i've never
been a babysitter well i got paid
fifteen dollars an hour um and that
was i think that's the most i
ever got but i knew people who
are making twenty or twenty five wow
um
i'm in new york especially but yeah
it was usually fifteen an hour but
i don't know that that's people's rate
nowadays in big cities i think it's
probably pretty low for my famously got
one dollar an hour to do it
wow everyone knows that so we just
have to babysit your little sister know
to baby sit up friends daughter and
son this was
recently ah no look if you like
no when i was like fourteen maybe
i have a vivid memory of reading
the ah the latest issue of ah
bilson cabbages new mutants when i was
doing this but um i was i
was i would watch them and the
the one girl would throw the cat
on me which is how i developed
a fear of cats
and ah and then i would only
pay that fear yeah sort of i
don't really like hats and i'm really
allergic to them so that doesn't help
but um but ah and so then
and i would complain i'd be like
i'm only getting a dollar an hour
so it would be like at the
end of the night they'd give me
like three dollars or four dollars it
is ridiculous that they
take care to protect your children yeah
yeah then but but my parents had
a good point which is they said
they're not very well off this is
a church church family oh very well
off and this is something that you
can do for them while making get
rid of that fucking that another mouth
to feed yeah really tell me about
it maybe you don't
have two kids if you're broke
hi people what happened you turned right
wing i'm on your side
um so anyway but ah that was
that was the i i don't think
i ever babysat after them like i
it wasn't something that i did was
left a bad taste in your mouth
i'm sure yeah bt in the em
um we take a break by
we're back welcome back most interesting episode
yeah oh yeah what a sizzling topic
we had between the ads but you'll
never worse you'll never hear what when
hopefully they'll be ads um no nine
what scott in addition to ah riding
your bike rides close right side glasses
what is something that you did as
a kid that you would never do
now and lauren same question okay i
would that i that is like out
of fashion now no no no
of doing it would be like what
no oh you can't do that well
oh man that does remind me that
my dad and i yesterday were talking
about how weird it was that dog
shit everywhere no one ever picked it
up um back in the day true
yeah they would just run away and
they would yeah
and no one ever thought about because
it was like oh it'll just crumble
and fertilize the grass
um so there was just dog shit
everywhere yeah um in the seventies and
early eighties okay so that was a
thing that off would often happen was
that you stood up in touch yeah
you would step back then it's true
and i think it's like harvin annoyed
probably isn't he like the guy who
kind of you know that was his
whole platform his whole thing was how
we started toys a killing up cleaning
up san francisco and dodman dog show
too powerful and they just shit on
it
um i mean is there stuff that
i used to do that i wouldn't
do now i mean i was thinking
about how i never locked my bike
up but you're talking about like something
physical i guess anything i tell you
what here's maybe a more interesting question
because i think that is obviously there's
a bunch of shit you wouldn't do
that you did as a kid you
would do now what is something that
you did as a kid that you
wish you could do now
i'll go out to i'll go with
ya hugo when i was a kid
every summer we used to play me
and my cousins who lived next stories
to play flashlight tag oh and that's
fun it was so my fondest memories
it was so much fun it was
just it's it was exciting it was
like we would come up with
strategies and stuff like that it was
i loved it i loved it just
that feeling captured do you ever play
capture the flag yeah so place towers
yeah we didn't do we didn't do
that we did like running basis was
when we did a lot um
we said we used to play like
wiffle ball in our backyard um i
remember where all the bases were you
can do that
i get not my little backyard oh
this is another way in your old
family home backyard you go there what
if i did okay to play with
along the beatles started to love you
just like a little kid and yeah
yeah go sneak up on those maker
i'd wait i'm sure zombie makeup is
like i i died like it but
i also get
i need to grow food
who says that go stone grow through
we don't know oh yeah fifteen to
see you age yeah yeah i like
those all tight they don't fit right
they just like weird these are the
only clothes i have these tough skins
are killing me i do sometimes think
about like i have investigated
camps to rent you do this as
a kid
yeah right i've really been wanting loves
i miss investigating things no i i
saw episode iv i sometimes have thought
like oh it'd be fun to get
a bunch of people you know like
one hundred people and rent a camps
and go to go to camp for
a week and do stuff like capture
the flag and stuff like that so
i've thought about that and you know
my friend had
my friend had a really fun bachelor
party up in ohi where essentially it
was like where the bionic woman lived
that's right where it was three days
and everyone was like playing pool games
and there was a basketball court and
i'll start all sorts of stuff and
i was like and it was like
every guy you knew and i was
saying like why do we why do
we
have to wait for someone to get
married to do this why can't we
just do this like every summer will
yeah no girls allowed absolutely but but
it seems like no one will make
the time to do it unless it's
for an official occasion like if i
were to send out an email of
like ok we're all getting together ah
you know i don't know men's retreat
or whatever i think some people would
go like yeah i don't know i
don't want to go
what you said mandatory we're gonna fight
for our rights yeah that's sin whoever
wins gets to stay married to their
wife yeah only half will win
we're gonna draw straws to see who
stays married i don't know what i
what i did as a kid i
i guess one thing that came to
mind initially was that i could ride
my bike without my hands but i
can't do that now i couldn't do
it then i can't do it now
i should be able to do it
then i wonder if i could do
it i don't i do not know
what the
secret is just to put my feet
up on the handlebars while i was
eating i could like do little things
to my cigarette not do that now
at all and i would not even
try honestly i i sort of miss
waterskiing i'm sure i've talked about it
but i feel like the last time
i ever did it was when i
was twenty two but i still feel
like i could do it
even though it was i don't think
it was a childhood thing at all
no but i mean but now i've
i feel like ah wouldn't i break
my neck doing it or something i
don't know you would but you could
do it
you want me to do it well
i'm gonna break my neck no it's
gone i want you to live forever
oh okay i will
okay um how long do you think
we'll live is that mormon we talked
about this a lot i'm going for
a hundred i feel like i'm going
for one hundred yeah man yeah yeah
my i see i see you both
living well into your late nineties i
come from ah i come from a
people who lived
in into their late nineties i don't
but it also doesn't seem fun and
well written no it does seem like
when you get really but then again
i gotta say all the old people
that i that are in their nineties
that i've known were all from generations
where they came from generations where they
were smoking and like yeah
all this stuff that that we know
is bad now so maybe they weren't
having as good of a time as
we will in turn look right no
i yeah no like staying engaged and
um with some sort of marketing for
some sort of community and having a
hobby or two yes yeah and not
like the proud yourself
if you get bored
if you still have your proud boys
when you're in your nineties i'll be
so happy for you hey gaming oh
the serial yeah oh my yeah boys
around me tricks are for kids yeah
um yeah it's i just don't want
to be i don't want to be
old and bored and i don't
want to be old and alone and
i also don't i don't want to
have like alzheimer's yeah let's let's agree
across the board we do not want
have all time let's make an alzheimer's
backhoe i don't want to i don't
want to ever retire denoting i know
what you mean although i've meet you
there but i tired tomorrow well i
think
retiring housekeeping
i am a microphone shut i think
that retiring is ah is for actors
because yeah like you can do that
in every job yeah but like that's
such a key like betty white is
so you know with it because she's
like you know working on tv shows
well into her older age yeah and
like it seems so cool it'll be
a hard day
if there's ever a forced retirement where
like people go yeah you don't really
have any job prospects anymore like you
know the comedy is moving funny old
person i feel like that's going to
be the best the best time of
my career is i think i will
be a good uni will personally shit
think you'll be straight and eighty yeah
like
you're coming into your own there will
be a lot like someone's grandpa and
then you how many you say something
weird and everyone's like the fuck was
i start to look really old i
think there's also gonna be a lot
of younger comedy fans are gonna remember
me it's like well let's put that
guy in this yeah and and all
this shows like seven seconds long and
i'm like a weird platform you need
to pay forty dollars a day
four
yeah and you'll ever see him i'm
like i guess i was fun back
to my mansion i think i think
youtube is actors i think it will
be fine getting old i just think
that at a certain point if i
want to make stuff people will be
like and now we'll know but when
when really old people
i'll start pitching ideas you know you
gotta go
ha once i no no no there's
some there's some really old people in
this business who are making things yeah
totally totally but you had your legacy
established thing if you keep working i
think you're okay if you just never
stop you know it's it yeah i
did work with someone once who um
had worked for awhile and then had
a family and had
and worked in like ten years and
then it was like i'm getting back
into it and then they pitched just
like the worst jokes and i was
kind of like oh i gotta say
it's current you gotta stay current you
gotta stay on the internet ten hours
a day homeboy i got some bad
screentime notifications recently i need i'm up
to nine percent oh my i made
myself last night i
made myself i watched three hours of
ah a new show i actually did
have lasagna for dinner like you did
this is crazy how did i know
that i was watching you um war
of the worlds on epics which is
very well done but it's extremely grim
there's like not a light moment in
it i mean i'm that that recent
tom cruise film was
grimm i was surprised by how fucking
dark oh yes yeah but i i
like i was i was looking at
my phone and when the first episode
started and i was like you know
what i'm just gonna i'm gonna put
it over and on the charger not
gonna i'm not gonna look at it
and it was actually it it was
difficult at first because it was
just the reflex of like i'm gonna
grab my phone and whatever yes but
then it felt so good to that
i made myself do it right so
good to focus on something especially a
nice like a piece of art like
a show that's like a fast and
furious movie or well even that you
know exactly just to
go i'm watching this this is what
exactly nine percent visual anyway you know
someone someone was writing an essay on
the movies the other day thomas swift
they said that that um if you
if you watch something on cable it's
too easy to dip out after ten
minutes because like if you are or
or or even just like streaming it's
too easy to go
i'm not interested in pick up your
phone whereas if you're forced to watch
something in a movie theater after maybe
iraqi ten minutes you can start to
enjoy something where you would never give
it the chance oh yeah i remember
rocky ten minutes picture show you have
come i also want to point out
i met jonathan swift earlier amy wait
what did you say i said thomas
swift i don't think oh tom swift
was
like a yeah he's like a revolution
and adventurer something yeah yeah um wait
so reform and make a great tom
swift by the way what i think
he's a kid isn't he yeah you
and your kid outfit goes make up
his tom swift is like huck i
kind of i think but like a
later period i don't i
never read those books but i think
he was like from the z like
from the fifties from the nineteen i
just remember my little referee like wow
like reading tom swift dime novels you
know but it looks like it went
into the fifties like the style of
the books got more yeah by the
way thank you to so many listeners
for telling me that the stories
the books that i read where the
alf alfred hitchcock presents ah oh yeah
that's not that was the three adventurers
of the three adventurers yeah yes that's
the one where people are trying to
figure out that quote that you know
that was something different yeah okay um
i also wonder even touching back on
the dog and addressing dog ga story
from earlier that i
i have had a sort of fear
of dogs get missing being missing ever
since i was young and read the
beverly cleary rib z novel which was
part of the henry huggins university get
told a funny story on her podcast
and the episode with ed helms where
she she loved that book so much
much that she did it for book
reports for like many years and like
in middle school they're like you can't
keep writing keep doing really i read
revenue
ah still good still good ah nothing
really new popped out
she was part of the general's crew
because going back to circling yeah and
drills crew where the rat dropped down
in the mouse deer bull sorry mouse
the dead mouse we taught dead men
sorry one mouse played this party not
play this party he dropped down and
gave him twenty like spiderman and tig
head tendrils
yeah take she was a creature she
um she is like an h p
lovecraft thing and she a tendrils she
wrapped them around their necks and yeah
we girls we barely hear any sense
now
federals or hair generals or heralds are
hair tattoo ties but you're thinking of
regular hair you know na bazi bazi
goop water bobby goop you don't think
that's the title
it was like subsidy to me by
ear this tendrils are three yeah everybody
knows the bank alright we have to
take a break we'll be right back
with the three-door
we're back everybody it's a single fitch's
mad bitches where the bitches level badgers
bags all goes over of a brutal
vol thirty two eddie boo
and guess what it's three your time
as was foretold by the ancient prophesies
this is a game called political candidate
it is submitted by nicole kez de
what a fun name there's a z
and fun nicole oh
two people becoming cold has ended
but why nicole z you are so
far away from oh no zip coal
the mike was actually saying karlsson i
know but we can't hear you to
see url become a political candidate being
interviewed at a political debate by the
third person the candidate speaks by having
each person say one word at a
time to form the sentences has to
include a platform campaign slogan and a
closing statement so you say what you're
running what your run
for what you're smoking is and what
you're running to um everybody understand yeah
of course is so you'd understand anyway
done it in my mind and we
did it well that's the episode thanks
for listening everybody well that was fun
okay um okay first good question and
that was also my questionnaire i scoured
the alternative task lauren and i will
go first okay
ah canada thank you so much for
meeting with me today um this is
an exclusive interview on the first to
talk to you about your campaign and
what you are running for what you
want people to know and any final
words you'd like to give so let
me let me ask you this what
is your platform in essence
all i want is to
show the world that my
little
idea is ah great okay but you
haven't really said what the idea is
what what is the idea what are
you why are you running for office
i believe that everybody has the right
to show
shit wherever
want
okay is that the only yes the
only plank in your in your platform
yes it yeah but
i also will say that there is
one little exception what would that be
i don't ever want to shit
it again
that seems unrealistic what what what is
your slogan what are what do you
draw what are you hoping will always
singing you
god ah jans oh
is
my ghee
see your campaign slogan you've got a
chance with mikey
oh sorry your coinbase login is i'm
always singing you've got a chance with
me
yes okay yes and ok what just
i know you're running short on time
what would you like to leave people
gods plenty of time okay um name
your biggest influence in running for public
office i really love
lil rel
howry
the comedian yes yeah and after
reductive
comedian and actors reductive gal also game
show host thank you
alright now i'm running short on time
ah what would you like to yes
please why say a little more what
would you like to tell people ah
before we close out this interview stop
listening to the windows
ninety five theme
alright just writing this down stop listening
to the windows ninety five theme alright
well good luck
huh
bike
alright hey now paul and scott and
i will be the okay interviewer
oh i'm so excited to get to
speak with you mr tim tom this
is such a big day in our
city we are finally going to hear
your platform i'd love to know what
it is that you're running for what
is your main platform first
you must i increase your limits of
your mind oh okay so i have
no i'm coming with open mind so
what is the what
what is the main part of your
platform that you want talk about hallucinogenic
cts are the
best way to
open your doors to perception alla huxley
oh la huxley the writer
okay i don't know if i've heard
of them but um that's great so
do you have um something else you
want to say
oh yes we i have a secret
ok city oh a secret slogan i'm
sorry blah humbug
i think that one's been used before
ebenezer scrooge in christmas carol but i
say
boo bum hug which is very different
right so your slogan is boo bum
hug
that is correct
likes is great
the u i
ah knew you would
yet
let me ask you do you have
any anybody who really influenced you for
to wanna run for on this campaign
on this platform actually madonna in truth
or dare was so electrifying it
made me shudder too
orgasm
oh i'm sorry to say i feel
like you're on the verge of being
cancelled um fine
okay well that went about as horribly
as it could i'm gonna go back
to the newsroom and not report on
this way what hold on
you know
interviews are scary honestly and i need
to tell you something
i don't have any
testicles or
toes you really didn't have to tell
me that um that is honestly information
that we don't need as the public
um but thank you so much for
your time mister tim tom i will
say i don't think you're gonna make
it onto the ballot this year just
judging by the way the crowd has
dispersed here ah wait what piece
people were listening oops yes okay see
yeah alright very nice now paul and
laura and yeah wow
ah it's so nice to see you
i know we have a long relationship
and i know you personally and that's
why i was hired to do this
profile piece of you but i just
want to say that none of that
is going to get in the way
and even though i know you so
well and nothing you could say would
surprise me
but um you know i think this
will just be a friendly chat so
ah first of all just let's get
the basics out of the way ah
why did you want to even run
for office
this is a difficult thing to talk
about but i always wanted to be
a
emperor but we know that is it
ah thing here will sure i mean
you've talked about wanting to be an
emperor ever since we were young children
playing in the school yard you are
always saying i love the emperor and
star wars
and you know palpatine is my hero
and so i knew that going in
but but why here why now well
finally i can tell you that
i'm dying o of what
a big disease how big souls
big oh god that's horrible how long
do you have left
one hour
no well i don't think that's good
for your chances i and
two
decades oh okay well that's i mean
that opens it up a little bit
then i think i can see why
you would want to spend your last
twenty years on earth i mean you
may die before that not of whatever
disease the big disease you have but
you may like you know get hit
by a bus or something tomorrow is
not promised to any of us so
it's great that we're taking you know
our chances well we have ah you
know breath still in our bodies here
so i think that's wonderful what is
your platform though
one
thing i
want to accomplish is
recalling all
senators and replacing all
congress people with
birds
ah birds okay um oh
or
i well
destroy this nation
o k that's i mean that doesn't
sound like a really electable do you
have a slogan though i mean it's
not very catchy oh people are dirt
aliens
gross
i hate you
aw sway so much yeah all people
are dirt aliens gross
i hate you also much yep
got ah
huh
right okay well um surely there's one
thing you're going to do on your
first day of office poop in a
yes
class it seems like it'd be hard
to get that in there without a
funnel right i've thought about this so
many times
don't cry it's fine i'm sorry this
is just making me emotional i've known
you for so long and to think
that you've been thinking about shooting glass
for this whole time while we've had
so many meaningful deep conversations on my
end
and you've just been thinking about shitting
in a glass holder well that's the
way the brain works
yours maybe not mine no i was
focused on our conversations oh brains do
okay i don't look i i honestly
i really think you should see someone
about this because it seems like you
have some sort of mental i'm gonna
trying to see someone
but you keep getting in the way
i'm stopping you from seeing a therapist
i mean look i don't know what
i am sir the phone up please
oh hold i am getting called wait
it's from you oh
okay hello
hi it's me
are you home yeah i'm with you
he can i talk to you for
anyone there ah yeah why don't i
pass you onto my associate grade oh
okay
whoa whoa i hear you need to
talk to someone about yeah mental problems
want therapy now now okay well i'm
available ah but you have to meet
my rates if that's okay i'm four
hours an hour
oh
that's too much too rich for your
blood no but it could be cheaper
i'll i'll do it for three three
dollars an hour what do you feel
talk to me tell you what i'll
do it for ten cents if you
just tell me your problem in the
next minute i
once too
he wants to what oh that about
speaks
he wants to speaks
about
problems will yeah
me poops
why are you talking like popeye suddenly
i
got to see
likes how bias four eyes gets whoops
well pooping is natural so you don't
feel don't speak like popeye to try
to stave that off i just go
ahead and do it and then you
know you'll be
jesus
it's not on the phone itself
put
that other guy back on ooh you
don't like me i still want my
ten cents you fucking cheap skates see
you in hell
hi what happened you were talking to
my dat guy was the most irritating
person i have ever met boring husband
heard of
that's my husband you can't say that
about him get
ouch
of my life just because i married
an irritating person yes or stay married
of your life or stay married okay
i'll stay married
and stay in your life i guess
okay do
you want to hear my slogan yeah
yes have you been working on it
because you haven't you had a really
terrible one everyone should suck their own
mingle
okay look i'm sorry this is just
i don't know what's happened to you
within the last ten minutes but i
hate your friend anymore in going to
the therapist know that's that's part of
the ten min
minutes that i've been having a problem
can i please level with you please
yes what's going i'm suffering from a
serious
attack of the disease
that the aforementioned disease that you didn't
tell me that just the big one
you're having an attack right now and
that's is it causing this behavior or
you're just having an attack and it's
unrelated
it's unrelated okay well it's a huge
scene so you're just an asshole now
hey you're being an asshole
no
i'm not
okay are are you
making fun of how i speak yes
i've never brought it up we've been
childhood friends ever since we were young
i've never made fun of the way
you speak i'm the only person everyone
in school made fun of you all
the time and now you act like
this to me
yeah emperor
and now you're saying words on top
of each other at the same time
for
you
emperor you that's not even a school
freak
yeah i'm a freak is everything just
one word freak dragon person
address this
emperor as emperor
you're not an emperor yet and with
the profile i'm writing you're never going
to be one eat
dangles okay and by the way no
one calls dicks dangles anymore okay especially
when you see someone do okay look
i love you i gotta go i
i love you too so
kisses get
workforce
alright the end out yeah and yeah
and then and high on guys great
to see what a fun season that
says being ah been down with the
pandemic and person on zoom all over
the place ah
and you'll have things you'll want to
talk about i will to go wow
go do you do wow
it was it stab eighty seventy yeah
alright love everyone love you bye bye
uh