through the arena
freedom freedom
beat up three three three three three
three
ah it's called freedom and you heard
a sad bunch and that's why i've
never done it because that's what it's
called we wouldn't call it that and
wow we wouldn't sell it if we
didn't call it that we say it
three times we don't say it three
times yeah because freedom appeared in the
mirror i e under the table no
nairobi is one three m appears in
the mirror yeah
what he's supposed to say you say
hi freedom hey girl like barbie we
are them and we say hi to
three of them do we have to
say it backwards three times to make
it disappear charge three yeah you messed
up say it three years say three
times fast he chimes three jibes three
times did you do today three two
what does that
nothing nothing at all for any devils
baby you filled it comes to everything
now we need fruity pebbles as well
as both parables we need pretty pymble
shirts we need fruity pebbles shirks fruity
pebbles food is available
it is the perfect know it should
be literally you as barney you as
fred barney will your blonde quote unquote
and then a blonde fred and a
brunette of barney what about a redhead
vel that's how we don't get sue
and then who am i i guess
stupid oh great pebbles yeah sorry else
would you be right i was thinking
maybe the dinosaur like scott dean lee
bar should be fred i'll be wilma
yeah it will be pebbles and i'll
say if everybody hellsing if we've ever
had someone draw that and we'll make
it a shirt yeah and good you'll
get a cut of the proceeds i'm
sure yeah twenty dollars or so i
think that was a wanker
for for seven hundred and fifty dollars
oh guys hell is one it'll be
like wu tang yeah i'll make one
really expensive t-shirt we are like wootton
in a lot of ways yeah we're
nothing to fuck with shirt i mean
that's a given some of us are
dead
wow that's right this used to be
five them and the item huh
if
all thirty three to let's just say
now if one of you guys does
will continue doing the show yes i
die show's over that's true that's true
steward yeah yeah yeah
it'd be too much of it well
you'd part because you could just do
your other cvb talkback show huh yeah
it'll show you still talk back will
you gift us to show to do
whatever we want with it to manipulate
your voice do whatever we want um
in perpetuity throughout the known universe yeah
for one hundred dollars right now
okay yeah plenty of hundred dollars no
oh shit i can't scrape it together
ooh let's call the bank ooh ooh
ooh buff hello bank yeah you avoid
sons all have sorry i can hear
those two people scott ball were very
excited we need o doll gotten paul
yeah let me pull up your file
you knew but does it okay
fly just came out of my computer
oh no oh runway flying really is
a long fly with long hair just
crawl out of my computer and i
guess i'm gonna die in seven days
these stars oh shit oh gotcha you
want one hundred what now doll whoa
okay you mean doll hairs no
no don't just actual u s current
soy trying to buy you know lauren
yeah of course we're trying to buy
her likeness forever
okay i think it's worth a little
more than that it will tell her
price that she gave us okay that's
her fault but women don't know their
worth and i'm always saying boy that's
true because you want to holler yeah
people people people up hello laura oh
i'm sorry are you you get the
phone yeah okay i'll hang up high
is lauren yeah hi
this is really a bank hi bay
look i heard from your buddy and
who is it you're willing to sell
ya bike for shit a bank should
make you're willing to say likeness rami
should make dollars what's that make sorry
i just heard from scott and paul
that you were going to sell them
your likeness for one hundred dollars in
perpetuity yeah i think that's too
much and i say fifty two low
sweetie you can skip five hundred really
thousand will point million can i have
that i will give it to you
okay and i'll sign the contract with
them kind of an early norway or
because it's me make who will think
making some me make what is it
about
the gym food i got the script
idea citizen kane who's citizen game who
wants to see a movie about a
citizen aren't they all about citizens exactly
pake i gotta go clydebank i love
you people but i'm back to on
the phone with hey it's higher so
i just i mean whoa paul and
scott i'm sky you know what you
meant i just spoke
talk on the phone with her okay
i'm gonna give her five hundred thousand
point million dollars you're gonna give her
that and i'll sign the contracts with
you guys here to get her likeness
but my name is gonna be on
a stamp with my notary stamp and
we'll be all goes that a conflict
of interest you being a notary and
a bank yikes oh oh you're missing
the headline
around here which is that lawrence getting
paid we don't even have to pay
her for the likeness what so we
just own it we just own it
forever thing and we can make monies
yeah oh my gosh let's do it
what what do we want her yeah
i was detritus let me test out
the textile check you guys are gonna
just have a personal conversation
oh no i ran away but i
came back to my phone was off
the hook and i heard you were
still talking oh hey well my joke
is that your call waiting that was
me hanging out oh oh wait a
minute let's let's test out the technology
to have lauren say something really weird
okay okay type it type in something
any chance you did it easily okay
and press send and learn i'll say
it i put my foot my mouth
hey what are you guys doing oh
hi hi laura oh man wearing a
computer stuff um yeah my man's computer
my computer why did it sound like
my voice was coming out of that
computer ah we're watching what are your
videos oh you're funny funny video like
my funny video yeah so viral videos
your own for things like the latest
jurassic
ah you're pregnant right yeah yeah yeah
yeah watching your pregnancy funny funny videos
i love going viral um what did
you come to see us about so
i want to pitch a little something
oh so i recently acquired a lot
of cash and i was planning on
opening a water park and i'm wondering
if you guys wanted to be invece
esters
well let me talk to paul about
it yeah mine hanging out here for
one second i can hang out should
do what do you have any water
she obviously wants what i mean tap
oh maybe that's good enough okay let's
find out okay hey um we probably
could give you a gallon of ap
for something like one hundred thousand two
hundred thousand dollars a piece doll
dollars to hollers and water different fe
yeah forget it water mix just don't
do it behind if when i die
what she just said goodbye chung eyes
chelsea
oh my god that's so nicely hung
up on you oh my god alright
okay yeah what if we what if
we say you can use our hose
and yes we will pay the water
bill yes change for a cut of
the profits okay let's say okay hey
lauren wow
ah nightmare huh what oh where are
you dreaming just track yellow was trying
to do some crazy stuff at a
movie theater and it was like biting
into our news huh he was like
getting from the screen going like ah
what was it a vampire movie i
don't know i was like a dream
i don't care if it was a
therapy that was it was a dream
it's going away i don't even know
what
was okay it was just a dream
dream dream where she's still doing it
still should've been dreaming this whole time
and we're back hey lauren where were
you just you just fell asleep during
our freedom puck i did yeah yeah
crazy i dreamt you guys were gonna
use my likeness in perpetuity why would
we do that would be nuts yeah
we're not gonna do anything like that
no we don't know how type type
this into your computer
hey it's me lorries scuse me oh
love racism whites
are you sure didn't say reason that's
oh sorry but there's type auto correct
and always auto corrects to racism really
weird what did you think goober made
that happen
big goober goober computer technicians goober goober
computer tickets goober technion but commissions
good boring commission made this happen goober
goober if you had to eat one
movie theater candy for the rest of
your life what would it be oh
i got there's two in mind yeah
yeah
number two
milk duds
i didn't even know that moniker of
them i love milk duds wait they're
malta about their peanuts chocolate you're thinking
of whoppers johnny of whopper is what
milk duds milk duds are chocolate and
carmel and their vera i thought was
actually very true not peanuts know that
scoopers oh but then what's
a raise and that the reason that
reason is a raise was okay hold
on i never really explored all those
when i was kid i would always
get bumped to crunch and i would
get i'd get an oh yeah yeah
nestle crunch or sour candy let's look
at but nowadays are i know that's
what i would get though well also
my mother entitled to do that my
mother would sneak the candy and that
was the one oh
one christian thing she would allow her
oh chris well this isn't really viable
lotto results will do
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
doo allowed us to do new new
dilute and judging saying don't take the
cake into the movie theater oh do
do do do de gato render unto
caesar what is caesar's them that means
constanza show
upa and it was a wow christian
family he would do as he was
taking that kitty in a movie they're
doing the wrong thing that's got motto
do do you need it pump that's
on boom so that's a really good
song there's no way around that and
we
joke around a lot on here no
no we're always kidding home that's that's
a hit was it's a right that's
a yeah that's a number one with
no bowler yes that's a abused number
speaking of number one yeah junior myths
oh those are really good but you
know can't eat them i can't eat
a whole box here once i'm going
to get all your what you eat
or what you were getting
nervous when you brought stuff in the
movie theater then like so like open
your pop and you pick something you
like but they know yeah can you
thought like a police officer was yeah
come yeah a scorcher to jay my
my friend and i we did this
a few times where he would he
would buy a ticket and then open
the side door and let me in
and then that's real dirty
and then we got caught once and
they were like do you have your
ticket stubs and because he had the
one he was like oh i have
mine i was like oh i lost
mine but because we had one they
were like couldn't kick us out but
they're like we're watching you yes something
i can't figure out how this could
have worked but yeah
we never did it again though so
it did work you will have the
ticket stub you can stay
i don't even remember what movie was
but probably maybe that's actually weird he
don't remember i remember the theater i
don't remember what movie it was the
theater orange county apple six wayne a
park eight the artist guilty apple six
because it sound real it does sound
real would you guys ah stranger things
ever um i've snuck into movies i
thought wow you know the famous story
when we went to see what famous
we we said we were going to
see mr bean but we saw a
threat
dr bean sky i remember sneaking in
with a young lady to see the
um mr p we didn't we didn't
intend to sneak in but there was
nobody there at the box office whoa
just like walked in we were very
early and then we were sitting there
like we just read i guess movies
are free now everywhere and then we
we heard somebody come in and we
we like hid on the the disgusting
flaw not theater and it was worth
the tow it seemed worth it to
we were like in our early twenties
yeah yeah it seemed like we had
to do the yeah the two dollars
you are saving was important yeah yeah
oh back then it was a corner
mark but i also snuck
into a concert one time um i
got there early instead i was reviewing
it for the city paper wow what
was the concert it was the pogues
and you know you can support and
you had no relationships at the paper
none and the guy at the at
the door did
didn't care huh did not care it's
a good lie because who gives a
shit there's no way the guy believe
me he was like okay rally young
because he cared how old were you
began in my early one right yeah
and you're like hey sir i may
viewing this show for the local star
oh and he's like ah okay hello
family
have a ticket with the breaths yeah
i don't think they just give why
was it a one-off show from a
band right why would they have since
the pape why are you reviewing it
why it was good i'm sure he's
like twenty three to the pole galley
the lights went down everything was amazing
and electric at the elm
whoa that was when i discovered ah
that the pogues had a mosh pit
element to their show oh and you're
like little reporter yeah freedom of the
press ah you were embedded the little
report
ah were you pushed around it oh
yeah and i got out of it
immediately yeah you're like oh yeah i
was like yeah this is not my
seat right i'm gonna go back to
the bar oh my god wait i
just got my mom sent some old
papers to me like old ah what
kind of papers
old writings of mine oh boy ranging
from age seven to college there's just
like a variety of things in this
box could you tell which was which
yeah my writing has remained the same
since i was a child i wrote
some good stories when i was in
second grade that was my role consumed
my writing period the next
this paragraph and you'll find out like
well my my college papers i like
glanced at one and i was like
i sound smart like i was like
those were the good old days when
i would like try to use vocabulary
or something and then we got stoned
and read the papers and they're not
i mean it wasn't smart oh it's
hilarious it was like so funny i'm
clearly a great idea space yeah
i'm like i'm analyzing a poem for
eight pages on my yahoo's yeah there's
some bullshit in here i remember the
things i wrote when i was in
high school and college and they're terrible
yeah like like why do they make
you write things when you're so young
i mean you can't write brutal i
remember when we started to have to
type things yeah um when i was
in high school you could you didn't
write like right
out your essence or whatever we had
to save them and my mom my
mom had an electric typewriter and she
had different ah um fonts font heads
you know yeah it's wrong it was
like a capitals all capitals and then
the actual capital letters would be a
little bit bigger but all-caps remember a
teacher of mine had a p
problem with that yeah they're like this
is not professional yeah it's like we're
you fuck oh well a lot of
the notes on my papers were like
please see how to actually cite this
properly and i'm like i don't care
you understand how uncool you sound right
it's interesting how much i don't care
about citing this more leery or anything
really when i was an elementary they
they typed everything like
like the officials you will study show
element yeah abbott elementary oh abbott elementary
should meet this show elementary was also
over elementary abbott elementary so i'm distracted
elementary elementary and the strike i've been
ill mary's got the elementary abbott elementary
abbott elementary is
yeah yeah yeah um but they they
would send everything out in those cursive
typewriter stuff did yeah oh yeah yeah
that's that was easy that's me was
like real church bulletin yeah font yeah
it's a pretty font no one so
when you were when you changed it
out you should just pull off all
the letters and put other letters or
how did you do that
no it's like it would be like
no it's all yeah it's just impress
yeah yeah and you press a button
and the ball changes oh and it
was an electric typewriter dear it was
not i didn't know master i missed
what that meant i wasn't sitting there
in my smoking my camels my whiskey
by the by psi electric train
i actually don't think i know the
difference like when you talk went one
in but what does it do because
checked it does it for you it
has yeah you just tell it what
to type oh okay that's a tidy
cursive font somehow james joyce
it was like no actually you don't
know it is it is this ball
right so that you hit a ball
moves around and it moves around so
instead of individual keys instead of this
thing i'm reminding these forlorn instead of
these the ball has the letters on
it yes my arms on a ball
and it sends you imagine electr
local impact can and that's cute purse
yes hubert cute you essentially kubert yeah
i'm interested actually i don't i don't
know that very i'm played with one
of those well who are you tom
hanks you don't have to i like
to have a little typewriter set up
in my office with just one hundred
different typewriters that i think are cool
i would love to have the space
where i could dedicate a room
yeah to useless things but i just
like to look at i know i
told you about my friend in college
who had oh my god we all
had two bedroom apartments and he had
the mo yeah to only have one
bedroom and in the other bedroom he
had just a typewriter and a desk
for all of his poets obviously so
saying it just seemed so cool so
did he sell these poems for one
dollar
yeah like on the show we like
yeah we like it we liked that
show can you if you were to
type something in like final or not
final draft but like word or something
could you do the cursive font do
they still have anymore oh yeah anyway
yeah i like the cursive font it
was just recently i'm big into fun
we were taught i love fun really
what's your favorite font your f
f oh my god i love a
branded printed double shadow oh she's done
have you ever thought of creating a
paul f tompkins font yeah just like
based on my handwriting and it looks
like shit
no but i mean you could you
could create one that that is actually
unique i feel like trying to i
that would break my brain
let's do it so yeah why want
my pain i want your brain i
think you can do a lot your
brain brain is natural brain is fun
we were just talking i was talking
about how we're microsoft word is now
a subscription-based what gets i'm like okay
that's not fair pages yeah we use
yeah and i
i also like my computer broke that
i had funny or funny or die
final under half time huh
i used to funny or die on
i cant access to the malaysia see
the landlord v whenever i was little
left laptop because i'd play your diet
um i had found after that i
got a new computer and then i
had to like get it again because
the code didn't fucking work like this
is bull items to pay hundreds of
dollars to use this thing that fuckin
final draft code is like that is
the key to a treasure map yeah
have to protect i know but the
microsoft thing bothers me so much because
aws microsoft you have several different passwords
for different microsoft things right right or
you have to keep changing it it's
so frustrating so that i will be
doing a live show and then like
i want to access this document yeah
so i can make notes before a
show starts and then it's like that's
the wrong password i'm like well which
i can never
let's to put in for this i'm
a really what are your bets the
same as the as the fuckin you
know but x-box password yeah you know
it's like too many posts your x-box
password it is one two three four
five six seven eight nine x whoa
it'd be better if he just made
it one one one one one one
one one one cause you wouldn't have
to move them out about six nine
sixty thirty nine
nine six nine i like the x
x x i heard it for twenty
and then like the the the security
question is what's your favorite thing and
like oh yeah six nine six nine
six nine i heard a story on
another podcast called election profit makers which
is we don't talk about other podcasts
on the show wow okay alright guy
bruno
oh wait talk about podcast no no
humans shapiro quito taguba already yeah wouldn't
have movie where you why your bruno
the first thing i think is the
famous sasha baron cohen character that everyone
loves it was a podcast toast about
to wipe everybody narrative day one million
and time we have to take a
break when we come back we'll hear
about this podcast if you'd like to
know more contar
venue listening okay
and we're back and paul before we
left was going to tell us about
another podcast yes you could be listening
to instead or you could listen to
paul talk about behind a paywall though
oh okay and you are willing to
pay i'm willing to pay these are
these friends of mine they're very funny
david reese and john kimble
a joke election profit makers and david
was telling a story about some job
that he had where there was some
piece of equipment or technology that required
a password the guy that knew the
password left you left the job and
then david i think took over the
job and he had to get in
the city couldn't find the password and
he had to write to the guy
and say hey what's the password for
this thing and the password was six
oh wow that's so funny to have
to say yeah i thought your eddy
said the guy had no like it's
you know like ah but it's like
he was just like joe scx ah
that's so dumb
i mean good idea great idea yes
well you're always thinking about alright over
again our house wi-fi password your housewife
eyes wi-fi our house wi-fi now you're
just looking for holes here like it
i yell
i've held it up crazy place but
it's it's fart fart which makes us
laugh and we always like when it's
a friend it always makes us laugh
to say but then when like me
or or someone i work with astrocyte
over the phone to a technician yeah
i always tried to disguise it by
saying okay it's ah f a r
t f a
and then usually they'll type it in
and go huh
yeah you guys are foot you know
what i'm not gonna charge you a
thousand dollars r t f r a
u s h e r r a
y m o o g f f
a r t h c yeah yeah
i'd like everyone to do is try
my cup of coffee spoons napkins
ah does yes if you're driving i
don't know it's funny if he does
that is funny it would be if
he did but i don't know he
did i don't know if he did
if only did a dummy season four
hours for fifty five napkins was advising
god joe pesci because sinead died there's
a lot of ah
articles about japan
well he comes up a lot because
why it really was the host the
following week of snow like i was
yeah what if i was i wanna
smack the i have i have to
admit something i've read five of those
articles i don't know why but i've
read it as joe pisco each time
and i've just been imagining job but
prob
probably because because he played frank sinatra
because it's always an alibi not true
sinatra also said this and i i
guess i've been conflating the whole time
frank sinatra said something about him yeah
he was like i would've slapped her
whatever the hell's wrong with you i
know what do you care i know
i know i hate everyone just loved
the po and they loved the catholic
re lower lapping women i was praying
for you passed out praying for you
love so much well years later it
came to pass
you always pray about the pope i
hear you every night i do always
pray about the pope yeah but paul
tells tell the story please of what
happened two nights ago was it when
you were talking absolutely yeah talking in
your sleep i hear the secrets that
you i very rarely talk in my
sleep but it has happened to a
handful of times over the years and
every
it happens i'm not like somebody that
talks to my sleep like mumbles and
then i continue don't say your passwords
in your sleep do you zach sex
success x x x x he's talking
to his password was password so type
it in reader's e-mail going to bank
dot com immediately sex three is just
three letters
your whole patchy yeah for everything it's
like it says you need more and
you're like nope trust me you put
zach you figure it if you put
sex the computer goes that one works
yeah by the way what is getting
to confess to confusing with everything you
have to add to passwords now right
it's too much too much like you've
got to put this in you go
to and now i'm used to it
now
no but see here's the thing i
feel like i started using like google's
like hard strong packs just now using
google oh my god and i let
them do the password because and i
save it or something because i'm but
a lot of what i used to
write them all down because i always
put my password and then i started
doing that i'm like lol just let
the comps
i don't remember but then my computer
died and how did you get this
on the new computer it doesn't remember
it didn't remove like if i did
that that usually remembers yeah not all
order or whatever i have had and
saved on the website was to remember
website exactly remember in the cloud but
then like if it remembers it in
chrome right then it won't know so
remember on your phone xy o n
anyway it's a nightmare for me personally
i don't want to speak and i
struggle i struggle with passwords and michael
speak them annoying because i don't know
what they are for anything okay the
end what i like to i i'm
into like the special characters and all
that stuff because i come up with
the little phrase or something for php
places that i use a lot yeah
so that i can remember them yeah
okay and so i'll type that out
using the characters and all that shit
replacing letters with numbers sorry for ya
and so i have like a certain
system that i use and shows just
incumbent upon me to remember the phrase
some of them like microsoft which i've
had to change so many times ah
it will it will feature
her like um an expression of rage
at the website
it will feature an express your your
password is like how upset you'll you're
like yes a shit website yeah exactly
yeah you should shit website that describes
my penis there was one i think
like sa twitter there was like it
was like for cbs or something like
that where the password and i remember
i had to like go into my
past
awards and show it in everything and
the password was pleased god
yeah my mom does a unique password
for every single thing and it's something
unique to that so if it's like
instagram which i don't think she has
but it'll be like we love to
take pictures nineteen haha twenty twenty three
or whatever that far from what i
do but she she can't remember any
of them so she has to write
them down in a notebook
and like i've seen her do this
like flip through the pages of the
notebook know this i have that i
have that notebook i have that fucking
passport number and then i misplace it
and then i go i can't find
my notebook and then whenever i change
the password so like i can't buy
the notebooks and i'll just make a
new password then i don't write it
in the notebook then the notebooks useless
it's like it's us it's a samui
notebook should be
yeah if this isn't a thing that
we which is in my home regular
issues does the notebook have a special
place where it's supposed to go now
that's what you need to hear right
i need a notebook place your right
okay look always goes here that's a
good idea underneath under nina with a
notebook needs a really good pencil
with a good eraser attached because it
never has a pen and i got
fucking then or yeah exactly there you
go it's a real nightmare or zero
if you're buying something for lauren for
christmas it's this notebook and a pen
and it's attached yeah i already have
it and a safe
but you need the little pencil i
got a pencil i just need a
bunch of take hey golf pencils those
have erasers motherfucker here's a question i
need a pencil with a really good
eraser wonder i picked pink girl i
have a pencil that has an older
reason it's like basically rubbing a piece
of plastic dome in yeah why don't
you take pictures of
of the all the pages and then
you'll have a backup because danny goes
to the cloud and so i'm gonna
hold glenn see it but then by
then all your websites will be hacked
anyway i don't you instead of taking
a photograph draw the page without the
password oh okay yeah to poster into
wallpaper and just hang all your passwords
are hidden in wallpaper over the whole
sapere with your hidden path
passwords yeah it looks like paisleys do
people out there struggle with this i
wanna know tell me in the heroes
fun okay now of course they do
yeah and if they don't fuck you
yeah yeah here's my story yeah sabbah
true oh no about a girl that
i would
so far so good um so when
i do talk in my sleep which
is very rare i don't i will
talk at conversational volume and i will
wake myself up wow and so i'm
waking up hearing myself say the the
sentence and it's jarring and weird and
so the other night
i i awoke both janie and myself
up saying this executive like this his
they will jesus christ ed everybody loved
him except the rover
ah crazy i was dreaming when i
was doing an andrew lloyd webber bit
for somebody and that was the end
of the bit and i don't what
makes your brain do this i don't
know it's me say it that loud
so funny that i it's it's an
actual funny it's yours yeah like how
is that i feel like i've had
dreams where i say something really funny
and i'm like laughing i'm like that
was so funny and i laughed to
my sleeper bunk yeah yeah yeah but
i don't remember usually i've had girlfriends
tell me that i laugh in my
sleep you've had six se yes we
just live together so they laugh during
sex and you love when you fall
asleep that's right i laughed thinking about
them laugh
but when i saw i asked so
this girlfriend i had told me that
i left my sleep i said what
did it what does it sound like
and schilling she said
oh jeez yeah this is horrible oh
my god this oof oh me i
woke myself up laughing though like like
full on laughing yeah that's fun it
is wonderful yeah so disorient it's still
sleep now okay i am sure sure
sure
my name's paula pumpkin wait what did
i just say ah yeah i think
i was talking i just woke myself
up what did i just say you
didn't say anything i heard oh i
heard paul say his name was paul
f tompkins when i was asleep that's
what i guys i pretended to be
asleep i wasn't really asleep what in
lauren you said i'm
my name is paul f tompkins that's
to what end why got you just
said snores i said snore snore snore
snore yeah
oh i think i was dreaming about
snoring so i was saying snores nor
snore imagine snow or snow are so
high again how do you like this
noise yes na
i do do you yeah regularly ah
from the river swilling yeah squeaks ah
no i think i at most will
go like ah every once in a
while yeah when i was pregnant i
was not really bad wow amy you
always say that was the big i
think it was do you
think it's going to come back more
and yeah back inside and then like
it's just everything was pressed up on
everything you know i slay i don't
snore often but i go i will
go through like a phase of snoring
for like a few weeks or something
yeah you're just like yeah i'm ok
yeah she doesn't
january like he's just going through a
phase she's still like her she's calling
people obama sleep saying good luck if
you hear pulsing he's just going through
a phase you just want more little
things he does from time to time
my older brother used to snore like
great we shared a room and eastern
or like gray really it was brutal
that's really annoying and i had a
friend stay over my house snore
ord so loudly it was hilarious you
could hear it in the get from
the yep wow yeah yeah yeah storage
i mean you can't help it so
why do we have it oh my
god one time what's it doing for
my friend evolution doesn't exist because well
obviously if it did we would eliminate
snoring all
although or is it something to scare
away animals
that's probably what it is what about
your rose good friend what is zipper
the fame rapper dipper big dep where
not the constellation we yeah we grew
up together and we um in high
school we were having a coed sleepover
with a bunch of theater kids it
was like one big room and my
friend's house and we were sleeping on
the floor and he was snoring so
loud and i
i reached over and slapped him on
the chest really hard because i wasn't
eighty a teenager you know just want
like yeah and it hurt him so
bad he was like oh wow
i hope it was like oh i'm
so sorry i didn't know what i
was doing you know like i was
just like it's a thing of like
we were just like you know you
think you didn't realize your own strength
yeah because are waking up out of
sleep i didn't think i was going
to hurt him yeah it was wrong
just like stop and then like he
was like that actually really hurt you
hit him like a fucking snooze alarm
yeah ahead
feels to this day yeah he's really
upset with me we've i tried to
get him to talk about it over
and over and over no so i
had a i had a woman that
i lived with that snored pretty hell
woman that you will live with your
if you know what i'm talking about
you blinked her alive poly and it
was it was definitely one of those
things
where it was like waking me up
in the night that that's how loud
it was yeah and it would you
know be like just kind of like
yeah shah ver a shake or whatever
well like mike has a really hard
time falling asleep so whenever he snores
i don't want to because he's too
tired because loves to play yeah yeah
yeah but i just don't want to
ruin the sleep that he's gonna wake
him up out of
it even momento told me to do
he'll have a hard time going back
to sleep um yeah call you you
come over yeah and a whispering space
they'll be really excited whispering his face
hey mark
if he just woke up and saw
you doing that it would be weird
will let's plan that okay as a
surprise that when going to sleep next
tonight um to bhopal are you free
tonight by god no plans
oh my god no plan i was
in my twenties living downtown philadelphia i
had a some roommates hats in the
belfry etc etc etc
what was the one that ah the
woman across boys for tots hold on
i want i didn't remember i got
a matter of eight for the next
anyway not obvious is the problem okay
isn't a choice it is about to
its toys for boys was about bids
it implies a certain type of toy
and it's an expression that's not really
a
common expression top like a spinning top
no
toy time do you think toy time
implies toys yeah i like toy store
acid i'd be like i think they
might tell toys to be think of
toys that implies toys
ib i've been very toys um jacks
in the bell oh wait what's a
jack in the box checks at the
belfry know what's the toy second case
the toy it doesn't apply specific toy
but a type of toy type toy
wooden blocks blocks legos
his lego awesome
subsidy whatever i'm like i wanna say
it la um what chemicals are a
toy yeah and type of okay okay
um the brand um spheres
balls ball dees dina dolls toys dot
corn
ah come on come on oh hey
wow what does the star with the
vo hey this good boy what letter
does it start with it doesn't it's
not a real toy oh my god
it's not a specific toy the gate
is a genre games people refers to
a genre of toy
oh what marry mortals we be oh
my god just get up and just
sell me one more thing
what is this what is the name
i'm sure oh i'll take is that
what you want yeah yeah okay gone
forever the last wound up that's horrible
yeah terrible it is terrible and this
and this woman worked there oh my
god i remember i sent you this
woman worsening guy how dare she the
one that i sent you like that
like one of those names yeah where
i was like is this what this
is supposed to be
yeah it's the okay so it's the
word darren texas a business the other
day the word double dash o letter
o salon double low salon smaller than
say zappos heroin double o soul the
untouchable song yeah but you do
think it's double o seven yeah yes
double o sal double o spelled out
yeah salon the only way this makes
sense as if it's like at an
address like www something like double o
seven i doubt it is because i
feel like i feel like that's not
an excuse for you to pick up
your
phone no it's on it's not it's
not a that's not the address okay
so double or maybe oh what if
the person who owns it has two
o's in their name like it's oprah
humphrey
who open three
can you think of another name that
starts with own free olive okay how
about one that's all of who live
a little more calm and caught more
common than olive is getting common but
let's common oh no that sorts of
the sea amen
aman on tooting common too
dar jim coleman dude and two-toned on
whenever i hear a reference to common
i think of him saying look around
from that one commercial from a commercial
okay that's didn't need he was in
some disney win an academy award for
a song where he's just like this
sucks yeah oh wait you did something
like
but you did something at the last
wound up and then what happened because
we just got distracted behave of the
name yeah yeah i wasn't telling the
story of years wow know you were
doing
i just worked you're telling a story
about when you were so living in
phil yeah had a bunch of roommates
and we would like we hung out
all the time we drank beer all
the time hey um and so when
i were up listening to music and
going wow perfect family in the most
recent thing family
we listen to this song dean lou
that's when twin hi raisa yeah
it's nothing i'm sorry said
i'm obsessing how i keep doing what
we say i think our scent when
i first saw you i just figured
that was the song that you were
listening to is like that if that
sounded like what it was like no
sounds closer what scott was doing so
what is it like a family man
mer man ran every new new new
email me anyway because we're closer than
you know it's been you know amp
it was the song roadhouse blues by
the band the doors oh i love
your eyes on the road my favorite
band of all time keep rising already
heads up on the wheel and so
we're listening that we're all drunk and
i say to my friend sean boyfriend
roommate i say tomorrow want you to
ah wake me up before you with
this song
yeah
and of course i forgot all about
great and the next morning ah i'm
awoken by the loud sounds of the
song and i wake up to see
the bottom of a beer bottle right
in my face yeah and did you
have any idea do you know what
the smell was so mad he was
like you told me to do this
i was like wow
wow i guess you got me there
and did you remember telling him to
do it yeah when he's when he
said that oh okay right and just
drink the beer does that song i
don't think drink the beer probably sure
that door's song doesn't go like this
whole lifeless yeah and
slightly related to take a break
we're back we're back and this is
freedom by the way i'm paul my
name is lauren i forgot who i
am now you'll figure it out really
by the end yep absolutely i know
you will okay it's i feel like
it starts with a w recently on
your dream what what what yeah
yes recently on his podcast you heard
his name are you gonna throw the
garth rock
yuko throb how are you i'm gore
through my name is dorothy up and
i'd like to borrow my name is
better too
on scott hasn't seen you are trying
to place the phrase
i visited you could i knew that
you could from what from billy crystal
crystal wait i was trying to place
it what was how you were like
i can't why i can't remember where
this comes from what was it was
his of course is jasmine character yeah
no i know everything about the billy
crystal theme but why were we talking
about the phrase i knew that you
could i don't fucking know
dude that's not the important part of
the story because i know when my
parents fight the funny part is the
mini you said i knew that you
could i would obey yeah and we
cant remember the that's right i think
so strange interest was like he's gotta
know this is can you dig it
i knew that you could well next
time text me while i'm doing the
episode
one thing yeah yes oh no oh
no laura are trapped in a jar
fucking sanders damn i could hear punch
some holes in the top of the
jar so she can breathe i'm trapped
in a jar i just wanted to
say we should hear some listener voicemails
i know somebody else who used to
be able to do that thing oh
really your mouse yes then they were
arrested for their participation in the january
six uprising oh
it wasn't like right after oh right
alright i never really tried to save
money many different things like that it's
really good translate every word would you
always say the same thing i want
to think
that's great if you could see lauren
right now i'll post a video she's
doing she's drooling like a maniac yeah
there's not there's a street you're not
dumbing down and knows it's not it's
coming down why is that in there
jethro tull please what that part of
the song
yeah why did you put that shit
on ginny
young is not a bad selection of
something apart
i know i've brought enough dbt cbt
infused gummy
here we go these are weird to
play voicemails yeah because know like if
you'd like to call us ask us
for advice it gives a conversational prompt
you can call us that high claims
eight this is katie it's great this
is kate from minneapolis minnesota i'm wondering
again what's allowed time you are so
hungry you had to eat
something like a monster and went on
a long bike ride once and we
stopped to get bacon cheeseburgers and multe
and i ate them so fast rarely
see oh my god i on a
long bike ride my yeah and you
just diarrhea the whole way home i
would like if i did that i
would lay down for a week yeah
i'd live in the park sleeping every
grade
it yeah um i will say this
speaking of eating like a monster first
of all i do that everyday lot
i eat very three times a day
i eat very fast i eat fast
too i'm always done before janie for
anyone i know it's kind of embarrassing
a lot of times i hear people
talk about it and they say like
oh that's because i grew up in
a large family and you were always
worried that people were gonna take no
that didn't have
to me i just eat yes why
do you eat fast i don't know
do you think it was a large
family i always assumed that but maybe
not maybe i just wanted to get
done with dinner so i could watch
tv yeah i used to have like
my parents would not let me watch
tv until like all the peas are
all the spinach or something were done
and i remember there were
quite a few nights where i just
sat there for an hour and i
know like wonderful world of disney in
the other and me just sitting there
crying and going i don't want to
eat it i would have that to
about like a cold meat ball on
my plate i'm like no i would
love a cold meatball right never was
yeah alright but you know i actually
do love called me a pediatrician just
told me about something
ing what i don't know if this
is like a common thing like way
to describe this with kids eating but
it's she said you provide the what
and the when ah like like of
the food fucked what food will be
and when you'll be served and the
kid provides the weather and the how
much whether they will eat it at
all and how much they
needed if they don't eat it you
move along and then they'll be hungry
she said when the kids are hungry
they eat so she'll be fine i'm
like because i definitely get into a
bartering system with like if you give
you these fine lines and i'll do
this no laurie i know is not
awful schnell she's in charge he up
she bosses me around
she made you do this podcast yeah
sure i'm going to quit yeah but
really loves the show um i remember
being at a friend's house and his
stepfather made me not the stepfather no
thank oh no he this guy was
a superhero he was just an asshole
um i they serve baked beans i've
always had a big means i do
to this day make youtube thrill just
roll just a musical fruit
and i would not i didn't want
to eat them and he said you
have to sit there until oh that's
nice someone who wasn't your parents wasn't
even my friends' parents oh my lord
that's crazy this guy was a true
asshole and a mania he was a
real asshole and his mother ah my
friend's mother eventually did divorce him and
then found this great for that for
what he did with the big enough
of those happening you don't cross my
son's friend
i'm trying to do the last time
i ate like a monster do you
have a story
just every day i mean every day
i go to bed feeling bad
yeah it does check out this one
thing that i cannot help but you'd
like a monsters popcorn i can't eat
popcorn not make a mess yeah and
i don't i feel like i get
that taste of it and i just
want that salt yeah it tastes so
good i can let himself down i
love it so much wow yeah do
you think it'll kill me oh
i mean if you're a slug if
i just if i lean back open
oh i thought you just dissolve boring
shake it was really good so being
able to breathe you choke on it
will be able to swallow you die
oh my god it's like let's try
videos of people doing that the cinnamon
challenge so good it's so good it's
so and they always think they can
do they always go wow i know
there's this
guy what is you eat like a
spoonful of cinnamon powder yeah and then
like you just heard it close your
mouth but then people will look like
spit can't fly why can't you do
it you just can't swallow too much
just crazy i could do it all
right let's go get it okay here
oh my god oh god eater yeah
um what about yeah yeah i don't
have any so i don't really have
a crazy one i feel like i
just saw hers wasn't crazy she like
wow right nate a couple of shoes
but i mean nothing standing out to
me as like a time where i
was like i had to scarf down
a ton of it i feel like
you know if i get home from
a long drive i'm like i gotta
just eat something i was in the
desert for you know without any food
or water with horse was named yeah
that's right
right yeah oh i need to buy
the oh that's the least you could
do here's what i like about the
desert you can remember your name yeah
and the reason is very simple there
ain't no one for to give you
no pay
that makes so much wonderful yeah okay
this is from wonderful i will say
also restaurants if it's like one of
those shared plate things which everything is
now yeah thomas it's always more dined
with us before it's always too much
for stock you're gonna tell me about
topics i don't know i've been going
to a place lately which i'm not
going to name here that
that is the top of style and
it's like a perfect amount every time
i have to say everyone gets a
bite on everyone gets a little yeah
i'm okay right before we went to
into the woods we went to a
really nice restaurant which i can't remember
the name of an r and r
we had a we had a waiter
who was receiver who was very like
businesslike and we liked it it was
obviously a character
he was putting on a voice in
a way like of like oh i'm
mister professional you know but we like
to enjoy that amount okay so like
did you clean please help you so
much with what you are looking to
order let me tell you about our
restaurant you know just like very businesslike
but i'll tell you we asked like
what the good amount was any any
took it veg
very seriously and calculated in his head
and was like well i think this
is the right amount and it was
perfect wow she every time we do
that here's what i feel like happens
every time they want you to order
more because to boost their chair weight
yes and it's because like way too
much food and also the prices are
not reflecting sharing prices yeah that's right
proper individu
jewel entrees top like the menu and
go everything thing that we want everything
so cheap here oh guess what you
have to order eighteen things get the
fuck out hey yeah but anytime so
we'll we'll you know you have to
have a long discussion with the rest
of your table like how should you
like this there's like yeah you finally
reach a consensus and you'd say we're
gonna have one of the
one of these one of these and
then somebody always say is that enough
and then the several go i get
like two more things they do that
yeah but i feel like my like
why don't we get all of that
and i will add if we need
more yeah well exactly yeah so you
know if they're nice they'll say you
can always get more if you want
yeah but you know what they do
they take the menus away
yeah i mean if and then you
then you're lying everything oh yes oh
if i want more i don't know
do you a birthday cake and they
won't give it back to either yeah
they're like oh so now you want
some more yeah even though i told
you you should've gotten two more things
yeah alright this next one i felt
this is bad hi guys this has
been i'm a pacific from michigan i
am a moon
adult roughly docker right now i was
just wondering what law you guys enjoy
or were you best at if anything
grown up okay cool let me bite
what did we enjoy or what were
we best at so if you're really
good at something that implies you don't
enjoy i was great football but i
didn't like i had to quit before
i got drafted yeah i out the
draft the nfl draft is even if
you don't want to do it they
draft yeah if you are actively playing
football that's it oh my god
i liked i like playing basketball i'm
not good at it but i like
it it's fun lauren has just sank
three threes while she said that other
guys thanks to my chair like losing
conferences talking about it um but i'd
ever was good at sports group i
never never wanted to play sports i
was on the basketball team in fifth
grade and then that was it and
then i did the
course the women's comedy basketball lee horse
here which i was briefly tell my
doctor told me my jaw would break
if i hit it with basketball because
i got my wisdom teeth removed in
my thirty or no twenties and they
were holding everything together and it was
a very thin bone in my jaw
when they took them out and then
he was like you got hit in
the face of the basket
you could break your jaw and i
was like well i already have been
so i probably shouldn't do this she
says well which team were you on
the kimi drillers
i used to like when i would
say for the first ten years of
me doing comedy it felt like every
three months every like you'd hear word
like hey we're gonna go down to
the park and do kickball and then
like everyone would show up yeah like
nick's words and would come like everyone
involves fun i feel like i remember
that happening in new york but i
don't remember hearing
about it so much one last thing
about my teeth make it make sense
yes because i waited making any man
he's removed they'd grown into the bone
oh yeah that's why oh no yeah
oh nah nah no no no no
well what if we did a kickball
team already out of it
i'm busy
the fish with the pitbull no problem
yeah well good about ah i feel
like the last time i did it
i know dave ferguson was there birthday
boy and i was and i was
playing first base and he gave me
pointers and i felt embarrassed because i
was a forty year old man and
he was giving me like like all
he's like oh yeah he's like ok
when you play first base you should
probably like you
no keep one foot on the bay
like it was kind of what you
should know well it's like i'm a
forty year old man and i not
that i plan virgin and virgin and
he gave me forty year old virgin
it's really interesting combo to keep your
foot on it i was not getting
married you were married for thirty to
forty
yeah i was not good at sports
i was on thirty eight baby i
was on the baseball team in eighth
grade um i don't think i ever
even swung at a ball at the
plate much less got a hit um
and i played right field and had
a perfect fielding record the one ball
that was hit to me i caught
a wise yes but i was good
at i was good at game
games games like running bases or flashlight
tag or things like that oh right
i was good at stuff like that
i was on literally obviously i've told
you that obviously you know played right
played right field because i was so
bad boy big ah you know line
drive right into my balls and my
cup i don't remember that store okay
i'm
wrong last grateful to hear it ever
left anytime and i've always they would
only allow me to check swing i
couldn't really swing what's generally allow you
to check swing my coach because he
was like well you can't you obviously
can't hit it just do a light
just do it it's basically like doing
a bunch whatever and so anytime i'd
come to the plate everyone would go
everyone move up
don't move up wow she's just a
masculine but once i hit a triple
and it was just dang nice work
and everyone was like we went into
gloomy i gave you the wrong advice
everyone moved back but no that's too
far back you're out of the stadium
someone find that ball and they weren't
yelling they were just talking like this
seems like a common theory yes
just come to me like people are
not afraid to not spare your feelings
oh totally ya just say the thing
outright oh i don't know whether i'm
overly sensitive or just whether you know
and just remembering like perceived slights but
i don't think so
yeah well you're not very good i
think now i think kids were babbitt
genuinely like not willing to well kids
suck of course kids will tell you
but i'm not adults know my i'm
like well that wasn't very good i'd
mean coaching well yeah i mean coaches
in little league like the town asshole
wow was my coach
he stands in the middle of the
town square just been like i'm an
ass so what do you want me
to do ye hear ye fuck you
and everyone's like you wanna be the
little league coaches like sure i'm not
busy bitch i remember he oh you
lived around the corner from the church
we went to and we would have
to pass this house every sunday and
i would like look at the house
and go like i hope i don't
see him yeah
that is such a while you hear
into his house i hope i don't
see him i hope i don't say
oh shit we passed them you mean
person's houses such a thing now yeah
it's such a visceral feeling i've been
reading old nancy comics from the fifties
just like the new ones are great
new ones are great they are actually
oh my good olivia james doe they're
great way right now
now paul but ah i was roasting
him and then i thusly was roasted
i rose
i expected to go that way it's
just so funny like all the things
that were important in the fifties that
aren't important anymore there's like so many
strips about people looking through a knothole
at a baseball game so you have
to pay for it and then like
and then like reading re they always
shout at baseball games
go robert robert robert robber to the
blacks to the proper yeah robert robert
robber because that's like it's it's in
so many of the strips that it's
gone and he's stealing it means like
you about all yeah bad call robert
robert rubber and it just people going
robert robert robber let's bring it back
yeah the word robber isn't used very
much no it's no because people yeah
it's like thief burglar do you know
what killed it cops and robertson's yeah
that movie your not a cop you're
a robertson
that's a line in it but we
used to say that all the time
it's a good well no okay the
trailer cops and robbers since what is
that it's a chevy chase movie jack
jackson changes and he he pulls chevy
chase close to me you are not
a cop and then we would always
say because we saw this trailer so
many times we would always say you
are a robber so
what was the plot of cups and
robertsons i think they were under they
had to be undercover in like jam
well sort of yeah probably yeah it
was the robertsons who knows chevy's thought
he was a cop just because of
his proximity to cops he was like
i'm like he knew he was roberson
i'll tell you that much he knew
he was ok here's this is colette
here we go and go collette ongoing
freedom gang collector fabulous aka cincinnati here
wow
my tag is defined in the dictionary
as a wish especially one in the
form of an ugly old woman that
special would you rather claim one hag
or have eight hags claim you okay
by now this is real topic week
oh god
oh topic we haven't gotten into we
haven't gotten into this topic yet about
whether we would rather have one hack
claim us or we haven't explored this
i know so i think it's really
clever question we talk about this on
a preview i think i totally worry
about when i claim to hang but
if i had you'll know but
ah whatever other claim a haggar have
eight hands claim me no i don't
want to hack running around in my
kitchen but if you're claimed by eight
eggs you don't have a kitchen you're
american with that
i i kind of think i would
like eight hags to claim me yeah
what are they going to do with
you maybe they'll make me a hag
yeah right they'll make you ah hey
i guess i'd rather be claimed by
eight hags and have everyone's write your
name one i don't yeah and i'll
make you high i think i'd rather
be claimed by eight hansen clay
im one hag because who knows they
might claim you for a fun purpose
yeah they were maybe a maternity test
oh there is the idea of a
hag running around your house like hey
that's like scare time yeah and you
have to claim them it's fun for
the first twelve oh wait are we
saying that if you claim the hag
then the hag is running around your
oh yeah for wasting the hag
i is running my house you have
to claim them well if i claim
her i want to control you're responsible
for so i think i'd like to
put her in like an aid not
just reached er yeah yeah yeah put
her in like a little house in
the back yeah and then i'd like
to buy her an apartment also i
want to treat her right like hey
she's my ma disrespected i they i
want to get her a hair
blow out every week every week and
only want to make a blow out
jonathan loudly and john remember
did you ever watch his realities you
know john ho jonathan his his his
gcn oh wait that his sister his
sister created the pussy yes that guy
did watch that shit a reality show
and it was so funny and it
was called blow out right now is
called blow out that's right and and
this is back when reality tv was
still new so you'd watch anything yeah
valley yeah and it was all just
and blow out everyone in in beverly
hills and meanwhile he has a line
of like hair goop yeah and and
wait let me look up who that
says i just remember him calling his
mom and crying and going like mo
mo we got into so far
guide is a four oh yeah jonathan
antin okay but yeah that's remember this
oh my god goop it's a forum
ah that's amazing so with us i
hope so so much it seems like
you're saying i forgot all about that
show i watched every episode i know
why amy and i started watching vanderpump
rules from the beginning whoa i watched
this season let's get everyone tells me
to do but i'm just like we
had friends telling us like this will
be an enriching experience for you interesting
he is a bit coy w i
forgot about that that's a bitcoin can't
wait to get to it i know
in the open in the first episode
we do see a man shave his
foot
airhead which i've never seen oh yeah
i mean support everyone who does whatever
they do yeah whatever you need to
do to feel good about your never
i mean i've never heard of that
i didn't know is necessary i also
think waxing feels like would be more
effective in that situation yeah you should
give consultation about okay i've been watching
laser it's i've muttered every once in
a while
cool up and i take lasers my
tyler perry
cool up and i take turns ah
feeding at night after the bathtime we'd
take turns feeding and reading the story
and putting to bed right and what
you said about your dogs that you
left so sometimes like cool dad a
key word i know right so i
thought you cl take turns giving each
other each other's math and reading stories
okay cool i was sure the worst
of times would it be would you
like to have someone read you a
short story yeah why not if i
wouldn't mind someone literally tucked me into
bed and i'm all cosy and warm
and like put a nice rack on
my head and ray that my mom
made me read her the stories because
i was such a good reader that
she was like
if you read the story sounds like
a trick and you're really john krishna
yeah he killed her down and attacked
her yeah it was forcible rape if
they made ah a grownup story that
was the length of a children's book
yeah that's a smart idea yeah it's
like you read to me and this
is like great interesting
but anyway so let's see what colors
recently recently every time she has to
do it she'll come downstairs i'm watching
dr pimple popper do you're watching yes
that's just for women why women seem
ah like this is just my experience
that women seem to be more in
shares
gender well you like watching it's not
gender by the way the big issue
of course is that it's often not
pimples it's gigantic rosiest scenarios yeah so
am i every pimple it should be
i'd like to see once in a
while a pimp just a pimple just
want just like your simple just really
a really bad one and you go
in and it's like oh that'll go
away and like two days yeah pop
it honey yeah know what you gotta
do you
gotta watch doctor says crutcher because that
guy squeezes little people see i was
gonna oh he's squeezing symbol does that
say dr simple pimple who just does
pimp doctor several years pimples and not
big ones either the tiny just little
blackheads that's so gross why don't you
go fuck yourself yeah
just every kind of just every comment
to say pimples plea yeah can they
see pimp ambos because these growths that
are out of control while guys were
out i'm right thank you to everyone
who called in we love you all
um if you would like to call
us of course hag claims eight or
i claim one
i mag i want um and if
you or you claim when i get
it yeah i know i was confused
so um but if you'd like to
re who cares if you'd like to
write to us three m usa gmail
dot com we are three usa on
all the socials and if you'd like
to listen to ad-free versions of this
why don't you get the
the two cb world dot ca yes
and i think i still
yeah i think i still have a
show in two days yeah it hasn't
been cancelled august august nineteen maybe it
is august nineteenth at dynasty typewriter doing
a live scott hasn't seen about mamma
mia here we go again rowdy screening
and anything goes at the screening i
mean like you're also going to show
anything goes basically yeah we're also doing
that so it's
long night but also we contacted the
police department and they said like whatever
happens in there we're not gonna prosecute
okay does anybody do run free screenings
of plays
crowd to play you can yell and
scream yes rowdy screening a term yeah
oh yeah yeah i don't if you
just set it to make it show
like we can say whatever you want
dude everyone i mean it's a term
that sean said i'm assuming is yeah
i think it's become a thing in
the last handful of years yeah i
feel like i first heard about it
with cats i think oh yea yeah
it sounds
really fun will come by one should
go alright maybe we'll um also fy
just five days later dynasty typewriter ah
super ego forgotten classics me matt gourley
jeremy carter mark mcconville and james bladen
we will be improvising a book that
none of us we promise has ever
read um we take the first the
first line bassline that you
you read it like you speed read
it right before once you decide it
yeah because you really noticed my pulse
range yeah because then after there is
there are prizes for most yeah most
places to most close to most most
closer to the sources yeah um and
that will be a dynasty typewriter will
be live and live streamed ah tickets
go to paul f tompkins dot com
slash live also september tenth mean nicole
parker at lodge room in highland park
that you will not be livestream because
of bad wi-fi in the venue but
that is gonna be fun show me
nicole doing a variety show two person
variety show for the first time with
a full band sketches music all that
shit it's gonna be great amazing yeah
and i don't know what my
shows go to my instagram by goodbye
bitch the next day
uh