further
motion
um this this so called freedom this
is a co-creator this isn't to show
code three dumb lady i'm in awe
but it is it is i know
that alien came to try it again
alright races show called freedom this is
a joke update um some other show
is
called three don oh my fuck wrong
with you stab it
do do to to to stop it
kill it that would be funny shoot
it in like ah to do like
a movie a version of julius caesar
with ah yeah yeah where everybody has
abrupt yeah
a production of julius caesar faithful to
the original show everyone here is so
and so he had to sell him
because it said stabbing yes and before
any big speech famous speech the character
has to do bobby yeah yeah a
little bit yeah avi immortal bard yeah
yeah cushioning for live to see poppin
oh my god
guys he never knew we could play
a game like that no what do
you think shakespeare would think of bob
but do you think he would like
my favourite whole poem about it a
sonnet a poem just pong yeah just
a little roses red pop it is
just a whole song just a little
sum sum what do you think he
like i want to be the last
person to ever live but you gotta
because i want to know about everything
that's been invented but do you guys
think shit everyone's actually real because i'm
gonna have to give you a real
lesson in history you think that he
was cg a bunch of people i
was a server all women and they
were all scarecrow yeah and they were
stuffed with newspapers i heard
women stuff with newspapers who put a
scarecrow in the front yard and yeah
this is shakespeare yeah and then they
would listen at the door and people
wanted to talk to shakespeare and ask
questions like would you write me a
play yeah sure they would write those
questions down put them in play yes
and then behind the be like sure
yeah sure romeo and there was like
thanks shakespeare have you been to the
globe
theater i have been to the no
i haven't been our men i've never
been in the globe i feel like
it but you've been to london i
have but i've never seen france to
write oh yeah guess what else i've
seen oh boy no way not this
again yeah dirty dogs i fell v
is the is the globe something you
should go to if
twice yeah i know you could do
well i really love to i've been
on the tour multiple time really why
multiple times says i've gone multiple times
and then people want to go and
it's like different people and different things
and it's not in the other you
know when but i'm i'm remembering this
out i meant to go to the
globe theatre but i went to the
glob theatre oh no okay because i
went to the
goober theater and that was real sticky
yeah yeah yeah
okay janie has been to the globe
she saw i believe i play mark
rylance in otello wow i never saw
a show there and she got yelled
at for taking a picture before the
show oh really i'm sure yeah she
explained the last longer
yeah did you choose been like if
i take a picture my mind i'll
forget it yeah exactly when we saw
springsteen on broadway there's a big thing
about no picture no you know do
not take out your phones and take
pictures we are in the front row
and it was i was so like
oh man i wish i could take
a picture and then everyone in the
world has taken pictures the entire time
but i was a good little boy
you know
m p there's some controlling people with
these cell phones yeah
you know i said lock them up
when they entered the place i say
lock lock him up lock actually really
luck they did that to see i
really don't approve of that like when
like a yarn pursuing something or whatever
then they put it in a sock
so whatever show recently they did it
and it was like i kept reaching
for it i don't think it's fair
to not have it yeah that's my
because what if my axe
as to everything yeah so what if
what if i start choking and needed
emergency assistance yeah you can't tell anyone
around you i'm not a big fan
of phones during the show but i
don't want to lock people's phones i
just think of course you shouldn't take
it out during the show but what
if i had like you know what
i have a child at home i
have this or that i'm like i
should be reachable here's here's this day
and age when it's possible to be
here's what we should do instead of
giving everyone like one of those yonder
pouches that you put it in it
in you assign someone a phone chaperone
a shopper phone and you've talking then
like keep making it weirder they they
don't they don't have your phone because
you need to be able you need
to be able to reach it you
have your phone when you pull it
out and they slap
up your hand unless you can block
their hand and explain why you need
your phone okay i think it should
be this there's a designated time every
five minutes during the show where everyone
can look at their phone for no
matter what the show is everything cases
an emergency every yeah
we make it ten no i just
feel it be five five thirty like
for a play you want to keep
them lmao
yeah here's how to say emergency could
happen at any time yeah you don't
want wings goodbye yeah yeah well then
in that case i have an addendum
to the shopper phone yeah and i
think they should hold the phone they
should be standing right next to you
with the phone and then if you
want the phone you snap your fingers
and we have to give you the
phone that's more like a phone butler
it's like a chauffeur
no show foer yeah oh shit oh
shit oh shit oh shit ah shit
jehovah phone ye da da da da
da does your phone chef foe stefon
how we planned she phoned show boom
yeah sure okay god well duh shabu
are you me doing shariah
disability of shoe referee lauren have you
ever seen the movie roadhouse starring patrick
swayze there is no chance i've seen
it although mike told me i was
like my favorite movies right now it's
like basic instinct that's must be good
right he's like we watched it together
i was like no we didn't and
then he's like yes we did
we watch that movie not longboat remember
how horny i was it was during
the pandemic i was like no we
didn't i swear we watched field attraction
he goes no he watched both those
which basic instinct than i put on
the trailer and go no no no
and then there's something happens to go
oh yeah i've seen oh yeah how
annoying is that one hundred percent yeah
um well well also you should trust
your husband because
cause he is the head of the
trust you're right and he's there to
guide you know it's true i always
said yeah yeah you should respect him
and honor him you're right you're right
so what were you gonna tell me
um roadhouse that movie first of all
it's worth watching because it's insane it's
it's crazy nut yeah um i'll rest
by the way used to do a
character based on the musician in the
roadhouse the healing
a blind guitar player yeah what was
the character i forget but it was
very funny on stage was on stage
now okay yeah it was very fun
can't imagine whatever
um but there is a a moment
that establishes this the bad guy in
town played by ben guevara huh and
to show that he has ultimate top
mattress guy
what mattress guy
isn't there a mattress guy who sells
mattresses like ours mattresses nevermind
fuck ben ghazi era the mattress salesman
this is i don't know if he's
related to this mattress salesman but he
is an actor ok because everything we
talk about has to connect back to
a mattress salesman around i want you
to make that rule it's working ever
since the tour we did together it's
working for us but i think it's
not working for you we do
mattresses we shouldn't have guests couples counseling
right now to talk about the i
grow weary of it so it's not
working for paul and that means we
should probably pivot okay well that remember
france yes um honestly fantastic comedy what
was it payback when they're moving the
match or the couch up the stairs
and they can't get passed around the
corner and some of the that's some
of the best most fun sitcom extremely
well done yeah yeah absolutely love it
i'd love to get to do a
scene like that only two so just
one scene yep i was looking people
i love remains why don't we just
re-enact that in scott stairwell and then
rita oh we put
it's a great idea it is funny
so the county sure yeah we're hearing
the oh no we're hearing him oh
we hearing yeah i want to play
the and so we keep jamming your
head to the recipe and going like
pivot
i think i have a couch costume
is it just like dirty rags it's
a potato potatoes dirty oily rags
you can light on fire if you
like so he laid it on fire
by mistake while we're moving it up
the stairs rose smoking yeah yeah yeah
so bizarre it's like crying and we're
like pivot and then his head slams
into the wall that's right the smolder
yet so bizarre the bad guy until
they know is the talisman thing cause
i was like i love to own
a town oh wouldn't you and then
you could do this i'd like to
own it but i'd like to run
it too i don't want someone else
to win this thing
he dead zones and runs it i'd
rent it out to people okay ideal
airbnb town but yeah you wanna you
want your town for a day that's
what you would do you think i've
got cash to rent a town for
a day not on trash day how
incredible would that be like especially if
you get one that has like a
carnival going on during it that's what's
been so tight we will wait so
you you're saying you
rent the you are the renter yeah
you get to rent a town from
you rented on a day that there's
a carnival yeah i knew i could
do anything that's in the town the
owners like for the month when they
provide hardware and i have a car
don't leave a bottle of wine there
will just happens there's a carnival that
and it's like it's like airbnb's we're
all gonna vacate the town but there
will be a carnival
what like everyone has to do their
job kind of scary when carnivals just
pop up and they're like oh there's
a ride here right now and then
you just supposed supposed to get on
and entrust it yeah i started joys
i don't i don't know about that
why because they're moving from town to
town i like how they have a
game down the dial but it's hard
with the zipper that i'm not so
sure will don't go in the
and you cry baby oh my god
we went with him here and there's
a carnival i'm calling your ass and
i'm making you go on every ride
i'll go on every ride really twice
really yes really yes three times real
yeah no times not no handrails nothing
else please borrow to a carnival man
you're gonna go on every ride three
times three times
he's up in your fort go huh
yeah okay four okay so next carnival
that by the way the oshie carnival
thing is there's a carnival all the
time there's a carnival carnival over toshi
but i'm talking more about like rink
eating i'll go to jail part one
that's in like one so yeah yes
not like a big old yeah no
i know jack
which although go out and go on
every ride six times okay okay we're
gonna call you on this can we
tape you on good yes six times
each ride six times we try should
we do an episode where we're on
to know i don't want to be
me i'm gonna barf i want you
and way is good god is that
he goes on six six times for
every single ride
yeah you're gonna have gone i'm like
wait who pays for the rough sixty
minutes ten times i'm going on ten
times in your bang i'm not paying
that was never said you know i'm
paying i'm paying it i'm going to
write ten times each ride okay ten
times alright hey this is a promise
i think it's too many i'm actually
bored at the idea now i want
it to be three bore little crybaby
oh my
oh god yeah so here's what things
aren't well who the fuck is that
he's driving down the road listening to
the song show boom okay his convertible
show boom show and he is just
driving him back and over the media
it is the weirdest sounds fun expression
of power it's like heena there's nobody
who's no one can stop him so
he's just driving back forth over the
whole road singing show boom in his
class it's fun it's wild i love
it i tell you when i drove
over the medium median
in front of a long island medium
you probably did but i don't remember
it so i feel like it's fair
for you to repeat it while i
was so i grew up in a
town that had it's own private police
will ruin the town i grew up
in a small town had it's own
private police
so they would bug they would just
pull everyone over and i got pulled
over so many times i was young
and i did not know that when
they say like hey you mind if
we search your car that you can
say i do mind do not do
that and go okay we went down
the station well yeah there you couldn't
there was like these little just beat
the shit out yeah i know little
business card with like your rights
on it that i remember somebody has
well we've talked about this yeah the
trading cards that you've known it was
like a thing that was like oh
yeah okay no you're right car you
can't search my car hey i have
the bitten latin tape you can search
my car when we few
search my car when i'm with you
but i like him
like yeah but i've been i've been
pulled over by the show lmao so
many times t and they'd hassled me
that i saw these ice i was
making a left and checking it twice
i saw this police turned out who's
naughty or nice i saw this police
officer pulled someone else over and i
was like man
when is mae king la la thing
not your nice sounded like but you
did in attica man
it's just because i wasn't not nice
i was just santa claus but to
treat me like awesome man feels so
sad
it was guti gaultier gotcha
goty but addict okay yeah yeah nah
nice
treat me like what's the opportunity we're
lucky enough to get a true one
hit wonder i've never heard who won
whoever earned even a passing mention of
him he gets he must disappear we
love goatee and that's why we were
big fans and we would love for
you that your we would love for
you to be on the
show okay whoa are we saying before
by the way paige davis never got
back to us why so she's off
the list i cannot believe we didn't
hear from her not only did we
spell not even to say no thank
you because we spelled out exact schedules
yeah go down yeah to the
tea yeah it is a minute it's
customary to r s v p responded
to several play it it's a little
rude to not respond to play i
actually feel like look is she still
someone i'm used to know of is
she still someone that i think is
our number one fan yeah all that's
assuming that she
is so all the more strange you
need to lie down in a coffin
yeah my attire
yeah guys i got a little tired
well don't i'm actually feeling great because
your eyes are closing but you're also
your teeth are my eyes honestly feel
a few pennies over i feel so
heady but
but where is page why didn't share
as well i don't go i forget
who we're moving to next yeah video
was on i think it was um
the basketball player um oh yeah reggie
miller yeah that's right he's so gaultier
is after reggie miller okay so are
we putting reggie miller on notice right
now that geez this is
okay yeah you if you're doing long
walks with fork angle would be let's
give until september first he's local i
think maybe today
labor day let's give him till labor
labor day weekend close remember a day
maybe possibly my birthday this year i'll
find out a little closer my birthday
i remember september six i'm wrong yeah
yeah keeping your birthdays aftermath no labor
is the fourth my birthday i mean
wow these later and oh wow and
then scott what's paul's birthday september twenty
three know how am i supposed to
know we've told you a thousand fucking
guy hair well guess again why should
i know this off the top
did you know your eyes too
i don't want you to know it
well i wish i could i wish
i could raise it from my mind
too yeah i wanna normalize your bones
so you never know when my god
i want a normal item to make
or maybe make you know member i
just have normal store outcomes man in
black they made me not remember
it should have been to say do
whatever they want i'm sure you don't
remember what else did they get up
to with it normalizer yeah really yeah
but you did it
what if the person did have to
cut them off yeah whatever oh i'd
love to hear the response song i
said i'm sorry that i cut you
off i feel like a meme that
was like or not i mean here
is why i caught you all and
it was like gaultier hits different when
you're not a kid anymore i'm like
so you are a kid why say
you were a kid and that song
came out with
it was not the only ago but
that's okay people are kids and now
adults and then they're hearing the same
again they go oh it's about a
breakup oh i was five when what
does the one thing that they exactly
they just thought it was someone who
moved away yeah someone was if they
thought they were losing the alphabet so
when his dad got a better job
yeah it was fun and their mom
like my mom like to listen
to it
oh man well go to a we
love you come on the show after
reggie miller and reggie miller you have
until september first to contact us we're
not going to give you our info
know but you know how to get
a hold of us reggie if you
come on the show you will be
the the only guest ever on threesome
yeah and that's a big deal and
i don't
i think we have to tell you
what a big deal that is it's
a huge deal and by the way
we're not even interested in you that's
not how i think of a deal
it is you're interested in regime miller
we worked together on our last show
and that's right chinese i'm actually very
interested in seeing him again i'd love
to i don't know my could you
could be less interested but could be
nice you could you could run help
please
extremely nice oh that's good to hear
that's yeah here but it'll get the
threesome treatment we're not going to treat
him any different than we know each
other which is sad i know will
not remember anything he talks we can't
we won't remember his birth if we
start acting all polite it's going to
be a really bad episode exactly yeah
so the differential mr reggie miller na
re you think reggie miller reggie if
you sit in the fourth
chair yeah hey you better expect you're
wanting a fourth of the treatment yeah
we dole out to yeah exactly so
i know the sounds enticing so contact
us before september first we have to
take a break we'll be right back
never meant to guy will not break
my own pace just because i was
sent know i am no but but
the book to put the pottu amman
to sing like to dance i filled
your stocking up but you didn't
even think like you
really thought about this christmas
parody of somebody i used to just
flows out of me
um
now i'm just a center that you
use to just assessor
you gotta go on nealon paul's you
gotta go on a silly spoof to
i love to sing that song if
i get a guitar player to do
with me yeah or what was the
one i play cool instrument that cool
up and i did blue yes one
of those blah blah blah yeah cool
can i did are we human
in or am i santa it's good
are we human oh i shan't i
mean and i'm standing here looking at
prancer good law we go home in
santa sounds good it was really good
did you guys switch off lyrics how
did you do it i can't remember
how we do
did it i think i was the
lead singer and she was my backup
dancer or something like that but very
progressive yeah no need to have her
in front of like karaoke queen she
didn't want to know your karaoke queen
oh that's right um ice queen i've
never been invited to do that show
oh you should be and just because
i will turn it down doesn't
today is why they never say well
it's so chose i did a bit
that i might have been at that
show similar or christmas parody show it
probably was that if you don't know
what this show is it's they have
people on you can't afford it the
worst christmas parody challenge and aaron whitehead
and i did one asked alvin and
the chipmunks we mean when we say
made it like gross
smile
yeah
me i want my home
i was like do i still want
my dough
yeah sometimes just a simple folk yeah
and i'm seeing crush of course it
did yeah dildo factory i love marry
so much i saw her the other
side hundred million you should not allowed
on the show while she's not allowed
on the show know she'll never be
on the show well we we went
to a dodgers game yes i was
a little jealous of pictures
the head with a baseball i didn't
think fully um and holly i took
holly was delightful she liked it she
ate almost a whole daughter dog wow
what did you do with leftover well
i cut it up onto a little
plate and i left it on the
plate and then eventually threw it out
um yeah we're using it's still there
or you want it
yeah
i think it's probably the traffic but
find it ok
this trash can at dodger stadium my
dodger dog would be in there i
don't know if i told you this
that one time i went to a
dodger game with river butcher and a
woman a couple rows ahead of us
like caddy corner chen i'd say dodgers
with an s i said a dodger
scheme it does use a dodger game
i don't think anyone cares yeah i
don't want to be seen as theirs
i don't think there's this
style guide for that yeah i guess
i yeah i say dodger game yeah
okay yeah because i think there there's
one of one of them is a
dodger yes los angeles dodger but if
you ever have two in the same
room which hardly ever happens by the
way yeah they're ever in rooms no
roosevelt so they're always outside
a person yelled at you um no
just assuming ah because that's what i
wanna do someone told me to keep
it down that's all
they were listening to the game on
the radio oh yeah you know i
like that i like that too yeah
it's so silly she's oh weird about
that because you you can't sometimes you
don't know you want to hear the
play-by-play yeah
and you just want to know what's
happening and so i really i it's
so old-fashioned bad and people keeping the
school during the score i see so
many people do there yeah do you
think those people who keep the score
like they do it for every game
or they just like this is a
fun thing to do to do it
for the library of congress oh honestly
i was looking at the scoreboard going
what is the score i cannot figure
out there's there's a lot to look
at yeah stephanie did explain to me
where it wasn't i just kinda was
like ah and then i didn't really
pretend it yeah yeah so we were
we're at the game and ah we
were sitting back to ask you to
play home plate no i begged them
i said please let me play
hey we need tonight i'm wearing a
hat you have to let me play
yeah and you are the only one
there wearing a hat
was everyone was bald other people wearing
it and proud yeah sort of wearing
that
you can't have hair if you have
a hat
hair is wavy hair is a hairy
head if we're saying nobody had hair
or nobody had a hat that also
means imp didn't have hair yeah right
and then this lady yelled at you
guys know she's still didn't go
she got hit by a foul ball
wow where it hit her in the
abdomen oh no what are you paying
attention ah i thought it would be
i'm just curious if it was like
she saw it coming or she didn't
see it coming i don't think she
saw it coming oh my god what
does she saw companies like yes yes
yeah right
yeah yeah so what iterate the gut
um and it hit pretty hard she
o was okay but it was like
do they give you any sort of
compensation if that happens too oh no
yeah that's what it's part of the
fun somewhere on the tick in sporting
fun you might get hit somewhere on
the ticket your greet someone their ticket
it's like hey someone that's okay you
know someone
ticket i owe somewhere on the ticket
huh you get hit in the head
with a bottle
and that's fine i would love to
i should look at that find that
liability thing cause i'm sure it's like
anything that happens to you is not
our fault i know when i saw
the nine inch nails the nine inch
nails how many of them with cool
op we were in the pit how
many nails are in the nine inch
nails oh there's hundreds of nails but
they're all nine inches
is that's while it's not his nails
on one inch nails nine nine inch
nails on your hand no oh so
they'd be ten yeah no no their
nails their nails like that you put
into it yeah how do you know
like the nails used to crucify jesus
because they talked about this during the
show you let me okay they talked
tell you about the show yeah they
talked about why they're called the nine
inch snails do they do every show
yeah but i don't think they just
want you guys any luck out there
let's get it out of the way
let's talk about the elephant in the
room
but um so cool up and we're
there together and cool up was in
front of it because it was packed
we were in the pit cool up
was in front of me and i
had my arms around her oh and
then she went to romantic actually shutter
she went to go she went to
go to the restroom and then you
had to go along with her
roger now yeah um no you don't
get up on the tank of the
toilet
so i stayed there and they they
were the band was constantly throwing water
bottles full water bike swi like like
with the cap off so that the
school would get wet so that the
cap was off and they would they
would like a trail of water would
come ah come like shoot across whatever
and then they would go
into the crowd and so like mere
seconds says or were they throwing the
bottles are they're holding the bottle and
throwing the water the bottles the bottles
yes like they take a sip out
throw the hoe when your hip so
maybe they were trying to cool everyone
down because it gets very hot or
whatever i have no idea maybe really
like suck my kiss
iss and then they would do that
yeah it would seem red chili peppers
suck my kids
stuff like um but mere seconds after
she went to the restroom i looked
to my left and suddenly would boom
right where her head is oh wow
water bottle right in my chest oh
i was lucky and i think she
had to piss yeah
because otherwise her head would be different
now well she had to get the
water out front had yeah yeah her
head would be a different head right
yeah yeah yeah um and then you
look to your right and then you
realize that some of these people will
not be here yeah exactly yeah it
turned out it was me yeah i
never went to another show but yeah
close the person that looked at you
go with a ho
all right you know that's so awesome
when a teacher does some really cool
shit like that and you're like whoa
look to your left let's you write
years from now you won't be gradually
with these motherfuckers it would be so
cool to be teacher and be that
fucking cool oh so fucking fools fucking
look around everyone in this class
washroom some of these people will be
dead in ten years yeah that's just
the way it works some things will
never change that's just the way it
works something j age but that's just
a way waste was that song blue
that is popular way it works it's
lower and did that over it
massaquoi was just the way it works
but some things will never change
change asia
just the way it works do you
think of his name was bruce horny
would be more or less successful than
bruce hornsby um well he was said
he was so norm core it might
have added some eds to him he
was boost cooler
he is bruce course yeah like if
i know anything about him he was
bruce carr and could he's saying yeah
could well for sure can go on
the way i play my show and
top you bet yeah somebody radiate on
the eighty eight that's just the way
wars is that's just the way it
is he had one other song to
ah that's this huge one
i mean he had he had several
other songs but in twelve but hits
yeah like this i know there was
another one that that i remember hearing
on the radio he wait i'll tell
you what is big mandolin wind wow
man the wind mcl could never happen
now we will mandolin
wow no
oh that's of course within range bruce
must be in the ram and the
range up to he ditched the range
f after nineteen nine stub you brown
band up to cafferty yeah yeah we
go to the dogs oh wow you
all know dogs huh
you know the worst example of his
alice cooper who the band was called
alice cooper pooper scoopers and the first
covers and this is alice cooper and
the super duper pooper scooper yeah and
then they invented the pooper scooper because
of that my dad once wrote in
an elevator with alice cooper oh really
down her up good question i don't
know
but i think it's probably can you
have the makeup on or nah he
was just an just like no other
details except recall that that was a
cool moment but so did your dad
say anything to him or who's just
like in his head gone i don't
know if he did can i want
i do recall my dad seen chris
farley on the screen going hey chris
in any way back and that in
chicago it was nice yeah
this nice yeah sorry can't talk gotta
go do yeah looks running wow
well in this whack spect chris oh
no no disrespect intended i just tell
it like it is you don't just
merely just the way it works something
curvature um wait so how did your
dad relais that he spliced with alice
cooper i mean did you know this
story as a kid that i heard
so
story it was just he was it
was just he told me yeah the
way you tell it it's not a
straight lie certainly don't make it a
story oh i'll get more details get
more details could you texted him right
now sure what makes me point out
something a story it's got to be
more than one sentence
fair one day i generally get it
with alice cooper elevator i wrote an
alligator with ellis i was trapped in
an alligator with alice cooper was like
jonah in the way it was yeah
it was real parochial situation we build
a fire that's all we got
smart thinking on behalf of pinocchio don't
you think
very brave considering he's made of wooden
true he could have yeah that little
nose that grows when he tells a
film let me tell you something it
gets pretty bad totally
why not cio old dirty joke rachio
i never saw the gomo debate so
good i know i have to sound
so good really yeah it's great and
it's amazing i'll check it early as
i'll watch it tonight
i am well you remember it i
might watch it later wait how do
i know what i haven't haven't actually
seen it like with mike and bobby
can still really good question i don't
know but i'm in the middle of
watching some other stuff right what are
you watching right now well i just
finished last night a great kind of
finish reality show ultimatum queer love oh
okay i've seen the trailer is ultimatum
and colon queer love yeah yeah it's
already ulta
madam colin struggle to meet him queer
love wait they started with ultimatum straight-leg
didn't have any title under nose just
ultimatum then they did a they should
just cocktail germanium again yeah yeah just
go online maybe have someone explain it
at the top and go like hey
everyone it's the second ultimately like duh
just so you know yeah this is
just queer people anyway
but it's mr ultimatum here it was
fantastic the guy had to sally watch
the finale thank you for watching our
programs or else what we like to
do is present you with love stories
that you can relate to well i'm
kind of well session like coffee
i'm watching succession season three because i
gotta catch up yeah that feels like
i'm just kind of like putting in
the hours at this point do you
really want to see what happened to
dang yeah deleted data data data data
data data it's like guys write more
than one song that nay ah where
we watched a succession
after my show yeah during the show
the band played the succession theme and
i played just the pretty thing oh
how fun it was really fun did
you get the right keys every time
because we put tape on them i
love that
it was really fun that sounds really
fun okay here's a question for you
okay i have an answer for you
if you're going to a bake sale
what would you hope to find caped
cake cookies this is a big sale
just by one person like you know
it's a community based community or nothing
that's important because there's by the way
there's this ah
girl down the street the one i'm
walking the dogs who like even on
a holiday recently is sad really thought
you were gonna like cortisol no no
no she's selling lemonade oh boy she's
not all i think she's twelve okay
selling lemonade and then i was i
was so
so i was the first time i'd
seen her and then i've seen her
like everyday since i said to cool
off and she goes oh yeah i
she couldn't give me chains i had
to buy a macrame hat as well
wow so so venmo first of all
yeah in this day and age nobody's
walking around with one dollar i found
it charming of like oh how fun
like she's doing me because i did
that one day in my life was
like oh let's have a boy yeah
there's a lot you know i definitely
eliminate sale she's thirty somewhere like everyday
business i never did it every day
yeah
griffey did that as an adult my
nephew said outside and sold his pokemon
cards and it was successful and and
people bought him he was killing it
puzzled their kids
they were excited i feel like like
this when he was like seven or
eight said eliminate should they just buy
like coke at costco for the cheapest
price and then sell it for yeah
two dollars by president select yeah wow
that takes me back
summer in the city okay what do
i have to find a city like
if you were like oh there's a
big sale like to me i'm kind
of like i'm really hoping for like
a gooey brownie i guess my dad
who left me when i was wow
nothing's you like muffins things out of
baixas you and hope for the mobile
themes i like my things really kind
of muffins blueberry blueberry muffins blueberry muffin
i make good ones from the new
york times um the new york times
reported on this yeah you make good
ones i make good ones from the
new york times lower and lacquers recipe
on the new york
and times that's really good for muffins
yeah for blueberry muffins i like blueberry
yeah maybe i'd want either
cookie or a gooey brownie sounds good
gooey brownie well i have never really
made amazing brownies i would like to
try brownies are so fucking so good
when a brownie is good and is
tough and when they're not good it's
really disappointing yeah you rather have a
steak or brownie brownie
every time yeah i think every time
even if you have not eaten i
like i like steak fine but i've
enjoyed brownies far more i would rather
have a brownie over a steak yeah
yeah so if you went to a
steak restaurant you were and you you'd
not eaten dinner yeah and and and
and it was your parents and your
parents said their backs life yeah your
parents say there's a lot happening
you can only order and they're still
in charge of me yeah yeah you
can only order one thing on the
menu you would pick the brownie if
it's on the menu
if it's a cart that comes around
later
yeah there's no way you would pick
this lake yeah and you'd go home
anyway
if i was a toll
you can have one thing we're just
one thing sustain you for the next
three days but and it also been
a steak or brownie but they said
the brownie was really gooey
i eat the brown if you've sustained
for three days meaning you can eat
this now and then for the next
few days you can't have any yeah
yeah me saying say me same museum
alright we need to take okay
hey we're back and by the way
i want to say i went to
a concert
yeah recently i saw the national and
yes who opened for them soccer mommy
open now they reach out to you
paul wait i'm paul yeah i'm talking
to you yeah hello what is they
reached out to you to say just
to give it to offer us tickets
to see the show which was so
nice because i played one of their
songs
in one of our three cher's yes
yes hit the post and ah ah
you i was already going and you
guys could not go so yeah it
was said it couldn't go cause i
was like what a cool message to
get that was something so i go
to this concert and ah first of
all i got i got one person
coming up and saying by the way
i'm a pittsburgh
oh shit yeah i'm it love it
and then suddenly ah watching was the
national already i don't think so maybe
it was in in-between no i think
the national were there and suddenly there's
ah a tap on the shoulder and
it's the young man who reached out
to you and he was like hi
i just wanted any talked about ah
he plays in the band and he
he talks about how much he loves
the show did he find how did
he find it did you have a
seat that he got you know why
you just found me in the crowd
but he saw you from the stage
well you're i don't think sounds like
i'm gonna go get that and i
was sitting down wow his torso is
really long oh you might have been
the only one sitting down that's how
he recognized yeah wow someone's a loser
i will say i was on the
io who's that old
dmae okay
who's who's that old man you shouldn't
be going to concerts
nobody he talks about how much he
loves the show oh so yeah anyway
so and he said he was at
pittsburgh and so it's always great to
hear from you piss pigs out there
shout out to celebrity piss pig ryan
gaul that's right that was flattering to
me that he listened my old pal
from bazillion
i hadn't seen him in a while
and he confessed to me the green
room of the usb theater that he
is his pick one i love it
wonderful alright alright so we're three char
we have three ch are really know
what it is is we played this
game recently but we learned from a
comment that we were doing it wrong
and it's actually really very bad economy
was good for once yeah
and we learned something the game i
don't know if it was called umbrella
or if it's picnic or what it
is but it's the game where basically
we can we can say we're going
to a picnic because i think that's
a common one we let we hope
into pure nickname she's everywhere so besides
what the rule is for the picnic
yes i feel like i haven't been
to a picnic in years yeah
like i used to go to them
all the time when i was young
yeah i feel like at least people
would be able to year at the
silverlake reservoir everyone bringing cheese ever bring
one cheese please anyway the way it
works is the one who did the
reservoir alters it no beverages one person
comes with the rule for what's allowed
the picnic
like the other two people try to
bring something in the person in charge
tells them whether they can bring internet
thing we forgot is the person who
knows the rule also has to say
one thing they're going to bring to
you hell yeah nah she's dousing it
everything in the world yes okay i
have it you have it yes ok
okay hey
hey how about that picnic can we
come depends can you bring something yeah
i'm gonna bring potato salad no ooh
oh i wanted to come i was
gonna bring a teddy bear now you
can't come no oh i tell you
what i'm gonna bring though i'm gonna
bring a large bowling ball okay a
larger yeah
like not taking place in insights
you probably won't get her okay no
the guy yeah well i'm gonna bring
a globe
yeah i'm sorry i'm not gonna allow
you to come piece of shit i'm
going to bring a twenty pound weight
fifty
seventy five one hundred pound weights get
it up three hundred pound weight on
a pub or eight thousand pound weight
you can go
what are you going to bring
i'm going to bring ah ah dona
a metal doughnut
a metal doughnut yeah you know i'm
talking about ripple yeah of course oh
yeah yeah ah i'm going to bring
um
a ah cement hula hoop
no
no the fuck are you laughing at
i don't know you fucking wrong you
know who i'm going to bring a
hairbrush the size of this room no
you cannot bring that oh okay does
it feel so open come back at
me
i'm gonna bring a face mask
focus up with this guide
he's gonna bring a pulling paul face
mask was metal doughnut any little allowing
me to bring an eight thousand pound
weight
ah ah i'm gonna bring
the big black shoe
yeah yeah you can come huge black
shirt not huge no but a black
a black shirt as long as it's
a ten issue
okay
i'm going to bring a an oversized
yoga mat know last day how did
this
no look i'll tell you what i'm
going to bring is i'm probably going
to bring a lacrosse stick
okay
i'm going to bring a big basketball
yeah come on yeah i'm gonna bring
a basketball hoop yeah you can come
yeah whatever you want i'm gonna bring
um catcher's mitt
i'm gonna bring golf club yeah i
wasn't sporting equipment yeah why didn't i
have to be oh no that was
yes
i don't care how big it was
what was the most little doughnut but
that you put around the baseball bat
oh my god all right what do
you think it was i said paul
you know what i mean that anyone
yeah i do i thought it was
something dirty
you're a baseball guy your guy anytime
somebody says you know what i mean
i assume it's phil okay i'm ready
with my thing okay hey who are
you let me get that picnic i'm
your neighbor yes hi i'm your store
i'm your pastor yes i know that
i consulted with us both whenever you
make you
life decision thick i didn't learn this
one is picking tomorrow i would love
to be picking how about this i'm
gonna bring some lemonade that cool refreshing
drink now you can't come with the
foot and i'm gonna bring collection of
vinyl records no you can't come
you know i'm going to bring um
some some like little wintery boots
little wintery boots alright well i'm gonna
bring a thick woolly scarf
you can come i'm gonna bring a
dollhouse you can't come
i'm going to bring a dog
okay
i'm going to bring
a mink coat you can come i'm
gonna bring a coat with like a
ah like a fur lining on income
yeah it's very thing yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay paul stern alright now this
is too easy i know that's true
glad you're here and oh my god
you guys yeah oh my god brenda
it's me brenda i'm having one amanda
picnics friend i'm here to brenda are
you coming to my picnic yeah and
kind to your picnic well what are
you going to bring stupid i was
gonna bring a dress you bitch
you can't come i'm sorry oh no
brenda i was going to bring my
calculus textbook oh no you can't come
i'm sorry oh no i was gonna
bring a set of key ways i'm
also going to say what i'm going
to bring remember yeah sorry we don't
want to be in danger territory sorry
i'm gonna bring a fancy picnic basket
ah oh i'm going to bring a
picnic blanket now sorry i'm gonna bring
a wicker chair
oh no sorry oh what are you
gonna bring ah this guy i'm gonna
bring i'm gonna bring a bench to
sit on oh things that are three
dimensional so i'm gonna try
i'm going to bring like um a
tree okay you could come okay i'm
gonna bring the halfcourt basketball court i
mean okay you can come okay okay
what are you going to bring remember
good question remember you told me to
eat my own ass right and guess
any time
so to say
and you've forgotten both time and then
you're like whatever i'm gonna bray ah
patio umbrella but not the canvas part
okay i'm going to bring a guitar
okay oh yeah i'm gonna bring a
sly
slide
i don't think he could come i'm
gonna i'm gonna you know you're supposed
to say no you're mad at her
good
okay what i gotta break by dutch
clogs okay i'm gonna bring a bed
that's made of wood okay oh i'm
going to bring a bumblebee this made
of wood okay you got co i'm
gonna bring oh wait your turn come
go
alright guys wooden spoon okay you could
kind of bring a trojan horse so
you could go my memory oh what
an ornament okay you could come up
i'm gonna bring a piece of paper
that used to be wood okay i'm
entering a door okay you go
he's a real student of huh that's
yeah
great time great time we fixed it
we've redeemed ourselves yeah it's likely like
assholes and like christ redeemed the world
with his blood yeah that's right thanks
for the well by the way his
blood pitch hey he's never said it
thank you think hey no one's ever
said this to him before but thank
you jesus jesus is it time to
go get away would it be so
bad
if i got one thank you for
going through my buddy just say i
mean no one asked me to do
it granted but i didn't do it
d nice to be appreciated could you
know what here's what sucks though yeah
that i know we have to go
vacuum cleaners so we didn't ask to
be born with sin in the first
way we didn't ask me
born in first place but then we're
just you know whatever going about our
lives trying the best we can and
then it's like oh jesus died for
your sins great thing but then that's
all i need to know about it
now i can just live my life
but now you can still go to
hell no you have to do more
oh no this was yeah hillary wait
i think this is a good thing
to get into
like it's right now because we're about
to wrap it by the way it's
for jesus it's transactional love which i
don't appreciate how bout it you know
i mean jesus is love language gifts
gifts acts of service yes extra service
gifts accessing we were just learn
lauren cheney and i were just talking
about this last night what do you
think here's is my my giving love
language is gifts and my receiving is
touch oh yeah i don't know we
we guess each other's and it was
very sad you have to do them
ah do to a quiz or do
you just kind of go with what
you just read
the list and then we just kind
of guessed oh there's a list this
makes it easier yeah yeah it's narrowed
down for ya yeah okay minus just
being a good person who does the
best can wow none of the list
that's shitless so it's not a style
yeah damnit so therefore you're lying yeah
oh no yep
well the lawyer he listed and this
is freedom the podcast and if you
would like to listen to ad-free versions
of this why don't you go to
bb world dot com or stitcher premium
or go find it up go fuck
yourself if you would like to send
us our creature like the kind we
just played
you can email us at three am
usa gmail dot com you can also
leave us a voicemail if you like
under thirty seconds please please make sure
your voice isn't annoying oh please go
to broadcasting school yes and then leave
his voicemail yes and you can call
us at high claims eight it's great
and then do you guys
i have shows coming i'm sure i
do but it's too far away for
me to know right now yeah your
phone is too far away for you
know i just i don't haven't planned
that far yeah we're probably in the
middle of july know we're at the
end of june or the ended yield
good friend yeah make fun show a
dynasty that i'm planning now but you
know what's right yeah all my instagram
to see june can you give the
date at least know i don't have
the date okay that's how much i
don't know yet okay mom but oh
good idea and i have a plan
okay yeah i hate this okay i'm
gonna say this though july ninth you
can go to my show and that's
what week after my birthday you know
shit ones qr log september something yep
am
july nope and july and you're getting
close though july ninth at virar it's
like guides were i tobia my wife
lodge room and highland park at apollo
tongues dot com slash live for techies
yeah and um by the comedy bang
big book these guys wrote stuff for
it i wrote stuff for it
we all wrote stuff for it what's
everyone in the world wrote something for
it from scream and um it's good
you'll like it it's really it's a
really fun book ah hopefully you can
read you fucking there's lots of pictures
though there are lots of pictures you'll
be able to tell what's going on
if you can't even if he can't
just look at pictures yeah what's wrong
with looking at pictures
but by the book twice once for
looking at pictures once for looking at
words yeah yeah that's what i do
buy buy them for your neighbors to
just leave them on the doorsteps like
how great would that be if one
day you woke up and there was
a book on your doorstep do you
know what i'd be a little creeped
by one to put in the bread
aisle of your supermarket yeah
i'll tell you what if i ever
go to a supermarket i'm in the
bread aisle and i see a copy
of the comedy bang book i'll sign
it for the store oh that's great
there you go so all the people
who worked get a chance to read
a page and have a barrier breaker
yeah exactly my bio my my my
arm and i saw a guy my
size da hey
uh