yeah that's true
anything you
i miss listening
my
oh yeah it's us again it says
you know like we are he needed
to do at this point i know
it's someone's first episode but do we
need to introduce her i don't think
it is please allow me to introduce
ourselves i'm lauren i'm paul i'm paul
okay so now whoever is listening to
know who paul and scott are and
i'm lauren oh no oh no this
is a disaster i'm really stressed we're
getting around everybody if you look all
lorry if you look up our voices
you'll know who our faces are honestly
it's true honestly honestly and i'm being
totally candid with you guys if you
don't know our faces by now
now
what are you doing you will never
have
no them ooooo didn't you be forty
cover that were they just doing hope
so just exclusively covering your thing yeah
they turned into a cover band they
were good like reggae bands english reggae
band show with original songs and then
they did i can't help fog it
and now i was a big one
we were cocked it was for cocktail
if it was different cocktail because was
it for kaka kaka hama sugar thing
it wasn't a whole michigan was it
because you'll be forty for cocktails feel
i think this is a debate that
rages circles those few people if i
gotcha and we wonder will never know
ah the red red wine of course
they did yeah that was their first
number one hit to have four or
five years after it came out wow
because a d j in the middle
of the country started playing it and
that's the power d jays that cj
power of d j d jays can
change musical culture and influence people
it's funny drunk yeah laurie a couple
of drinks during the break visit lorna
allows herself to get drunk for one
episode of season yeah just barely
he never tells us which it is
now and i didn't i we figured
out within the first two minutes yes
put up i put a vodka tampon
in my butt in the bathroom
ah doesn't your ads you know is
that a fun way to get drunk
i don't think so i think it's
a fun way to go to the
hospital really well because it gets you
blackout drunk and like three seconds doesn't
it i don't well to put a
vodka tampon up your because i get
blackouts into your bloodstream because of your
membranes insane in the membrane but it
can't be that much
brains in your butt
i'm gonna look look for giving vodka
tampons like that give me i'm going
to look up vod content please definitely
percentage of our listeners going you guys
are squares you don't put vod yeah
there are there are no
ah hold on please read a real
website on someone's blog there so are
now writing their vodka st i read
this on a mommy blog there are
no side effects from sinking a tampa
or why it's probably a myth so
are people really taking their vitals straight-up
the june or the poon it's highly
unlikely boom
a noon for any picking this up
vagina or anus god god i got
it first any evidence of people actually
doing this is purely anecdotal it seems
that most stories come by way of
a friend of a friend's cousin well
let's just do it will tell well
yeah come on like that was that
time it was just an emphasis right
now but no but
you set a timer i will just
see what happens how drunk can i
get i do that i've never thought
about it being a an urban legend
but it kind of makes sense because
either way harrison major risks okay here's
either way if you were able to
successfully as it was you not be
successful that's it's easier than a pussy
it's easier than uzi
even if you were able to successfully
do this buck to tip ups up
your ass you could do it's easier
than pussy you could do some serious
harm tampa may not hold a lot
of vodka but what high school this
what it does hold gets into your
bloodstream quickly because it bypasses your stomach
i even bother cities and absorbed by
your stomach you can't vomit it out
if you've had yeah
that's why now we upstand there there's
the ouch factor to consider doesn't the
idea of alcohol down there sound a
little painful well it absolutely is alcohol
is highly acidic and the mucous membranes
in the wazoo and rec do our
sin and sensitive oh and we thank
god
odd for that thin saying in the
meme the jew and rectitude the twin
suns
raccoon not only will it burn like
mr charles dickens but it could also
come for kaka potentially damage your mucous
membrane oh no yeah damage i don't
have much mucus you know at somebody
that i know posted on instagram that
you used to know why actually still
know them somebody that is no
posted on instagram that they um they
have a lot of followers just people
might know this person is that they
um did like a sort of tiktok
health fix like they got a tip
from tiktok for hell hemorrhoids situation involving
sugar i don't know what the whole
situation was sugar but it created abscesses
and he almost died oh
oh he was he posted about which
that was really nice because it's like
people you love what you learn you
see these tik tocs in these instagrams
that it just reads as facts like
this will fix this so this is
a good cure for here's how to
save your fruit like all this sort
of bullshit that you see every day
and he followed on them because he
was just working in his busy trying
to like me just get deal
this i'm not too busy i thought
that i mean it had to leave
or preparation h it happens but anyway
wow crazy huh crazy stuff everyone's careful
out there taught everyone doctor don't make
your own medical medical advice from tiktok
if you turned off the episode before
we said don't put vodka tampons up
your bud then god god save you
if you're asking if you turned it
off and went out and
did that and i don't know what
to say disclaimer in this episode listen
to the whole thing yeah yes the
way that you manage this episode of
three adam needs to be listened to
in its entirety yeah stop whatever you're
doing do not be distracted while listening
turn your chair to a wall stair
and write down what we're saying and
read it back
ah
well that's right yeah that on that
that's a hat on a hat on
a hat is a good idea yeah
double hat because honestly hats get cold
well especially in terms of comedy way
yeah that's when the shoes that's a
hat on a hat yeah like it's
nothing it's so
funny when someone walks into doors like
hello mister hats yeah i have to
some laughing already well you know my
friend posted about this that i am
curious if you guys have heard of
this the pocket lady know any anything
anything know anything scared about ok i
knew what the pocket leading it seemed
like a lot of her followers did
not know about the pocket lady the
pocket lady was at my school carnival
and it's basically a mom or somebody's
bold other people know populated with us
right now
uwo this this this this this
she had a dress full of pockets
all over it or like i sort
of interrupted and there were other pockets
pockets on pockets all over and then
in the pockets were treats like little
toys and yeah getting choose like taking
a walk right exactly you could use
a ticket to get she's launched from
the pocket tomic and something comes out
of her pocket i think
vodka tampon
edgy look nice
yeah i'm drunk my friend was trying
to make a pocket lady costume um
i don't know for what sorry wow
wait does she a nationally known figures
she was at her carnivals growing up
so i mean i think it must
be saying it's kind of sure you
are familiar with the bacula she came
to my carnivals and i think she
was a local soon every car no
i think it's literally just a old
old wives' tale about the pocket lady
and people either do or they don't
total and i mean hey people they're
free to do it or not doing
it if if i have the opportunity
to marry at a school carnival yeah
for my child i will i'll be
the pocket lady yeah why not it's
fun yeah it is to walk to
put all the fun toys in there
and you'll need a ticket yes you
know you went you win a prize
you get a ticket like
you play games you get tickets and
then you can get a prize you
use a ticket to get know you
buy the tickets and then you see
their ticket prices you know sometimes you
sometimes see like if no the street
ball yes then you get tickets if
you play sneak ball sneak ball gives
you tickets carl gives you tickets my
staple is a game where people were
you through like ticks
oh goodness into the whole like a
dickens from sleep
are you in star wars right now
i got i guess from softball
i got chickens from steeple sneak sneak
bulk do you remember how in the
original star wars how slowly harrison ford
talks oh yes listen kid yeah well
you know that's time like that whoa
know anymore sir because it's like that's
here at faster on bro you know
new show yeah to talk a little
faster that's for damn sure eighty three
know what if eighteen eighty three was
a show called thank you the twenty
three okay what if well there's the
other one he's on that already know
sam bailey's well what if what if
his show was like the west wing
where everyone was talking and walking really
fast and nineteen thirty three shrink on
a rage shri nineteen twenty one
does it with you you don't want
ignite here ninety twenty three i don't
care what's an item like trump when
he's on nutrient twenty three shrank tanker
it's called shrinking shrinking oh yeah wall
street whatever what if yes what if
trump didn't want the voters remember when
trump couldn't remember when the plague was
any kept saying the move
what's the movie nineteen twenty nine or
whatever the one that's all in one
take everything seven legal thank you so
yeah he kept saying like nineteen seventeen
instead of nineteen whatever it was was
it was it when the when the
last nineteen eighty wasn't nineteen eighteen because
it was like a hundred years later
yeah year yeah but he kept nineteen
seventeen because of the movie
james terrible it was all the one
shot
speaking of shots yeah it was all
in one town do um speaking of
speaking slowly last night we watched a
documentary about peter o'toole my favorite actor
oh were you in it no and
i kept looking for myself and you're
like oh i'm gonna be a failure
yeah yeah they must have filmed me
i'm not familiar with him
em what would oh man i'm on
google emily fats maybe you've heard of
lawrence of arabia i have my favorite
year which i saw on a plane
projected from the back of the on
a little project oh wow those were
the days when he was bay oh
he was a oh sure peter o'toole
was bay bay yeah yeah yeah looking
like a snack
snack
and i'm looking at competence making hundred
and five just leaving me gagging for
it i missed out
not a current picture because yeah passed
away twenty eight thirteen yes yeah i
mean it was looking like a snack
when he was alive he was looking
like a sec for a long time
it's looking like a sack ah because
i'm like a nut sack for the
last thirteen years it's like exactly yeah
and that's like a big life i
started off looking like a snack and
end up looking last are all the
snacks comes for all the snacks yeah
yep ty
i'm calling for all the snatch so
they're they're interviewing various people one of
the people they're interviewing is kenneth brahma
who talks about how slowly and deliberately
peter o'toole jackson lawrence of arabia then
they show a clip where it's not
that at all where he's citing and
easy he's been like basically like fucked
by the editors on this yeah well
it's
it's his fault he even sites like
the dialogue yeah when he says this
and it's really drawn out and they
showed it's not drawn out at all
and they do oh okay so he
was funny was wrong they're just going
well let's just show it even i
thought you were saying the editor put
in ah intentionally put in a scene
where he talked really fast
yeah baby words of rabia lords arabia
fish hamburgers
ah the best god i would i
would love it if he were alive
to do that sam robertson no no
fifty five hamburgers fifty five hot dogs
fifty five fifty five teachers fifty five
five french fries
whereas other good movies besides my favorite
year and lawrence rome lion in winter
linemen which is an adaptation of the
play tim and katherine hepburn what does
the law and young anthony hothouse your
mansion with that alter and tim and
leader of the time lords timothy dalton
that's right russell on himself wow yeah
i don't get it but i'm happy
for you guys thank you yeah i
know i want everyone to know that
guys i made it through the jodie
whittaker seasons and i'm on the other
side and i'm a made-up what is
that dr hill yes no any event
dr yeah well when they had a
female doctor you didn't like that unfortunately
wow yeah
you know what it kind of it
sucked because she was the first woman
to be to do that role in
the stories were not stories that's not
just have not heard have the right
that's why it's unfortunate i show roared
yeah yeah yeah i got better by
the window i will say like yeah
like each season got better yeah tom
and now the original guys back right
yeah yeah yes russell
yeah russell t davies is back but
yeah i'm i'm up to the um
the david tennant years yeah those stories
are so good yeah it's like some
of the some of the stuff is
legit scary oh yeah it's it's really
good wow learn you don't care look
look i might have to do newcomers
about it
you have basically like let's it's a
failure and episodes yeah to watch um
i could make a list for you
if you were to do that okay
i have i'm open to it because
i have i don't know what money
i mean you know i've actually ranked
every episode of the modern wow and
direct-to-home season episode because i was giving
it to jason because he started
going into it might help to like
figure out which episodes to watch yeah
because he found it very overwhelming oh
of course and i ranked the theme
songs which season had a best oh
yes absolutely i feel like twenty ten
i i will tell you exactly what
johnny has the best literally staring into
space well i was thinking well that's
what doctor who lives so i get
it
i was looking for him in his
telephone booth
i know some you know that much
about it yeah i ah best theme
song is season four let's hear it
cue it up scammy series fall series
four series worst theme song the first
jodie whittaker season it's so it's all
my hair that goes in for a
bad theme sarwar i know everything about
it was so disappointing it's not cool
it's not cool it's not right i
may was tao right and i'm glad
so i may i may write my
dissertation of ranking of the doctors of
all of them of all of the
because you've been watching since the beginning
yes wow since black and white days
i'm gonna do my definitive ranking of
every episode and character of sebo
okay no i'm not and i'm choosing
google ah yes yeah probably office i
won't do that because i don't care
off the top of your head who
is the who's the best character and
who's the worst character taught my head
yeah i'd say best character we're looking
at a little thing called zack morris
probably ah nirvana because we were the
hottest he
is hot right worst character screech yeah
yeah russ in power king if anyone
screech powers for instance greige power though
shame is speech but always addressing powers
yeah screen right answer but people think
people always think of screech crackers but
screech behind thought neither what i'm just
kidding
people always make it
people always think the same screech crackers
risks to arena was rescued screech powers
raises to dogs too sad it's just
jessie was a tough character to let's
be honest ah yes in terms of
like flatness it's just like shut up
huh jessie spano yeah how do you
know that i've watched one episode four
april rachel that's right that's right she's
coming back with it i saw something
about that actually yes so she she
put them behind her patreon paywall everyone
should do that i got updates every
minute yeah i would wake up with
there'd be like thirty
emails that i'm a patriot it's crazy
it's crazy i take your crazy yeah
yeah mine will my limit that you're
mad you mad woman i saw elizabeth
berkley in the virgin megastore ones that's
guy i have this same exact thing
with sandra bullock where like i've seen
them on screen being like oh yeah
fine not you know i'm not in
not into it
it and then you see them in
person is the most beautiful person you've
ever seen like yeah if you're like
oh my lord like that is a
shunning back and showgirls days i think
she was filming this movie at that
time when i worked to tower video
she came in with paul verhoeven whoa
and they have their fucking arms wrapped
around each other
interesting well i have celebrity gossip oh
okay gossip or just you saw someone's
are on playing
someone did for her yeah for sure
many people have seen around him i
once was at birds yeah right or
usb show no honestly you really really
well okay let let's hear him out
okay restaurant next usb everyone goes to
all the time yeah right and this
is not a story because i'm not
going to say on my book i
saw two
the cast members of of of a
cult favorite tv show arm in arm
and i don't think it and like
sort of like cozying up and canoodling
canoodling and i don't think yeah ever
came out that they dated dang i'm
wait to hear this kind of impressed
when people are able to um like
if two stars of a show are
able to keep that under wraps
went to sars around yeah and they
keep it under yeah under her like
you know you know who didn't do
that on dexter
oh yeah my next bro and sis
and dexterous isn't that so complicated from
my brain yeah they played brother and
sister but in real life they were
having spent like married right a day
then they got the rowers when i
saw him at the bowling alley i
tell that story with the story tell
anyone is they actually were brother and
sister oh and then on the show
they got married yeah yes yeah and
it was it was like an any
and they had to pretend they were
married in real life but they were
like this is weird we're brother and
sister yeah you know what i think
i might be ready for a rewatch
of six feet under oh yeah it's
good so good that last love to
revisit that world
of sadness most wonderful people characters that
i hold in my heart i actually
want to say after watching muriel's wedding
with arden yeah i was reminded of
how good of rachel ah who's in
that movie oh rachel griffiths so amazing
i'm john six hundred know the acting
is so good i will start with
the firm
first time like five years ago yeah
oh so ready for a rewatch i
loved it yes batman to watch i
don't want one
huh like a little little booboo my
well this woman was batman
would you would you would you see
this change watching man
this bitch is watching it from the
beginning this sad bitch she's battling what
would you do if you said would
you knock her upside her head to
get her to stop
would you slap the taste out
she's putting up your ass knew it
was there
you knew it was their way of
saying
yeah
amor back kicking of being kind of
austrac austrac nope goodbye no sorry not
a word oh you're late or rest
i'll see you guys in twenty twenty
days your lip and don't ever run
zip
zip your lip don't ever runs it
okay you have to go and close
your lip i don't like you it
because you made a mid-may
you have to go and just grumpy
no rake and it was you in
your stupid face and then i'll laugh
and lasts sigh will go and race
do the photo wow
i liked when your like when you
said you made a mistake i don't
like you anymore
yeah yeah
where were you gonna say though that's
really her name being struck by one
mistake one mistake in there and neither
out of my life week was genuinely
solve this bitch me honestly do you
do if you heard this bitch say
the wrong words when all this miserable
bitch roll word
on a plug guest
on a podcast booker
this bitch you hot hill what do
you kill chill fun when mule so
long i know it's i said the
guy from ferris bueller no no no
that's what i was thinking yeah i
wanna rock what he does allan rock
no norm whoever the sausage king yeah
this guy from when i did west
side story by the way ah so
we did personal
ref we did um thrilling adventure hour
show this past oh a great and
richard kind was one of the guests
oh my gosh so funny delightful richard
kind yeah great well that's that's it
and after the show i'm standing by
like we get off stage you're standing
like and i'm proud boy sandy i'm
sitting down um
i'm standing like right inside the backstage
and um i'm talking to somebody and
there's stairs that lead down to the
to the dressing rooms spooky and i'm
scared then all of a sudden fucking
alan ruck appears wow and he like
looks around somebody hey great job di
di di di di di di di
di di di di
got back then right behind it it
went boom bow baum
mom mom wow
a don't don't do
oh someone should put those songs together
yeah i actually would fit together really
well i went yeah so yeah by
yello yeah and then the succession national
team by automobile thumb dang deleted di
di di i have to post online
me ah helping out with the succession
i post online show yeah i played
the ring i wanna post on me
he just waves so the fossil rock
shows up rock shows up and then
comes out of the stairway ariel enos
his wife oh wow oh my gosh
she's so good on odin kirk's new
show oh lucky hank which i have
not seen it yeah it's really good
she was taller than i so he
was shorter and she was told she
was twenty one i r rao you
touch
used to time i don't just do
nine she's solid three one i saw
him at de vinci co did de
dah dah
it's a deli in studio city this
does odell and can't get a word
so what do you do the elements
hong kong hong kong d'amato the deleon
studio san ventura there's two of them
there's another one in the city as
well the one on the one by
the bowling know monaco's know it's it's
got a joining d and then next
we just shut down now this is
deliver over there and they're smaller come
ah i don't know oh do powers
yeah oh do pilots yeah hi shiner
shiner if anything and i say diner
you know you sally a fucking idiot
i'm bid i made a mistake and
i'm gonna step on a rake and
i'll go everywhere until they take my
buddy away because i'm
dead
um why do you say that i
saw allen rocket bars are you crazy
and that's a crazy story that's awesome
that's god that is god and that's
why i don't gossip and that's awesome
so so wait so they they were
there so they were there but that
was like an odd thing they just
walked down i didn't know they were
together like yea marry they didn't mean
to enter that building they're like where
are we what is this stay with
they did seem he seemed kind of
confuse she seemed to know i guess
she saw his experience so i was
like i'm not good either i'm not
going to be dumb like him this
was the bourbon room in hollywood
oh okay um but that is not
my story that was just a sidebar
i like it thank you here's my
story about the actual story about being
starships good to be the story but
we'll look at but listen to this
blow awestruck by someone in like a
sort of crunchy way yeah it happened
to me with two people that i
interviewed me
any years apart one was summer glower
was in firefly firefly yeah that i
never really had ah like i watched
that show and yeah that's pretty i've
never had a thing for her but
something for for some reason in person
i was like kind of flustered about
i'm really caught me all the fall
oh i mean the summer
wow and the other one was mary
steenburgen oh i bind her she's beautiful
she is i did um ah but
like i'm the only one i said
it like i was like i think
i say you have i think she's
actually review yeah i did um behind
the scenes interviews for stepbrothers oh okay
and um i interviewed her
she's just like i was absolutely oh
yeah she's fun i've hung out with
her into dance at a couple of
times and it's they're both so great
did they ever stop talking about the
ocean know i was like just go
live there if you love it so
much and i'd be bothering me their
basic the oceans got trash in it
and they're like me
i'm getting get a grant generally totally
yeah okay it doesn't and the ocean
is huge yeah so we can't afford
to put a lot i transfer fine
if there's one paper cup in there
sorry what we should be doing is
filling the lakes with trash so it
gets like you know set up into
a little area that's kind of like
yes it stays still own place and
trash belongs in the water whatever once
a month you skim it
yeah wherever there's water we should throw
trash wow you're ever there as well
throw your trash in your bathtub do
you think will come to the point
where they start making like trash buildings
where it's just like yeah guys scraper
out of trash yeah it's like nebraska
or something they're just like let's go
to a wheat field and just put
like a huge land like ah like
fucking like five thousand floor why not
trash pile it
should do that now they should it's
a good idea compress it oh my
god compress it make it solid yes
i only use but you can still
see what the trash used to be
well for us so you can have
fun looking at it yes if there's
a teddy bear in there and like
some fast-fashion depeche mode how many tasers
called fast fashion no i think that's
what it means the best
oh huh
oh
i didn't know that
lauren has a new personnel
funny thing to say that's cute but
that was before it was really a
thing
ah well it was probably a thing
that it wasn't an issue how many
teddy bears do you think just get
straight up thrown in the oh my
god you know what your recycling teddy
bear i donate ten years if you
were paid to do it over are
paid to do it absolutely yeah i
think teddy bear should be on line
sort of hanmi
down basis until it gets to the
point that it's like nothing and then
it shouldn't be like to fly exactly
exactly yeah yeah yeah and you can't
let it touch the ground now remember
the days when you could burn all
your trash how great that was i
still do it every day love it
i burn nothing but plows every time
i have people leaner burnett yeah yeah
yeah i love throwing it like a
cow i like
in there yeah just light it on
fire smile mouse and it's so good
for the neighborhood and it just looks
everything someone barbecuing is like nope yeah
everybody comes over their mouths are watering
like yep i'm burning milk
ah do you use glass milk jugs
do you drink milk i don't drink
milk because i'm a grown adult yeah
i only have milk because of the
child yeah we i started to realize
we have to start buying milk and
i'm now a few months she needs
a strong bones can they drink oat
milk they can but please different um
you always find a man almost fell
over different vitamin proper
eighties available in different just the right
combi uni to look it up for
yourself and decide i know guys from
all personal choice doing research yeah i
can't give us information on podcast i
can't tell people you don't want to
be a tick tock live feed their
kids no no no make them get
ulcers in their anus oh my god
oh my anus my anus
my anus ah my anus i'll get
to my anus second to them that's
exactly it yeah would you go to
space for one hundred dollars yep we've
heard you talk this much really times
hundred dollar would you go in that
submarine though oh my god the one
that and knowing it was gonna yeah
well yeah slowed the way
yeah no no why even if you
know as if they said it would
never happen and they actually knew that
and you could see the future you
knew you'd get back would you do
it now i don't know if i
would i would yeah it was like
the james cameron i think i'd be
so scared no seats and what how
there were no seats yes but how
long is it supposed to go like
how long were they supposed to be
down there i would think
it would take a while to get
down yeah it was supposed to be
a one day excursion maybe it was
one day and you have no seniors
kind of like lying down look what
i saw i was only supposed to
be one day video of it and
i thought theirs was asleep their toilet
that was just like
yeah but if you had died i
than you are not they have a
sign yeah it's like okay go on
you sort of police what you eat
right beforehand yes so that story is
so tragic but um it's an rpg
i would be so afraid it's enraging
i also you know one thing my
memory and that's my big fear though
is to die like anytime i see
a movie that's set in space and
they're like
like oh no this thing broke yeah
and we can't get back to earth
and i just that and being underwater
and trapped knowing you're gonna die is
just like my biggest my biggest fear
other than falling downstairs are my three
because every fear i have is on
the list and those are on there
as well i have a fear that's
like that where i'm afraid of ah
being attacked by a big long headed
alien whose spit is acid well that's
really scary yeah one thing i just
want to smooth operation stay away from
by the way i think i think
you should stay away from ah should
stay away from home alien alien to
the third power
and cubed can i just say one
thing about submarines yes so they only
only one and never going to stop
i know that's it there's a new
three-term always willing to okay you each
get one so think about what you're
gonna say okay but not while i'm
talking about mine they each age they
bolt the ah from the outside yeah
and they put seventy there's eighteen bolts
and yet they
i do seventeen of them and i
wonder why is that i heard about
this i did not hear about that
and i disagree the idea that you're
being bolted in from the outside and
that even if the thing popped up
to the surface of the wall wouldn't
be able to get you wouldn't able
to get out that's what they have
done they have a porthole where they're
like i don't like an indiana jones
he jumps on periscope
i just don't know you know how
he jumps on one at one point
or you know he doesn't i mean
yeah he's holding onto the periscope but
he has to get in portal and
can i just say for the record
i what i mean is the thing
that you turn the wheel yes that's
so sorry i don't stay i don't
think they have that richard hatch it's
yeah we're really talking about was largely
based upon the submarine opening
that's right now there was i forgot
those two richard hatch's there's battlestar galactica
yes my youth and then the sign
and the naked guy yeah the naked
felon yeah what did he do i
forget but ninety thousand which was cool
with it soy bomb oh my god
soy oh we love you soy bomb
i love you so where's soy bomb
very bisbee but
i just want to six people are
probably like that submarine thing happened a
million years ago it were not recording
so far in advance it also happened
a million years ago here it's over
it's over okay now we know when
secretary mountain current because you think this
is too long ago to talk about
it is yeah yeah we know it
already it now we have to say
one thing about okay i wanna hear
they're shaped like horseshoes
okay that's not true what
and paul so you the second i
said you'd just say something he said
i got mine yeah and you just
had a lie
it's not alive if you actually think
it that's really a fucked up way
to live alright here's my one thing
alright yeah they fucking stink yeah you
know it's you know it's outside i'm
smoking yeah even the outside smells
true it was like old poor um
guy i think about these these fucking
rich guides that yeah who wants to
eat for the ocean they want to
explore space they always have to do
it there's existing entities that you ride
part of yeah but they're like no
i have to build it and be
the boss of so because it's there
i don't know
what the fuck i'm talking to is
there already a james cameron built thing
to see that these know because he
sought yeah but he like it already
paid he geiser he is somebody who
made his own money like wasn't born
in money and in an industry where
safety was a thing that's talked about
all the fucking time yeah thank because
he
he's got a boss and he's responsible
to somebody yeah you know and then
that's the crucial difference yeah and then
these guys are just like that because
this fucking guy first wanted to build
a rocket he wanted to go to
mars and then it was like wow
that's not that profitable so i'm gonna
go off to do the dad yeah
that'll be my fun little business but
it's really well because we have the
movie titanic you can see all the
things yeah exactly yeah and that's that's
it's better like we watched it the
other day did you yes it's three
hours yeah it is did you get
any ah nuances on tactile ah no
we just talk about the nineties for
a quick second i recall seeing the
entire like yeah hey start
being a nine nineteen ninety and then
going to ninety nine thousand actually i
saw it in theaters and i recall
there being an intermission because it was
three hours that's been that used to
happen i just remember that yeah it
happened but it did not happen i
don't remember with titanic but that was
a thing it was a thing that
used to happen but not with yeah
okay because i asked the menu in
my theater unless the thief
later was like we're going to do
this out of the kindness of our
hearts or something they just stopped the
movie in the middle i remember that
ever happening in my life but i
were i associated with that lawrence of
arabia which we were talking about earlier
ethics right intermission yeah ben hur the
one the one time i've seen it
in a movie that technically normally didn't
have it was the hateful eight quentin
turned
did a seventy millimeter center rama dome
version that had an intermission and gave
out programs and stuff but what were
you gonna say um but where do
you want to go then you see
at the bottom of the sea so
you're not good enough for that or
it's it's not good enough for you
how did we get there where were
you going to go
oh so you're not committed to build
your own submersible
i'm sorry about titanic you just rewatched
it because my friend nicole parker is
yeah titanic totally right now on titanic
yeah um and so but solidarity cheney
just put it on and i was
like oh i'll watch this with you
totally that we should watch
she gets one free pass a day
to put on whatever and by the
way when you said you were giving
her a free pass you med like
to have sex with celebrity weight but
she took it to mean putting on
titanic without asking you yeah and you
just got in corrector that's it ain't
that the way that men do things
giving their wife's free passes would mean
would a man do of his bitch
one person that movie is pretty much
exact i have not seen since it
was in theaters yeah pretty much i
remembered pretty much everything except for the
evil butler that is remember that cowls
henchmen anti
alfred he's an anti alfred wow you'll
get this soon i get it now
and he weirdly has ah he gives
too much of a shit about ah
jack dawson you know what i mean
like wow yeah what does that poor
little souls ownership yeah he's so loyal
to zane that he's like he actively
hates this guy
it's so stupid because he's hot and
then also there's so many false endings
with ah yeah you know at the
end where at one point saying style
this is clearly okay it's it's almost
over and then oh no he's they
still have to run back into the
boat with billy zane shooting at them
yeah now the most super that the
boat's sinking we don't need some
guy with a gun yeah yeah yeah
look like it's already a bad situation
that's raised the stakes
ah alright we have to take a
break okay and i don't know what
to tell you other than that great
and we're back and it's time for
a three-acre
oh we're gonna play that one we're
gonna play that one yeah we're playing
um no more jockey yes no well
we played this before and i guess
we didn't play it entirely correctly we're
gonna try to play correctly but look
trying to play correct it's all about
it's ah it's it's not about if
we're playing it correctly or not correctly
it's about our fun while we played
and if we're not having fun
then we've played correctly oh you know
what if we're not having fun then
you probably are and if we are
having fun you probably aren't yeah and
that's just the way the world that
that's just the way it works really
that's just the way it works remember
just the way it works ok this
is submitted by john okay he says
this is also a popular game from
taskmaster the british show i say mr
dickens all you going to write another
story very good british shoe christmas is
coming mr dickens
but you have another carroll
okay here's the rules the basic thing
you blame has it's own wiki by
the wind that's just a little too
much player orders determined by coin toss
players take turns naming a person you
are not going to toss a coin
by the way we don't carry cash
okay three of them is a cashless
podcast district generally a celebrity or other
well-known person
and a category that person fits subsequent
plays must not breach any of the
categories it's already already but here's here's
what it is we name a person
example as kanye west and we say
no more rappers and i say albert
einstein no more scientists now we can't
we can't name
anyone who's a scientist or a rapper
at this point so then that's great
then i would say meryl streep no
more actresses and i'm now your fuck
and now we're playing the game and
i was
we're in it we got written it
then tricked ourselves into places that were
so i would say annie liebowitz no
more photographers okay
now can i say peter o'toole no
more actor yes yes
ah
john f kennedy no more presidents
john wilkes booth no more people who
have assassinated presidents okay
um
albert fish no more cannibals
his yeah his name he should just
eaten fish but his name was fish
yeah that site also he's like start
eating himself that would have made him
feel more like a cannonball my god
maya angelou no more writers ah ooh
writers in general yeah it's what writers
writers write very broad
okay if i'm pow well i suppose
postpone know you got ah that's alright
bob oh no i can't say him
because you said writers you almost had
him good this is why it's hard
okay ah ok ok ok ok ok
ok ok ok ok ok ok ok
ok ok ok ok ok joan jett
no more rockstars yeah
none taken
umm bab are no more elephants oh
yeah
oh
marge simpson no more cartoon characters yeah
um
that
the velociraptor from your movie i forget
his name but chris whatever it does
is always is always petting him yeah
ducky ducky no more dinosaurs yeah
it's a barney
um actually i can barney rubble no
more caveman wait that's a cartoon cartoon
cartoon you're out was out to oh
god okay we're playing that seriously um
or or this has first name someone
who falls loses so we can just
say that he's a loser know why
don't you guys go okay okay
yeah um you don't want to be
a loser i already am awe
um tesla no more inventors
i thought we oh no that was
who did you say albert einstein was
which scientist scientist yeah tesla is the
same probably fuck around ah man yeah
okay let's do it again okay right
reverse order hold a second here's something
interesting yeah ah
um the game i've been used until
a player challenges that name fisherman early
category we did that if blair concedes
to a challenge the game is over
in the challenger wins following the naming
of a category a player can ask
name another to have their opponent name
another person who falls into that category
oh person fails to name another so
you could have said name another and
i would
i've had to name another scientist and
i would have said steven you would
have had to name another inventor who
is not a scientist that's what you
mean no like someone who doesn't who
would pass the test i don't know
what i mean i just read what
was on the lucky because i like
what i'm saying is harder and not
the rules okay
i like what i'm saying is more
like a game where it's like oh
we do this rely time where we
try to change the game and we
were like you'd be like no you
didn't get it and go with the
name and other and then you'd like
i can't because i can't think of
someone who fits that category as well
it's inventor no
i want to start us off okay
um cara de levine no more models
barney fife no more policemen
um
mickey mouse
no more cartoons
um
ah anne hathaway no more actresses johnny
bench no more baseball players okay yeah
ah harry kallis and more baseball announcers
dennis rodman no more basketball players mr
bean no more funny people
okay
kim jong woo no more dictators
um donald trump nobody who is in
home alone two
nobody wow
no work no bar no more peoples
who wasn't home or to joe pesci
oh no yeah yeah oh yeah me
too
this made me think of joe pesci
i forgot he was oh wow but
i made me think of him because
he wasn't due okay so the specific
socratic good but name another name of
the person who wasn't in home who
was wasn't home alone two oh um
um um daniel what's his last name
oh my god why would you go
macaulay culkin yeah okay i'm hey would
i do that see it was hard
enough it was hard alright um ok
it's it's i get i get it
i get it i gotta go go
go go i gotta get mario andretti
no more race car drivers
um
excuse me i'm so parched i'm saying
macaulay culkin maybe so thirsty david byrne
no more singers
nirmal armstrong
no more space travellers neil lane no
more ring salesman from the bachelorette
well i can't say jostens
to be here
that beers um the hoagies and grinders
um
oh my god oh my god he's
losing it pete or beauty no more
piano player okay sally jesse raphael no
more talk show hosts
michelle obama no more first ladies
um megan markle no more former royalty
for her she's i guess she yeah
you can do current royalty i know
i love that open for you hey
thank you
um
but you can't do funny people
oh has anyone gotten to know no
one's done and no one was funny
you know i technically did i guess
because people are beauty was a comedian
oh he was yeah you're out and
oh and he's not around and shit
okay you gotta challenge him okay okay
okay um
okay ah johnny appleseed no more gardeners
okay it should be easy enough
um the constant etc baba duke no
more fictional nor libertarian
no more queer icons were fixing the
skerries
um
walter cronkite no more news people walter
e smith no more furniture sellers loses
well to use yeah we build
i guess that answers my question yeah
um
she put timers on it it's hard
yeah two three oh wait why am
i
cutting down from something yes one two
three four
ah shinzo abbe no more prime ministers
okay
he's too funny
learning prince william newmark current royalty vince
william gray grint prince prince
well i guess if he still prints
or media programs no he's he's still
like okay so that's still crazy when
the grinch stole christmas yeah yeah once
the king dies then he becomes king
um do you think if by the
way he passes away harry suddenly like
a everything's all good with ah i
thought he'd never leave yeah um
yeah yeah i do think that yeah
everything's cool right i mean all that
all that stuff about me being i
think that um but people ppp ppp
the game is without any kangaroo no
more captains okay um mister rogers no
more pbx show
characters
my character he's a character
can't say captain phillips can't sign i
to say nor the guy who in
the middle becomes a captain he's captain
now
ah
purr purr purr purr purr purr purr
but damn that to me
of metallica never had
hello
alright i to think this game is
it's ah it's it's the point where
as a listener you have to go
who who would you say if you
like pick any person in the world
pick any yeah yeah just pick some
who would you say pick any person
in the world who would you saying
who fits all those categories child i
think you've got it but i think
she was a pbx i think she
cbs she was so small
funny yeah again i when you're out
but challenger name and other now their
wives nbd yes i know yes we
don't know what we mean oh the
frugal gourmet oh thought pause you got
your ass you smack your urmia frugal
gourmet style michelle malkin never free
ma ma una caja a frugal my
gourmet please oh would you go through
with her or what would you do
if if this gourmet or maybe the
fruit do
well guys that's it yeah i'm sure
we played it wrong still and that's
why i say that's why you listen
i bet i played it i'm sure
i played it or not well played
slowly moving
you said shut up
he said gay rights he said um
so look if you want to write
to us since a three shift from
you to say oh yeah right yeah
although i saw an instagram following grade
a and if you'd like to call
us just dial hey
eg claims eight navy great if you
i have a show on august fourth
that you can come to in-person or
livestream dynasty oh my god please please
come to my show at lodge room
in highland park sunday july ninth i
don't know why it's so hard to
tell sell tickets to this fucking show
it is a great show runs out
of town
join ninth yeah you don't have ah
the holiday weekends just like started expanding
to the week before and the weekend
i've not noticed that but i'm saying
stop that practice yes and get to
this show come to the show it's
a variety show it's comedy music like
i i put so much work and
love into the show it's really good
and it baffles down
that i can sell out in other
cities but i you know it's a
what the hail a struggle whoop but
look those good lebar mummy whoop huh
i mean look i have a show
coming up who do you in august
but i don't want to say what
it is yet in case we haven't
talked about it but yeah as i
fall beyond the lookout los angeles who's
michael mcdonald also shows oh shows along
with the duty
oh the audience it's just kids
news for kooks too
oh no no to explain what a
tv news i'm like michelle and i'm
here with dupes for kids will learn
that your last name was doobie doobie
brothers were giving kids a big fence
oh kids need display full well how
bad was that recording that re-run did
going to be it was just mentioned
on the tiny portable table and i
guys wanna listen to it at home
for fun a worthless but he was
being paid by some shady guy that's
true when i'm worthless that i made
one of crowded house
house in nineteen eighty nine and u
c san diego oh no scott they're
here oh shit anyway when guys say
ooh ambulance hello
five is right
bye bye
uh