three
see ya
group up thumbs up oh wow zoe
wow he's out we pavement maui wowee
i'm sending oh lu i simply cannot
drive fifty five you think sammy hagar
says maui
oh yeah oh wow a couple whoa
well the lava down town sammy hagar
what have you started a sister chain
of restaurants just for women called maui
wowee sister jane
what is maui wowee mean we'd yeah
good good weed from whites but why
oh why oh why is it just
for women it's like restaurant's secret deodorant
yeah it's it's a way it sounds
more feminine yeah that's cool i'm i'm
starting off strong remains women's weed
i love when products are gendered yeah
yeah like i just loved do shoes
hey everyone welcome to three-time they have
this very they have those hershey candy
bars those hershey candy bars what are
the ones where are the women why
candy bars may just they highlight the
word she in the middle of her
she knew oh wow real yes and
are they are they pink or something
or is it just exactly the same
she
e is a color i keep memphis
pink or similar colors on the actual
arm not the pack no no no
no on the package that's like halloween
when reese's peanut butter cups highlights the
e yeah
that i think is cute they actually
they should add extra ease for halloween
i think i think a halloween gimmick
is cute i think a christmas thing
is hugh i think a breast cancer
gimmick is cute so cute
i think they should make races for
blind people and like cross out the
sea on races what like ghostbusters
there's no see those it's not as
e it's s e a past reeses
it's races oh yeah we're gonna have
this debate look wow this is my
people's pronunciation we call it reeses reeses
pieces but that is the stray nose
starts to make sense it doesn't exempt
it makes
all the sense in the world darling
woke his pieces is spelled normal darling
ah yes reeses species r e s
e apostrophe s e c yes reeses
pcs shouldn't races just lean into it
and put out a brand called reeses
pieces they shake to make people happy
like you know it could be east
of the mississippi if you want they
should do regional
yeah they should do regional products in
every area they should oh wow the
accent is put it put them outside
by side and see which sells better
and then just change your name to
it whichever fun oh great permanent names
permanent name change depending on what i
know
a fun promotion but no it's a
permanent name change i mean i know
we have talked about this hell it's
not cool i'm positive we have but
i loved when i got to vote
on the new eminem color and i
wish they would do what did you
vote for deer blue i think
black because i'm thinking well i guess
heroic cool options black eminem's yeah there
are black imams aren't there
oh those are beans oh shit you're
thinking of beans stupid eating beans you
all banks little bags of raw beef
yea and you think it tastes good
i hate i think chocolate taste horrible
youth chocolate tastes horrible let me get
this straight you ate a bag of
beans thought it was chocolate now
you're ready to render your judgment
it's the only chocolate i've ever had
did you ever but when you're a
kid you ever been into baker chocolate
and thinking it was gonna be good
and then it turned out to be
a horrible angle yeah but that's a
real tough stuff and once you know
you never did it again oh that's
real oh i did it four times
after that really
i was like this maybe i bit
into the wrong end this time for
sure the wrong end yeah i should
eat clumps of brown sugar really tracks
the tracks yeah it was really good
just don't take clumps what do you
mean when you say use to you
mean like any weeks ago
i would like eddie murphy that klum
says such things i would eat a
lot thank ya took me a second
i would climb up on the counter
and get my low pause in the
bag eyebrow which i'm up on the
counter would you get a box or
ah sigh latter i i think i
was able to do though like push
up coming although there was a point
where i
i was climbing up there to get
these special cookies that my mom had
that were some keebler cookies that i
wasn't allowed to have why not they
they were hers what does happen i
would eat them because i would eat
them all and always on
so shattered allowed to have their own
cookies moms need to smart wells imac
well i'm marketing a smart wells cookie
tomas
and in the commercials a mom hiding
in a closet eating cookies like an
animal so used to client you you
would climb up and there's a jar
of brown sugar and you just so
sugar whoa lauren are you kidding i
love that song but why did you
do not disturbed so um i did
write that that's my new song called
he's calling and it's all about us
christ
the rapture yeah like he's calling you
home that's that's mike's friend joey and
this computer is connected to mike's phone
and every time i'm doing a podcast
joey calls i swear to gwot hey
joey knock it the fuck off and
i am disturbed and it's still rang
what's up ah joey maybe my best
to have it on do not disturb
rb how you doing joey that's what
i always wonder
what was your favorite treat to sneak
to sneak i don't i also snuck
flintstones vitamins oh i like my ter
um chocolate chips out of the bag
of course nestle toll house chocolate chips
that's honestly when you're in a pinch
that'll do yeah sure oh yeah um
pig um and i like
here you talking to the the pig
i'm saying that'll do i mean i
also i also liked you know i
mean taking a spoon to a candidate
taking a spoon to a can of
frosting oh yeah that'll do it too
i used to be able to lick
the beaters if my mom was making
you lick the beaters that's what she
said
yeah i like your oh yeah i
always liked always like the bowl that's
made you get billy virus permission oh
did you did your mom didn't beat
to have frosting beaters oh yeah no
no i like i like netball that
was part of bacon looking for you
it never deigned to lick the beaters
is out your theaters i'm just like
gonna say i licked the beaters nasty
oh yeah heard or haven't kevin say
that say that save it save it
use it release it put it out
there and of course it's a child
a famously ate an entire bottle of
flintstones chewable vitamins you'll see those were
really good i would highly mature were
horrid so you did your wear whatever
i mean strong
bones and stuff yeah oh my god
my bones are like diamonds they were
so they were so hard they were
so dense um i used to jump
out of buildings why don't y'all make
one flintstone vitamin as big as the
bottle yeah and you could eat it
like you gotta live with yeah it's
a deal
that sounds really fun maybe you could
fry it you know what coated with
some bready and yeah yeah my mom
was very unhappy and she never bought
those again they were too good honestly
i mean like i have had them
in more recent history and they're not
good what
like as an adult i ate it
to see if it was really good
it's crazy that flintstones like cornerstone thing
aren't they now i'm really sorry now
but i wonder when our vitamin or
the no other cartoon particular cartoon you
think spongebob didn't want to do vitamins
so bad and yeah like yeah we
can't we can't horn in on the
flint
stones you think the fairly odd parents
didn't have a formula for vitamins that
they couldn't use you know bojack horseman
did gene i just saying they still
have them and they also make the
most gummies which is really too good
yeah did you come in vitamins are
great a smorgasbord of flintstones vitamins and
various forums i
i would make a shark coterie like
the candy shop cooter of flintstone vitamins
gummies flintstones gummies not real who do
you who do you like to eat
the most i love to eat fred
who did they make the knick fred
they make barney barney wilma wilma the
babies damn ma'am what about the heady
hobbles and bam bam down when they
would be the same size as the
other ones alright let me see them
yeah they'd be the same site let
me see i'm gonna look at all
the picture they should be to scale
oh my god they look so gross
they're like the worst color okay so
they
i have fred wilma bam bam the
dinosaur dino um they have barney wilma
and barney the damn no betty i
mean betty bart barney betty and bam
bam okay no penny realised they all
know they do have pebbles i sent
bam bam toys i don't know they
please
the mom and dad the baby and
the dinosaur okay the moms the dads
the babies the dinosaur no mister seeley
and yeah what's up with mr slate
what about ah the way what's the
name of the great gazoo or whoever
there's nothing huh i love you flavor
options to put the gazoo in there
there but i don't remember there being
different flav
evers i remember them all the different
colors there there's like a there's like
a dusty red there's a dustin dirt
orange the beautiful gc ca yeah yeah
we i do remember the i love
the texture we have to yeah to
read a chocolate message from our sponsor
flintstones vitamins butter and flintstones wanting to
say they are welcoming everyone with a
noose
you can get five thousand cans sent
to your house every month with the
code but much
you know ah people talk a lot
about yabba dabba doo but what about
yabba dabba d as in vitamin but
you need more of it what does
cycling doing yoga as well what about
yabba dabba don't forget to take your
vitamins isn't it weird that the flintstones
are extinct it's so strange they are
bone their entire family line is extinct
yeah there does only their descendants who
is it real girl there ma somebody
descended from the no there has all
gone like doing roger stone me go
back to my yucky romance history
i think roger stone sharon stone of
course of course stone follows stone phillips
was he this good so rolling stone
those arthur kent i'm sorry the rolling
stones
all of them
every single digital pilot their brothers people
don't realize yeah the rolling stones are
all brothers they're a family yeah yeah
they're septuplets
um can i tell you about a
new show that i watched oh god
i wish you would a
sorry um this is lawrence topics um
there is a horny topics really yeah
it's danny recap yeah yeah forces yeah
of course like you were gonna tell
us about some narrative show you watched
oh my god so there's this show
that's fantastic and i wanna recommend it
and i think you're both going to
call bullshit on this show and i
don't i don't really want to hear
up one hundred percent so the show
is on netflix it's called tyler henry
life after death this is tyler henry
the the medium who
was on the show hollywood medium as
he was a young teen and he
was a medium that would read like
celebrities but was he the hollywood medium
yeah so this is now he's he's
now he's a bit older shingle yeah
and then in the whole show is
i liked the hollywood medium but it
was a little bit a little bit
cheesy for me this show and that's
saying some visualize it right
is he over eighteen now yeah he's
in his twenties he has um his
what twice a week last nine somewhere
in there somewhere in there yeah he
has a waitlist of three hundred thousand
people trying to talking from him whoa
and then they selected people from that
wait list to be on the show
so it's just regular people and he
does these readings
and he's so spot on and the
there's just crazy things that i didn't
want to give any spoilers because some
of it's so fun for the people
out there who will watch this but
he reads people like he will just
say say things that even on the
drive are saying like he reads people
yeah paris is burning style when he
drives over he's like he's in the
car he doesn't know where he's go
knowing he's being driven and he doesn't
know who it's going to be in
hell like z paul you know it
but he'll be able to tell what
helped scotty's media i think it's going
to be some women okay you know
where he's going always he can see
ahead of him
we can also see far ahead of
him ah where do you stand on
mediums it's been shown believe that yeah
i knew i knew you'd say oh
look if his waiting list is so
long some of these people on a
cough up the money and go see
my girl teal swan and get yelled
at who's that oh she's in she's
this uh
um ah grifter who there's the a
series about their nail the deep end
teal swallow wait i just write i
just read a read i read an
instagram post saying that i should watch
that because if i liked nick sam
i'll love this is that true yeah
it's only four episodes so very manageable
can you tell me too much she
he is a coy character i can't
wait i wanna watch this and so
is it a is it a reality
show of her or is it just
watching a documentary about her and she
was literally a grifter that's known yeah
it's it's very obvious when you watch
this thing can she sue you paul
for saying ah ooh thought about that
why are you going assume me
unforeseen no but i'm just saying like
you don't believe in it so you
might just say that about well because
she's not she's not just a medium
that's that's like her her supernatural gifts
are just like a sort of side
thing it's a sort of way she
is like she's able to prove what
she's saying to people is like well
i could talk to dead people
so they said this or whatever she's
rightly like a self-help guru um it's
very intense and she is clearly like
a like when you watch this thing
you're very much aware that she thought
this would portray her in a positive
light oh the doc uh-huh yes like
she doesn't realize that people
will because she has enough people that
are willing to pay for her nonsense
um she doesn't realize like and the
average person looking in on this is
gonna say oh she's like a monstrous
person who has severe ah issues like
you're yeah trying to say that she's
so far up her own ass yes
she can see
at our eyeballs yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
that's what you're trying to say she's
so far gone she can stay out
of her eyeballs yeah that's what it
was trying to say yeah so couldn't
get it out so but lorin you
you believe what she said while i
believe in it when someone seems to
really have the ability i feel that
i can not believe in it when
it feels fake or it feels
like you know i've had some experiences
where i with um mediums i did
a podcast where i went and met
with a few people that's part of
that was called it was called psychic
show doesn't exist anywhere because it's probably
on stitcher premium um it's so it's
so irrelevant to my life now that
like i don't know i can't even
imagine
that would be that interesting honestly um
not that it matters i guess what
my life is but you don't i
mean i don't know just like a
long time ago i feel like at
the time i remember talking to you
about it and you i hope it's
okay to say this that you felt
like you ah this sort of seeker
aspect of it for you was kind
of satisfied
by that experience yeah it wasn't something
that you really pursued much yeah i'm
not like somebody who's always checking in
with some medium about like what i
should do next my life although i
do know a lot of people who
use astrologers and think and i think
that's fun and i think it can
be really accurate and also i think
can be really helpful like one thing
that i think i love watching the
long island medium and
i even the times when i don't
believe it the people are so like
warmed by it it helps them i
feel that it's a valid like source
of you know comfort to people that
like if they feel oh this person
just told me that what i'm doing
is the right thing and that makes
them feel good that like that's really
amazing i mean people
remember on video games and it makes
them feel good so same thing you
know it's exactly sure free exactly the
same well and as real as this
but tyler henry gone tooting around and
diddy kong stadium can i give one
spoiler and people out there i'm sorry
if you want if it's spoiled check
thirty seconds this man just accused me
of going tuning around and donkey kong
stadium i said diddy kong diddy kong
forgive me p diddy kong he didn't
call theirs anyways over i wanna see
ten anything with that p down did
the theme song to godzilla he should
return it for kong and it would
have been p diddy kong yeah so
wait let me tell you go on
the island tell me tell me what
you think about
this ok i'll give you my unvarnished
opinion i promise i'll give you my
gym varnished opinion oh wow no no
what i mean would you believe urn
so he said would you believe no
he did not that's jonathan madness
would you believe oh no it's ah
maxwell smart would you believe oh that's
right oh here's my shares what i'm
why i'm inclined to believe okay let's
just do what interruptions just don't just
give you like whatever you want whatever
you say we're going to tell you
the truth and are true and that's
just our truth no matter you know
it's not as
necessarily or treaters what i liked about
the show because they're filming it like
documentary style that he says they're day
that become the get proven within hours
that there's no way he could have
known one example being he's doing a
reading for two people that he um
knew
he was younger that goes back to
visit them and he basically brings up
do you know anything about a fire
they're saying it's too hot do you
know anything about our area wait okay
somebody's somebody's communicating him from hell is
that what's going on they were saying
they were saying don't trust this guy
he's like that's what i'm getting when
i'm getting the the
images that i'm getting are don't touch
the fire it's too hot do you
know anything about a house fire or
fire in a building there going no
no that doesn't ring any bells he's
like ma i don't know what to
tell you that's what i was getting
like he's so in my opinion it
felt like oh maybe he's wrong and
then he sits an hours later hey
say it was a fire that someone
later confessed to
setting so it wasn't and it was
ah an in a chinese like sort
of museum of sorts like ah center
where they showed like historical artifacts as
these people were at that they work
they owned that they owned and it
got set on fire by a person
a transient it said later confessed and
they were going through town and they
just set a fight so decided hey
would never set it on fire whew
that's a that's a historical building i
wanna give you my janet varnished opinion
um i don't buy it and i
think there's always an explanation for these
things that was an example of one
that was like there there's a camera
filming him he says
this thing and then it came through
like it's a little different when it's
so a dead person you know sire
at talking if if it was like
a fire at their house
maybe and a serious fire not like
not just like it was a serious
fire know like noah's i'm saying a
serious fire at their house but it's
a fire and why does it matter
if it's not serious meaning like a
grease fire you put out in twenty
seconds oh well yeah right that would
that would be less impressive you're saying
like but without but that would be
something that i think people would go
see he said the fire and you
put it out in twenty seconds that's
what because of his warning good for
you can i also say twenty seconds
yeah long time to have a fire
in your home that you're trying to
put out
yeah well you know agrees fire i'm
just saying it's a good show i
think there will always be something in
your life that you can trace back
oh no i do think that is
realistic like that and i actually like
i've talked about this on another podcast
where i i basically did a example
of how i could do that same
skill and like lead you into saying
things that make it makes
sense then it sounds like i just
came up with also i do i
see how that's a thing but i
feel i believe in i believe in
tyler henry i do i believe in
taiwan i love to have a reading
with him and i'm putting out there
he believes in you i'm sure he
does and let me may i make
this is on topic this is a
recommendation i'd like to make it's time
for paul's recommendations
oh newly segment i think yeah i
think we have a song do something
like yes yeah okay yes he is
a guy and he likes stoats he's
a guy and he likes stuff it's
paul's recommend oh my my laptop with
paul f tompkins nice hey every
body ah there's a a podcast called
ghost church ah that is from ah
jamie loftus who does great ah journalistic
podcasts and it's about the um the
spiritualist movement which is essentially like mediums
people communicating with the dead and doing
saying stuff like that and how they
are still going today um this this
specific sort of new quasi religion um
that um ah does ah you know
ah psychic readings and stuff like that
not psychic reads but they they they
the their whole thing is they communicate
with the spirit realm and blah blah
blah um and even though the founders
of this movement have been were discredited
a long time ago like in their
own lifetimes the thing still like they
confess to ah just like faking all
these you know spirit visitations noises shit
like that like they they eventually okay
okay after they were well that's interesting
i would like to listen to that
yeah it's from it's great one more
thing yeah is that helps just one
more thing we've learned yeah can you
sing this song it's final na okay
one oh really
with lowering is
one mah things sound like there was
an argument in the middle of that
theme so i think there was and
we have to recreate that every it's
weird themes
i like it to songwriters yeah two
people start seeing you at the same
time completely different songs that have a
mini arc
it's a third person comes in he
will say things that only that person
would not really specific thing only that
person would know they haven't talked about
it like for example his high school
teacher who you see on the show
he like in high school came up
to her and said something specific like
lorraine says you
it's okay to cry or whatever and
she was like she had just that
someone who had died he didn't know
that she hadn't told him that what
if i came up to me it
was impossible to find it out the
secret
it was it was real what if
i came up huh
brian says that you can finally let
go
i'd be like
not mean
riling a guy who got brown so
it's not you it's not me but
like a guy brian says i can
find like oh that really doesn't mean
anything to you what if i said
to you but if my love my
it might be wrong i might have
i might have heard it wrong if
my here's what i i love what
if i said to you let's we'll
play around this real quick what if
i said
just to put if i walked in
the room when you both were in
there and i said this ah there's
an older female figure who's coming through
and she said she wants me to
tell you she's proud of you does
that mean anything to me
lauren as an old lady in the
future obviously the message was meant for
paul he's crying what if i send
to you the minute you walked in
the joint
i could tell what if i said
ok lauren this is okay this is
real what if i said this is
dee has a message for you
working sensing in d c working d
do you know anything with a d
i do so anything with a d
a dinosaur wait wait i think take
your vitamins i think it might be
dees nuts huh hey how did you
get in touch with them ah i
told these nuts never to contact me
grave ah alright we have to write
we'll be right back
and we're back we're back yeah oh
where where where are you where on
zoom where in the world is your
friend paul tomkins i am in los
vegas nevada what are you doing there
i am in an hotel room well
my um
what's her name janey my wife her
her father and his wife are ah
traveling back home they were in hawaii
they're on a layover here and then
they're going to continue on to their
home and ah so we decided to
meet them here and spend some time
with them wow that's nice i thought
you were doing a show
yo know where every performed in las
vegas never know where are you staying
oh i'm not going yeah oh come
on just tell me where you stay
in vegas are you in the tip
of the nose of the sphinx is
there a string the hotel where the
tip of the nose of the sphinx
um where does not have a nose
where in the empire state buildings
like new york where we are at
a hotel called the aria what does
thou or even heard of oh is
this halo oh i'm doing little mermaid
i was doing little mermaid as well
oh i was also doing little mermaid
three
we gotta try a little birds didn't
envy you when did you gamble it
all paul you're not no money yeah
your life i gamble with my time
for sure um yeah but i i'm
not a big gambler i might gamble
while i'm here janie likes to play
craps really which is what's her what's
her number that she likes to get
for
what is crops i feel like i
just always go along three roll the
dice roll the dice and hope exactly
like the first your first roll if
you get a seven you win but
if you get any thing else other
than two
is that right too or yeah she's
got a seventy win but if you
get anything else other than two and
then you have already lost and i've
seen this you have to roll again
and match that number before you get
another seven because seven is the most
common number that you can roll and
so you only can roll once in
the next person rolls know you knew
you bet you can roll as
as long as you usually when you
crap out as they say meaning you
get a seven before you match your
point it's customary to like pass the
dice on because you're no longer lucky
if that makes sense but that seems
fun that seems like roulette and that
seems like equally random craps is the
funnest table in the casino yeah because
everybody's having a good time because panda
everyone is
starting on you yeah yeah yeah like
hey we believe in you that you're
going to do it and if someone's
on a big streak where they're just
like hitting their point or like you
know rolling seven on the first roll
yeah like just sharing big party if
you hear cheering in a casino that's
where it's coming from oh yeah and
it is fun it's fun to it's
fun to just like be around it
you know to see everybody like
ike get theirs so into it and
people are joking with each other and
encouraging each other and shit like that
it's really it is fun it really
is it's fun it's fun we used
to play at um at mister show
with a certain person had made their
own craps table that they were wearing
to parties maybe we'll see him on
tv very soon unos
ah hey any of us ah you
know have had wonderful show business career
so you could see any of this
on tv very hey it's true it's
true he might be on shows that
we've never even dreamed of being like
like the news
ah strange trip it's been yeah well
i mean everyone everyone in life the
older if we're if we're lucky enough
to get old we're all going to
turn crazy know you don't think my
my parents all of their friends from
back in the day
are all nuts all their church friends
yeah yeah they're all insane
yeah that is cool you know it
is pretty cool but you know do
you know who i look at as
norman lear who is yeah kept kept
his ah marbles and his politics and
you know it's true seems like still
seems like a cool guy he's almost
one hundred years old right maybe it's
the i don't have to get bad
opinions to have it
older people who happens to get older
probably also have bad opinions when they
were younger maybe but i but i
also think that the internet preys upon
old people in and is is a
way will just mean it's not just
old people but lonely people in general
and people well there was a really
interesting profile oh my god did you
hear about that woman eleanor rigby she
got yeah
by the internet yeah but they're not
there's a profile on yeah i a
woman in the midwest who is supporting
a particularly odorous political candidate and um
it was a profile on her and
it was really the the part that
i found really interesting was her talking
about how without this she feels very
adrift in her life and like nothing
matters and she's like ah she just
feels this existential dread and she's like
you know she was talking about she
was building ah ah floor for for
these political rally she was having she's
like i can hold this screw and
i know that
real and i'm real but you know
the more time i spend on the
internet you know i don't know it
was very interesting just that that people
people people's lives they feel like you
know what is the whole point of
it and they sort of feel like
you know if they attached themselves to
these really weird opinions that it's making
life worthwhile you know
well what's so strange to me is
like there's other communities you don't mean
like you don't have to fall into
that community if you're looking if you're
looking to to ah you know connect
with people there's there's communities that don't
feel like
anyone who disagrees with politically is a
pedophile you know what i mean yeah
like there's there's people there's hobbies and
stuff yeah there's like model trains one
or more old people get into pokemon
it's right i want a playing animal
crossing they would love animal crossing they
would love it that maybe they feel
like they can't pick up the controllers
with their arthritic hands oh i need
to pay ridge but i'm out of
bows
raccoon will evict me
is that what it is i've never
played it oh that's what it is
yeah i've played before crossing is weird
it's a weird game you've played what
i played the course on ah ah
the mario kart eight yeah of course
i mean it's a weird game but
it was like really a comforting game
with being in the pandemic i had
never played before was but it was
like my little world that i was
in
and it felt just like your world
was not constricting but rather expanding exactly
i was going to say do you
remember we visit each other's islands i
do remember ah and that was only
one time it was always so great
we'd go into each other's stores now
is always fun to see when you
had some nice yeah
gotta say i got a switch recently
and matt apodaca like said hey here's
my friend name befriend me and then
nothing has happened here's my friend name
wow like how damn i so am
i you have to do it anytime
i'm on there it looks and it
goes met up dog is not online
so
oh what am i supposed to do
you just wait he was hard to
know he holds all the cards yeah
well it's all the car yeah hey
matt come on i'll go on right
now by the way one of the
people halfway one of the things maybe
why he's not granting your friend request
is you're pronouncing his name wrong because
it's a potato why actually thought it
was it's made to a paddock
aiko made a potato yes so crazy
i thought it was april's and bienes
reno thanks yeah and that's his nickname
this is nice it's inmate april's and
bienes aicpa aco what yes it's incredible
that's in crisis big news this is
big big news big big
news this is what is what are
you doing oh anyway my favorite my
favorite gambling is i played the animal
crossing slot machine you did like no
doubt
yeah i'm pretty sure there probably is
that's what it makes me laugh when
you go look at the slot machines
and they're all these like trying to
there's a cheers one and yeah that's
how you get in there man i'm
like oh they only see one yeah
such as anyone very popular there's a
golden girl slot machine people really enjoy
yeah i'd like to see their friends
while they're gamba
oiling it makes it more fun yes
where's the parks and rec flop machine
i'm sure they have when they have
big bang theory i mean anywhere is
the green acres slot machine green acres
is the place to me whereas aren't
the arthur slot machines says shit top
between the moon and new
a even better movie
but thanks my dude the remake i
was talking about the cartoon hey i
forgot it's called hey arn oh arthur
sir alright mister cartoon just arthur just
arthur arthur the aardvark oh i was
thinking of hey arnold he's the football
head man right the hell are we
doing i don't know does anyone enjoy
listening to this no tell you what
why don't we
take a break let's get our lives
together okay like i mean let's move
in together the three of us yes
three that's my boy think about it
alright we'll be right back don't think
too low
oh nah we're back hey you know
what i heard i heard the oh
no tiktok song in the wild once
and it was very weird wow some
real song yeah oh no oh no
oh no no no no it's got
oman
when when gordon ramsay's daughter cracked the
egg on his head huh yeah no
yeah that's the sole right god yeah
that song is playing during it yes
well maybe it's a song that people
put over but it sounds the song
sounds slightly different in real life there's
like a weird filter on the on
it that when the people use it
for when the people use it for
desktop when the
people use it for tiktok when the
people huge for tiktok their asia le
roux sound known the boys take lorne
and that's the way that dishing it
now when they do it to their
voice scott and i don't know while
we're talking bout why is tick tock
wat is
all of this stuff oh he's the
oldest overall never heard of tick tick
woo
oh ooh talk
black black speaking of blobby maddie boo
bop boo baby we have our wow
we have a brand new segment we're
gonna debut and we've never done this
before we've been talking about it for
a wow wow and it's finally time
it's it's come to pass that we
are able to do the segment a
while that really going to happen
an oh my god i can't even
believe it i know i'm ready for
this i went my perry easy i
wet not so segment i we all
wet ourselves we all concentrate and we
pee our pants alone these um be
in the paw t e p t
a proof copy pasting that's
holly know what does peaked
ah we finally got around to singing
pee pee in the potty abby be
in the bad day i'll speaking of
pp and the party we have a
voice oh we violet we came up
with a phone number we gave the
number which is haha input too many
letters but it still works anyway well
doesn't work here's what happens you have
to just stop typing before you get
to the t well you could put
in the two you couldn't you know
if you do that goes do do
do this no number but wait but
wait i did it and it worked
hello um shit on the landline yeah
if you did it on a landline
start dialing but on the phone why
i didn't
biden used to five laura and i
did it for my cellular phone in
the car after one of our recordings
as soon as we got the number
huh huh law
in put coach h doesn't have to
print press call l a i n
your call cannot be completed this dial
is that including is that including the
area code the area code is haha
no it's ha ha ha the area
code before you four five two
for six i'm going to try this
seven eight i'll call it the same
time see if all those years ago
okay because it's four two four two
five two four six seven eight o
can be completed as dialed okay what
if i press the nodes just aha
in pu what if i would have
food you do
haha in poo haha what if i
what if i owe law in poo
doo doo doo getting dupes and i
was doing reach out and reach out
and touch faith as i would reach
out and three yeah and touch oh
in poo look
special guest special guest on the show
special where is she going and what
is she doing she's gone poolside baby
she's a waterpipe oh now she's wet
once she's given us a show jamie
jamie's got a kindle or screaming your
name into my ears
oh you heard okay you heard ya
heart so anyway we have a number
i have a number it's haha in
poo to the tune of reach out
and touch faith and ah we've finally
got some voicemails and we're going here's
what we're gonna do we're gonna play
some voicemails we're gonna figure out what
to do do we ever want to
play voicemail what i
i know it why do we use
just mining giving paula massage
i didn't even catch that yeah it
was crazy she like came up behind
you and went like why she couldn't
just give me a saas oh yeah
really yeah i'd like one to janey
she could give me a challenge
since it's exempt zones okay so we're
gonna la la in pu this segment
basically and this is like a cheer
this is a segment where we decide
whether we ever want to play voicemails
ever again yes and it's a bit
of a game this is a good
game
alright so kevin why don't you hit
us with a voicemail that you personally
have deemed worthy of listening to one
podcast and what by the way we
made chevron listened to all of these
beforehand all of them he refused to
do it and we said no you
have to do it we need him
do it we pay your salaries what
like that lady in the patti lupone
yeah exactly
and so he then he was forced
to listen to them all but then
we didn't force him to sort them
out into like this is worthwhile or
this isn't worthwhile he actually paid us
to do that it was listen to
them all and let us sort them
out yeah but then he was like
can you just can i pay you
five hundred dollars and
for the for the honor of sorting
these into different categories and make no
mistake this is for the honor it's
for the glory of law yeah that's
right so we let we allowed him
to do that we split the five
hundred three ways and um so now
we're gonna hear the fruits of his
labor law read it rip ah early
in foot l
ah l a input freedom goodbye perfect
okay so yeah i've made my decision
well hold on a second we can
make a case by case basis that
kind of thing we don't need we
don't we don't want
that'll that'll he also just sang the
song wrong it's good that we've heard
it to know to know that don't
need that bullshit i am glad that
there's a recording taking up some of
the space in the world
you know sort of and there's only
time which strapped in the way that's
written yeah especially in our heads like
that's now in my head and i've
forgotten about something else yeah that's living
rent free in my head i'm a
charged yeah yeah okay let's get another
voicemail oh yeah this is
keanu reeves okay yeah calling on behalf
stop start if it's whatever is it
oh okay wait i'm remember remember scott
he sounds like that oh that's right
yeah i think it's yeah
pow ah man lucas
anyway thought i'd welcome all of you
aboard to forget it oh no i
don't want any of those six okay
give me one that's really good cabinet
you keep listening to because you love
it so much and you you fall
asleep listening to it and stuff yeah
because you don't use it we don't
want that right no we don't want
agreement we don't we don't want people
doing pretend
voices no ah and talking bullshit no
i want real hardcore and real shit
i want i want people to call
up cry
i want confessions confession like oh yes
confessions we depth read him confessions freedom
confessions we definitely want yeah yeah yeah
hot secrets give them if yeah was
this what was the thing where people
would write little confessions online postsecret postsecret
i want i'm an avid follower i
have many of the books we want
that
it so you will have battle if
you have a low confession like to
make murders
i did say little
little murder please don't want others confessed
to a murder because we have to
figure out what to do with that
information if you emerge kevin was gone
we won't ever hear it if you
burned anyone under five feet tall we'd
like to hear about it yeah that's
horrible
for eleven and under alright if you've
murdered anyone over six foot dulles yeah
alright next voice mail to be judged
i've got some low slung mo hey
wanna freedom gang it's rolling calling home
this file i was calling with a
question for you i've got a nice
class reunion coming up and years and
i was wondering if there was if
you guys had any suggestions for ah
for ways to make it not awkward
um and make it kind of like
almost like a game of it did
you guys go to your high school
class reunion if so what would you
do as a friend
and was it on there was enough
on the cake pie i don't mind
this one although i like my talks
we've talked about it on the show
already we have yeah but you know
i've been i've been to all my
classroom unions my my kind of game
if you will there is to have
sex with my classmates wives yeah oh
good yeah that's fine
game that makes it past one time
well definitely not awkward if it passes
the three minutes
to have sex with all of them
um i didn't go to mine because
i wasn't invited but i did see
like facebook or something that it was
happening on point and i never got
the information was just like a twenty
year it would be ten it was
my ten years your tenure but even
then it was like we already had
facebook and it kind of felt like
i knew what everyone was
and you just ate that is the
thing too yeah yeah that seem weird
in this day and age where you
can keep in touch with people from
your past so easily if i'm gonna
say if why are you going if
you're needing a game to not make
it awkward well i mean the person
wants to see everyone and see what
they're up to yeah you know like
i think i think what what was
refreshing like go into skies
yeah yeah whereas guys sash i'm like
a long wig and then to what's
from boots what are you doing these
days i think what was refreshing about
the ten year for me is just
how everyone was really nervous and everyone
was sort of like feeling judged and
then i had i saw someone that
i kind of bear
rly new and and i was talking
to i was like what are you
up to she's like well i'm unemployed
i'm living with my parents and things
suck and i was like how how
honest now refreshing and she wasn't she
wasn't putting on airs show wasn't trying
to impress anyone i thought that was
really cool and so i decided just
that it would be sort of like
that and i think everyone is really
no
service and everyone is worried and when
you realize that you go in and
just like try to put everyone at
ease and and be non-judgmental because everyone's
no one's judging you everyone's feeling that's
right everybody puts their pants on one
leg at a time it's just that
some people are more successful than you
i don't i jump into my pants
with both yeah that's what i do
to try
but everyone does stupid i stand this
on my like um headboard on like
my tip toes and then i like
leap forward with my feet first it's
really hard cause i can always risk
hitting my head on the wall and
i jumped straight into pants that are
held up by like contraption but i
made yeah here's what i do i
don't put my pants on i get
my pant
tts to get on me i lie
on my back but my legs up
in the air i throw the pants
as high as i can and hopefully
they land oh my leg like the
legs land over me and i can
just fall naturally onto my body i
just i used to lower my old
buddy know you hold on because you
spoke last before paul
now holding your right your conversation hog
i don't have a shit let's not
forget our rules yeah the rules are
it goes if we're ever wants to
talk or you just shut up all
right no no no no what does
he want to talk we shut up
how does that make sense so advice
when shopping for anyone else when always
like you're saying that when you wanna
talk were so
used to be quiet
um alright so advice if you have
if you're asking for advice that's a
decent thing you can call it about
let's hear another voicemail and decide who
step on more and this is killian
north carolina i'm on my lunch break
i'm teaching kids summer camp and it's
a harry potter theme and i don't
know any teaching summer care to kids
and i just wanted to ask you
guys
what fell they know how to do
them because i'm pretty sure they're gonna
assume you're capable of some intense magic
anyhow take care feel later i think
you have to teach this and look
it's far too late as we we
know she's got a lunch break did
we get back to her soon enough
yeah i don't know anything lunch we're
not that number
it doesn't reach any of our homes
so we're not we can't like call
you back what we should do honestly
as we should have a haha input
nine one one number that if it's
an emergency text us in emergencies that
we can get back to them within
twenty minutes and it's four numbers right
it's it's hala input but you're supposed
to stop after h a h a
right and then put in no one
one like a way to remember it
is haha input but only with ya
yeah don't do lie input and then
then add nine one one i remember
because that's when the planes hit you
know
or try to bring try praying to
us yeah we'll listen to prayers
let's get one more kevin let's have
another one hi scott hi paul hi
lauren great to hear you guys so
nice to you thank you this is
my first time so i'm like i'm
um yeah i guess you guys might
just want to update what you're telling
folks you're saved the numbers haha
input when i don't need green tea
at the end there i guess if
you're counting that last day now both
use y and t then swiping your
correct otherwise haha i actually have to
say i was really enjoying i was
enjoying his chi was enjoying his the
way he spoke and i was enjoying
how it felt real yeah
value lovely think he was gonna give
us an update on his life i
know here's that you're just saying don't
call us with things that we've already
just discussed minutes before in the podcast
like we talked about at the beginning
of the segment so what's your point
of view calling in it doesn't make
any sense it's just repetitive but you're
calling right now just hang up also
it's not a
criticism line okay yeah want we want
praise
we want you to pray to us
and we want you to sing it
zenas to us it is right to
give us thanks and praise give us
give us our flowers come on we
deserve them no okay so what do
we want from this we want we
didn't want confessions minor confession minor confessions
not about one niners if people are
soliciting
advice solicitations are fine yeah and a
life raise that you think is um
oh yeah ally interesting yeah journals if
people want to do produced versions of
any of our jingles where we're fine
with that also if anyone wants i
love to play that if anyone wants
to do produced funny prank calls
our four are under ten minutes and
then we can take credit for them
yeah that's great and we released them
as an album yeah that's yeah i
love that all right so remembering style
prank phone calls yeah that are like
with really good voices though exactly sizzle
just so ah please
dial haha in poo and ah nah
no oh no obviously p you are
the problem the problem with pew um
great documentary so ah thank you so
much for the people that called in
we we may never listen to these
ever again
i probably the same ones you meet
i'm gonna have kevin will listen to
those over and over i'm having kevin
burn this onto a cd for me
right now so a lot a lot
and i loved them so much and
they and they made me feel really
good and you know even even the
college correct phone number thank you for
taking the time because yeah thanks to
thank
yeah we saw that overall we loved
it we love you so much but
but we at the same time i
cry tears of joy yeah i just
loved it and i just immense so
much it made so much it meant
so my sajjad sorry much soy
mulatto remember that's ha ha la ou
doom oh hey what a weird disjointed
episode this was and i loved every
minute of it well you know that's
you know yeah that's freedom when one
of us one of us didn't nevada
what do you expect yeah i know
you know there's different rules there did
you guys consider getting together in one
place so it would just be a
two ah zoom window for now we
never considered ah no were you secretly
relieved that i made it so that
you didn't have to be in the
same room with each other i you
know prior i prefer being in the
same room i do over that as
well because it's we have breaking threesome
new wow
whoa did i did early digitally later
in italy leaving chevron just put in
the chat k p the the guy
fucking mid a game a game that
needed work and we bagged him to
work on this idea for weeks for
weeks he refused to talk to us
and now he finally just emailed
here it is from k p hello
three pool fun i like it i
like i'd hate to be a total
biff don't get that but it seems
to me you are all too chicken
to play my three tow it so
it's ah it's back to the future
okay because he clock will chicken and
then bok bok in parentheses bok bok
bok chicken choice why
thank you mom it's i don't know
bach but thanks thanks easter bunny bok
bok everyone is calling out for junket
but you cannot bring yourself to do
it i guess out of fear of
having too much fun well when he
threatened hell no i mean he's obviously
his back is up because we call
him out on his bullshit yeah i
believe he requested to know what
the big prize was for winning that
was part of what we requested how
does the answer to the question what
is the meaning of life sound spoilers
it's love ah if that doesn't whet
your beak that's not how that expresses
na what that means then the winner
will get a story but it is
a theme with chickens then the winner
will get a story on my instagram
dedicated to them
that i will leave up for two
hours oh that's my where are you
being a scrooge about your leave it
up for twenty four hours meant to
no one's going there anyway i pin
it asshole put it in your highlights
yeah that should settle that the proverbial
balls in your metaphorical court okay k
p you obviously haven't been listening and
this is why we haven't heard from
you in weeks because we
as for that shit in your ears
you have shit for years dude okay
p we ask for tweaks to the
game i can't remember what tweaks we
asked for its we've got some on
us it's not on us we put
it out remember what we said you
know four minutes ago let alone four
weeks ago your job is to listen
my dear boy and listen can't believe
we got threatened on our own podcast
because okay yeah your job is to
listen and and follow orders yeah not
to disrespect us in our house yeah
alright kpi that's another week that we
are not playing your game so so
click on that yeah and don't write
us again k p
we clean unless you've cleaned up your
fucking act yeah please and apologized to
us each individually i want three separate
apollo i don't want a collective apology
because i don't want to share mine
with lorne yeah i don't want to
share my with paul no i want
my own apology ah yeah k p
considered standing for
or keep apologizing because that's yeah you
need to do son yeah alright and
in other way we don't even need
to accept the apology no we don't
know that well oh no no no
no accepting it is not a separate
early going to happen now will be
based on the apology we were see
that yeah it'll be based on my
feelings when i hear the apology if
i'm
like oh my god o k p
you messed with the bull and you
got the horns so ah get right
with god and tweak that game and
maybe whatever else we said yes and
do all the things that we said
alright well that was three of them
were three dm on instagram were three
of us on instagram and ah
twitter three m usa gmail dot com
and of course haha lane poo on
the phone and if you want to
hear ad-free episodes go to stitcher premium
or cvb world dotcom
and paul have a great time in
vegas have a great time and always
become ooh thank you this is an
old changes all the rules can you
go put a hundred dollars on black
on roulette and just see what happens
and then give us the winnings i
was actually thinking about that exact thing
today oh and for giving us the
winnings not that part
i would like to see you do
that i was walking by the roulette
table i was like what if i
just put a hundred dollars on on
a color and then yeah whatever happens
happens but then i thought if i
lose i will be upset you could
be mildly annoyed
oh yeah it was but it's your
it's your play money it's your vacation
money you know i see lower but
this is what i was thinking i
was like if i have this little
budget of gambling money right yeah but
if i do want to play last
if i do go yeah stuff like
that is just over and like i
just tore up one hundred dollars now
that is true i love to sit
there and play for a while on
on alright
so does the episode is over goodbye
what but i got more i wanted
to
ugh