yeah
ah who turned this off immediately i
don't believe i don't blame you if
you never started i was
i know but that's speaking very hearing
this and you never even started listening
i don't blame you but you're a
redneck if you're within the sound of
my voice and you can't hear me
i'm sorry guys welcome to threesome yeah
we're back can you believe it after
last week's episode i can't i thought
we were just gonna quit we're still
will dealing with the fallout wow everything
she said was a lie i just
wanna put that out there okay and
everything i said was what lauren would
have said if she were telling the
truth
and everything scott said it was everything
he didn't say when he wished he
could have said it to goofy broke
up with into a twenty girlfriend twenty
twenty yeah
wow because you think i am going
on in here
revealed as far back as you could
see your like searching couldn't think of
a year
just during the pandemic yeah except before
know it doesn't exist endemic gu ma
oh my printable goo blah
hey everyone gotta pay them a good
wow man wives understand that is i
and maybe we talked about this a
lot but the the people who had
affairs going on when the pandemic hit
don't think we do talk about no
we've talked about it at some point
i would say that they must have
been you know shaking in their boots
well how do i bring covert back
to their
wives yeah that's the thing husbands do
you keep doing it or do you
resist a good time to go like
hey maybe it's we got so high
but i can't risk and getting this
life care is good for the virus
from a waterfall would amass code yeah
it didn't didn't someone announced at some
point like you can fuck with mass
can but you can't kiss what
someone once someone says oh gee i
bet a name the person that my
thirty five g qa things over to
my alter ego dirty voucher hey everybody
look you can fuck will you kiss
isn't pretty woman rules
ah yeah you get that no i
have not seen it oh shit but
i've heard i know that's a thing
okay yeah you know that's a thing
i know i know that's probably the
one thing you've picked up on i
yeah speaking of pretty woman yeah gary
marshall is a very pretty woman like
garry marshall who directed pretty woman i
just watched the movie soap dish
for the first time no and i've
never seen it and everyone was like
ya gotta watch so i never see
any it's it's not bad there's some
good there's some good jokes in there
where only tell us what kevin kline
fantastic knock clients kevin klein walks up
to talk to me on the other
side so she's there he says given
close to philly fans kevin
ooh and i am calling from soap
dish and they should come right in
the movie started i recently learned he's
married to really gay ch yeah great
couple there is one unfortunate joke in
the movie okay that does not hold
up at all well there's gotta be
i mean brief years brief moment of
transphobia that i have to
say is mercifully brief like they don't
linger on it in the way that
a lot of movies older movies would
yeah but other than that it's a
very good movie yeah so you like
very good it's fun you like the
pairing i probably won't watch it it's
a fine film honestly it's going down
down down down no i think you
would enjoy them i think you enjoy
it
i just watched it for the millionth
time you've got mail or maybe i
just put it on cause it was
on netflix i was like sure i'm
gonna do some computer stuff if you've
watched you've got mail for million times
you should take any recommendation i give
you guys ah well you're not gonna
like what i'm gonna say ah perfect
film why start so fanatically terror
fuck me
no no trans folks dave chappelle oh
yeah he's simply an actor in the
movies simply guy i'm not thinking about
that i'm thinking about the meg ryan
tom hanks pairing dining it does make
sense of tom hanks and dave chappelle
would be best friends well that part
is random okay but not perfect their
chemistry is off the charts you guy
it's i'm talking about the roma of
course you hate it i know i
don't hate i remember it being slow
and i didn't say it's bad it's
not slow and it's not boring it's
actually very good i mean shop around
the corners good so i've never seen
that old film i'll watch that instead
i don't want to lie alone what
who's in it though ah everyone famous
is everyone who is
alive at in that year well that's
true we believe the population was much
lower yeah and it was great because
people got to go see the movie
and see themselves on screen waverly like
it's me but
yeah like sleepless in seattle
i don't remember ap so long still
i can't do this with you guys
and sleepless in seattle was based on
an old movie yeah right guys up
top and i need a job that's
a great one it's another meg ryan
and tom hanks great i pay for
joe vs the volcanoes never see i've
seen that it's great
because they live in that weird movie
right yeah i love yeah though it's
both in that and they're both yeah
what they believe is their first one
yeah surely times this you should watch
over to the watch that it's ah
john patrick shanley who did moonstruck which
is i love that's perfect that is
a perfect movie night it's one of
my family generally favorite movies yeah yeah
your general family yeah
mom aunts got the idea of them
sure yeah yeah when you think about
them in theory i think moonstruck are
fun sandals yeah do you like these
like you know why see them from
this side oh my i recently lost
them in my own home and i
was going kind of shouted a track
around them yeah i think put a
tile on em um
and then make contributor ragu
i yeah she shouldn't but ragu right
like riko i know dear i know
around my house my canoes ragu mike
and found my sandals and a basket
of hats
basket of hats you thought it was
a hat and you threw it in
there this or mike thought it was
to type the title of your self
help book right i found my sandals
and a basket of hats well let's
break this down who threw it and
then what's the what's the lineup factly
what happened tell ah so first i
need long subtitle for yourself first yeah
coffee
to get the title the title is
i threw my sandals in a basket
of hats colon and other things i'm
not telling my husband
ah why didn't you tell mike about
no it's my that's what the cause
you are blaming wednesday with this guy
sounds like our not so but solely
not not know if it's a carrot
character character yes yes yes the character
of the character of me who's much
sillier and cure amelia bedelia style
what happened to this so but so
amelia but yeah
i was packing for disneyland which i
had a wonderful time visiting um with
my nephews and family and i um
i was grabbed my sandals and then
i went like i need a hat
so i went into the closet where
i have a basket of hats a
basket is it a closed basket or
is no it's actually here's
what it really is it's a free
gift basket i was sent with some
bachelor goodies in it for to promote
some bachelors oh and it's a nice
woven basket it's random that i put
my hats in there indeed but i
dan duh and i was grabbing heads
and i must have just put the
santos in there and walked away and
grabbed whoa this is adventure many many
days
cause i wondered where are there i
thought i'm losing my mind and then
i thought i feel like i remember
holding them when i was in the
closet and then i i looked in
the hat basket many times didn't find
him but then i went back and
actually dug in there and there they
were i had an experience like that
recently and i was so mad where
i was looking for something
in a drawer i like you were
like team i'm sure i left these
yeah in this drawer weren't there condoms
what yeah my ultra thin extra tiny
i'm sure yes
i'm sure okay last chamber atx just
smile usually can't make it out you
have to use your hand and feel
good yeah and then this and this
is i'm gonna say
this was like last
october what date thirty first ooh you
think it goes did it couldn't find
these fucking things and then what were
the drawing the other day you don't
want to say they were they were
a bunch of tin whistles but amy
sedaris
she has all these little drawers which
keeps little things a bunch of tin
whistles yes i look i have you
a brooklyn hipster
it's something that they don't know it
seems like someday they'd they'd have old
timey bicycle lacks their ten i'm somebody
that does variety programs oh boy what's
gonna happen much human rights little it's
you thank you very much lauren for
that you're not like anyone else you
are you
i like this line of reasoning yeah
and so okay here's what sounds do
the whistles make is it like what
sells for like a penny whistle like
okay so like yeah got it yeah
it was a slight slide whistles no
slide whistle is a slide whistle right
so it's a do they have holes
in it that you can think i
got it
will you lauren i'm simply saying the
track up of you playing with your
tin whistles i didn't do a single
pull to see we're doing this slide
whistle i didn't do and that's what
got me yeah here's what that's what
got you confused yeah here's what happened
i didn't do it until way in
it starts with a death oh
oh my friend neil mahoney passed away
i'm sorry alright thank you well this
is i know but i feel like
i can't just say okay
or he passed away i feel like
it was like the beginning of coffee
yeah i remember seeing that thumb that
was released yeah and then we had
a memorial service for him ah me
i'm gonna say service was a party
actually it was it was like when
things started kind of opening with the
vaccine yes exactly postback post vaccine and
so um i was asked to sing
a song
rng um at at the at the
party and it was ah a song
by the poem a bitch
and a bitch and i said yes
um and so they the band was
rehearsing at my house and the song
the key of the song was pretty
low for me and i said can
we change the key the guy playing
the penny whistle only had the one
whistle i said i have a bunch
of different keys let me go find
them how
oh handy wow well you think yeah
and then i went looked in that
goddamn drawer they weren't in there i
looked i looked all over the place
did you blame janie
yeah of course i look i look
cool for the guys because i thought
janie how like a little parade with
some neighborhood animals and they chat a
little tin whistle and they were walking
around playing that was her pandemic project
yeah its she would do animal parades
yeah um this before squirrels could give
you covert yeah because if you share
a whistle with a squirrel yeah you're
s o l
some might say you're the son the
son in law um the son of
law is sort of law poly so
i couldn't have i could not find
them and it was like ok well
i guess we've got a saying in
this trash key and then i phone
this guy got anything on there that
could help me with the key
what i beg your pardon like an
asshole lap
find it here you play the pistol
you're going to find it into the
oh no no he couldn't change key
oh yo-yo his penny was always in
the key of the gaul original recording
um and i was so mad and
then the other day i found the
they were exactly where i was exactly
where i'd here's what exactly where you
looked for years what's up yeah
yeah they were in the fucking drawer
where i looked you looked and look
find them
i feel like i dumped that drawer
let me tell you something's fishy please
do you ever use the fish did
it ever use the old phrase where
you pray to st don't shoot were
more saying attention please come around me
i say tony tony tony tony o
dumb things lost and must be found
that's what i was taught st anthony
st anthony please come around something is
lost and cannot be found i'm respectful
to him tony today we're good friends
i did a button tony tony turn
around but tony let me tell you
one that happened recently with this because
i whenever i say it it fucking
works it does maybe i mean when
i don't say it doesn't work because
i don't do it
but exactly it's a thinker
but what happened was mike couldn't find
his wallet we're spending while talking about
this where is the sanctuary where such
a bad feeling yeah to not be
nice said the key phrase as said
previously i walked back in the room
it's sitting right on the fucking coffee
table like it was right there but
there was nothing else on it there
was no way we didn't see it
huh do you i think tyler henry
the medium put it there for me
do you think mike's wallet and my
penny whistles would you believe large briefly
but anyways now weird think of that
it's like is your brain just not
seeing your brain your brain is editing
because you know here's it was not
wednesday it was several for tin whistle
i only believe in science and facts
and what i believe is there's some
part of my brain that's not accessing
that because i'm thinking about it so
hard well no there's nothing like such
a spirits or mediums or go
it's there's no such thing as psychics
i don't believe in anything like that
i i think what i think what's
happening is you know how you know
how if like something is messy in
your room yeah your brain use that
sock to clean the one on your
day you guys have ruined me
i wouldn't my mind would even go
to that but it does or what
does that mean okay so you're in
your diner always there you're on you're
here you're in your dining room and
on the dining room table there's some
male that you've like left there yeah
your table gets so out of fucking
control yes exactly hey so when you
go through your your dining room
you edit it out of your field
division because you don't want to be
unhappy and looking at it would make
you feel because it's annoying because it's
annoying so your wallet will try that
your wallet was somewhere that you like
we're editing and out of your thing
and you're like not recognizing it as
a wallet because you recognizing it as
clutter
right maybe oh that's my theory i
think you don't have to shit on
it i said amazing granted me i
think already that actually helped me maybe
i think generally either is carly rae
because that's crazy here's my wall head
don't call me tony
tony
yeah
well i'm glad he found his wallet
i'm glad you found your whatever the
fuck you guys thought i found my
sandals no okay i was pretty upset
they're my favorite i'm glad you found
one of your sandals um kinda taste
making fun about amy stares actually yes
so the other day she was having
an auction to raise money for diabetes
um what do you call
call it charity and it was um
alive there was they were doing it
live in new york where you could
go in and be famous yeah just
like saturday me so yes me and
then they just things they did a
livestream auction george skis and i love
her so much so i marked my
calendar for this and then i oh
i
i couldn't wait i was i forgot
and i was like oh aren't you
checking your calibre i knew i hadn't
then i just wasn't paying attention to
the time i showed up thirty minutes
late however i was very invested and
i bought a piece i got something
in a bidding war whoa with who
david soyer stranger but i and coutu
is watching
it so she was texting like oh
my god oh my god but i
couldn't look at her text as i
was in the bidding war worst is
so crazy and um and she also
later wants something really awesome but i
got um this really great painting and
done by by who amy sedaris well
the it's it's this is all just
stuff that she owned oh god it
and some of it was like thrifted
to most
ever but this was a john deere
a painting from john derry which was
a store that i already collect things
from but david sedaris is partner hugh
had painted godzilla onto the painting whoa
it's like a sort of like an
old angel
dr store yeah got me i like
i love i'm so excited i got
it recently in the mail i can't
wait i can't wait to hang it
up i will post it in my
store it's like what's arrived already yeah
right i just misplaced my fucking hammer
and nail well i know where they
are going to happen will come on
that's one hammer one nail magical
but it was so fun to be
part of an auction with such fun
things she has such a weird things
i text army and taxidermy and i
didn't catch anyone i was watching but
it went on for hours and hours
and they had to continue a different
night there was just so much gods
and so many people on the on
the line bidding was she on hoarders
recently and this is this is the
way they're doing i don't know
why she's getting rid of all the
stuff now but celebrity hoarders would be
a good show oh i would love
to see us about yourself well didn't
martha stewart i think she did like
an auction saying i haven't watched it
my mom was talking about this it's
like i'll she had like a whole
barn full of items and then celebrities
were like calling in and like getting
things early like amateur
yeah that's so fun that's us celebrities
like who julia saw chris knew her
dad probably i know yeah she bid
on some plate settings said oh risk
cardassian you know you know you guys
want carnations every week know every week
i've been to all every primary i
do watch that goddamn southern charm which
is it was a terrible show that's
the thing i don't know i can't
put anything past you really or couldn't
say yeah i mean he whistle news
yeah
you know there's you've got a collection
of penny when you know what also
have an ocarina o of times that
joins the sweet potatoes circle with holes
around know that's a pitch pipe i
think okay what are you thought korea
was circular it's not no okay it
is like it's like an oblong thing
it's got a little um ah kind
of handily thing coming out of it
that's
at the end of that you blow
into and it's got holes
the and you blow into i got
too good
guy too good
i'd like to look at when it
looks like a lot to look at
what it looks like easley yeah please
bring your arena around or arena show
me the arena arena arena arena okay
okay arena yeah it does have holes
all over it i will give it
that does it's like yeah it's not
like a ppa
potato they used to call it this
they also refer to it as the
swallow that i could see it with
this one yeah it doesn't look not
circular no it does look not so
how about this one it's a sailor
moon i wasn't angry enough law among
certain angles sailor moon ocarina s perfect
circle producer that is oh the maynard
keenan i get ten percent off if
i type my email right now
a corrina corrina corrina corrina corrina corrina
corrina corrina o o j
two karena developed holes
oh go oh i wish there was
more shit like that like yeah where
falco puts a timeline of mozart in
the middle of that song yeah i
would you do that comes with him
recording that song yeah wow that's so
crazy what did you have to is
what does falco up to is alcoa
still with
and around oh do you think he's
dog
oh bao bao da da da
you also are i guess this still
happens i didn't ninety eight o nine
e don't know ninety eight falco died
in the dominican republic
they should edit that into the song
yeah sieve died of severe injuries receives
thirteen days before his forty first birthday
was mitsubishi pajero collided with a bus
on the road linking the towns via
montalcino and puerto plata in the dominican
republic can't deal with this at the
time of his death
if he was planning a comeback the
prophecy was true
hey that was a long ass time
ago says he predicted that he passed
me passed away at forty that's horrid
yeah beat him
well i'm in my falco year forty
that's awful man that's bad i thought
he would still be with it i
thought so too enjoying the fruits of
his labours yeah yeah scott speaking of
being with us how is your birthday
it was airtight it was great and
i'm with you great did you do
anything special on the day that you
care to share with our listeners
well i forgot people were listening to
this oh shit i sprained my ankle
the day before just like when you
wrote that horse yeah but this is
worse ah why because the day or
the horse it was fine i walked
off it was fine sure so it
hurt more it still is is that
a boot not a boot but a
high shoe
huh he's wearing heels she's branded ah
spring playing pickleball oh trying to be
cool trying to be trying to playing
pickleball du da da da blowing the
same pickle ball all day as everything
i say you guys should say okay
okay everything i say
ah cool i've been trying to get
me to play pickleball for months had
been trying
even turned on him ah so i
played pickleball really enjoyed it for ah
about an hour and a half play
what shoes were you wearing load load
low pumps but like your kidney knew
a nude kidney
the loofah tons my dear
you
yeah um you were you wearing ah
we're letting you know i was wearing
a gesture right well ah sneakers shoe
sneaker but but without a high back
yeah or side and so the next
day it was like let's do it
again and three minutes in rolled my
ankle know and
you fall to the ground eyes went
ah and then fell to the ground
and then i had my phone on
because of a text i had to
get
and it started beeping immediately i'm like
wow and i went over and picked
up the phone wow because you had
to see the information i did i'm
gonna send you this text and you
need to see it live well it
was something that i needed to so
you didn't need to see episode timing
worked out poorly that you yes i'm
in pain but else going
see this wow i want i want
to milk this pain but i always
hear your you look like you're robert
de niro milking no big rig i
want to milk the pain but i
want to answer my tax um who
i've carried to the car
no ah i thought i thought it
was gonna be i thought i might
get back out oh and then i
was like ah i'm gonna i'm gonna
not just in case yeah and now
it's been five days and still good
doc doc i need go doc docx
maybe and then sofia birthday were you
sad because your ankle hurt i was
sat well ah we ended up not
going into town or any thing we
were out of town we ended up
not going to the town because right
because you went to a special location
for me yes yes yes yeah lately
you kind of have to just chill
in your hotel ah at the pool
or whatever and then we interrupt did
you do
rice oh i did yes inclination no
guys ice custard everybody i love these
rice it's it's rest rest it's rice
rice in colorado it's ice now it's
rice stirred what is this guy doing
that's right every rice rice a sigh
rice rice hay and ah yeah and
that should do it i did everything
you said in front of it you
put restriction but yeah i did i
didn't really have anything to constrict with
so i did i did all that
but i have been couldn't take off
your t-shirt or whatever rapid runner
i that i'd be nude from the
waist up turned into strips like you're
on a desert island
that's too bad you hurt yourself oh
it was fine it was really funny
going to town yeah but it was
really that's your move it was really
nice i was with some great people
and we had a nice dinner and
those and and was very nice ah
glad to hear that yes so like
every nice day and then paul and
i
and janie and kula the old broads
we went to we went we talked
about this on a previous episode of
what we were going to do but
last night we went to see martin
short and steve martin at the hollywood
bowl i love them and was it
fun it was very odd ball great
it was absolut so do they do
a show just the two of them
how does it
work will see they used to do
shows separately they i've seen martin short
do his show which was like an
hour and a half settle thinking is
it he would do singing he would
do comedy and he would he would
address his jiminy glick oh good we
always watched jiminy glick ah when we
need to be cheered up when you
watch saying quickly and he he interviewed
we want to watch something funny before
i would put on committing like you
would interview he interviewed a local television
anchor and then i think he did
i'm pretty sure he did ah ed
grimley as well oh wow well cost
yeah full costumes for all of that
so he so he did like an
hour and a half show and then
steve martin also would separately do
do an hour and a half show
mainly of music i feel like where
it was like his banjo museu whereas
mainly banjo stuff but then he would
you know like talking between the songs
and then they were like i think
they had to er the or they
got the opportunity to do a show
together and they just kind of combined
it where they had each did less
time and then they also wrote
much of jokes about each other yeah
i've seen them kind of do that
on something on tv yeah definitely they
had a netflix special yeah yeah it
was always that it was it's really
good because they can do less time
and then they seem to be having
a lot of fun doing it together
it was really great it was real
i mean and it was like densely
packed with jokes like yeah it was
they were fast vast they were not
pausing
for the laughs all that much right
it was it was great because they
and each one was hitting really well
yeah which like you would think they
would pause for laughs but no they
were just like like i'm rolling mean
like every job i think i laughed
out loud at every single joke which
you know how rare that is impossible
yeah and it was like i could
not believe it like there were that
there was like no joke
i was like oh my god i
love the one of martin george was
well steve martin is a lot like
the movie deliverance it's all fun and
games until the banjos
i unfortunately don't remember that movie i
was gonna um
i have never seen that movie i
saw it for some reason i saw
zenith but i know what the reference
being yes i'd like to know wheels
and why does it have guns in
it ah yeah it's about guns sure
sure guns of the flesh variety
going into he love god
i love huh
one no one even lower when was
that kiss love gun love gun yeah
let's see you got every joke to
you so that's big i got every
single truth i got and oh my
god when they when you said you
left it reject you actually bragging that
you got every joke right yeah
the funniest part though
the funniest part was anything anybody would
pick up on in this vote it
was the perfect cry when martin sure
does jiminy glick in this show he
does it as like a ventriloquist puppet
that steve martin has control areas and
steve martin asks him about very celebrities
and they put the pictures of the
celebrities up on the giant screen
and it's like what about this guy
and then oh i think the day
you know whoever critic you know kim
kardashian oh i think she's whatever but
for some reason he puts up a
picture of elon musk and it is
the lowest rez version it's on these
giant screen oh fucking funny i was
laughing
it's so hard that they could not
get the highwood bull oil that intentional
no i thought well it's not intentional
and here's because later on they do
like a sarah mclaughlin thing and they
show pictures of ah puppies puppies rainy
and there was a low rez yeah
i was like well they're not trying
to slam that puppy got him just
like there
have to be better pictures of ilan
musk out there but oh my god
it may be fucking die really if
it was it was bad like this
really funny to see a blown up
big screen that is so funny just
like the first one on google image
oh exactly and then the question i
have is how to jamie's picnic baskets
were worked out very well recover well
yes it was like he had a
drama having a cutie birds yes yes
yes i how did you know about
this i had private texts with janie
a whoa yeah where she is asking
your help or no it was about
something else and then she mentioned i
have to go get this picnic basket
i have to while she said because
ford's her will know that i did
the timing worked out where she had
to get on a certain day because
they were closed on july etc um
but there was good yeah it was
good i mean there was a
local drama she got a a tack
by air and a hat yeah wearing
sandals so yeah yeah there's like a
littler bear with him wearing a bow
a pick on nick baskets yes yeah
right i've heard of this yeah i've
heard this i've heard of this yeah
oh i heard that there they don't
harm they just won
and all they want is the picnic
basket yeah they're actually very friendly nice
day up for authority though yeah which
i don't like at all
when they when the weirdly enough when
steve martin started playing his first banjo
song i started tearing up for some
reason because it was meaningful to you
i don't know something about nostalgia for
my youth there's something not right that
for no reason it hit me right
before the show started like wow this
is momentous like these guys are the
novelties are people that love them
these these are like two people that
got me into the life that i
have and the fact that they're still
performing doing great shows and together yeah
like there's little that's a lot also
they showed clips beforehand of of just
a wide swath of their work and
it's fun that took well it's been
since the seventies first yard and and
really the eighties that we we have
been aware of martin short but it's
just like they've done so many things
and had so i mean steve martin's
career is so crazy the amount he's
done yeah that's true but just the
amount of things that he's done is
so massive yeah yeah from a young
age and then he still had like
twenty five
years where no one even knew where
he was who he was where he
was working in disneyland and knott's berry
farm it's like so crazy twenty five
years yeah he went to to get
famous well he wasn't when he wasn't
working there he wasn't oh but he
was a baby during some of that
you're telling your counting baby when he
was a baby he wasn't famous yeah
when he was a five year old
artisan funny he was
as he was famous at six but
then started not being famous again at
seven he took a break to work
at disneyland he was all washed up
at seven yeah but it was just
crazy to see like oh yeah all
those movies and all those snell appearances
and all of those television shows and
all it like it was it was
very overweight
filming right he's also most people where
he's had white hair for so long
that he's seemed older when he was
younger like in father of the bride
he has white hair right but he's
not and cubes
presumably we don't know that he might
have shaved that mercifully they don't show
them in the film they say at
the very end like at the end
of the crit i think it also
has pubic he pulls he pulls the
waistband of his pants down very far
for the cradle it's fucking best check
out review
say okay so he was forty five
and father of the bride yeah wow
which was twenty one years ago of
a bride alright it was nine thirty
one no it's it's i mean yeah
his book by the way born standing
up i've read i mean for him
to be selling out you know universal
amphitheater and big
rig is an arena i guess i
mean it's it's and then to have
then forty more years of doing incredibly
diverse weird amazed things like that it's
a dream that's so cool i still
haven't sold out the universal amphitheater well
i don't count that as part of
the dream because i didn't ever happen
but i towards the do your dreams
are only reasonable
yeah but my dreams are absolutely things
i could accomplish i had a dream
last night that i was like being
possessed by all my god and it
was like it was so real but
it was like i was very aware
of it and i was going like
oh my eyes turning block like i
was like asking questions oh hey my
eyes turning back from this demon let's
move out to possess me oh no
i mean we guess what's going on
guys like are they
do they look like are you talking
to my voice sound like my boy
we have to take a break speaking
voices right back
yeah we're bad bye bye babbitt babbitt
the big black people in poverty blue
ah yeah we almost talk like minions
and let me tell you something scott
i listened to ah the episode of
scott hasn't seen yes about about despicable
me to pick up depicts the bullet
and it made me want to watch
the movie
i haven't played slayer yeah i liked
it i liked some of the stuff
some of the moments that you were
talking about sounded really funny yeah i
enjoyed it check that out ah if
you haven't heard it it's like it's
good it made me want to watch
the sequels which i have not done
yet but yeah yeah how many are
there well there's there's a new one
being born to poster there's
despicable me three there's minions and then
there's this new minions the rise of
gru i believe so some guys film
the rise of love those little guys
they love those little guys with the
very cutesy i have not been exposed
to all of the overexposure of the
memes and stuff like that i've only
known i mean yeah i see the
ads every once in awhile but i
feel like i've i've
i learned a lot about minions without
knowing anything yeah what i mean what
is there to know really i know
they don't speak english but they speak
many of these queen's english they were
around for the rise of gru
but like the language they speak is
like a combination of a bunch of
languages right they call it menu knees
but yeah i believe it's i don't
think they the rise of the room
they were like they were there there
were wasted essentially yes i knew about
gro yeah they watched well how could
they not
to go with all tom do you
think that song will incorporate the song
that movie will incorporate the song rise
by herb alpert and the tijuana brass
i actually know for sure ah proud
of you for good for the ramp
or you fear the notorious b i
g sample i don't know it is
it's the the general hospital song right
yes where it's like wham bringing really
ah there was a nonconsensual sex scene
between luke luke and laura yes and
then a laser in an underground thing
the ice princess the kiss dines man
that that was huge when we were
kids yeah movie general hospital the soap
opera oh yeah when you start looking
laura i thought from a soap opera
but i think i'm gonna movies
no it was general hospital was yeah
was fucking so big that even i
heard about it my mom knew watched
all my children so i i'm more
familiar with that universe um but the
general hospital universe i do know luca
laura it was nineteen eighty two probably
nation this is when it went in
just like exploded and like there's that
song general
a hospital general hospital ah that's just
a song yeah it was all about
the phenomena because everyone was like people
will hop song yes hop song hit
the top forty everyone was watching it
everyone was talking about it how were
people even seeing it if they were
at work yeah my mom would tape
it on our vcu oh and then
watch it everyday should take
it again on the same tape but
you forget that soap operas were designed
for the stay at home mom yeah
but i mean if but but it
had to have been so big but
i remember dallas was also huge at
the top for yeah who shot
oh yeah falcon crest yeah not as
huge could anything be as big now
is that i don't think so i
mean yeah isn't a lot of opportunities
but but everyone still feels like there's
something that everyone's excited like many thrones
even stranger things you'd like would just
huge um million people you know are
like oh don't give a shit about
but i feel like soap operas because
that's that's more rare for everyone to
be interested in that like it's a
very specific style of television yes it
is weird this is this dumb thing
that is just designed to like
make housewives have a tv on then
suddenly everyone's talking about it one year
and then no one talks about it
ever again there has been discussion about
the only thing that is designed to
make housewives have a tv while i
like susan lucci from all mitchell's right
lou was now only five trillion times
but everyone that's right she finally won
she did she finally said yeah good
yeah thank god we finally stopped
talking about her early and then she
dropped it on the stage yeah she
went up she put her hands on
the trophy and then she died yeah
but you know i guess what's kind
of funny she became a trophy she'd
be because of our internet you know
that we all share we can find
people don't know we we all have
three or three of us share an
internet bill yeah
we're on a family plan with three
family the family plans yes
wrote a freedom friendly plan we well
why aren't we all on a family
plan setting out goals and better our
golden years together we should all be
splitting our utility bills in our show
and we should all be splitting our
phone bill so that i can look
at who you're calling
oh am i in your top five
top five oh my god those little
circles who have you ever called like
my awesome bar called you wanna know
yeah like any legitimate call everybody read
your calls okay like outgoing call like
like who are you doing freaks calling
you to oh we only have like
somebody i called mike because i wanted
to tell him what happened on the
previous call that i had it before
usally on our company that i was
coordinating some ah catering with oh what
are you catering dear i don't want
to talk about it and then i
called um who's this that i called
who is this i spoke to a
serviceman and i spoke to my friend
dan who calls me all the time
we down i have a few friends
i talk on the phone what do
i know don't share anymore i have
zero friends that took i've got my
friend dan who's also known as big
dipper he is a rapper oh sure
and then my friend arden marine we
talk on the phone really yeah that's
a lot of my recent calls
not all the other ones were at
disneyland and we were like where are
you where my last call was last
wednesday to schedule a haircut your last
call was last wednesday wow i literally
have like five today before that june
twenty first i don't even know what
this number way you never call no
i don't i oh how do you
get out of this i only look
i'm ever
a day out of this every day
i'm talking on the phone i i'm
only calling like businesses i never i'm
never ever owing to chat how do
you do just once you've sent
about i don't know scott okay and
i couldn't even tell you if the
other call that i mentioned was made
by me or received by yeah yeah
because it shows a little picture of
phone with an arrow pointing out if
you made the call oh that's huge
knowledge oh god it okay so i
call i literally can't believe you've had
you've made like two calls in the
last two weeks
z that's it honestly it's one call
and you get spam calls and then
the previous call i made one call
in the last month
no i mean one call last week
and then the the last call that
i made before that was june thirteen
but see i do some things that
are kind of old school sometimes i'll
call places to pay my bill not
like um like a call at my
podiatrist because like the emailed me and
i'm like it's more annoying to send
them it's mom but i address in
the mail and do all this stuff
i'm gonna call
doesn't look campaigner is having a column
hey over the phone and then i
did that for this other like framer
that i use like weird but i
don't think that's weird everybody's talking bout
my corns and bosnians why won't they
just let me danny wow steve's record
i don't have corns or but yeah
we know your wiki fee score it's
a ten
yeah isn't that so yeah wow that's
literally perfect um let me see those
um no nosy kid okay i called
kula today from the car because the
garage clicker was no longer in the
car and i had to leave and
i said can you click
garage and you claim you kick me
out ah then i called ah my
coworker this morning and we had a
nice catch up ah regarding regarding difficult
some business stuff i didn't make a
call though oh you're only speaking about
making and then i then two days
before i called my mother nice and
then the men were gone
back into june and then the last
going ryan gaul
spoke to him on the phone i
spoke to him on i called him
at the very least joe's out of
bed and jumped down to pocket dial
me recently was mitchell might mention of
doughboys fable this young man doughboys spooning
yeah spoon spoon explanation really what he
pocket down with you yeah let me
see if i still have any yes
so many times you have so i
told
you that matt walsh was would butt
dial me constantly yeah and i would
hear his conversation and then his boat
would be like hey scott hey i
just wanted to call you
hearing the conversations is crazy i've accidentally
recorded voice memos or like you know
when you press it to the auto
the audio keyboard starts typing what you're
saying like a long paragraph just appears
and it's like all the shit that
i was just saying dangerous alright and
i use voice memos a lot here's
where we say
and a voice oh yeah and four
i was doing i was doing that
with instead of taxing people i was
doing videos i was recording myself as
videos and sending that listen here's mike
saying hello
oh
he called me he sounds so hello
hello he must have seen that the
phone was ringing and he picked it
up thinking that it was known like
it was answered like it went to
voicemail so it was already like i
was like someone call me if you're
hearing this please tell mike to get
a shit together we have a listener
voicemail about this stuff you're hearing this
tell
oh my god if you are hearing
my voice right now tell mike mitchell
to get his shit together we have
a we have a listener voicemail about
this top okay let's hear it yes
she was here since we're talking because
i loved a lesson yeah don't give
a shit hi it's good from oregon
hi i'm i texted my friend darin
everything he was my wife and said
hey let's make an excuse to get
out of going to the dave matthews
concert with their no i was driving
in durham's kitchen and i looked up
and his phone dings and he looked
at me this was really awkward you
have any stories where you escalate to
the wrong person more embarrassing dad does
so
so wow little standing in the same
room as the tv in the kitchen
that's so bad i mean i have
told the story that i had somebody
do that to me about me ah
yeah they were picking me up and
then they wrote something about me it
wasn't exactly it wasn't like that but
in the fucking robot now it's been
attacking all three of us i always
always this to all of us the
other day he did yeah you you
texted all of us didn't you and
you said whoops that was meant for
a different thread yeah but it's always
wanted to actually about i know it
wasn't about like i don't know that
i've touched i might have i might
have done that once before were like
wow
where you feel you get scared that
you didn't your whole body is like
yeah pulsating yeah yeah it's terrifying the
best we ever had was we had
this
janie and i were journey calling thank
you who i was next after that
guy harry ocie and i can't believe
they hired him or no that's queen
dear oh i'm sorry journey famously it
was a guy like curry karaoke that's
so great and they it is isn't
you know it's just like american idol
i'm skipping all the steps it's just
you just you nailed it you got
one voice it's like that guy there
you go oh you were on your
phone so janie and i can't email
jamie and i were arranging
listening come on we were arranging a
car to the airport i think it's
a service called wings it's like it's
like uber but specifically forbids ten day
picture right of the yes tony shalhoub
in the back but not kill the
net i've never heard of this wing
yeah yeah yeah yeah and so this
guy sort of red bull gives you
this guy we
higher checks use connect with them directly
and um he texted ah janie um
ah you know the time i'll be
there blah blah blah is when my
car looks like everything then she got
another text it was like oh yeah
she's ah she's been looking great lately
um you know obviously on a steady
diet of dees nuts
it's
she showed it to me we fucking
howl laughing then he wrote back like
a minute later and said hey sorry
that was ah that text wasn't few
i was talking to my cousin um
ah about ah ah our other cousin
who is ah she's been on a
weight loss program or other laws and
yeah whatever it was it was like
it was like one of those allies
that so convoluted right well that was
like my friend said it's about any
concert then he texted up well because
he was trying to make up a
different story yeah then he texted a
picture of a bag of nuts
oh hey well actually that kind of
is next level kind of fun deal
since i was so fucking i literally
don't know but my friend said oh
i meant sent to my husband who
she was in the car with and
then it's like let us make any
sense i mean it's like okay and
i just said i know that you
didn't mean to but that's okay we
can
but that's fine um it happens embarrassed
i have more trouble with email where
it's like you think you're responding to
an email said that you have talked
about this book where like gmail was
confusing to me for a while where
ah jean legs if you get on
it with email someone emails know how
to log-in what's
next each male come on man this
would do the whole alphabet i can
have hs e-mail oh man that would
be so willing to wait for that
i think it'll happen pretty fun in
our lifetime to go back and do
a through there is still email hey
i go a through daddy's gotta have
somebody that's already been taking care of
new email b mail email d
e mail email f mail g email
each email i male j male k
male l male johnny m male and
male o male p mail q mail
our mail asks male for ah chee
mail you via email w mail
female x male y males email none
of them are funny
but we made sure we did it
via e-mail sounds like female though so
it's kind of funny yeah if it
was all women female yeah and men
arpino valentine's day yeah well hello really
oh well you know the ladle well
hello if you guys go with you
absolutely
i believe the only only lately little
yeah
can you please play another voicemail why
because i want to like that one
actually okay
that was a good one big skerrit
yeah thanks lily hi lauren hi paul
i just mean i haven't easily so
i um missed his mankin for my
friend's address a few years ago so
that i could send her a piece
of baby clothing for her new baby
um and i never sent it because
i wasn't sure what to write in
the note i was going to send
with it this is for you wonder
why i wonder why why this person
wasn't sure because i mean hey being
boxes i was thinking about how their
baby they had brought relief she felt
weird maybe just say maybe it was
a mistake to say for amy
selling so and to put the baby
saying this is for your baby it
could be love you yeah um i
want i understand the perilous yeah it's
it's easier to do nothing when you
really think about any less it's harder
because look she's still thinking about it
my knee of yourself dear when my
niece was little donate the item did
go into the light
dear
when it's time it's time it rises
dev and deer that means your time
here is done um when my niece
was little she sent me a um
it was like a flat stanley type
thing where i had to like take
a picture with it yeah and then
send it on and then i didn't
do it you never did like
and ruined it it's ruined the trash
oh no it it the state of
my home for a long time how
old was she oh my god like
so eight children for you now and
it was never brought up again it
was never realized you were the one
who ruined now she's fifty one years
old ms any sense at all
you should yeah you should forgive yourself
paul foy have i forgive yourself dear
off i go
once you free yourself you can finally
your bits irish exactly uday everything you
have left on your to deal with
flat stanley yelp
i don't know i you know i
have had that happen ah on the
receiving end and i've also that i've
been on the giving end where i
say i'm gonna do saying that i
don't do it yeah and then i
feel i might remember later like oh
fuck never to that and then don't
want to say it but i've had
a hundred people say they're gonna give
me something and then it never arrives
and i wonder what happened with men
okay but
okay so i guess life's hard man
are going to send it and you
didn't that's where maybe say hey i
just never sent this oh my god
i can't remember because it was i
think it was before i even had
a computer so i would not have
had email i think it was mailed
to me and i don't think i
ever responded or maybe i responded to
said yes i'll do this i don't
ever i did this
for co op sr did a great
job did it in front of mann's
chinese wow that's really exciting everywhere it
was the best every everywhere and now
i hogged it she has a kid
of her own who couldn't care less
about flat stanley and his flat business
yeah he just wants his own shoes
to worry about shoes while he's out
of the shoes shoes
remember the over videos yeah kelly
shoes shoes you know the person i
well that's his alter ego character yeah
um but you don't know him i
have met him yes i see yeah
she is shoes it was that which
is a moment in time yeah you
know two thousand and nine nine grid
nine comedian
character person ever received money money money
from the shoes video i should hope
so i hope so everyone saw it
what about the honey badger person i
hope they got rich yeah what about
the trix rabbit i hope he got
rich he didn't even want money he
just wanted that fuckin serial wow driven
insane yeah well
l what a bass let's go to
break i wouldn't let him have i
don't know i don't know they'd say
hey do you think anyway before we
go to break jang anyone's ever fed
a pet rabbit trick serial out of
like oh rabbit's like a sense of
justice or a tiger frosted flakes well
he was allowed to have them
okay he i mean i don't know
that he ever did tony i'm saying
is it is it misleading mark like
are is is there suddenly are there
animals dying because kids are like oh
this tiger likes frosted flakes let me
feed and then they die because if
i don't i don't think so okay
i mean because i'm i'm for kids
feeding tigers anyway this is a kitchen
thing ta kids if you're listening do
do not feed the tigers don't care
what country it's in yeah yeah i
don't care if i was emailing and
respect your items don't email food to
tigers but i'm saying there are certain
cereals where the mascot is not allowed
to have the serial
it's an and there being a mascot
against their will like with someone feed
a cuckoo bird cocoa puffs yeah well
that just makes them crazy yeah he
was cuckoo for it but that's why
he couldn't have it wait he he
wasn't allowed to have it i think
people try to keep it from him
because he had a condition you know
he's under a conservative ter shit exam
exactly free regards thirty let's go
i had a lot to say
well yeah hey everyone oh i know
everyone's very excited and they're listening next
to their cathedral phones um with a
roaring fire in their hamburger phones saw
father with his pipe and slippers mother
baking seven pies um the lid
will baby and his best net rocking
back and forth at breakneck speed and
now it's time for a three cheer
and this is where we play a
game and we call it a three
cheer but it's a game and this
reacher but it's a three-tier yeah but
it's a game it's a game but
it's just a game but it's a
three chart sure yes we call a
three-tier but it's a game but it's
a feature and this
time we're gonna play the one where
we can't remember what it's called or
who submitted it and we don't care
we don't care what they're gonna win
back the heart of the show it
becomes public domain wars that's right yeah
whoever submitted this you've already had your
little moment of glory oh it's time
physical i'm free to go
so my last remaining this is just
name on three
so this is the one where we
do a scene ah the first it's
two minutes long then it's one minute
long yeah thirty second of it then
it's fifteen it's called dwindling time frame
dwindling time fray dwindling time gray
frey doe yeah oh
alright so and there's no there's nothing
about these teams they're just sees yeah
they're just yeah okay think anything it's
hires yeah i think we just make
it up as we gone hon dau
paris ten starting now hi guys
what just say it going like this
is soo hard for me to say
it's just i know what this is
about talent what do you think it's
about because i don't want to do
the whole thing where like i then
say what it is if you don't
know what to do oh no i
know what it is what is it
someone stole the cookies from the cookie
jar the cook cookie jar yeah the
one that looks like a
cook yeah well cooking like guy fieri
vietti vietti sorry yeah i have a
cookie jar in the shape of guy
fia yeah you're really upset because there's
cookies missing what you're trying to say
there i used to have ninety seven
cookies in that jar it's life-size i
know these are jumbo y'all live here
but or where
you will now there's ninety six and
a half well we're each allowed to
someone ate half a cookie when they
shouldn't of done that i want to
know well know they wrap know they
obviously cut it with a knife okay
because it was a clean even cut
and then they wrapped up the other
half of what is this witch hunt
you know what i'm also looking for
a witch okay um
dillman yeah you've been on this like
i still do ever since
you went through that sort of like
embarrassing thing at the office you've kind
of been on this yeah we were
like i'm trying to point the finger
other people it's like we're not how
were her new hair about every office
because everybody that dildo hearted for me
pickle tan i can't get into this
but pickle ten did tell me because
he was there
obviously the day that you fell into
the trash can face forward your legs
were flailing about in the air kicking
in the air heat upward cp mall
down but it went up because sky
sky and then when you pulled your
head out we try to get out
of the ben your hair got caught
on all the gum at the bottom
of the bin and you ripped out
the center of your hair and
you should have pulled your head out
a year ass so that being said
why would i know you wearing a
baron but you're trying to have pickle
tongue dominance at home i've never known
your name was pickle too
twelve minutes
how long was now we do six
minutes no literally that was two minutes
two okay now you do the same
scene in one minute and great i
don't remember anything neither okay it wasn't
like hey everyone hey hey hey hey
oh what happened tell us what's up
why do you see wrong not gender
related something wrong but i'm gonna tell
you
you just say it what does it
wait i know what it is when
is it someone stole the cookies from
the cookie jar yeah that's right my
guy scary shaped cookie jar has huge
humanity as we know life size giant
cookies i have ninety seven cookies in
there this morning a bitch ain't one
someone took out one of the cook
keys
cut it in half with a knife
okay we know what you're doing i
know what happened to work you had
that embarrassing situation where everything we should
know about what happened to worry dildo
til nye chilton told her me and
because um he saw you saw it
happened at work so you can happen
you fell face
face first into a dumpster you had
your legs flailing you paid upwards you're
pulling yourself south sco and your hair
got caught to the gun at the
bottom and ripped out in the middle
of your head why would you do
that pickle man you shouldn't put your
pickle man picks
shit yeah didn't get to it skim
it under deliberate that was good alright
thirty seconds thirty seconds and go the
gentleman okay do you know what i'm
gonna say yeah you wanna say somebody
stole the cookie from the cookie yeah
that's right why guys getting your training
schools because you had a dairy
chanel work and you want to assert
dominance but i don't care because pickle
tin already told me that you lifesize
face down into the dumpster european straight
up and your haircut content shows solo
and that happened yes stillman why would
you tell her a pickle mads pickle
ton as you should know i never
knew your name was pickle town huh
a
alright fifteen seconds here we grow and
high guys don't like cookies for the
cuckoo yes the guy perry she died
like sigh you literally had a janky
happen
their head face down to have it
up as you pull your hair out
and then you're trying to tell doe
going on he told you that tillman
pilton told me mickelson
alright seven seconds the luke perry
huge seconds okay plus one luke perry
guess what what does that mean isn't
a movie it's like roadways as long
as you can say audible okay here
we go hey everyone cookies okay yeah
yeah yeah hominin because your head fill
facebook yeah i'm staring yolo who told
you that thing called da dan really
perfect her right thigh
three seconds and come yea still don't
oh
one second
and da
oh dildo
was a long ass like oh no
i press press three again right now
we now we do one yeah oh
my thank ah just kinda daughter remember
to remember sorry
alright here we go dildo to come
in
wow
oh no sorry you really made me
laugh and say it looks bit back
when you when we were on tour
that time did you break it or
did you sprain that you broke it
yeah walked around on it for a
while your ankles got a lot of
problems alright well but footing one we
gotta go we gotta go into the
light dear thank you all for listening
in ah we are three team usa
on um instagram twitter and three muse
gmail dot com if you want to
send us anything and call us at
holler in poo you figure out the
numbers and our it's our instagram if
you want your ad-free episodes or the
archives go to stitcher premium or cvb
world dotcom and may god have mercy
on your souls yeah he won't oh
no not the god that i know
that dude's fucked up well goodbye
uh