ah doo doo doo doo doo
us
de de de de de de de
de
uh
yeah wow oh wow it's so fun
like i was another people have been
sending us remixes that was a remixed
by at punk who on twitter is
at punk oh one and that is
the rock opera remix of the theme
song and that was great i loved
it thanks thank you thank you paul
when you're buying out your song ly
app pong buying my own i read
for the paw taking a love dick
loved it's xy of dodge don't look
at me like that paul it kills
my spirit soul rain oh god look
at yea hiring
oh and welcome back to three-day i'm
paul f tompkins county this what a
cunt was what i beg your pardon
because more is this what kind was
this who sent us this punk whoever
it is no whoever whoever's twitter relied
into shubin doesn't follow traci rearden oh
i see what you're
talking a bow low cool snub of
off book oh yeah all of them
but no no no you don't row
just check in and check out don't
want you to do any there's always
my wanna do good i'm a j
bar tow all right so we're like
hey
nah this on the screen is kevin
january we were playing that theme from
a twitter account and kevin's logged into
his twitter and and lauren is taking
umbridge that he does not follow her
fake account whereas i'm mad that he
is logging into twitter at work my
fake account is arriving
yeah um i'm scott orban and over
here is paul f tompkins yeah i
already said you didn't and my name
oh no okay you said she didn't
like who are you i'm lorna who
are you supposed to be i'm supposed
to be learning it works what's your
best halloween costume that you've ever had
who are you supposed to be is
really like you give us a real
james lipton well this was your classic
was i was called wonder the robot
yes yes i know that robot great
picture i've used some of the picture
i did toxic another great ending the
picture to just paul yeah i don't
get it i did and then she
deleted it from her phone and i
do and then i
said delete the cloud because this could
be humidity the cloud elite the dark
loud delete your cloud that's sansa delete
your teacher cloud your bitch by the
way when hillary clinton said delete your
account it was not funny i don't
need politicians to be funny no we
don't need us need everyone talks about
like it was the
fuck like oh my god she got
him it was the funniest he was
not funny of course it's funny can
i say i don't need politicians to
go on saturday night live either it
was a little funny just because he's
such a twitter maniac yeah but it
wasn't worth it wasn't it didn't work
he still has that account also like
you know her like staffer was
like exact her like her twitter person
is like i'm going to delete your
account is that okay ma'am and she
was like is that a thing in
thy light is i know like this
not what humans do yeah i know
i fucked up when i did the
three emojis heloise feel that your student
debt i'm like you're a lucky man
go to the polls oh alright anyway
so so small wonder was a classy
sd
pokemon go to the you you never
oh you got oh so she doesn't
even know what it is oh keep
on going to the polls alright so
small wonder was good what else he
got they did the mannequin challenge you
know i've ever really gotten too into
halloween i feel like we've discussed a
little bit that i don't really care
about ah about
you asked if you don't now or
you never did you're all about ghosts
and goblins you don't care about costa
like go so like god was like
come to harmon hi sandy yeah um
but i don't really care about doing
the costume thing but i guess it's
because you know we get to dress
up and be dumb a lot but
do not do not care now or
you never cared do you like hallowe
even when you're a kid when i
was a little kid yes but i
was a cat basically every year just
different variations why i love cats and
i wanted to be a cat yeah
i was ironically a winter power ranger
trying to be again bringing your ironically
hillary because i thought i was too
old for it in fifth grade oh
wait you were ironic about it yeah
i was ironically i was
like this is funny for me to
be a power rangers kind of when
i would when you're tapping yes yeah
although when you're ten if you just
things greatly not to allow people think
it's that you just want to be
that but that's pretty funny i don't
know if i've told you the story
before oh i hope you have and
i don't
spank you i didn't want to bring
it back really bad because i can't
remember this is a story i've thought
about i thought about this it's not
even a story it's a moment that
happened in my brain that comes back
to me so many times those are
weird there was a girl that i
went to high school with who was
hot john which a grade i wouldn't
write school and high school with her
she's like kind of a nerdy girl
and remind banerjee the kind where she
took off her glasses she was beautiful
like oh how beautiful she was she
didn't have glasses she was just ugly
oh was she put on glasses yeah
shit the berkeley nice little person
and she's like she's like but jay
she was kind of nice it's about
her she was kind of a deny
girl and i saw a commercial for
some halloween costume like a ready-made halloween
costume that involved like having an inflatable
headpiece they would make commercials for halloween
yeah yeah this was like i remember
this i remember this
seeing this thing so well and thinking
oh my god she's gonna because we
were having a costume party at school
i was like she's gonna wear that
she's gonna wear that i became convinced
thought she was going to where it
was like she is the diet she's
the type of person that is going
that would do a thing like this
because i wanted to awesome was or
the size of the head because of
because the costume was such
a dorky thing and i was saying
your yoshi do that because here's your
concern for i was concerned for her
the costume was like they they just
made up characters they weren't like established
character that they just made up a
thing i was like no kid would
ever want this and was that's okay
what if she does that i was
not so much that i would prince
authentic native costume
just make i was thinking with the
peanuts gang as well oh okay here's
the mental game i'm like oh that
sounds the pretzel gang the pits okay
hey get out of pretzel gang back
at it um were damn pretzel dough
is she um i don't think it
was that i was like
oh she will definitely be wearing that
was it like what if she wears
this it was like bad with that
kind of yea that'll back fires like
that weird cringey when you start to
have empathy when you're a little kid
and it was cringey and it was
making my heart hurt and then we
had the party she was just like
dress like a gypsy or whatever chipset
yeah
romance like she's like yeah yeah she
was a romney person who doesn't gypsy
party it was that kind of thing
yeah like everyone so everyone had their
own homemade taiwan on pc but you
can't do that anymore but those were
the days the lowest party we could
be hobos and gypsies and everyone loves
it and if you weren't a hobo
and gypsy you were actually the weirdo
everyone's so sensitive when i was a
kid every year
for halloween would have a jew party
everyone dressed up like a jew so
what did you like her or were
you just know you're just empathetic it
was just so random yeah yeah yeah
yeah and it killed me like i
can still remember the feeling and catches
cold you show up wearing so that
she sometimes yeah and she's like i
mean i will see mercilessly the shit
kicked
oh wow wow wow i'm trying to
think through my costumes i definitely was
batman when i was about five and
i've the cutest picture of my brother
and i he's superman i'm batman is
the tiniest little finest
the two men needed to save everything
um and now anyway that's a great
tagline can can i see a man
who needed to say it every batman
and superman that two men needed to
save everything that's so nice i was
a vampire and i remember my mom
doing like
i'm doing makeup for the v the
widow's widow's peak or um i was
i believe i was luke skywalker one
so i got a karate outfit and
that's how i did yeah that's a
good one i was han solo were
due to our vast my mother made
me of s o me a black
guy and make and i had a
ray gun my aunt makes costumes for
her grandkids
and she made them for her kids
when they were little would she made
them for my kids ships
was making her costumes are amazing and
she did one for my cousin's kid
from the game fortnite i think it
was fortnite there's a big tomato head
characters at a thing anyway she made
this are you making him like he
would know and you wouldn't he's the
youngest person i know had to guess
this thing he's late he's been looking
this character's head look
i like ah she made this costume
and it looked so good she like
made the head out of like just
object you know mentioning objects she formed
with mascot is like her own design
wow it was really impressive that's cool
it looks it looks like the pringles
guy is the pringles guy is the
pr guy but tomato sandwich potato king
rip i'm meals
guys is a rip off of the
pringles guy i'm gonna slay riding court
would you wear what if we said
this year let's do real costumes and
every all three of us really do
a costume on the day itself or
whatever on halloween or at a party
or something yeah we do it i
it's such a i remember every year
i went it was
there was a mandatory thing and yeah
it would depend on the the man
i basically never want to impose community
service do you go to helloween party
i decided shoe to wear a costume
for halloween i think when i was
in my thirties cool up and i
would go to and so soon we
would go to at least one every
year and it was always like what
are you going
to be this year and then i
remember we would always do it so
late that you would end up going
to the thrift store like it would
be like the thrift store we have
costumes and then it's just shit they
put together like hey you're a you're
a pimp yeah you know so but
it was always wait way too late
right so and then a certain point
i was just like i don't have
any enjoyment
and yeah doing this anymore yeah you
know i don't care and i don't
i don't even like get tricker treaters
like yeah we don't get like i
said we gotta be awesome i will
address i would love to stand i
just don't get that i would love
if they came by
our place is i think all the
kids go to a nicer neighborhood well
you know where i used to live
we lived over by bob hope's house
yeah and in a a really nice
part of toluca lake and people would
drive in there yeah yeah and so
one year it was it was really
fun i had a whole bunch of
friends over and we just walked around
because everyone is
such a like a rich area and
i had like the shittiest place in
the rich area by the way um
make every everyone it was it was
a condo literal like you know there's
like one but a condo and then
an alley and then rich houses right
so kong don't thank you so but
every place would would decorate with like
haunted house shit and have mays
this and all that stuff so it
was really fun as an adult to
like be drinking out on the street
and going through love drink it on
the street drinking on the street checking
on the street today straight straight straight
i was doing billy on the street
nice um though here's the thing though
one of the year i was hung
solo yes i'll never get this one
lady she's like who are you
you start was just coming that this
is seventy seven huge hit yeah seventy
seven vs huntsville she says it came
out in may of nineteen seventy seven
yeah feel by october there was no
it was a slow burn and it
took three months and and there were
lines around the block and people couldn't
get into it for months at a
time yeah there was still by october
local movie
theaters celebrated one year of showing star
wars yeah um so she said who
is supposed to be and i said
han solo and she said huh so
where's gretel and i was like oh
fucking no it is that i'll never
forget i borrowed a friend's cat costume
for one of my year your cat
every year i'd outgrown all of my
fringe color every
my growth spurt so it was a
great cat this year my friend gave
me her old costume and it was
like a bomb it was a full
suit like you get in it and
it had a head oh that's no
fun and then this woman said i
was a monkey and i felt so
i was like six or so i
was like so sad when you a
monkey and i was like i'm like
huh
so how monkeys have pointed ears bitch
yes how often are adults right when
they guess why don't think they should
be guessing they should shouldn't they should
be saying who are you i think
i should say oh i love your
costume wholemeal were wrong tell me about
your costume here's all they should say
wow you guys look great yeah and
give that candy yeah i
it maybe i don't know i like
all the recognition i got very shy
i didn't like you for sure know
what they are you could say yeah
oh you're from frozen but you know
oh you're a guy with a best
and a ray gun
yeah oh you're a future murderer
i i would get weirdly shy about
oh yeah it was a costume that
having to talk as well to like
like i was shocked too like i
could talk to my little friends and
everything but i didn't like your dumb
little that whole my stupid little friends
i didn't like this exchangeable girl that
used to go trick or treating with
it's good i fell in love with
her and her name is jeannie
i was so shy once i was
thinking about this the other day i
don't i don't know how it's possible
that this happened to me bring it
on but i know i have will
be able to figure it out i
have relatives that i don't trust my
memory on it but i remember it
very vividly but i've relatives ah and
had relatives in other states
still do but when i also have
relatives i went to arizona once in
multiple states i realized i went to
arizona once to my grandmother's house you
go and i go and how did
you get
i slay oh but i'm like what
was the route you like did you
go over the river you go whoa
yeah the whole the whole deal oh
but you guys you had to give
it
i yeah they get there so i
go to the i go to the
house and my grandmother says oh by
the way there's a boy your age
who and i'm i think eating i'm
saying i think i'm six i'm like
grandma um so i'm six or so
and she goes there's a boy next
door ah who is your age why
don't you go knock on the door
door and ask if he wants to
play and i was like shy and
i'm like nah i don't want to
do that and they're like yeah yeah
my parents are like yeah that will
be so fun probably just getting out
of their hair whatever um i mean
doesn't that doesn't that sound terrifying yes
but i remember the idea you want
to play that's hell
i would never do so all i
did was i went and i remember
playing in the rocks in my life
by myself for i was lying in
the rocks yeah because it's arizona and
there aren't like grass or anything so
i was like at about ninety minutes
i decided that's probably enough
to make them think that that i
was there for that long oh and
just pretended i just heard it and
then i went back in the house
and they're like how was it i
was like oh it was fun it's
great guy yeah and i got away
with a lot of car they never
as far as i know they never
like asked later about the oh what
do you think of my grandson or
anything like that it was just like
i got away with every
the story of when i was like
tagging along with my brother and his
friends and then they kind of ditched
me and i started picking flowers from
this person's yard all around this tree
and i was making a little bouquet
for my mom and this management won't
stop it in a flower he was
screaming i mean you understand now that
you're yeah but i told i was
only like six or so
evans old enough to know they ran
home and threw them in the gutter
on the wagon the wound
around you know really at because i
was so upset and embarrassed and then
i just didn't give them time i
used to when i was in high
school okay i lived across the street
from my high school right oh weird
but i still heard i still had
to the dream you could spy on
everyone
but i was on i was on
the one end very spicy just look
out your window of your school and
like see where everyone goes so they
talk to you just run like make
a bee-line fro i didn't have to
kind of get out the binoculars yeah
i you still started to go down
a street i didn't have that kind
of view but i lived across the
street so but the problem was as
i lived on one end
and my first class was when i
was a senior was the totally far
end you know so i still i
would be so late every day that
i would drive my car to as
close as i could get which was
part of the suburbs and i would
park the car and harvard yard of
course paul just yawned so hard sorry
guys i'm tired too
um so i would park the car
as close as i could get to
the school it's just you and yeah
and cover i didn't make a sound
i was quite yeah i know johnny
sound live at the acropolis so i
would park the car as close as
i could get to the high school
and these guys are like
snap chatting hiring always story and shadegg
remember that i do remember that coming
back um do to to to so
but the thing was my my mom
would still make a lunch for me
when i was a senior my god
and just to make your own lunch
give her mom a break or just
go home but that's the thing because
i would go home
relax but she would shake my house
know she'd make listen she's made me
a bag if she'd make me a
bag lunch and we should go home
which would have a sandwich chips and
an apple in it yeah right yeah
and i would be so late i
would never eat breakfast so i would
as i'm driving very hurriedly to his
closest eye
to get to the school that i
live across the street from i would
eat the sandwich and the chips for
breakfast for breakfast but i would never
eat the apple because i i didn't
want to eat the apple despised it
so i would instead the evil warm
inside i would instead to crumple up
knowledge gamble and managers from the gardens
would grumble which are ya
wanting a second
he's trying to turn it on friedman
out really focused on your number you
should be glad this book on my
interrupting your story me
good i like it better guess i
would create a way now that that's
that's a heart he wants a center
up because it means we're paying attention
and we're silent rugby mommy daddy for
y'all would crumple up the apple noisy
bag around the apple right and i
would leave it i was there just
rot in your car no i wouldn't
leave it in the car because i
wouldn't want him to collect
i would put it on the ground
next to my car that's disgusting
and i'm the stories you tell are
not ah
ah and you're not a disgusting pig
so love going home in the middle
of the day because it would seem
like a nice reset yes i would
well that's the thing xd i just
take the apple back no why didn't
you just eat the apple that your
mother may know i know but i'm
talking about like young because i was
young children like i'm talking about you
young sheldon and that ties me to
talk about young show it wasn't can
we finally talk about it i was
a boy i was a rude genius
who wore a little bow tie and
i grew up to have them doing
forty six episodes here and we haven't
talked about young sheldon yeah and forty
six yes to share the listener doesn't
know we've cut it out of every
episode oh that's so far you claims
bring up sheldon
dan can i just say that the
guy who owned the house know that
i would park in front of every
day got so pissed and like four
months into it confronted me he's like
you're leaving an apple ios able to
i would do five days like i
would go dude buys my apple so
you're driving where you're you're not pa
you know i'm parking in the suburbs
across the street from the school here
because you can't park on the school
yeah but no i would join like
kids park on the school grounds or
you could you could you just take
it to the parking lot is on
my side is where my house is
it's all the way over there i
need to get as close as the
single time first-class is demented though you
would if i was your parent i
would have gone out i would like
i would
you fuck you are my beret wasteful
gas wasting bitch apple hugging get up
five minutes earlier as waste i always
take i'm not gonna put an apple
in your lunch ever again because you're
never gonna eat it and guess what
you're going to walk to school and
you're gonna be late when you get
up late
you've never been laid anywhere never
no but it is annoying that you
would drive one inch
an inch on the map what wanna
jump up
there was dragging you've never been that
lay where it's just level and i'm
always your early person relatively so i
know i what i do is i
dick around until the last possible minute
and then i'm late major and it's
crazy because i'll be doing nothing and
then i'm going okay now i have
to rush i'm stupid i'm later to
get david he's bored by himself
sorry it was yourself and love yourself
offense to you that he was young
um i am later two things that
are in my neighborhood than i am
two things yeah further well it's the
old principle of anytime you go to
a restaurant i mean my own principle
anytime you go to a restaurant because
you're paying attention anytime you go to
a restaurant and there's no one in
it you get worse service than when
they're like who cares because they because
they're fucking around in the kitchen they're
just like doing drugs yeah i've seen
sweet bitter i went to a restaurant
recently where i think i had a
new service room
every five seconds every time some excuse
hey i wanna introduce mean they would
bring someone over or to be a
different person hey i'm going on my
break yeah second but ah jimmy scott
and then they're like jimmy's going to
carry this advancing the next time we
look at that guy that's on jimmy
it's gonna be a different it truly
was like so why are you here
like it was just who are you
i saw an eighty my
soup and lentils i saw an episode
of cheaters you know that show cheaters
yeah ps so i saw an episode
is the greatest episode i've ever slept
with joey greco here's the thing so
first this guy comes out who has
never been on cheaters before two of
this yes yeah yeah so he comes
out in a tux he's like welcome
to a very slow
actual episode of cheaters and it's not
joy gregory show things like set them
up like yeah yeah like fake situation
and then they well i don't know
that it was fake because china would
follow him around with a camera but
i think yeah you're right i do
believe it was revealed later that yeah
would that some of it was fake
but so the baby and also they
would try to like catch them it
was trump mean yeah yeah trapping so
this guy he's the executive producer
think of cheaters yeah it comes out
and he introduces like welcome to a
special episode of cheaters you've never seen
him before tex edo he's wearing a
tuxedo he's like we've been on the
air three years or something like this
and now here's your host joey greco
this is his last episode yeah and
then joey greco comes
out in air and introduces and introduces
you know how joey greco would come
out and and and it would be
a blue background that they would put
like the houston or dallas skyline by
and he he'd go well this person
is about to do something in something
but then he had been fired by
then so the person who went out
on the actual cheater run was a
third person yeah
and who ended up being the new
host three oh somebody on a podcast
was saying that they were working on
a tv show where they were like
essentially a reporter but it was like
sort of what news and it wasn't
the news but it was a version
of it and they loud if the
row the first news program got to
call itself the new yes where it
this is the last show to go
to a different job and so they
had a big send off for her
on the show but the show only
been on for a couple of weeks
and she was like no one knows
who i am like why are they
doing the sendoff and then the show
got canceled like right after right now
they did benda so he did one
send off a few days before the
big south goodbye see ya soon and
we're cancelled
none of us will be here can
you imagine i was watching fosse verdon
the other day and i was and
at one point this is a minor
minor spoiler ah gwen verdon is in
a show that cancelled after the first
performance and i cannot imagine that feeling
that with it being so raw a
show where like they like put it
work on it for more money put
it up in like it's a lie
and they were like we got we
caught wind that the reviews were going
to be really bad and ticket sales
were soft and so well ah cancelled
after one performance that's hurt i can
not imagine i mean i guess tv
shows that happens like wonderful as i
think it was on once and then
it was canceled even though they'd filmed
thirty
and a lot of shelter girls era
i think they only aired like one
or two no i i watched it
yeah on real tv on dvd no
i watched it as a thing
he watched i will say i saw
the ah the tv show emily emily's
reasons why not which only aired once
and i saw the one that aired
and it's weirdly makes me mad that
i saw like come on like my
feeling about that is just to air
them all you made them all just
air them
canceling a show and not finishing what's
already at least play the ones you
already made was the point of all
that yeah money was spent you're just
gonna show a rerun of something yeah
i don't get the people like that
people want more but sure what was
wonderful wonderful halls was really great to
tell about it because i'm looking at
the paragraph
in question should i tell her about
it cancelled after the fourth episode oh
wax oh yes but i guess i
watched it on dvd western dvd yep
um he works in a niagara falls
gift shop jays the reluctant conversations various
happy to her by the way yeah
so great yes monkey carolina and how
do you say de vargas she was
on hannibal because it's so brian rachel
err yeah um it was very imaginative
and whimsical and ah
the funny there's lee pace who i
did the seth meyer show with he
was the main guest oh shit he
was very nervous oh i always had
a crush on him from pushing daisy
why are you talking like it was
an ambitious days anyway yes yeah are
you nervous and using halt and catch
fire was which is a great show
guardians of the galaxy as ronan the
accuser
or lee pace very nervous he plays
seth meyer he played in immortal elson
lord of the ring and he's very
nervous seth hire somebody pays you went
to juilliard these great lee pace's great
well it just reminded me of like
if you're not a person if you're
just an actor who's like acting in
front of cameras all the time like
how that would
i'd be very nerve wracking it's nerve
wracking anyway oh yeah well yeah i
mean it's nerve wracking enough for us
of like who are used to going
out in front of crowds but for
him it's just or a person like
that who's just a film actor doing
those shows is like it shouldn't be
that hard they don't make them easy
guys you know they don't do this
a greener i think his middle name
is leanna ringer
look at him rinder look at the
picture right above it i think he's
grinning like a motherfucker make them more
facility last names i think i like
when jimmy fallon plays a game with
somebody like to see people loosen up
a little bit yeah i like to
see people stretching beforehand i like that
would be that's the show
i like people stretching him i think
ah i'm being a leotard i think
the conversation should be looser and the
people shouldn't be expected to sit and
be like this this should be a
show yeah this is real little be
a show i tell you something i
i i feel like i always do
very badly on talk shows i'm not
a good panelist feels hard what happens
is i think that i
think a lot of times the audience
like the the people who are who
are producing the show know who i
am but the audience has no idea
alright so it's a weird i'm in
this weird twilight place where you talk
about national be funny but it's like
i don't think it's gonna be funny
they don't have a basis yeah why
why would they be interested in a
baby pale where you meet you
no yeah i wanna see that picture
you've seen it yeah yeah you're right
i feel like i always bomb and
it's always awkward and i feel really
but i want to get good i'm
like i can see like you would
be good i feel i get too
nervous i can see a version of
my life where i eventually become or
left it's firing at them like i
wanna be like amy sedaris which just
goes out and does whatever she wants
but people already know that and expect
that that's the thing i would prefer
to like what i'd like to do
it jimmy carter's part
mastodon is go out and do a
bit like steve martin used to do
yes that's but no one knows who
i am so i can't do that
stuff so when you luana i mana
talk show you've got to explain who
you are yeah and that's no fun
this is very relatable it's very relatable
to everyone like okay substitute talk show
for everything i knew
ever seen i say isn't meant to
be reliable basis of sexual orientation became
a topic of public discussion when in
twenty twelve he was identified as gay
by ian mckellen oh my god we're
doing the hobbit that's not cool because
having was described at the press a
blunder and an accident on his party's
base one about by them yeah ian
mckellen he blundering around here in an
interview with the new york times in
twenty eighteen she's just doing a league
greener pace very nervous
identified as gay by the gallon in
a blunder and that is yeah a
year later okay of course years later
we have to dig a break six
years later
we're back we're back we're back the
three of us the threesome boys damn
freedom did we call ourselves there was
a do a new one random boys
oh there's always in the last episode
yeah i don't remember if i was
ah no freedom boys were
i have no clue and it was
mere minutes ago but yeah year minutes
your cats meerkats dad was a meerkat
it was mere cats ago lauren you
when did you stop wanting to be
ill when did you stop wanting to
be a cat and why did you
want to be a cat um i
wanted to be a cat you like
me
yes on your little schneck giving the
middle finger she's what that's right yeah
yep read it and weep oh hey
yeah
i want to be kept forever because
it was like fun cute gneezy and
then i think you mean for halloween
yeah oh you didn't want to be
a cat and real life no you
weren't insane sometimes i wish i was
my dog seems easier you wish you
were your dog yeah being like enslaved
essentially we've we've done this yeah we
haven't done this path but um you
viewed very differently due to you you
have a dirty are your dogs as
slaves little sleaze uses dogs you actually
read every nervous dee loves his dogs
sleep what's your favorite dog you have
me whatever dog you have i will
say okay we have two dogs now
and ga
the one that we got first um
spent a lot of watch the oh
so we're gonna watch kevin sent an
e-mail she sent an email of work
yeah it was for the screen he
started to send a work email to
sell my soul guy or so we
got your you listening to these idiots
talk and talk again i hate it
here i did see it's
so ga ga chua spent a lot
of time with her because she would
take her to work every day when
she was doing jillian rush she was
in the office and so i never
really saw georgia all that much and
now georgia has been the cradle in
the suv's boo now georgia it has
come around on me so hard to
where she like in
the morning she can't do anything unless
she comes over and gives me kisses
first so it's like if i'm when
she gets up if i'm even upstairs
in the kitchen she has to come
running over to me and gets up
on her hind legs and i'm like
ok honey i give her a little
kiss and and then she'd mentally is
like fine but she you get wow
get up before her yeah sometimes my
i guess my dog is that weird
dog sleep in your bed if my
dog is still asleep i tried to
go back to sleep i'm like okay
what does your dog sleep and no
no because my dog sleeps in the
bed but then when i get up
she'll get out but she if she
gets up before i get up i
mean she's going to piss or shit
and yes well that's why when i
hear her feet on the ground ago
that's why we create our what that's
why we create our dogs yeah she's
normally she'll normally hold it but if
i hear her it's like for whatever
we also rocky angle rocky we slept
in the bed with a lot and
it's just constant coming out of the
covers going back into the covers and
i just would never get a good
night's nocturnal owls are they really
yep i got my cat my dog
nocturnal meaning they sleep all night no
they come alive at night when they
live in a tree it's yeah yeah
i'm a dog expert man dogma expert
i'm a dogma ma max
yeah your dogma ran over my karma
of the two great tastes every time
i ran over my dog shut up
no one makes more sense was that
like a bumper stickers yeah it was
like back in the eighties it was
like when everyone was talking about karma
you know is a way they got
that's over was a way of making
fun of you know how like everything
in the eighties was making fun of
anyone who had any sort of yeah
spirituality exactly you know this was like
huh yeah you're talking
about karma will your karma ran over
my dogma if anyone even tried to
think about their fellow man they were
ridicule ridicule or or about not acting
like remember i love remember how alan
alda being sensitive was like yeah thing
to like make fun of time like
oh who are you out in all
the real men don't eat quiche ah
come on i didn't even know what
key
sj was before either hearing that it
was terrible because real men guy it's
a very vicious very feminine food but
only to embarrass you but it's pronounced
crash
squish
based upon the sound of when i
drop it on the floor that goes
with a little squish oh that's cool
it's way shy got my wish all
squish i dropped my question going around
among get out this
yeah that place everybody's going to go
see the fisherman oh wait i that's
wish that not that i'm glad we
brought that rope
that we are playing yeah jumper
oh damn three them boys have gone
deep into boys have gone off the
rails here deep and look this is
our last episode that people are gonna
hear why didn't she had a pump
an hour like them want the more
okay yes should we pump it up
or make them want more we don't
know what to do with this voice
the last one this is the last
one of the free ones yeah me
okay so we want a better outfit
my freedom gray mother i want to
oh you
you know that is like no one
i'm scared to be jim morrison are
you scared of a lizard king yeah
you should been scary yeah this is
very very geico gecko yes they lacking
jim morrison was the original geico gecko
commercials are getting crazier and crazier they're
just they have nothing to do with
it okay here's any here's commercials now
stop it first of all commercials are
good if you want to see him
local l a improv actors who improved
something relatively minor really funny in in
an audition and they're made to yeah
they're made to replicate it onset because
it was slightly different than a non
funny person yeah and then and ah
here's commercials though these days which is
just like they throw with a silly
situation out there of like ah oh
man i want to get rid of
my car and then like
you know a giant crane picks it
up and like throws it across the
the street right and there and there
and then it's like boy you don't
want to be in this situation do
you well another situation you don't want
to be in and then totally unrelated
thing exactly does anyone know what i'm
talking about yeah i do and here's
the thing i produce lot of those
commercials and i think this is raw
i think commercials should just be like
this
get guy co-insurance and then it goes
it's better to drink coke i like
how about mcdonald's this show that you
don't want somebody hold me just shows
just new commercials each one just shows
you the thing and they're all three
seconds long and i was like do
you watch one hundred of them yeah
between every ten it's the same person
and all of them
now there's no actor it's just the
logo with a voiceover it says do
this how about mcdonald's how about mcdonald's
have that drink coke drink coke for
dinner
every day just get weird weird yeah
drink cocoa butter and marshmallows how about
this hey what about the sky co-anchor
oh my god coinsurance we had a
mutual friend paul who was so upset
at mcdonalds who was like why doesn't
mcdonald's
donate their all their advertising budget to
charity for one day because not everyone
knows what mcdonald's is i'm like that's
not how advertising works we all know
what mcdonald's is we needed like put
in our brains of like oh yeah
that does sound good i'm gonna go
get it
like his point was that commercials are
only there to tell you about what
a product is i don't think i'm
entirely huh how about that you take
the money up to my chest you
take the money through my mouth i'm
in birmingham for one day which won't
stop anyone from wanting it and then
you donate
that money that's the thing i think
his i don't think he was trying
to say because he said no you
know no one forget like he did
say that though he's explicitly said yes
go the fuck that was it neil
yes it was neil campbell i wish
i guessed him neil peart neil peart
from our friend new toy food could
you julie fred i'm
please i couldn't hear him in between
all the drum sounds
ah drugs out did we take a
break no yeah we already did good
we know it's not alright let's take
a break
hey listen did you ever see i
know this is coming out of nowhere
guys oh my god did you ever
see the video for she's gone by
hall notes i why would you bring
something like that up i just think
about it
ah they'll get a lot out of
it
oh she's gone oh well ah no
i want the devil to replace it
she's gone what's in the video paul
um it's them sitting on a weird
set the second one down yeah so
they're sitting on like a tv set
this is a very early days of
videos and look there's
like a weird murder shack in the
middle of nowhere yeah let's spring behind
something and it's daryl hall hear us
back he looks like a weird like
a gigantic poof his head ticket or
poo had chosen to poof
okay there there's chart is there though
to see the sleeveless t shirts
this is what passed for fashion with
a back in the seven cars next
song from
that show with stephen merchant i don't
know hello lady yeah was it i
it was one i don't know starting
christine was supposed to teach us how
to tap dance yes will make i
send you guys daddy the instagram ad
for the tap line were like you
guys should sign up for this i
honestly was kidding it was a strategy
obvious to a dummy no strap on
top on what's on tap fun yeah
robber things you snap onto the ship
onto your sneakers and has taps in
the soles and then you like do
a workout while tap while it seemed
like it was an exercise video is
like exercise while you learn how to
tap and then it was like a
billy blank style video
come on make those sounds come on
here we go yeah and like you're
doing wings and stuff like soups yeah
literally it's good
yes in mud yeah it's very sloppy
alright this video everyone should watch the
daryl hall and john oates she's gone
is a great song so just listen
to the audio day like i don't
like video they look insanely bored to
be their smugness it's hard to tell
if this is a choice or if
they're really mad that they had to
make this video and every time they
get to the line i'd pay the
devil to replace her a guy walks
by
a classic devil costume and daryl hall
literalism here we go and he throws
up some fake money
laziest video i've ever seen in my
crazy it's really crazy shot in approximately
how long does the song yeah exactly
always get the reacted on to play
the guitar for so should we do
another take of this
no we got it i mean i
will say that they look cooler than
covering his hand there's knowing he's actually
because darryl hawley kinda looks like bowie
you see he's got a bowie hairstyle
and he's kinda got a little glam
outfit weird platform birkenstocks office yeah cool
like someone just put it
together for fun this has nothing to
do with all of it all videos
up until about nineteen eighty two were
shot at like public access space stations
with that kind of technology and the
others in the end they're all like
this where it's like you know screen
technology they're all as bad as this
until michael jackson the same way your
lord in the sea
of the michael jackson video vanguard award
hi why do you bring him up
all the time you have to set
the
to sit the dial
we've gone up there euro day did
you see michael jackson's conversations the cutest
thing where this families these sons got
their dad surprise tickets to see janet
jackson's always loved her his whole life
and he was so excited oh so
justin timberlake
look at these tits and then he's
standing there like that they get him
backstage after the show and he's he's
based reviewed he's talking to is his
family think about what a thrill it
was to just see the concert he's
like the biggest thrill for me was
just when she came out on there
on that stage and i was with
sam and and i was like i'm
in the room
i'm with janet jackson it was just
incredible and she's she's my same age
and so we're you know grew up
alongside her meanwhile she's like she's like
ah kind of like almost resting her
chin on his shoulder like trying to
and he doesn't notice her for the
longest time and then he she finally
puts her hands on her and she's
like thank you so much like won't
even
look at it because he's so happy
i get it i'm talking about the
jackson anyway i ever met she's a
pie seller right to her face i'll
love you baby i love yeah would
you give me some room to talk
about hey we'll be like shut up
you bitch i sought i'm like the
news and i kept news that it
was going to be a bad like
something was gonna happen right
like this man wanted to go to
the concert more than all at the
end they like and then you got
to me or like suddenly he shits
yeah that would've been a great human
interest story
man it's just he is very nervous
shit his pants they call him the
soiled fan ian mckellen told everyone should
it is a blunder that man shit
his pants
ian mckellen movie
tell me a secret
ah it's just like lord of the
rings and did quite patrick stewart has
one black toner hill just aren't the
gaffer out of that shit
ah oh by the way comedy bang
bang we are gaffer once in the
middle of a show you gotta do
this thing that you were mocking in
mckellen for doing yes he's gay
no once in the middle of a
show i was in the middle of
an interview and suddenly from right behind
me because there's a fake wall right
by me i just hear ah oh
so fucking loud ah he fell asleep
in the middle of a taping of
the show and was snoring so fucking
loud and i was like the reviews
are in that's it
cred i was working on something in
the wardrobe man fell asleep and took
a picture with those really funny but
then he did get fired later
football label multiple fl sleeps but like
i thought it was funny but i
guess people really would not think that
if they were in charge i didn't
like send it to them straight to
judd apatow yeah look
yeah well guys it's time for reacher
well yeah it's time for three years
do we have one i do did
we pick one sure okay great yes
it's okay i like this game categories
one player see category and the other
players take turns naming items that belong
in that group the category computers obama
lou bopp read
to
scott i know that you're paying attention
and that's where interruption is coming i
am but tires important information category categories
one player states a category headaches categories
one oh i see like a crazy
one it does look like categories it
does because the one is categories categories
one
huh higher seating category no it's categories
yes one player states category and the
other players take turns naming items that
belong in that group category can be
as broad oh you want the spotlight
again narrows types of dogs traditionally a
club rhythm games
up to space oh now we're lee
pace keeps up lee grinned release greater
pace got very nervous famously gay so
players wanting to come up with their
response the end of mandatory chosing and
we counted out coulter easy the game
is the game continues until players were
out of ideas with category let's do
it alright let's do it
that's how fast we're going alright
we do we alter dogs
wait you'll see like schnauzer do are
we going clockwise see you names and
dogs huh
speed know how many dogs you know
wow i do a lot of dogs
first of all there's fuckin eighteen fifth
eighteen thousand dogs here and this all
started slower
though you can do it faster good
for you too okay okay
dogs schnauzer pekingese koala pitbull
mr worldwide you're out a dog eat
around see you can't you're your own
worst enemy i know you're our worst
enemies it's okay it's your we're your
association sickness we go against each other
games for you i actually don't know
a lot of dogs we go get
each other about we go against each
other with dogs isn't this the site's
alright
poodle
cali
labrador
golden retriever
i think you're done
just get a faraway look in their
eyes up to them and do it
again now paul comes up with the
category ready and go
cars ford honda
saturn taurus nissan porsche tesla jeep mini
cooper delorean range rover
jeep cherokee lamborghini
prius corolla toyota
ah sai on
focus odyssey
ah crown victoria and
i was saying it
how dare we were like we were
doing like companies and model cars though
they're all cars all cars throw cars
so you're out i guess i'm out
he eyes he screamed over the one
that i was saying although you took
a lord you have to keep going
god that looks okay next you just
got i mean stephen scott
chevrolet lebaron chrysler
camaro ah porsche i said that already
i'm out
yeah wow the judge was so much
to yeah okay you just the last
category ready okay and go
audio equipment headphones
i hate you here buds microphones computer
windscreen speaker
chords subwoofer ox chords
engineer love che agreement no you're out
he's not equipment us kevin does not
equipment us he's a person
i won't admit that hgb my cables
hey since you shouldn't pay to him
two
i want you and did we all
win one we all won one i
think did you win dogs did you
win dogs know she was famously out
it's a no for me dogs
i do one more alright you pick
it body parts nose dna yeah just
out of the way head
less ball right bow to small toe
but dinah
joe pugh bees but
fingers behold anus hey they're kind of
different okay lords out he said bustle
that's a weird way you say it
i say i knew
who is it to me yeah i
love my doula upland rice eyebrow liver
large intestine small intestine pancreas kidney foot
plague our skin
nose hair knows we were saying oh
yeah oh you went three times
oh no i should yeah that sounded
like what you were saying i was
doing the soccer thing what was that
like oh hey there that's just like
the the the judge was hamas yeah
yeah that's just a hair away from
it behave
a well this is our last episode
in the free feed yeah guys this
is the last one place gets to
a freemium yeah if you're listening on
stitcher premium will be back next week
enlisted for but if you're listening in
the future when we're free this is
the last one because we're recording six
more but they're stitcher premium exclusive if
you want to hear more of this
show go sign up for stitcher premium
get a free month and then cancel
after the makina went on charge of
what happens after that first huh no
we're not but hey you know you
probably have a lot of great programs
that you're that you'll probably end up
staying but if you tell yourself you're
gonna cancel yeah you'll sign up and
the guy yeah here's me dollars a
month listen you stupid you've you gotta
trick
yourself set a calendar or rick yourself
that says nancy stitcher up never gonna
hurt you oh oh never gonna run
around and desert
we're gonna see ya never gonna say
nah cry never gonna say to pass
for dessert you but here's the thing
for sleeping around each other fossil whoa
it comes out on stitcher first and
then much later it's releasing the three
feet so if you only know it
as a free show
and you're you're gonna write you're thinking
about rainbows are you ever gonna do
more freedoms we might be doing the
now on stitcher
yeah so here look at our instagram
figure it out figure it out i
figured out the grey but i figured
it out buddy guys thanks for the
fun thank you i'm trying out a
little more enthused well right i love
you guys thank you for the good
times the great times and hey between
thank you for the bad times now
even know you know no
thank you for the bedtime know if
you've given us bad times real bang
thank you for my sham friends champagne
from a real friends we love doing
this show and we love that you
love listening to types of champagne types
of champagne carvel but with volker don't
real
i don't know anymore
um alright that's cool those are the
only types of things that we knew
ah luxury automobile your money bridge of
caviar
thanks everyone hey lucky guy we love
you bye
uh