three
ah oh yea okay did you guys
notice that i was doing a little
character in the theme song no lauren
no i tune you out i'm scott
why do you
i'm not i to you fuck me
fuck me you to me how do
you out you to ne out i
do me too me too me too
me out
love that song it's so good so
good lauren would you would you like
to be an alien and go to
another planet and then right now goodbye
now and then alibi wasn't another planet
i would be an alien right johnny
she got you i mean but you
didn't go to another planet being alien
and then give the the the alien
to you aliens would
be an alien give them give them
an impression of what humans are like
but you're acting really weird i went
well yeah i would just do if
i went there i'd be like okay
so what planet man doing xanax okay
don't be them you won't see alexandra
i'll be the z anoxia
okay and i was i was one
of them i was gonna say ah
we're using lee north think
better put well what if it was
half xerox half lean earth in our
our planet's split wax cleaved in twain
yes plextor yeah and then they they
come together and you both are from
there yeah and i'm arriving yeah like
a spaceship i mean it's it's it's
it's an aspect shuttle it's invisible like
wonder woman's plane why
did i get it we shouldn't all
be earthy to spray candidates so yeah
i feel like it should be like
nasa that i like got sent out
like yeah you know it's like like
asda oh shit that's good maybe let
him have it did okay okay so
you're arriving okay and i'm getting out
and we put on our universal translators
ooh good so much like captain marvel
wearing flippers
we should be recording this for our
sound effects record oh yeah what do
we have hey just pouring water tank
scuse me hi hey will you speak
earlier you're using universal translator yeah you
have yours on to alum speaking english
was yeah we know because we can
understand it because you are wearing what
is english like english is the language
of me
my country in what's a country you
want a country it's like a landmass
on a planet i mean customer enough
on plaques or question asks you
a country is like a landmass on
a planet that we kind of arbitrarily
determine yeah it has it's own rural
you lost me at english
so i'm trying to teach you i'm
here to just kind of explain what
human being what earth do what are
these you mean tara yeah tarot terror
are you guys still there we thought
you would be extinct by now because
of the way you treat each other
ah yeah we're doing great actually rose
good deal always act like everything's about
to
end and then it gets at least
five temporaries before it gets really dire
again okay what are you doing here
i'm here to teach you about human
beings from earth i didn't realize there'd
be a test okay there's we're just
minding your own business and see oh
i've didn't think i was going to
school but we're so nevermind don't have
to lie
wow that was our first contact like
hey i thought we did pretty good
i think we did pretty good it
was it was kind of impacting
nah i just wanted to abduct you
what was good stuff and you're all
right here's my buttle do whatever you
need if you're not we just handed
to you oh yeah just portable we
have portable teacher uhm i don't think
so
oh she says you've jumped off that
cliff she jumped into our battles and
out of our cars
zooming my bottle
she was simply awesome
hey we loved her
i loved her we woke up and
suddenly we were in love well yeah
i'm back oh and i just climbed
out of two buttonholes hey congrats you
look like it i gotta go now
you know i don't care that she's
back anymore wish she'd stop announcing she's
just gonna leave right away oops i
forgot my apple watch but yeah oh
that's what that is wow primitive earth
technology apple oh i'll be back just
to explain that really quick oh is
a fruit you can bite it yes
we used to have that now all
of our food
is gas oh what does that taste
like it's gross
buy it tastes like what humans call
petrol i'm just gonna stop acknowledging her
i'm back i just wanted to let
you know something anyway so what do
you want i just wanted to tell
you guys about games thinking about going
because i don't think you have that
here for you to work what do
you do at work um you're we're
talking we're yeah we're know i know
i'm just back and i'm not ff
from here we know you're back be
polite to hurt all your announcements yeah
anyways you can go now so yeah
pretty fun to go goodbye yeah okay
anyway yeah that was fake i'm actually
still here
i hate earthlings okay now i'm leaving
this is what you were like as
a little kid
probably yeah yeah because pretending to believe
yeah waiting around the next thing talked
about me
sure the bed
so going to school with my books
tied up in a belt
much like samantha partington
over the american girls she had a
thing to carry her books that there
wasn't a belt but it was two
things with like a strap yeah so
it was like a strip of wooden
beam on the top o buckles of
round and you'd slide the box like
a pilgrim's hat pilgrim's hat do you
do we talk about this before like
when you were fucking kid you had
to carry around a
bunch of goddamn books on your baddies
yeah bags ever and then go with
some people were as low slung because
i was cool at the time yes
and then and not hinder your walk
and then we had to put them
in our bathroom lockers we weren't allowed
to carry backpacks all day exactly we
did talk about i think i would
carry a safeguard and move along i
would carry a stack of books because
every class expected you to have your
book with you your textbook with you
but i never wanted to go to
the locker because my locker was filled
with whatever shit in papers and stuff
that were there in the first couple
of weeks and they never went to
a taped up on there exactly but
once again my locker was my pride
and joy i loved going to my
locker yeah and i loved organizing it
and also all my classes were all
over the place so it was like
it just would
waste somewhere and even at your school
yeah so i guess when you had
to go learn how to put on
pants get train yeah
i was thinking about could you ever
put on pants the opposite way you
mean but first girl style like instead
of going into him they go on
you we want wait we've talked about
this too and i'm fighting we we
did talking about just because i said
i throw my pants up in the
air oh for them to fall down
over me know but could you could
you put your pants on where they
they come up
if through your where you're doing inside
out know you're going and say you're
you're there inside out you put that
you put your feet on top of
your plane into into the into the
the leg holes and then you go
up and you turn them right-side i'm
sure you could but some why i
want to do away you need to
know you know you're so here's what
i thought you
i'm gonna take my pants off ya
putting your feet through the leg holes
yeah enter and going inside it right
from inside out to rights item scott
know it your brain works in such
magical ways hulse what can we ever
understand a creature such as you study
me i guess why
or a microscope i'd like to put
a giant opinion you stick you on
a boy like a butterfly did i
tell you about the benz dude like
whoa the who the bug dude and
junior high
i don't think oh did i tell
you but the pocket lady o two
no stories although i don't believe you
sounds familiar by nine noon um ok
we had to do bug collections in
had to got to in science class
in junior high know that for i
call bullshit on that you bring me
the bug bring me the bugs i'll
tell you what i think
about it we had to do leave
you what they are
no you had to end and call
causes got big grainy get next and
they would tell you what bugs you
had to collect right and you had
to pin them into styrofoam and identify
them and all that fucked and they
and you'd go where the fuck am
i and how do i get these
bugs and they're like get a big
net and go and go find them
places right and and they go hey
there's a park across the street with
a pa
pond there's a whole bunch out there
plus this drunk teacher yeah i was
like yeah this is comp this is
what i wonder it's a big ask
so hung over right okay guys i
don't think it's going election i mean
we dissected frogs and we know we
expected from glam so other people's insects
baby frogs and eighty pigs but so
the bottle is sick when you think
about it so the bug collection thing
king yeah and some probably horrific i
mean i thought it was gross but
i didn't think it was like inhumane
but i didn't want to do think
it's bad now so the vogue collection
i went out with a with a
net a butterfly net or whatever and
try to hold on a second yeah
were you provided the nets are you
had to get the net buyers think
you had to get the net by
fucking garbage terrible because my horse i
went out one day to the park
and swung around
the neck the net just going i'm
trying to get a book and oh
i can get okay okay when people
talk about where you believe they would
do with the time machine i would
go watch this
in a here let's go fucking with
some net that would change the course
of the future forever if we want
yeah the talk about the butterfly i
never talked i was gonna say it's
not okay not catching a butterfly effect
so what can you do better for
them so you get you get like
three months to do this right you
know i fucking hopes yeah yeah so
there's it's not like he's saying hey
do this tonight the rest of your
academic legs that you find well you're
certain no you're supposed to find certain
bugs and be able to identify that
is so rude obviously not
cause if you kill one you go
to jail yeah you can he can
it goes to hell because it's in
the middle of asking forgiveness for instance
interrupts some baptize so you don't know
so basically like the clock is ticking
down on this three months right and
it's getting closer and the first couple
of months you're like yeah at some
point i'm going to try to get
these bugs or whatever yeah this
is doable month in it's like yea
i gotta get these bugs but i
can still do it right i mean
it's gonna come down to the wire
and then the week of you have
no bugs in your life this is
how oh boy it was in biology
classmate was my software euro is actually
a freshman year class but i skipped
it freshmen cause i really don't want
to do and then i was a
sophomore in it with all these
freshmen what was kind of fun and
there were two other sophomores and we
had to do a project where we
i know where we had to like
do like an internship for like the
whole semester and like go to a
scientific internship of some they wanted people
to do this or they or you
just showed up and said you have
to take me on as it was
like it was like you had to
figure out all out yourself and so
of course i
just ignored it for like ever months
and months and i was like oh
shit that's due and then my friends
mom like new a biologist or whatever
who was like going to like do
ah like get some samples at a
creek and i like went
a miserable hike tagged along with these
two people randomly and like helped them
like collect yet for one day or
so yeah i say and then they
say oh yeah then i wrote the
whole thing as if it was over
say damn well you know i had
a i was not gonna i wasn't
going to graduate high school and the
the person calls me to talk you
into it
yeah i was like alright i'll do
um no they called me and said
oh by the way you're not graduated
graduating high school because you never did
your so i hope that's not how
they said it oh by the way
you're not graduated high school oh by
the way well at the office yeah
obviously oh by the way oh something
that just came up um no they
said you're not graduating high school because
you never did your work study thing
and i was like oh yeah
and this is another insane blogs the
books from five years ago you're supposed
to like kind of figure out yeah
how so i was like what unfair
so i was like what do i
have to do and they're like well
you should you should have had this
already but you you need to do
one of these few things right so
i went to the i went to
the public access tv stage
ocean where i had to find a
woman with hairs gold is the sun
find a raven's feather black has the
night so i hadn't done any episodes
of that tv show in my senior
year because i was going to the
high school of the arts and i
went to the head of the public
accessing like yeah i haven't seen you
around this year i'm like dude could
you just say
sign this please do come and bang
bang you just sign this thing saying
i've been here all year work yeah
what's it gonna take to and he's
like alright but only if you come
back to summer and do more episodes
of your of your show like we've
missed having you around i'm like i
promised i never saw again but i
graduated high school your law this story
is they begged you to do more
episodes of your show i get it
only a week let me show you
for your high school kids show is
the best show on the network
ah listen child we love having you
around here it is oh good good
shows it's so good anyway so i
went to tv camp at the public
access station yeah but your shows were
good two shows were fantastic i would
love to see them i didn't get
to do any fun show like that
some broadcasting thing where it was was
just like radio show i told you
about this because there was the there
was the local newscaster who someone just
described the richard geer rumor to him
and stuff oh yeah it's like no
not two people out well it's it's
it's richard gear rod stewart and this
guy i'm rod stewart i heard
separately rumor was it super rumor gerbils
for both i never heard her by
her journals for both but never gerbils
for both please
it was everywhere it was i'll have
turtles for both um two for a
durable but if it there was so
i did this very like we do
adults have a durable
i don't know that you really get
to kin pet well this ties in
my bug story okay you caught a
terrible
put it up my hands
ah no so
paul and if i'm interrupting you please
let me know but you pause laughing
right now because i've just i know
i've told the story before and it's
like it's not worth it it's not
worth that you listener if you haven't
heard the story you go rewind this
podcast and just rewind every other episode
one and continue okay so
sure
it is though it's a kids pet
it's good it's bad because your ability
to and talk to him raster the
causes is giddy big yeah there are
some adults who have guinea pigs yeah
but no adult like has what about
the old boys why like why don't
people have just one goal of horrible
yeah that's why that would be so
no one has to show sucks sus
oh that would be sucks
so anyway so the devil's life span
two mondays
so it's the week of having a
turn in and i'm like what the
fuck am i going to do about
this bug collection thing and and my
my friend goes oh there's this dude
who sells bugs
oh perfect and we're like what and
live and no no but a's leg
he's he lives in a web he's
like he does this to them all
day long he does this for all
of us junior high students you gotta
go to his house and pave paper
bugs bootleg bug me
as a science teacher in cahoots with
the bug man oh i never thought
i did the bug man looked like
the science teacher with a fake mustache
by any chance thank your science teacher
and drive around laughing at you all
trying to jump around with idiots just
find the bug man and he's just
counting these like waiting for his like
camcorders going footage of all these dumb
fucking kids then he and the bug
man laugh at it
and they're buying in the manner himself
and looking at the mirror please go
mister signs of the boatmen
ah so we go over all of
the ideas to ah how's everything we
hear about we hear about bug man
and we're like okay we make it
a point i forget disappointment but yeah
it was like you have an appointment
after this guy's job
yeah but all those days it was
after this guy's job at his apartment
right i'm sure where he caught cockroaches
under the bed yeah so we come
to kids so so in my mind
he's not catching syphilis in my mind
this is going to be like a
simple transaction of he goes oh hey
great here you are you'll need this
bug it will what kind of bugsy
need okay it's this amout
out of money and it'll take twenty
minutes channel star supposed to keep the
bugs alive for like months no no
no you killed you they're dead they're
dead and you put pins in them
and and and display them and put
like that name of it was never
pardoned that's good that's good from the
very beginning you are killing these diameter
it's like it's like lee yea or
you have to keep it
a lot if you can keep this
in the snow fly spider life from
your parents
fine true so that's what those things
are supposed to live that long
but it was like going to a
drug dealer's house or something where where
sounds like it for sure you'd knock
on the door and the guy's like
alright well come on in here and
we got oh no he's a creep
of course i have a lot of
bugs here is my selection and he
goes but the thing about it is
you can't just buy the bugs from
me you're going to
have to answer questions in your class
about like an uncle so i'm going
to have to give you a lot
of information about love you can't say
anything bad about targets ah so he's
like you i'm going to have to
teach you everything about each bug oh
you're trying not to do that sir
it was five fucking hours we're sitting
there
live sleeps apartment as he teaches us
about every bug in our eyes or
glassdoor and we're like wow it's the
fucking bugs master work that you put
in and of course then i arranged
things free i arrange them on my
thing i turned into pay for i
turn them in and the teacher never
says one word about asks me any
question about it just like his head
was down
down on the desk yeah because he
was like i have this whole five
thousand bugs around me maybe kids maybe
you weren't supposed to be able to
do yeah you are all supposed to
fail ok somebody you found the bug
you found the bug man of cypress
california
ah mr signs and the bug man
mr bug man bug man of cypress
california that's alright creepy we have sick
break we'll be right but i
and we're back aramaic yeah and what
sort of bogus yeah some you want
to say sign kevin but we're off
the wrong track yeah wow knew the
things that we say to kevin oh
very friendly guy
merciless oh kevin like ming let me
tell you something kevin loves to spill
the tea and we lap it up
like little pigs he's given give a
small these more tea
well we're back and you can do
about it you know stop the podcast
yeah like most others and never listen
to it again
what were you gonna say lauren yeah
what were you gonna second tell us
now no but no but tell us
the other thing you are going oh
fine i'll say another thing if you
want a yeah you might say please
say another thing think back to high
school and all the ways i'd procrastinate
things and all things i didn't understand
that i was just going along with
and it's just crazy when you think
back to that time
like you're just sitting it's crazy you
don't understand at all what is being
explained so not listening hey yeah sounds
like your life now yeah true i
just cross over a little bit i
struggled rectal questions newcomers i struggled to
sign so much my first science class
in high school was abs introductory physical
side freely
of arable piss syndrome
wow my piss drone
irritating i even beat it doesn't burn
is just irritating me
peta syndrome
sidra
what's p s year introduced
it's introductory physical science hon what does
that mean i don't remember yeah needless
to say i was not doing well
in that class physical so what would
it mean i wonder well it's like
that's where you have your your beakers
and your erlenmeyer flasks your blood sugars
share buttons yeah here be yeah why
i'm making potions i took chemistry and
i was like why
am i doing i know and i
was able to teach chemistry ah well
here's what happened to me was i
was so bad in it because we
had tracks you know track one traffic
inspector check for we did not have
fields one through whatever track mean that
means you're are you does like you're
a dum dum yeah yeah i'm a
truck for is that like what
trump yeah yeah that's right you don't
need to know santoni you're a dreadful
well real work on wrong i was
track one oh that's the thing i
grew up smart yeah and so they
expected me yes yard i was walking
believe i was one of those people
where they say you're not living up
to your potential and it's like actually
maybe this is beyond me well i
was
like you know me like like what
what i don't know what your dad
oh yeah bro smart i'm clearly having
a problem with this yeah and you're
accusing me of not applying myself i
was like maybe a kid can't do
this i coasted through elementary school every
ou didn't and everyone's like you're you're
incredibly smart and then come seventh grade
where they're like now you
have to do homework i was like
oh no no no no i don't
like doing this i've been able to
homework till you're in seventh grade maybe
six or so i mean you've got
some states actually had a lot of
homework growing out homework every every grade
from what i remember now kindergarten they
made me tear national weakness
i
um this disease come out of your
eyeballs this weekend huh
so there was some project that we
had to do at some point it
was an individual project it was like
all of us doing the same thing
and i was i for some reason
i had to write this paper i'd
write a paper on something we all
write a paper on something oh yeah
even write papers for some reason i
chose know this isn't high school this
was ipos
and i chose computer languages i can't
know what the what the parameters were
but i was like i don't know
i like video games and meat is
i don't know yeah and i just
remember like writing this thing because best
i could trying to make it into
something about like cobalt or yeah yeah
cobalt dos and all this
shit oh my god i did not
do well i remember the the
like das boot
you can't have both talks
you can either get us voter doesn't
ah
but i remember the teacher being mr
hill friday and he was being he
was acting he wasn't acting mr hill
frisch mister he was all these are
pretty joy hilferty right now
israel for it you've got to stop
this you know hillary was mr hilferty
and he was acting like i was
trying to pull it over on him
like i dude i'm trying the best
i guess i didn't have the language
to say come on man you have
done compiling i can't do oh yeah
no no no there were some some
and also sometimes i just hated the
teacher and i was like i'm not
only for you so then i moved
down to
track two for biology yeah that's hard
yeah i did great know waterfall i
was like yeah thank you and then
the fall so that i did well
and in that and then the movie
back of the truck wow and i
was like no this is like the
other one but more yeah i'm not
going to do better at this than
i did at the one that had
injured
victory in the name sven did they
movie down again or no i want
to go to summer school for canvasser
and then i didn't have to do
science in my final year i feel
like i'm having the craziest mind melt
right now because i thought your shirt
said metallica this whole time yeah and
i just saw it and it looks
like it changed yeah like right in
front of us like no one
two if i turn to the side
what i feel like it feels like
lenticular i am just wanting to like
throw up like it felt so confused
you are so confused you under throws
i was so certain that's what it
says no and it doesn't so i
think i hadn't looked at it and
read it multiple times right well it's
in the metallica fan yeah but you're
really you're crazy fuckin saying r e
m okay h h q it's the
same rpms franklin i don't i don't
know but that really made me feel
weird
yeah you want to throw up you
were so yeah put your head between
your knees dirs your head between knees
out your own ass okay well science
i took i took biology in ninth
grade the best guy my home but
where we had to dissect a frog
in that worm no no i did
the fraud that old yeah
dissect that frog and that was still
think about they did the work i
expected gross i could picture it like
it was yesterday i really am sure
the pad that was on within the
tin structure it was like yeah in
a tin baking pan yeah yeah yeah
like and then you're pinning and you're
on your page looks like it would
have been yellow material yeah like and
then gerald and then
yeah and then pudding and then gets
the pudding pops i just remember the
smell yeah it was very nasty yeah
well my my whole thing is is
like you know how how we know
all those yeah this is your home
is my entire thing this is sums
you up yes okay i stand by
day okay and you know you know
are gonna say yeah i do okay
and p
apple are gonna say this is scott
aquaman oh he's good when i think
about the scott this is what i
think okay you know how when a
person is convicted of murder and therein
jail for twenty thirty years he yeah
they're exonerated yeah they get out and
then they sue the state for putting
them in prison erroneous
mostly yea me and their awarded several
tens of millions of dollars i don't
know about this what happens this happens
a lot a lot yeah because the
because they were they were exonerated helping
dna because the state he said yeah
yes erroneously so i should
get tens of millions of dollars yes
they should that's what i'm saying and
yeah i leave gift cards this ties
into my thing so you know
you know how i've talked about this
i believe like thousands of appleby have
given you gift cards to every store
in town and that should do it
right just apple music you could go
anywhere you will
so can't pay rent my my junior
high science teacher who made me cut
obey jessee cut open a worm or
something and i didn't get a good
grade
ended up you cut it in half
having an affair with one of the
junior high school student yo bubble boo
boo boo boo and dad nearly disgusting
she graduated when the high school so
he applied at the high school and
later there i can say it was
a little grok yes i'm discussed and
he was he was convicted and all
that oh shouldn't i be able
to sue the junior high for making
me take a class with him for
tens of millions of dollars out of
time yeah i mean that's that is
absolutely sick and i know what you
don't say insane there are so many
stories like this
there are so many stories like oh
everyone knows my expecting the same routine
like it's just it's insane i think
that is just so insane oh yeah
it's terrible um there was an english
teacher my school yeah who had an
affair with ah one of the students
um one of my classmates yeah and
they ran off together um and how
far they go
a mile yeah before they were gone
that's scandalous as hell you almost have
been losing your shit oh it was
wild and we had a few scandals
in my school i told you of
course about the the teacher that was
in the school play with us oh
yes i lose oh then crystal students
he kissed a girl and he's like
rice yeah the taste of her cherry
chapstick but yeah he was cast as
huge justice emil de becque in our
production south dakota mass and there was
a kissing scene he was cast by
himself no it was he was he
was accused by election no it was
the people he was on in the
drama department oh it was oh i
thought he was it was stranger alum
no and that even a great share
ugly these are so glad we told
the story against her back so yeah
i could learn that wrinkle so yeah
he was so good at drama as
what what kind of teacher was no
i do not was just using book
i guess this look because he had
sort of a european flair about him
or something yeah guess a meal demand
a mustache that
it's it so he wasn't even within
the drama department whoa yeah it was
so weird sick it was weird at
the time i had always assumed this
was your teacher who is directing the
play was like look none of you
assholes can pull this off no that's
what made it even more insulting was
like wow hey how can we can't
do it yeah right yeah that's solely
we're nuts
and then i ended up being double
cast as luther bills with a junior
i think wait you're down there the
other one was a teacher and a
student and they ran off together
no that was that was separate teacher
separately this teacher who was cast to
the play also made out with a
student did not have any did not
like have an affair but obviously something
did this more than once and then
the person who ran off with the
students they stay together i don't know
i don't know what happened to them
but that english teacher he gave me
a bad
grade on my paper about black like
me because he said you didn't prove
to me that you read the book
what was what's allowed wonder what you
wrote black like me i might just
copy the back of the book you're
well anyway so just had you picked
this white guy i included like i
put penguin books in there that i
probably shouldn't map um you don't know
what black like me is no
why did you do you don't i
guess i don't really because i never
read it this was an experiment in
the i wanna say it was the
sixties where a white man had his
skin um darken because this is like
murphy kind of thing exactly it was
yeah what the eddie murphy yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah and so he went
out in the world and and so
what it was like to be treated
yeah right and pretty good it was
great loved it
like everyone assumed i had a big
penis
he had a great time
wasn't there a movie like this concludes
with so i don't know what all
the fuss is about but it was
like a comedy facilities watermelon thomas howell
so called watermelon man um and there
were like there's there's a lot of
variations all in which i'm saying i'm
saying hey not sure if that's the
wise all you have to do
trust me you don't want to on
this count he's right it was okay
okay star c thomas howell and rae
dawn chong okay okay two minutes later
rae dawn chong
um then there was joanna man of
course so but that was not that
changing race yeah that was just a
classic drag yeah yeah man forced into
doing drag because he has no other
choice it's got planted www nba and
that was one of the movies that
i was asked to things so rewrite
your asked to rewrite it they it
was sent to me isn't as an
eccentric
and then you were like it's perfect
i can't do anything to this knows
one of the ones where i'm like
this sucks this will never get made
happen me a lot where a movie
but i thought sucked then came out
but to be fair they also but
you want to end did not did
they redo it didn't know it was
just don't knows just one oh just
at the time yeah it was ah
yeah they said please we have such
a great
idea we just need the script to
be good was the yeah that in
my career that would happen a lot
where it's like hey here's a job
opening to rewrite joanna man yeah and
then i read it i was like
this will never get made why would
i waste my time on what's the
name supposed to be a play on
some that's i've talked i feel like
i've talked about this because it's like
well it's like do you want a
you want ryan but
not saying that we know use and
you can say he's playing a woman
yeah but i think marijuana is like
joanna marijuana man no it doesn't make
it soon as much as you want
it's never going to make it a
phrase that we all use hey we're
looking for somebody to play in the
wwe and nba do you want a
man that's the only way that those
those
plays those plays on your work is
if it's like a common expression you
have to just like mrs doubtfire it
is actually er we don't doubtfire no
men men doughy guy fire created by
women doubtfire i always do and are
you missing this doubtfire my mind when
i've discovered that was based on a
book my mind was blown
and apart yeah bible
make a backfire based on chapter chapter
spacer say a young adult novel whoa
yeah yeah yeah yeah that actually may
go without saying that i would say
in a book form you'd be say
it does make young adult novel but
also makes sense that it was written
before because you know it's like such
a great original
idea and it's like no it was
such a great place but it was
a great movie i know you hate
his shakespeare but i've never seen it
i've never seen nissan shakespeare yeah no
just him oh just the idea mr
snow this was shakespeare's life he had
to do this yeah do you see
shakespeare never he never wrote about it
so yeah yeah yeah wrote about yeah
it's like dude
write what you know is such a
great story i gotta help those like
to worry yeah yeah but sure willy
plea and then when eyebrows catch on
fire everyone is going to judge turtle
heartily that pie in your face the
queen will laugh
however rarely jewelry is a great name
hi chortle heartily heartily with the weather
charter the hardware here is gonna be
done for the roller burke vs don't
stop bothering me the sun's gonna be
the sky until the clouds come by
though the rain comes down baby with
rain comes out everybody gets wet ready
buying here's what janie and i were
saying for days after watching an episode
of yeah the offer which was like
just making up a thing that would
be in the kid stays in the
picture was it a good idea absolutely
not did i do it anyway you
bet your ass idea
thank you for that ready
hillary okay listen to a sincere pitch
we have to take a break we'll
be right back okay
fuck it we'll do it live that's
right we're back that's right it's still
freedom like it was before no you
are not bill o'reilly don't adjust your
podcast don't get scared about fucking will
do it lie low rye zotto o'reilly
yeah here i am here i am
you know i'm telling you man
kind of okay let's let's hear a
couple of voicemails because we haven't heard
him in a couple of weeks yeah
wanna see it look
i don't have a lot of high
expectations for this you know you hate
this probably but look if you haven't
if you have a call to make
no i call it set haha lane
lane lay into you and and we
don't want jokes and we don't necessarily
know what you want to give you
advice but if you want to ask
us a question yes well maybe answer
it that aligned giving advice if it's
question like giving thank every advices okay
my favorite things unsolicited advice so this
takes the shine off that a little
bit yeah but um just call with
your phone number i'll call you and
give you unsolicited fuck yeah don't see
phone number on there um but yeah
if you have advice if you have
a question for us if you have
ah like a um ah feel
the promotion of of any of our
jingles yeah like a produced version of
any of our son jingles that you'd
like to do if you want to
share how we've positively affected your life
yeah or negatively no kevin yeah wow
kevin now want to do kevin you
have ah slammed my hand on my
corps lamb hand i just want me
oh no
alright let's your notes here the first
one i meant my link
hi guys it's brian long time caller
first time on time there so we
all know that mtv the challenge is
the greatest reality show of all time
but with that show aside if you
could create your dream reality
to show what would it include and
what would it be about like gain
is okay branches okay this is an
okay kind of okay it's i'm saying
no we are we are the change
involves some creativity yeah starters are a
good thing to call on with because
you know we always need them yeah
absolutely oh because honestly i'm gonna say
this right
now are tired just not interested in
who would win in a fight between
anything and anything else yeah oh no
no no oh no no no no
no you knew right yeah shit here
we go
um lauren sleeping now i'm thinking how
will my you know that's my shellfish
i'm thinking you know i always kind
of like um celebrity daters yeah and
i always kind of like celebrities celebrity
daters gambling like it it it follows
celebrity celebrity on a dating show like
two week follows with celebrities data and
files yes so
it's a celebrity who's following who it
goes sucking each other yeah i think
i'd be interested in a celebrity fear
factor with joe rogan now as the
contestant yeah sure
dr raji playing against him vow oh
gee oh gee
he found dr vo g oh boy
i know it was in the bow
geez i like shows where people have
to live together time like we've have
to live in a small space you
know an apartment or something together just
deal with each other like that boundary
celebrities but if it was celebrities i
would probably have fear factor we watch
like reese witherspoon anita scorpion so many
tales fears involves eating a bug i
know it's wild yet who wants to
call the bug man of science he's
gonna chomp into a scorpion to five
hundred venues i bet he was spitting
those bugs out right before we got
there you go i gotta sell some
of these
there you are pretty severe don't go
to paris before of the kids what
are you guys
do you have one you watch more
realities to shy children iyo i tend
to like ones that are that have
some sort of competitive things so in
the competitive category a little more than
just following people around with fake storylines
oh okay insulted other than the bachelor
is fakes but that's kind of competitive
right there so i think i think
an
actual ah season of the bachelor with
celebrities would be fascinating um where it's
real where it's real celebrities and they're
literally looking for love or they're like
hey look this is where we get
into it like when we were envisioning
these things when you're saying celebrity yeah
you mean like real celebrity yeah really
like whoever they can diet other
or bachelor contestant yeah right celebrities for
reality tv yeah i'm saying like hey
george clooney is looking for love person
i thought oh they'd be fantastic that's
what i also think i would like
to see bachelor with um older people
who've already maybe been married or they're
ready to actually be married i think
that there there would be an interesting
bachelor season
if like people who aren't football players
yeah or cheerleaders i would love to
see a doctor who's forty five and
yeah and got dad bod yeah and
a small penis and he's an asshole
need to swipe soon to be
want to see this
i want to see just an out
and out lunatic murderer on a tv
show
i've always been curious
ah now i do think that that
too to watch a show as produced
as well and with high enough stakes
of just regular people who don't have
to work out eight hours a day
yeah because it would be interesting yeah
i agree because they it leads to
boring conversations because they don't have any
interest besides bus tour eighteen waiting
in waiting whey protein wave wayfair whatever
the fuck they drink um wayfair did
we answer this timely well youtube is
god hasn't oh i mean paul i'm
sorry po maybe i get a turn
i was staring at pawns and scott
hasn't go go your way you're like
the your show would be if i
could make up a show
launch
it's babies writing dogs that are dressed
up like men i mean
yeah but that's almost like one of
those youtube channels of simian virus what's
the baby dressed up like cowboys cow
wow here's here's cowboys writing men my
ideally ideally to me it would be
like a fat baby yeah in just
like the diaper but with a cowboy
hat and boots yeah spurs and the
dog is dressing like an elegant gentleman
oh yeah of course she good that's
good and then they're strapped in and
what do they do though like what
what's the narrative i mean there isn't
one can see rightly is old enough
for whatever yeah they run errands around
the house they want it that's too
much plot for you i think it's
a race but obviously it's just a
meandering to get from one point there
no prize there just like this is
a race los actually one of them
crosses the finish line right yeah but
it doesn't it's like where they go
you follow them wherever they go yeah
but really i think it'd be interesting
to follow a baby if you were
like you know how parents always protect
a baby from leaving the house and
barrier you know yeah it's like okay
put a baby in the pair
aunt's house leave all doors open and
then does the baby stay it creates
the baby leaf babies are always trying
to protect their children yeah but you
know what i mean like hey what
would what would happen if it what
i said babies
babies protecting children what would happen if
we left all your doors open would
a baby choose to stay there or
would a baby just take off the
baby and i stay or should i
go janki janki jayson i was i
don't think there's enough horror competitions of
like people trying to scare people even
a scary house
there was like a stranger kids stranger
straight educating disease see
oh my god did i didn't mention
it but i would think if you
just stay in a haunted house where
then they have things that are intentionally
scaring you like someone stepping out of
someone saying boo yeah who can do
i would like see spent nine hundred
house challenge i would also like see
if it's like a um haunted house
creation competition like you know the the
murray able to make the house yes
mitt filling out with goats like to
have that christmas light fight thing oh
yeah that's right yeah that's a really
good idea some areas
block somebody should make that and a
chain i should make money from it
you should go pitch it yeah ah
guys this is copyrighted so don't steal
my dad is so true wow that
is a good idea who do i
partner up with um let's figure this
out the hollywood hayride people think yeah
this is brought to you by the
genius minds
hollywood a ravine to go on shark
tank do i yeah you do and
right h p t h t h
p v tv
we all have i p s no
matter what you're capable baggage yeah national
syndrome international
oh i got this syndrome from france
whoa a traditional values the pieces home
they say international peace syndrome alright let's
hear one more one more one more
we'll see what happens that was a
success yang this is ryan and rainbow
kinda see ashfield call for your advice
so i recently bought an engagement ring
from uncle fuck and five know want
ask but you're married you got exactly
how i should ask i would love
to know your advice on maybe some
news and i got some hosel youtube
and also just your own experience whether
asking or being asked mine was more
of a telling how it went and
instruct or maybe you wouldn't but
yeah would love your advice thanks so
much guys huh it's nice oh ah
well she's gonna know now that you've
broadcast eventually she was like yes everyone
listened to the show yeah i think
the more sincere the better yeah like
i'm not a huge fan of performative
ah anchor ah marriage proposals i would
see
a few at restaurants i worked at
and with people applauding and i always
felt it was noxious but that that
that's just me i think there are
some people who might appreciate the doing
it in front of like a bunch
of people or family members but for
me i think the way you ask
the more sincere the better say what
is on couldn't disagree more
jumbotron
mary jo johnson throw a ring in
a jumbotron you're married
joe job
i agree that i i think that
a ah a sort of trap that
people fall into is they feel like
they have to make it special when
it's already an extremely special thing you
can do some things to make it
special like go to going to a
favorite restaurant or a nice or nice
location or whatever exactly but i think
the actual act itself be
honest be open be sincere i agree
be on guard i think sometimes over
planning can create a situation that is
not comfortable for either person yes now
that said if you are the type
of people that like that kind of
thing then hell yeah you know what
he means some people do like that
sort of stuff yeah like for instance
mike dressed up
like ah chess piece yeah and then
asked me to move him
and then each square would uncover a
word yeah right it was over a
giant field some of those ones that
are like scavenger hunts you know what's
coming from the first thing and then
it's ten yeah that seems like a
lot of effort but i remember he
allowed you to choose the move so
you ended up spelling out will me
you marry yeah and i was like
whoa yeah the fall you know what
i won't speak about our proposal but
it was perfect and it wasn't what
you think
what do you think what do you
think i think wait youth i never
actually asked you to marry thanks i
got to say what i what do
you think i think is that it
tells you what the opposite is ok
also what's the a direct opposite was
it on earth no booze on larger
was fucking out of this world ah
it was amazing
once an apologies if this person is
still listening and listening to this but
i once had a ah at a
live comedy bang bang show someone wanted
got a message to me backstage saying
i want to ask i want you
to ask my girlfriend to marry oh
no and yes and i refuse to
do it i was like yeah you
really should just do this more i've
had people
wanting to do that in character yeah
and it's like you don't want that
you know i think this is this
is something that will be special to
both of you and the person it
has to be able to process what's
happening i think that's like yeah i
disagree with that i think if it
can be if it's because like i'd
get away many things happening like that
like there's someone else asking as a
character young wait what or like if
you
do it if you like surprise them
too much with like a like a
lot of people around like i think
a lot of people wonder if they
marry the other person right the a
lot of people around thing to me
sometimes it's like a hedging of a
bed of like what you can't say
no because there's some oh yeah yes
yes yes yes which is which is
like a a comfortable yet
they can't they can't and they won't
so i they don't and enjoy it
but but if if you are if
if if you know the person wants
you to do this and is waiting
for it and
you you know that it's good or
whatever and you both love big spectacles
maybe it's okay but i've just yeah
like if you're calling asking how to
do it you probably know that it's
not gonna be a you probably know
that you're not going to a big
crazy thing cause you probably have an
idea of what right right right yeah
your history yeah right sometimes you don't
necessarily even have to go to the
original thing of like where
are you met or anything special but
sometimes that's a nice thing if look
at where we are i had no
idea mine i didn't really plan anything
more than the location that was all
i location location location yeah and we
were in real estate
but that was it i didn't i
didn't know what i was gonna say
i knew like the very first thing
i was gonna say right and that
way yeah yeah yeah yeah very similar
to me i mean i was just
kind of felt like i was just
rambling yes it's such a nerve wreck
when you actually start doing it it's
like overwhelming with emotion yes you don't
want to feel like you have to
say a script like just speak from
the heart like i talked about the
most stand-up janie famously
interrupted me during my proposal right well
i think maybe my i may have
told us to but cool up we
were we were at dinner i was
planning on doing it right after dinner
and at dinner she's like are you
fucking going to ask me like she
started complaining about it going like i
mean it's been ten years what what
is going
gone with you why aren't you aren't
ya and i have this like bringing
my back and i was just like
i'm just already the other one already
a piece on yeah of course and
then and then when it actually happened
the first thing she she burst into
tears and said i'm an asshole i'm
sorry that's a beautiful story it was
it was my friend like went to
some redstone friend at her apartment
and because they were long distance and
then she opened orange county and she
was like yes and he was like
didn't get to say it like it
is possible to even get yeah you
drew that's true but i think i
think if you're simple and you're just
speaking stupid keep it simple stupid kiss
yes just a simple shithead just a
challenger dan
i was measured stitcher my common law
wife now
well we hope that helped if it
didn't fuck you yeah full preemptively fuck
you
well look we're running out of time
i don't think we have time for
three-tier because we took calls what what
do you think we don't have time
of shevchenko show we want to do
it we were like yeah but she
hasn't changed just yeah he says with
a low now turn the lights off
and on makers be quiet because like
you don't have to leave but you
can't stay here
well that was three of my guests
i was three it was great it
was a good episode like this calls
i like just calls those calls kind
of call that's how it can be
you guys if you just like fucking
it oh that's so beautiful it can
be if you come to your senses
oh my god well please ah check
us out threesome usa on twitter and
in
um i've never heard you say that
but i know i never want to
know what it is three am you
say gmail dot com and of course
haha if you and you can never
been easier yeah you can hear the
archives of this show as well as
ad-free episodes on both stitcher premium and
at cbp world dot com you can
also go jump in a finally for
all week
a guardian or a law if you're
in sicily because we care about each
other now you with three of us
care about the three of us v
and vi
uh