try it out
oh
oh whoa
welcome to three adam that this is
of course the friendship podcast with me
all of tomkins
me the crypt keeper from tales from
the crypt do some puns do some
funny ah hello boys and ghouls also
ah i love this i i'm i'm
grieving at you from over here who
is that of fun on grazing or
gazing waving wave three oh got it
yeah and me
me is barney the purple dunce oh
i love you i love you barney
you love me or have you stopped
loving the people that lovely honestly i
had to stop because it was too
many it's no longer as no one
likes barney now do they that they
don't there's they're trying to get a
movie trying to get a move in
it well there's learning
movie now well ah hipper cool one
yeah as ah minute yeah what a
terrible idea oh my gawd
um i never watched barney i did
yeah scott you're lying you never watched
barney i don't even really know what
he does is selling like sesame street
he loves people who love him sure
yes there's barney there's baby bop you
know ah triceratops yeah and she's re
early q and the kids on the
show actually wasn't somebody who's now like
oh selena gomez yeah it doesn't say
so yeah i was wrong she was
on it but i watched it sort
of ironically tracy alerts when she was
fifteen unfortunately saya dua race those entire
season gray
do you guys watch things like when
you were too old for them but
you were being like i'm i don't
really like it i'm just watching it
but then you kind of think it's
comforting and so you keep watching it
yeah i bet i did i can't
think of anything right like i would
i did that with a lot of
shows like arthur um have these questions
are just designed for her to know
because i you have an answer i'd
love to hear your life to a
very specific question i have a lot
to say about my spark for things
about myself you know
oh fairpoint fairpoint couldn't i just do
was go can you turn my head
eyes down a little bit sure i
can turn around in your headphones jay
z well i really liked richard skerries
busy town that was a great show
what do you mean what is busy
town because he knows it was these
books that cougar town but without busy
philipps a yeah
ironically
the town that busy character moved away
from moved to cougar town she's like
it's everyone here is busy
can't stand out kesha um it was
it was a book series and still
is i love to read yes so
you like this i mean the average
reader there is a little worm who
is in an apple who wears a
little heavily worm and yeah and he
goes around and he's busy and on
the show it was a cartoon about
these p
oh and slash animals that are not
people dan yes they and the town
is very busy there's a lot going
on ah they have a nonstop nonstop
they have cops acp sure cops aren't
bastards i agree yeah it was one
of the cops pig because that great
things come
that's so funny like it seems like
you shouldn't be able to do this
what was your favorite bear who's your
favorite show in fifth grade i got
grey probably happy days i remember yeah
i remember just like being so bummed
if happy if you if i couldn't
watch happy days huh and then i
remember there was one where jony posed
nude or
like a photographers trying to trick her
into my such a thing on those
shows yeah and and like i really
it doesn't happen in life maybe it
happened a lot then because there was
like no internet and i remember there
was there was a repeat of that
episode on and and at the beginning
part my dad wandered through the room
and he was like why are you
watch
doing this again it's repeat and i
would always watch the repeats of you
know what i mean like it's on
if you wanna watch daddy fuckin asshole
and then when the plot comes up
i've heard like you know going to
pose nude he goes oh i see
why you're watching this again dad fuck
you and show no sign act out
if you're listening yeah minnesota guy and
you ass
you ask but you did bid you
take bitch out sorry learn you weren't
here for that i like it
i loved their they used to run
a happy days and laverne and shirley
bassey wow can you our our entire
task sending back to back with laverne
and shirley and lenny squidgy all right
he's quaking right piece clean just died
he just died they were so fucking
funny so great it was so fun
funny yeah god damn hello
hey ya that was exactly my kind
of idiot would think that such and
such is a good idea hello
who could have murdered the black doll
huh oh
i wouldn't touch that with a six
foot pole
ten football why are you saying that
the joke is i wouldn't touch that
with a ten foot pole and then
i think lenny said well i'm a
six foot pole
ah
ah sad buddy alright go ahead with
what you watched no i already told
you ah was bernie and arthur and
um when you were when that is
why i need to yeah yeah that's
what i'm saying i was watching yeah
the point of it being q you
know but um i guess when my
sister was born i would watch
kind of monitor yes sawyer much how
old are you and she was ah
eight and a half oh that's a
pretty big guy a pretty big um
and so are you about my mom
when my sister came out it's a
pretty big gap
but that's part of it i think
too is like if you have a
little sibling you can like you can
really get yeah you're sort of re-experiencing
watching through their eyes and stuff like
that um that that's always i remember
once i went to disneyland with a
bunch of um this is when we
were twenty five or something we went
on a trip with ah these people
at chinch
jane where i used to work oh
my guy and we all like yeah
we all had a smash run drill
we all had a slush fund that
we would contribute to with our tips
every day and and then at the
end of it like after a year
we would all like you know buy
something with it or whatever so it's
like very um yeah i think socialist
sorry birdie
i'm like how much would you have
by the end of the year i
don't well enough enough where we did
a trip to disneyland where everyone i
mean that's pretty good so it's like
basically a hundred bucks a piece or
whatever and then and then food and
all that kind of stuff so we
were a turkey leg sure particular quit
on the cab a little bit of
ah puckered
you pull your face like a horse
z bag and i'll never forget it
so we went to we went to
disneyland and and i remember like a
lot of the waiters that i went
to were all very cynical about it
and making fun of it the whole
time and then we were also there
with people who had just moved to
california that year and had never been
in this is some time yeah and
just recently come into some money ah
hook it was all of my
my like good friends
all my good friends were making fun
of it and i was like this
isn't fun i want to like it's
fun when you join yeah enjoy things
and experience so i'd like just hung
out with the people who are like
new to it and they were wondering
like why is he hanging out with
those squares and now all the squares
were like why what does he want
yeah cool guy doing so you i'm
sure is
what they were all one group yeah
but there were enough of us groups
so there were enough of us where
people split off and were like ah
i don't want to do this lame
thing i'm going to go do this
clue what i'm going to do the
coolest thing to disneyland to go on
tom sawyer's island kiss girls that was
something that when i was growing up
is girl that was something that i
heard about
when you're like ten eleven twelve thirteen
or whatever fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen
twenty one
you would hear about kissing girls eight
hundred and twenty six weeks per year
about kissing you would hear about like
okay you can go to tom sawyer
island and there and then hook up
with girls oring oh there's like a
bunch of girls hanging out there who
are wanting to hook up his board
is already there hi
right what if you go there yeah
but that's because it's it's so big
and there's not a line you just
run around this island and it's not
there anymore
but is there i don't think it's
sawyer island is still the same but
i think pirate island or something i
i think the the place that i'm
talking about tom sawyer's island where there
is just like a big island where
you could run around while there is
there are caves and stuff there's similar
thing to that where you take that
little that like raft over like everyone
stands yeah
yeah that's that's what it is yeah
but maybe they will you want to
go into you can see some pirate's
booty yeah maybe it is still there
i don't know in any case i
don't really don't want to hear this
further for the record you don't want
hear that it's still there it's not
fun when you're an adult no but
when you're a kid and like promise
of like hooking oh girls oh yeah
so i ri
remember going there and being like very
excited and then like you know you're
sort of like looking at where all
the girls it's sort of like going
to central park yeah like trying to
get a blow job so yes i
went and i've i will say like
do you think those girls are now
they're trapped on an island i know
i must be really hungry
will say i think they live on
kisses what did he would go the
kisses nattering covin i have an old
crowed
b i want to go with someone
being me
you say disneyland i want everything to
be normal ah i don't know it
isn't normal by the way i should
just tell you that that's true the
world isn't disney okay okay no wonder
they call it the normal kingdom
i will say the first time i
believe i touched a boob was it
like it was anything you believe he
was on adventures several didn't believe adventures
in inner space which was known as
star and grab some lady
ah some guy ma lunch so i
believe i touched him
was like that was my purse your
post
glitter boob isn't first
if you called your puss your purse
get my purse coin bursts open up
my purse but that was known as
ah paul doesn't like it
fake i know why when i watch
layer s m h
ah but that was known as the
make out ride because that was the
darkest ride pirates of the caribbean was
dar o mighty but it was the
darkest ride where it was like some
of it was just pitch black other
than space mountain which was too fast
to like how weird would that be
like making out on spaceman
difficult to direct your choosing
i will say one of the weirdest
movies i've made out it's getting up
like your mouths oh yeah
one of the weirdest movies i made
out in was thy storm where i'm
like a first date with this woman
and we were just making out the
entire time and the whole crowd was
like why does going on go a
crowd like why this movie um but
yeah adventures an inner space super dark
they got rid of it i r
i p when it was gone it
was like wow
there's not really a lot of places
to go make on disney landing was
it based on the movie innerspace not
the eighties one ah buddy it was
where you shrunk down it was like
a sixty s kind of vibe to
it oh incredible the ah what the
fuck is called fantastic voyage i think
it might have been that yeah show
test right
is that a theme from it or
just you are doing atomic dog band
da yeah and dad mow edge yeah
uh oh
thursday vi i'm about i'm really what
it is that's coolio song yeah it's
okay i thought i was wrong
anymore you were doing are you doing
tommy dog oh no wrong melody yes
oh yes and you when you sing
it sing it ko da da se
da imam rabbi right yeah blah blah
blah coolio i'm coolio where is he
coolio healy where are you
out he just goes oh lauren coolio
is here he's right
ah
now i want to get a cameo
from coolio i wonder if he does
cameos oh my god i'll get a
cameo for from coolio you know my
janey and i were browsing around on
cameo yeah i did i did a
fake cameo so funny i just said
random things like very specific thing very
accurate and then i started thinking about
what i actually be able to do
that because that's the way to do
cameo that i would enjoy if i
say live you could say whatever you
want i'll say your name but i'm
not gonna say anything else you're not
going to prompt me into yes i
am jane these things i this will
just be some private comedy for whoever
you buy this for right i'm gonna
make some shit up and that's it
that seems like a way in right
yeah go ahead make your million dollars
yeah here
on camera oh my dad like called
me into the room to show me
the news honey come in here honestly
he's like oh i'm sorry i'm having
a go like this and then it
was about that guy from the office
making a million dollars on candy and
then i explained cameo in all of
it's glory to my dad for ten
minutes and then that was it i
think that you shouldn't be able
to replay cameos for anyone who didn't
buy i agree and i don't think
the cameo should be on the cameo
page of the person because you can
watch it you can actually
don't like that and it's so it's
so weird yeah it takes away the
specialness first of all and then it
takes with it surprise and also some
people do the exact same thing every
time yeah um my friend did get
one from someone from ninety day fiance
and she sent it to me and
it was so bizarre as um this
guy paul wait actually we were going
to talk about ninety
fiance than someone so we didn't get
into it and then oh okay go
ahead and get into it will do
either of you watch it no no
maybe that's why we didn't guess probably
why why the conversation dead end fast
anyway there is a character aka person
named paul who is married to this
woman carine and they now are about
to have their second child
child and their relationship is very interesting
but he um he's a very weird
guy he ah he did an eleven
minute cameo for my friend and she
did a full tour of his house
and someone like andy kindler do like
hour long ones just to be funny
about it or something like that i
wouldn't be surprised
but that feels like a waste of
time for who him yeah but that's
the joke i think if you were
to say the person watching it i
would agree as well
i mean that's interesting i don't know
so i appreciated that he went on
for eleven minutes because it's like good
value for fifty bucks but also it
was just like wow he really did
a whole he shared a lot of
personal i saw his whole home that's
why there's a french fry in the
bed and he didn't take it out
why yeah the idea you don't even
know i can't
any you don't even know it's it's
too it's like an understand the french
frying the bed but not taking it
oh yeah you know i legit you
guys oh colonel interfere trend but when
he went to visit her and she
lived i wanna say the amazon it
was truly like a very difficult place
to get to amazon island he had
to go to work
oh walk through water at a certain
point in his journey okay
to get to her and
some proclaimers shi'i yeah he put on
two condoms on venus just to get
to mosquitoes or bugs in the water
would go in his penis oh and
then in the cameo he made for
my friend he showed his penis sheath
which i guess now he has a
penis sheath instead of condoms
for that base which long just move
out they went to america then they
went back i don't know they've had
a lot going on but so he
has a full penis sheath and he
was like keep it on this on
this structure keeps it keeps it straight
i want to cause his penis he's
sure i'm sure he picked it up
when he showed this little nub
and there was a sheath on it
and apparently he keeps it stretched out
on that nub and it's like a
shoe tree
i'm just so fascinated but that's that's
part of the thing with cameo it's
like there's some irony to these a
lot of these purchases which um you
know yeah you know he doesn't carry
slugging money well we were looking at
christmas time and there were and i
think i sent you one laura and
there were santa clauses so there were
some clauses on cameo
yeah many times i gotta get one
many times but there weren't so there
was like what you'd expect there were
guys that like had real beards and
obviously this is the they do this
you know every year yeah then there
were people that clearly just like i'm
gonna buy a fucking santa costume and
alumni make some money the one man
and me was like
depressing this guy's beard mustache we're bobbing
up and down as he talked it
was so bad it looked so shitting
it made me angry yeah it should
that this guy the gall of this
guy it should make you mad you
unmitigated gall of santa claus yeah mitigated
gall i'm jenny
in carp and danielle official have a
podcast called talking cheap where they go
through pbc to show that instead of
this it's really funny they they'll talk
like three people and of different like
types of personalities and and costs and
then they'll guess how like how much
it is and then talk about whether
it's worth it and
play some of the cameos and it's
really enjoyable or are they ever worth
it yeah some of them are you'll
be like oh don't how much money
like twenty five bucks that was fun
i would that was a good one
he put an effort you know that
kind of thing but then sometimes someone's
like three hundred dollars and then they'll
you'll find out they've been doing the
same thing for every single one and
you're like yeah that's not really worth
it can you imagine
engine making twelve fifty an hour and
then spending twenty five dollars on a
cameo like working two hours of life's
i can't i mean i'm part of
but when i don't get about it's
also it's mostly isn't it mostly people
getting it for someone else i whole
lot of gifts yeah i don't i
don't think people are buy it for
them so okay i'm gonna get you
the coolio cameo
what do you want what do you
want to say i want them to
sing fantastic voyage and they teach you
the dough into the tune of atomic
dogs yeah please get me um any
one of the ancillary sopranos actors who
all use we watched a bunch they
all use a bunch of mob talk
and every day i knew hey
hey do you want to have a
down with me but it's like that
kind of stuff feels tough like to
do like an old saying that you
did yeah i don't know one thing
you did know i said the anointed
okay i'm sure you heard me but
yeah but i mean there's like that
whole angle of it some people will
do like if i mean i think
that's why that guy from the office
made a million
dollars so i get that yeah what
does he do one i don't see
and i guess his the news program
said that his his news they are
reporting on it her dad called her
to watch the news they said that
he was he made really sincere videos
like really um he put a lot
of effort into them oh that's good
that's what i would do i would
put a lot
really great at it yeah no you
with everything going to fire comey would
just be the best yeah i feel
like with most things i do i
wanna just you know put the most
effort and be the best yeah it
turns out really good i mean if
i did i gave one hundred and
ten percent and probably would make a
lot of lists
that's what i understand about people who
like move out here to be actors
and they don't make it it's like
we'll just put a lot of effort
into it and be the best yeah
like just really good and just do
it like i don't really get it
like if you want to make it
why don't you get
i want to tell us ah blind
item story oh my god i am
coming guessing and if we guess you
can nod to a silently and we'll
go no we got it right
and then all of a sudden woods
tops talking i wonder who it was
if you if you're out there and
you like blind items followed dubois on
instagram that this is the ultimate gossip
instagram okay blind item here we go
um i this is not that salacious
story but it was a story that
bonemeal um that somebody that we know
i was talking about around i gotta
know was talking about a person who
recently relatively recently at the time had
become very successful and was doing very
well and ah and so the long
goodbye
i want to know what one will
ever know and i want no one
knows who this great story that we
only heard there was a person talking
about someone so the person we know
was talking about seeing this successful person
a while back ah on some hosting
like some like you know compilation vid
audio type show that's like on nat
geo or animal planet or one of
those where it's like essentially funny more
funny moments video roundup or whatever i
love those one of those and you'll
see that kangaroo punch that guy
if antonio whatever his name is from
fresh pow santo rubio if he steps
down i am i was watching tom
bergeron who you know whatever but what
a gig listen tyra banks santos galliano
ever wonder what does she she she's
no she's not on amc she's on
dancing with the stars that would be
so bizarre she was funny yeah bags
here's another guy getting hit in the
balls with a wiffle besmirching um so
he's so he saw this this guy
on the show and and was was
saying like oh i can't believe he
gave up so so early you know
you like
he's so talented he gave up and
it's like then this is a guy
who's gone from this person we know
is gone from success to success to
success to success and it's like you
don't fucking know what are you talking
about of course i didn't say anything
not giving up yeah you are powerful
in the moment you were a coward
and just seeing the serbs go of
course i didn't have living in both
you say sir i agree agreed didn't
give up please don't need to be
scott what's the crack jute bow we
went about that
the crop fairy came just to hype
after we're gonna take a break after
lauren talks and then when we come
back we'll be talking about the crock
fairy the giblets yes good events that's
i learned that's what they're called know
is that true they're called giblets yeah
crowd that weird huh the crackberry made
some gibby delivery
ys anyway i just think that special
jubilee really harsh to say somebody gave
up went by the way probably no
one knew they even did that show
yeah it's like they probably got a
bunch of money to do exactly nothing
who gives a fuck you near money
to eat and then you turn what
you eat into shit and you need
money to buy toilets exactly
a you need money to buy toilet
diane moment it's about toilets toilet so
old i have money do you have
toilets
when we were buying toilets was at
this place are previous placing remember for
you buying we went to home depot
and
just like hey could we get a
more powerful toilet like our toilets backup
sometimes in the guy at home depot
was like alright my man and wanted
to high five me for what i
hear ya big ships and using too
much toilet paper fucking oh i'm gross
yeah guys gross me
plus your shit i called courtesy flush
you and that guy deserve each other
not nasty alright let's take a break
alright we're back oh right we're back
and of course on one of our
previous episodes i was talking about how
the crock fairy was coming every night
and delivering what are they jib giblets
giblets and where do you keep so
do you put your crack at the
foot of your bed in the crack
free from there they are on
your pillow they are by the little
i don't know what you call a
bit like a little ah
shoe shoe tray shoe tray kind of
thing by your front door okay so
the crux where the front doors to
the shoe fit the gibbet ferry can
get in very easily yes she just
snacks and so every morning i would
worry me true cherry they every morning
i would wake up and there would
be a new gibbet on my crocs
i talked about how there was ah
a piece of sushi what was the
very first one the very first one
way and piece of sushi is it
one at a time yes okay vs
won't be first of all it was
a piece of sushi second one i
talks about this is a ah bowl
of avocado or guacamole with a few
twenty previously avocado yes then since then
and i i you guys asked me
about this the other day and i
told you since then just a third
one appeared and it is a slice
of bread just so everyone can visualize
scott is sitting like one of those
pulls toys where it's like a little
wooden guy and when you pull the
string between their legs or legs pop
up as hitting like my theater and
see
stirrups i'm about to get a pap
smear
let me hear how old is this
schmear like you put it on a
bow
that's football it's great
ah that's an inside joke for ah
so the slice of bread by the
way ah the the crock fairies gotten
me because these are things i love
apparently according to the grunion love you
love bread and the slice of bread
says i les lys let's get this
bread on it oh sure absolutely sure
yeah
so then the rockferry alerted me to
the fact that they they had ordered
a bunch of giblets and then the
rockferry thinks strange of the rockferry to
do yeah no they don't make things
okay but you're just a middleman i
mean hey that's your business rockferry why
don't i be surprised but they know
they had ordered a bunch of them
m but thinks they threw them away
because they were all packages with bigger
stuff and got you know like jets
are small that's david's are small and
so no more tibbits were coming until
christmas oh yeah i woke up and
there are two giblets on a one
on either foot and it is little
groggy on both feet
wow little roku here's grow gou everybody
scott
doing here a store i see how
nice do you wanna build a snowman
afterwards you wanna build
i sent those to the croc ferry
you sent these to the croc very
nice very didn't even tell me with
a note saying you know what to
do whoa i think she was waiting
for me to talk about it on
her show a huge huge this is
the biggest reveal in threesome
history i am pleased as punches pilot
right now that must have been really
exciting for you really released toll yes
it was because i was wait i
was i was waiting to hear like
disease restraint so i get to reveal
such restraint that you and so oh
did that hey tim to actually you
know put myself in my place you
did
i try to go to the crux
conversation a little sooner but i forced
you go back to the other conversation
and he must have been having anticipation
you might have been dying inside know
what was great was i forgot oh
right what about the you forgot about
the growth whatever grow goo no no
i forgot the weed had brought up
crocs grand we're going to rejoice punches
pilot really pleased that he says
it's so pleased i don't know he
got to watch sams
so he does he would not have
anybody to me like punches pilot from
outlast your hands and kill jesus let
jesus be killed
lauren you heathen you don't even know
what we're talking about i don't care
yeah yeah i'd never read that bible
you gotta get yourself to church girl
know i know it's like christmas all
year alone how would you go would
you go to christmas eve master you'd
watch on tv is that what it
was though i loved going to i
used to love going to
midnight mass when i was a midnight
mass and that mass why it's like
the rocky horror picture show well i
was a kid yeah and you have
to throw things if this thoroughbred um
i got it because as a kid
you gotta stay up late which was
fun it was just very exciting and
the next day was christmas then you'd
we will like come home we get
to unwrap one present oh yeah
the yeah that's the carrot yeah yeah
yeah and when i was in the
choir and i sang in the in
the choir for midnight mass that was
a blast it was so much fun
you got to super spread got to
super spread yes we did cove
ah you gotta sing all the the
dramatic songs oh the dramatic christmas song
what are their the most dramatic religious
was carol of the bells is the
most dramatic yeah yeah um which by
the way i was listening to home
de um dong you're the man now
d know you're the man now being
young you're the man now
ding dong one seems to hear words
of good goody you're the man now
dog podcast and dan lippert was talking
about carol bells my as performed by
the trans-siberian orchestra yep but he called
it chairman of the bells and no
one caught it and it made me
like him chairman of the best carry
me of the bells that's me baby
and chairman of the bells rating ding
dong
that's a frank sinatra letter said oh
god rest you merry gentlemen very dramatic
satan's powers mentioned lauren you need one
more person here to know what you're
talking about
yeah ooh can we get hoodoos you
who can we get for fordham marry
harry mary
mary i would love the law of
sharon may hear is them yeah
cause she's the best but unfortunately there
can only be three the diocese yeah
that's it i just have to be
talking to the nobody hey didn't you
have fun talking about arthur yeah for
tuesday i guess i saw if i
were to die though you could bring
marion that would be oh hey guys
marries and yes if
paul dies what the show's over thank
you nah by day you have to
pull the glue if i die the
show goes on but you only talk
about me and say nice things forever
every episode
last one episode oh come on that's
harsh you don't think we have four
episodes of nice things to say now
you honestly have one
maybe two
i just spilled oh no not my
things nobody can die here i did
too oh yeah okay report went out
for the people who haven't died yet
that's what the people who haven't died
yeah that's us we will get you
never get to pour one out for
yourself well that's the thing i think
that we should have fake
ah not funerals but i guess funerals
or wakes or whatever for people in
the community week because they're always so
touching you know when one of your
friends dies and you hear all these
nice things and how much they mean
to people and it's like yeah there's
the opposite as well what do you
mean you hear well hear loud shit
talking during during awake yeah
yeah really well the ones i've been
to like who your mom who lets
see yeah
savage takedown
anyway but isn't that a good idea
to have a fake funeral for people
yes i do will have a usb
sunset comedians can't be serious during yeah
i know like the the reason it's
so touching when they're dead is because
they are so serious it's like this
yeah this very funny
person is so serious now i guess
weddings are sort of like that but
you know like there's nothing in between
a wedding and that's why like club
keeps saying like let's renew our vows
because she just want a big party
where we say nice things to each
other in front of people you know
that you know i want to do
that too and genie's against it but
i wanna what i wanna do is
because as your life goes on you
there are more people in your life
life that weren't there when you got
married you know what i mean we
have to agree on this just for
the spanking category mutt idea i knew
bullets should do it and i think
it should be the second we're going
to have a party we have a
big yeah vow renewal wherever we're like
everyone we know and we just go
through and align everyone we know yes
everyone we've ever even spoken to like
matt once yeah even people on tour
who have come through the lines wow
they're all here they're all you're all
invited um would you do it at
your house it's your favorite checker from
the supermarket i've a friend who keeps
making excuses to like have a big
party
every year and i think it's just
they like the attention it's like this
people like what are what are so
like excuses well you know it started
with a wedding and then it like
it just keeps changing of like okay
now we're doing this thing and this
is where people say nice things about
me and yeah a lot that's amazing
saying yeah and every time it happens
i'm a little suspect of like you
just like people lining up and giving
you tribute usually you could only have
that that type of event where like
i i've been to a birthday party
where people got up and said things
about the person and everyone around the
table had to say something which makes
me really emotional like and not
a good way like i feel very
like i feel like cetera i feel
stressed and i feel like i cry
like because i can't believe it's out
you have to do it well you
see this is this is you though
i've learned about you you don't like
being put on the spot like this
in a big i don't and it
makes me really uncomfortable if you had
to prepare would it be okay or
is it no i've been thinking about
it all
all day it's like i just don't
want to do it and i but
i but i don't mind saying something
nice i think it's not hard to
think of what i would say but
i just don't want to do it
but the problem is like how do
you get like my feeling is you
can only do that once every five
yes or events like i don't want
to get up every
year in year like what's changed nothing
and it just feels like self-absorbed like
oh who wants to sit there and
make everyone do that yeah yeah yeah
do i see my note once you
hear yeah why isn't a while your
fiftieth birthday was on that was awesome
said did people say nice things about
you know janey janey did a speech
that was it that's right
jane potatoes but it felt very whoa
was lee got us which by the
way i would say she did a
toast and i which i did not
know it was gonna happen i was
very it was all a very warm
event that were it felt like yeah
yeah it felt like people speaking about
them i sang rock lobster that's just
a long song as very out of
breath like within the
first to very long suffers two minutes
i was in lieu of people saying
nice things i did ask people i
had a live band and i asked
people to certain people to to perform
songs and it was here what was
so great was i it was the
i got the best of it because
i got to see the i got
the rest of it the well i
tried to use
i tried the rest and then i
said saudi funded for the best yeah
yeah um i got there ah to
see the um the sound check so
i got to see all of these
performances just for me i was the
only one in the room and ah
and then when the party started people
talk through the songs
yeah i had not anticipated apnic so
annoying i'm not it's so weird because
here's why that wasn't my memory of
a biggest people in the back while
you had allowed song which was good
but i guess i don't mean my
song i just while you're watching the
others i was i was standing on
the side of the in the wings
you know and i could hear people
talking during way
and for the reviews to come out
was the postgres safe running authorities i'm
trying to think about if if people
around me were talking or what was
happening i rough chi remembering i was
probably in the back but it was
but it carried i like i could
hear it backstage the acoustics in that
room were yeah yeah yeah interesting i
feel like if that if i had
closed the bar for the for the
the roses todd glasses whole thing you
gotta you gotta put curtains around the
did not it did not answer anyway
i wanted to do it but it's
true did not occur to me and
i should have i should have if
i did it over again that's what
i would have done i really enjoyed
your sort of big band version of
it's a sin by the yes boys
i was so much fun was great
but had you ever always always very
for
or was that a new arrangement and
that was an arrangement i'd done that
song once before i largo but not
with that not with that big band
with a horn section on everything so
good it was so much you think
you would have a sixtieth birthday
black bass or a party we hope
you'll have so much buzz do you
think it was exuberant the full stop
ah would you do it again i
would yeah my word yeah it was
it was really fun it was ah
that was one of those things where
planning on having a fifty fifth and
you're like oh yes huh what do
you do
fifty five thousand no i would not
do a fifty five no yeah if
i make it to sixty yes i
will have a party for fucking short
course you well i don't mind if
people talk about how they're gonna die
and get a fifty because of the
pandemic hey sam i'm twenty eight
oh you're your cure aging doubt yes
further
i don't know if i want to
do birthday parties and i mean maybe
maybe later but i did a thirtieth
and it was fine but also weird
i don't my thirtieth was very stupid
it was just like it was at
the drawing room that bar oh i
think i had my fortieth id and
where call-up used to do her show
on monday nights that mexican restaurant oh
pedro's no no wait wait shit anyway
but hey hey feel like it's like
you have this expectation i feel especially
with thirty like you're supposed to be
like i'm thirty well you definitely have
one on twenty one yeah yeah and
then twenty five you're like oh i
can rent a
car tomorrow
a rent-a-car eve gonna drive everywhere
um
but yeah i don't know yeah expert
i mean at this point it's just
like give me another one please give
me one more right can you please
please don't take me home please god
let me margaret
someday be home it's me margaret how
old is margaret from it are you
there god it's me well isn't she
getting your period so twenty two no
i mean how she now twenty two
she's no longer having periods
how old is she yeah well she
was getting your period when was that
seventy thousand like say it was seventy
three so she she's in her seventies
now she's sick sure yeah
of course people were born seven will
absolutely blogger cool who love oh shit
i called you cool why let's not
explore the
floridians silly i'm in love with you
during you catch that it was published
in nineteen seventy and she was in
sixth grade so she was okay so
she's born in fifty nine
oh fuck yeah tend to that and
i am an i did that at
the ariana grande's song thirty five plus
thirty four like club didn't understand it
and i was like until she's listening
to never heard of this song never
heard of that it just came into
a little bit over the top or
use the point of soggy yeah hitting
me just came out but she's like
an i thing
she's like will you fuck me all
night long and i'm like and they're
playing on series like me all like
oh yeah huh do you want to
fuck me all night um you want
a thirty five thirty
it is very weird by the way
like driving around in your car we
have serious like satellite and in her
car and it's weird to hear the
curse words like on the radio you
know what i mean so to hear
ariana grande's saying like the fuck me
all night long while you're in the
car is just in you're not listening
i don't know what it is but
hearing like the sort of state your
bad reception
static and then she's like fuck me
fuck me i remember getting like me
this sounds amazing it's horrible i remember
getting a ride home from ah about
your dad i was babysitting for
and there was like a really nasty
song on the radio about just out
there it was for the time for
the time when it was um god
i can almost remember it it was
like wait i want to say something
about twister something um it was a
song about twister okay i'm going to
look this up wow the song was
probably nice
ah let me think how old i
would have been i might have been
in college but it was really awkward
regardless i was probably it was probably
two thousand between two thousand and three
thousand five okay song well i'll tell
you the twister soundtrack had van halen's
humans being on it because that had
been it i don't even know
if it was enough mr was the
word but it was something it was
something really like like but related
like literally during your twister song but
related right handed but twister song but
related i was babysitting this kid and
his he lived in chicago and his
dad gave me money to take him
to dave and busters which is like
chaotic with like just you and a
kid like
so he was running all over the
place and it was very stressful
is it
didn't love it we are gathered here
today to touch bucks
ah you know that region is killing
me
just youtube
it's youtube close
ah
chiefs huh
the video is funny
put the
ah huh
isn't it yeah yeah if you build
up for this if you want to
do it right
if you want to use dwight in
my book
oh good stuff i'm here the white
on the bus isn't the chocolate rain
guy no tatum day bite your tongue
bite your tongue days on day baby
boon will die before this
joke lid re so you felt embarrassed
in the dad did what was he
like he just left it on and
we just sat there and listen to
it would you put this parked
put his hand on my knee
this feels terrible to have to drive
a babysitter home especially when choosing if
you're in college drive yourself home now
i was no i could i
i can't remember what the circumstances were
that he was driving me but but
whatever like what what does a good
conversation that can occur in something like
this like what are you up to
at school like my dad knows shit
how does the song make you feel
i had to get rides from parents
will because i babysat a lot as
a kid and then they would drive
me because i was like in middle
school
and i remember just being so awkward
with my clarinet case in my lap
and being like earlier why would you
would practice your premise look at my
law
it's just a machine gun like ah
like the valentine's day massacre i used
to have to babysit is this spanking
time i don't remember but i to
have to babysit ah my our church
friends kids and i got paid one
dollar an hour oh my god and
church friend key
one dollar an hour or no our
dearly beloved do you owe one dollar
an hour to babysit these kids
would you buy with your like two
doll and nothing it was i mean
even at the time it was smaller
he's like a tiny it was not
a lot of money what could you
get how much was a coke ah
to fifth position
i remember learning when i was like
eighteen that you could buy cokes and
they would be like thirty cents a
piece rather than a dollar like if
you bought them in bulk we have
talked about the sums okay in any
case we've talked about that buying coke
yeah thirty stocks about the price of
coke yeah ok let's talk about okay
i can't remember the price
of things like that when i was
a kid even though it was very
important like yeah knowing like ass and
how much everything was yeah i don't
remember any sense here's the one thing
i can remember you throwing out numbers
i think they were fifty cents for
most my child and then they were
sixty five oh yeah yeah i feel
like i remember when sodas went to
a dollar like a twelve ounce so
yeah
yeah that seems like a lot top
the one thing i remember vividly as
in high school they had in the
cafeteria they served ah at once a
week they served this thing called hot
cheese on a roll and that's exactly
what it was it was melted cheese
inside i want to throw inside a
kaiser roll it's like a grilled cheese
bar
grills what oh god you dare but
those those costs sixty cents wow sixty
cent ah ha cheese and roll and
they were molten hot like they would
love it i loved it yeah did
you actually make one yeah so we
get really good advisor role and then
what kind of cheese
i think just american cheese american cheese
you like american cheese i love it
i think it's very underrated you don't
like about awesome american cheese or do
you like like deli american cheese deli
american cheese oh look all you know
both are you make something with american
cheese i make a scrapple egg and
cheese sandwich
that's that doesn't sound bad to have
like american cheese in the middle of
like scrapple and stuff like that but
that's that's a good usage perfect i
really wish i liked cooking i really
don't care about which i did too
so annoying janey loves it but i
don't mean he loves it such a
pain i don't have any ideas like
i don't know how to do it
like i don't know what goes where
like look something up online i've done
respite i had a period like i
had appear at a time you would
appear last have a period like last
year i had
when i was like really cooking out
of a recipe book cookbook and i
was like ah planning it like i'd
open the cookbook and pick a thing
and then go get all but part
of the problem is that especially now
you have to get so many ingredients
if you're not someone who cooks a
lot like you have to buy so
many things we have everything stocked here
because cool up for some reason
like keeps all that so we have
like everything you would ever want wow
full stocks like pantry and stuff like
that so when i started making cakes
it was like i would look at
the ingredients ago we can't possibly have
this right gahanna all right here we
don't have what does this floor slower
the company my dad flew helicopters for
more fluor
but i just wish i had a
chef yeah see that's where this is
headed now we'll just we'll get there
just to go like my ex is
my hook not really and we yeah
we we don't give up so early
okay
but we like we both don't really
care to try right right so it's
not really like i've done a lot
of those hello fresh type things yeah
podcast they send you like a box
and yeah yeah so i've gotten like
a bunch of those over the years
and i do those but like that's
really specific like the it's hard because
it's just like i that i make
that thing but then i won't probably
make it again because then i had
to get all that stuff again what
have you started small with stuff that's
kind of basic and then like that's
what i shall now because i feel
like i pick a big recipe in
my lord yeah peanut butter and julie
that i can do we made smash
burgers the other day we cool up
getting smash burgers kids oh oh oh
fucking good
they're amazing well what hit was yeah
okay i have a question what did
you manage there's a kit i want
it because that is sunk okay so
it's it's a pretty basic kit but
basically what you might do to help
is it has a like i guess
i'm mining right now sorry you're making
yourself
i can't believe i'm just lying right
why are you doing this like mining
watering plants
no but so it's it's it's like
in and take i mean maybe every
time you go over here maybe bb
taking a bit baby
but it's almost like an iron it's
like it's like a cast iron kind
of flat thing with a handle on
it so when you put like like
an iron yeah but he's round right
it's round yeah so you make the
burger you make you make ah ground
beef balls you put it on your
ah unique tick you for
fuck with it
you put it on his honor skillet
or whatever each for frying
he put on a frying pan you
ok you smash it down with this
with this cast iron thing so that
it's it's as flat as you can
get it huh and that way it
grills the edges very crispy and sounds
bring it ah and then the other
what else is indicate it must have
been
one thing the dry ingredients know not
to be for anything you say i
want just go buy beef and brown
beef soup article by b kid is
just a piece of paper that's like
here's what you need oh papers ah
paper comes in paper paper because you
gotta put data paper remember paper i'm
just trying to remember what's in the
hay
yeah
oh this and there's lots of plastic
i also haven't found a recipe for
burger sauce which is like like when
you get a fuck are you talking
about when you go you know when
you go to like in and out
and the sauce it tastes like burgers
when you go to in and out
and there's like an orange sauce that
they put on you know what i
mean it's not mustard it's it's thousand
not yet a woman it's
it's no moster it's like the island
and nah yeah sort of but it's
basically a shame it's ketchup mustard mayonnaise
relish vinegars sugar already hollering i don't
want that it's really it was really
fucking good they were like the best
burgers we'd ever made okay they're amazing
but one of the worst one
ns well ones where you don't know
what a cook and you're like is
this done and then it's wrong did
i just eat raw beef
but i think about my mom making
noise
alright let's have a moment of silence
where we all think about my mom
um but but making dishes you know
because she she got married right out
of high school right and so she
became a housewife and she wanted to
be a housewife because you want to
get out of the house so that's
what society told her shining on which
house curb she grew up in a
which house she wants to claim oh
boy drops because she wanted to get
out of the house but then she
had to go in that she got
to go
into a different house my house is
made of food i gotta get out
of here but she had to learn
how to be a housewife and essentially
my dad like you know went off
to the war in vietnam like right
when they got married so she was
like and had had a baby with
like the worst and so had had
a baby or know how to do
it and had had like help from
relatives sort of but she learned how
you know
no like i grew up going like
my mom's cooking is like she she
was very good at desserts but like
we have this kind of the same
seven things you say mean things but
then you realize the internet isn't around
and all she had was like one
cookbook that that someone had bought her
when she first became wives cool yeah
it was like essentially like
american cooking that's so basic and so
she learned how to do food men
love yeah she would like experiment occasionally
but if it didn't get a good
response from ah from the canvas early
on he's looking for someone he's like
a vasan lawn helicopter but there's also
a big lie
like squirrel or something on that fence
in any case or some fans are
pointing yeah yeah okay now it's right
side up so i can tell it's
a squirrel but it was upside down
for awhile um it's on top of
that fence up there i see but
yeah so she she basically like figured
out how to do the seven things
that kind of came out good where
it was like okay i think i
accomplished the mean
love then didn't yeah yeah and then
did them for the rest of you
know or whatever and it's just so
hardware is now we have so many
resources of like you can look up
any yeah recipe online or like you
have a dish at a place that
you really love you can kind of
go like oh what's in that and
then you look it up and they
and you like kentucky fried chicken you
can learn how to
well the problem but it's a double
edged sword because now you can look
up pornographic recipes that's true you go
you look like horn kids it takes
your entire life and you can't even
cook anything
the one thing i i am kind
of good at that i learned from
a cookbook is vegan pad thai oh
that sounds good is really good and
i want to make it again ah
species mikey no i don't like spicy
spicy to an okay fair enough if
you're being served by me despite c
does it upset your stomach
gk yan i also just don't like
the sensation of being like this is
so hot i can't even see straight
i don't like people always like that's
so good i don't like going that
far i like i like some spice
but i don't like i don't like
it where it's like i can't take
this city yeah yeah alright we have
to say break speaking in not being
able to take this
and it's delicious she's a frame talk
about space sound too afraid let's go
to a break i can't take it
and we're back and it's time for
three churches not confusing okay so listen
look we've been getting a lot of
messages from people this is not a
confusing thing that we do and it's
never confusing and it's not this time
either so i didn't see one comment
where someone said that
you saw all the comments i don't
always look at comments but before you
do but when i do look at
all they're all ah
the comment was about how christmas find
out who game we use the same
questions we did last year which i
didn't realize oh did we so we
don't ever remember remember that but i
decided that game is foolproof way you
do it every year i'd say how
would you funding to do the same
questions every year and now the exact
same only genuine thinking
my you've been to spain yeah you
know i'm saudi presented to us like
josh or whatever like these are new
this time but it's the same one
if you would do that to me
the day or the minute after we
recorded i would go oh yeah okay
well that's bad so this game brings
the same game as that but it's
not related to christmas okay but it's
the find out who game and why
what we're gonna do is each one
of us will come up with a
question as we go around and we'll
write down who we think it is
the same way we all have to
come up with questions like well just
go like the most likely to blank
and then we write down in the
but yeah sure you could say that
blank blank in the bud
and then i'll write down like the
questions so we know what it was
okay then just shut up here's what
i need you to shut up man
no matter what i just said a
lot of work no one's not okay
little fucking you have to think about
you dropped it very early in the
show why didn't you tell me because
i
thought it was funny not to it
was okay so i'll start okay
and we and we're writing down our
answers to this yeah okay who is
the most likely person here to work
with animals if they were not in
their current job who is the most
likely to work with animals like would
you be a veterinarian or a zookeeper
or animal wrangler okay
who out of the three of us
has gotten into an argument with a
neighbor with like a ah it doesn't
have to be direct next door but
with likes a neighbor in their neighborhood
okay palm
paul who is most likely to be
scared by horror movie i feel you
can say horse
well there goes my next question
um okay
who is the most likely to love
taking a road trip
you rolled your eyes when you said
that which makes me think it's not
you
um wow
that's an interesting wrinkle the game
um who hears most likely to be
scared by a horse
scared by a horse okay
ah
who here is most likely
to give a child an unusual name
oh
now we pause while lauren writes down
not only her answer but also the
question it was a long question it
was a long one i guess get
rid of the who well i don't
write any of that i don't you
know i skipped that read something i'm
not an idiot okay so it's like
when you're on this is like when
you're on millionaire and the people who
read that oh my god
hey u c d and then the
lambo okay is it jay they tell
you not to do that they do
okay this is what i wanted because
you can say don't like say if
you can figure out a way to
make the question shorter yeah because spanking
we've covered this okay spanking pen um
who is most likely to arrive late
late to a party to a party
like very late okay oh to a
party that changes dance party ah changes
my hand sir yeah wait till they
get a load at me
okay who here is the most likely
to jump out of an airplane go
skydiving
go skydiving go skydiving yay
for that one for some reason where
other person's last name instead
alright um
rate
who here is least afraid of spiders
least afraid of spiders
okay okay one more around yeah so
we go to twelve okay yeah who
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
i think so
um who here is the most handy
like ah you know around the house
who here
is most likely to have skipped a
grade skipped a grade in school
who among ye
is without sin
um
who here is the murkiest when they
are alone with their spouse wow wow
we are going to find out some
shit get real crazy okay now ty
time to go through it time to
go through hell as always it's time
to go through it that sing the
song about um the theme of the
game okay yeah find out who oh
god i know
find out who game i'll find out
who game now is someone to go
through it knows time to go through
it now it's time to go through
it now it's time to go poo
poo perfect one who just likes especially
to work with animals i do we
all say i agree
i think it's obviously lauren because when
we went to australia and she cried
when she held the the what was
the koala it was cool there yeah
i say lauren i said lauren as
well i said paul
who is it actually
there there's two three sides to every
story on the truth i wanted wanted
to be of that when i was
a little kid but now i don't
know that i like and i like
being around animals enough that i'd feel
so like i'd have you have a
cat right i have a dog and
and yeah that's it's you franny and
zooey alright fine isaac fran
a dewy base now oh franny and
lulu it's franny and retailers beam carpenters
see more i i feel like i
was not as interested in animals when
i was a kid as i am
now yeah like i have i have
ah an affection for animals that i
it's not like i didn't like animals
but i just i didn't like it
i don't think i cared i don't
think it was interesting thing me i
used to think having a dog was
a really weird thing i would be
like i used
just a bizarre costs like a wolf
why would you keep it let it
be free
okay who's most likely to have gotten
into an argument with a neighbor
um i sent me because i have
oh i said paul for some reason
i said me too i have you
though paul
yeah okay shows of you have you
i don't think so i at the
most i like used to take the
broom handle in like go bonk bonk
on up there starts asking me like
yeah what do you think yes you
don't be quiet
um i don't think i've ever i'm
trying to think no in fact i've
i've oh well there we used to
have a neighbor who was just kind
of weird and she she ran over
to my house once she was like
well what are you going to do
about this and i was just like
i'm sorry who are you i didn't
like know who she was just like
i'm your neighbor we met like twice
i'm like oh okay sorry yeah what
what are you talking about she's like
what are you going to do about
this situation i'm just like i what
do you talk she goes you keep
forgetting why yeah
she was your tree that fell into
my yard i'm like oh i and
i had some people over the house
working on the house and she's like
that's isn't that why all these people
over here
to get the tree out of my
yard i'm like no they're just working
on the house they can though do
you want them to just like well
i'm sorry i guess i didn't know
that you didn't know that your tree
fell over oh my god what a
situation anyway that was the closest i
ever came to an argument with me
just like staring blankly or going what
are you talking about goodwin though and
she felt very stupid no she woke
she
she's fucking dumb she's fucking dumb dumb
alright um mostly going to be hey
oh sorry oh did you not ask
somebody keeping score oh that's is that
part of it where it keeps cool
see i i actually was thinking of
this and i kind of decided not
to because yeah i think i saw
i thought you don't want the score
the score stars cares hello find out
who really
otherwise i would just vote for myself
the whole time like yeah it just
feels okay sorry just just asking a
question oh oh jessie away it was
really necessary
okay who's most likely to be scared
by a horror movie i said lauren
me too i only my mother you
liked horror movies no i care about
them less but i used to be
too scared oh as before twenty i
thought that you actually liked them so
i said paul because i like them
and i thought you like them they
first one i liked them too huh
so it's lauren actually an interesting okay
i do get scared by them but
i liked i get scared by him
by like cool op can't even watch
him so i don't know all of
that i don't get to see him
all the devil mask yeah i know
who's most likely to love going on
a roadtrip i said paul i said
me too i said me because i
couldn't quite tell i first said paul
and then i was like yeah but
i would too so i just said
miss true but who would like more
i thought it would be me because
then i started thinking about you me
it love you yeah it is
should go went together now you make
a movie called the trip i love
those movies who's most likely to be
scared by a horse
is that next yeah
oh wait i thought no way my
father was wondering between what number is
this that's five now i thought there
was one in between others one in
between two you do because he said
horror film and i said horse roadtrip
was in between oh we okay sorry
oh
wait but this is number five oh
okay yeah i said paul is most
likely to be scared by i said
scott i said scott i don't want
her writing but your sky two were
you scared
um i guess i was a little
like am i going to end up
like christopher reeve but then once you
get on it's like fine so i
went i did it at summer camp
for like literally ten minutes they do
they just put you on a horse
may lead you around oh but i
remember as a kid it was scary
because you feel so high up yes
but i just did it like five
years ago and it was fun i
guess i haven't ridden a horse and
a long time i feel weird about
it like there because there's trails here
where you can go and do it
right but there's like a one on
the one hand i really would like
to do it but the other hand
it feels weird to do that to
a while i think i've said this
before i don't know if i've said
on a podcast how could it like
it my belief is that wow men
get rich
which they get into planes and when
women get rich they get into horses
yeah mean i was like get interesting
fuckin boats yeah ooh both suck yeah
me so rich to get into boats
i hate boats and for what i
love them just rent a boat one
day exactly your real emoji um we
would fill in horses abolish the filibuster
we went horseback riding and costa rica
was beautiful
nice was on the beach i know
in the cloud forest was wow sounds
magical this is the bougie as podcast
oh okay who's the most likely to
give a child an unusual name i
said lauren because i thought that she
would name the kid after herself and
her own name is unusual wow you
i said me i said scott ah
wow we don't we'll never settle this
well we've never settled until one of
us has a kid names it can
i guess oh palsy one who's right
because he knows he would whoever is
right i don't know that i would
but i feel like i could see
it i feel like it's a thing
that i've made fun of but then
i could see myself
doing it accidentally doing whatever is right
she's getting me should get the kid
that's yeah it's like rumpelstiltskin
his name rumpelstiltskin yep okay who's gonna
who's most likely to be very late
to a party
okay so when you just said very
late i was gonna say paul he
but the late sucks but
because i said we do i said
call for the party i didn't say
paul for the party because paul is
usually early to parties well that's because
of janie yeah jamie's like we have
to go now and we get there
we're the only people they know that's
corrupted i'm like that too mike's really
not like that son was bodily but
i'm also early to parties because i
want to i want to leave
give them early too so that i
love to do that i love to
leave anyway i said lauren because i've
i knew it wasn't me and i
didn't think it was utah because of
the fact that you're early to every
bar never makes me late to parties
oh mike does he prefers to be
late was doing his her only just
like he's like was just keeping
going out it's keeping it out swe
so chill he's very chill okay so
who is the most likely to jump
out of an airplane
paul i said but i don't think
any of us would i said lauren
because i don't think mere paul would
i said aquaman because i didn't know
who i am last i don't know
i just wrote it that way i
don't think any of the sciences that's
why none of us would also because
of your contact the way you have
your contact card in your name always
capitalizes oh
when i write a hocker minute automatic
capital it does on mine too because
i don't know because i tell you
have it in your contact thing who's
the least afraid of spiders i said
scott i just got to i said
paul but it probably is me so
i mean i don't like them i
you know i don't like his aunts
or are you scared events i well
are you scared of ants the chinese
think i think we've talked about the
movie i saw were where all the
ants went crazy and and the the
people had to breathe out a strong
crazy and and then a person went
so crazy crazy hello
donated the pool filled with water and
jumped out of the third story into
the pool and a hallucinate there was
water in it and then you'd go
out there and it's empty and they
broke their neck i didn't like that
um i liked it anyway and i
don't like hands spiders i usually like
co-opt the other day well no i'm
sorry that was a dead bird that
she may be rid of but um
she'll always be like there's a spine
here in this room and you have
to get it okay fred schneider i
do there's a spider in the row
but you have to get it tend
to assume mike should kill bugs but
what's kind of a it's just kind
of i now i just kind of
do it because you have enough chores
yeah but spencer the stove to do
the washing i'll just go i'll
and not even sometimes we get crickets
and i really hate though
i'll do like bugs and gen i
have to deal with all the bugs
i'm not a big bug fan but
i i will do it but i'm
not happy about it i will say
bringing up costa rica again when we
did go a laugh of the trip
was going to the beach and when
we were there there are i think
basically crickets in your room and your
hotel room
room all the time and they're up
on the ceiling and all that and
you just have to accept it that's
a feature and a bug
you get a mesh net around your
know and i was just kinda like
okay well i guess this is just
part of it but don't it's a
little unsettling and i just have this
image of me watching doctor who on
my bed while they're like crickets everywhere
fuck but what doctor who or my
i-pad the fuck
i bet the most handy
i yeah i said me this shows
this so ten ten i said me
i said paul i said lauren whoa
we're all handy let's get an ikea
thing here and figure out who puts
together so i'm hung up my own
curtains which is amusing it's not easy
i've become handy around the house in
a way that i never anticipated
that i would and i do take
pleasure in like figuring things out for
when it's like
good things
when i'm like oh i know how
to do this i think i think
i know and like even if it's
a first attempt and it doesn't work
and then i look up something if
it's satisfying say mom called me three
days ago and well first of all
i have her her phone number is
one of the ones that can like
even though my phones on silent i
will
i'll have it ring because like if
i'm sleeping your mommy something went wrong
yeah yeah so like it it i'm
already unsettled that suddenly my phone is
ringing yeah and forced i pick it
up and she's just like scott
and i'm like oh fuck okay what's
you know you're just waiting for these
calls what's going on and she and
she like configure out how to get
the tv off of netflix onto regular
tv and i'm like oh my god
you're making it sound like an emergency
and so like i took her through
what
button on the directv thing to like
presses hold it down for two seconds
okay but now i can't move it
i'm like ok now keep pressing that
button will cycle through all the h
h d my things and she's like
what is atm i'm like well worry
about it
well that's the plug like everything it's
like a high definition plug that and
she's like oh so each one of
these is one of the things that's
plugged into the tv i'm like yeah
what's the my part said for so
at the end she finally like how
to and she goes scott you're a
genius
i just left it like jesus yeah
i love it i just have had
to do this kind of stuff forty
and set it up anyway okay okay
you are not a junior
yeah talk to my friends polyvore set
the record straight we all know how
to do this mrs oscar manheim is
zuckerman
okay if she could figure out a
podcast i would be very scared about
the things i say
ooh skip cut most likely to skip
a grade which one is this is
number eleven eleven i said scott
this one is that it's my that's
my mom calling you zuckerman
i said paul but i i know
none of us i sent me because
i was offered it and you are
offered and i passed why because i
just didn't want to be younger than
everyone in the grade i would plus
i now have don't you wish that
you were i wish i'd doogie howser
the shit out of this my life
would be so much differ
aren't um plus i'd just i was
really smart and offered to skip grades
but then when they started giving homework
when i was ten or eleven i
instantly became bad at school because i
hate homework yeah like hate any kind
of like assignment or being told i
had to do stuff it's like let
me learn this shit in class homo
work is weird it's a weird concept
like you're there so long in school
you should be able to accomplish everything
while you're there i never thought about
until i was well out of school
and hearing a parents talk about it
and maybe some teachers i don't know
but the idea of like abolishing homework
like yeah
seems like kind of um classes because
not everyone can do this stuff at
home and everyone has the time the
resources and all that kinda stuff you
can fall behind because you can't do
that but you do it all while
you're there like when we go to
work um you're there for eight hours
or the same amount of time you're
at school you're not then like taking
it home with
you and going like let me do
some of this while i'm at home
no fuck that sometimes you know yeah
i guess okay last question she asked
with their spouse at home i said
paul lauren would you say said paul
but then i just added an scott
together
kissing each other i also said me
yeah i think you are we say
we say i love you constantly at
home yeah to each other no
each year side pieces
we said under our breath
fuck i love you know what nothing
cool that's very mushy with me yeah
i can see that that's kind of
what was pushing me in that direction
yeah well maybe she can get him
to mush it up with her most
of the shit out of it is
make mushy
whereas lomaia but i do feel like
i would say i view you guys
is just like high-fiving at the end
of the day and got right time
to sleep
later bro that's so rude
but that's fine you can have that
energy but i wouldn't want me to
imagine hey that's what i'm saying stick
like that but i do think that
like kovind like really zaps the fuckin
like cool oh and was like well
yeah your deal well you're also each
other for more than five sec yeah
yeah i mean we're doing you know
autumn sam
you so often do stuff and then
like meet up at the end of
the day and be like what do
you do what yeah and like have
be excited to see each other now
it's just like just a constant you're
in my field of vision yeah twenty
four hours a day like i'm grateful
that before hours of day i have
a partner that i'm excited to be
around like still now it's a lot
of times you swap
not part of the plan
hey m t hgf nb absence makes
the heart grow fonder
america's funniest home videos
tyra banks alright that's gonna do it
for this one that was good we
learn more about each other i enjoyed
that lauren oh here comes the sun
now and the sun just suddenly came
out good good time to be able
to move these umbrellas all right that's
gonna do it for this episode hey
hey if you're having trouble moving your
own umbrellas we hear yeah give us
a call we'll move him we all
have to
move our own umbrellas at some point
and we're no different we love you
thank you for listening we'll be back
next week with more of this bullshit
guy
uh