three
ah
ah good
i'm still shouting thredup think you've have
you ever had the fear around welcome
to freedom lauren has an important question
go have you ever had the fear
of someone throwing acid on you yes
all the time you know those stories
of like jilted lovers oh yes story
yeah yeah i'm more about like you
know the guys out
tough to really worried but i've heard
these stories yeah wait a sec i
love with the guy who would like
walk around the supermarket squirting like semen
onto people that's what i'm mortified that
was cool
yeah that's actually cool the gist man
the gist man babe did somebody order
a's like just man and reggie red
light special martin davis lebron james man
oh wow blah blah as anybody wishing
that jeez what were the circumstances of
the acid was like a guy who
was like in love with a girl
she didn't like him or something so
he's like i'm gonna ruin euros ass
she's
like two beautiful or something yeah wow
beautiful washi so gorgeous but there's a
documentary about that too i think and
the documentary about what about throwing up
bad habits know there's been more than
one case okay sorry to work was
she like yeah i'm not going to
get remember there being a really twisted
ending to it spoiler alert that they
end up together oh so it's so
far thing so why it's something on
netflix um have some respect ladies and
gentlemen yeah
yeah it was really really messed up
that's fucked up so don't do this
i would like to know about love
what if someone came up to this
is acid it was just water and
said this is acid and then threw
it on you what would you do
i'd probably scream and ride on ground
whoa whoa whoa bro baby what i
would do i would say you lied
to me excuse me i'm not even
going to react don't you think if
someone threw like a cup of like
crumbs anyone said they were spiders you
would snuggle
these are spiders hey one spiders new
and then you'd go oh it's just
a couple of crumbs do you like
going oh hums i really gotta crow
do you like going through a hundred
houses and everything just stuff that you
don't like haunted houses at all no
i've i've ended up in a bunch
of em but i just don't really
think so
oh how amazes i like him if
there there's still some good as the
thing you know what i mean because
it doesn't have being the same thing
over and over again is you're you're
you know you're walking down a corridor
and there's the other day yeah crazy
love is the documentary on netflix about
to be two tabs um and someone
jumps out at you yeah somebody jumps
out at you but sometimes they're good
good sometimes good but it's very rare
and most of the time you end
up seeing them reset you know what
i mean like far enough away that
issue when you have to get when
you go through like universal studios are
not scary farm older there's so many
people that these would all be great
if you it's just you going through
the maze and then you know you
you
wait like twenty seconds for the next
person but because you're just there with
like a long stream of people who
knows if you're gonna scare oh there
was one at the the hollywood hayride
oh yeah be great and now it's
not good the first time i went
through that man there was something that
happened that was so scary they threw
like a garbage can at us or
something in it like
hit right next to the hole in
the hay ride itself on the hayride
itself yeah hit right next to us
and then they pulled it back with
a string or whatever like yeah it
isn't really creative and interesting now it's
just like boring is boring yeah but
they had a haunted house like amaze
right that was all strobe lights and
no warning
at all yeah that makes you say
oh no warning but yeah you kind
of you have to tell people you
have to legally luckily none of us
had an issue with that but it's
like there was i remember like i
had to think back like it wasn't
on the ticket there was no when
we bought the ticket nobody said just
so you know it's strobes yeah and
that's also not even that scary it's
more just disorienting yeah like
i feel like i went on the
haunted hayride for the first time like
two years ago and at the end
the last thing was all about trump
like it was oh yes yeah someone
just trump and i was like boo
that was the year that scared of
a skeleton yeah i want the skin
over scary skeletons get of stinson always
scared of the president yes that's just
a bummer yeah
yeah and it's every day anyway with
this president boy i've really i have
gotten to the point where i can't
watch the news because i can't see
video i don't know who watched any
physically yourself hire some um i went
to knott's scary farm with paul ross
neil campbell once checks out and um
what did they
every every maze i don't know how
you know how
because i don't know if you've been
on the other side if you'd have
you scared people amazes before you ever
go ahead okay duh duh if you
don't a few places yeah in high
school we did a charity one at
the school i did one when i
was ah i think two years before
freshman year and um i hadn't been
born yet
it's been a twinkle
in others eyes she was born to
them he was a baby come on
and um anyway so i've done over
the years but you pick you can
always like tell you like you wanna
pick someone you're gonna scare and not
the people were like whoa very scary
you know yeah you wanna scare the
shit yeah somebody so i don't know
what it was but every maze that
we went into eh
every monster focused on neal
like not paul not me right they
all just like like a bee-line towards
towards neil and he was just there
going i don't know what's happening when
my physical one i hate how had
um the universal studios and stuff they
can run right up to you yeah
when you're walking around yeah that makes
me very uncomfortable that it can be
right just a guy look
it's like a zombie just like run
or schemes oftentimes they're on those like
wheelie sneakers yeah and that countrymen long
if you do that i don't know
why they say it kind of scares
you it is scary but it's like
why are you snorting because it scared
you yeah i mean it worked
oh yeah you got your answer just
creepy the guy it's ah i'm honored
finally dude thanks
who would pay someone to do something
like that well who would pay sixty
plus dollars to go in and experience
the yeah the last year i remember
the hollywood hayride being really good it
was very it was the year it
was like right after mad max came
out the mad man redman
mad men fury road i love it
don draper just playing guitar on a
truck which maybe i brought this up
before water he is mad he's mad
max madsen local commercial um that's before
you know the commercial because you're from
that he's nodding yeah the chevron by
the way
it's not she doesn't it's not young
where are you guys from chicago or
some toggle land okay so what happened
on this hay ride that was so
good i one of the thing that's
oh so it was right after mad
max him out so they had um
people on these these tall bendy poles
with these blasts on oh so they
were i was here i think right
it was acrobatic great yeah they also
had a weird thing where you went
through like a war zone yeah where
people were coming up to you in
the makeup was great because it wasn't
like really gory it was just unsettling
and they came up and like they
would hand you a note they wouldn't
say anything to you but they would
have to know then the note was
weird and unsettling it was great it
was really
autistic and then went on shark tank
and they said yes oh so that's
a change i don't like the next
year the theme was clown yeah because
it came out ah have you ever
been to like um there's this thing
in law called delusion delusion the haunted
play on to play no two i
think i'd tried but it was holdout
have you
really not a retard ever heard of
it
you are delusional dubai it's it they
basically use some like abandoned neil patrick
harris produces me oh maybe yeah they
used to make abandoned mansion like you
know sort of house in l a
and they make it into a play
that you like walk through i love
somebody i've always
pretty fun i wanted to produce one
a comedy version yeah i could pedro's
i don't know if you remember oh
my god yeah it was so cavernous
yes so many rooms i wanted to
do something like that where like comedians
just each took a room and that's
fun yeah it's like what are they
called sleep nomor yeah are you but
this one you're on a specific path
or like you can't just go wherever
you want oh you're following
a story and you're like running from
a scary guy at one point there
was one point with this they changed
the story every year so one time
we were like under this gigantic like
a dining room table that was really
talk as if you were a little
kid under it and then these biggs
big like legs walked by oh you
wouldn't right yeah outside of the table
you know so it was really scary
because like what is that let's go
let's go to it
this year and record an episode during
i'd like to have you ever done
the queen mary one yeah that one
scared me too much that's where i
had to kind of pull oh really
too many people in shorts yeah they
were really jumping at me in the
amazes yeah and i was getting just
really scared i was like maybe this
isn't for me to sing about the
jumping is like there's other ways you
could be scary
you don't yeah like oh hearted people
you can more people you can channel
my head at a weird angle
coladas is creepy cool up hates them
and we went to we went to
a couple and it was okay and
then she was like i hate these
i don't want to go back to
that does she hit the ghouls and
you're not supposed to touch the yeah
and then what and this and then
when we first started dating i was
like hey we're we're going to go
somewhere tonight i'm not going to tell
you what what it is
and um then we got to a
mutual friend's house and they let it
slip oh yeah we're going into this
haunted house thing and she is the
maddest i've ever seen her and she
met her the purse yeah i'm of
than that purse and she like went
home and didn't talk to me for
a few days and it was like
it
was there and then we went to
the hot place i went by myself
and it was she would have hated
it was we had to like crawl
into a dugout tunnel in the ground
you know somehow really like those those
places where they're like make you do
stuff like i like so i'm like
topics for raw stuff yeah it was
one that i heard about
where it's like you walk into some
weird room and then you like see
people having sex and the it's like
twisted and weird and you go to
another room and you like and you
get some likes to latch on you
or you're being like locks
you can help yourself
you get handcuffed and like a dominatrix
comes over you and just start spanking
you and you have to like it
but i don't like the idea of
being out of control i want to
be able to leave yeah yeah right
i like it to be kind of
more of a show yeah i don't
want them to be looking into my
eyes i get to be a play
and last for about two hours with
an intermission and to be about hamilton
yeah and they want like to be
songs yeah
seats gin and tonics tickets m and
m's for expensive amounts programs
good merch and that's it
hi guys if you do like calls
yo me know do you only wear
clothes
today only only work you gotta hamilton
yeah just the hat that's all you
wear yep you bought the hat yeah
he's sitting here nude with a hat
on and i didn't even notice i'm
taking joe cockers advice new to the
hands at a song i left my
head on nude and a hat on
the same runway i have been
been hearing about that that musical hades
town yeah but the tonys were all
but yeah i had not heard anything
specific i just heard like seen people
on twitter or like broadway people and
you know who you are i'm sub
podcasting you right now but people saying
that they really love this show and
then seeing that number on the tonys
i was like i think this is
a thing that i would really like
oh yeah should we go we should
go but hey oh no we're gonna
try i talked to off air about
it but um ah snake and i
i put it out because i don't
way you weirdoes showing up face down
when we're there was a eighties down
as for the boys
downers hurt the boy three hundred three
three boys are going eighties down to
hear the three boys are coming daddy
down today
no wait i'm laura are you one
of the three deaths yeah why would
i not be okay boy hey just
you yeah just me and then what
i don't get the guy i'm the
threesome boys
ah so i put it out on
twitter because i really was so curious
about it i said should i is
it dumb if i buy isn't a
bad idea if i buy the soundtrack
right oh yeah and listen to it
before yeah or debate that i said
you know you told me not to
listen to what to call your own
hansen oh dear evan hansen yeah
and i did it and then i
thought but i might have been more
excited to see it if i hadn't
left yeah how did that affect you
did you like them just as much
i liked it because i loved the
songs by that point so i was
really excited to hear all the songs
but i i filled in a lot
of the holes because i didn't know
all the plot i could like your
old apartment yeah i couldn't figure everything
out from the soundtrack because they leave
there's a lot yeah well that's my
that's my
point is when you listen to a
cast album before you see the show
you you don't get it you don't
get why the songs are good because
you don't know what's happening well but
here's the thing okay so people said
you should first listen to the original
concept album right because then you get
the whole story yes yeah it's really
a new post this and like bony
vera made that not what didn't
you do like all the songs or
something owner know why i thought you
posted a screen grab of that i
did post a screen grab me i
think they also like so it was
sort of like sometimes in a musical
they they make a an album about
at first such as jesus christ superstar
yeah viva evita was a vietnam visa
that was
in a concept album first i think
it was the yeah so but ah
and no no it was yeah it
was what's cause maybe i just don't
know anyway which one yeah and then
they base a musical it's called hades
tell you find anna you spoke these
guys are on their phones but no
it's germane to the that's why we
have this guide will he does yeah
because he's just saying he doesn't know
balls slapping computer and in justin vernon
is bones bony ver oh my word
and i know that and bruce wayne
is batman
man one of the funniest things in
bazillion dollar properties was ryan gallen drew
tarver you know doing one of the
talking heads segments write their characters and
ah so you know it's like ah
you know he's like ah bruce wayne
and he's like you know it's like
bruce wayne being batman and ryan says
batman right like how there's it now
the idea that you would know of
the fictional character that you would wrote
both those fictional characters i feel like
that's a kevin sasha thing that's a
i think it's a tremendous joke right
it's a tremendous because i remember we
all wrote those before they happened and
i'm pretty sure kevin
or that one but yeah it's funny
it's a good one yeah it's good
well enough i will take the credit
away from ryan yes transferred to good
stuff good stuff kevin good stuff anyway
she wrote the music on east mitchell
okay she liked the concept oh yes
i love it so let's go to
this shit go to this shit if
you're in hades down out there and
you're listening oh freedom boys wanna go
the freedom boys some theater seats gets
the threesome boy somehow seats we want
some out we want houses we will
only take house seat we want house
eighties die in these towns
three two boys have spoken we want
a backstage tour back stage we want
to be in it we see it
put us in we want to see
the first act and we'll figure it
out enough that we're in the second
bill practice one of the songs where
people are just standing there yeah not
singing and not doing anything
we want to be in it so
the concept album is not the same
songs it's just i think it's many
if not all of the same sometimes
they'll apparently an album and then yeah
like they'll like they'll do different things
with it once it actually gets apparently
there's there's a there's a couple different
versions there's the concept album then there's
the original broadway cast and then there
is the cast that's ah i really
ignore the initial yeah mate not that
touring company but it's like the cast
is happening now i guess um that
that hasn't come out yet
oh yeah okay i think there's original
cast recording then there's the soundtrack and
okay look we've got we've got to
get in there and roll up our
sleeves and come on eighties to come
on anyway you haven't offered us tickets
yet we've been we've been talking about
you for the last ten minutes send
us presents one of the things in
his presence we want precedence we want
an
equal amount to whatever you donated to
serial
and we want tickets to hades town
and we want a backstage tour and
we want to be in it that's
all the freedom boys oh shit on
one of these are we getting the
the money in cash
they donated just what you wanted in
like gold or like checks or venmo
or what i'd like mine couponing go
to the bank i want cash but
you know some people are afraid to
mail cash because it gets stolen it's
true yeah remember when we were on
tour and we would get our field
buyouts and we would always
every single time when they would take
the forty dollars or the twenty nose
twenty dollars we would each get twenty
dollars a piece we'd be like yeah
yeah yeah scott what's up it's not
haiti town but it's very close why
does not even call haiti sound wasn't
this donor well this is a different
musical okay just call text
the bat out of hell musical recently
booked spots on the show and they're
extending a special offer to hosts please
let me know if scott is interested
in attending the show's final dress rehearsal
on thursday in new york city third
wait where's their august first just thursday
day
any thursday
oh no it's a specific thursday okay
just bid if you can you take
to get there on the right one
click the link i mean yeah if
they bought me a buy me a
first-class yeah i'll go to it yeah
definitely yeah i'll be there we were
not if i was a comedy bang
bang i will tell you that i
was just listening to bat out of
hell the regular album just the other
day and just the other day
yes it's that and i saw a
pretty lady you know what just oh
bat out of hell is a an
album that meatloaf has the for loaf
but i thought i was going to
sound like an handling it was his
breakout i think you don't know that's
a singer yeah just like me oh
yeah i think he sold fifteen million
albums released and jim steinman wrote it
wrote the songs for away and yeah
they must have made a musical based
based on the album i think you
know what i it's knowing nothing about
this yeah i always find this kind
of interesting because it's like they have
to create a story around just like
random yeah stuff that doesn't make any
sense i mean the songs in data
hell don't even make any sense you
know
the most open window okay soon me
it took and then paradise by the
dashboard light doesn't make any oh what
are they gonna do with it isn't
harry carey it was that part it
was filled rosato boy things also dead
by now all right so who plays
him with that we want to play
him maybe they'll get yeah well went
right back to meet lo
tfw properly this was meat loaf right
back to me listen i really love
deer meat their low heel will do
the phil rizzuto part will do that
will come on august first and the
three of us will simultaneously do the
phil rizzuto ah okay just tell me
love that that's cool
um yeah we need to take a
break we'll be right back
we are back to back three of
them boys are back the boys are
back boys backing down
what are you guys going do tonight
wow well i'm gonna go home i'm
going to walk my doggies and then
i gotta say cool ups gonna get
home and we are gonna be home
around the same time and you know
we've been talking about pizza so much
have we been talking about pizza on
the air you have yeah you know
i've been off i think it was
yeah i was oh yeah i was
a little more getting heavy into local
pizza i was a little upset because
lauren started talking about pizza and i
was like well did you bring pizza
and she just didn't start talking about
it you asked me if i want
sick pizza place on my trip oh
you asked us if we went to
a specific pizza place no yes pi
no oh ma we
oh oh oh let me not be
the referee let me tell you how
when kevin asked me how my trip
to japan was i said it was
i said did you get that nature
they're exactly and as you say it
was like a pizza i brought a
valid pizza but you just said that
i brought up what pizza place we
ordered from and that was you
no yes it was i didn't say
that i said you brought up pizza
to begin with and it was you
but you just previous just three seconds
ago you said that i asked what
pizza place we all went to and
that was you know
i didn't ask that yes you did
paul she did i didn't ask why
i didn't she did she didn't just
say that i didn't say scott asks
what pizza place you go into she's
twenty dollars why oh
oh he said why you're supposed to
just give it to him if you
know what's good for you no no
that was very very telling
i love by the way how upset
you got about that's you making a
mountain out of a molehill my friend
that you would even believe i'm upset
your your steaming right yeah this isn't
the three-time boys what are you gonna
do i'm gonna eat pizza this made
me hungry for because yeah pause coming
over let's all get pizza right let's
order pizza or
i haven't had regular pizza in a
while because we've been when you consider
regular pizza like well the opposite of
what i'm about to tell you boy
this is which is what teams ah
the cauliflower crust oh yeah i mean
good here's regular pizza
it's purple on the base
it's round like this wrangle from the
top
i thought you doing big suit know
i know but i'm griping up normally
tears what regular pizza is like the
base is trying to look like shrestha
gone black shreds
and hot pink circles yes
it's like a ninja turtle talking but
i might get pizza that's what i
might do tonight and i don't you
know look the bachelor i watched it
already are you caught up icon back
from japan's you i basically started doing
his instagram stories i wish i was
doing a radio or reviewing it right
now you and i would text each
other's really good wow
caught fire a little bit meaningless like
a handful of people like when i'm
doing you guys talk to each other
with them yeah we have a text
chain it's just me and her just
about the bachelor
you don't watch the batch there's other
so there's other topics you could tell
me you're watching your bachelor let me
see if there's a i've discussed any
other topics tell you i feel a
civic duty to do any board the
bachelor on my story in a in
a quick amount of time so okay
a lot of scheduling stuff what happened
a lot of scheduling
stuff between us and then a bachelor
thing i sent you a video about
the bachelor when you were in tokyo
and then some gossip oh boy about
people we don't know um about celebrities
oh yeah we were having celebrity oh
and then you send me these pictures
that you took of me where i'm
ah or i'm a whoa oh my
god so funny with a snapchat fill
alter oh no baby one should baby
when i saw the post em you
posted the yeah alright yeah custom again
and then ah oh and then we
talked about ah something that we can't
talk about but we talked about yeah
interesting is what we taste so a
lot of stuff here a lot of
stuff ok but what if paul and
i text about we have a private
chain to you do
why do what about so first we're
talking about twitter dot com
and then paul always sends me like
funny dogs that i should fall off
true oh funny dogs on twitter's this
one owen from all kinds of places
oh griff what's ones looks like a
weird puppet this tongue sticking out okay
and then i told i told paul
about this japanese toilet that's very common
you know there's toilets so
it's basically a rectangle hole in the
ground no i don't think i've ever
seen one of them it looks like
a urinal laid down onto the floor
and was sleeping and taking a nap
these are women's restrooms matter if they're
just women's but i came across them
in women's restrooms right and i um
was always afraid of them because when
i first wanted to japan a couple
of
years ago the first toilet i saw
when i was in the airport was
this and it was a hole in
the ground it's basically a hole in
the ground the bar on the wall
and i was like like are you
supposed to lean back lean and squat
over the thing and it really intimidated
me especially because i was really twist
like the like you're like i'm not
trying this and then the first time
you like hovered above it like rosa
to me it would
any the craziest was but i was
so afraid that i was gonna get
peel over myself if i didn't if
i just did it wrong yeah and
then i told paul about it and
then i did use once and i
had to tell him i did it
oh they had to because i was
out to do it all over yourself
no i did great but and what
did i say in return he was
proud of me but i i did
it like a baseball dime
and like they had like a little
public restroom there and i went in
and i might at that point we've
been walking so much through you're talking
about how when you guys went you
want like ten miles a day you
did the same thing and it was
like i'm my hosting blogs are wearing
the wrong shoes so my back was
hurting so much and then i i
had to pee so bad and so
i went in and i did it
but then i almost couldn't get up
because my eye was like squatting in
holding onto the bar
or why would they do this like
the purpose my back hurt so much
i was like whoa with it all
of my mizo to get up if
you have to do a pull-up to
get off of a toilet what are
we even doing guys you know we're
dying we're working our core know but
i was still impressed by i wondered
also if maybe someone out there can
tell me or i could google it
but if the bar is more
for like people older people or people
who don't know how to use these
toilets and if typically you don't need
the bar if you know yes why
don't you use the bar you know
what i mean i nobody was a
real fool maybe it was like whoa
wait wait wait wait are you like
are you holding onto you you were
sort of like me like you're in
a roller coaster i was holding onto
it and you hold the body well
i mean if
you're just squatting over something you don't
need a bar i guess if i
was wearing a dress or something i'd
be easier but if my with pants
on i would get peel i guess
what do how far did the pants
go down to like knees or their
pants
you mean when i pulled him down
kaua'i
i've pulled them down past my knees
past your knees like what to shoes
i didn't pull them to the shoe
so between me and shoe
cashflow what's normal for the two
do you mean your pants over your
knees whereas civic questions and making you
feel nobody i want to picture you
on the toilet do you pull your
pants all the way down i've had
your okay paul have you seen this
where you go into a men's restroom
boy and someone at the urinal has
their pants all the way down like
pastor noel boys yeah
yes a grown ass man string why
on earth would you ever do it's
weird what is the reasoning okay if
you're out there and you do it
and then you have started doing it
will stop doing it but also we
hate with sorry no commenting about you
but it's weird to see there's probably
gotta be a reason but like what
just not getting pee on your pants
if you're going through the i don't
get it i also i honestly don't
don't know it's it's beyond me why
guys do that it's so crazy i
also think it's so i think it's
weird to have urinals i think they
should be like outlawed why can't you
just have privacy yeah well i'm all
for that i think that all because
instead of making when you that's gross
when you go to a movie theater
instead of having one big room that
has a
a lot of places for a lot
of people to go to the bathroom
instead make like thirty little bathrooms this
is great they should just be all
over the place okay so nice surprise
every seat in the mood so over
me in the movie theater there should
be lawyers there's doors everywhere sometimes over
door brick wall so the door there's
a toilet sometimes my pop side made
to the
that's fun
sometimes a scary clown have you what's
the craziest thing you've ever used alone
the craziest toilet i knew we didn't
have talking about this i don't think
that i've ever made even been on
a crazy toy i don't think i
was either i've never encountered a b'day
oh japan is all about medallion yeah
i want one so bad well i
will say that we happen to realise
it
when we went to like europe and
stuff they're usually a separate toilet yeah
like the yeah yeah in when we
were just in japan i will say
that that anytime you walked into the
bathroom it had a motion sensor with
that toilet crazy
like the toilets like like oh please
shoot me
oh my love she's norm and you
can also press a button that makes
like water sounds so it covers the
sound of you going oh so yeah
like i had a friend who when
we were in a musical together we
add a our dressing room had a
tiny bathroom and he always would like
blast the sink on yeah and then
sing because he just didn't want any
nurses to be i don't think i
would ask the
other person is saying i wouldn't want
to be singing right but think about
if we had this in america when
you are in a public bathroom with
stalls you could have a sound going
have a sound going i feel people
are the sound of like artists it's
what japan is so much better than
american i've always said that everywhere i
also use a home the floor one
time in france and
old restaurant downstairs basement i went down
there and then all they had was
a hole in the foil like like
ivy it was like a toilet hole
but it was they had seen your
dad explains it it was really cool
it was a very small hole in
the ground and there were feat marks
and there was a how smalls this
whole like quarter-sized would get a shit
in
you don't have perfect aim and then
there was a um a button or
like a foot pedal on the wall
to flush and water air so sophisticated
as a have a pedal who is
crazily say there's there's a ton of
toiling let's say god yeah give me
some one guy the way i'm sitting
with my back to a screen and
ever
sounds like pointing it'll turn around i
can't turn around oh the mike won't
that one there i think that's like
a twit okay now they're looking at
pictures lawrence i presume the restaurant france
actually in the what the listener is
like wondering what was there was there
a bench tour sort of thing nose
just was just a hole to hole
in the ground like the taking
remember it out
i went knit
no it wasn't it was what the
the toilet was supposed to be sure
it was like a twenty there was
no elevation to it it was known
literally it was nothing like the japanese
one it was just a hole and
then would you recognize the phrase out
of order in french if usada do
not come in here it's quite possible
americans like stop shitting please stop shitting
in football
that is funny because i feel like
anytime you're in a strange situation you
just go with it like i guess
i guess i'm supposed to shit here
yeah lady ladies possible i was somehow
wrong but i don't think so
what were you doing in france that
was i was on a trip with
my family i was like a teenager
ooh la la are you interested did
you yeah did you speak any french
at the time no i don't even
know a word did you speak it
i didn't and still don't never will
i never will never will did you
take a language i took italian i
did that in college for two years
i did spanish from seven when conversing
italo
even a little bit sure but i
got sammy yeah it goes ha yeah
just bochy me yeah yeah that's about
it that was cool was gonna join
the girls i like
i like yeah girls i like i
like hey you'll feel for the loophole
i want to go to italy hungry
like the wolf no i just want
pizza oh my gosh it's it's what
is the next place on your bucket
list italy is probably where i want
to yeah mine too i wanna go
you've been there no never been we
went to france
nsw in england and i'm sick of
england sick of the english people love
it you like england i used to
love i was an anglo file and
now i just i've added i still
talk to so many english people recently
i'm just like god get navigate
wow really strong opinion i was just
remembering we went to paris for our
the climate agreement yeah for the common
core
to protest us oh and i um
we went for our anniversary a few
years like god is almost ten years
ago now no my gosh it was
a while ago it was like twenty
nine pounds i write about you said
you got married ten years ago
yeah we outline dot com we so
seven years ago next year it will
be ten years okay so it was
it was seven years ago yeah twenty
twenty twelve so and we i did
a gig in ah in london at
the soho theatre like eighteen years after
collapse freshmen
then janie came over jane came over
for the london week and then i
was there for two weeks skim over
the second week of london and then
we spent a week in paris and
i forgot that at the end at
the very end of the paris trip
i got a um immersive infection in
my leg oh is this the only
time you've had mirza
no no no yeah because he told
another per second right the first time
is immersed first time was in new
york it's an immune thing um where
you get like
i don't know how to describe it
it's like a big cystic thing first
time i got on my face and
i discovered i was sick when i
came home from work in a mirror
lately oh wow
i looked at you i thought it
was a blemish i just thought it
was like a zit that small at
first yeah yeah and but but who
cares it was it it got bigger
edge
versus is it i was not trying
kept thinking how could i could go
when i want to sleep i just
like after work i laid down on
the bed in my clothes on woke
up in the same position the next
day and i was like maybe i
should go to the dog woke up
in the saint the exact i had
not moved like i lay down the
bed and was there a
chalk outline around you how did you
know that you should go to the
doctor i honestly don't know if that
if does justice leave just sleeping with
me oh because i like i fell
asleep so fast like i didn't eat
dinner anything like i came was like
i'm going to lay down for a
second and then then there's the next
morning right and i have weird yeah
you're right when i had mono it
was even that well i
had it for two weeks and just
someone had this someone had to say
to me yeah it's the kissing disease
someone had to say to me like
you're you've been tired for weeks and
before i was like oh maybe i
should go to a doctor i've had
i had mono this is of course
i was you know we all get
method nineteen different people know i just
checked my checked mine because i was
like oh i should turn that off
if it's ringing
ing in it i did not get
a message but i will say that
ah when that emergency ah thing happens
it's wild isn't it when everyone gets
a message at the same time yeah
it is i i guess i turned
off those journals oof yeah i turn
them off to the first time that
happened it was terrifying i know at
first you were afraid the first time
never a little bit
they honestly though ama are thinking so
sad because you just feel helpless like
okay now i just know there's some
child being kidnapped and what am i
gonna like yeah look around license plates
all the time and just be like
ooh is this the guy or am
i gonna say they're onto me i
got a hider better
have have had waked so then i
got mirza again and frank yeah yeah
so the very end of the trip
it got bad enough it was like
the last few days and got bad
enough that i couldn't walk properly what
because it was on my leg and
it hurt so much and i i
had to wait until i
got back home and you're like han
or not honeymooning but like having an
anniversary in france does this mean for
you you don't want to be like
this sucks but france ca soccer blue
no it was great it was i
thought a great time i forgot that
that happened until janey reminded me recently
that's how good a time we had
but then i had to have it
like essentially like what do they do
i have eight and deflated you know
when they land something what do they
do fucking it with a needle or
what do they do yeah yeah was
it early they're taking out all the
fluid i mean yeah it it hurt
it fucking hurt and i didn't keep
the fluid do that do they like
give you know i still have it
you want
oh oh my neck like angelina jolie
wait have we talked to dr pimple
popper
no go ahead or butlins that your
alias is yeah i don't i don't
like to do specific gender things but
this seems like a thing that women
are willing really like dark i do
think there's some something about that i
also feel like i was someone who
liked to do that i think it's
because men have peace
is that erupt and so we're good
on in that respect bar
and women want to make the penis
rose i know yeah your grow your
time we get both a grand term
for what actually happens so raw
you robbed
if anyone said that to lauren i'm
going to a rise
you do
i don't think i see that said
to anyone
is it a month and we no
huh
because you're
what if neil halo
and said i'm glad they're dropped
what if suddenly one of y'all got
so scared when the ghouls were targeting
him
ichi just came i've got erupt
ah good stuff what was the thing
neal said i always i remember the
exact gallery wrap
when we were on tour and went
out on the balcony of the hotel
oh my guys and it was about
hey whoa we should talk till i
could not stop loving have we not
told this story we haven't i don't
think we know maybe on the big
bang oh my god best of awry
we were crying but which was tells
it all hat all chinese
balconies shallow balconies those cool we were
like y'all excited about these rooms and
so we're getting into the car to
go to the show and neil said
anyone else go out on their balcony
right and they're like i think we
all said no yeah we were like
no because it was super windy yeah
and he said i did oh he's
always like well it was windy and
it was cold and i was scared
so went back inside
right
it was like so madam brought it
up was eating at home i got
scared i went back inside he brought
it up and like there was no
reason why west would go because it
was so cool yeah but then he
just wanted to tell us that he
was scared he did he got frightened
and but he also didn't get why
it was funny oh my
oh do you go i was fun
i think you surprised we were crying
about a pretend mean i mean it
was we where we live probably the
way he delivered his astonishing yeah but
i guess because it was like we
all had the shared experience right yeah
like we did now you have to
tell us what it's like yeah i
guess he thought we all went out
on to our balcony good for you
it's like
eddie would have yeah he thought we
were all going to go yeah no
so frayed yeah yeah yeah we all
opened her but balconies saw the weather
and didn't go out yeah ah good
last time you were like laughed so
hard you couldn't stop
i don't know i feel like it's
been a while i feel like it's
maybe laugh like that yeah that's that's
special yeah it's very i always get
jealous when somebody's laughing like that and
i'm not really thinking it's as funny
but i want to laugh a lot
you know i hope you say to
the person it's not that funny yeah
oh come ah the best thing you
can do i hate that it's like
someone supplies kill a word
i feel like i come close to
it on this show a lot i
think i we say something funny i've
no lauren i'm going to a rot
i
why does my backward oh
secretary i feel like i have i
didn't know he's like why are you
a secretary i feel last longer here
bosses coming time i get into that
i get into that euphoric laughing here
yeah yeah where it gets very silly
yeah i yeah i agree my cheeks
are very sore right now
who loved that though
paul's been beating here bikes
gotta squeeze that sherman
um no i i love to look
i love to laugh loud and long
and clear that's cool you know i
love to laugh did i tell you
when i was in high school and
i said the rule how many years
after your freshman year this this this
was this was three years after my
freshman year right right and we
did um we did that illegal version
of mary poppins called the practice topic
manner before broadway show i did a
version of mary poppins i couldn't even
tell you if we paid the rights
we definitely did not because you had
to change so much yeah okay and
essentially this was the the movie script
adapted for the stage yeah i did
eleven
in the year after the disney aladdin
came out and it was not the
disney aladdin and everyone was bummed yeah
that sounds lame know to dare not
shut your eyes
um and we did so this i
played bert the chimney sweep yeah and
there's any he was called bert the
chimney sweep in this oh yeah no
every everything was the same here's the
thing was just a different title so
no one who owned the rights to
mary poppins would come as i was
they changed the title but at certain
point to cover a big wardrobe and
set change they wrote
on a screen and they showed a
scene from the movie that's crazy nuts
it was right it was not so
i'm playing by the chimney sweep we're
doing the uncle is an uncle albert
is the guy you're the lin manuel
miranda palsy well i was the dick
van dyke know lin manuel
the only version i choose to brag
fair enough fair enough i was yellow
them in this and we visit revisit
what was the meryl streep character
yeah and this was played by edwin
plays uncle albert who is related to
mary poppies and chatter he's also vaguely
magical but when he laughs he makes
you fly up into the ceiling and
so then everybody starts laughing they're flying
up in the ceiling and so the
how did you pull that off for
yawn rope but let me tell you
the kids the two kids
dhs and mary poppins run wires their
own big heavy cables which when they
got hauled into the air is crazy
in retrospect like i remember doing high
school shows i think and maybe a
college show where people were using the
fully fly system yeah and on wires
and that in retrospect is fucking crazy
i can't find that there are eighteen
year olds think about it now
yes like in charge of absolutely well
you drop into the air of peter
pan like the horrible peter pan that
goes awry it's like a school production
and on wires and it's so funny
it's fun it was on this american
life matter no but the kids basically
keep going up when they don't expect
it was so
well this would be so like mary
poppins would be standing there you know
very statuesque holding her umbrella and the
the raising of the umbrella was the
signal for her to fly away right
so there be like this jerky is
oh my try to like keep it
together right and act smooth but but
she's being hauled up on a rope
yeah it's not like a sophisticated system
yeah right so the the so the
two banks' children and mary poppins run
their cables and they're all the exact
same age
that's exactly right
and ah myself and uncle albert are
on
wooden platforms like just columns covered with
black duvet teen right to make it
appear as if we're just floating in
oh okay and so we had to
like keep we had to be sitting
like this with our legs and arms
out and so my stomach hurts so
bad after a show my god because
we
you had to stay upright to you
know convey the illusion and it was
really any company anywhere loud to everybody
oh my god people have to be
like how did you achieve that you
i thought you were actually why such
were flying
genuine power are you a witch vs
lucky you going oh he's sitting on
a thing and yet you felt the
responsibility like keep your legs totally pleased
it was when we were twenty two
are sick you are like just zero
huh yeah it's like look leaning on
the box
i love to laugh
huh
i did mary poppins and i was
an old banker oh sure huh it's
a good pairing the original one act
on and it's a fun one and
i want to see half of the
new one on a plane and i
feel so it's worth seeing something we're
seeing every other season taken
so every other scene
i was enjoying it but i just
got tired what haven't seen the old
ones that come over tonight will watch
the other half oh you got a
pizza what are you doing desperate yeah
you asked what we were doing like
you had time we were gonna i
didn't know i mentioned anything but i
was just wondering what everyone's up to
more like juicer why don't we do
so
i have to go on a trip
tomorrow i have to pack yeah lawrence
going on a trip to ah the
windiest cities gaga and she's not gonna
be back for a while but don't
worry there's not going to be any
interruption in our release strategy got an
hour upshot we will be erupting general
theory schedule
no interruption but plenty of eruption alright
we have to take a break we'll
be right back
hi we're back hi we're back we're
here we're so back yeah we're so
so bad i think so hopefully out
there all of your days have been
great um then you're right i just
want to say that molly dodd i
don't care about the nights i really
want your days i want your afternoon
to be perfect
i hope you have a great morning
and then the rest of the day
is like ooh it was just bored
i wish i hadn't mercer on my
mercer every day around my cheek stop
stop
if if the only cure for your
mercer on your choice mortimer was someone
like versa i don't know what it
is i didn't have any slice years
himmler sherries or cow bow you got
mercy but it's the only cure was
that you were delayed down and someone
were to stomp on you like grapes
on
wow oh shit i want to i'm
looking to see if the divot there
was like a divot in my literally
for the longest time oh no it's
finally like kind of filled in but
there's ah there's a little mark here
lol i'm like i see it like
a booster shot but that was like
a shallow you know like trampoline of
skin wow yeah
little mark what does his daddy's home
wow
why does mel gibson keep getting opportunities
she's you know i really think he's
worn out his welcome oh i think
he's paid as that supply
let's debate
didn't he say with sorry once good
enough for me um are we gonna
play feature yeah man yeah let's do
a feature do we know what is
yeah paul knows what it is yeah
go okay a three boys your age
oh yeah boy this we did way
back in hs reward oh yeah it's
an old goody that we all
i like to play cold gti with
yeah that old chestnut onto your hats
and glasses hold onto your turbans your
curly shoe
cuz it's time to do gti wish
by the way i saw aladdin the
other day for the first time since
oh the original cards are talking about
it just yet i saw him i
didn't know arby's i saw the cartoon
for the first time since seeing in
the theater on opening day and um
yeah there's some interesting stuff
cultural he um anyway go ahead
so the idea of this game is
one ah player will make a wish
to kind of wish you'd make with
the genie i wish i had a
million dollars and are we trying to
make it as bulletproof as possible or
are we just making a regulation seeing
well scott that i don't remember okay
well let's see how she
shakes out i think the idea is
you make it just like a regular
roll yeah and then the onus is
on the genie to subvert the wish
a monkey's paw that shit some rockies
paw that shit and may and come
up with the ironic granting of the
wish okay
i'm
i just shivered shivered and scott offered
me a headphone case that i draped
around her shoulder while paul was handing
me a jacket i don't have a
jacket i'm not gonna take off my
shirt
a gentleman is always code please take
it off ok magic mike this should
do i look like really cool now
yeah you actually look like robert palmer
yeah that's weird and you're gonna look
like his backup girl oh my
the idea is that the the genie
will then grant the wish but in
an ironic way that fucks over okay
let's try it you'll be a genie
poe great
are you upset you do the hardest
part for you under the refers to
all these you know i'll be the
jedi i'm gonna get e
i am the genie you have freed
me from the lab holy fuck hey
language nah sorry i just this is
the first thing here i've been in
this lab for thousand years old even
know what it means god you've been
in there for hours yeah yeah i
know what fuck beads okay so you
gotta be doing it you've ruined me
didn't take long anyway i will grant
you is show master one which i
shall grant to watch carefully okay i
know exactly what i want sounds familiar
i wish for the i wish so
that never in my life again
hold on do i have to
are you talking like yoda
go like who's gonna go which way
with somebody on this yeah or like
you know wait my turn at a
stop sign very well you wish is
granted yes you will never ever have
to wonder who will go first
street is it right yes yes because
you are confined to a future and
everyone will get out of your way
oh they don't don't at me people
in wheelchairs i know people would consider
it let me actually okay let me
go back oh so jesus right look
he's he's been in the lab for
oh okay oh right
one doesn't either pc culture and i'm
just realizing how shitty people could be
and that they wouldn't let you have
the right exactly okay so welcome and
also you won't be driving okay i
want it i want my wish yes
i want what will go down the
street and never have that thing we
were like oh who's going not have
to waste swaps and then also when
i'm in a car i don't want
to
go whose turn is it at the
stop sign and have to go
well your wish is granted today you'll
never have to worry about that again
because the other people will always just
walk right into you they won't give
a shit they're just gonna body check
you no matter how many times you
try to dq and get out of
the way they're just gonna plow right
through like you're not even there and
same thing with the cars you are
going to
try to make a terribly rather just
gonna go cut you right off every
single time but you'll never have to
wonder about it again we didn't want
to do that it's too late i
granted you wish oh judy so you
say when you leave yeah
okay alright so i'm a genie now
and you're the issue like the stupid
piece of garbage it's all dirty clean
it off a little bit gti whoa
are you really a genie hi yeah
i'm a genie i've been in here
for
three hours and i freed you yeah
man the last guy three hour eggs
i have the last guy like just
got out of like three hours ago
wow but you tried doing anything being
cramped for three hours i mean like
you wouldn't last three minutes respectfully i'm
not going to try that okay is
that your wish you want to try
it oh do i get a wish
oh
oh i just have that right okay
you get a wish i'll grant you
any wish think carefully about it though
because you may not like oh okay
i get it i get and i
ok i think i get this might
be monkeys paw you yeah sort of
yeah oh yeah yeah okay so what
do you wish for i was
wish for
he's doing i want to be doing
the considered by everyone to be the
handsomest man in the world ooh
well your wish is granted that i
said considered by everyone because that is
airtight because i have made everyone in
the world dead except for you oh
you are the most handsome person in
the world because everyone else is dead
enjoy your life but i finally feel
good about myself oh yeah alright yeah
i mean you're the gold standard i
feel like i did pretty okay you're
okay enjoy reading library books or whatever
it is you do oh i broke
my glasses oh that's a monkey's body
weight did you do that yeah broke
my guy broke your glass
chat on him that's just begging jamie
a beautiful scene
beautiful beautiful scene okay alright so i
get a wish here
oh man this cave is so brighton
lit up so well
not like your usual caves
it gets so much natural light in
here is so strange oh here's a
lamp rob me
don't really need more light rob me
i guess i could rub this lamp
oh my back ah what do you
want
oh and thanks
yeah he got upset
ah what am i gonna wish or
something what is huh yeah yeah yeah
good to read you my little metal
thing yeah oh yeah oh yeah
where are ye you rubbed the lamp
you can wish
why did you have to have that
written down the thing i remember omens
yeah you said one thing twice here
ye okay yeah right here yay quotation
marks so i knew to repeat it
just right here eat twice instead you
wrote here ye turns medical repeat ditto
marks whatever anyway alright well you gotta
wish you honor what i gotta go
back and back in my lamp and
build up some stuff to erupt
oh god ah honey gee i'd never
heard that oh wait no that wasn't
it
oh okay oh no your wish is
granted oh man i wasted a wish
why is my wish granted because not
only have you never heard that you've
never heard anything your ears are removed
and filled with putty in the past
are you hearing me right now
wait but i heard but that's the
present
forward yeah why heard it though and
then
i'm erasing your memory so you have
no memory of anything good happening or
bad or
easing my memory what do you have
like a and like neurolife
nothing good or bad or anything will
ever happen to again because you could
just kill me your love is okay
with me i'm gonna live with you
for the next eternity and the next
eternity i get someone else to rub
in this silky lamp haha right well
what are your interests
what do you do in the lamp
oh no i can't hear anything oh
gee hey you play my music as
loud as you want
ah
g g finally has some freedom is
loud you who was complaining before like
you think it's allowed to say what
lauren is now crying laughing
ah and that's how you play how
you play someone to g as a
place someone's genuine
this was a genie wish i wasn't
irish wilson has three cheers guys and
this make good good luck i'm good
because we need him what does that
movie i say make a good all
the time because of it but it
was that dude who was in brand
obama days no brown bunny
gallery vincent gallo buddy directed it or
whatever oh buffalo sixty slow so i
say wow make it quick he goes
in to span time with you no
no no is that felt fucking time
so he goes into a restaurant and
he asks for like a coffee and
he goes make a good make it
good wasn't it in brown bunny that
chloe seven gives a real blow job
yes i've never seen that
maybe lovedale do you think europe's probably
unless they get interrupted what would it
take over i can't even erupt it
i can't even imagine showing my penis
in a movie let alone can a
man at home i can't imagine anything
i can imagine it i don't like
it
i can't imagine doing i've had like
nude scene dreams oh really yeah yeah
yeah where you are supposed to give
a nude scene i have i have
to give one
hey i'm here to give you this
new tv
i know yeah charge
my gift to to you i have
dreams about like trying to find somewhere
to take a shit sure i needed
and then and then like people are
coming in and i've i've like new
dreams where i'm out of the house
or something or i'm somewhere in public
naked and yeah it's real and it's
what the weirdest part is
sometimes in the dream i start to
get used to it and then i
remember like oh no this along yeah
i think a lot of times i'm
wearing like a shirt that's just barely
long enough to cover my butt
in virginia
oof
i also have
wow enough
like so awkward cause you're like okay
bend over sit down that's embarrassing i
forgot pants dreams why do we have
em dreams what are they means what
do they mean like um you like
having dreams i do it's fun to
like him even if they're weird scary
dream but still like what what is
the trinity killer
hey who doesn't dream like what's like
the problem you have if you don't
drink i don't think anyone doesn't dream
oh really everyone has to dream even
dog dogs dream yeah i think that
dreams what are you gonna say i
don't know it's weird that dogs have
dreams it is weird because one of
the title we know first of all
i guess i don't
because they're like jerking around sometimes yeah
but generally imply that's the thing about
like we love them in anytime there's
a fact about nature i'm like how
do you know that where they go
oh a dog can do this this
and this and this like well how
do we know we've never talked to
a dog right how do we know
yeah we don't know maybe their bodies
just twitch when they sleep yeah maybe
they're dead at night and
and they come to lebron james just
say that's my choice like toys choice
yeah sick dogs are dead aren't you
right super dogs are dead when they're
out of your line of vision even
they're dead i'll probably see it i'm
gonna some way by toy sir i'm
way behind my pixar's yeah yeah i
loved the toy story franchise i'm sure
i'll see it just wondering
what i really was i don't know
if you care yeah but what i
don't know your story forest you brought
it up and then you're like oh
well he mentioned toy story storylines like
oh i wonder if you guys would
go see that theater i mean like
oh yeah i don't know if i'd
go see it in a theater yeah
i'd be fine to wait till it's
on tv yeah those movies are so
pretty no network tv i love
this emergency i love two and three
so much that i thirty three alchemy
was not which was three through the
one dollar yeah i didn't love that
one oh did you ever see that
video of the guy who tricked his
mom into thinking you know the part
in toy story three where they're in
the ah they're they're all about to
be
crushed by the thing they'll give me
incinerate yeah incinerated right so scary so
so ah he re edited it i'm
sure i've talked about this have i
not talked about on this show no
he reacted so it's like you see
that shot of them really scared and
the in the incinerator coming towards them
and then it fades out and the
credits start
and
and he shows to do with eddie
and he puts it back in the
dvd player and the mom watches it
because they've rented it or whatever and
the mom watches it the next day
and they're filming it and she's like
god what a weird story god it's
a good point why would it end
like that so they're all just dead
oh my god he's so funny
and she's just all invested yes she's
just confusing going what a weird ending
what so all the toys die
and then they finally like springing out
of like no we read there's way
more to the movies they get she's
like why did you do that kind
of frank is this it's so funny
it's like one of the greatest breaks
that's tremendous i would see that it's
really good guys we gotta go we
gotta go it has to end sometimes
we gotta ended lauren you go
gotta go to you you wanna play
i'm gonna go we're gonna miss you
am i miss you guy i mean
you're very solicitous established you're not to
listeners we're all going to hear each
other next week but we're not going
to see each other for like three
years you're traveling that's why
i don't think so no anymore oh
yeah okay well we'll go we'll get
together we'll record another episode around this
month but it's next month and i'm
trying out are all get together what
we have to record we have to
record so yeah here we'll get together
then listen this is how friendships are
done in modern times is there is
worse we recorded by guests together yes
we we would never see each other
if we didn't record a pipe quickly
why would we why would we have
why would we i don't like you
guys and
that's it alright it's raw
weird praying weird like alright we'll see
it i love oh my
uh