yeah
ah yeah
through
oh well you said you're gonna go
so
the entire time do it again okay
ready fuck it we'll do alive so
nah that's something
understood
ah cuts up i was gonna do
it i thought it was fun so
yeah only it is fun start on
that's why i wanted to do it
oh right sorry go ahead
wow
not to understand
i gotta get it on
oh i can't believe you didn't let
him do so i just read you
let me have anything it was so
to have anything it sounded so fun
to do is many have you want
to do it so bad began any
have anything that was
tunnel joe is a quick patented dental
drum corp hundred robot isn't it weird
okay i got it not to get
all political but you know i do
it how every president every single president
has it except for the
no but every president like they're a
million people doing impressions of the president
and and this one it's he's so
repulsive that people can't even bring themselves
to do impression you know like yeah
there's like gross like when george w
bush as much of a monsters he
was everyone out there was out there
gone you know what is what did
he do not not gonna do
do it but george w bush what
did he do he was like the
earth is flat
oh but it's not even fun to
do a trump impression anyway welcome to
the show and think about it
ah um i you're you're turning off
fifty percent of the audience right now
way you're no way i'd be shocked
if anyone who voted for trump follows
this pot know i think they do
i just think that that people who
vote they exaggerate exaggerate like fifty percent
of the country love it it's my
favorite thing would be will threaten you
like
at that like mm oh okay i
mean you're gonna lose your audience have
you um watched when they see us
on netflix yes sounds like you're so
late
you're so lame this is not a
documentary it's docu drama
i suppose the central park five yeah
right and i've i've watched one and
a half episodes yeah whatever parts but
we always so watched it all in
one day it's like brutal i start
watching a show buying dash what they
did to the person oh my god
no just the first part it's so
so i mean of course i know
the story but not that well but
watching it and then seeing like the
way in which these people clued into
this but then the detectives also know
they didn't do it within their core
coercing them and also straight up just
like lying to make it seem like
it's true yeah
it is so horrible i can't even
imagine that's like everyone's worst nightmare to
be falsely accused of a crime did
you use to have a lot of
worries about going to prison eventually i
used to like being in the army
and going to prison those were my
two biggest because i think that the
movies first of all in the eighties
there were a ton of movies where
people went to boot camp
but didn't want to be there yeah
so i was always thinking about that
like being in boot camp and having
a drill sergeant yelling emi but also
there's a ton of movies where like
people go to prison for whatever reason
yeah and so i just grew up
think i think i'm at a point
where i don't think i'm going to
prison in my life yeah but it
could be an accident it could yeah
that's the thing it could be some
weird accident where i'm just like wow
l going to prison for three years
goodbye i saw scary watching oz when
it was first on hbo and i
watched i think like a good three
seasons of it before i realized it
was pointless i don't like well what
why am i watching this this is
not fun it's not entertaining to me
did we talk about all the sun
raised by tv but what is the
permit is someone who goes
joel who's falsely accused him falsely no
no ones falsely accused this example show
about a bunch of people in prison
oh but but may sound familiar it
kinda goes through the eyes it a
little tang it literally is google itself
sir the p o v character though
is like the dude from wayne's world
who
um yeah when
who goes to prison looks like ernest
goes to jail nobody he's like he's
in there for a drunk driving facts
oh okay so okay so then then
he has ah scary oscar winner ah
j k simmons j k simmons like
tattoos his name on his ass or
something i think a swampy area
neonazi yeah he's terrifying and that's the
first time i ever saw him do
that eminem is scary
you should give that role up that's
my opinion was that they use little
marshall mathers you get em and i
wasn't john goodman the first yellow eminent
baby but i think if you win
an oscar the meme goes to somebody
else like let's spread the wealth a
little bit do you remember paul back
in the nineties when i started comedy
and you'd been doing it for a
long time um
grew up to be born but there
there was there was there was talk
between us ah our our group of
friends and one of our friends had
supposedly been offered the the role of
an m and m yes andy was
a big thing of like are they
going to sell out and yeah do
it oh what a lame first
like dev to judge them for that
but i mean i remember an ama
all day every day oh i know
i will try this one for a
week but yeah
i don't ask the freedom challenge ah
we're talking about brand clothing
right then i remember at the time
i didn't know anything about comedy or
whatever and so it was like oh
is that not oh okay yeah i
get i mean i don't know billy
west is the other one of the
other men emerson used to be you
know chuck a dark chocolate peanut butter
crispy it was junk jon lovitz now
it's billy west john goodman was the
thing node shaky synonym simmons
nz sing wow all these great intimate
million increase summary case sentiments j k
cinnamon he should have his own company
he should be the simien eminem
semi-matte mini mini mini mini mini mini
mini one why don't they have a
cinnamon them in them that sounds good
i feel like cinnamon yeah that should
be the truth do you like it
in the winter exclusively or do you
like it all year long only in
the winter can i tell you something
man make a confession again this is
his confession can't go
question like the peanut butter m and
m's better than reese's pieces can you
say oh true peanut butter imams are
top tier ii phone our lawyer mall
candy that goes in your hand now
it goes peanut butter goes in your
it goes cafe butter and can feto
my palm of your hand because i
need all candy goes oh no it
means no matter what you do unless
you're like warming up your floor jumping
into your hand and then you melts
in your mouth peanut butter eminem you
really want an m and m's deal
here's what i wanna do i want
to write them right now please okay
peanut butter top i like you better
tell you you're ranking m and m
flavors and they or candies that fit
reasons your east or she's describing her
outfit for when she beat a better
time to shop the crispy um peanut
because peanut butter peanut um eminem's um
um
i mean i so i don't know
what you're doing because you mentioned reese's
pieces not seconds ago it goes are
you racking ministers ranking candy seminars for
now just to see that you want
a candy peanut is a tyson m
you up i'm yeah she's an actress
she's talking about she mentioned reese's pieces
she's uncles uncles yeah she's neh
ever been talking about reese's pieces she
mentioned it she mentioned it she's clearly
talking me a second hey until i'm
fucking so thank you and only fight
me if you disagree with my ranking
now it goes peanut butter m and
m peanut m and m
crispy eminem crispy levine m and m
like chicken
shh yeah reddit wait go back peanut
butter
peanut pretzel crispy i'm like the principle
milk wait till she's finished millwork dark
chocolate mint almond carmel raspberry that they
have that many m and m's even
have coconuts not listed on the wiki
also nut
here's his marinca and him
it goes peanut
oh is the number one sorry no
no no no no sooner sooner it
goes peanut butter number walk that i
i'll put a number one dog fog
bad food and like i think i'm
gonna give it can be interfaced barclay
goals people use so much fun imitating
him chicken mclellan lie
goes ah peanut butter peanut butter is
number one and then we come down
a number two which is a dark
and milk chocolate dark and milk chocolate
that's right it's a combo it's kumble
okay by the law then it goes
mako
the mean it meant his number three
for you yeah you're following very good
than it goes plain plain plains kind
of the best though in a weird
way i almost put at the top
it's reliable because plane is what plane
is like chocolate and then what's inside
it's just chocolate they didn't say this
question then i don't know then
it goes omen then it goes let's
see mars is one damn ximenes should
know it's the whole planet they'll listen
to at home you've heard my ranking
i actually want to move plane from
like seventh to first
why did a dramatic upset plane is
bomb i don't care enough about candy
to know what any case let's just
go is eminem's is a plane eminem
i just know i try to okay
but then what's inside but the outside
shooting outside to catch a show i
an order sound equipment
wait and see through the booth he's
like this is a recording i need
to get some new equipment this is
like he's on brand right now
this is scott what's inside the piano
i know he's not you and then
then the essay is a chocolate what
the fuck do you know outside of
ross here's my adheres more questions because
your candy dandy non canny bitch
i don't have one but if you
don't have one you live or united
fucking twelve anymore
what's your favorite movie comic books rib-eye
yeah you bony and weirdo what's your
favorite candy paul ma no one's ever
asked me this before my favorite candy
what's you favorite chocolate candy today you
know what's how andy probably reese's cups
are my family oh yeah have you
ever had a big cup
yeah have you ever had a christmas
tree oh christmas tree like those oh
i love this is all peanut butter
like i don't like the christmas music
christmas or the easter ones those are
the best it's one day i'm saying
it's mission because she oh she or
the shape of an egg which basically
suppose just peanut butter inside right it's
like opening up a jar of peanut
butter and just you don't know cycle
are you happy over here
and spread it on my penis presenter
butt cheeks and open mind and call
the doors
you guys doing show are you further
up for this show okay to down
and that's me trying to explain to
candies this alien oh yeah call me
a moron daily basis he got the
concept of candy right away how are
you
but here's my question about m and
m's the candy shell is that chocolate
too whereas yes now if i hope
know it's just sugar candy sugar it's
like sugar it's a crispy short the
christian church but but but if i
were to take all the chocolate out
yes would there be chocolate around the
outside of the can never mind i
have a quality review scoop it out
of
an imminent no but i'm saying if
like so white with color on it
and then in then you haven't chuckling
side but i went by the way
i went to hershey pennsylvania because i
was fascinated with lamppost with the chocolate
drop on it
i that's how much i love candy
as a kid i thought about it
all day long what you're saying we're
mature no i'm just saying that it
it has no bearing on my life
anyway you like a deck all day
i dream about candy okay if i
said those let's see if we're gonna
have a candy bar for you will
you diagnose data if we're gonna have
a candy party everyone got
a favorite what would you want there
alright can we first talk about the
candy party
yeah what's it what happened to the
candy co but here's what it is
it's a party or like it's at
your house at my house yeah you
got a lot of space anyone travel
jesus there's no pleasing this guy i
find my houses but it's just a
cleanup around i'll take care of it
alright or somebody around the border of
your also
so thinking about like what point do
i want to go to bed are
people still going to be there to
datetime thing i mean like i'm shooting
for
you should take a nap around three
okay good from one to three freak
so there's a beautiful handmade shelf that
lines the perimeter of the room made
for the party made for the party
i'm going to it's roots the width
of a candy
the width of a candy candy bar
this fall rapidly it's the width of
the whoever has the biggest category so
it's it's five to contact every guest
just like who has the biggest candidates
probably the width of charleston chew or
the toblerone you get at the airport
or it has to be at least
why does it reese's peanut butter cup
cause that's gonna come up a lot
oh so every
guest fills out a form on google
doc and we find out what everyone's
favorite is it's shareable and we all
can see it before the party no
blown i'll do shit on the slack
it's a google poll so you can't
see whatever went okay they filled out
their own survey and then around the
border of the room is each candy
bar with a person's name in front
of it
abandon see what everyone's favorite weight but
they can only eat that or you
know what they want you eat theirs
to see what it feels like to
be them there's only one fill out
a form that says what it feels
like is it like a white elephant
where you all trade candy trying to
get on the train rolls
first oh yes oh oh no i'm
going to try the molokai but we
don't know what he likes because he
wouldn't say so what would it be
if it was at that party too
grown up to say what agency i'm
not i'm trying to think of a
candy like okay i i i i
went to seven eleven you were like
i wanna have a hankering for some
candy or would you pick
very if it's very well put i
probably wouldn't say i have a weird
answer is gonna be like a hot
dog in a gun
yeah
can you really order that like i
know they sell condoms and hot dogs
acting like he doesn't know if you
were to go to seven eleven and
say do you mind okay i'm gonna
buy this package of condoms i'm gonna
buy this hot dog do you mind
putting a condom on a hot dog
i honest what they do it what
i what i would do in that
situation yeah i would put a comment
on the hotdog you're saying walk i'd
walk up
with them was the kind of empathic
right say so they could scan it
you know the
like either grocery store i'm buying both
of them but show them there's a
condom ah yes i was not referencing
i mean they'd see it only see
that's the freedom challenge i honestly hear
every three
oh please do this do not steal
either item you do not say oh
we need a picture of that and
when you picture the receipt thanks and
we need video but we need both
we we need both we need so
we need photos video
we need someone edited together with musician
i wanted scored not you know copyright
music i want you to hire a
composer sand your condom and autocracies to
collin anderson care of your wolf and
then when we along with most card
throw the postcard or two yeah but
i want to see video of people
trying to get the clerk to put
the condom on the hot dog oh
don't bother the yeah this was still
include the clerk this isn't weirdness to
just put it in front of them
don't ask like in the heart of
it the clerk might even yell at
our our listener for doing oh yeah
like oh oh and if you're listening
in england clark thank you is called
a clarke slater announcer clark okay fuckin
weird and i know scott's been trying
to get away from the answer but
what's your favorite
handy okay okay it used to be
when i was young i would sit
there and dream about candy and i
think i told you the story of
wanting to buy a package of chocolate
chips and dumping it into a tub
of whipped cream and then i was
like i know that you are thinking
about this all day i never thought
about it that good why didn't you
do it why did i had this
dream of of writing or driving my
bike to
the grocery store doing this or sailing
but i'd only and it was like
the snack like because sometimes i would
have a peanut butter and chocolate chip
sandwich for lunch and that was great
i used to put peanut butter i
used to put chocolate chips in peanut
butter nbn router yeah i would just
put it around why would do i
enter a jar and then spoon it
out yeah oh so but um i
used to like three musketeers
a lot when was everyone i was
explains aw yeah yeah i think when
i when i was when i was
a little milky way was i remember
discovering milky way and three musketeers because
i was always like a snickers peanut
butter cup kind of kid and then
i was like whoa there's a whole
new world out there i didn't really
like whiskey tears didn't like nuts until
maybe recently so many other you love
not zero
as begging i love him in my
mouth i love these nuts
okay that's nice
do you know de
snoop dogg said that did he not
dray these bn to it i don't
actually know that fact ryan yes he
doesn't know either well why we're asking
ryan he's behind glad he was the
owner last time who said dees nuts
don't please oak on the album and
it was snoop and says snoop says
it yes snoop says thank you very
much i was right about that at
least
um and i was like d's nuts
i have i've been trying to shrug
emoji i will say i ordered i
ordered racist pieces at a movie recently
and i put it in the popcorn
oh i don't like that one
and that was i don't know about
people do that i know that but
that's so nineties
when coupe was born yeah isn't it
nice to put your dump your candy
fucks into the popcorn it feels like
it's so what's wrong with it though
you know i used creek you know
what i used to really like is
ordering an extra nacho cheese cup from
the movies and then dipping my popcorn
into that oh wow that makes
a little more sense to like cheesy
popcorn what's wrong with cheesy popcorn now
they sell it for reals i like
that barf gucci's are gucci's i like
um a sweet and savory combo but
but popcorn is not the the the
one for me yeah like to to
mix it with chocolate does not doesn't
do it for i went to universal
studios
the citywalk for fun for fun actually
chloe zhao who haven't i because we
lived over sort of by there and
and a nice listener gave her an
amc card where we would get into
movies for free
that's a nice listener yeah we will
we would go there a lot just
his presence to to to drive there
um you could park there for five
dollars if you went to see a
movie and so we would go there
a lot and casey wilson would always
make tickets cheaper for cool i mean
she's a child we would
we would always send a picture to
casey wilson of cool up having fun
at universal citywalk in case you'd be
like you have to stop going there
wait why would you sit in her
because she made you understand why anyone
would go to universal citywalk but okay
so i went to universal citywalk and
they have a store called popcorn propolis
right yeah where
you get gift doctor you get gift
packages of popcorn right and they're like
you can what they're they're like you
know large large like like can gift
wrap tins of popcorn and stuff like
that and so i bought one for
a relative for for a christmas thing
my dream right and it's a decker
narrative like popcorn tin or whatever they
would not let me into the movie
with it like because they're like no
outside food i'm like this is a
decorative this is a christmas yeah yeah
obviously no outside food you fat pig
yeah
you're gonna just gigantic um the um
outside food thing i was recently told
was ah just their preference but they
can't really enforce it really just vain
they tried to enforce it on me
and i had to go throw it
away and it was an expensive yeah
i like lengths didn't have a popcorn
check
do yeah
chef girl
and then at the end you're the
only box i finished that kinda chicken
was right there well we don't know
if that's yours
you could be anybody walking into the
street
ah walking in on the street walk
into my lmao you don't eat candy
well when you say you put up
and buy it i don't know i
don't i like it but i just
have never bought it what what like
i don't think to buy it i
don't buy ever market or ersten when
you market everyone's
oh you know candy aisle the shoe
store i'll have a starburst every once
in a while and like a doctor's
office when i go to the grocery
i go to the candy aisle and
look for my candy for like my
coworker my coworker korean has like a
jar of candy and if i ever
go into her office and sit on
the couch i'll occasionally get a camp
i'm
i can't even remember what candy is
in there because maybe she rotates it
or something that is good can i
want to have a candy jar she's
so buy one my dear you're old
enough now i can truly can do
to get permission no we can't have
candy in the house on a regular
basis because we will follow yeah that's
the thing i try not to have
a lot of it because i will
just eat it
all night like it's crazy yeah but
um like around halloween or christmas i'm
like fucking all bets are off and
i can buy a bag of candy
oh you know what i do like
my my sister-in-law makes really good um
candi christmas i'm trying to remember what
it tastes like
like it's really it's it's really really
good really good candy trimer what it
tastes like yeah what is it what
is this bruce
what does it look like what kind
of candies it's like fruity it's mould
notes in a mole rudy is a
ground i'm just trying to remember if
it's peanut butter or what what flavor
it is but like come on you're
trying to remember if it's peanut butter
i can't remember your brain your brain
is dumb because my brain doesn't remember
candy exclusively
a my wife's family yeah
oh hey these relatives in west virginia
one of her aunts makes this candy
that they calls they call it sea
foam candy but it's not sea foam
at all has nothing to do with
stuff like salt water taffy or anything
right it's actually like a cream candy
like a it's very hard to describe
you know that textures ice water it's
like the texture is your butter
or mints know it's like a thing
that occasionally you find them at a
restaurant or something like oh yes it's
a very specific way around butter candy
yes cylindrical mint yes it's like a
hard cable when you bite into it
it's like it becomes very soft and
melt in your mouth oh is that
consistency like dees nuts
they're really hard at first himself i
noticed it was free
but it's ok but maybe my not
so heartbreaking to see the accident site
and they look at soft
if someone said that
i love your amazing mutton that's so
my doctor but don't you mean your
day think i know i had i
had a problem like that one time
i had to go to the doctor
oh really oh because here's the thing
in that sack sometimes this stuff can
get twisted around yes thank you don't
know what's going on yes
oh i finally have testicular cancer yeah
and then you go to the doctor
and the dog's like no no here
just let me untie these you go
on different you go on typical routine
oh yeah i think that happen to
me once tess recycling it's very scary
yeah very sincere nachos hurt your nuts
those hurt yeah one of them is
very hard and solid yeah oh
chelsea oh no i'm pretty sure this
happen to me in my twenties because
this is ringing a bell yeah me
too yeah weird food yet that is
fascinating well what am i going to
remember every ohi everything that happens to
my nuts
i don't know i remember like i
feel like eighty percent of the things
that happened on pypy i feel like
you've been like i think that happened
to me once is weird because i
think i know everything that's happened to
my vagina and he came with if
a peanut butter taste yeah this guy's
crazy
you remember everything that's happened to your
vagina in terms of like medical issues
yeah i'm gonna know if someone brings
them ago yeah that's happened to me
yeah check but then you're going i
think maybe my knuckle twisted and got
so hard i had to come back
oh crazy yeast infection check yeah been
there done that got the t-shirt i
well look i was thinking about this
this morning i can't remember ever i
was trying to remember people that i
did that i was in theater with
house trying to remember like i'm getting
people and i was like love it
i guess this is thirty
years ago i can't remember this yeah
i think it's good that to me
has always been great because i think
like my whole life i i feel
like i was very aware i can
remember ever whenever yet i'd go we
met one time and it was right
here when then i'd be like you
know always if someone forgot me i
remember i now have no idea who
those people are that's my i'm and
i'm happy for it
i did a documentary on my parents
and how they met a few years
back oh yeah and i remember asking
my father about like other women he
dated and he couldn't remember their names
and i was i remember going like
this you can't remember their names boy
sucks to get old i don't think
i could remember the names of certain
i'll learn the names of people that
i dated and why there are there
are people when i think about high
school and i mean i think about
like doing the shows in high school
there are people that i can see
and i in my mind i can
remember like vivid exchanges with them and
times that we had camera their names
but then everyone somehow it'll pop in
my head like as we were just
talking about it i was like i'm
not gonna remember people's names like brad
eberly
like i brought my he'd just popped
in my head i was like oh
yeah but it's like it's like i
don't like when people are very presumptuous
about you remembering them i find that
really rude like yeah like we met
like i hate i vote and seven
that i guess when i go up
to someone and go hey scott ackerman
they go i know it's like well
damn i'm trying to save you
yeah i've always prefer someone to reintroduce
themselves even if i know yeah but
if i'm like pretty sure i know
that guy's name isn't if he goes
digital i'm like thank you yeah yeah
now there's no part of me that's
wondering or better yet to go i'm
saying so we met doing this and
i'm like thank god i used to
be insulted by that when i still
remembered everyone's name and face right now
yeah if so
nobody doesn't remember me it's fucking fire
yeah yeah i don't take it personally
yeah paul f tompkins who could forget
you you'd be surprised ah emmy academy
ah poor paul for paul i ain't
me if they had facial recognition software
that you could install into your eyes
would you
no why
i don't want to have something in
my eyeball you have contacts don't you
what if it feels like we're installing
it into my ah no i'm saying
like if you had noodles good when
it feels great yeah it feels like
a massage all day i want it
like like a neck and neckline was
too that's kevin you know bats paul
that is scott i'm like i know
these people but if it was because
he
i was like black mirror now it's
if it was like black mirror where
you look at someone suddenly like ca
and came under stats came up yeah
it's like you met doing this yeah
yeah that'd be kind of cool i
guess but but but everyone wouldn't they
always be like blinking weirdly every time
you met anyone what if you made
it so
it's not like that oh yeah no
know i feel like you need to
blink to dismiss staying on that likelier
episode where they are like having memories
in the guy i love that sort
of a playback on tv yeah so
tom collins in it oh really i
believe so i don't oh i don't
know that i know what he looks
like i mean mature nice guy tatiana
sky wife nice guy um i don't
no but i feel like everyone always
glosses over how much people will just
be like twitching like you know some
other meat with rice for sure you
know like a it all works perfectly
other than the one person who has
the monkeys paw or whatever oh in
the episode it's like their eyes like
glaze over right like a like a
it's like a film comes over their
eyes when they're well
okay well that's what happens in the
mcallister episode yeah because i were you
thinking of my guess they reuse that
technology what technology do you wish that
they would invent that has not been
invented teleportation yeah yes that's my main
when would you trust it though i
do it in a second like well
this is the question i
had about self-driving cars with my parents
where i was very surprised i said
to them like i don't know like
trusting the self-driving cars my mom mom's
like it would be so our lives
would be so much easier the fact
that i if there's something wrong and
i have to go to the hospital
like i have to get your father
to drive me he doesn't have a
license
you know all you know they're just
like if i could just get into
a car program it and it drives
me there he would be in it
i would love it so on there
are probably fewer accidents for the most
part because yeah because yeah my concern
about it is it has we have
to do it all at once well
yeah everyone everyone has to coach into
the tv thing that no on just
hold on a second scott
yeah this is what you do this
one room or you wonder oh you
wonder oh he wonders about oh he
wonders about things now i wonder what
kind of candy bars but doesn't know
because i remember
i feel like it has to go
to all self-driving cars yes you probably
bored with teleportation i feel the same
way about lasik words like i'll let
it go for a while before yeah
yeah you don't want to wait for
some people no no no i would
not i'm not going to be early
to teleport to the first guy who's
going to do tell but okay the
first guy whatever but the first person
who pays for it ooh
i can't imagine being that but they'll
probably example way into nothingness i remember
seeming well it's not even possible is
a teleportation possible while your particles have
to become little and then they get
sent through a tube but i wonder
okay so if you if you did
it okay stay male your articles say
you're thinking about teleportation in the way
of they they dissemble your particles and
then reassemble them somewhere else right instantaneous
mostly but what if they did it
like a fold in time where it's
like you don't dissemble you just step
through like a doorway that there are
different dimensions ones happening right now ah
jimmy and other earths another language like
another dimension another dimension the dimension do
you mean like multiple realities or i
mean yes the multiverse
and that you could go to another
reality and be in like japan right
now no
sucks i also do not believe in
that i like it i think it's
pretty like you think there's another lauren
who's know i guess i just think
it's cool to think about another dimension
maybe with not another me but another
version of the world without you in
that time yeah how could you even
imagine we said well i mean a
lot of them
that's the weird part about anytime you
see science fiction with you know multiverse
kind of things is everyone's in everyone
has a slight change like we only
wear button downs i ever go che
yeah but it's really like most of
the dimensions wouldn't even have you in
it yeah they'd be like bugs like
ruling the world or something well also
just like your parents would not have
had sex
ks at that particular time
how do they have sex laura
but you know what i mean like
the only reason that you are who
you are is because they had sex
at that rate one instant you would
have been a total different person isn't
that cool any other time i think
but there would be more blimps yeah
that's true but i'm saying to stop
lamps me just stop you just was
like female blimps like a month ago
you shouldn't let your cancelled blimps cancelled
i know what is your what is
your issue there are ways to bare
a waste of all hot air
they are diverting resources that we desperately
need for balloon when have you ever
seen a blimp that made sense or
knew needed the blood the goodyear blimp
goes by to go okay good yeah
something about good year then i go
what is that anyway tires or something
well isn't it even know the blimp
doesn't even tell me enough it's a
huge advertisement they could put hay
hey guys a good year is it's
tires you actually need them for your
car something like or maybe good use
on even tire since like gas something
i don't even know that would be
great if it was on that readout
on that screen hey guess what good
year is it's tires you need the
radius strange that people don't you know
i mean when the goodyear blimp was
invented everyone knew what good year was
because they were used to putting on
their own tires
and now people oil tar butlers so
am i don't why do i need
to know about goodyear tires if i'm
going to get new tires do i
go to a tire shop and go
to show this is my point store
this is my point is we used
to put that we used to go
by the tires i'm still trying to
take them home and put them on
ourselves and you are born in coop
was a star of the sky
but you but i'm saying you you
go to a store and you don't
care and someone points out attire yeah
whatever whatever and you don't care what
brand it is or whatever or they
don't that's the point that's my point
that's why i need good year so
i say i need a good year
tire i seen the blimp i saw
a lamp over the football game i
like blimps and
i wanna go ride in one because
i think it would be terrifying why
i hear the hot air balloon is
terrifying oh hot air balloon is fucked
up how did they land the blimp
i mean the blimp this just handed
down yeah they just said it to
anyone deflates yeah they broke a hole
in it and because
i think it's the same way they
land any other aircrafts like they have
to they make a gentleman foolish is
that well a big blimp running down
and runway and then taking off has
anyone ever seen a bland to take
off i don't think it runs other
i think it's i think just really
low rates loud airing and then it's
up so
can even go anywhere why do we
have this it goes all over the
place alright i don't like our i
love it aren't blimps and durables in
general weren't they going to be an
alternative method of travel or something that
that somehow got abandoned and is actually
what they were gonna just comical put
people up in the blimp part and
have
like you could feel like a hundred
fifty people in there in that it's
like she's like oh it's like more
economical than a subway or whatever but
for some reason we never itched all
right we have to take oh okay
alright you this you don't want to
listen we're taking a break
i was saying it's more economical girls
were taking a break no i'm intrigued
to know no no not oh alright
let a woman do some brave going
on your fucking idea about a blimp
vs the subway know they thought it
was more economical to take a blimp
than a subway no it's not better
it's better for zone is better for
our environment
let's go to break yeah i don't
know no no no no you can't
you can't just go to break whenever
things don't go your way
when do you want to take a
break now hold on now everyone talking
about you and your turn remember fuckin
mitt romney or the let's go to
ben bates now you've searched away what
he's going to break p he got
his chest talk he got his chance
like you gave him a lot it's
one cedric miles you're talking over her
break oh okay yeah you gave him
this is
all break talk by the way re
talk alright we'll be right back no
we'll be right back
ah where back oh jolly i like
i like glimpse i would go oh
dalai you know you should go on
a blimp and stay there
i didn't mean i pray you don't
mean that i i heard some terrifying
story of someone going up in a
hot air balloon and in them like
being blown to the middle of noise
yeah it just sounds toronto here's the
thing about the hot air balloon is
that it's you and maybe somebody else
and
then that guy yeah that was like
heat homes proposal story which he's told
on various pono kurt braunohler oh they
both did it p are you serious
he proposed a hot air balloon and
the guy was there or am i
mixing it up no maybe it did
and i don't know i heard that
curt story was they went up in
a hot air balloon but he didn't
realize that his
soon to be fiance lauren had a
terrible fear of heights oh yeah impede
pete stories that they went up and
then the guy was just standing there
when he proposed but didn't even think
about that like there's yeah you know
that's the thing how did ah did
pete think that guy was gonna go
overboard so i don't know i'll just
hang over the side while you do
your business i don't know
just bang from this road yeah and
he was like cool see in five
minutes paul how did you propose i
know i've heard the story i proposed
ah to janie um at the spot
where she first took me to sullivan's
island right and it was an it
was an a pa
fucking lot of this place called the
sand dunes club and my i've talked
about this in my standup my whole
plan was um to like walk out
to the beach it was around christmas
time walk out to the beach and
you know and jingle bells jingle jamba
by mess and then how does that
do the walk onto the beach i
would what what does it have to
do with that was chris
oh
don't hit me
i made a fist okay yeah i
was gonna just about i'm very nocturne
jaw i'm a very touchy feely person
because lords next to me i was
gonna like tap you on the knee
and many it's my feeling then i
realised i'm not gonna make sixty nine
where she is she's wearing holey jeans
because it's a fashions of the damn
wing needless pants yeah whoops
spence okay keep going there so close
to being shorts so um because the
first time she took me to sullivan's
island it was fourth of july weekend
we parked to this place we walked
out to the beach it was like
a beautiful moonlit evening and i was
like i'm going to recreate that except
this time
time it was christmas and i forgot
that there's no moon if so it's
just pitch black and it's freezing oh
and so we walked back and i
did my whole speech and everything and
not get switched to do was it
from a play or was it it
was the identity i did the first
for the way you want me on
that wall speech from a few minutes
she was crying she was crying um
i said you can't handle the truth
will you marry me
um i i ah brought the ring
out of my pocket and she burst
into tears like she had no idea
at the prospect she had no at
prosecuting marijuana then i talked her into
it i was like here's the pros
and
you bought a long list yeah she
she i do agree the pros outweigh
the cons lot of cons but there
was one more pro that's right it
was a real squeaker
sweet um and how long until you
got married was seven months or so
how long it was almost a year
because we we knew we wanted to
get married in south carolina but there's
a very narrow window of time when
you can do that where the weather
isn't either dangerous or miserable and so
we had to wait
wait like you know another we will
be doing in the springtime so we'd
wait a year yeah biggest regret of
my life that i didn't make it
to that wedding i knew where where
was i we talked about this recently
i looked it up i yeah i
there there was there was some there
was some commitment that i yeah like
with the comedy bang doing television yeah
something like
lame i know and this is before
we were friends i know once i
wasn't even invited you weren't born in
my friendship yeah my fridge and lord
i know you want to be at
our wedding but i wanted to but
i wasn't bringing
um sweet sweet sweet sweet sweet we've
we've talked many times about not like
a renewal of vowels per se club
keeps bringing it up vowel vowels and
vowels and i live like that
huh i'd like to buy any pat
already like to buy and renewal of
my vows vow i'd like to renew
of alpen
like wants to do it but you're
like no no no well i think
i think
i think that
she she because we have a lot
of friends who are not able to
be there or we weren't friends with
them yet i just think she wants
me to express my love for her
in front of people again yeah because
i don't see it that way
yeah your very own love that's why
i would like to have some kind
of things i'm gonna celebration here i'm
serious alright i know you're in love
with her okay i want to make
it clear when i know you only
made the joke because i felt like
it was revere enough that you are
um but yeah i think well i
mean sometimes we have friends who like
they constantly have
parties and i think they're always looking
for an excuse our party i'm already
so you know what i mean where
it's like any life thing that happens
is like let's have a big party
and i'm like oh you guys just
like having parties what i think cool
up just just wants that like expression
of place why did you get married
how many years ago ah it'll be
eleven in september i think that's fair
what was the date again september thirteenth
um well i think you that's enough
time where it makes sense to do
a renewal of vows it's not like
it was only maybe twenty twenty
where ours is but you know when
you and i think about this but
here's my oh hold on are you
going to do it well wait as
a third to say ah we talk
about it because there are so many
people that are in our lives now
that we're not when we got married
yeah and it will be lovely to
have some kind of celebration with those
people because they're important to our lives
here's what i think about
this now you go scott for you
specific yes domo don't say it to
me don't say twenty because you'll regret
that do it if it won't because
something's come up on the twentieth year
i'm canadian i'm saying there was some
reason why that's why like we did
a big nice like the year on
our ninth year when i was in
charge of our
our whatever we were going to do
because we've been alternating disease control each
year yes yeah like i submit the
peaceful transition of power
i know last year but but i
did a big special thing even though
it was nine because it was just
did a sort of show your first
law who will know we went to
hey i said let's dress up and
so i was wearing a tuxedo and
she was wearing like a big fancy
gown big fancy gown and then we
went to the skirt yeah we went
to the ah train station where we
got married that we started there and
then we went to olvera street and
had ah a nice mexican lunch in
our tuck
ks and and everything oh this is
a datetime datetime yeah this is this
is good this is earned you know
years of stuff i think and then
we went to the opera which has
over my years oh that was two
years ago two years ago so that
was pretty big hobby i mean it
wasn't his god er gu na and
you paid the guy to do that
it's a male in the middle of
the show whenever it was like oh
and that's an english um alleged so
where were you going where you're going
to say anything else about renewing the
vows i don't know i think it's
nice but i'm saying i don't really
necessarily have a feeling about it myself
i just got married so i don't
really have an opinion oh congratulations things
by yesterday
bray but i think that if ah
one person really wants it it's a
very nice thing to did mike proposed
to you did you propose to mike
i proposed that's right and i know
where yeah but don't say i don't
have one i don't really i don't
but i don't know the proposal story
i don't think it really was um
well ah what ah we had been
saying we talked about that i would
do it so it be like we'd
like i didn't want him to propose
to me yeah okay so sisters are
doing it for the ball because it's
a masculinity wow
to get down on the id i
mean that's why i wouldn't do it
without getting too into my personal life
yeah i just felt that's not what
this show is about well
no i could draw a line some
lie no i felt that for mu-mimo
my pool i want to be the
mumps you know the person who decided
when it would happen because yes he
was ready for whenever i said yes
so yeah oh that's yeah okay so
i was thirsty very thirsty your thirst
trap
i'm a thirst trap and i trapped
the search your mother but so i
knew i was gonna do it um
well i thought i would join this
one day and then it kind of
was like if the moment presents
and then i just kind of said
it and i kind of threw my
whole thing out the window i had
a whole like oh your dad really
right and then i was like yeah
just like this guy just isn't crying
does i had a whole i had
a beginning thing and then i realized
immediately like i didn't plan anything else
out yeah beef up the middle of
this yeah i knew my story it's
interesting how
having been on that side now the
nerves of it are so intense that
it's like it's crazy it's like yeah
i was so nervous all day yeah
i wasn't probably being normal like i
was just thinking like oh i really
want to yeah and so it was
like it's a really specific feeling yeah
yeah yeah crazy yeah how did you
do it again you told oh god
stories oh
yeah you know andriy i'd go to
canada i mean yeah we know and
like lonely island i was on a
boat
yeah like lonely island also like no
when god drowned the world so like
paul in a month when he goes
to solomon island that's right up there
with south carolina the southeast of carolina's
florin lee's um yeah wind it was
yours it's served it is very nerve
i don't know because it's not like
i wonder why is that it's not
like they're gonna say no although the
people who say no i wonder about
the person who's asking like i wonder
about their mental state like how would
i mean how is a point that
was viable the whole like she said
yes if there's a question may
maybe don't die nobody also think oh
you're the people that are surprised at
the person said yes yeah and if
i know conversely the people who say
no i think about the people who
asked like what are you even doing
but i think that if the person
says no i think that can oftentimes
be a wakeup call because it was
so much pressure on knowledge presented yeah
like well now that you ask i
guess no but but idea of saying
no instantly like i feel like i
can imagine the world where someone says
yes and then like two days later
like it's like by the way oh
yeah i actually know someone that has
she said yes and then i know
i know people that's happened to you
and then they got married later yeah
well yeah i know people love each
other
no i didn't know yeah ok but
i know people that that felt know
what they got married
no no do each other though
okay so you asked me william paulo
you marry me no but really you
gotta really make make it like a
real proposal right right okay paul i've
loved you since the minute
that i saw you this is real
i don't i try to imagine my
life without you and the only way
it works is as if there was
some sort of natural disaster and you
were killed instantly by a tsunami or
something new i was the only every
don't say that in there
i don't know what to do in
the middle of this i had that
great opening of a great ending but
i lost the plot in the middle
but paul
i don't want to spend another minute
without you will you marry me now
let me try ca paul what is
is this a game just trying to
get him to say yes is the
feature yeah what yeah let's see let's
go let's see what you got alright
if you bought lauren if you can
convince paul to say yes you guys
have to get married
today well fine she's literally the boss
here very very dumb legally there's so
much
you're very dumb okay you're very
paul hey what's up
i don't know if he's in the
right headspace for this law are you
okay
we think about our relationship
you want me to think about it
because that's what i'm gonna talk about
ever since we first started doing podcasts
together
i've been
waiting for the day when i can
make you my wife
ah
and i'm finally ready to ask you
laura no
oh right that was really that was
worse than how you turned on scott
because it was like you pitied me
yeah did wow that's that does not
feel good to be turned around really
really bad yeah wow god yes paul
we've known each other for such a
long time yeah and i can't imagine
any more time when you weren't in
my life there was a good chunk
well you can't imagine anymore but yeah
your so important to me why is
lauren here by the way so i'm
not here i'm just in your head
i might constantly thinking about
oh sorry pretty good
oh that you and the scenario you
can't stop interrupting
yeah you freaked out at me for
interrupting and then you interrupted so much
you deserve to get so shut
wow paul go ahead
it's a job just propose
who me shut up lauren he's proposing
to make me i'm talking to him
so you and you said to know
yes please just focus on me sorry
i'm just not feeling well you mean
everything to me
will you marry me
yes yes really yes ah yes call
my bluff you're bluffing yeah i thought
i thought this would get you out
of my life oh i have to
be so awkward that you wouldn't talk
yeah oh yeah
oh i'm retiring i don't like this
game it's a good day i guess
we gotta stay focused i just wanted
a happy ending for one of the
couple is that what you said every
massage ah alright let's take a break
rose let's take a break
hi everyone welcome back to threesome and
it's time for features if you have
a feature back to three-term it's three-tier
time reacher welcome back we are back
now with a feature it is the
time of the show where we do
a game
it's a feature or really it's a
three-term um we're gonna leave today we're
gonna play switches and pitch at the
time of the show when we do
a game we're gonna play switch-hitter pitch
again this is an old favorite we've
played it a couple of times and
this is the feature where you will
gain one of us says the title
all of a television show or i
guess a movie that already exists and
the other tv show okay will keep
the tv show show and the other
two people will be make lousy house
the other two people then have to
say the title of what the opposite
of every word is and that is
their title basically of minutiae it's one
person pitching the two people oh it
is oh right right so stuff it
was family matters you would be like
ah single strangers strangers in
it's inessential strangers or something and then
the person has to then pitch that
show and then also sing what the
theme song of that show would be
exactly okay so ah who's going to
pitch first and who's going to save
the title first i'm gonna pitch someone
say the title okay
okay alright um alright ah one i
don't do you yes okay good
i'm trying to think of any tv
show in the world and i can't
think of a single what lo and
hi thank you for coming in hi
lauren did you fuck okay you fucking
construction when do you tell me the
title sorry gee i'm getting to it
yes pardon the structure i actually had
i got there confused and i'm not
sure if i did it right because
it was like every wall or only
had one car did you run into
cars know so you didn't crash so
that's good sounds like you did it
right yeah you're doing good you doing
anyway i'm talking about that just i'm
sorry all right lawrence so i understand
you your project
you're pitching to us today it's called
no no she has to come up
with the opposite you tell me the
original the sky soft yeah thank you
law and order
so what does this show that you're
going to be pitching and i hope
so called law and order oh my
god because louder
no tom john no no no junk
junk
what are you picturing my isn't a
fun new show oh fun um it's
off to a good sign it's dramatic
it's heavy it's everything it's kind of
everything it's kinda got a little bit
of everything everything i hope it doesn't
include sound dunk dunk
copyrighted you wouldn't think you could copyright
that but it actually is three pete
is also covered yeah oh is it
yeah you can't say it oh well
what do you owe me money right
now or you didn't copyright it so
so sorry um okay just leave okay
i'll leave the deck here you can
look at it while you're leaving baseball
while you're leaving tell us about your
show this showing because we love to
watch you walk away crime and mess
crime and mass wow what does this
show about so it's about people who
commit crimes and leave a big mess
behind oh
roles like evidence or just they look
untidy we don't know if it's evidence
or not we're eating a sandwich while
the robed and so the people come
in and they come and they make
people do trimers oh criminals she doesn't
know what she's talking about does she
i mean it's a tv show it's
not stretching a real life thing i
guess maybe it's she's worldbuilding right now
where people are called kramer's circle this
is set in the future and that's
how you know oh were you not
listening to me no no do we
still talking i was i just saw
you guys go into the table oh
we whispering to each other oh about
someone else what did we miss we
kramer's like primers do big messes and
in each apartment does they break into
it's all within one complex so we
see the homeowner or the apartment renter
and then they are living there and
then the snow so i'm sweating i'd
you okay it's sweating buckets it's very
hot in here is it
yeah purpose okay um so the kramer's
come in and they do bad and
they make a mess and then it
never gets resolved never gets resolved every
everybody entire how long does this ever
gets resolved each show is going on
indefinitely so i need to be on
every network because ah ever
the time you switch to channel there's
another crime happening is different and it
just continues on forever so we like
my apartment living happening after and the
person of every paint the apartments we
might they might there might be a
good storyline yeah so what is the
when people switch to another network or
the hearing theme song sorry you which
ones which one of you is joe
what was joe
joey i'm joey and joey i'm joe
joey joey joey joey joey joey joey
and joey so
joey is looking very yeah i'm confused
yeah are you are you pitching to
learn every network gotta yeah because well
you can arrange to have it be
on every network yeah so you're you're
trying to get everyone now where is
this
what network is this you even know
what network it is hgtv because my
understanding was i was walking into tv
building where you control all the tv
okay would you excuse us we just
use able yeah i'm starting to slip
safety
yeah who who gave her the recommendation
to come in and how did she
book this point she's my niece oh
so you can imagine sophie i'm just
gonna remember which one i was yeah
exactly so wait you're her uncle uncle
joey
alright so which your sister your brother
got it out okay alright so uncle
joe joey i just feel safe
wrong call i'm not your uncle bob's
my uncle
hey i wouldn't call it a day
and you just make this okay no
wait it's gonna tip it our him
yeah because you are not doing good
is there a wow is there a
theme yeah it goes like this so
it's called crimean mess good grandma roasted
by the way
it goes like this good good
good good cut cut cut cut cut
cut
the lady could good
are you saying words
could go joey
jujuy
crime and less mess onto did it
could he needs institute
time and the xmas i don't have
a legal guardianship of time is do
it time is did it didn't and
cook good
alright well okay well thank you for
coming in and pushing me out the
door okay
my shoes are untied don't try to
check in here
okay i won't
goodbye duval date nope not for you
not even like just something nice you
could say about me
look you you came in here with
a smile on your face and you
know you're leaving the same way you
have an idea that you believe in
why am i leaving with a smile
on my face have during the one
so bad here i don't know that's
whatever is wrong with you continues to
be with you amen okay bye alright
hey
a scene so that so we win
if we can actually convince the people
to yeah yeah that's how you win
so there's only others like you in
that one that one hurts
who's next sky or show is house
of lies
hey everyone it's ah so i'm so
thankful that you saw me i mean
i know i've been failing in the
industry for a number of years and
been kicked off you don't need to
come in and say that we already
know it and even kicked off of
the lamp you've been kicked off of
the the yeah the afternoon show that
you had which was a nightmare i'm
just a
big failure and um every show that
i've ever created has lost money and
i just really appreciate you seeing no
no no we took this meeting because
we're morbidly curious what do you have
to say i'm morbidly obese i have
to say well both very busy you
know what i feel already that i
don't think i like you why is
that why i actually know you from
your programs
you did your vi yeah i know
another year in here yeah i just
have a thing about me i get
it i get it okay but wait
until you hear the idea because you
remember people aren't going to be watching
me on television they're going to be
watching this idea
sorry my my coworkers to piss
that's a lot don't have a very
loose urethra
alright my show is called truth apartment
truth apartment yep and you hate it
already but even here it's about let's
see okay let's let him bury himself
i'm okay you know we're prejudiced against
it already does you no wonder one
goddess ever heard of her um
she's got a little ah tool on
her cheek yeah but skull tool on
your belt called the magic lasso e
and you know what it does when
she ties it around ah someone i
know it makes people tell the truth
it makes people tell the truth i
okay actually going to answer but you
raised your hand and even hold on
you so she got this on paradise
islands and someone said hey why not
make the whole plane out of it
and she's like ha that's funny but
it's
instead i'm going to use this material
because they grow it on paradise island
like hamper basically oh yeah i'm gonna
make now you're talking about i'm going
to make buildings out of it so
they make an apartment building out of
this and anyone who goes into this
apartment building has to tell the truth
and it's like big bang theory but
what if the roommates like big bang
theory is like big bang theory but
that was
yes i'm listening but you know how
so many other episodes are about like
people lying to each other and covering
up truth what if they couldn't do
that like the movie liar liar where
jimmy tell the truth but also said
things that he didn't need to say
exactly yeah in a weird strange so
what if it was big bang theory
where everyone told the truth to each
other and
you seem so are the episodes five
minutes because there's no deception and no
confusion the episodes are two minutes um
even better yeah so delivered the perfect
short-form content yeah we have a new
platform are bringing out called dumbbell and
it's going to be um all the
shows are two minutes or less i
saw a movie i was good people
view down ball dumbbell d u m
b a dumbo it's no no no
it's dumb you are in burton's dumbo
oh no that's what you are it
was good no no no i'm saying
listenable dumbbell is a platform yeah people
watch lapping years they watched television shows
that are two minutes long as they
receive through text messages i'm about to
give alabama give you an offer and
you're being so full
fucking insane over that driving us crazy
offer it offer it so i want
to just explain the platform yeah it's
called dumbbell and we have two minute
programs that are texted people based on
subscriptions where they pay upwards of ten
dollars an episode via text message i'll
get to write is more and you
get another one i'm in and will
texting stay
top will not end it i'm in
i'm in the only way you can
edit this by saying more enough times
to the point that we understand you
mean stop now dumbo is already successful
and now we have we really were
like ok now they're exaggerated and we
are reading we're in charge of choosers
we go oh they i think they
meant he's making a joke by saying
more shiny times yeah it got um
yeah but we have to kind of
know the person and their sense of
humor you guys do offer several file
oh not apple research i mean we
want you to be part of the
double okay dumbbell is gonna be the
next big timber stumble
it rhymes with tumbled that cleared up
yeah tombo
starring bryan cranston yes exactly kick your
jason's that come out your butts i
don't think i like you but okay
and ah but okay i just want
to complete my pitch about dumbbell because
okay well i thought i was pitching
to you i don't know because i
want to pitch the platform and see
if i think it's a good fit
okay working on dumbbell for the last
fifteen years are you drinking your own
deals like sixteen it does yeah so
it feels like that those who'd done
a lot of trees just had an
earthquake
dare you and you don't restart no
save water my entire family is dead
i know about the earthquake we don't
want your idea congratulations yeah no whatever
where if i sang the song now
you have to give us the theme
song
true ou support mans where six p
bull live they're all friends with each
other until they start telling the truth
than the hate each other but they
cannot leave because they bought
the doors and they nailed inside and
everyone had to sit down with each
other till they cried and died in
the truth a partner shot you can
never lee e you've never leave i
don't think you mentioned that but did
not
and that was half the cheapest big
part of it so the first happy
you think that she's missing that the
cameras are now one minute of the
people to true so it's hard when
they can't leave i hope you are
taking that because i will not sing
it again in other words just taping
it like this your video is sold
in the room i yes we finally
got to show on dumb dumbo
ah first first show we're gonna launch
with you or gonna put you on
the billboard singing the song it's going
to be a live video i'm gonna
do it live yeah and every billboard
video building so i gotta clear my
schedule know you're gonna stand on a
billboard and i'm gonna stand on it
and then if you die we don't
have to make your show yeah and
this happens in ten minutes well
what do i wear because i can't
wear these this i mean all all
very uses old tuxedo it's about a
year out of date i need a
current one no you wear that get
written me a current tuxedo you're you're
screwing the deal it's current tuxedo get
out of this office this is my
office leave i invited you
oh here i know that's pulling a
real power move get out around gumbel
headquarters you're taking over my office double
h q do i still have to
pay the ram do you must pay
the rent i alright paul you ready
yeah i'm ready man okay um your
ah your show
is dateline nbc
okay welcome who's our next meeting who's
this i think it's um joe joey
joe joey johnson's joe joy judge
hi my name's paul i don't know
if i'm the right guy
no i said no looks after him
oh after julia joe johnson after paul
paul left you were discussing who your
next excuse me person's going to paul
tomkins and then joe joey joe john
johnson jenkins joe joey g junkin joe
g congo have competence paul okay should
i were just trying to plan our
day my i'm i'm chevy and
hi shaven and this is vivian dvd
and people call me d thank you
call me s thank you so much
ssd for having me
i'm very glad to hear your pitch
because we loved everything we wanna love
you love you so much we love
your feedback on it to make everything
you've done but we just haven't yeah
we just always love you we're tight
with the purse strings just no misers
we just never do it but we
always we always want you and we
always you leave the rhino i wish
we could but we want to keep
some angeles
going i think it's going to happen
and then later say no no my
absolute favorite thing in this industry is
all the people who say that their
fans have me but never employ me
yeah well yeah where are those we
are though definitely people here game but
will never employ you to thumb you
so what do you got for the
c p for the c what do
you got first well i have an
exciting new show
show well this sounds exciting it's called
marriage dot
cbn marriage does cbs yes and the
cbn stands for this sounds like a
web address it's not have you ever
gone to dot cbn i haven't but
maybe it's a new thing i don't
know like dot gov not dot edu
you are right i am right it
is not a website yet
oh stupid going d no no no
you both look very smart oh because
because you did you hear that we're
already talking about the idea yeah it's
so confusing that it's spiegel what is
exact marriage dog urged irish duh yeah
yeah yes wow hey and so isn't
spelled marriage d o t or is
it just
a dot it's just a dot okay
and what's about and is it real
or fake aren't you curious as to
why cbn stands for yes please tell
us cbn it stands for crypto buying
neighbors whoa cryptos very popular low current
so ca
current sees current cryptopia yeah yes exactly
so that marriage so these okay marriage
dot cbn it's a website but it's
characters that live on the website oh
and they are neighbors and they're both
buying crypto from each other back-and-forth and
venture wrong about anything or buy anything
with it they
they they never buy anything with it
except more crypto love so we're constantly
i'm talking to they own any possessions
no really no clothes nope no boat
no motor car they're both nature a
single luxury they're naked they're both nude
by choice so nude oh so they're
nude nine you're not
by twinkies photoshop by tomatoes is when
someone strips all your clothes from you
yes and nude d's when you choose
to take photos like i want to
take off my clothes i'm calling a
char there to nude people wait what
is the emotion it makes when someone
please think harold ramis wants to do
with this
these these dead nightmare leaving low rodham
you oh okay they meet on the
website marriage dot cbn okay where they
are trading cryptos back and forth eventually
this is for singles who want single
crypto lol no one does not and
cherishing it's only
yeah well they shouldn't even be on
there oh this is like an ashley
madison situation jackley wow you know a
lot about that d yeah he had
a quiet nasa affair that was on
madison the terms of service on that
website you you got a real everyone
knows she's a real creep yeah there's
a huge ah cancelation i cheated on
my wife with her
well i didn't sign off on you
this is the least i've known she
was asleep eating she was asleep
davion bess i'm i'm calling you d
rom because i'm so mad
i didn't know about this
davion you didn't know about this i
wrote you that note to be in
we're trying to accept a pitch by
paul i'm not i'm that's right i'm
still here
and so they fall in love on
the website the two people who are
training what are their names you haven't
said their names yet the is free
you get to this part the names
are deviant city mo
i love this
wow even a character named sven how
cool yeah but representation matters it's been
does it does not enough vivian's on
television wow so is it just these
two nude characters in there anymore
i mean so it's kind of like
naked and afraid but their nude and
charge yeah toe is the alternate title
nude and in charge of the russia
i love this i want to buy
it how how long is how long
the episodes every episode is ninety minutes
long and is it a comedy is
it a drama neither neither no jokes
no conflict daniel i think it'd be
great for drunk our new app drunk
yeah it's ninety minutes shows that you
watch when you're driving and we say
hey everyone
should drunk driving everyone should be drunk
everyone should drunk driving yeah and so
it's it's gonna be really successful we
have fifteen people already talking about it
on different platforms yeah we've got we've
got a bunch of very different platforms
to like not even similar platforms there's
so there's so different so a lot
of we want to do it so
you feel is
here's the offer we'll give you a
thousand dollars an episode budget and you
get paid a thousand dollars on top
of that yeah so two thousand dollars
an episode so every episode yeah and
you get that we're talking two grand
to big one two k two k
two large
per episode and you get to make
two episodes and you get to slap
one actor per episode and then we
announce it the same day we cancel
it yeah and we don't show any
of the episodes ever and they go
into a vault they go into the
disney vault pay us two thousand dollars
per episode that you
made yeah and they're right next to
the song of the south and they
make a big fancy ride at disneyland
based on it based on this thing
that no one will ever get to
see again you don't get money for
that you don't get any money for
that how's that sounds great
ideal has been made a deal is
struck your ridge great
don't get so excited i'll do a
dance when we give them yeah most
people dance i mean yeah i'm very
okay you seem excited is everything all
right everything's fine anything else you need
to know about the show or know
i mean i'd like to hear the
theme song but marriage dod cbn
pretty short for a ninety minute episode
i like it i think we let
it go because it could be ringtones
it can be gifts it could be
yeah memes it could be everything so
i learned are you afraid that you're
gonna have all just see myself out
wow do i sign this when she
want sign these contracts here huh
okay okay he's gone well what do
we do with the rest of our
day because you can keep four thousand
dollars and just split it because our
next meeting isn't for another joey joe
joey jay jenkins is coming in but
not for another eight hours i got
to sleep
that's our show people and scene we
gotta wrap it up we gotta wrap
it i have to gotta wrap it
up gotta got a rapid to exit
the scene we couldn't wrap it up
fast enough
love you guys a ton love you
too so much thousand pounds should be
uncomfortable with it flung me to the
moon me say
ah let me see what spring is
like oh yeah oh oh ma
oh my hey and hour
da kiss me wow oh yeah iv'e
play ball hella law you oh oh
oh oh wow worship and doe in
other words
please me mama na
nah ah oh dude bang huh huh
thank you wow
bye
a