nah
how you see three huh
hey i'm going to be jay
um oh yeah oh the way we
sing the song dude that's how we
do it every single time oh mcdonnell
remember how fun it gets don't know
about old macdonald these day you know
griping god oh i've been singing about
who's the lady who's going to be
coming around the mountain when she comes
oh i love going to be ready
i just was i was singing voices
can you write racking my brain for
a song for her and that one
just popped right in and she'll be
riding six white horses when she comes
and then we'll all go out to
greet her when she comes and i'm
like she always rightly fuck she doing
she riding them like she sort of
lengthwise across them six why
ride horses i think her legs are
spread onto all the way up oh
um so she's straddling six complete origins
show straddling things like horses when she
co was jumping around to all of
them as she goes oh like oh
shit i thought she was in like
a sort of cart and they're pulling
it and she's encourage when they're okay
yeah
um do you think well that don't
mean we never find out her name
yeah and we let her go any
where she's going what she's doing we're
joining the song les media rez because
i was thinking am i forgetting something
no it's just starts with she'll be
riding six foot yeah like i guess
that's asking her to come has already
occurred your your
like you're turning a corner and two
people are already discussing this yeah yeah
it's exciting actually no i mean they
drop you right in the middle of
the song you're playing matches stuff's already
happening you have to act like you
know who they're talking about it's like
pulp fiction with just like things out
of order and you're just like oh
my god i'm putting this together and
what about that song um
someone's in the kitchen with dinah what's
that yeah we never we never find
out is it her horse from the
sun she came to visit dana crossing
yeah so the extended dinosaurs i guess
yeah getting close she'll become thinking about
the extended cheaters oh
oh yes
good songs good songs great old really
good songs these are the songs of
my youth but but my to my
point earlier huh kids today they're too
busy with tick tock to listen to
songs i like these great wonderful songs
have already things like oh and here's
another one i was almost done
yeah when i was young useless in
songs like abcd f g i used
to listen to twinkle twinkle little star
yeah these are real song great distinct
melodies songs that touches something and also
told a story i used to also
baba black sheep i love that one
melody i know i know it's not
a fad i was playing
this like toddler playlist on spotify and
there was that song the ants go
marching one by one hurrah hurrah okay
so it it rhymes with the video
a little rhyme at the end with
each new number so the ants go
marching one the little ones like the
ants go marching one by one the
little one stopped to have some fun
and they all go marching
down to the ground get out of
there okay then i went to the
ants go marching seven by seven hurrah
hurrah the ants go marching seven by
seven hurrah hurrah the ants go marching
seven by seven the little one stopped
to pray to heaven and they all
when i went what did he stop
to pray to well i guess
it's better than him dying and going
to heaven which is where i thought
it was headed yeah i guess you're
right one died i went to oh
a little one's got a lot on
his plate i just was like he's
praying he's closing a door he's he's
doing all of these things that arriving
with numbers you think of this the
same little one that asked everybody to
roll over it
as part of the extended yeah yes
yeah for sure i know that song
by the way need to write that
one down what is that one you
need to write it down
rollover rollover they roland made yeah that's
a rollover rollover and they all rolled
over and one fell out and do
in the head and the little ones
said well omer well alone where you
gotta to know all of these i
don't think i know that song and
i don't think i'll ever sing it
you are gonna sing it in
about oh no six months you're gonna
sing it no never gonna sing that
song you're gonna sing it in six
months emmys gonna be it's gonna be
a number one hit yeah you're gonna
sing publicly you're gonna go to the
studio you're gonna stay down rollover
orchestral food that would be so lame
i just put out one single in
my career and it's it's as over
roll a reboot
i also read ebooks yeah
did you know a scope you probably
know this maybe it was to lauren
back in the old tin pan alley
days i'm out somebody will
and for this reason i'm out they
would somebody write a song and then
every popular singer would do a cover
of it they'd do their own version
of it and then like one person's
cover would be the most popular one
but there would be multiple versions of
the same song out yeah so okay
i didn't really read
allies this but i've i've noticed that
when i'm searching for an oldie that
there are like many renditions but i
never really put it together thought about
it that was like a sort of
intentional thing to see which one would
pop it's just yeah i don't for
graphics i think it also went into
the sixties to where like bob dylan
a lot of his songs were written
for
for other people to sing them and
they became hits for other people even
though he's saying them himself on albums
you know like eight miles high and
all the cast yeah yeah but ah
he shot eight miles high well did
it didn't eat no no sorry roger
mcgwin wrote that i'm actually saw roger
mcguinn three nights in a row and
every single
ninety when this song about a horse
what why
no actually this kind of horses this
betters is the difference
say miles high intro was this about
a plane ride i did
the plainly went up eight miles
i just loved his stage or is
that it was always the same as
always one sentence wait oh wow he
always delivered it with that same emergency
yeah this is a song about a
horse this song about a plane ride
i took
because like i don't need any context
know i don't want anyone else i
know without knowing it's about a plane
ride little lakers like kelly clarkson when
she sings her famous song shows a
song about surmise
since you being behind is behind those
hayes alive that's her famous song
here is a song about someone who's
been gone
yeah this is a song about you
that's how i
and what you did
what i did this is watching you
up this way and go th things
he goes this is talking about somebody
i used to know
ah
i also like when stage patter is
like longer and then it leads to
the big hit single things so like
in negotiate example it would be like
him telling a long really boring story
about you know i was in ah
america sh
boring good why is that boring that
actually already started really interestingly he's really
what if he said well if he
wasn't montana i might be a little
less excited what if he says are
ya fans in montana lauren i'm going
to tell you the story behind the
song but i'm coming that's good about
during combos yeah yeah yeah show where
having a fall conversation it's but it's
it really
that really did feel like i was
a ghost i've had i've had that
happen all right your first name by
the way this no i've had that
happen already yeah by the way paul
you the lighting on you were on
zoom today well it's let's not even
let's be real my nose is running
like a faucet my friends and not
a faucet that's been turned off you
know a faucet that's been turned on
exactly
yeah but paul the lighting on you
you do look like a ghost you
look very pale and wan
i mean the outdoor light i'm i'm
sitting right by the window yeah and
i feel like i'm getting a lot
of nice natural light in here you
are but for some reason on my
computer screen it looks you know you
you have to wipe the jibs off
the skull oh here
for once
but okay here's my point please wow
what if gaultier he introduces the song
because he wants to keep the song
interesting yeah he he warns everyone hey
i'm gonna tell you the story behind
the song but i'm gonna actually keep
it kind of dull so that it
does
didn't render the song superfluous yeah right
so you will get some io things
and foe because all gonna be boring
shit like about the weather what i
what i haven't breakfast paul what would
you rather would you rather hear a
story or hear a song
well i mean it depends on the
storyteller it depends on the singer but
okay so the world's greatest storyteller
versus the world's greatest singer so j
k rowling
members so what's your alias what's your
aka oh robert goals bley to the
remembering i don't know
what does she write under that alias
weight she has like another alias yeah
j k rowling not her name i
would assume ah i don't know just
kidding rowling has hurt shame she wrote
she wrote a bunch of of mystery
novels or something under a a male
alias well that's probably where
yeah they're they're all about they have
trans stuff in them don't i will
say i with ray were the were
those books successful is the question i
think she put them out under the
alias because she just wanted to she
didn't want a bunch of j k
rowling fans to to buy it who
expecting you know wizard shit and stuff
like that
but then i think her alias got
revealed before it ever even came out
so it happened anyway or something well
you know like why aren't there wizards
and wands in here yeah you have
you do one thing and you do
it well one one and that's five
wizards yep
it's a fight over it
ugh now that's that's a book is
it like hungry hungry hippos style yes
yes there's no middle and someone gets
eliminated yeah oh my god yeah i
remember hunger google's um it's not really
a story of one guy wait is
it a song
omg though it goes like this it
is i mean there's ripples um no
so i just saw i'm like ah
my friends page she posted like a
old post from like years ago where
she and her friends did humans doing
hungry hungry hippos so i just tell
you about this guy's telling me oh
i've never heard of so
they it's a really funny video it's
like all the people are okay so
each person has a has a partner
and so like they're down like a
wheelbarrow but they're on there holding onto
like a um like a little board
on wheels like you know those little
things with handles scooters or whatever sure
and then they have their hands on
their legs are being held up into
the air and
they're being pushed into the center of
the circle where there are balls and
they have to try to grab them
and bring them to their signs in
their mouths are just using their hands
oh that yeah that's not hungry hungry
hippo ah that's a hungry hungry hippos
yeah it's hard to say for me
make them marble eggs and then make
them catch them with their teeth
yeah yeah and i maintain choke on
them yeah and choke on them and
lose their teeth and choke on their
pride make them buy down the marbles
and gioco yeah
that gives me a bad feeling when
okay so they own like hand trucks
like how do they because otherwise i
believe also mentioned in the stuff this
scooter i'm trying to describe we used
to use them in gym class in
elementary school and i don't know if
there's a thing that you used to
use like that where it's basically a
pl
plastic board with handles on the side
and four wheels on the bottom like
the bottom of a hamper or something
it's like and you're just you are
laying your chest onto the plastic and
holding onto the sides and then you're
being pushed into the center and then
like the thing i'm grabbing like a
mechanic users yeah but not exactly it
it's like a how can i
it's sad because is it escape board
with a handle no it's a square
it's square so so equidistant on each
side exactly the same on all four
sides wow and anyone can measure it
and it's going to be proven true
and i've definitely told this story that
when i was in fifth grade we
used to play with those on like
friday and gym class yeah and i
was racing my friend around the gym
with basically running with my legs but
then using the scooter yeah it's like
you're sort of pike position and i
flew straight into the wall my glasses
went into my forehead
head and had blood dripping down and
it was a terrifying or one of
your many head injuries as a child
yes yes yes yes so may i
of course used to do handcart races
when i worked in a warehouse of
a payroll company duda duda yeah
yeah i love those things but is
that the pallet jack were is so
much fun to write yellow jack yeah
ride the pallet jack tell me all
about what that is well it's my
series of books that i write under
a pseudonym i'm a lady your names
pallet jack mean jacqueline palette
did you work in a warehouse ball
for ah for a brief time yes
yeah me too brief time my people
must have been so happy to have
you around the warehouse being funny oh
boy did they they were like here
he comes the clown
sometimes i would have to deliver the
mail to people and i are packages
or something that that we would get
in the warehouse and i'd have to
go up up to the other floors
and like deliver them and i was
always like hey i'm not just a
warehouse guy yeah you know like i'm
a person just like you i'm much
more than this
this
i could do whatever you can do
i bet
that was when i was listening involves
thinking and using a computer because i
only want to do musicals that's me
it sounds like you
that's when i was attempting i would
just get put into weird random jobs
but to be a temp you have
to take like a typing test and
i remember i got
it was all computerized and i got
i got off at one point i
can't remember why you're supposed to like
type out a piece of paper that
they give you when they time you
and i got i got it off
and so like everything was gibberish when
i turned it in and and ah
the person taking the test because i
i got one thing
ing off and i'm done pretending to
type i got one thing off ok
you can't see what it's typing yes
you can't see what you're typing so
it messed up everything so the entire
thing was gibberish and i said oh
i mean i think i got one
thing wrong and it did all that
and she goes yeah you're probably fine
and she just gave me like shit
like because normally you can see it
yeah yeah
yeah i think is a key detail
yeah exactly detail it's a kid to
tell but also like what's the worst
it's going gonna happen is the company
that hires the temp for a day
or two is going to call them
and say you sent us a bad
temp but they'll be like oh no
we're so sorry sorry that eighteen year
old in the pool of other eighteen
year olds
it wasn't quite up to snuff yet
let's see i always felt like and
i had a lot of friends who
tempt um i always felt like that
was more stressful in a weird way
than i mean many jobs just me
out but the idea of temping was
stressful because it's like you go in
and you don't know anything and you
have to do things and act like
you know stuff that seems really hard
there's no pressure on you because no
one
cares what you do so they don't
give you any assignments no no you
you i mean i worked at the
payroll company for like a summer and
by the end of it everyone you
know i knew my duties and all
that kind of stuff but who gives
like no one no one's like no
one cares the bar when no one
cares about everyone people's lives with my
incompetence people didn't get their checks ah
people can get operations i typed gobbledygook
for names
thanks refused to cash checks
did you tell paul no never
why not why not i was a
retail guy that was always my job
it was really you'd be so good
at retail because you're just personable and
you want it you want people to
feel good you know for a while
yeah yeah yeah and then now you're
not know and it depends on how
long you let how there's a
cutoff for how long you can work
one of those jobs yeah and and
retain like a pleasant personality is it
because the you get tired of what
you're selling or you get tired of
the experience
um everything you get tired of living
your life and being you are hey
there's an easy solution for that hey
my god i know it's painless and
bring many changes
ah yeah so remember a temporary no
no but i was temporary at every
place i worked yeah
um other than movie star that's what
i did i of course worked in
the boat dock and i worked um
ah at a coffee shop for about
a couple i basically spent more time
training than i did working there and
i hate literally scared um be careful
don't drink coffee and those in
new york and everyone's like moba doka
doka la la latte or everybody i
go to yeah you got it and
then i would just be like me
and then panic and i'm take forever
and stressed out umm of course one
time i dropped a bagel and it
was last one of that kind of
blah blah blah anyway that looks like
it went extinct yeah it was
super dino bagel and with dinos last
one i know it had diode dna
if it's kind it connected back like
if you had cracked it open it
was basically an amber like you know
thing with a bug inside but it
was gumbo ama sorry i'm doing a
boston rob from survivor oh sure sure
so um
nba
i haven't seen survivor yet but i've
been told i would like it
at this point i don't know what
you're waiting on
i just don't care twenty two years
later
there's no time it's never too late
right no nothing it's never too late
to learn a new skill
yeah um yeah just i wanna just
say one thing which is that okay
say one thing and then we have
to take a break make sure it's
good making good well it might lead
to another conversation okay but we'll do
it on the other side ie so
the other day i went to a
paint store coincidentally this is the paint
store where
in the alley behind a beastie boys
video was shot i just learned on
doughboys from art and marine talking about
it jill's painted out water there was
no those video shop they didn't have
the the mural yeah and um it's
a very nice paint shop it's just
like a kind of a hardware store
and i how interesting rain man
i just mean it's not like fancy
vote okay very good
just you know need to say it
like multiple times you know you're doing
a very interesting paint store i hate
myself oh no i'm fine my mom
actually i love these actually love the
flavor and you could instantly tell how
many of the work well i they
dropped paint chips and then i ate
them oh yeah because that they were
chips yeah um but anyhoo i had
learned on a blog of a interior
designer that i like call ah called
emily henderson i'm not british but that
is her name she posted years ago
on her blog about this idea i
don't know if she invented it but
from the blog i remember thinking that
she did to if you're gonna paint
a room you get like posterboard and
new paint
pieces of board the different colors and
then you can hold them up in
the different light you know sunlight over
here a little dark you know what
i mean so that yeah um and
i thought oh such a great idea
so then i was gonna do that
when i'm going to paint a room
in my house which i'm doing now
and i went to this paint store
and now they sell
all foam boards cut two little squares
and they have a little label on
the back that says what kind of
pain is this where did i put
it what was the date and i
thought that was really cute but i
also wondered if they stole that from
her and then i also just wanted
to say it's great because if you
are someone who's interested in this kind
of stuff you can save all the
colors that you've painted and then later
you might want to do a different
room and go oh this would actually
be
good in here and i don't have
to buy the paint sample again just
wanted to share that little hot tip
it's a good tip for news you
know you don't care about that stuff
i used to paint my own place
a lot and and so that would
have come in handy i'm not gonna
paint it myself because i
for various reasons one being i can't
move the bed i need to hire
someone to do it hire me you
can't move the bed yeah scott have
you seen this bed sweetie i can
boot i guarantee you i guarantee you
i can move any bed on earth
oh baby so you're gonna come over
and move the bed how much do
you want to bet
i can't move the bet a thousand
dollars yeah okay so if i come
over and move the bed i win
a thousand dollars but if i can't
move the bed you have to move
it you give a lee away from
the wall into the center of the
room in ten minutes yeah in ten
why take one time limit because you
can't take all day i don't want
to hear you
huffing and puffing in there for hours
alright we have to take a break
our back and i know we're talking
about paint when when you're talking about
a weakling you are yeah let's hope
we were really talking about that was
the subtext hey you're gonna take all
day to move a bed
all i wanted was twenty three hours
not all day okay okay you're gonna
stay up for twenty three hours moving
bed yeah and fine and i know
your place is haunted if i stayed
the entire night i went ten thousand
dollars less true yeah um remember when
you used to be a million dollars
if you stayed overnight on an house
in fl
asian man it's gone down to ten
thousand is only ten now yeah this
is what i wanna say to boomers
like when you were young we was
johnny dollars a million dollars yeah of
hope
do you do when news but i
just want to touch back on the
paint type for a second yeah when
you are in your home do you
think at all i know paul does
do you think at all about decorating
you just go someone else has got
that covered too though i wish this
was like this i wish
shh this thing was like this i
in in the first place that i
bought my condo i decorated it myself
and i i was watching trading spaces
a lot this is in the term
wow century so your room was like
covered in seashells glued to the wall
and straw
no but but i think i think
they because it's on camera i think
they would like use these bright colors
and stuff like that so i got
tricked into that thing like oh okay
i'll do i'll do like i'll paint
one wall red and painted a lot
of it this pale yellow and it
just was bad
bad it sounds and it sounds like
a disgusting combo it was it was
and then some brown as well it's
terrible and so and so now now
i am also replaced as a prank
show it kind of is because like
truly people would be so upset when
they go back in their house because
it's boring it was so cheap
first picture with a prank the home
viewer yeah yeah and the whole fucking
with us they were pranking homes
this guy there was one designer who
would always put like little like humpty
dumpty around the room it was just
really weird early yeah very farm themed
that's yours and to be fair i
mean i don't know that was how
he was he was an actual egg
he was a negative is kind of
his yeah gosh i guess no one
mentioned it ever you know because aig
man who wore pants
it's yeah well he's very fragile
but so so finally when i moved
to a different place we just keep
everything white basically or off-white yeah yeah
it's just so much better and so
much calmer and yeah yeah way better
million colors yeah you like well i
mean you have so it depends on
the space too you have the where
you are right now yeah oh my
my i'll just say your address if
that's ok
but um your podcast space has great
wallpaper and i think of it's like
a smaller room that's used for a
special purpose or like ah ah ah
powder or something like that you yeah
great wallpaper you know yeah yeah i've
done i've done some wallpaper yeah right
if you're director of powder powder for
your daniel powder
yeah she's down
soothing powder ever since you had a
bad day
maybe he's like getting hit by lightning
he's like the character head of bed
i had a bad day do you
think because you almost fired my powder
probably because the singer's name is that
so yeah that makes sense the song
would be inspired by what they're doing
something similar very everybody was calling him
powder and it made him have a
bad day
yeah yeah and that's the story because
like no i have hair i have
i've tan skin yeah we have no
idea what he looks like by the
way um oh i know exactly what
he looks like i can you do
exactly you could tell me no you
show him i enjoy five pictures of
different people in one of them or
is daniel powder and i'll tell you
which one is daniel bow
i really wish i could get a
lineup going really fast without you so
just pick just pick five red you
can just pick five random pictures no
flame random ones dad powder and then
we'll see if we can this would
be great three shirt see if i
can identify your daniel powter honestly i'm
looking at him now i wish i
could send you like game
oh what if i look at five
other people yeah that's only two
i typed in i type the reverse
run around all the bases now because
i was like what's that wait wait
wait scott you said he's tan and
he is really tan and then i
typed in tan men and that's like
a name of a japanese dish and
that's all it's about i'm like there's
not they don't
have one picture it's hand man and
it's so ten men is just oh
it's it's in another okay got it
ten so rom and soup got yeah
okay but i'm going i wanna see
a tan man and i want to
see multiple i want to see a
tan man oh yeah and you want
to see him together or separately
yeah i want to see a tan
man eating ten men i wanna see
tan entertainment and just want to see
you and your five tan men eating
ten men listening daniel powder while watching
powder yes so they're playing this already
over the movie is this a t-shirt
yeah that's a t-shirt but it has
to have that sort of screen where
remember
like in the nineties when like t-shirts
had like a sort of three d
there there was a period of time
where it's trendy to have like a
little three d image on your t-shirt
i mean i was a child so
i had this and it was like
if you turn one way it kinda
looked like something else what the fuck
are you talking about it was like
a little piece of like a plastic
kind of yeah kind of attached to
your shirt was in the
hologram it was like scratchy scratchy like
lines on it it was lenticular okay
and then you have it be like
a cat and like
ah when you first look at it
it's like a nice kitty and then
when you go sideways the cat seems
very angry yeah yeah yeah yeah i
know exactly or or the reverse could
happen to you i guess where you're
like that's an angry cat and then
you're like oh wait a minute no
it's a nice cat thanks ya fuck
that's wild
it's pretty crazy man what teachers can
do these days i'm remembers when there
were picture books when i was little
that had they would sometimes you're just
just be the cover but sometimes it
would be the whole book where it
would be all those sort of lenticular
but it didn't the image didn't change
but it was it had
depth you know i mean it looks
kind of three d and you it
was very satisfying scratching feeling and sound
the yeah take on it yeah but
i remember being fascinated by them because
they were beautiful they were really beautiful
to look at here's what you're i
have a question about children's books that
lauren maybe can answer and paul thoughtfully
fried away when i was a child
but when you were a child
you thought like a child i thought
acted like a child when i became
a man i probably chopped yeah that's
it yeah um okay so i i
eating readers ah i've been reading these
children's books that we have to my
daughter
yeah
um okay so when i was a
kid and i read a read children's
books to myself i don't remember all
of them trying to make the adult
cry oh my god there's so these
books are the fucking tenderest books i
swear to like i just went awry
corduroy i haven't read quarter it's so
sweet when i know it's funny well
you know what she's also at the
age where like when hollywood's her age
and i would open quarter i don't
like too many words not gonna bother
like but now hollywood wants to sit
for a longer story so i'm like
i'll read these longer stories and that
one's not super long but it's just
got you know some of the pages
are a little more and
evolved and i'm like this book is
so sweet it's just about the sweet
little bear and this girl goes and
buys him and their friends it's just
nice well the ones that i've been
reading are all about like me the
read because i read them out loud
by the way i don't really i'm
just late and she's just like hoping
to take something away from the experience
but when when when i read them
too
her it's all about like me the
reader and how i feel about her
and stuff oh yeah it's all they're
all designed to be like i think
you're so special and you're american and
all this kind of stuff it's like
hey e he's up he's allowed just
want to read a story about a
bearers forever my baby you're my baby
you'll oh i'm afraid of that one
where it's like then like the adult
purse
isn't at the like it's all about
a baby then the baby can hear
the parent at the end and they're
like holding them like a baby and
like this yeah fucking weird it's like
hey i want to be in charge
here i don't want i don't want
to show weakness to my baby absolutely
you don't you definitely don't want to
show weakness i don't want to be
a cook do you have that book
on the night you were born i
think it's like polar bears dancing on
the cover and it's like in the
night you are
born there was never anyone in the
whole world ever like you and you're
the most special person in the world
and the wind whispered your name and
then let's whisper it together and now
holly whispers her name and the page
like you owe but also and she
says it before i get to it
she's like book authors stop doing this
like just write a book about a
pirate or something you know it's like
like i think you know you can
get books like that for sure talking
about pirates like kids don't need to
have pirates explained to them they just
seem to be on board right away
you know what i mean but everybody's
so worried about if two men are
kissing yeah explain it to your bait
yeah your guy oh i know i
know
so many things like that yeah all
the concepts that kids grasp without they
don't give surely they don't care but
here's my question because i was reading
some some books about animals and the
only animal the ones
wow what do we got we got
a horse he's ah that's your question
what are they oh no no the
only animals she's seen are two dogs
to spread our scientific in-person right yes
in person so when i'm reading these
books i'm like oh the the cat
goes meow right sure like she is
no what a fucking cat is i
know but she's gonna start to learn
all that it's actually kind of weird
i thought the same thing i also
feel like that's what the pictures for
a while but that's what i find
really fascinating is that
and i think i mentioned this but
like holly i was very shocked when
like she was noticing all types of
dogs as being dogs and all cartoons
of dogs as being dogs and like
she knows she knows i mean dorm
of like this type of nose and
and four legs if they're tiny if
they're huge like she knows what they
are when we're out it's just that
it's that's amazing to me but katherine
jones never wanted to anything else instead
it was adult not once
not a chair now that's more like
wow not once
she's never once she's never once called
something other than it's name she's never
once done that she always calls things
exactly what exactly what it is yeah
like a cat and a dog are
so similar like really what are the
differences when you really break it down
um names
yeah
like your da they're the exact same
thing no this bold i don't think
they're really exact like if you looked
if if you saw a cat and
a dog could you tell which was
which
i wouldn't want to because i wouldn't
want to be rude but wait
timeless what what japanese on with wild
horses she was like talking about when
she was reading these books with her
kids when they were really little she
liked didn't know the difference between a
goat and sheep
and it made me laugh so much
that you took them like a petting
zoo and she was like i don't
know what each one is but now
they're supposed to know what every thing
is it's just like some are very
hard like a mongoose or something i
don't know that if i saw something
if i saw a mongoose would i
be able to say that's a mongoose
rikki tikki my dear boy
i'm sure i would say it's a
rikki tikki tavi but what i say
it's a mongoose i don't yeah you
would yeah you would well yeah you
know fun is going to the zoo
with all the animals can be really
weird like when watching holly look at
ah i don't i never know how
to say it but like a taper
tpr tpr yeah i'm like that's a
really weird animal and she was kinda
where
faded out she was like huh ooh
like ooh it's like so strange and
like i don't really know what it
is well we have these cards they're
like flashcards with animals that emerald likes
to look at because they're black and
white and very striking and there's you
know there's good ones or skunk there's
penguin she really likes penguin perfect for
black
and light too yeah yeah but then
some and and it's like penguin ah
skunk orca stuff like that and then
suddenly there's ring-tailed lemur they make some
fucking leaps with this stuff i feel
the same way or i'm going yeah
luke really i'm just like why are
we jumping now she has to know
what a ring halo lee
rumor is yeah why don't we just
say lima why don't we just go
like let's just kind of narrow it
like let's just broaden it a little
bit because sometimes it gets very monkey
or something you'd like him even monkey
gorilla i start to go now i've
got all these types of monkey rang
a tapes and here's a trick here's
my theory
okay so i learned all the animals
from my a to z book or
eight hundred for yuki listener thanks and
this was like last year you focused
on that and you really it was
it was during the pandemic yeah yeah
but um where it's like you know
a is for aardvark and all that
kind of true there should there should
only be twenty four animals and they
should all be a differ
that letter so you can just memorize
that do you know there are twenty
six letters in the alphabet but
wait wasn't the show twenty four about
the alphabet
were you accounting for x and z
and saying cut those out we don't
need yeah we don't don't we don't
need zebras and animals zebras zebras key
you're right no waste to the waste
yeah but we need to get rid
of x x is a really tricky
word with learning letter with learning words
like just
like why do we need x we
have a c k we need we
should make up a bunch of louis
c k
we should make up a muslim saint
louis x that started with x and
then just kinda like get those into
the culture so that we can just
start having fun things on the page
like a xylophone is not well yeah
wow we have we have xylophone we
have xenophobes thank you for that x-ray
and we have x pacers yeah it's
not enough it's not enough
we need more than you and that's
why we're saying we want to do
things losers out there to create new
words but it should be like she'd
be like xenophobe as like that's what
x stands for zena folks with zeal
yeah because this is kind of stuff
we want the decoding kit they don't
everyone should be a phobia yeah yeah
yeah awful
oh boy okay so some on the
animals
what who who are the picks for
each letter like a you've got gotta
go aardvark because of the double a
because the double a it's so good
and by the way who's who's calling
an aardvark aardvark saying like oh i'm
gonna put a double a at the
beginning of this like what what lunatic
ne yeah they were just having fun
i think i'm gonna say yeah it's
true
what about anteater i think anteaters are
more financial than an aardvark fun in
the sense of like genocide for ants
because of the widget it looks like
a vacuum
it doesn't look like exactly it's probably
the animal that looks most like a
vacuum out of any i don't know
elephant though even that looks like longest
time i thought aardvark and anteater were
the same thing and i think there's
a lot of confusion around right that
there's it only be one and we
eliminate whatever we make them extinct whenever
the other
the one is do you know why
i thought that because of the cartoon
the aardvark and i was just going
oh i think you'd say about arthur
the aardvark not on game
alright well he's a great guy is
he the guy from the famous hand
yeah the in the fist oh yes
exactly now okay have you seen the
pride and prejudice with um tom lambs
gans from succession oh my god or
nightly i saw that a million years
ago but when i put together that
it was him in that i wanted
to watch
that again because i love him i
saw for the first time a couple
of years ago and it was really
enjoyable um so i recommend every watch
but i know that there's a thing
that he does with his hand that
i remembered that that a lot of
people that are fans of that movie
remember that and they think it's very
romantic and i forgot to look for
it when i watched the movie and
i still don't know who
was but it was apparently a very
notable thing that he does oh i
don't remember but i always picture the
arthur hand when i hear he does
it with her hand or he does
it with his own hand he does
something with his own hand that is
apparently very magical magical it's not him
delta man her something romantic finger banging
oh my god
paul was like this isn't it this
isn't something might be finger back
mean there was a finger banging scene
in the movie yeah well i didn't
put ten minutes all about how they
won't go all the way but they'll
do everything but yeah right so there's
an anal sexy
we have to take a break
alright we're back and we have some
voicemails right yeah people call people call
us we're cool yeah people are phones
are always ringing off the hook if
you would like to leave us a
voicemail you can just dial
hag claims eight the number eight just
style that don't tell anything else no
a wild hag running around killing eight
people
nice can you imagine eight people dying
at the same time that would be
crazy but at the end of a
hag yeah yeah
i shudder to think it'd be crazy
anyway we're gonna play these voicemails that
some people left us are a producer
madoff producer is going to play them
hit it matt
hello everyone i love the show i
have a question for everybody um i
actually took paul's recommendation to read the
alan carr book on how to stop
smoking and i have quit vaping for
like a month now those really great
recommendation thank you so much paul
um i am my question is first
gotten lauren did they have a book
that really changed their life like like
this one has for me and i
think for paul in the paul did
you have another book that was really
effective in your life love about these
guys that was such a sweet message
first of all congrats on that
absolutely congrats congrats on leaving that message
hercules reminded me of this a number
that we used to call in chicago
when i was in college there was
this number and it was this i
don't know who did this and maybe
someone out there knows about this it
was the cafeteria lady the lunch lady
you call her and she had a
really sweet acts like that
really sweet voice and she would say
huh hey baby the lunch tomorrow is
going to be mashed potatoes we got
green beans we have a really nice
piece of chicken and you are just
going to love it i love you
so much we've a great day and
then you just hang up and that
was it it was just that was
just a different lunch every day it
was for your school or no it
was
funny i don't know it was just
like fur it was just random everyday
she changed it wow i know isn't
that funny i kind of love it
i wonder if anyone out there knows
what i'm talking about it's like moviefone
for lunch yeah it was really fun
but you had lunch davao boxcar
ah i remember reading a book about
so this is in my early twenties
i don't i don't know the title
but i remember it was about relationships
and it was about
i remember it being about how like
there are different types of people in
the world shit what was it about
i just remember the gist so it
changed your life the database just if
it is like a successful relationship is
usually with two people who
i have a lot of stuff going
on interesting in their own lives and
then they meet up at the end
of the day and they check in
with each other about their own lives
and they hear about each other's own
lives and an alessi not being codependent
yes i think it was about codependency
it was a less successful relationship is
to people who are constantly wondering what
the other person is doing
and or like sitting around the house
letting the other person shine and while
they don't do anything or whatever and
so i remember that being kind of
like yes that's the type of relationship
i want is with someone who has
their own thing going on and is
not just sitting around waiting for me
to do stuff you know so yeah
i'm trying to think if i you
know i think i had different moments
with books where it was like like
read like eckhart totally or whatever then
i was like yes and then i
stopped you know thinking about any of
that so i don't know that there
was like a book that really stuck
with me forever that changed something for
me in that way other than just
being books i enjoyed reading
um but maybe one day i'll have
that book dealing with the public i
could think of that kind of had
a big impact on my life was
ah
it was a story it was well
as greatest story ever told yeah it
was about a carpenter wasn't it yeah
it's about a carpenter from a place
called nazareth
oh i do remember friend of mine
giving me zen and the art of
motorcycle maintenance i read which was supposed
to be some kind of you were
supposed to get something out of that
mind blowing yeah i remember liking it
but i i remember going into it
going like oh is this about how
to fix a motorcycle and then realising
it was a
a narrative like yeah a little ways
in and then kind of reading it
and going like yeah it was fine
i don't remember every single thing about
yeah i mean obviously the fountainhead is
how i tried to live my life
yeah of course atlas shrugged yeah yeah
um how to how to influence people
what is that book called how to
win friends and influence most people yes
how did you meet your books and
they smashed them together more value for
the buck
um but yeah i mean i don't
read a ton of self help books
so yeah i prefer to let other
people help me yeah yeah i've had
periods of time where i enjoy a
self-help book but now is not one
of them there's not one that really
feels like it you know like the
cartel was the power of now i
remember thinking it was all about like
lee
being in the moment but um my
name is called the knauer
yeah i can sit of our you
know sort of the power now the
knauer
i'm for books about pirates and what's
that
what's a pirate yeah you've never seen
a book that and obviously when you
were a little kid about a pie
never there was
yeah well known is the concept of
pirates winner what does it introduce to
people because i remember reading treasure island
and going like oh i know what
these are
actually i know it from a cartoon
who cares about pirates why are we
so obsessed as a culture with pirates
third all this eating the sun yeah
they love each other bad they're fun
they're swashbuckling you make your own family
they did yeah pirates have a chosen
family and i think that's beautiful yeah
so sweet
alright let's hear another voicemail vm as
we call it
hello this is joe i got a
question i'm on my way actually quit
my job oh and i'm just wondering
if the three of you have any
good job putting story
yeah i love to hear it that's
really all lucky guy wow great day
hi good how are you joe i
hope that went well
i thought i did too but i
think the only job i ever got
to quit and not be fired from
or have the business go out of
business out from under me was when
i did telemarketing which was the the
worst job i ever had and there
was a i worked there for about
a year and then
then um towards the end of the
year i'd gone home for thanksgiving this
was out here in l a i
got home for thanksgiving has a really
nice visit with family and friends
just for a few days and then
when i came back i had to
go back to work and it was
payday and i went in and got
my check and then i like went
to the threshold of where the phone
room was and i just turned around
and left i just couldn't do it
and you didn't get your check
no i did get my check oh
okay i won't get my check first
and i left i didn't say anything
to anybody wow nobody ever called like
nobody cared they didn't quiet quit i
was saying oh it's quite possible and
i'm sure that that happened all the
time that people just didn't show up
again
yeah you know when you run a
soulless operation but it was tough because
i had no plan you know what
i mean i did not have another
job lined up i had no other
means of income at the time but
i just i just could not do
it
trying to think if i have any
good so i mean mostly they just
involve me going in and saying like
hey i got i got a better
job and i'm going yeah i figured
my neurologist me like dreading going with
everything in my being every second of
the time i wasn't there to the
point i'm just like i have to
call them then i would quit and
then i would sheepishly go pick up
whatever money there was and that's what
i did
i mean i used to fantasize about
you know tearing off my servers apron
like kobe bryant in the middle of
a game you know tearing off his
jersey and just throwing it you know
in the middle of the the restaurant
or whatever but yeah now you just
just kind of just quit and said
hey i'm moving on um yeah i
never really had
like a big confrontation with a boss
either really oh i mean i got
fired from marie calendar's for drinking we
all know that but we all know
that story yeah for by the banana
lady
yeah but ah yeah you got your
revenge with that story oh man i've
been milking that it's a famous story
for thirty five years this um but
ah no unfortunately i never got did
i ever quit bob and david know
everything just evaporated usually that's in show
a business everything just evaporate yeah i
don't have to quit anymore
yeah because they show business quits you
yeah what a country yep
should we play a creature yeah okay
okay this feature is called this happened
to me submitted by rosalie mutta you
will tell a short memory that happened
or didn't happen to you with the
other players names and dates should match
even if the story is fabricated agree
however if you go with a fake
store
an altered scene or plot from a
movie the other players have to guess
if that was a real memory or
a fabricated one and if they say
it's fabricated they have to guess the
movie the scenes from example it was
ninety ninety five my friends decided to
pierce my ear at summer camp ice
was placed on my ear and then
a lemon was placed to catch the
needle this was from lindsay lohan's parent
trap
yeah okay okay first
i mean it's a second to think
well memory okay
i mean one the one thing i
can think of that comes to mind
immediately is in nineteen seventy two when
i came back from the army i
yeah
my father was the head of a
crime family
why is that funny too
let's examine that why is that funny
to you
so now you got your families and
this happened in nineteen seventy two you're
laughing at your killing bay remember laughing
at the army you were remembering it
happened in thank you so do you
remembered when this happened i was telling
people about it nineteen seventy two whose
stories about you telling the story he
has episode forty
okay never mind um okay let's do
this no no no no i'm just
going anyway i'm trying to think of
um either a memory or
how i'm told all of our memories
i know we've told all our memories
um okay okay i do i do
have a story alright i was working
in a restaurant
and a manager came in wearing all
yellow and she was she'd been crying
the year was nineteen eighty one
me and my friend new year's eve
were playing a video game and our
goal is to turn the game over
which is to reset the score yeah
you get a score so high that
eventually goes back to zero
our aim is to do this before
the clock strikes twelve
at midnight
we are listening to a top forty
radio station
we are playing the game we're making
it happen we're trading off asking the
controller to each other
and it's getting down to the wire
exactly at eleven bongs of the clock
we turned the game over we celebrated
and then we went to sleep
wow that was gripping that was gripping
um
i'm gonna say that was a real
story
or i'm gonna say
it's not real and it's from freaks
and geeks
scott is correct it was a real
story wow you know so bayberry did
it i can't remember the name of
the game but i love it but
i was like um it was an
intellivision game remember intelligent ninety yeah yeah
terrible controller because they have the disc
right yeah and televisions like we're gonna
crush you atari nope
sorry it's like our ceo i'm gonna
kick jay's ass
um alright um here's what did i
do it right yeah we know you
did it i was okay it sounded
like a movie
when i was a teenager this is
just a small memory when i was
a teenager anytime i would be
ah god i can't do this
anytime i would be reading a book
in public my people in my town
would just like
be obsessed with me and talk about
me and how i'm a little odd
sometimes that even sing a song about
me kind of altogether about how i
was weird and they just couldn't put
their finger on it but they always
thought something was good about me but
there really wasn't any weird i just
like reading books was the same town
where there was a
monster man who lived in a castle
the beast yeah he was a guy
like
like you were weird yeah they kind
of i know and then when we
were together it was like oh hell
broke loose like yeah channels like that
was alive people wouldn't shut oh wow
yeah i'm talking about talking teapot
that was just a blip in their
lives actually got to be people get
at a certain point it's not like
you are strange you were the strange
one because of books i know except
this is my point you know yeah
that's just provincial france
i think this is a real story
it is okay it does me my
friends ah one new year's eve
okay i have one
i forgot all the stories that take
place in new jersey
okay when i was fifteen my family
took a family trip to australia down
under as they call it
um and we went to the beach
one day in sydney and um
was with some friends i didn't really
know anybody but i met some people
that day um some like other kids
i mean you know fifteen year olds
um and we were just kind of
like playing around throwing a football around
and um then i saw out in
the water i saw ah
it was like a i could tell
is a body it couldn't tell if
it was a man or a woman
like sort of flailing a little bit
like you know so and i was
pretty close to it and i looked
back and there wasn't a lifeguard so
i went out out there and it
was pretty shallow so it was like
there was really nothing going on but
it was this girl who had gotten
a cramp
um and you know i
i'm not gonna say i saved her
life or that she nearly drowned you
know but ah it was you know
i helped her out at least you
know when we end we ended up
dating and we got together and all
again stuff anyway
i think that's fake and i think
it's grease
yeah it is greece
okay alright yeah yeah
let's see
um
thanks to recover your own memory yeah
i'm trying to think of what what
happened in my life just think of
yesterday
with yester the movie
remember no one knew who the beatles
were anymore
i remember there was one halloween where
i mean my friends went out trick
or treating and there was this um
scary house in the neighborhood that we
always dared each other like go up
and touch the door whatever and halloween
was especially scary to do this and
um and i remember my friend went
up and touch
at the door
and then a guy came out and
you went on a killing spree
i think that's true when he killed
a bunch of people he got a
bunch of people did he kill you
no no oh cool oh i was
just a witness to all of this
oh you witnessed every single death i
didn't want this every single death i
witnessed about five deaths i think right
out the street yeah cool okay that
reminds me of a memory a real
memory from when i was growing up
that um
my friends and i um we loved
to hang out and that's normal i
think and at the time a friend
was like do you guys want to
see a dead body and he suggested
that we kind of walk along the
train tracks
um and just through the town until
we came to where the dead body
was so your friend knew that there
was a dead body there not just
that hey if we want to change
back far enough will probably yeah i
would say today is like asking me
hey do you want to die right
now and he's taking me too yeah
kill me somewhere yeah yeah um it
wasn't that
that it was that there was really
this person who'd who'd passed and they
were playing there
yeah that really happened fuck yeah i
know
oh that's crazy yeah that's real that's
real israel through its kids i remember
i remember ah this was probably in
the mid nineties me and my best
friend um his name was beavis we
this is gonna
roche
across america we sort of did because
because the whole country yeah
anyway nut there was like an lsd
trip and stuff like that but it
was i don't really remember anything else
happening i remember when we were kids
in maine and um
ah we were little kids we were
like a tight knit group of ah
outcasts freaks and nerds and um well
we found that there was a clown
that lived in the sewer
and isn't that what talked to about
weird that always happens it was so
this is like the thing i ah
kids today don't understand but if you're
an eighties kid you get it yeah
um sounds were clowns like they lived
exclusively in sewers back then they weren't
all bad either some were found out
they were great in fact if you
eh
like you if you were the proprietor
of a circus and you need to
hire clowns you would just go to
the sewers yell hey throw a man
oh yeah and they wanted jobs so
they were kind of always tend to
weightings yeah because their dream was to
live in an apartment so yeah um
so there's other all high rises because
they made so much money exam
exactly don't even get me started on
the clown uprising so i remember this
rising homage like real bad um and
then we felt stupid because even though
one of us did get killed he
turned out to be just a big
spider from outer space matter okay that's
crazy that you didn't realize that
he looks i'm telling you if you
saw him he looked like a clown
okay do a picture yeah writer okay
yeah that looks like a cloud that
looks exactly like no way oh wait
you turned to this it's lenticular
outer space k you didn't return yeah
we never looked at him sideways oh
we always looked at him straight on
i have one deep in the eyes
oh okay good
so back in like this was the
ninety s i was like
i guess you would say i was
like a paleontologist and i loved dinosaurs
sure and i die no dna right
i got involved in this like wasn't
like a museum it was like it
wasn't an amusement park wasn't a zoo
it was kind of like all of
the above combine
which i thought was a great idea
and i sort of was brought in
to like um check out you know
these dinosaurs that have been made um
from the dna that they found in
like amber and fossils and stuff oh
i know and that's the only way
to do it it was a really
big thing so like we kind of
made
dinosaurs and they were aggressive and oh
i know it every couple years one
of them would get out or be
like kind of untenable will probably shut
that program down right no they kept
doing it they kept doing it yeah
okay they are interrelations they eventually clone
humans now
no the cutters kept thinking it'd be
fun to see a train of thought
i'm pretty sure they did nope they
just started be cool to see a
t rex okay never wow no never
ever did that pretty much appealing until
they never because this was my this
was just like my job right as
paleontologists who worked at this place did
you ever meet any stupid ass girls
who worked the computer
yeah yeah there was this girl who
was always yell oh yes okay well
i don't really think of people that
way just um so she was always
scared yeah um but yeah she didn't
die so i'll see her again yeah
yeah yeah
good yeah that's real that's that's that's
true obviously we played that game and
thank you to whoever sent that in
if you'd like to send us friends
early matter you can write to three
usa at gmail dot com listen that's
our show everybody that's our show yeah
do you want your ad-free episodes of
this go to stitcher premium or
or cbp world and that's going to
do it for us and look hey
keep leaving those voicemails because we just
answered two of them we're not liars
no we're not liars we're not we
tell the truth always while we love
to tell the truth and then there's
another podcast that always tells lies yep
yeah um but look sorry about the
zoom ah
needs must as the devil drives and
all that next time we'll be back
needs must as the devil drives you
heard me alright
but we're gonna be back in person
next time i swear to you swear
to you i swear to be was
a chance gives way to be getting
one more chance please baby please please
just this is what we had to
do with what we had to do
for right now alright goodbye bye
yeah
uh