hi i'm paul f tompkins hello i'm
nicole parker and we have a podcast
that we have done together this is
true it's coming out on stitcher premium
yes it is it's called the neighborhood
listen yes it is based on all
those neighborhood apps you might know what
they are you go on and it
talks about the goings on of your
neighborhood priorities or you
no mail that's missing what was that
helicopter all about were those gunshots or
fireworks that sort of actually were improvising
in character we have special guests also
improvising in character inspired by posts from
the actual apps that we have on
our phones yeah they can't take that
away from us cats so don't forget
go on stitcher pr
premium get yourself your account and listen
to the neighborhood listen tuesdays starting september
seventeen join us won't you you will