show your lake oh no this is
a disaster
oh my god your right
damn it
this time i'm probably going to nail
it yeah
no you don't
paul you're off your game boy oh
boy what happened to me today and
i know a g for lunch in
the last week since we've seen each
other i ate for lunch ah seven
hot dogs seven hotdogs every day fifty
five hamburger
we had forty nine hotdogs wow yeah
it's a lot of hot dogs if
you think about it to eat to
eat no to have around the house
sure it's a good it's a good
amount you know what it's a lot
of hotdogs to just see forty nine
hot dogs i don't think i could
fit forty nine in my eyeballs i
would be like i gotta close these
things the fucker you are you mean
seeing seeing them yeah i thought you
meant
nt trying to cram hotdogs in your
eyeballs i've tried to get that it
why because there's these little tiny cracks
in your eyes that things can fit
in if you try real hard what
are you talking about this guy's like
the corners of your here let me
poke you know
it's not a crack in my eye
our eyes are so delicate and it's
freaky isn't it crazy that you're there
just out there all the time it's
scaring it's like when i had that
ah that speck of dust when i
walked through the construction site in a
speck of dust went into my eye
and i had to wear that eyepatch
for like months alright and and then
i remember like so
nobody tried to pull that speck of
dust out they had a plank in
their own eye yes and you were
like you're a hypocrite
and he was jesus christ also you
know what if you have a plank
in your eye know like and we're
trying to get a speck of dust
on somebody else's i i think you're
being very nice yeah it's a nice
thing to do i mean like and
i'm assuming he's at work he's an
ophthalmologist or something nobody wants a speck
of dust in there i do think
if fishy
idea oh yeah i want a tear
here is the idea in the bible
that you're pulling the speck out of
your neighbor's eye for aesthetic reasons you're
like pleases news doesn't fit in with
the h away now i don't personally
know this story it's not even if
you ever read the bible no oh
you got not even part of it
i've read part of it was on
a podcast that dan klein did where
they read the bible when i read
i was the only bible you've ever
read well sure i read passages here
and there which passages task is i
don't really know lying only are they
all just out of sight whoa like
i'm just interested in me as someone
who didn't grow up religious yeah
good page doesn't come up a lot
would have to read what occasion would
like someone's wedding where they have a
paper that has like oh yeah like
a thing in it or like evolve
love i am like a clanging gong
yeah it's really um yeah and i
mean it just doesn't come up ah
much at all i would say you
know it's
funny how little the bible comes up
in your life if you are not
actively trying to insert it yeah life
yeah yeah yeah is the okay so
christianity my theory on it is oh
no here we go worst part about
it is the part where they because
i remember just being at church and
going like hey this is all cool
until like around ten or something when
pm ten pm yeah suddenly the freaks
were coming
no check them out at night to
church because i'm mad i teacher trish
um no at like ten years old
i remember one of the the pastor
saying okay it's not good enough that
you are a christian part of being
a christian is you have to go
actively recur
fruit all the time and if you
know anyone who's not a christian you
have to convince them to be one
or else you can't hang out with
him anymore it's ok not to do
that
i think normalize not doing that's like
the root of all of the problems
in in like religious you know behavior
i think is is the evangelizing part
of it how many people do you
think that are the this is people
getting mad if i say this oh
but people that are that are true
christians that actually
really are compassionate loving people as opposed
to just what feels like very american
christianity which is like just judgment yeah
we're right that's that's what yeah it
seems like it all is yeah if
you're not a christian you're a bad
person yeah like how many people do
you think that are christ like i
mean not even christ was like that
because he
cursed then victory oh he hated that
fig tree he was he was angry
and he was angry it's the first
recorded instance of hanger oh he'll shoreline
the term do you know the story
um no this one is walking down
the street the other day okay he's
hungry
he goes to a fig tree i
think this is at a point where
he's like he's he's over the whole
thing i think i'm going to be
crucified yeah okay so he's going it's
kind of sinking in he's like this
whole plenary two and a half yeah
and so he's in the middle i
feel like in this this is my
hazy recollection of this he's in the
middle of giving something lesnar
back someday when he's full of righteous
anger and then he he's hungry once
to get a fig from this fig
tree fig tree doesn't have any figs
on it so he fuckin curses it
to wither and never bear fruit again
and i think the fig tree is
a metaphor for a woman wow
stretching himself
ah
i'm staying out of it you're saying
out of it because we have i
don't play don't know well i know
we have religious listeners i think religions
fine if you want to do it
and just keep it to yourself that's
that's my tip on religion but it
is i you know of course the
gva ball the thing is you're trying
to the idea
is you're trying to save people by
converting them to christianity yeah here it
is the parable of the barren fig
tree not to be confused with parable
of the budding fig tree there's ana
to fig really ever heard of but
i wouldn't get confused because they have
very different abilities yeah um
wait a minute this is terrible not
that jesus did it himself oh does
he oh he talks about it as
if someone else did it a man
had a fig tree planted in his
vineyard then he came looking for fruit
on her found that so he said
to the gardener see here for three
years i've come looking for it see
here see i don't think it's a
fruitless fig tree and still i find
none cut it down
why should be wasting the soil he
replied sir let it alone for one
more year until i dig around it
and put manure on it the bears
fruit next year well in boardman hours
in the bible they just don't believe
he's said any of the stuff that
you're saying it feels kind of sounds
like the one about the budding victory
yeah because that one i know really
well
jesus
like when i just put up jesus
curse it auto auto completes to the
fig tree so you read it okay
well here we go this is from
mark eleven twelve through twenty five thank
you mark the next day as they
were leaving bethany jesus was in bethany
by this issue
ramage is written in sarcastic tone i
think so yeah okay we all had
italics jesus was hungry seeing in the
distance a fig tree in leaf he
went to find out if it had
any fruit when he reached it he
found nothing but leaves because it was
not the season for figs well that
makes it worse yeah
yeah it's not even the season for
figs then he said to the tree
may know whatever eat fruit from you
again
and his and guess what his disciples
heard him say
he's added to the tree
people heard him stupid tree
yeah like he was like my no
one barefoot or i weren't like what
not nothing oh okay i feel like
you say something you hear what he
said did you remember things she's done
that cheek hers to that tree it's
inanimate object it's just a tree dude
get over it it's not even it's
next season what did you expect
spec to you think this alone i
think invalidates christ as worthy of founding
a religion upon yeah i am and
i would say they talk about how
he's never sinned
add sin i think that's a step
counts wrath yeah if that's not wrath
what is what is wrath cursing someone
as a sin
i mean just do
like i'm not getting to get almost
almost one i just ask you a
question not always trying to investigate not
not getting what you want
for no fault of the other thing
and then and then ah enacting consequences
because you didn't get what you want
that is a sin because you were
acting without the proper information that's on
you and by the way fig trees
are not just there to give everyone
figs all the time no no although
did people own
trees back then no you will out
yeah render unto caesar what is caesar's
sees around the trees okay geezer on
the tree caesar made the salad that
was a commercial when i was a
kid you these kid givers who made
the salad caesar made the salad i
had a great caesar salad yesterday oh
my god tell a lot everything
a good caesar salad is really good
you know it really is and wanted
to really mixed you know the dressings
really tossed almost like every single segment
has dressing on it do you like
the chose do i like a toad
do you like a show and toby's
um you know what i never would
notice or complaint if they're in there
it's not the kind of thing that
i'm really worried about i never think
about it if they are if they're
like finely chop it a tiny tiny
tiny i always stayed away from them
because they they look like little slugs
yeah oh no i don't eat that
but but then i
yeah very enough when i worked at
of course cafe koryo
the little slugs they made them with
the with the full anchovies in there
and they were delicious and so i
said you know this is paul's and
disbelief that that hasn't really come up
for me but i don't know that
it served that way that i'm in
disbelief yeah you looked at hers her
it like the pig trades beyond love
tiny with very nervous eyes ah didn't
happen wrong
false i think i think they i
wouldn't memorize that whole day africa yeah
what is it it's a super kind
of jonathan frakes so he did a
couple of cows yes i want to
memorize it so i can do the
entire thing shed because it's funny how
long has it is fifteen minutes how
long do you
think you could do right now off
seventeen minutes what more i can do
it i can add a couple
how much of pi could you reckon
you can recognise how much of pi
could you memorize if you had to
if you hope to here's what i
don't gun to your head three-point well
yeah for the end
that's it be just fine it should
end there yeah you know what i
mean it's sad what are we doing
good but it doesn't you know what
by the way what what what do
we get out of pi what what
does i know it doesn't mean there's
no point isn't exactly it's got it's
own symbol and shit radius knew about
it by it's like hey coindesk
mr i'm ok here just saying three
or four i don't need something in
between why did that one character on
season two of the wire have it
tattooed on the back of his neck
he did never seen that so when
hub were having um escobar almost double
escobar
the follow omar
he is the brother of another famous
actor what tom cruise you know how
a little cruise
wait third republic is yeah the band
i can't believe i'm playing in his
last name um and now trying couples
trying to place his okay what game
his brother well but i can't remember
his hollow wire character thank you that
chant that should get you right there
nick so bought ca xhaka please
played by a pablo schreiber dr ram
i worked with him on orange is
the new black but i received them
while i worked yeah here's an orange
is the new mom you owe him
on whatnot i worked with him on
a independent film ah and it was
a brief scene beware duty i was
it was brief nudity
i showed my penis for one second
but but people could freeze on it
yeah no it was unfeasible that's that
was in my control guy so frickin
gone girl yeah he should have put
that just kanye yeah but no um
kevin bacon and wild things ah bruce
willis in the color of night
three major penises in ceremony ted danson
a three minute little ape i don't
remember that once your embassy
you ever seen ted dances dick and
some little lady
ah yeah have you ever walked in
on the bathtub
it's just it's just casual like a
periscope they're just hanging out chatting yeah
it's not like a sexy scene it's
just yeah it's a dozen starts just
like playing with the bubbles and you'll
briefly see his penis ah
he reveals this oh what are we
to all you work with so i
played a james lipton type aa interviewer
viewing his character who was a famous
actor and um it was fun that's
fun um i also interviewed him for
that show speak easy that i used
to do and at the end i
am
accidentally called him we have schreiber wow
oh no the identity fortified i don't
like mic setup up at all he
was of course he was not pleased
about that and thankfully the editors left
it in good like that didn't need
to be in awe why they never
would never occurred to me that i
would have to say oh
by the way cut out the part
where i called the guest the wrong
name yeah yeah shh that's so no
they also i wanted to pitch that
as a tv show and the editors
put together a reel that did not
include me in it
it was just all the guests why
so i guess can be on anything
yeah they already are i don't get
that yeah i didn't get it either
needless to say nothing happened ah alright
but wait so in in the wire
yeah is this blue-collar do dock worker
guy right yes and he has a
he's the cousin of ziggy so
vodka that wayward rail your son of
nick's uncle frank sabol that's exactly correct
and he'll watch this someday and it'll
all you've ever seen go wire oh
my god you ever watch oh umar
newcomers the wire
guy can you imagine having to watch
every i mean it's a great show
so like eight seasons or something knows
much five one episode season yeah we
just like figure we get either people
like this i think it's if i
don't get that way if i remember
it's four seasons of thirty four season
of ten or thirteen and then the
the fifth season is like six or
eight team yeah yeah
yeah um but he has the pi
symbol tattooed on the back of his
neck and is it actually on his
body though and maybe that's a good
question and i don't know but either
way if it's actually his body cover
that shit up why did that character
actor has it made me question saying
well i'm gonna look up pablo schreiber
tattoo do
none of us have tattoos i think
we're the only tattoo is podcast yeah
that's incredible the only tattoo list podcast
a wild weight stay of home comes
is also tattoo liz podcast okay what
about
i mean i don't know add to
cart is not um bitch sesh do
we know if casey daniel of tattoos
questionnaire and i told him hold on
hold on there's
there's a reddit thread we don't have
tattoos halfway through season three with that
wondering why nick and season two has
a pie tattoo on the back of
his neck there you go oh my
god it's just deeper and deeper than
a bunch of people just surmising things
i think it's cause this tiny minuscule
deter
yale was probably my biggest gripe with
season two oh no i sound like
the person i cannot for the lowest
time you imagine a reason why nixon
buchu would ever have a tattoo like
this anyone know how hard it is
to cover tattoos my pine jesus christ
freaking out but now we don't so
we don't
no if the character if it's a
character tattoo or the actor's tattoo we
don't know i don't i don't know
that we'll ever know well why don't
you look up actor and the i
did plus tattoo and that's what came
up and then i looked at one
thing and then i stopped well then
there was another picture of like him
in another role where he had like
tattoos all over his body oh i'm
not sifting through all this is really
hard to figure out
out yeah you figured out two guys
you guys talked to each other let
me have a moment of peace while
i know i don't like to say
lauren hours yeah i'm fine how are
ah the it's very hard it's really
hot out and it's disgusting it's sucks
damn right now oh my gosh
like paul we're really having a hard
time without you on paul get back
here we need you paul okay i'm
michael scott we ever go horseback riding
again i really enjoy it when i
did the last last time we did
it oh no no the last thing
we did was that yeah at so
yeah i would yeah yeah at the
wine taste
same thing where i hurt my ankle
right but it wasn't from the horse
no no i told the story like
it was going to be from the
person it was me stepping in a
hole yes yes yeah um would you
ever go horseback every minute i spent
writing in many many years probably since
i was fourteen but i recently saw
some pals on instagram or on the
trail and in griffith park said it's
really fun and
then we were talking about going um
i would be interested i'm a little
nervous because trails and griffith park i
mean you know i've hiked up them
and stuff like yeah it's like a
horse goes but two horses go on
those yeah i've like when you're hiking
sometimes you'll have to go i don't
want to do that at all or
if there's like a dropoff yeah no
no no i wanna go on
a baby like a rattlesnake comes up
the horse goes your and you fall
to your death i don't want to
go on that i wonder how many
people have died that way on griffith
park horses i think a thousand a
day okay this is worse than the
clean back a re i've said this
before and i'll say it again horses
are so fucking big why are they
so scared of things that are so
much smaller than that i know just
step on it just step on or
or
or walk away yeah should be the
bigger horse so maybe they know it
maybe they know it's poisonous a rat
the rattle is there so that you
leafed the was like hey i can't
control myself maybe our horses have been
bitten by rattlesnake once in their life
and that's why things go they're like
oh not physic and thinks oh it's
license
where did you find out found
published drivers is skilled canadian american entertainer
the cast of candies most popular for
his depiction of nick's aback on the
wire also the entertainer showed up in
law and order special victims unit american
gods schreiber got a primetime emmy assignment
for outstanding guest actor in a drama
series for his job in orange is
the new black i admit pablo has
likewise been a piece of broadway shows
and his presentation made a chosen one
for a tony award
just published shriver have any tattoos and
their meaning candy actor explored publish schreiber
allegedly has no tattoos right now he
has no tattoos that could uncover a
specific significance driver has a decent constitution
and frequently shares shirtless pictures on a
few web-based entertainment oh good notwithstanding
no tattoos have been seen till now
tae bo has additionally never discussed needing
tattoos future needing with the media yet
oh we are additionally not serious discuss
it at home we we we we
are additionally not certain about how affectionate
pablo is of tattoos in any case
the entertainer has of late featured in
the hulu
yeah he's named candy the show includes
a genuine wrongdoing mini series that recounts
the narrative canny montgomery the show has
been eagerly awaited in the fans can
hardly hold back to watch the show
the show will deliver on the thirteenth
of may twenty twenty two a progression
of genuine occasions in live in the
plot of the show schreiber is featured
close by a few well-known
entertainers in this show up until this
point the show's trailer has been delivered
and it has previously figured out how
to get the notice of many individuals
trailers you're down and meet pablo schreiber
new girlfriend on instagram publisher seems by
all accounts to be single all the
present time nonetheless he was originally pitched
to jessica monte they have two youngsters
together o basic all the time of
that was standing there is dr pablo
separated from the significant other and has
been single for quite a while according
to his web based entertainment the entertainer
appears to be single right now he
has not posted an image with somebody
who could be his soulmate
i have this image of someone who
could try so frequently post pictures with
his companions as two children on his
virtual entertainment accounts publish reproduce your entertainment
account yeah like instagram pablo schreiber networth
explore publish drivers assessed total assets is
four million as per the sun and
there's been essential for a few calling
up he said
how much do this profession for gallion
time really go oh wait this is
the last is the last paragraph schreiber
is exceptionally capable and has been in
media outlets for quite awhile now considering
his fruitful acting vocation it isn't stunning
that pablo has aggregated a powerful amount
of cash all through his profession pablo
is by all accounts living
serenely with his vocation income wow was
hard to believe that ai is putting
systems you can live serenely yeah i'd
love that that's really nice with my
vocation income i would love to live
zarina i know i know but it
doesn't always work that way these people
thinking like true deer he wouldn't get
a pi tattoo like his character wouldn't
why because
he's a stupid dock worker like stupid
people get dumb tattoos and stuff all
the time it's not that he's stupid
it's that there's nothing in the character
doesn't talk about his deferred today march
fourteenth now that would make sense to
me what if he says to this
his first episode you know my birthday
march fourteenth and no one has put
together yeah my birthday
three days after my birthday three period
one for period blank the year i
was born alright we have sig break
okay
and we're back and have you learned
if you ever thought about getting a
tattoo i recently sort of had the
urge like a couple of weeks ago
i was like thinking about that randomly
and but i was like but i
really still don't i really don't know
what it would be
i really feel like i have to
really like whatever it is cause i
could see myself because you wanted it
like aesthetically somewhere and yeah be cool
to have something there yeah but i
meant even you know spot as much
as i sort of understood people getting
them more and not that i don't
understand it but i mean for me
it's always been like i need to
have a very specific
the thing right other people are more
like indiscriminate about what again i think
that's also cool and i think once
you get one you're more open to
getting up on trent it's less like
a big deal but i um i
think would have to be very finely
drawn and i think it should be
small and i have to really like
it what about i don't know dog
if it looks like a cartoon character
i should like an artist read wow
wow i really wish i could see
that dog yeah it didn't look good
it looks like turn it around it's
brain and be like wow huh and
try draw force yeah
um
do you guys have any other buddy
look at dog they chose brand is
fully explore yeah falling out slide i've
never i've never seriously thought about getting
a tattoo probably the most i thought
i ever gave it was when i
was in my twenties and started to
know people who had tons of tattoos
and
thinking about what would it be but
i never there was never any image
that i could ever generate there was
like yes that's it yeah
i think growing up it was it's
so strange because i think growing up
in a religious household there are things
that the bible doesn't talk about that
just my household considered to be sins
or whatever and so getting a tattoo
was like
i don't know whether it was considered
a sin or something that you just
shouldn't do is something my family was
really yeah against it my i my
parents were like oh my mom was
always like you don't ever get a
tattoo remember when i'm protecting us from
getting teenage things or something but i
don't know maybe they're one of the
people at our church had one he
had ah an anchor i believe on
his arm flash
epic classic and it was always like
anytime he would be in shirtsleeves it
would be like oh my god he
has a tattoo and my parents explained
it away of like oh he was
in the navy yeah look at that
again took forearms his legs are a
blight why is he fighting that guy
named brutus brutus
oh wow hey god that is a
great picture i love it yeah yeah
you should gotta do that i'm three
put on the three-time page when this
episode ascended to you there was also
a thing of people that there's so
few people that have one tattoo yeah
yeah and i think he used to
be like when you were in the
navy or something
if you get one to be like
hey i'm in this group or whatever
i'm i got when i was doing
my doctor who i'm still in my
doctor who rocked a hoo ha vanderpump
i watched it on the plane so
it's watching my gym it's a solo
mission yeah and then when we call
it we call it going to work
day is like well we gotta get
back to work
no punch the clock we're in season
five now we just passed the new
orleans episodes legendary time in the show's
history um but the third doctor it's
so funny that we watched so much
reality and yet you picked a show
that neither of us have seen i
know it's strange i mean i've seen
the recent season that was coy
that's a bitcoin so that's that's okay
so i know that people he's talking
about you know what the scan tool
is and don't tell me and i
have seen clips from the past of
things happening but i've just vague notions
of what when they showed like black
and white but then there's one thing
in color yeah that's their that's only
do the flashback um so the third
doctor
in his first episode a man named
jon pertwee was the actor um who
was in world war two and his
first episode has a scene where
he is trying to hide from some
people so he takes off his clothes
and he gets in a shower in
this locker room and you see like
that's how i like to hide from
people this is fucking green puts on
a shower cap and it's like singing
your song yeah like scrubbing in the
show like running away you wouldn't be
the person doing i mean they're not
chasing
him they're just looking ok so but
you see we were looking for a
head closer you see not only zealand
does he have like a shower he
doesn't get a tattoo on his arm
right because he was in the hip
i think it was linked the merchant
marines is right but you also see
like kind of his upper ass like
you see his tan line and the
white of his what episode is this
i gotta check
this out time stamp it's so weird
it's very very one as well as
their wiki my years on theirs wikihouse
of course this was the late sixth
late sixty s yeah it's crazy it's
pretty shocking yeah um and they never
explained the tattoo way of like oh
the doctor got a tattoo or it
wasn't was he regenerating rejected and
what i got a tattoo you imagine
you're a whole new body and there's
a tattoo always already doctor ever regenerated
as a baby and then that and
then like thirty years later we catch
up with him and he's whoever i've
waited my whole life show starring a
toddler i would not mind but it's
just doing nostra toddler stuff and there
yeah yeah alright alright well
i think that waiting for him to
grow up so he saves the world
yeah actually zine good doctor who episode
is like he regenerates and he's a
baby it's like oh no he did
one time become so old that he
became a tiny little creature i know
is there really no episode where he's
a baby know that feels like a
feels like come on what are we
doing but there's like a zillion eps
assos i feel like they would have
eventually gotten there i think we have
seen him in flashbacks as a child
or they i shouldn't say yeah wild
yeah but i don't think as a
as a baby maybe not well yeah
the original well anyway we're getting way
but yeah but so the different doctors
all represent one person yeah but every
time same person
same person yeah every time they die
oh i thought it was just like
we're revealing this story with a woman
now and it's this oh it's it's
like a clever thing where like the
first doctor who had to have to
bolt and so they were like we
don't want to end the show right
and so yeah he was getting a
little too frail to do the show
anymore so they came up with the
idea of regeneration
in in which that it'll be the
same character but he'll just look different
yeah huh and so and it's genie
although they said a number on it
that seemed unattached unobtainable at the time
i was like fourteen or something like
twelve twelve yeah okay like well it's
never gonna never get to read dr
yeah and they passed twelve already and
had to justify it yeah yeah but
yeah it's it's very
the inch in and in fact when
reggie left comedy bang bang we were
considering having him regenerates sue whoever that
person was but we liked the episode
we came yeah yeah okay yeah you
like it you don't have regrets about
it i don't know if that episode
no regrets um and then do you
have a tattoo you want to know
i so so
so i just i i also think
that okay growing up in the eighties
i also feel like the nancy reagan
thing of like just say no people
make fun of it but i also
think it kind of worked in a
way because like people would offer me
drugs i'd be like oh no thanks
you know and it's like instead of
ever getting gilded into it it was
like no yeah and so this couldn't
be just say no thing
i know a little bit of manners
never hurting no bitch yeah people are
trying to like people are always trying
to destroy your life sometimes like they're
like alright yeah they're just trying to
give you a good time huh really
but yeah so i never wrote goat
i'd never even throat goat
you guys miss this world going about
nancy reagan no what about her she
used throat coat throw goat she was
the goat of all throats
just like legendarily oh that's right oh
i did hear that i've never heard
a remote ghost thirty was throat goat
that's so because i try deeply i'm
saying this to you the term goat
wasn't popularized until l cool j popularize
no they didn't call her
that back then oh okay i know
they did she's a roco okay she
would like to is really good greatest
of all time jobs got to get
bigger
she's your choice and then going back
a bucket line will freak me out
how bad another throat good thanks
oh wow what was that noise oh
do you oh no he never got
hurt do you think jimmy stewart oh
hey you probably shouldn't get one from
ronald reagan than from this
you ever just poem i used to
love yeah oh cowboy what was this
oh it was the tripping on the
ninety six step or whatever no okay
let me let me read up so
i used to love jimmy stewart movies
so okay not fucking jimmy stewart i
wasn't in love with him
i was normal i wasn't obsessed i
didn't write letters to him i did
not show up at his house okay
um but ah yeah but you know
my parents constantly trying to figure out
you know gifts for me that were
thoughtful and i feel bad because like
who knows what i was into it
any particular very hard to do this
so by the one of the
guy blinking
oh gifts with a t
you're talking about a specific jimmy stewart
poem
like this guy okay oh boy k
k was aged eight stared into the
sog um so they got me this
book that i'm looking at right now
jimmy stewart and his poems and i'm
just like i don't give a fuck
about this guy's poetry jordan his poems
the top stuff and the hotel and
june is made
like the devil is meeting jesus that's
mean i guess yeah it's like a
step video any he would he would
read it on carson all the time
and it would be like the same
poem i don't know probably why you
are here again he would he would
definitely read different poems because i'm looking
at well well this i will real
dracula help
throughout his dubstep okay jimmy stewart doing
dracula go yeah oh good good good
evil
i vote to suck your blood i
don't drink vi
oh i'm a bot
laura laura join us come on only
episode have five only really seen what's
wonderful it's a wonderful life yeah that's
i mean that's his best movie what
i don't think fires in that
there probably are i mean okay so
he goes that's interesting he goes to
that dance at night yeah with all
kids who are like are now do
you think vampires are real yeah i
would say like is going to crowd
scene in a movie ten percent of
the popular actually vampires okay yeah what's
more realistic to you aliens or vampires
more realistic
what's more likely to be something we're
going to encounter okay i would say
aliens are more realistic although i'm not
necessarily in the camp these days who
are like oh yeah all these whistleblowers
are telling the truth i think like
they're all insane
it's like their city government i think
that's real okay you think the government's
insane
um i so i think aliens are
more real than vampires i don't think
there's any evidence of any vampires i
don't think there's any i think i
don't think there's any event i will
jane and i were talking about the
aliens last night and she thinks she's
thinking like i'm i'm she was saying
i'm starting to think they're
actually going to come like their actual
wow and i said
i welcome them either way either they're
going to come and save us from
ourselves or they're gonna come and obliterate
us isn't that saving us from ourselves
you know
i will tell the aliens what i
tell ants when they come into my
house there's nothing but death for you
here yes what you say to ants
until it's give your aunt telepathy to
all your own friends there's nothing but
death for you leave us alive and
say go tell the others yeah
i feel like the alien thing is
sort of like the rapture we're all
like oh it's gonna come it's gonna
come we're all going to die and
it'll never happen okay but it might
happen after we die oh no and
then they get here and they're like
oh we waited oil and da
and it's god when we were listening
three of roscoe clean american quadrant i
can't believe your lifespans when a hundred
years you think there'll be an episode
of freedom on the golden record that
they play for aliens yeah they keep
updating it right yeah they keep calling
it back and those guys like long
stuff like it's like a long hour
of just us y'all shitting yeah
recently he was just stuff like lose
yourself and it's all eminem thinking based
but i think it's ninety percent emanating
and then then the real time our
team and stuff about imams and stuff
about him which is why our episode
will be up there yeah our taste
test episode that's right yeah it's on
theme is what gets done fleet they
need to be slightly out of the
flavor
ers are good so when they get
here they don't waste their time trying
every flavor if we if we have
done that as a service to the
aliens i'm proud do you think it
was a waste of our time to
try every flavor i enjoyed the best
use of time that we've ever had
to lately i feel like we need
to do more because there are a
lot more flavors you think can making
them yeah what was the flavor that
that we all texted each other and
we were
like whoa look at this from a
lot of christ yes was it kyle
dandy or something i don't remember i
don't remember but we should we should
definitely go seek that out yeah what
if we went to japan because they
have even more flavor over a house
together as a family do they do
eminem save a lot of kit kats
save a lot of a lot of
things he must have
lot of eminem's right i don't remember
seeing imams i don't know but sometimes
i feel i'm i don't know but
i am i'm thought we could just
go to like little tokyo and like
get some kind of global oh sure
we could go nice okay neighbors can
we look at our calendars we're all
going to go together oh to figure
out a time when we go to
japan go oh yeah little colors right
now little
okay little tokyo okay how many kid
kits you have here okay so what
about tomorrow no bad for me bad
for you yeah okay what about this
week's pretty rough yeah okay we'll go
to next week what about labor day
ah maybe yeah let's say maybe
maybe on labor day no maybe you
know what wait what are we trying
to get i don't know we just
said we would go to little tokyo
together um yeah let's just say maybe
on labor day say maybe on labor
maybe on babor may early on babe
huh savion glover savion famer
her savion glover right probably
i don't think it's ever come up
in conversation to me i don't think
anyone's ever mentioned him to me well
i'm proud to be the first yeah
that's great thanks the thing that stuff
dancer savion the the famous ted danson
penis
he has no his yeah he does
have a penis yeah and he's a
famous phoenix well yeah yeah um you
know that i'm only free on labor
day
um i yeah i just can't determine
that at this time but um yeah
i mean sure we seven am yeah
we'll go at seven a m
i think i'll
that would be really great
yeah let's try it's too late we
just rolled a little tokyo seven am
where i'm going and what kind of
candies do you have here where are
the funny items
yeah isn't it funny how the different
things are funny yeah it's kind of
funny funny equals different
you're a simple man i'm a simple
man funny equals different because in bible
study if i see four things that
are the same and a fifth one's
just different i think that's small
alright we have to think i've crossed
the oceans of ty find you are
nothing but death for you here on
this earth aliens oh man if jimmy
stir was in independence day yeah welcome
to earth
welcome back it's still three of them
and you're still you and guess what
it's time to listen to voice mails
you leave em we listen to them
yes good deal if you would like
to send us if you'd like to
leave us a voicemail don't send us
one leave us one just
leave us ones leave a voicemail take
a voicemail yeah take one away from
us you do chase taken on our
plate and you answer it if you
would like to call us you can
of course call us at hag claims
eight it's great alright this is from
wow let him say who
who he is but yeah yeah well
i'll let him tell you hi guy
hasn't been i'm one of your pithiest
little piggies
love your show but my question is
what is the most dangerous thing you
are either done or been a part
of when i was fourteen i got
a pitchfork stuck in my leg when
i worked at the devil it was
a big rusty metal pitchfork and i
used to have to get q tips
how can the whole make sure
ah this one time anyways great day
guys thanks for this i'm assuming that's
been solo i feel so good yeah
yeah otherwise known as kylo ren yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm deeply familiar
with um super senior we're done like
that like that kind of like most
dangerous let's do this
ben you heard it lawrence going stupid
this day if you stick your chips
in the holes they're not going to
heal up stupid oh my girl sky
hose again most dangerous thing god i'm
sure there's many i used to have
to think well i know i've told
this story before but one time i
was trying to assemble an ikea case
bookcase
and of course i did it wrong
the first time it falling like howard's
end
what i don't remember that for hours
isn't that how ah the the whole
climax of the movie not to give
spoilers for howards end but therein how
it oh it's so good paul you've
never seen our damn seen howards and
i just know the story but i
didn't know about a book oh my
god howard zinn
um that's like weaving we've kind of
seen it because of the inheritance ooh
yeah we all saw the inherit origin
inquiry i loved the inheritance yeah although
we were you know what we were
talking the other day paul you are
in character saying that plays that were
split up and took all day should
be illegal and then what the
first thing that pops in my head
was did he not like the inheritance
i forget oh yeah because it was
all right yeah android yes yes yes
yes well of course he would like
yes anyway um but i i was
in my this i was in my
thirties so this is not good thirty
nine no not quite there okay but
i in order to dig out um
one of those little wooden dowels one
was a little wooden pegs that you
always have either too many of or
not enough of i used a swiss
army knife oh and somehow had it
in a position where this was this
sermon i've snapped closed on my finger
oh and i looked at it i
looked at
the blade like embedded in vapor like
it was happening to someone else yeah
it was so weird to see yeah
and then it gush to blood so
much blood that actually had reminds me
of when i was little and i
was playing with a stapler and stapled
staple through my finger like the whole
way ooh and then i was like
showing my dad like yeah any
pulled it out well that's good yeah
but it was still you go to
the hospital what have you shown that
to your to anyone sucks to be
you yeah yeah my staple my dad's
pretty um pretty confident in the face
of things like that like just go
like com yeah selected yeah what was
like the weird creature that was in
your house that he just grabbed oh
my god that was a huge gremlin
and no like that was more recently
it was like a shield the gremlin
lying well but it was like a
row just crazy it was like inches
long like a palmetto book when we
went out to lunch and then he's
like i shouldn't tell you this but
saw a huge roach in your house
and i was like or whatever it
was real thing is gigantic he's about
where it went enjoy this he he's
don't know why i'm like why did
you tell me that and then we
were watching tv and it was crawling
by my head on the couch sounds
like to me an orange head he
just stood up and grabbed it with
his hand and opened the door and
threw it outside
i wish i could do that yeah
honestly it was awesome but bugs give
me the the creeps but i will
deal with them but i will not
not to the point where i will
grab one with my hand yeah although
you know what lightning bugs of course
i let them crawl i mean yeah
ladybug absolutely yeah those are these wasps
yeah yeah no no no
no i gotta draw the line somewhere
okay um i don't know if i
if i had to act so i
interrupted if i had to act in
something where like a tarantula was oh
yeah i don't i don't know like
i don't know if i could do
it i bet i bet you would
talk to the triangle or yeah the
wrangler and they would go oh it's
really you know it's like you
just gotta get used to it they're
not dangerous blah blah blah you do
it but they're creepy i know but
you do you're you're you're not a
coward thanks for believing in yeah i
think you would do well i just
know that you need to work more
and see would just be oh yeah
it's fine i forgot about that reason
yes absolutely yeah i mean so you're
listening butter and you want to turn
your show on
someone's face a guy who loves bugs
yeah
i would say in terms of like
dangerous things that i did that had
no consequences they're all bike related me
and my friends would drive around or
bike around the college where i went
to college for a couple of years
junior college and um there were these
ponds that we all like would jump
over the ponds with our bikes
and i would always think like oh
i wonder what would happen to us
if we've and none of us ever
fell in and then also riding the
bike into the pool over brian hussein's
house we would do that oh yeah
yeah where we would like the first
time i did it i just rode
right into the pool and the minute
the the front tire hit the water
it flipped over and so i flipped
over on it but then i
like oh okay you have to like
jump on it yeah in order to
fully just sink into the pool hey
which and how do you get the
bike out and just toss it out
it's not hard but then tall john
would ride from the roof into the
pool that's a nice job that's so
even more insane because he's taller than
the pool yeah he is yeah it's
a ten foot pool and he's eleven
feet tall yeah totally calm tell john
i remember when i was a kid
there was this would z area um
where there anyways like there was a
big know he'll lose a sewer deer
but it was usually hey gary yeah
there was a big ah just like
a big thick rope hanging
from a tree that you could use
like you would who put up this
rope i don't know but you would
run grab the row right like swing
out over this incredibly steep drop oh
yeah and it was thrilling but but
it was very scary but i remember
working up the courage to do it
and what i did it it was
exhilarating i was always too
scared of things i where i went
to summer camp they had you know
the big high dive board oh dive
to me it's turf i would never
ever ever yeah and all my friends
would do in and i and i
remember them i think it was part
of camp where they made you do
it and i was like terrified and
they're like come on come on yeah
and
yeah and and i was too much
of a coward i was just thinking
yesterday about how when people just jump
off of rocks into water i'm like
how do we know that's deep enough
where you are i know i don't
like that i don't i don't trust
that but everyone's fine but do you
want it to be really deep or
you just sink and sink and sink
i will that's not how it works
you go into the center of the
earth i guess you know on our
honeymoon why there was a waterfall that
we we had one of the great
guidebook back before really this kind of
stuff was on the internet all that
much but great guidebook saying like all
these like secret spots and stuff like
that and so we went to this
you know waterfall i remember clapping very
far
frightened of it not for herself but
for me she's like don't get too
close don't get too close you know
and i thought i was being very
safe ah but you know that was
one of the things you read in
the book of like you know hey
you gotta be careful because people punch
their death and you know and i
remember my uncle got married on a
cliff and being just so frightened of
that and all the guy
guys yeah all all the men who
were there were like yeah come on
over here to the cliff i'm like
but anyone can just fall in yeah
you know yeah anyone's allowed it it
can happen any time ah waterfalls of
course because playing video games i will
always look behind them for treasure yeah
coins yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you
hide some treasure there
ca what if i hit like an
old church
and inside is like some first aid
kits and some like mentos just fun
stuff fun stuff you need yeah yeah
alright let's hear another one thanks ben
okay thank you ben drink question peanut
butter gang this is mad that is
not well i was just wondering what
do y'all do to spark creativity
when you're just not feeling that inspired
love you so much bye
we're not the peanut butter gang are
we know we've never been a pretzel
game with pretzel cannabutter again said another
i think we've been that is there
a hyphen thing i think we've been
the peanut butter game like i don't
know and i don't think we've ever
been the peanut butter people okay the
peanut butter people i'd like to be
yeah okay and we are okay the
peanut
other people okay okay um i don't
know what i do actually i don't
know if i've ever had i'm trying
to think of i've had that conscious
thought of like i need to do
something for inspiration here are the things
i've found work take a shower that's
like number one i was gonna set
to actual ah because you're just like
not think you're going
doing something else so mindwandering you ah
the the worst thing you can do
is sit there at your i mean
it's not you can still work it
out sometimes where you're like okay i'm
gonna grind this out in front of
my computer um yeah you can still
you can still work that way but
i found it's better to approach
your computer when you already have it
in your head of what you're going
to do so the best thing to
do when you're feeling just stuck is
to go take a shower and think
about it in the shower or go
take a walk outside i used to
hike occasionally and by the time you
would get back from the hike you'd
have everything worked out in your head
and then you just like type it
up that's the thing this is like
a lot of people go like
right to the computer and go like
ok now i'm working because they're trying
to think of what to write yes
or whatever you gotta think of it
beforehand and then just get your computer
and like looking around my desk chair
a window yeah um i also feel
that i have a lot of ideas
in bed when i'm yeah going to
bed to bed and i've
i've made myself get into the habit
of right like making a note of
things when anything i'm not talking about
like when you're falling asleep and you
think you have an interesting idea and
you down it's gibberish yeah right i'm
saying like when you're when you're still
awake and you're lying there in the
dark and your your mind starts going
what about this what about right things
now like make a note of it
i can use
like if i'm in the middle of
a script i can i'll think about
it at night because it's like one
of these problems it's it's a lot
like what they tell swirl problems it's
what they tell you about doing crosswords
is like set it down in your
mind will continue to work on it
even though subconsciously even though you don't
know that you're working on and then
you pick it back
wake up and you're like oh yeah
i know this answer wow um more
of us
yuna e blank unum
i mean you're like let me just
tie my name is melina yeah i
hate batman
but but um what was this oh
yeah when you're going to bed like
like it's and you and you're in
the middle of a script and you
haven't quite figured out a plot point
like i've found that like your mind
continues to think about that until it's
worked itself out sometimes if you don't
do it before you're asleep sometimes it'll
do it in a dream or
do you think you'll have done it
a dream but yeah like going to
bed is so if it's like ten
am just go to bed
yeah oh my god i wish i
was in bed right now oh my
god me too for i am no
my other thing is driving house music
i would say because i think i'm
listening music i start to picture things
and that kind of gets me like
like note soils and this is this
is very simple but watch or listen
to things that you enjoy and think
about why
why you enjoy them think about what
it is that you like about that
aspect of creativity and ah apply that
to something that you want to do
you know what i mean like because
sometimes i will i will find i'll
enjoy something that has nothing to do
with a thing that i want to
do but i look at the approach
each of it and say oh i
can apply that to my thing even
though it's completely different from this thing
but i the more you think about
how they do the things that they
do why you enjoy it what is
satisfying or enjoyable about it um you
can get lessons there that's why your
news you wanted to show about the
chef in chicago yes so good yeah
the
the lion the lion yeah that's great
job yeah i love it alright let's
hear this is ah this is no
name okay thank you peanut butter this
is ebank ooh hello lauren paul and
scott i once shot a fly out
of the air with a rubber band
wow i don't know if i've
ever felt so proud of myself in
my entire life and i needed in
that moment have any of you ever
done something totally meaningless i have no
real world but felt like you had
accomplished something astounding and also what was
that thing
this is hot off the presses whoa
this is a recent achievement yes this
just happened and i was like what's
funny is i was thinking i can't
relate this to anybody because it's never
gonna be great i can't here we
go purely
i'm serious
i thought you meant ah
you're spotting me say i can't relate
this anybody you're going oh great right
now i'm down you'll be so excited
that you this came up because you
were just thinking about how there was
no way to yes bring this up
so this past saturday of course bob
barker died at the age of ninety
nine i had my show in
ah portland coincidentally now we tour with
two horn players a trumpet and a
sousaphone coincidentally the trombone player that plays
with us in les was in portland
that weekend and he came into the
show
and this was about i want to
say twenty minutes before the show i
said i think we should do this
i will at the top of the
show i'll say thank you all for
being here because it's such a sad
night of course bob barker died and
then you guys play the sad huh
oh yeah yeah and they were like
ok we're all like yeah that'll be
funny and then we die
did it i just set it and
they immediately played it and the laugh
went on for such a long time
and it was so satisfying that's it
was so i was trying so hard
not to laugh and i it just
it felt so good oh good it
felt so good and i was like
i wish i had recorded this yeah
because it was like
it was like one of those things
where people were laughing in waves yeah
i mean they couldn't believe that we
did it we couldn't believe that and
it but it could only have happened
that day yeah you should know you
should try to get your next show
why it works so well you did
say we've done this at every show
this is the first time it's really
but it was so i it is
like a a warm memory for me
now that's great oh how lovely thank
you
i guess my thing equivalent to that
is like i was training to get
fit when the toilet
what happened to you
it went away this year trying to
take a shit i was taking any
shit and it went into
like yeah like i hit that fire
with a random yeah exactly where i
want exactly right in that toy you
tell it said surprise yeah i'm here
to ah sometimes talking is a lot
shinobi we should just do the show
not as a show and where we
don't talk oh okay so we just
skyland scenario and silently yes yeah we
don't record it
it has to be what does we'll
just go did it and are on
our own house zoom yeah yeah and
we turn off the zoom yeah we
turn on your computer and we just
do it in our own houses and
we'd never see each other again yeah
sounds good to me people often think
like it sounds like like lauren wants
the show to end there's i've seen
comments like that and which always use
specific
or like us or like i don't
know i've seen comments where it's like
i'm saying sounds like they're getting tired
now that's not how we feel it's
one of that like oh life is
busy and sometimes it's hard so it's
also you you have another thing you
have to get to yeah and you're
doing the show for a while it's
like yeah no one like i said
i don't try to read into the
fuckin shit you just gonna settle into
differ
aren't rhythms as it goes on yeah
and also learn she gives us a
big lecture at the end of every
show about what we did wrong what
we could do better grade there is
that tension that's hanging over every fabric
kind knows like every time they messed
up but i i'm coming for ya
she makes us line up like she's
a drill star shit yeah we have
just handed attention yeah just like her
manners part
oh yeah oh yeah i remember that
one now ah matters hardy alright you
should throw manners party for holly i
will do nothing of the sort just
wait a minute part of the thing
that you wanted to happen i don't
know
did you ever request for this party
that she for her birthday yeah no
but i did her favorite things which
were bluey and monsters inc right yeah
decorations were on theme can you imagine
if those two got together oh my
god i actually think that bluey is
a monster and really fully came through
the door at night i'd be a
little scared i mean it's talking
yeah do you know that there was
a dog named bluey in australia who
had held the record for a while
for for being the oldest dog oh
i didn't know that yeah and that's
why blue is bluing i think so
he got it with some yeah you
got to assume if there's no connection
to that that's weird if you went
to the creators of bluey and you
said
so maybe like cry k yeah oh
yeah stress test for sure it's just
the truth means truth truth or god's
truth that's god's truth yes truth zone
god's wounds god's wounds as blood gods
i don't know this is blood
his blood is blood gods i don't
know that's blood oh the blood of
christ compels thee
the blood of christ compels thee yeah
yeah isn't that funny that's one that
i know from the bible yeah okay
so here's jesus we're back to the
gcc's drums yeah and he's like you
guys got to fucking drink my blood
like speaking of vampires or vampire where
anything christopher byers remembers let's get out
of here
right we don't have to go we
do have to go ah so remember
how claims aid if you want to
leave his voicemail if you want to
suggest a three-tier to us freedom usa
gmail dot com if you would like
to follow us on socials threesome usa
all kinds of places and if you
like your ad-free versions of this show
go to comedy bang bang world cb
world dot com until then until
will you do that
we will never forgive you yeah but
thank you for listening we love you
we love doing you and i have
to say next week is our final
episode of our season yeah it is
yeah oh makes so you know you
got one more week of us so
if you're getting tired of us like
lauren gets tired at the end of
the show you only have
one more
london it's this cool show we don't
know if we're going to get picked
up again yeah so what we need
you to do right is call and
write to collin anderson and go cry
game and let him for a str
you have to open with crikey mate
yeah he likes that in truth i
need
more threesome in sw truth yes truth
crikey mate in strength i need more
thredup signed tbilisi sign bluey yeah he
loves blue he loves until heels yeah
thousands of emails from louis oh it's
gonna be so happy yeah he will
pick us up for an eternity yeah
alright i'm my keys in my hand
i don't know if yeah ok bye
hey anywhere by
uh