nah
oh wow it's a rainy day here
in burbank coleman weather pounding the southland
region three dm always made me down
i was trying to do the paul
williams version oh
oh interesting did he i think he
did and if he didn't he should
have been pretty high
make him such saying a little bit
of karen carpenter oh my god that
was a door's really cute the guy
who won four was it our arm
yeah and he's saying the carpet yeah
yeah he was like i grew up
listening to the carpenters and then he
said his he's saying his speech in
the melody he did play a weird
al yeah on top of the little
parody i grew up
emulating a carpenter jesus ah that's why
i refused to call the bad luck
after guy call there was only one
other carpenters we don't have i don't
see enough brother sister duos we've said
it before we very true carpenter i
like when it was rallies
you like what's ambiguous you like like
a certain gay type just love it
see ambiguously gay duo i remember growing
up and being like that's how i
learned ambiguous meant
i remember being an adult learning newsman
and i'll bet you did hey yeah
a little hey let's
ah we're back together in the same
room y'all ended up dodging covert i
didn't get it that's why they call
him the artful dodger that's yeah they
do call you that a lot also
i do pick people's bucket that's okay
and you've got to you have an
army of orphans will now the vague
and past yes yes yes yeah poor
ueno i'm really sa
sorry he was my fucking die ah
how did he die covert covina yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
how what how was it covert how
did he die how did he
jack covert he out of covert eleven
ah while but he just had an
interesting eleven yeah oh wow um so
you were dancing between the raindrops you
ended up not getting yes so we're
back in person yeah for you yeah
i really thought because people because you
were on a cruise ship yeah and
i was getting i was getting notifications
left and right well
everyone there had it yeah of course
oh i went to a beautiful wedding
nights and i saw tawny which is
why i'm jumping to that i say
wedding that i didn't go to oh
it is this i feel like i
was there because of instagram naomh peregrine
andy beckerman is wedding like oh no
is well you weren't there well i
wasn't there oh no it was not
the wedding that i
ended up not going oh yeah how's
you meant to stop this guys other
people were left that wedding to go
to after the ceremony to go to
there were the same day yeah didn't
realize it was i was able to
me that was like this the pressure
is amazing for these party goers the
prep time alone to do but it
was so beautiful and it was such
a special what was beautiful about
naomi literally was so beautiful about this
wedding the luck that we like to
say the love was incredible and it
was palpable but name sir you're able
to look at that night i could
should have we should should we get
married for the podcast nonu paul no
no the three of us should we
like anytime you start a podcast with
someone you should
have a podcast wedding i think whenever
you should share bank accounts yeah for
sure yeah um what i was just
saying we could see each other in
the hospital they came down when they
when they had the ceremony which was
beautiful in the end the officiant was
so funny i just met him that
night but i didn't know him and
after they came down the hallway mendez
had they left the aisle down you
know after
the kid the kiss was the perfect
strangers theme song and i was in
heaven yeah i was on cloud nine
okay well let me just get into
it because i wanna mix up ten
ten songs right now um hold on
i think i'd blossoming my head immediately
i think you want me to find
it yet cause i'm singing punky brewster
i can't stop
op will sing punky brewster while i
looked for this okay i can't now
because i already seen monkey poo see
please seeing punky brewster for me you
do a favor standing toe on the
way out
a ride dan bo wings of dreams
oh and i was so happy i
truly it was like this is my
dream scenario does that make you cry
yeah
melissa
nothing could range but sometimes you just
get a feeling like you need some
kind of change
no matter what the odds are this
time unless that's going to stand in
my ways they didn't start it here
though we didn't wait thirty seconds one
minute here started with the corner three
went
standing toe away
ajs rise and foe waves of boundary
the wind london the wind and rain
down for better days some shit that's
so foul lazy so nah dream another
so stop me now and i must
have been were about really through it
this and the writers must've been like
that's less width oh my god two
pages they don't need to do it's
my
my life my dreams nothing to stop
me now and that's all over bulky
you know it's like it's giving it
such grandiosity like by the way is
now they're arriving in america
it's so fucking full version it's also
come on with the idea of being
perfect strangers yay and i was okay
has nothing to do with the relationship
know jesse frederick bennett salah a performed
by david bomb iran let me say
it's a great song but really what's
being perfect strangers however shit out of
that i loved the
idea of coming down the aisle to
that we were it was treating well
that's what i'm trying to say i
can't find the word do you know
what retreating from things too yeah it
was i had never heard there's a
processional and the recession i had never
heard the song but the song learned
about blah because i wrote a script
once said at a wedding and i
said here comes the bride plays as
everyone left the via the
the place and my mum made me
feel stupid when she read it and
said it would be the recession wow
you idiot yeah hey melody she went
down the song i had never heard
that was something like i was like
a slow indie rock song that was
like pick my back my uzi yeah
my
sorry about that it was like don't
be afraid of love and that i
just loved it so pretty i mean
the balls they've been together forever they're
just getting married there don't be afraid
of planning the wedding was on the
anniversary of their first kiss the really
thirteen years oh up and i tried
to well at one point i pitched
hey should we get married on
the tenth anniversary of our first date
and she would i'm not waiting that
long wow
and how many years into the marine
side ended up being nine and a
half oh come on yeah not weeks
either hey we were looking at the
scarecrow and mrs king theme song the
other day jason masuk isn't well hynes
i don't know that song i don't
know i don't either it is so
long
this is not how i guess it
would have gone but yeah dramas too
if we're cleaning house game i need
you to play the who's the boss
theme song because that's the best most
emotional theme song most emotional most most
any what most evokes emotion which one
ah nostalgia this
song is making me crazy
this sounds like mang is making money
crazy but we're i mean we were
just laughing at how long because it's
just like yeah it's ton of stuff
is happening underneath all of this like
they're trying to tell so much store
yeah just play who's the boss that
you can feel what it feels like
to move somewhere in the fall i'll
just close this tab of that or
you're gonna say unicorn to be me
i'll close the tab i had open
you like to the unicorn movie because
i've made a reference in a purge
i went to the premiere well it's
still perverted um i went i made
a ah no someone made a unicorn
reference on a on an upcoming cb
episode and i said with lauren lacus
and they were talking about a show
yeah there's a show called the unicorn
around the same time wow that guy
being like a single dad or something
like well because unicorn right right right
hot single person or i mean didn't
that used to apply to like throughout
but it was a three symbol that
was the premise in arm and that
movie is that it's a unicorn as
someone who's coming into a couple i
thought was some
who did anal oh my damn horns
you look cool
it's just the bots
oh first we have sonya oh man
this isn't it people don't get excited
videos go to play after this ad
hey why don't you try google chrome
you can do chromecast
season three apparently o aired september twenty
three nineteen eighty six may nineteen nineteen
eighty seven yeah d does this make
you feel nothing you did nothing still
not oh i never watching i was
too old but that's not really it's
it's like i still like it would
do something but i guess not no
us soldier for this thing you never
were
watched it's not objective be a great
song i'm sorry
brandon leper around the band come on
you can go be someone's made this
is good because it applies to both
of them yes cmo lost a dream
or two
what it's a street in connecticut probably
why did my post get to have
kid take theme songs and no one
else he would i mean believe it
or not will leave you with one
got to be mike post wrote so
many tv rose hill street blues that's
i'm a widow how will be believe
it or not alan thicke wrote a
song like robot he
your kids michael hose and somebody started
pete carpenter why did they relate chart
because i will listen to these songs
like it's fun okay well i'm gonna
look up mike post's discography and we'll
see that michiana tv i mean how
did they get on the radio like
they were just like playing the full
version on the radio cause people liked
the theme song i think that they
just won the
it's it's another way for them to
make money so the they probably sent
it to radio station wow okay here's
here here's a full version of this
link be sure to watch welcome back
kotter this weekend here's what he comes
up in the middle okay
here's here's the one that started
the lowest which i don't even know
what it is manhattan spiritual what that
charted at fifty six but who knows
what it is okay so then
you have magnum pi at twenty oh
short charted at twenty five absolutely ah
the banger it's a good song it's
a great song grin you have i
don't think i know that one magnum
pi yeah it really was yeah well
see this is the thing like we
have nostalgia for the things we may
understand how new value word is due
a pool
show anybody who
this is magnum pi this is i
know how stuff works we oh my
god i went and spoke to some
high schoolers last year why i was
giving them drugs alright you have to
speak to them
to make a desk the sarah connor
it was kind of a funny thing
because basically this person i'm working with
asking i talked to his daughters improv
class okay tell the story will make
it more yeah yeah so i went
to all the way to the west
side and i um spoken to them
and then he was asking me it
was me and brandon scott jones
and he was asking name-brand scott jones
some questions about our how we started
doing improv because these kids are just
getting into it and all this stuff
was very nice but one of the
things he was like what what did
you like like what about what what
made you want to be funny and
i was like i watched a lotta
tv and i watched a lot of
us now and like i was like
you wanted that attention and i was
like you don't know what i'm talking
about but like three's company
like the slap stick and three's company
and then they were all just like
dad i was like i'm not but
i was like but that was older
than me i was like um it
wasn't even my you know like oh
like i'm guy i'm but i'm not
battling it was like when i was
in high school and if someone was
thirty seven billion year one thousand like
you would say someone's like he's like
thirty like you're getting laid off okay
yeah
yeah anyway what did you what if
i'm extremely old played up with your
own
you're accepting an award and then suddenly
data okay so let me let me
tell you that the ones that the
charted higher um i will also say
i did improv with the children and
they were quite fun oh they're all
very cute usually when they ask a
question it's usually like hey who's your
agent can i have your age well
honestly their questions were very informed because
they're
or in l a like it was
just like write the questions that they
had i was like i would never
have thought to ask this alright brandon
scott jones another person called by his
initials like me b s j yeah
really yeah okay charting at number ten
two singles charted ten rockford files and
hill oh rockford files is a great
that's a great one yeah
a and then his history blues like
two connected to the show i feel
sorry l a law was at thirteen
that also charted isn't can remember that
one l a law yeah oh goes
like this it's like it's the law
it's that late
this is the seattle target
oh i want to have ships now
bitchy legal style
oh sure yeah you remember you see
but this sounds like a song like
that sounds very theme song yi yeah
this is a way like a rock
lighthouse does i could yeah james coming
onto the screen and the person so
how did this chart like why were
people listening to this for pleasure that
shows a hot show people loved it
but is there a theme song episode
number
his highest not at number two believe
it or not i'm walking on air
what was the greatest american year that's
his hope that his yeah what what
number number number two what's like to
reach for like where where we what's
what are his highest or were at
the top so that's that's where it's
yeah yeah okay never had a number
one hit okay play a little bit
of the rockford files yeah it's so
good did you ever see the rockford
files no i don't know what that
is i want i remember when i
was a kid in
syndication i want to i feel i
maybe ten years ago i started watching
the pilot because i was like i
gotta get back into this and it
was so slow those
i like this what's it about
this part sounds
that elect that sounds different to me
that synthesized part sound can i guess
what it's about based on the name
and the setup
it's about monica blair yeah zaki background
of threw me off i sort of
like my first thought was it's like
exiles it's like aliens oh like okay
rockford files like some detectives files music
cowboy
yeah he sort of he's nice james
garner and he's kinda has a cowboy
vibe
he's a p yeah okay great yeah
he's kind of like a downtrodden guy
yeah yeah like lives in a trailer
yeah disney um and the show would
open with somebody leaving a message on
his answering machine and it was always
somebody who was kind of mad at
him for some reason right and it
was a different message every time so
they had like this little cold omega
it was always different yeah i did
watch colombo pilot yeah and second episode
recently colombo pilots wild itself cool up
could not believe it she's like when
this is the pilot when does colombo
come in it was it it was
minute nineteen yeah i would find any
problem for a long time and then
well
because the gimmick was you see how
the the the killer did it first
oh and then colombo figures it out
you know set out and you watch
him figure it out with whatever you
want on lot of the limb yeah
you want and he doesn't watch already
know right he he breaks like three
eggs right and then touches everything in
the
so change was good she was losing
her mind i get out of my
kitchen colombo that's funky but he always
is like it's funky he always shows
up pretending trying that sort of nasty
i just decided he always shows up
pretending to like be there for a
different reason yeah it was so he
can grill the person so it's always
like oh i was in
the area i miss his name peter
falk yeah he's like i was just
kind of ah looking at the property
or in the air and i was
wondering if i was admiring the bush
out front looks so vibrant and green
yeah maybe you could tell me what
kind of ah yeah by the way
oh i like him master he was
looking great you guys think did you
kill you
a wife yeah and then every episode
is an hour and a half that's
the other thing why is took so
long because it was filling a movie
slot is what i found out later
it was filling a two hour movie
slot was like history of the week
yeah how much he got paid i
think i probably at least a dollar
i think it was one hundred dollars
per half hour so and that's
not bad this was pre residuals this
is pre residuals and also different i
mean you'd adjust for inflation has also
got to comment yeah house cost one
to all or see this really rich
yeah yeah yeah three houses over every
half hour yeah oh that's a lot
he just moved around he'd watched the
show in each of his houses i
love that that's the thing he would
get paid to do the show and
then they would
pay him to watch the show that
that's a thing yeah sure i could
fudge the nielsen yeah it's like he
watches his own show i had a
relative neilson box at one point i
knew someone on my aggravate had a
relative who had one sighting yeah i
always wanted one when i was a
kid but wouldn't that be so fun
they they care what you think it's
like now now we can we can
give feed
back on instagram ads but that's not
the same no i didn't go to
lame tv testing when i was a
kid i would i would drive up
here with my friend and and they
would show us like shitty sitcoms yeah
and we would turn the dial and
stuff yeah yeah people can be very
hate-filled i would imagine because when you
have control of that dial you just
want to send it if i don't
like something i'm going red zone oh
yeah i was
i was zero almost the entire time
because it was so hey lover hate
love age yeah yeah it's one way
to share did that show make it
to air no i never made today
or it was so fucking bad it
was i mean it must i must
have been it must have been nineteen
eighty nineteen eighty five yeah you are
yeah it was your pilot oh no
that you wrote oh i'm so sorry
did you ever have a pilot that
you
wrote did you ever have a pilot
that you wrote ah never not over
the phones like book and that was
bill cosby show british guy did you
have any energy
right um i have written a pilot
it did not go so i've never
written anything like on me but it
but someone was entertaining that idea brief
they were briefly entertained the idea yes
oh yes it was very cool so
cool to get that call we entertain
this idea briefly hey we
thought about it and the answer is
no so loves you thought about it
i appreciate that i was my mind
at all i remember once doing a
i was on a um focus group
for cigarettes in philadelphia so i just
remember just the concept of cigarettes it
was of new cigarette that we were
trying wow what was it it wasn't
square what was the
new was it was square and i'm
sure thought i did one of those
ones for like sixty
for rabies i don't know how i
ended up there but i got sixty
dollars and i had to like give
my opinions anybody remember what it was
and it was a movie ooh yeah
of course i famously did movie surveys
wow for the n are so famous
for that that's i think that's what
i'm most know you're on your own
empty because i reached the most people
in america for sure was calling
them at their homes and having them
giving them the opportunity to hang up
on me what's the weirdest thing you
did for money we must have talked
about this oh my god sex yeah
right oh yeah of course but weird
sex yeah sure we are sexy weird
to them exactly right you know and
i'm trying exactly right it was it
was an educational thing for p
shame oh god i gotta go got
and so you just had sex in
front of a class yeah yeah and
they were all like e i said
and i said i'm glad you did
that because
if you had to have okay if
you had to have sex in front
of a group of people and they
just went knew the entire time would
you be able to complete
oh really
no if you had to have sex
but it wasn't sex i mean this
is sex i guess but it was
it was like foot people sex where
someone would people say it's only involving
feet and genitals and everyone's going
oh yeah if i were on the
foot end of the equation i bet
i could do it
i've been a good that means nothing
to me i don't care it means
nothing
maybe more embarrassing because you'd be like
trying something
wait it would be the first time
you did this kind of thing yeah
but i've all my clothes on except
for one shoe and sock right no
yeah well my screen you can see
it now you could take a shadow
outline or silhouette so it's fetishes are
such a wild thing when somebody's into
a thing that you're not it never
occurs to you to be out to
and knowing like that's their whole thing
yeah it seems like it's just like
a lot like i
when i ah i watched real sex
growing up due on hbo yeah and
a little too real for me yeah
it's like all like give me some
fixes like yo ma people ever going
to parties yeah but i love when
they would like interview the people on
the street quarter and be like oh
do you like blow jobs yeah guy
like to add
a blow job everyone that was that
was a taxicab confessions oh hell yeah
like street interview yeah yeah yeah which
was so great like they did on
the first season of sex in the
city yes which is so reasoning i
just like wanna go out with a
girl and she's wants to put a
balloon i asked what call me crazy
and i'm like we never see that
guy again you're like why did we
do do
our first few seasons of seinfeld where
there'd be this guy that would be
talking in between this the scene where
everyone i think he's still that the
whole way through actually they did john
right yeah no nose bumpers know he's
yeah he stopped doing not know what
they would do it oh at the
at the beginning yeah he did get
a hand but yeah it was weird
i was in the middle at the
end he would do the lesson yeah
right yeah on stage um but
just remember and maybe or maybe it
was a true life like i have
a fetish or something like mtv but
there was one about balloons where it
was someone who is sexually attracted to
balloons and like in the shape of
boobs automatically are but
and then another person who liked to
sit on cake sarah palmer
or see people do that cake sitter
there is a natural thing and there's
no cake foreigners
there is okay but they fart on
kicks or they fart a fart onto
the they don't fart how did they
fart cake ish like they eat a
bunch of gay jeanine garafalo used to
cite that as why she did not
have a website because she said the
perfect one already exists yeah and it
was that cake fart i'm not going
to say but yeah ok
it's not orgasm we're okay we need
to take a break but paul's gonna
say it when we come back or
paul's gonna say it we promise not
to come but we swear we swear
at our comeback listen to the ads
but come back because paul's gonna say
it
welcome back alright cake problems but i
say oh my yeah but anyway you
know when you when you're a young
impressionable mind you see something and it
just sticks with you well yeah give
me traumatized do you have another demo
like that where you saw like oh
people can be into that oh but
see
sometimes doesn't make you into it when
you're young and impression oh i think
if you're like if you're like a
little little kid and then you you
know because it's it's not a whole
lot of those things start this is
horrible but i remember seeing when i
was like i was too young to
see this ah my neighbor had ah
you know a stash of this was
like your classic ah
adorno's in the woods yeah yeah they're
wet damp ah and everything in between
i don't know why he says he's
got the goods
ah and jim one of them when
we talk about your new lyrics yeah
okay first of all i'm a huge
fan it's so sickening though jim lizard
i love everything about you your i
mean really endorse perception i'm gonna write
some poems okay but i gotta ask
your new song poor nose in the
moods could it be about anything else
that's personal experience and do you and
yeah we liked the melody we just
kind of like maybe you can make
it most something else like the valkyries
have you ever thought of
that
who were they i think you can
connect better with poor omegas probably heavy
metal well i saw one that ah
was like not one of your it
was like an off-brand yeah not one
of the main not playboy not penthouse
not swank or we we
which i always thought was ooh ee
yeah i had no idea
upi let me see that ui magazine
and because ah oui there was like
a photo there was like things that
make you say photosmart i think the
idea was like weird fetishes or whatever
and one was a top topless woman
of course no head involved you just
like i was neck down and fraser's
a pl
late of the way you like to
follow
um there was a plate of shit
in front of her knife and fork
oh no that makes me want to
gag and yet it was what i
wish i had never said well i
remember hearing a rumor about someone ah
i won't say who oh could just
say who no no isn't divine but
that's true it's yeah yeah right
divide are you doing that yeah i
just watched and i have not really
i've never seen that it's i mean
it's the very last shot in the
movie so you could turn it off
right before it that's the story and
so it's good to before that happened
i loved when jake was talking about
john waters read you know remember and
like they realized they didn't know what
the effects
acts were of a human being directed
well i guess i could imagine not
like yeah yeah by the way i
listened to john waters on ricki lake's
podcast and it was an interesting interview
if that's something that might be of
interest anyone out there in the world
but mister hey yeah i used to
i'm very i'm very fond of him
yeah yeah he was really interesting um
but
ah what was it gonna say you
were talking about oh yeah this person
apparently liked to make a woman or
you know he liked to like to
make no no no frankenstein he he
preferred for the woman to do the
following he wanted to get he would
get under a glass table and you
want oh yeah go on top and
is this chuck berry de putti putti
or um
danny thomas danny thomas says no it's
not allegedly by the way we can't
get a little closer to home
okay
as a minor ah alright we'll feel
it now i'm itching to take breaks
so we can hear who this is
um and if you're listening hey oh
i hope you enjoyed the shout by
the way huge news straight shit bodily
functions so do you do this speaking
of bodily fuck shit well you you
know our fondness for clara peller are
honoring the honorary where's the beef course
book lover whereas the beacon wonder we
love it everybody
we love her we are we love
so much want to know what we
love so much we respect her and
i was watching television this weekend no
way you saw oh cooler there is
a new clara peller spokesperson for wendy's
within yeah catchphrase what what is it
squares the beef are you fucking because
there they heard our ep
i sewed and they thought this can
come back yeah because their burgers are
square yeah yeah so squares the beef
and and here honestly they waited too
long and here is the spokesperson i
wanna know i wanna open it up
to the group whether this person should
be an honorary pittsburgh okay okay reggie
miller oh well basketball is my he's
first of all i met reggie miller
when i did early show and we
had a total of connection we're totally
in love really no it was the
bit in the scene but he was
so great i loved he was all
so is he very passerine i need
more details is he dressed as clara
peller
not that i could tell although to
be honest i would his eyes were
up here and i was not looking
down low is he has bad at
delivering the line is clara peller was
i think he's probably better at it
he's he's charming he you know what's
ironic he's a giant and yet he
stands on the shoulders of a giant
that's true repeller that's true and it's
trusting i vote no i can't you
vote no i can't it's not just
because of wendy's because of who clara
was okay that's okay yea though i
cancer ridden stenographer whatever i vote yes
because i think he's he's a great
person to represent the piss pigs and
he's and you have to think that
he
i would go out there and he
will have about i love to farm
a basket
he'd be on the piss pig street
team essentially out there repping for i
think just people for people to know
that he was one i think you're
good for the podcast yeah no look
even if you never said it i
would love to have an honorary piss
pig who is still alive and will
live for a few more years to
come sure but you know tall people
are short-lived when you get that tall
it's like extreme oh my god
the blood can't get to where it
needs to go no yeah that's why
i sleep upside down yeah i knew
it and not because i'm a vampire
oh i never thought about that well
okay so you have the final vote
well look i was bowled over i
was dumbstruck when i saw this commercial
and again if you're
this time piss pigs is the collective
nickname for our audience but you've voted
voted on what was the the thing
they were voting again ok guys either
was like sweet fans right he was
yeah yeah yeah and everyone said no
we're obviously pissed three durables i think
yeah very durables and sweet fans i
think it's like the top two yeah
yeah and i think also just like
respected audience when you say two v
two were in like single digit polling
i mean well nobody was nine know
it was wept the things was like
foreign survey yeah reddit i think yes
yeah it was if you can look
it up and you can look it
up and find it yeah yeah you
don't can't vote anymore because voting is
closed yeah voter you can but you
can see the results yeah so anyway
if you're
listening yeah we're trying to figure out
whether her ah reggie miller the basketball
player from yeah if you're just listening
now we're trying to figure if she
just right guys what what's up okay
so if you just tuned in what
happened is what you want just a
second ago for me recapping i think
we should people had just tuned in
i think we should reek yes from
the beginning really quickly
they just oh a couple quick lines
yeah talked about tv theme songs we
talked about fetishes hall saw a porno
of a woman eating shit the doors
had arrived to our ships yes and
with a knife and fork define eat
dog shit and then think that's pretty
much where we yeah yeah sure yeah
when you really absolutely like that white
people this clara peller was oh come
on i think
everything has been delightful clara peller honorary
piss pig yeah in previous episodes she
of course we talked about her career
and we we realize she was a
piss pig because of just everything about
she just fits the description now of
course she's passed on and she's in
purgatory um you think she's still in
purgatory she
there have been enough time in this
beautiful daughter she's a sensor deeper for
like a few years purgatory is a
long term and you think it's hundreds
and hundreds yes you can be for
some people but for clara peller yes
none of us is without sin and
she lived long lives to be ruined
but you're not bad enough to go
to hell yes it is to purge
you of your of her mark of
sin
exactly the younger you are in you
go to less time you spend in
purgatory yeah probably stands to reason unless
you're a bad seed and you've committed
many oh like ah the good son
you're the bad seed alright
that good son more like that bad
see this is that in the i
didn't see the movie but is that
align in the movie yes it is
how it is good anyway so let's
say directly and with that i'm saying
that then they eat dog shit they
all yeah they count out three to
see what they all say in unison
the good song more like that bad
jade and then
they bow and then i finish work
because we'll oh yeah there's a picnic
table with like the red and white
checkered table block um yeah it was
just read through that and it's a
very loyal knife and fork they all
can grab yeah it's just piled with
all kinds of shit and and there's
also a ton of different knives and
forks like different utensils like so if
you kind of were like i want
a small fork i want a big
four i wanna sport yeah yeah like
bachelor's apartment and i'm gonna ladle hey
it's like one little thing where from
many different restaurant shop yeah yeah yeah
anyway so how do i vote god
reggie miller who did he play for
the pacers oh no don't look at
me i'm santos i'm supposed to know
this but kremlin supposed to know this
i like him supposed to
know that the suns can i feel
like we need to
i'm i'm of two minds i feel
like we need to open this up
to the fans to try to tweet
at reggie miller and
i don't know no no no why
not bring the words to his twitter
open a new poll up under the
other poll okay yeah under the original
yeah yeah okay yeah picks poll and
and then you can vote there do
not inform him of this because the
voting is not it's tagged lauren oh
no you're not on twitter anymore damn
it isn't that wonderful
i really like you guys are talking
about to leave it's so great you
know i'm gonna wait i'm gonna wait
space to come out and then i'm
you don't miss it no i don't
miss it the only time i kind
of missed it was ah it was
not maybe it was the golden globes
it was whatever
like green like the oscars using me
know because i didn't watch it oh
i but i got home after my
show and i watched all the speeches
and i was like this is the
voice the way would write a love
love the speech lot of really good
speeches this year yeah yeah oh and
then some more store we watched the
ones that were available on hulu like
right after the show which was not
that
many and then we went to youtube
and there were a few more on
there and then one of the one
of the clips on youtube from the
oscars that just happened yeah was two
minutes of the r r r dance
number but not only too many joined
it in progress so i though it
was so like why weird are beginning
to yeah number yeah
it's really good it's like did they
not pay them if you watch or
have to feel you've got no idea
it was fun like that it's really
good i'm excited to watch it it's
really oh yeah yeah um yeah alright
so so little will leave it up
to the fans and will come will
come back next week with the results
of the poll yes again do not
tweet read hillary may not need to
know that the show is
he can't know until the results are
sure and then he'll be incredibly honored
be a core devastated well if he
does if it doesn't work go his
way then we're not going to tell
him i mean that's that's cruel exactly
i always appreciate when i go to
an audition i love not hearing back
oh well then you'd be in heaven
mycareer
also please do tweet the surviving relatives
of clara peller and let
i didn't know that she is indeed
an honor here's what i really just
gonna backfire speaking of the oscars was
the target of every joke weighed in
about how the joke was not funny
oh you mean so pauly shore that
joke bell was online they sell on
tmc or whatever oh my that robert
blake son that joke about my dad
was not funny
it's just like hey guys yeah we
get it if you're if the job
is about you you're going to think
it's not fun yes the time that's
how that works yeah that's not a
scoop think your dad just died what
did you think of us it's job
and care for it i thought jimmy
kimmel was funny yeah he heard he
did a great job yeah yeah there's
there's kind of no winning in that
job anymore yeah
because ah everyone just complains about everything
but ah sure buddy i thought he
did a great anon job where he
just like breeze through it but it's
funny it's sort of like not necessary
to have a host while they tried
it without yeah no one cared so
see what you need is you need
the posters with the host kissing the
oscars and having like a big armhf
a hoster hoster ice yet oh sure
because you look at it you go
jimmy those are not your oscars and
he's like no no no i'm gonna
give them away right that's right he's
he's like the trix rabbit and you
finally got the tricks yes but then
he gets a dream award show fan
i like having a home i like
having a host too i think it's
just fun it makes it feel like
an event i also
weirdly think they tried so many different
things in the previous years i don't
think you need the different things anymore
we just know you know we just
don't get the way like have those
come out tell funny jokes have the
same structure we like it better some
article that was like this generation wants
to be like davis generation thought that
wants to be like tick tock
and they want us to be lightly
fast quick things guys because tiktok like
i don't dance it the dancing that
i see on tik hai taught you
about doing yeah it's all just above
the waist with people bopping so do
you know what it is do they
have this special technique and i don't
trust someone out there knows more um
but there's a camera sort of filter
or app or some
when you're using where it kind of
keeps the it keeps them centers sent
ah but also like yeah and the
background can move a lot so it
makes them look like they're dancing much
more intensely really are it's like they're
kind of like dude you to do
but it's like you kind of it's
something that's happening every tick tock i've
seen has been like three friends getting
together doing the most
basic dance side decide and then laughing
and turning the camera off yeah it's
garbage it's literally trashed and our brains
are rotting
i can't i can't look at it
for too long it starts to just
yeah i don't use that starts to
ask you to come inside the phone
yeah be part of you know what
i'm talking about yes i had that
weird whisper it a siren's call sometimes
the hand starts to come out yes
and grab you by the throat
lawrence signing pictures of herself oh my
gosh so centered much calm no i'm
done and she's finally done i want
to announce that thank you so much
congratulations disease you can purchase these these
are very ah although i don't remember
the name of the person who do
drew these well delightful
fan art yeah i would tell you
but we'll find out we'll definitely find
out alright we have to take a
break when we come back paul's going
to say that thing that we wanted
him to say yes oh he's promised
dramas she's getting ready he's been hyping
myself up yeah we've been doing pushups
in the corner i look in the
mirror and i take my pants down
i say ruining my belly buds up
here
alright we'll be right back i don't
know why
and we're back and it's time for
three ter but first but first with
the corrections department yes has descended upon
threesome of all podcasts you believe is
a clarification um you remember we played
three via where we
have trivia about each other and we
talked about stevia it's a great game
we didn't we never got to stevia
you know i feel bad i know
so many questions things are to feel
bad i love talking about it oh
i felt the hip hello andy
e on the ah like the table
oh my god it's like a pointy
move because it's the class between the
two okay i'll try to do something
just do there's nothing i can do
alright and maybe there is but it
doesn't matter i could just be more
careful there's something you could do see
me in court um so
we first did the freedom trivia of
submitted by nathan diffie yeah great nathan
duffy and then we did it again
but questions were sending by a different
person somebody that lee yeah and just
wanted to clarify because there might have
been some overlapping questions yeah that um
nobody was swiping anybody else's questions they
are the symptom independently of each other
right and oh is that a question
wait i don't know what we're talking
about right well so we do are
you gonna explain this is just no
i am doing are you gonna explain
yourself call because we're sitting here waiting
for this to make sense so just
so both nathan and lee know
no one's they they came up with
their questions independently it just happened that
some of them coincide some of them
were they came up with the same
but it was parallel thought yes parallel
thought yes which happens a lot on
comedy okay it does and i just
got asked about a joke i made
earlier ah this morning someone texts me
and said what was your joke about
such and such because they're writing
for a show and i don't want
us i don't want thames that happens
you know you know even and i
said ask me if i give a
shit if you still give a shit
i do yeah i asked him please
don't do it can you pay anything
dollars sorry so lee i think lee
it doesn't matter but anyway so that's
that's the point oh no i'm well
if there were duplicate questions oh no
we may have whos
declaring early shining to to yeah because
i didn't realize that word we were
trying we're trying to to hear the
clearly or for both of them because
are both heated and they're both oh
my very upset both furious i was
gonna say i'm i'm in the middle
i thought maybe you were going to
mention that we got one wrong i
answered my own question yeah yeah now
the corrections yeah that's we guys
this is really embarrassed there was a
question and should we look this up
to make sure part of no part
of what is the best kind of
correct part of what i love is
that the questions don't come with answers
because they're about us and we should
know and i still didn't know when
i got my own question wrong but
here's part of why it was hard
for me it was a fact-based question
this was not my numbers on your
photos or my feeling as my memories
my feelings which is what i remember
the most is based on a fact
which i care about the least so
it's not based on your memories which
are not facts my memories or whatever
i remember hey our memories are not
looking i might say shit that's not
true but i would still know the
answer to the question because it's whatever
i've created them
my mind is running the past right
now apparently my first episode of coin
gaming i said it was with adam
brody it was in fact with gillian
jacobs and paul f tompkins me and
that does sound familiar but um i
think adam maybe it was my second
or third but anyways it was so
long ago it was a million years
ago if you
want to know if that's true or
not you can look it up i
just wanted to say that i might
have been wrong as david takes retro
greg takes it takes a village but
it takes a big person to admit
they might have been wrong it takes
a big person jump on that village
yeah what i don't want to do
it if you will i guess i
guess i just thought it'd be hard
to find out what's my first episode
it would be so easy that i
don't
where i do it very i'll do
it right now alright
well don't wait total sections
ah alright look we're gonna i have
a question for you but we're gonna
play this game which involves us or
this three-tier it's not a game which
involves play games on this we don't
play games yeah i'm saying game all
you having a law we play guy
but we're gonna play this reacher which
involves his texting
each other now i've turned on the
do not disturb on market i have
that as well because they the it's
the noise comes up on the recording
and it has happened so often and
with it on silent no on silent
well yes if it's on silent yes
but it's on do not disturb now
i will turn turn do not disturb
off and will hear the ding
ng if everyone is cool with that
but i need to hear and review
because it just because the recording is
going through this compute wait are you
here you're hearing me the computer makes
the dude we can introduce to do
it hey i do hear that
so i i'm going to turn off
do not disturb don't get mad if
we hear this ding
alright lawrence first appearance on comedy bang
bang yeah wo was episode one hundred
and eighty while you went wrong it
was a it was an episode called
jasmine called friends without words yes and
yes we're myself as garry marshall wow
lauren as traci rearden no it wasn't
tracy readers and learn tracy actually is
one of these things where i use
the name like god jesus fucking christ
twice within and gillian jacobs okay but
in the picture where you were a
different tracy reared yet no it wasn't
tracy rude and my name was tracy
and i was a foreign exchange student
who basically it was like i was
a manager not making sites that i
lived in spain or something but i
was only there for like us alright
if anyone even wants to listen to
this in the photo
think you should i'm sure i'm just
all over the place but in the
photo for the episode they also we
can see zach galifianakis john daly and
neil campbell why are they all i
think we were taping another one right
now let me see something and so
we all got into the picture together
wow that's so old let me see
so old my grandmother farts dust
that's so my grandmother as far as
i know it doesn't make any sense
even when i was a kid okay
so we're gonna play this game or
three-term sorry sorry sorry sorry god damn
i don't know what it's called are
you sure was that so old my
grandmother foodstuffs that's what it was when
i was a kid that's what she
said so the game i don't know
it's cause
called but it's where we each text
each other one word and then we
have we do a scene and we
have to throw that word in there
and then we have to guess what
the word is great great great fine
okay i know what you want to
know what my feelings about this game
what's that it's fucking impossible wow wow
we've done it before he never
guest really yeah we did did you
yeah i think guys got one right
i think i find it really hard
because you're concentrating on your own word
yeah unseen yes yeah let's try i
think the sound is the hardest let's
try it this time we're all gonna
get it yeah okay so we're gonna
text this way you can say that
about most games but maybe not this
one
no i just think you were so
immersed in your scene usually well you're
true you know you're doing i do
the work i think it should be
a phrase because i think that that
makes it a little bit oh not
gonna work and then will graduate to
a phrase if we find it too
all right um so i'm gonna text
paul paul's gonna text lower and lauren's
gonna text me and it's going to
be one word
and we're gonna hear a ding when
i get this word
um
alright i've texted paul paul has received
his word scott has received his word
i have received my word
where's that ding why do you need
a ding the fuck are you talking
about because my word came in but
i didn't hear the ding okay i
got i got my word
alright here we go never been more
furious really okay so
and and go begin
um i really and i know we're
closing the shop for just fifteen minutes
here too just so we're kind of
let's let's get through this meeting because
people do on ice cream and they
are waiting yeah i just thought we
weren't going to be putting fifteen minutes
is long enough i think it is
i just think we just need to
kind of because we have a lot
on the schedule that we have
to get through i mean we do
but i wanted to close the door
i want to lock it i wanna
just kind of get into it i
thought i thought that people are really
upset ironically vice chairman would be good
so that we you know the pressure
the pressure to get to get us
through this mean what are you guys
talking about oh my we're talking we
have family meeting philip i'm sorry i
just zoned out okay
a well is your word zone what
i'd never liked it
philip what we're talking about is that
this thirty one flavors is having a
lot of issues like thirty one issues
you could say that almost i mean
that would be truly is a bitch
one of them
we have thirty years su x well
you act so because your word bitch
supposed to get i know i know
i know it's not but alright yeah
i make funny jokes i make funny
jokes what if we okay so you
are actual aloof and i just what
me what are you trying to say
or do you try to say philip
i'm gonna say because you have you
have them most of the issues you
put onto the
the agenda the company agenda like bring
up your issues
oh okay is this gonna is this
gonna be what the is going to
be like is it you know already
exist some arbiter of what the meeting
is guy y'all i'm envious of you
because i feel that you get this
opportunity to just pretend like you don't
care and then you just get away
with it whereas i as the manager
have to do so i tell you
who doesn't care is all of you
because i've pitched so many ice
cream flavors that could turn our business
around okay well pitch some of the
flavors alright because we've haven't listened to
you okay every time you put we're
gonna take some flavor ideas right now
number one because we we have an
empty bucket here for our thirty first
flavor and people are banging on the
door so we need to make it
so please help us out of the
jam
we probably should have this off hours
we shouldn't
philip okay okay so first flavor fragrant
swirl it is regular chocolate vanilla swirl
yeah but when you crack it with
the spoon right you never go backward
like it's i do this no you
don't crack i mean i meant like
once you take the
first scoop out with the spoon okay
it smells like a child here and
we're yours there's the ting finally what
does that mean you're gonna go for
my idea no i have an idea
because everyone's woman said mine no no
his asthma
a second favourite what do we have
luminous ice cream ways you eat it
in the dark and glows like those
weird fuckin algae i love wages your
stomach glow or the mouth so you're
still all the way down i love
whoa yeah so it's almost as many
are like one of those glow worms
isn't like
when you go in for that medical
thing that's yeah drink that very minima
yeah yeah very inanimate it it feels
like that too
wow third flavor idea okay okay make
this one good please you know how
everybody loves that ah sparkling water yeah
i guess carbonated ice cream we call
it pop rocks ice cream you put
in your fucking we'll do we need
to get permission from the pop rocks
company know they're dead because they drink
coke with their own product
yeah died they all thought i was
doing that tough chat it was what's
this one called again this is carbonated
ice cream like one mile
the name of it is effervescence in
a can
okay
alright we all said our word effervescence
no karma needed yes he thinks you
off you asshole
yeah can you guess my harbinger yeah
he gets mine yeah because i gave
it to you
i'm supposed to guess yours oh wow
wasn't paying attention to groups
i get so confused
i was thinking more that's shall i
realised it was word
my was an end yes envious and
i'm still nbsp because you slit it
in there said it three times now
very well oh just sure i enjoy
it do we need to graduate to
phrase that i think i think we
should do one with the phrase because
i think it'll be kind of crazy
pays like i think it just two
word phrase not like not
like a quote but like meaning a
two word word do we go the
same way or do we reverse direction
reverse direction oh okay i was oeko-tex
scott okay i'm going to text laura
and lawrence context paul paul's gonna text
me alright
like
i've texted lauren paul has texted me
lauren has texted me but for some
reason the ding didn't happen it's what
happened in two minutes i look forward
to it and i'd love to see
yeah alright
but you don't have to have your
phone off do not disturb you could
just have it on joe disturbing and
look at the texts huh and they
still come in they just don't alert
you huh alright okay yeah okay ready
and go eliott will slow down slow
down who are you i bow
my new alien kicks a low pillow
bread high e t o e t
i remember him he rolled around in
my bike basket foe ah yeah hey
it's my name's elliott
yeah i know i called you elliot
oh yeah hey e what was your
name again edgar thomas he i think
you have to like do something with
this thing now it looks like it's
older what looks like it yeah what's
going on i'm sorry this is my
wife hi i'm julia julia you i
thought you grew up
together i did we did okay i
lived to blow you remember her from
halloween e t i lived in the
thought she was pete his breath no
no no no penis breath is dead
i was my brother oh no da
blocky t and she was dressed remember
helloween she was dressed as sexy nurse
e t go yeah it was like
nine yeah have we got together tonight
we fell in love
yeah and there's a lot going on
that night he had you in the
basket on stuff but also funny puts
the e t in the basketball team
the asker those good eliott yeah yes
iti we're gonna deal a hell what
what do you need iti anything for
you i have my childhood friend i'm
going through a nasty divorce
e be teasing for his idea that
character witness oh no don't do it
elliott do i have to go to
your plant what was your planet called
again e t lad i love that
look why are you getting divorced yeah
it's ah you're concealing their kids out
level difference you know star here you
remember ernie
libby was great she she's great yeah
she could see irreconcilable differences that well
it was very cute very cute we
love dirty e get divorce
you sound onto me i'm sorry you're
getting divorced this is how i always
kind of common nowadays you know just
like marriages just don't last and great
modern times by the banks well e
t any do i need to go
back to the planet or can i
do it from here kids can we
do it over zoom could do it
over zoo
oh well it's good if it's convenient
and yeah i don't want to leave
my wife obviously and we have eighteen
children where we're doing reality show yeah
it's kind of based on how he
was a child star but also kind
of just yeah our life because we've
eighteen kids yeah it's e t kids
and counting so it's eight ten is
one of them may well
one of them has a really long
neck and we've been gathering and while
i've been wondering because i remember that
we had sex one time but i
didn't slow notes like
slow down slow slow slow slow yeah
let's slow down slow down slut you
move too fast yeah go down to
this bridge
slowdowns let you move to fires alright
and we letter yeah yeah okay ah
i'm supposed to guess paul yeah i'm
saying or and no no no yeah
i'm guessing you i i'm going through
a nasty divorce
oh ah so disappointed so sorry wait
i thought i heard yours and then
i forget what it was well do
you wanna know his
yeah what is yeah paul what is
yours penis breath it's penis
ah you always find a good way
to bring him yeah yeah steely dan
yeah yeah those lou reed is low
yeah yes right um great character your
way or guesses right remember i remember
what i thought yeah barring something in
my head and then i went okay
and then i just completely forgot so
okay
hey i said it a few times
hold on no nothing mine was slow
down
ooh okay because i said it right
at the beginning i mean i was
like go down slot which then i
was like what's not backs why would
it be that yeah i said slow
down slow down ah yeah okay so
now is not able to guess your
lauren them's the breaks i did yet
said it a few tony remember here
i know you were talking over it
oh well that's my fault thanks
see but but i know but she's
into your routine again because i wanted
to be sure you heard was i
talking still yeah alright
ah it's true that's a good point
alright why don't you why don't we
go back to a word and it's
got to be at least five syllables
okay so text i'll text you lauren
will go back to the original way
what other way
sorry yeah i'll text paul yes and
i'll text lol okay so i'm texting
paul alright so doing phrase again no
we're doing what one word that has
to be at least five seven syllables
five syllables yes that's a that's like
that's a lot but okay
alright i have texted paul my scott's
got my word
i've texted lauren okay incredible and i
have not received lawrence at this point
still waiting for though and here it
is yep got it that ding never
contain never came but the thing is
not happening with the reviewing navigate to
it's happening when someone else text me
okay oh okay here we go very
interesting
because you open the text no i
didn't it just alerted okay anyway no
yours like when i sent you at
you opened it so oh but i
waited for the ding and then it
popped up on the thing didn't ding
and so i opened it oh yeah
here we go we don't need argue
but why do you want the ding
now i love the dang yeah
i don't hear it i get sick
carnival time carnival time step right up
oh i've never been to the carnival
before i guess it's carnival time it's
it's kind of i'm forty five a
m it's kind of time come on
out of your houses yeah i was
just on my way to bass the
slugger it's i don't know that i'm
in the mood for a card i
was jogging up and adam folks come
over here and slam the bell slot
slab the bell i have always wanted
to slam the bell yeah tell me
do you have any ah weird freaks
of their ah we do we got
a bearded lady okay yeah let's not
i won't say that's a freak yeah
somebody with elephant isis oh it's the
elephant with the long tail i was
trying to just oh i want solely
to see a freak somebody was
no potatoes are trying to think of
mononucleosis or anorexia nervosa oh yeah can
we hurry this along please sure rush
oh i don't know whether i want
to go into this carnival so she
can speak a little more expeditiously okay
really be better for me because i
would try to hit the ding all
right i'll
i'll give it right it fills your
ago i'd love to hit the dig
hit the dig that alright here we
go ready and abracadabra wow really beautiful
you say that most ambitiously
most indubitably the most interesting thing i've
seen these days
alright i'm sure to you this seems
like a mere triviality
may i smash the dig please smash
the table sir we're waiting for you
to smash the day you hit it
most readily
giraudo bo oh he's overcompensating something in
his bodies other means to try my
best to approve that he's a man
alright okay here we go most intuitively
conditionally
alright alright alright we've all done
ah
alright lauren can you guess what paul's
word was mister gave me the word
no i go you gave me the
e no no no it was it
was it was early on although fairly
recent once we heard mr right down
i know um yeah what the fuck
was it because you started taking a
bunch of words
oh my god what was that i
don't remember i did no i did
no hold on wait give me a
hint but then the scene got too
deep i know it was my character
yeah we give me a hint was
something that i said earlier
just say it yeah yeah you we'll
we'll we'll if he says it and
you knew it okay yeah i'll know
if i know yeah okay mononucleosis yeah
that wasn't my oh really yeah i
thought you you put anorexia nervosa you
said a few different things at that
elephant titus yeah yeah yeah yeah we
listed gotten excited about elephant titus because
it really opened
up to be able to say that
yeah okay okay paul are you gonna
guess mine
i want to say abracadabra
i said that to throw you off
it's expeditiously right app additionally expeditiously and
what was my thought expeditiously was to
throw me off ah and that africa
had ever been the second one right
i i forgot that i was supposed
to pay attention to you i was
paying incision to paulie it's really hard
that it's really this game is hard
so i do i don't either
no i don't have a guess what
was we're compensating oh good good good
this is a good game i'm trying
to sleep it wasn't most intuitively which
i couldn't say boosted very billing tip
i'd even want most in most
well guys thank you so much for
listening we have i mean what i
like about that game is we have
fun playing it yeah what i like
about the game do do do do
do we have fun playing it um
look if you want to hear we
haven't talked about three visiting on the
tubes for awhile boy that's true earlier
episodes from the beginning are coming out
on tuesdays we like to
call it three visiting on the tubes
um they're coming out coming out for
free bumped from behind the paywall if
you're listening without ads which you could
do at stitcher premium or at cb
world um you won't hear those because
they're all up there behind the paywall
without ads exactly but ah if you're
if you're listening to the free version
that's on tuesdays if you want to
call us
you can call us at
i pointing a po i'm sorry i
didn't realize ah hag claims eight hag
claims eight the number eight to number
eight and if you want to write
to us
good luck three mm usa gmail dot
com yeah if you want oh no
that's it instagram oh instagram yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah um we love you
piss pigs thank you so much for
listening and let us know how the
poll goes yes we'll be monitoring closely
but let us know how it goes
our slash threesome we're going to be
monitoring it closely but you let
let us know how yeah so we
know that we're not crazy
yeah please keep track of that poll
let i know and really everyone go
vote because it does make a difference
because you might be sitting here going
well everyone's gonna vote for my thing
no they're not no actually that's why
you believe yeah the a game i
wrote condors what your conscious should reggie
miller become an honorary piss pig yeah
alright well by law
hi
ugh