three
are there monkeys in here
you're a monkey
oh that's crazy i swear to god
i heard a monkey yeah anything yeah
yeah i know only you lose your
marbles am i going insane yes your
head in the zoo you're absolutely going
to but i do think about the
zoo a lot really yeah i remember
what do you think about it i
think i think it smells okay and
one by one so
i want to buy one with someone
else so i can say we bought
a zoo yes yes so kind of
like just on any given day you're
just kind of like the zoo smells
yeah and even our yeah and you
know you are right thank you and
thanks because you know why and here's
my theory the animals shit everywhere interesting
and then the people clean
enough but not right away i think
it's tourists okay yeah i think they
make the smell i think it's people
who are tauruses
can you imagine if we we just
lived in a zoo year round like
if like aliens abducted us yeah like
a slaughterhouse five kind of situation what
kind of ours suck man what if
people are coming by and looking at
us yeah i hope a slaughterhouse five
doesn't have honestly it's fine i hope
that every day if we are in
a zoo it's not that bad they
did a good job yeah because we
each get to kind of make it
our own
a very wide ranging habitat because evolves
planes we don't know we don't know
what the other planets are they might
be zoo visitors yeah they probably are
right because like yeah we think are
wonderful so you've got to put a
quarter like we think it's amazing to
have like planes and stuff but like
if you went to another planet and
you saw what it was like when
they don't have a zoo there yeah
you'd be like
oh we're actually really confined they think
it's cute that we get plain yeah
they're like well they also think they're
going somewhere i think it's cute that
we have zoos they're like oh there
is a zoo and the he put
these other animals in zoos yeah i
think right back role that's mortifying that's
really oh my god things that's humiliating
it's like when a child has a
little like kitchen place yeah
oh like oh you think you're really
cooking don't yeah that foods made of
wood idiot
hey welcome i read that there
welcome to three of them i'm scott
i'm paul i'm blind and this is
another episode this is episode two o
two just can you believe palin drama
monday oh if she was sunday oh
that's my ne oh la don't have
to and
sunday yeah the man that deadly
nah it's perfect i was listening to
it and i was like this first
of all i love that song but
secondly said out of the way let
me just make that clear none of
songs about how like just a hard
day it's been a hard day like
it's like i'm not gonna get there
which what did he she he she
wishes it was prince okay i know
prince rodin and then suzanna little prince
which was the name but suzannah just
expressing that for highway sunday into which
she was saturday yeah but i don't
have to run day because it's like
saturday you're still doing she yeah like
yeah kids you're doing i don't scatter
today are in the song falling that
catherine stolen princess anna pick up their
kids yeah i think they're just out
party it would have had good children
like trout together yeah i think we
don't know that they didn't oh my
god you're right that's a mystery
so you're just shutting it down the
investigation
this is a cold case lower that's
a mystery to it was understandable never
saw or cold case episode should have
ended with that yeah mystery the space
remains cold cold as hell this was
never solved it didn't happen
what did they did it didn't we
made this up at lunch
watching the show for years
oh by the way we forgot to
tell you all of these are stories
a room of writers wrote that one
ah
it's good is but it's good
i'd bet it's a good bet alright
so it's been less than twenty four
hours since we've seen each other so
much has gone down to so much
okay tell us everything i watched more
love is blind oh okay reality week
watching more survivor i'm not sure why
people why the hell oh so sorry
my trainers australia ah the traitors australia
love is blind um i'm people are
growing on me the first episode they
put in there people who straight up
leave yeah so which is a good
thing and then they have some love
happening and i'm excited but i always
wonder because the people who don't make
it to the altar are the same
ones to me like right in the
bachelor were in this she really should
but like what kind of situation would
you have to be in in your
life in order to undergo a love
is blind it's a great question kind
of you know i what i watched
that and i think about that because
i just go you're really limiting the
pool in a way but then you're
like but you've but these are people
who've been trying to date on the
apps and people who supposedly are ready
for marriage when yeah well
narrows everything down this is the last
resort i've tried literally everything else i
should go in this game show but
there's one guy who's saying who's literally
like i'm about a bad person i
don't think i'm a good person yet
or something and then this girl is
bad to get engaged to him yeah
she already knew that he said that
just like that's a red flag for
me and i'm like it should be
that's pretty much like it's a red
flag it's red glass you get one
hundred flags yeah yeah exactly it's just
one wait is this the guy that
had the lists of question now it's
a different guy that guy laughed like
yeah he told two girls the same
thing and then they found out and
then he was like here's the same
kind of language of oh i can't
wait to talk to your father to
ask him for permission
oh and you kept talking you know
who's really annoying and he also kept
oh sorry i don't mean to say
about him he also
he also kept ah talking about how
america was watching and they were like
okay but how about this relationship means
they put america will see that i
did this and it's like you're talking
about canada what about me what would
the person you're talking to like focus
on what you just did not how
it will be perceived by america so
you want to do this me
yeah do what you love is blind
i got to go on i wanna
see me don't tell me they should
play if i fall in love fishing
put one married person in there just
to like throw a monkey in the
rural monkey in the wrench but they
should they should be able to say
here to know you don't they should
be able to say that they're meh
married like at a certain point there
like i do have a secret i
am american but we are already falling
in love so wanted to see if
that's a deal breaker
and i will not get divorced now
my current partner is that a red
flag
that's a red flag but yes let
me ask you this because i've wrestled
with this now that i somehow have
reality programming in my life i know
this has been such a great show
such a turn around for you because
early in our early seasons paul you
were mentally out when we would do
rio i was mentally diminished yeah you
would be you
literally could see you out of the
island drinking a margarita thinking about zoo
talked thinking wow this is stainless
and that is my happy place i
picture myself tropical drink little umbrella thinking
about how much the suit smells like
shit
yeah vampire what do i tell you
i meant to see vampire vampire zoo
emergency vanderpump vampire zoo but you got
very excited but i don't think there's
anything that
maybe one of the perishing okay there
they're up all night going to see
skies it's all animals drink blood if
zoo i don't think i don't think
in any vampire feed this is just
a good idea if you know what
that here's what it felt like to
me when you say vampires you all
excited yeah studio sixty on the sunset
strip
vampire zoo we got it i'm doing
all like everybody go whoa i don't
watch that how can i access that
i when i have em all you
do yes i do he's collected them
i've been threatening tv watch podcast only
i do it yeah i gotta do
it yeah we watched the first one
for sean clements podcast it's avail
able to watch somewhere i guess you
two probably yeah or we rented it
but it's it's very good but i
will when i'm trying to say about
vampire zoo is i don't think i've
seen it in any movie about no
wonder why that is those two words
i fuck up and put together like
a world that has enslaved the vampires
oh okay
vampires in the zoo i thought the
animals were vampires ooh that's not your
talk that's a little vampire it's too
much crossover that's true because cal so
yeah that's really good actually watch the
little vampire see what you think why
does it go there are little little
vampire with jonathan lippe nick even though
we do try to always bring up
jonathan lipp nikki every day
day of my life that's the other
thing he thinks about yeah absolutely give
me always think the human head weighs
eight pounds i wonder if he would
agrees what happens i always come to
that i think about how much i
look i'm having trouble to drink right
here on my time on a beach
beautiful ocean waves ah clear blue water
like you can see for miles wow
oh it's um swaying palms sipping my
drink i'm start thinking about visitors smelling
like shit and then eventually after a
couple hours i start to think what
jonathan le nikki agree with me yeah
because anybody ever really heard his opinions
on anything no you should call it
kind of don't know what we're very
guarded but you kinda don't know where
he's coming from
yeah pretty much anything he's so afraid
to offend people call into our three
main episodes if you're listening jonathan jonathan
leb nicky please go to head claimed
eight dot com leave us a voicemail
do you think the zoo smells like
shit also what do you think about
other things also go to do you
think the zoo smells like shit dot
com where you can vote in our
poll
it's not about whether the zoo smells
like oh it's stuff that's just like
to grab your attention it's a poll
about like flavors of imams yes yes
how many are there and we're just
wondering yeah but um did vanderpump gets
you going on the reality
yeah you know what it did in
a way that southern charm did not
you were trying that southern charm was
the only one we watched because was
the town that's such a like mistake
yeah paul you were bad well believe
me we knew it was a mistake
but we couldn't stop making it season
after season because you would watch and
go like look at that building we've
been there yeah but you just didn't
know how much of the sound don't
you didn't know how good he don't
gaf you know like you know and
you're limiting yourself oh absolutely and and
of course with vanderpump now in the
wake of sandoval
all ah it being like the
it being about ah like the mass
completely dropping yeah and now they're acknowledging
they have an audience they're acknowledging people
watch the show there's not not enough
as far as i'm concerned where they
should be saying like you know the
only reason this is a quote unquote
friend group is because we're on a
tv show we would never hang out
with each other
they're getting close to that though yeah
i feel like they're getting very close
to that if this is the closest
company not even friends are to be
did not know that they're not even
friends maybe they're not friends any more
or that how much of it is
for show like like like we're doing
a tv show and we'd never hang
out when the tv shows not on
yeah there's there's like a scene coming
up so much time and later episode
where there's
somebody's challenged on it you know the
future you know is that from is
that are you are you saying that
in life you're saying that because the
cameras are here which is like it's
wild to watch but like i actually
we just really quick yeah okay really
quick just really really how do we
get it okay you understand oh shit
those two quick know i feel like
if if
you're at that point it's almost like
how we don't even want to share
a real story until we're recording it's
like they should just know i yeah
cool op story for mamas they they
they really could do know what to
communicate and waste good stuff that they
could be doing for the shows that's
why we just don't even hang it
that's why we need to do reveal
our connect
tions on this podcast every careful blue
yellow green purple i mean you get
a pebble to start you get glasses
emojis but um paul gave up on
connections because he thinks it's bullshit and
i just got the new york times
bummed me out i don't want the
new york jets the old gray lady
related the paper of record okay so
we're gonna say about vidant
a pimp ah so you said the
one guy was annoying on that show
and then you sort of backtrack that
you felt bad about it huh yeah
but here's the thing he is yeah
well i want to say i feel
like i feel like the idea of
these shows and i'm not saying this
is positive but i feel like
these shows are they're inviting us to
do that and they're giving us license
to do that that's that's kind of
their whole point is you're looking through
a window at these people and you're
making your opinions about them yes yes
and from week ten i know they're
talking about complicit in it but at
the same time they're they're young and
don't know what they're doing and then
suddenly there's a
pending on the show yeah some of
the love is blind people are not
that young but some are like twenty
four but somewhere like thirty three thirty
four year old but guess what those
people can be annoying yeah yeah yeah
and i mean it's a also a
really tough situation to not be annoying
in because slowly your trying to find
your husband and wife through a partition
and as lily saw
sullivan put it you're like in a
warehouse that's freezing it seems because they're
always they always a blankets around them
that's a recipe for annoying i do
think that they're getting fed more actively
because yetzer where the blankets they always
have like a girl learning blankets around
them but they're also just you know
wearing a cocktail dress
cute dress maybe it's like it's not
that welcome but like the pose is
very raw let it go they have
blankets around them all the twitter strangers
i wanna like in the movie lincoln
it's like when you lose you know
when they're cozy they're hanging out in
the little shared communities and interesting like
the whole blanket industry that's getting into
it once what about slanket
tz
once we got like people always talking
i was like we never talk about
saying what about buggies
but we don't need him anymore like
last time was the last time you
bought a blanket what let's see we've
got a buggy
when's the last time you were like
oh too cold in here let me
go down to the store and buy
a blanket i love i like it
i have too many but i love
single use blank hey why i love
i like we have like a big
shoe box full about like geez yeah
it's great
get all your oils on you blow
your nose on it
oh that's all that's a dream by
create these remember in the past we
can be the new my pillow guy
my blank emily blake it's my pillow
news on it's my way we do
it like like clinics we go blank
x
yeah and then that starts to become
the word for blanket and then you're
like it's actually a brand why don't
we call it bluffs like puffs okay
do you why did i got my
visitors were doing it why don't you
call him bleed i was like cheetos
whoa because i think people think blood
is involved okay what about chea blows
now she blows she blows jetblue hey
maybe she blows blows
well var she blows that one out
here that how about darshan blankets yeah
the r she blankets are she blankets
is if that's it's ok but i
want to say and the previous seasons
of love is blind there was like
a whole like lawsuit or something about
yes and i cut out people entirely
didn't feed them which was
really weird because i was watching that
season going like no one no no
one's getting engaged during their they ended
up with like two couples and it
was so boring well but but because
the title there are leaking a lot
they're eating a lot i think that
they weren't fed in the tenderloin now
look if sushi ala time you're always
eat maybe that guy's making a sandwich
these are all things
have the end of sushi all the
time that guy's making a sandwich they
seemed to not have access to food
at their mexico the notion that was
said in the in the sort of
exposed a doc right you series use
series we all series
you know paul i wanna bring this
up on monday paul and i were
singing the theme song to see age
pure cane sugar that's correct right before
we started oh yeah a little warm-up
while while you were taking care idyllically
always from just mckenna singing get on
doughboys okay that's already know what otherwise
you don't know it from life but
cna sugar still
exists why do they not advertise anymore
it was everywhere in the seventy s
and eight well that was back when
you guys didn't know that you could
just buy sugar right they so it
was like oh that's right now available
to the public yeah it was like
yes be like you could only have
it if your separation or you have
to the library yeah i rent it
but at what point are they just
like yeah
we're good everyone knows about us i
think it's kind of like it's gotta
feel great such a basic image so
basic bench
i can see the packaging and i
just go that's one o u c
h me my mom uses that she's
been around since ninety no six day
but they didn't start really advertising with
that song until the seventies or eighties
right and then at some point they're
like ok we did what we need
to do maybe the head of the
company hated that song you sing it
sia
a h pure cane sugar is not
the one raum o y e growing
in the sta when you go when
you bank maybe usually do see and
age pure sugar that slow la
maybe you should say weird breakdown the
song for the cigarettes get confused and
also so that's the writers like that
song contest yeah and then america uses
the singers yeah that sounds version what's
the version you know c and eight
c n h that's of the name
being amy i mean she's saying a
fast ver
asian fighter you're making that up find
it but that was name um that
was one of our main mom that
was one of our mutuals i'm gonna
text jest right now and ask her
to voice to voice mail it okay
and well yeah and you can plug
it in here but i was one
of our mutuals paul you and i's
mutuals
point about mcdonalds was they were saying
why does mcdonald's need to advertise anymore
they say could use all that money
for charity or whatever i think they
need to advertise and see i was
sort of like yeah they still need
to because the reason they advertise all
the times to remind you all the
time of like oh that makes me
hungry let me go today also thing
if they didn't advertise we'd start to
go what's going on there yeah but
that's what i'm saying about cn h
it worked for them sugar is one
thing it's one thing they don't they
don't sugar is one one thing sugar
is one thing yeah no no no
make dead okay four hundred
menu items it's made up of granules
though sugar yes okay so it's like
most it's out of more than most
things so is sugar the collective noun
for all of those granting all of
those things yeah well it's a table
the collective noun for all of the
atoms and molecules of water is like
water
or the name of like you know
two hydrogen molecules and then one oxygen
molecule no okay
what are you the oh you're still
texting js hello good morning i have
so nice to talk to you
getting into my dream home so the
stream about cn h someone online i'd
like to try to make it make
more sense but it's like someone online
was saying that they've now text all
their friends like they're joe biden or
kamala harris texting doing like this is
urgent urgence do this was to go
to movies say this is
asking you for your c zero know
lauren by not going to the movies
is there anything i can say to
get you to have lunch with me
how about the one so wear it
it was like are you gonna watch
if you know what is right you
your watch the state of the union
president biden will be humiliated that one
really that's so crazy i guess a
humiliated him by not watching yeah me
too i watched three times i don't
know what i was doing so you're
you're if you have you had a
binary choice traders or state of the
union
or i guess going outside or anything
around every trainer decision you actually were
able to do whatever you wanted right
yeah that's true gotta be on the
beach thinking about zeus i'm like shit
okay so but let's say you had
to watch something okay you pick traders
yes what if you had already see
you and if i didn't have it
interviewed already what did you have seen
all tr
eaters episode was harder from the beginning
what have you already seen the state
of the union
and what if you wrote the state
of the union anyone to see how
it got said hey everybody they say
the union strong everybody you know that
america is the greatest country in the
world so you're saying that depression
and that you're voting for trump i
don't age difference there it's twenty two
months yeah like we gotta stop like
it as a country acting like he's
older than yeah it's not that he's
too old know it's other reason your
title here's what i want i want
thirty five year old like they know
you don't
nah so i don't i don't necessarily
but there's also no getting blackout drummond
yeah okay what's come up when obama
was president who's like forty something i'm
like yeah let's get a forty something
pres fusion build that yeah yeah someone
who's got exactly the
yeah they have some new idea yes
and they're in there with it you
know with with talking about their their
hips i mean my basketball only they
were dancing i mean obama biden makes
good meals small given that biden makes
good names
i know he's in bed making those
those let's go brandon yoga another dark
room
super bowl
red eyes
alright we have to take a break
and read aizen by
ah
likes the band
and we're back paul still laughing about
me giving me shit
joe biden sitting up in bed in
the white house making them be like
money as i could see trump doing
that like for sure p m until
one p m when he would go
into yeah absolutely yeah he does yeah
yeah to eat often and it's clearly
him i mean that's the difference i
guess that's the main difference i see
between them although you could i feel
like trump
could very easily have somebody tweet as
him and they could nail the voice
oh yeah you don't i mean everyone
can do it simply everyone can do
i actually the one i'm the oscars
i was like is that real or
not but then it was i kind
of didn't know at first that it
was going to be trump but it
was kind of perfect that it was
real yeah yeah the oscars from two
months ago i don't give a shit
man yeah we can't talk about history
but we're still talking about tweets written
by presidents
former president still talking about yeah this
is presently actual history until history what
is your favorite what is your favorite
history thing when trump tweeted that thing
during the oscars comment yeah
so yeah it was such a big
deal it was like that kicked off
the industrial revolutions pasteurizing milk now do
we ever even think about it what
if when they kicked off the industrial
revolution if pitbull had been alive and
he could have performed at it okay
kick off that would've been so cool
mr worldwide it really feels like a
missed opportunity yeah or at least mr
lover
does that one of his name's no
sh
sure love a level oh i'm so
sorry i apologize to people as well
as ecologist plums the nose just here
comes oh what is this all famous
tracks
what does people do since he chases
other dogs
he shaved his head he's not as
mean as you think he yeah people
always think pitbull is like so aggressive
but he's actually a really nice guy
and he's actually really control people does
have a locking jaw
pitbull will wear a harness around his
mouth or muzzle if if if it
makes you more comfortable
if you ever see those pictures of
pitbull when he didn't have the current
pitbull look and he looks like can't
imagine he looks just so funny i've
never seen why does this high school
picture he has long hair so ah
what how do i access to say
people not looking like pitbull
ah this is a classic meme format
oh guys she responded absolutely no prob
i absolutely hear you play here we
go absolutely no prob here we go
this is just mckenna singing
add coming in at number two it's
just mckenna for the fifth week in
a row with the c and h
j goal
hi paul learning scott hi freedom listeners
well she's in a church c and
h c and h my mom used
to make her cakes it makes the
greatest cookies snacks and candy dan dandy
island kids love okay it grows clean
and sweet they eat it when it's
freshly cut and then that's
quite a treat neat touched by so
just by way th comes from the
sugar cane it makes the status sex
and candy in the bright pink package
yeah exactly isn't that cute so now
i've never heard that before so maybe
th still is putting out jams yeah
yeah yeah maybe every generation gets their
own scene h jingle and nobody else
can hear it okay pitbull with hair
people with hair dog people but that
is odd oh boy so it's it
reminds me of how
much like every human bodies just kind
of ridiculous but you've got to find
the way oh yeah forgot about that
the the way like the the one
thing you can wear that makes you
look cool or the one thing you
know if if it's shaving your head
maybe it's that yeah maybe sunglasses but
for him it was sunglasses wearing a
tuxedo and shaving his head those were
the three things in a combo that
make
like sunglasses like joe biden
with red ice yeah it's kind of
oh here's him with super long hair
look at this
oh that's hey that's a look he
say did he choose that age he
stopped balding he just shaved his sexy
felt like it i don't know this
is him with like totally different vibe
this is like guy from game of
thrones jon jon snow yes to jon
snow look you know nothing pitbull should
he go back to it he should
would grow it out slowly but surely
to here's what i would do for
people right girl and i so nice
i've always wondered and i should well
what i would do is i would
sit down and think about the zoo
and think i'm finally bringing it smells
good i like fighting breaking my silence
on this this by the way this
reminds me of like any nowadays on
entertainment news headlines are always like someone
so revealed yeah
or you know it's like they're not
reviewed they just happen to say it
that happen to be for some reason
i broke my silence on something
you asked me a question i tried
to not answer it um ah what
so far people and i still had
a full head of hair but i
shave it for a look oh huh
i would hide in my pitbull mansion
good for like a few months okay
right like howard hughes but yes i
wouldn't tell anyone no one knows where
i am right yeah and you're getting
groceries delivered but but you're saying like
leave about the door yeah i'm putting
on a voice like
that's good because i think here bulls
momo we exactly and ah that's intimidating
and i let my hair and my
beard grow okay good sort of like
a yandle never trimming the beard because
just like gandalf that's dirty like that
yeah this this seems like a week
maybe he did do you think there
was a mo or gandalf actually thought
i'm gonna grow
my hair was entity asked people was
like hey frodo should i grow this
out should i do like photo should
i do like all one length and
just like swept back yeah and then
photos like man what about a feather
cut
we got gandalf with like a jennifer
aniston really loved that's i love can
we do that into ai wow i've
never used ai yeah we do that
into ai can you please make pimple
with jennifer aniston i know this makes
me sound a million years old but
how do you even get off
how do you even do ai like
do you have to go to a
thing honestly i don't know i know
that there's a website owner one thing
i know that gbt or whatever right
yeah sure there's a bunch of em
now i honestly don't you just go
to a website and then ask him
to put something in and they does
it for free or do you have
to pay him
i think you get some for free
some for free like this one is
joining us try it so here i
go to some people oh wow i'm
next to you i'm hiding
mr worldwide right here mr area code
would sign up john i would hide
in my everything was just sign up
fuck this shit i don't want you
to know where i am i give
him i don't want to give you
my assassination cord you're hiding in your
house
i'm hiding my house i'm letting my
hair and beard grow
after i'm gonna say three months i
take a pair of i take a
suit one of my famous suits yeah
i cut like triangular raggedy edges in
the sleeves and you cut into the
short and the pants come in shorts
with like raggedy edges raggedy andy style
much like
it was not that raggedy but like
frankenstein style was like a fungi on
his rag doll sets more really work
yeah he was a rag doll but
he was actually very well put together
but it's very pejorative to call him
rag i think so yeah and raggedy
ann yeah yeah i'm glad they found
each other yeah they're siblings but i
call a press conference
are they who have sex think your
siblings they're basically twain i always thought
i always thought they were siblings or
dating love for siblings are dating raggedy
ann raggedy andy
that's why do you think they're siblings
things are dating those siblings or dating
siblings your data yes oh website instagram
you have to sign up for that
ah you have to set up to
have it you know you don't you
don't just sign up i mean unless
you want to be one i'd like
to be i call a press conference
in miami nach okay nach and i
say i was shipwrecked
i just our siblings by the way
oh okay loring raggedy ann and her
brother raggedy andy are a couple of
ragdoll couple a couple of coming to
say yeah you just said yeah i
rest my case your honor face dismiss
this is the sentence
a couple of years sentence living in
marcel's playroom with their marcy who the
fuck is ourselves with their very best
friends they go in a lot of
wild adventures oh my friends never heard
of anyone other than these two could
be thomas grady joan
continues raggedy ann and her brother raggedy
andy are a couple of ragdoll boy
works
it continues to save this the exact
same thing yeah so this is a
candidate to id visa many people are
asking about raggedy ann and andy and
are they pregnant and yes they are
and they couldn't be happier but they
are not a couple anymore should i
sign up for this just to get
the gandalf picture
why don't we just put a real
chance just put out to the van
sanders these pictures alright we want to
see gandalf with first of all beautiful
feathery feathery like almost like a fair
faucet i want yeah see like um
like ah in the same post in
the same swimsuits as fairfax vienna same
swimsuits nipple spoken golden girls kind of
look yeah sure sure okay we'll do
it in style getty
e and then we want to see
him with the rachel give us four
squares different looks for gandi did it
sell getty event getty images yes yeah
great first it was just pictures of
her
like let's shout slightly that's making everybody
i love people now when they go
to like red carpets or friends of
ours when they go to red carpets
they now like rip off the getty
images and they're so low so grainy
when she posed no i know it's
a real danger zone i've been a
lot of celebrities have this problem and
there's you'll you'll notice like a listers
posting grainy images i use go
let's let's wake up let's put the
glasses on let's get a second opinion
on this picture let's make sure everyone
can see it well why not buy
it from getting images yeah i'm talking
about literally like julia roberts pose yeah
grainy image of somebody else i'm going
i'm not like i'm not so someone
at our level we can't afford this
shit i'm not paying five hundred dollars
for getting him to myself yeah your
mouse and yeah i'm into me
either yeah nobody should send it to
you i feel if it's you you
should send it to yeah but because
they've captured your soul is a little
bit but anyway i'm just like we
need everyone to wake up when you
slow down you just share a few
people in your room get raggedy let's
just see if it's grainy or not
you know it's hard to tell sometimes
you don't know
no
james jesse we saw the large glass
stars the martin george steve martin show
we've talked about i think he was
thinking the lowest resume when they were
like to project at the hollywood bowl
a joke no no they were it
was it was part of their routine
where they were talking about certain celebrities
i feel like the elon musk one
was so low rep yeah it was
really funny it was such a tiny
tiny picture i busted someone on zoom
the other day i was like you're
when when they first come on before
they turn their camera yeah yeah it's
like an icon of their picture whatever
it was these small
this lowest his thing and he's like
oh i guess i didn't even know
i had one that must be from
like twelve years ago when i signed
up for weird yeah was it bill
nye the science covers yeah since i
was a flawless yeah i think oh
i stood behind him in line to
meet the president speaking of obama wow
like a county fair yep
it was the pie eating contest hey
everybody we want to go with me
me that i could do it
ah come on he was the president
we should be able to imitate a
big fucking deal you know what i
mean yeah i know it's like there's
shit everyone should be able to imitate
the prez yes that is our first
amendment rights yeah one a yes first
amendment guarantees us the right to be
good at imitating the president and with
that anna
i'm not saying we can be arrested
for it or whatever because obviously we
can't but just you can't cancel us
imitate a rest president's town
you can't can't have you been arrested
now i know you guys i have
yes you have for what smoking a
cigarette in the subway oh right we've
done this for my classic tales cigarette
in the subway cigarette and yeah no
so this is where the bathroom was
trying i was trying to do the
girlfriend of the coma
yeah there's a view
the cigarette in the summer though do
you think raggedy ann and andy had
a child it would be be i
don't know the damage well here's the
thing they should absolutely she's a baker
we need to expand the the baker
we need to expand the ragged verse
yeah why aren't they having kids why
is it the scarecrow in
their family yeah he's back now here's
what's wrong with what you're doing jonathan
green yeah you know who that is
now and scarecrow from wizard of oz
yeah all your favorite guys great care
pumpkin head on by the way can
anyone just call something scarecrow now because
i mean he's in wizard of oz
and batman that's like we want to
throw back okay oscar
grow we need to go bash in
their lineage can see who are the
parents who burst them because then how
did they fall that's how we can
expand the universe i'm just thinking how
funny it would be a scarecrow in
battle was oscar crow a scarecrow hello
kids scarecrow we have to stop a
scarecrow
it's just one way to stop a
penguin from a corneum so he insists
that's what he should be called isn't
that why i'm the scarecrow just adding
the word law to it makes it
so chilling man yeah but but mr
freeze is just mister free xy joker
she's not that scary so much scary
than steve miller yeah steve miller the
he was just a joke
acre the song was called vo not
even near midnight to ooker it's called
v joker the song but then he's
just a joker in the song yeah
but he's the quintin because everyone else
calls him the joker like he's talking
about himself so he's he's oh my
god he admit it yeah he's he's
being
very high magicians being very forthcoming with
his downfall if you're gonna come please
make it fourth do you think people
speaking of humble brags which i thought
but didn't say um are we allowed
to do that
for transplant i'm glad that's all the
teacher but but um you know our
good friend harris ah coined that term
and please incorrectly to create the lexicon
yeah it's in the dictionary butter is
is it you had to pay for
your app it was probably because they're
updating it with humble brush shit now
don't even get to the riz in
there because people don't use it all
that much anymore
no they don't humble brag yeah to
people is it snows it's slang this
it's so almost more like you just
kind of say like someone's annoying is
there a difference between now you just
say fuck you is there a difference
between coining a slang term and coining
a word that is then used in
perpetuity yes
but i think at being in the
dictionary gives it a very long lasting
like the person who came up with
apple yeah right
i was smell we all call that
fruit i was so early that was
god talking to adam that's you don't
here's what's cool though we have this
opportunity here we can do that because
there are things that have been named
like what like like what's this glass
glass although like it's made of glass
so we should call it something different
i'd call it
oh man words like that i'm gonna
call it i just made that up
window that's made of glass but we
call it a window yeah although some
people call it a glass looking glass
looking well looking looking glass it's a
mirror well that's made of glass yeah
i know well what about people should
call these looking-glass because you look more
outside windows than i do
yeah already here i can't argue you
sit around looking at a mirror all
day no you sit around looking outside
the window mean i look at a
mirror old dads look gorgeous you hear
so much make your run you know
you look marvelous he um no black
silly crystal oh sure he would do
fernand
endo llamas yes that does sound vaguely
know you know mommy rock ma he
would do fernando lamas muhammad ali sammy
davis junior a lot of semi zoo
a lot of people of other races
yeah did you take it i knew
the job good he was having fun
here's what comedy needs to be in
foreign and a common use case
but now people just sensitive used to
be a different era here's what i
know about billy crystal his hat size
is size seven why do you know
that does not call small i was
just mix come small because i think
he has a big head because i'm
seven and five minimal imagine how little
his body is telling
like a weird married up um i
don't know you can't be that to
i was shocked to this oh wait
i did a thing with him
you tell me you you did you
look marv i did a table read
with him but i don't know that
i was ever standing next to him
yeah he might have a long torso
i don't know tali is um i
would like five eleven five ten i
was shocked billy crystal five eight i
don't think so you said you're five
eleven i'm five ten he's probably five
i'm five nine
you could be five nine okay i
was shocked to discover i was taller
than killian murphy whenever i'm taller than
anyone i'm shocked these shorties really well
celebrities these guys seven they they get
into movies too much guess i was
towering shape that's the same height as
kelly murphy
wow i like it i feel like
it's because they don't want to tip
the camera
look at this video the camera ah
you know how like twice all these
don't get in in tv shows and
movies oh noes yeah men men always
shorthand they don't want to let a
shorter camera sure about that yeah a
lot of leading men are short a
lot of them are tall as well
okay but a short is also at
are
there's no media it's very rare that
i didn't know i could tell you
right now there's no medium it's very
rare that i've been in a romantic
acting role within the person who is
taller than me yeah most of them
that's hard
alright let's dig break
and we're back and it's time for
a thirty church god's true words were
never spoken it's three your time three
your time is where we play a
game and the time the do it
is now and what happens is if
you want to send us a game
to play a parlor game a gamey
playing the car simply send it to
us at three dm usa at g
mail dot com that's email for it's
so easy it's so easy so weak
that this one submitted by the mysterious
marissa marissa wow no last name like
share this is called out of ten
one player the guesser while remain
earning players agree on a number from
one to ten the guests are asks
categories the others answer with an item
corresponding to the chosen number on a
scale from one to ten one being
worst ten being the best the answers
can be subjective and the personal opinion
of the person answering reason try to
explain this game to the other day
did you realise yeah when on on
mike no
no i it was a game that
i had like found on a blog
a weblog okay this this blog that
i follow where they were talking about
gameplay at the dinner table and then
this all the people were commenting and
i thought this one this is this
is it's very interesting i don't remember
you saying this at all great i
think we all were like huh and
then we could ever ask wow i
don't quite understand yeah we do need
to we need to
slow it down and explain it again
for example if the number is ten
or a hymnal and the guests are
gives the category films the person being
asked to reply with a film they
consider a ten out of ten okay
i've had a few rounds the guest
or tries to guess the number okay
so basically because we're going off of
how we know
know each other yeah we're gonna say
oh because scott i know scott loves
that movie he must have the number
here's here's how we should score it
in my opinion you shouldn't after we
after the two people who know the
number give their things the person should
give their guests and they get a
point for each
each time they guess incorrectly and whoever
has the lowest number at the end
of this wins does that make sense
why wouldn't you get a point for
getting it correct because if it takes
you four tries how would we score
icy okay okay all right so ah
lauren and i will be the people
you're going to be the guesser
okay i will be the people and
we're gonna text each other the numbers
that what's happening so lauren i'm going
then do i come up with the
category i e o so just you
and me texting yeah so i'll i'll
text you the number okay
and i text you a number no
oh it's the same same for saying
no i got it okay so we
have our number all you can come
up with a category let's say actors
actors in terms of how much we
like them or in terms of how
much i think they are good well
i owe what we think
it's what we think because it's going
off of our subjective things like we
have a number so i'm trying to
guess i'm trying to guess the number
you're trying to guess the number yeah
so so when you say like i
think that's a harder harder like you
should be more specific like attractive actors
and then we but then when you
have a member
or yeah i don't want to do
that i think he should be in
should be like ah like ah like
ah different not about i just not
judge a person okay just because i
don't want to say under what about
their cellulite good catch
like lorenzo love
um i don't know fuckin so broad
should we just do films but i
feel like you go let's do films
just to okay just alright so ease
into their beaks i'm guessing the number
you're guessing the number we're gonna give
you examples of what of what we
think on a scale of one to
ten these films are of how good
they are okay okay
alright so then i throw out names
of movies no no no no we
we give you the name of the
movie okay accord i've read a number
that we picked oh okay and then
you're trying to guess the number okay
yeah i think i'm gonna do one
guy one okay i just need a
second okay the sandlot
don't don't guess yet because lawrence oh
yeah and then my answer is
batman and robin
and now you guess the number that
we have agreed on of what we
think on a scale of one to
ten those films okay one
incorrect
while you're saying now i don't know
how to play this game yeah well
you've narrowed down one but doesn't get
to guess again yeah well we're we
do now we do another category okay
yeah no i know nothing another example
another film yes another film
um
scream four
um scream five
four incorrect
alright ah fried green tomatoes
um
surely any movie
ah start at the beginning start with
ah you know wings
hello nice feeling of any movie that
rocket ah don't land before time
lamp weights and just striking tomatoes yeah
to incorrect
you've guessed one two and four alright
do you guys know each other i'm
lauren
i'm gonna say
um
wow i'm gonna say
jurassic world two whatever that one was
okay
i'm gonna say
um
ah
i'm going to say an answer which
is going to sound like the words
um
don't give away future seasons of newcomers
um i'm gonna go with ah mask
of the phantasm
mask of the phantasm
i've said one you've said too and
you've said for three yes you've gone
high okay okay let's do it again
okay i want to do the category
and youtube do the number okay paul
do you want to text me the
number of guy doing i do i
do okay
this is exciting what's our category going
to be well i'm i'm gonna do
a different category each time so i
can kind of try to get okay
a different tribe out for a different
range of how we're okay getting the
information okay we have our number ok
candy bar candy bar okay
heath
score
one incorrect
those those both suck okay yeah it's
my personal pine okay but they're not
the worst thing that you've shared your
mouth well
yeah um
they would say ok the next category
is um sitcoms sitcoms um
are wisely no changing him because i
want to have a quarterback she wants
to be able to narrow it i
want to be able to go okay
because i okay you seem so we
can go weekend that was our practice
room we can go back to you
with the other minimums i'm seeing if
i like this version yes sandy yeah
okay i'll go with ah
ah
i'll go with um
i'll go with what i will go
with is
archie bunker's place
wow
i'm going to go with wings too
incorrect
oh my god
okay um the next category is
ah types of hats
types of hats
um like the fedoras that the members
of an sink would wear
i'm gonna say
and this is a straight-up the tuk
the beanie five incorrect fuck this
well because a baby is very different
from a fedora whatever okay so
yeah we're different people i know i
know i know you know you individually
never where you don't feel like you've
been talking to one person this entire
time a day which would i would
never wear a beanie know i wear
them i don't wear them out that
much but i wear around the house
i get ebenezer scrooge nike so different
though
so you say ebenezer scrooge nikah that
is a hat i wear it like
that mode of transportation
okay um
tiny car
um rentable scooter three info
here's here's the thing that that i
realised like it's a scale of one
to ten so there's still so much
room for things to be like just
joey to one to five no no
i think you should get better at
this
okay my next category is by the
way we're not telling you what you
get a divorce if you re guess
something you asked on you okay vacation
spot vacation spot um i'll go with
like ah
a ranch in montana
i'll go with
palm springs for incorrect
i hate this game
are you sad you decided to come
up with different i'm sad i'm sad
that ah
you're here yeah right yeah is it
okay um fast food restaurants um okay
carl's junior
that's what i was gonna say oh
you're so it's like a carl's junior
and it's like a fedora and it's
like a heath bar and it's like
montana ran was eighty two six yeah
correct yeah you got it those are
all ones babe okay for you i
know that's the subject
active you know not how well would
you know yourself i don't wanna go
to a ranch in montana why not
i don't want to do that you
are familiar some early gold
you left a bear okay let's do
it again find your smile let's do
it charlie christian now who's turn his
mind so you get so lauren you
text the number of all please do
it please okay please
looking for looking into waiting i am
writing the app looking for your name
for your name
ooh okay okay
ah
high school classes
like the actual periods yeah like a
course you would not like the grade
okay yeah
um english
um history
seven no okay
body parts on your body
um
fingers ice eight you know you're interested
in your answer
me too musical instruments that you enjoy
listening to oh wow okay
um
cello
guitar
nine yes yes you think your fingers
are nine yeah i think eyes are
number one what's yeah eyes are ten
signs your eyes are ten guys or
a town and so so you would
least want to lose your eyes
yeah you'd think oh i wouldn't ally
think i was listening and based on
judging yourself oh like tracking like about
yeah that's that's perfect so like my
eyes are not my one of my
top features what's what's the what beats
it my ass
ah alright that's gonna do it for
us
yeah um if you want to send
us a three three-acre you can do
it at three dm us a at
gmail dot com and you know what
you can also leave us a voice
message especially if you're jonathan lib nikki
yeah go to hag claims eight dot
com and leave us
voice message if you would like to
hear um sastre those ah stature those
is what i was gonna say thank
god those are our three meme episodes
we do remember two weeks every two
weeks your little mini episodes where we
we answer your voicemail yes your voicemail
and good prompts a conversation and we
have fun and we do those every
couple of weeks on cbc work
old as well as at this apple
podcast thing you can subscribe to an
outcast premium lemonade has all the details
about podcast premium ask her yeah and
um you can hear ad-free episodes of
cvb world and then also on tuesday
if you want to hear if you
don't want to bother with cvb world
ah i understand that we're all of
our previous
episodes are we're all sensitive people yeah
ah well since people with so much
um you can hear we re-release our
old episodes on tuesdays that's called three
days editing on the twos and you
can hear those just a few hours
subscriber to just a regular old dumb
dumb and then paul and
i are going to be in a
couple of weeks we're gonna be on
tour with c oh my gosh bananas
i'm also on tour dates do you
want to tories we don't want to
say dates yet but just start remember
don't wanna jinx it the cpa we
might not get to know comedy bang
bang tour kicks off in earnest in
a couple of weeks in june and
yes earnest will be there yes ernest
goes to tour
each city were filming an entire earnest
movie yeah harry and every city it's
gotta be exhausted don't you think we
have one day to do yeah well
that's the challenge and then we have
to do the show at night yeah
god you know we're gonna don't have
some victory the show we shouldn't have
agreed to do this oh wait it
was our idea paying you eight million
dollars a million dollars million dollars
you get eight million dollars yep special
thanks to jess mckenna yeah um we
really appreciate hearing that that was delightful
i always love when she's things honestly
i've i've made her do that before
that same song yeah because i like
it should we have replaced oh yeah
sure why not alright and out of
place out what the fuck does that
mean to play us out for you
right now remember bill o'reilly oh god
yeah i know what play us out
meant what a weirdo and he had
a huge meltdown fuck it we'll do
it lie all right here we go
so thanks for listening everybody will be
back next week we love you and
thank you to see an age pure
cane sugar c and h
c and h my mom used to
make her cakes it makes the greatest
cookies snacks and candy their dan dan
dandy island kids all love okay grosso
clean and sweet they eat it when
it's freshly cut and then that's quite
a tree meat touched by sun kissed
bahrain c h comes from the sugar
cane
it makes the greatest cookie snacks and
candy in the bright pink package by