getting an early three
you can't do that every time
ah you're so early night i'm so
much time
ah woke up from luxurious now three
am in the moon and throw them
in the evening three minutes supper oh
wait super tie yeah i six after
evening what is the difference between soy
dinner
supper i think used to be what
people called lunch no
they're so rude oh no they know
hey when i think it varies from
place to place actually they used to
call it lopper ah it's an evening
meal typically a light or informal one
ooh okay so i can invite people
over for a supper party yeah you
could sit on the floor as you
say chris prussia a supper a supper
a summer party
my best buddy
i wouldn't bet ever for some looks
i invited someone to a supper party
i thought you said slumber party and
they brought their superman and i'm like
oh my god i did that you're
so embarrassing right now but let's all
get in your sleeping bag well sure
show up in pajamas with a sleeping
bag yeah and everyone is dressed to
the well no they wouldn't be dressed
up because it's a supper it's it's
formal short sleeves slit the shirtsleeves short
pants yeah dry pants yeah short hair
don't care you have to cut your
hair short preventing to a supper party
that's right it's a part of the
rules
i'm having a lunch party i'm a
lunch but you know what after having
holly's birthday party which was like a
morning dies embarrassing who's hollywood going okay
she's my kid um after having we
had our birthday from ten to one
or yeah and it involved bagels and
fruit and whatnot and i was like
and donuts and i was like this
i would do this with friends like
morning get together coffee a bagel we
had some like eggs and bacon and
you wanna do a whole breakfast you
wanna do the thing where you cook
breakfast for everyone like during the piano
but i want to do motel burgers
that's right i remember one thing you
said i want to do motel breakfast
yeah hotel real bars gusting eggs yeah
ah fruit loops and sausage patty that
tastes like shoe for lips in a
plastic like jar or bowl rules and
a plastic oh i was staying i
was singing a pretty petals in a
like in a
hotel in arizona a few years back
in the fire they had a pancake
oh make your own panel you know
what shape you know a hotel like
that and it was really fun you
could also make your own waffles i
but i don't want to i know
i don't i don't even want somebody
else to make them for me right
you don't want 'em past pancake waffles
it's really no pancakes or waffles ever
again it makes me feel so bad
yeah so heavy it is heavy but
i love
a pancake of crepes but about half
a pancake now you're talking is that
allowed i don't think so i know
they're round i know what you feel
about picking for the table what if
i eat out to the middle of
the bed if you just left and
you just hate it yeah yeah i
proudly say that i'm not ashamed what
do you feel up you're not a
soprano
oh and if i ate waves
ah painting from the table when you're
out for but thank you for the
table yeah everyone gets whatever they want
in a tiny silver dollar plane big
ass oh and when you die again
anyone can grab a couple bites now
i'm on the record with i don't
like to go out for breakfast yeah
i want period aim i want hear
in the congressional record
yes yeah i'm in the library of
congress i wrote a book about it
very slim volume yeah it's only two
pages and that's a very small seemingly
slim um but yeah i like to
i like to eat right away and
i this a thing i hate is
like if you're traveling with people and
they say oh we have to go
to this breakfast place and then you
all schlep over there
there and wait in line for an
i don't want to wait in line
for breakfast know here what you'll you'll
wait in line for lunch oh wait
like oh wait i really won't wait
in line for any meal at this
point i figured out i figured out
by the way like what are we
doing now if you're waiting for reservation
that's different it's different because there's
on the line yeah you're in the
restaurant they're like would you like to
go over the bar and get shit
that's drunk that's fine so if you
go in and wait you can't go
over to the bar
if you go in await you can't
go over the bar what anyway i
figured out by the way the other
day why we were talking about why
we eat fast yeah i think it's
because i'm always eating right before i
have to do something like today that
is i was showing shoveling it into
my mouth going fuck they're going to
be here fucks are gonna be now
you guys were twelve minutes late yeah
yeah and
are taking tax it was willing to
literally six minutes i looked all but
i looked at my clock yeah oh
but you over those guys where ten
minutes early as outside exactly yes the
time is late but see you live
here and so you're always on time
no really i'm always about that's what
i'm in i'm always shoveling food my
going like oh no the guests are
going to be
yeah i gotta get because i got
something thrown at me i had to
walk the dogs today unscheduled and so
they usually they walk at what time
ah eleven or so even when their
bowels and bladder are full yes yes
and then this time it was a
delayed reaction ah no we cool up
and i switched
ooh she weighs the more bodies yes
oh are you cool oh that's why
this is going so well yeah wow
come on oh yeah duh i didn't
make a boob joke huh you miss
your boobs and you miss them
no he misses mine okay i'm confused
oh yeah he's he has yeah he
has mine so he must be happy
i guess
oh guys i
i have a new this is one
of scott's classic oh guys okay it's
time for know guys like lawrence topics
i have a new ah ah found
dog story wow okay silently previously on
three i've had previously on freedom but
it was one of those new i've
had three experiences finding lost
dogs none of them satisfying the first
one by the way this the i
feel like this is the first i
mean i've never heard of saving a
dog saving okay i'll let me remind
you of the three times and you'll
remember okay so all i've heard of
is your cowardice in the face of
loss
see a lost dog are you doing
here where could it be who is
your odor so the first time ah
i was driving with cool up we
saw a dog by the side of
the road got out of the car
picked it up there was a phone
number ah no one answered i left
a message um texted as well
or this so no one no one
ever answered i said ah ah we're
over here you know i gave the
cross streets i said we're here tending
to remember this now about ten minutes
later a guy's walking down the street
on the phone and in the middle
of a conversation and he kind of
like raises his arm and i'm like
is your way
even to this can't be the guy
waving does he's on the phone we
but i get ahead of the car
going like ah are you he grabs
the dog never gets off the phone
that's right does one eighty just walks
away that's that's completely insane yeah either
i'd say thank you either a fucking
asshole or a dog thief
my eye those are your options to
be charitable i feel ease he was
a fucking asshole i feel like the
dog must get out all the time
or something yeah but does it she's
you don't know that i know and
i was waiting and by the way
we were on our way to something
and then i like zoo were in
black tie
just let the dog go and it
could've been hit by a car it's
true but i do but yeah i
i think we all understand that frustration
of like that overtakes you where it's
like you're so upset with the object
of the frustration the dog yeah that
you forget common manners exactly yeah that's
how i felt sure to it other
or he was just a total fucking
lunatic but
um so then the next two times
were the same dog and that status
feels like and that was a little
girls the little girls i am in
the dog is not that far like
three houses away but and just kind
of like standing there frightened looking and
i i found the dog i i
took it up to the door and
there and
they were just like what oh ah
get in here you know just kind
of mad at the dog and like
and kind of gave me a cursory
like thanks just like yeah in the
midst of like them i'm going i
told you not to let the dogs
you know i was just like fuck
why does bother okay and then it
happened twice and i was like third
time shaman just must be the charm
yeah but they moved around the charm
they moved away so i'll never know
third time shame on char fourth time
charm on the shame
um so tone down the newbie well
please don't be
so this time i get a text
from cool opnsense can you come upstairs
and i go upstairs and and there
is a little tiny dog to she
just shaking like a leaf in our
bush up there right by where you
guys enter time-sharing than a breadbox sized
let's pray that can like a tiny
britain a restaurant regular size restaurant breadbox
in a restaurant you know one that
has
like i know i know it's serious
so little tiny dog is just shaking
shaking shaking up is trying to coax
it out but it won't do won't
come out because ah too afraid we
i sort of get on the other
side and we're blocking it but neither
of us can reach ah and just
too afraid to come out i swapped
with cool up and i
and she's like it's going to bite
you it's gonna bite you i go
no i think it's ok and i
grabbed the collar and ah it's okay
and i and we get a leash
i put it on the leash and
after after it's on the leash it's
like fine mrs all i ever wanted
thank god i'm controlled by man
what kind of dog i don't know
i'm not great but i'm not great
at breeds yeah probably but we'll just
say mud so i don't have to
specify it is my favorite breed i
love it i love my mama so
i call ah they're struggling nuts you
have a bumper sticker type type of
strategy notes was
so i call the number and ah
someone answered the phone hello
and micaiah you have a dog named
piper and two yes and i'm like
oh we have or how many pieces
is the dog usually
i've just getting
i'm like we have er everything's okay
she's just burst into tears oh she's
in hawaii where the fires are was
on vacation and has been like scrambling
trying to get a flight back like
these both of these things happened at
the same time like this dog ran
away from the
fires from hawaii has that kind of
since huddled on foam
oh i thought it was here but
you know the fires there and you
know what if a dog cast away
had like a tennis ball that was
it's wilson
that's proportionately smaller yeah and it just
kind of constantly chased it and finally
chased it off the island and what
if it gave it gave up on
the ball what if a dog gave
birth to a ball oh my god
this is a movie it was a
golf ball and it talked and it
said tiger was my dad so tigerwoods
had sex with the dog
yeah the dog gave birth to alcohol
that makes sense his seem at this
point is golf balls
it's as big as cool yeah let's
golf tees and it makes sense like
if they gave birth to a big
sperm
hi team he is eighty i take
woods t nighttime
anyway so she yes yeah the the
dog was with her friend got away
at the same time the fire started
happening and um and the friend came
within like three minutes and the dog
had been missing for twenty four hours
or so like all night the last
spotting of it was some construction people
thought being chased by coyotes
that was hours before harrowing adventure yeah
yeah herring rib z like adventure but
who are these cars how do we
know this how did they structure people
saw this hat but going up and
down the streets going have you seen
this dog have you seen this dog
and some construction workers were like oh
yeah we saw it to just up
down the street food that woman was
definitely very scared that her dog was
eaten
yes yeah you know like pulses oh
my god like a big bang case
center out of this epic pancake yeah
um and then we a friend of
ours hadn't had we found had instagram
posted about the dog so it was
someone that we know i kept seeing
posts about this probably not the same
but different dogs but anyway so
so it was it was and they
were very grateful and it was it
was it was one of the you
know it's what you want out of
this experience of like you know you
take someone cares take the time out
yes someone cares about this dog yeah
yeah can i tell you this is
reminded me i have had three experiences
of a dog leading me to it's
house because he got out of the
house
and couldn't get back yeah wow and
you said here boy lead me to
your house it was just me where
your mommy lives show me where your
mommy
shake what your mama yeah so the
dog in each instance the dog came
up to me and then started to
like oh i'll try to lead me
somewhere
and like like it was kinda going
hey over here like how like how
a dog will be like want you
to get a ball that's under the
couch like yeah yeah you would like
like kind of come up to me
and like put its legs up on
my legs and then start walking and
then turn back and look at me
like to the child right and we
did the chalk step
into the tub like ally commercial where's
the dog dead yeah i think that's
a lot of them and not the
one i'm thinking there's only one telling
one the one i think it was
only when the one i'm thinking of
a bun tray of a multiverse of
commercialized things i'm just thinking of the
the idea of a commercial i'm thinking
of a golden retriever
okay that is on a tiny legs
doing like ah i'm thinking about the
black and white dog that's like unattached
legs doing kind of like to the
left now y'all one hop this time
two hops this time moran gay dancing
golden retriever and thank you i know
it's just a video it's not oh
it's just oh it's just if that's
just a dog that can do that
it's not just a sentient dog who
learned how to dance human style and
whereas outfits and not interesting just selling
anything he's just doing it for the
delay if it's not for fabrice i
don't want to hear it um and
there was one so the first time
it happened was like a little dog
who led me back to it's house
and then i knocked on the door
and
hey i got my horse once i
take the house down that's what you
said yeah i just i just play
my story a type i just played
you been taping paul this entire tie
have all doorbell footage accessible to me
all joel selber accessible to
me
and the owner was like oh my
god what did you how did you
get out to thank you so much
imo the second time bigger dog who
was very enthusiastic led me back and
then he was just a maniac here's
my question why don't they just go
back because they can't be kinder low
cuter they want yes they want to
get
they want a cushion
confrontation yeah yeah yeah yeah like you're
not gonna feel like a yell at
me for a stranger um and then
the third time with a dog that
lived right next to us who was
coming up to me and then walking
away and looking at me i'm like
what does your body when you see
the gate was open like the tiniest
little bow
needed the dogs like i can't get
through there ah i feel like i've
told this story but there was one
time where mike and i saw the
most like cartoonish looking dog where like
it had two eyes going in separate
directions like a tongue hanging out and
he's wearing a hat and a tie
it looked insane and it was just
sitting there and like i just was
like what's going on with this dog
it look
rcs bananas are we have this sunday
we were like are we supposed to
do something about this i don't like
how you approach all problems we like
oh hey or anything you seen from
the well
this planet we are we supposed to
do and came back and it was
gone we were like we just make
that up like it felt so insanely
i've never seen a dog that looked
like that in my life and you've
never seen i never saw it again
it was just gone and i was
like that sounds like a hallucination it
was tripping i was measured i was
tripping balls i forgot but thanks to
mike satu so
so you just type to to his
also trivial yeah and maybe he just
talk that is describing it it's funny
that when you see a cat wandering
around you're like who cares but if
you see a dog wandering around like
you must emerge day i do feel
like i think the cat knows what
it's doing like i'm like either you're
somebody's cat or but but my cat
has gotten my ida rest in peace
had got loose a hand
vl right i had a friend whose
cat came back after three months that's
it's too long yeah that is too
long it's kind of like that is
always wild to me like had a
dog that ran away for like it
was then like taking them into another
family and then like came back and
it was like a year later how
did you find this way back um
i got loose from them and then
like came back to their i don't
live with
you and then how did the how
how did the did the family i
think a story not adding it's not
cause i'm telling it badly oh daddy
but why are you lying your dog
ran away was taken it was gone
for many many months years i don't
know and that was taken out on
their family and they found out later
that it was and how did they
find out about the family let me
just get mike on the horn and
cleared up like wow okay so what
hi my hi hey it's me hey
boy hey my boy good to hear
okay asked you not to do a
poly w's that's better alright hey what's
out a laura baby i love ya
hey let's talk later
so mike this dog definitely talk later
okay yeah so lauren was trying to
tell the story she's failing miserably about
this dog okay you had that ran
away got taken by another frankly then
you got the dog back yeah let's
just all happen okay so i left
the gate open okay so what's on
you yeah i'm the gate guy in
the family
and failed at your job yeah so
one thing i had to do all
day and i was asleep at the
swell day okay i was like oh
and as a kid yeah it was
a kid yeah i was three years
old yeah trying to gate and bout
this ah doc gets away and our
lives with another family for months and
months a month
right and we had put up flyers
everywhere like if you seen this last
science yeah well i mean what's the
difference between a sign and a fly
really we i mean carstar carstar really
yeah yeah the weak quality we wanted
it to be assigned but we only
had fly material paper paper exactly enough
cards classic firewood
yeah yeah so wow calories really long
four colors four colors so we could
mix them together to make purple and
gray but so within the rules of
those four colors you could mix them
together to create other cuts oh yea
but nothing nothing special like pinks or
anything like that no don't take purples
not special pink is special
good d dad white toe barbie barbie
so and i can ha
as just who you talk to somebody
can yeah come over there bus
i'll take up on him
yeah i got got got what he
a billy joel heart attack i know
yeah
he does that kind of thing
a samantha alright we have to cigarette
okay
and hello speakers samantha oh yeah yeah
lauren i was listening to the old
ah with special guest lauren lopez yeah
where you you in the wild horses
oh yeah that's a fun sex in
the city it's so funny that was
fun thanks really funny how are you
accessing that i just still had it
on my phone
i know i kept a few i
kept a few eps night yeah ah
yeah i'm going to get at some
point get some backup of my patreon
yeah you gotta do it i now
i'm waiting to get the files actually
i'm waiting for some files myself
a win for me
do you have any compliments for me
paul yes scott i ah he's lying
around the room i love being in
this room it's what is that huge
stack of art books that are all
sealed ah um there seal seals you'll
biographies yeah
what does that mean behind the scars
seal wrote a biography of seals
um no really what is it they're
books but why are they all knew
because they're new why did you get
them because i bought them so you
bought a bunch of art books i'm
curious why they are the art books
or they sound like novel collects yoni
there's one called none of your fucking
business
nice to see around should your hobbies
and today's
alright i'll stop i'll stop right now
oh everything's fine everything's fine everything's what
you guys do this weekend oh god
what did i do i was in
portland oregon i did a variety opie
up there it was great had a
wonderful time the hotel ran out of
hot water what
oh no wow guy went door to
door door to door saying hey our
boiler just broke oh that's so ah
yes and you just what i took
a cold shower just this guy talked
there was i felt like there was
enough tiny residual warm water right you
really oh this hobby okay fuck as
well outside yeah right so
so um i made it through and
it was relatively painless but yeah suck
getting in there it was also one
of those showers where the showerhead is
fixed like you can't adjust it yeah
so there's no way to not get
in freezing cold oh yeah right there's
no way to like turn it to
the side a little bit yeah have
it just yeah but i heard an
interesting thing in the airport
what sound out of my way you
fucking book i was so fascinated by
it
oh interesting
there was a a father and two
kids walking through the airport they were
behind me and i heard the little
girls say
what happened to henry and the father
said what happened to henry well he
grew five inches he got a tablesaw
and he opened his own business ix
yeah so yeah
route five inches group okay let's break
this town so this was a child
who's somehow acquired a tablesaw open business
yeah like oh like encyclopedia brown like
table sawing for grade school kid maybe
it was a guy who got that
surgery you get where you get taller
maybe but i wouldn't say to be
if i were a father i would
not explain it to my child as
he grew five in yeah yeah yeah
yeah i don't want to give them
unrealistic expectation yeah that when you're like
forty you grow five inch yeah so
maybe he didn't grow in height he
something else grew in five it like
where
his hair is five inches longer so
say say you take the back what
you go backwards and the guy who
sees you spec you who used to
work with the father in their tablesaw
business or whatever okay so it's a
guy he used to work with why
would he grow five inches and why
is that necessary to the store wait
wait wait wait how did taking that
back going
going in both edit with the lascaux
the last piece of information first in
other words yeah like he he opened
his own business oh this is a
guy that that the father used to
work with right okay so then the
preview you're saying why did he open
with he grew five and yeah like
what how were those connected it is
the most interesting thing i would just
leave it at that right oh he
grew five inches
one with the end was saying like
i would say he grew five inches
but i think there was something that
needed to be explained about the rest
of that one hundred percent but the
the daughter seemed to have no further
quest she was fine with it yeah
he grew five inches got a tablesaw
and opened a business if you know
the update from when he leaves letter
saw him when he was
twenty eight we haven't seen him in
twenty years but what happened how well
he grew five inches you got a
table to open a business that's all
you need to know i mean this
time this child was small so how
how old could henry have been yeah
that the child would remember who henry
was right would inquire whatever happened to
him what happened yeah this feels like
what's the business that you opened with
just a tablespoon
i don't know tablesaw here what if
it is a children's book what if
it is a boring children's book the
guy who bought one table no it's
about like a little ten year old
guy and it's like oh yeah who
bought one table so any has no
prospects and then the story ends and
then the daughter goes whatever happened to
henry well he ended up growing five
inches
is hillary he got a tablesaw on
five inches you've got a table though
if he opened his own business whatever
happened and no no like henry who
oh no this dad knew exactly what
new henry we knew what i'd used
to be and what ideas now have
you is her invisible friend she stopped
checking in on that would be great
i like she stopped checking the day
i still think yeah oh yeah we
still like suppose you guys doing it
doesn't mean okay i have to keep
this up now
so that's what i was most interesting
part of the weekend for you i
didn't say that the show the show
was a lot of fun really good
time doing but it pales in comparison
to the henry story well something that's
haunted me ever since yeah yeah like
henry himself oh no actually
right now he's continues to grow and
as a buzzer rabbi i think my
most interesting thing is that i went
to a two year old's birthday party
and it was very nice and the
cake looked like a recycling bin full
of trash because the kid loves trash
kid loves trash
i love shit like dying reminds me
of my ah ah nephew i used
to analyze me my trash can
crash and it's trash day my nephew
used to hang out with guy no
knock it does kind of different for
one different different nephew used to hang
out with me don't often talk about
a different nephew second to your nephew
second-tier yeah definitely below like fourth on
the call sheet definitely below definitely below
definitely below um definitely chi was hanging
out with my
dad for awhile like they would you
know he would watch him and um
these grandpa they they went to the
dump one day and they still talk
about it he came back saying like
i want to work at the dump
and they never forgave my father oh
that's so cute it's got to work
at the dome and little kids really
love
trash like not all of them but
a lot of lot of little kids
really get excited about the garbage dragon
do you think that's why oscar so
grouchy because lobbies are always trying to
insert into kids and it's like i
wish kids were not so interested in
my life that should be part of
his thing yeah because i don't look
it would ask the crowd to help
you count or was he just a
guy who was like irritate
and he would teach you about growing
account is the cow sure but you
know how almost everything in sesame street
has to have some sort of lesson
attached to it his was like don't
talk to assholes or something yeah if
someone lives in a trash can leave
him alone
so i guess it was just like
it was learning how to deal with
things that make you grouchy or shades
yeah or deal with i honestly don't
know i don't need me was just
like hey wouldn't be funny we just
threw an asshole yeah you gotta have
someone who's all sunshine and rainbows i
thought they were all assholes a bit
no are you kidding me yeah big
bird sniffle up again
grey burns nicest people chicago suburbs a
little more angry i think he's quicker
to he's quicker to do you know
why though because burning it ernie burning
up randy let's see he's pretty pro-style
leave me alone about bernie's couple name
is bernie yeah yeah that's their that's
there a couple of portmanteaux yeah ernie
is a fucking asshole yeah ernie duck
yeah
yes he does stuff just really selfish
he's chaotic he's like he's just a
creature of whim yeah and it's frustrating
to what like one time he's practicing
the fucking trumpet at night when birds
trying to sleep yeah or are you
sure it's at night though because i
remember this it could have been during
the day and bert was like taking
a nap if still you know what
i mean
that's rude but but how are you
to know your if your roommate is
taking a nap if the roommate doesn't
say like by the way i'm in
my room how do we know that
he didn't do that they share a
room they have beds right next to
each other that's true it's right yeah
that's true that's right so anytime he
wants to play the trumpet he's got
a peek inside their bedroom and say
i kind of think anybody who has
a trump
lives other people yeah check and see
what they going staffers before he started
tooting on that fang you're not gonna
you're not gonna absolve ernie in this
in this situation yeah he's he's wrong
it's okay also he didn't even stick
with the trumpet some guy you've never
seen play it again yeah it's not
like it's not like then cut to
three years later yes he's real virgin
so yeah so
when i know how to neighbor in
an apartment building who would still seem
okay oh there's more who would sing
all the time um and she's a
she was a fantastic singer yeah we
had like an opera singer yeah i
mean she was like yes broadway person
or thing but yeah so but which
i mean is ultimately pleasant i would
say as far as loud singing goes
but just at all hours of the
day at night just like
yeah loud singing your neighbor also do
that no she i mean she it
was fine for like i i would
never really get too upset about any
kind of noise because you know one
of the you know remakes that you
make yeah when you're looking for arguments
yeah one of the four yes there's
one day you'll be empowered with your
word be impeccable with your word
annoys other people make noise ah be
on time and never ever fall in
love oh yes i agree with your
idea three of those okay you you
meet impeccable with your word you be
be impeccable you were always on time
aha you
you made a lot of noise
what was it well other people make
noise that's one of the rules you
other people may noise you other people
may know why and then you didn't
fall in love i never fell in
love in my life i was that
riley riley riley highly song oh which
one i never
and i never found hey why do
you imitate her like whoa i could
do the bang and frozen yeah again
in the danny but i never found
enough to deeply like that yeah i
think i nailed it yeah there's someone
in my neighborhood a rilo kiley license
plate like vanity plate wow
rilo kiley that's a deep the whole
band i mean yeah yeah sure come
anyone cause one guy and it was
just salute your shorts which was a
classic show on nickelodeon roads can wait
okay so like what's your name james
cheshire my old bandleader yes she was
a child she wasn't just beverly hills
writing child actor were they all child
don't think so i think he was
maybe even added to the band later
i'm not sure i think all four
of them were in it alright then
but i don't think it was i
think i think about that i'm not
quite sure they were talking about that
all that it's a bow that it's
about that was the sequel to all
that yeah hey about about thirty staff
was doing just that but um about
that why was there a show called
bag of chips no sugar but there
we should create a really missed opportunity
what if we create a cloud of
sentient bag of chips yes
and it goes and visits the all
that set up
a bag ship is about a living
bag of chips the show is called
a bag of chips what are you
looking at lauren my water bottle cap
has something in it a message yeah
it's my guy eat a pancake out
you dumb ho
i know it just had a little
bit of um you know something in
there too excited about to see i
would say oh like a spider a
little bit of dirt or something i'm
thinking what i'm thinking about something you
said earlier that you celebrate holly's birthday
from ten to one or something her
birthday party her birthday party yeah but
it is funny to think that for
a kid their birthday is only that
amount
of time pretty much they're not aware
all day that it's their birth yeah
yeah yeah for a long time yeah
we're going to a birthday party next
month that starts at nine thirty and
i was like another thing i know
i'm like i'm like this is great
i'm like yeah thirty eight yeah yeah
i'm like what we're what else are
we doing what time do you typically
wake up um at least seven if
not earlier scott
same question i'd has to be seven
at the latest yeah seven at the
latest yeah because of what was that
um but ah cause of like nap
schedules yeah yeah sure i mean this
morning us it was it was my
turn she started babbling at three which
woke me up
so it's a bit early but a
bit early she went back to sleep
but i couldn't get back to sleep
i finally got back to sleep at
five and she woke up at six
thirty more babbling i presume know like
this was true like i want out
for a half hour um yeah i
think i think the celebrating a birthday
all day that's fine but late
only people talking about their birthday week
oh their birthday months children come on
children come on yeah this is my
birthday month yeah they use it as
an excuse for like terrible behavior as
well yeah well because it can do
whatever the fuck they will this is
straight out of vanderpump rules really oh
okay it always tell us people in
the early is
near the site few seasons
question here
in the first few seasons especially there's
a lot of episodes that center around
people's birthdays and how important they are
and these people are in their late
twenties well they don't i mean this
reminds me of like it's a it's
the kind of thing and cool i've
had a few of these when we
were dating of like up until you're
about twenty three or so
nothing like you're when you have your
birthday it's time to invite every single
person you know to start i think
past twenty three i think that goes
up until a few years before thirty
really that people still do that yeah
and now it's like when people do
that after thirty for just like a
random birthday not like a milestone yeah
what are you doing come on man
i don't want to go to the
eden dead real like i didn't do
restaurants always there and knew i would
always like that place was really pissed
yeah i would do like um bars
like just a bar that's fine that's
when i would i for my thirtieth
i had a big dinner with like
that's okay too for thirty min yeah
but like but but what i'm talking
about are these ones where it's like
invite every ever
or when you know to a sit
down dinner not everyone knows each other
yeah oh yeah and admit it now
and then everyone has to figure out
how to split the check because everyone
is broken because yeah thirty yeah yes
yes yeah ah my thirtieth birthday i
remember spent at the drawing room one
of the most hideous bars and all
of los angeles yeah the tribe trying
to picture it it
has a sign that says open at
seven am oh yes it's on hill
hurst right terrible place open at seven
am yeah it's revoke no no there's
ah there there's a great bar in
san luis obispo that's open at six
am and everyone who had graduated from
cal state would like essentially
only that it would close it to
an open at six and everyone would
try to keep drinking pass two on
their own in order to have like
the first beer at six am on
the night they graduate that's gross why
um yeah i guess it's a curious
thing to say or i'm asked like
that i don't know how
to answer so i guess there's nothing
gross about it somebody wants pointed out
that there are people that work night
shifts that for them if they like
hello wind down yeah yeah absolutely it's
interesting you use your group all day
anyway yeah you've finished your workday at
you know seven am then you go
to bar i mean you're you're just
completely
he flip-flopped yeah so wait oh so
in new york is at four a
m the bars close i can't recall
oh my god some of them i
think stay open till fy can they
stay up until five but then yeah
okay when when what like why is
there even just one hour that something's
closed good question ma'am you know what
i mean everything should be really fast
yes every business every business
anything even a tabletop business everything re
resa yeah henry message do you really
do do do do
morse code yeah yep thanks he knows
he knows that he knows what i'm
saying cool cool i was just listening
to a podcast about braille and the
ninety nine percent nine percent invisible i'm
very popular i've i'm not a listener
but i know i'm a fan because
we listen a couple opposite stay great
um
that was really interesting i'm i'm gonna
try to explain braille but i would
recommend the episode i think i get
it no you know no it's ah
it's bumps bumps there's a history that
those bumps my guys oh don't want
to hear it oh i'm just glad
the bumps are there
i don't want to know how the
buzzer made it started is acting right
yeah reality we kept yeah though really
what are you doing on your face
that you're discussing reality recap i was
on bitch sesh lot cheek and i
did another podcast we agreed we were
going to appear in any other podcasts
you know why drive our numbers
alright but i ah i casually brought
up welcome to platteville a reality show
on t lc and neither of them
had seen it casey wilson and daniel
schneider and that set them off on
a thing where they basically realised how
amazing the show is this so now
they're doing a podcast all about it
which i mean people should
check out if you'd like to consider
the sister wife type of show it's
a family in macon georgia or not
it's no it's less come it's cairo
cairo but it smelled like cairo wow
georgia k row its really small town
and it's um and the family is
very sheltered and religious but then the
kids you're basically catching this for
only were like the kids are getting
beat teens and some of them are
venturing into the world and some are
you see how naive they are and
then you see some of them trying
to be a little bad and then
one of them still really religious like
praise in a closet for all of
them and those the hand movement you
were doing you were like whipping just
sort of souls you're doing okay and
then um over
time you see that the parents then
get divorced which is like the tapping
more recently and it's so insane and
now the dad went from being this
like sort of like um baba duke
figure no
you're right
the tall guy he's who's the tall
guy chained in the basement where's the
topics from a follow shani like
who's the tough guy alert wish master
scary thing for his big guy fantastic
guy staring for the spaghetti what's the
creepy pawnshop are d v pass oh
kevin the murder now what does like
the one that i referenced so many
times i can think about for some
reason this is really really tall the
slenderman yeah who's the tall slender guy
from like slender
man vibes to end he's like really
creepy series like smiling too now he's
like buff as hell kind of player
so i have to catch up because
they're all more caught up than i
am now september when that happened to
jon and kate plus a guy and
he started wearing ed hardy everywhere yeah
yeah oh yeah anyway so it's a
fun show if anyone's looking for something
crazy to binge yeah
alright if you're looking for some of
the crazy to binge that is laurens
what's my wreck made it made welcome
to platteville yes your last name is
plath and so that's why it's called
swat oh okay i'm sitting here going
like what the fuck is plath felt
what is lisbon and how do i
get there yeah how do i get
buff like this guy yeah i'm curious
what he's up
me to get buff where is he
now i heard he grew i ventured
i already got a table saw on
the whole business alright we have to
get good
and we're back guess what um that's
what shit yeah oh also i didn't
think you would guess it i'm sorry
also chicken about that
didn't see that coming yeah sorry what
was the origin of that guest what
chicken but i think this is funny
because it rhymes it's fucking stupid it's
insane
i mean i hate children yeah they
can't do comedy that you don't think
what's up chicken butt is funny it's
not what's up chicken but that is
funny okay it's just what chicken and
ohio does that's not what's up chicken
while it's up if you if somebody
says what's up and you say what's
up chicken but that's funny
that's so funny guess what what's up
no that's why that's funny that's funny
way what's up guess what what chicken
butt no yeah disagree funny notice agree
honestly one of the funniest things i've
ever freaking her alright we got some
more three v it's time for three-tier
if you want to submit a three-tier
write to us at three m usa
at gmail dot com yeah just do
it just came like throw caution to
the wind yeah live out loud tell
your family you're you're off the grid
for three hours do this does everybody
have the three via cr
questions hold oh no where are the
way we have to do something if
you look at the link where it
says you scroll down says new three
via then there is a link to
the specific questions there's a link that
says easy rabia on on the ah
link with all the goddess got all
the features
three via docs here that's your time
yes and then it will say lawrence
questions so we can't look at those
scott and i can't look at those
questions paul's question okay i can i
you guys can't look scott's questions laura
and i can't look is it at
link in the email or it's a
link in the document that you it's
a link in the document it is
a dab is down
at the bottom or it's where it's
included in the paragraph about three d
page one two three hey you know
what i'm gonna go to page controller
f yeah oh he's doing it very
good three via there it is sound
like a drug i mean you can't
ok first of all all this is
a twenty eight page document you can't
just go like oh it's in the
document
i need a little more other fucker
do you think i went down to
page twenty seven in this document how
would i know what you do with
your own time because this is not
my own time this is threesome time
this is freedom time sucks well that's
oh
three hundred times different than other time
i need you guys to get along
do you know right you'd like to
sit back there and watch raila yeah
you're the one stirring all the shit
out or like the joker okay right
do we need paper
i don't think inc so i think
the ink so
how do we do it before i
think people would just write down in
their notes app their culture i have
a i have a whiteboard here okay
great good okay okay alright shall i
kick it off yes ah opening my
pdf of questions o three v docs
here here
alright found it yes are you ready
i had zero info these are these
are trivia questions about me from things
that have been said on the show
okay okay question number one paul's mother
was the receptionist for her brother's business
what's music related service did the business
provide write down yeah
supposed to know any of this stuff
yeah because i know it do yeah
what music related service okay yes all
right question to paul taught us all
that the glade plugins shingle plugged in
plugged in is actually based on a
real song called rub it in by
billy crash craddock true or false nope
oh there's more chronic recorded a follow
up to rub it in called what
okay
okay alright question number three paul once
told a lie about his father doing
an impression of a famous actor and
being dead in order to get a
special inscription in the actor's book and
a book signing name that actor i
do know this
but i feel like i knew this
before threesome that's entirely possible because anything
goes and i know each other outside
of the podcast anything i've heard on
three of my will not remember yes
because you're busy interrupting it
i'm busy interrupting it oh my are
you guys seriously can you say i
know i'm the only one who interrupts
what thank you thank you for inferring
that i don't
quest for yourself this is a good
point yeah ah this is a two
point question poland told a story about
watching a double feature with his friend
scott argued that watching one and a
half unrelated movies a dvd in your
home does not qualify as a double
feature i don't know where one and
a half
comes in i watched both of these
movies
ah either way can you name the
two movies paul and his friend watched
you get one point for each correct
answer i'm i'm correct about that though
it's not you can't call it a
double feature if you just toss on
two movies at home right why can't
you i mean you can but i
think double
i'll feature is a special term reserved
for going out going out to two
plays and watching and paying for paying
for one ticket price that that for
something that is billed as a double
feature exactly alright ah and i've no
idea what these movies are question number
five this is the locket in question
first i will read the question if
you think you know the answer you
can lock it in by writing it
down and putting your pen or pencil
or fingers down you may not change
your answer once you have locked it
in if either player is not locking
an answer i will read a hint
if you answer the question correctly before
the hint you will get two points
if you answer correctly after hearing the
hint
if you get one point answering correctly
you get nothing okay
this has come up before
i once said that i didn't think
my name suited me and that it
had to i mean why do we
have time to like you before and
i didn't remember last it'll keep it'll
keep happening to your i need the
hint please give the first name the
middle initial and the last name oh
i actually like the hint i locked
it in you locked it in yeah
okay would you like a hint weight
so i can still guess if you
have not locked it in i've not
locked in then you can get a
hint i can only get one hint
or can i get all the hints
now that she's already locked it in
you only get one one hint okay
give me that hint
it's the first name of a famous
minnis the middle in the show of
a famous fox and the last name
of a character in the board game
clue i might be fucked
i can't wait to hear what do
you ah k a famous fox so
like vivek a it's not that
um alright and then ah characters and
clue you got plum you got mustard
scarlet throw colors
grape has had a clue color
mr grape
um i'm just going to go okay
got it i'm locked in alright
here we go question number one what
was the music related service that my
uncle provided piano tuning piano tuning that's
correct yes i didn't forget
and i get one i get one
number two what was the billy crash
craddock follow up to rub it in
pull it out eat it out you're
both incorrect it was you rubbed it
in all wrong
who to whom did i lie and
say my father did an impression of
this famous actor in order to get
a signature adam west peter o'toole peter
o'toole is correct okay i almost think
you i didn't work with him on
a
a a pilot one time ah an
animated pilot for something called super adventure
team i remember that yeah like i
did dana gould right and rob cohen
created it that was to not do
the series but he did do the
pilot and i got to ah hang
out with him for a day and
it was absolutely delightful oh he's not
dead that happens two point question
the double feature what were the movies
in the so-called double feature that i
watched a hard day's night and help
no
can you imagine i thought about dope
i've never seen them but i guess
it would be fun i just can't
imagine paul dewey both that's why
because you'd be like look at these
fucking guys
ah okay gremlins and jaws no okay
these were movies that i had not
seen before and they were coyote ugly
and battlefields okay so much
so here then i thought okay this
is the locker in question why is
the name that i feel i should
have and scott what did you say
said dennis r plum i said thomas
j peacock the two of you somehow
managed to get it dennis
ah yes jews the j what fox
i have no idea michael j fox
oh so it was an actual fox
here like a car tonight so was
i that's why i guess oh wait
should i get one point for that
or no no oh yeah that's tough
right neither of us get it or
what are we yeah i think i
think let me see riccio
what are the locked-in rules again because
lauren locked it in first i did
if you answer the question correctly before
the hint you get two points for
the answer correctly after hearing that so
you answered partially correctly you get the
point enough right yeah okay alright alright
i hope you're keeping track of the
points because i was not i was
i have one i have two points
currently okay i'm gonna do the questions
x okay lauren is going to do
the questia
eons i have two points paul has
zero and i like it that way
lauren s one okay
ah question one when lauren was a
teenager okay when i was a teenager
i had three run-ins with the same
police officer are we sure this isn't
the same thing we had before i
don't know keep reading on on our
third encounter what keepsake to the officer
give me
i remember this i remember it
and i'm happy to have remembered it
i really feel like we we may
have done these before we might learn
but it's interesting we're so i'm still
wrong every time yeah i feel like
we haven't done yours to me these
i think these are things we've done
but whatever we're playing again anyway and
everyone can just look pancake
who does that who does i who
do i think is the hottest simpsons
character i don't remember it's
haha
hottest simpson when i thought actually went
what did i say so you don't
even really know but i mean i
do when i saw it on yeah
hi simpson character wow
trying to i try to think of
any of them are hot just don't
think too hard um okay ah okay
for my seventh birthday my parents which
is really my mom and my uncle
threw me a party with what unusual
and boring theme
unusual and boring theme unusual and boring
theme
okay
question for two point question i once
surprise my grandma on her birthday with
a box of chocolate covered strawberries but
she did not appreciate because they were
too big and there were six of
them according to the story there are
two gifts that my momma always loves
receiving name them you get one point
for shit answer and rest in peace
my grandma
huh
um
man okay okay and the locking questions
getting questioner i will read the question
if you think you know the answer
you can lock them by writing it
down and putting your pen or pencil
down you may not change your answer
once you've locked it in if either
player does not look at an answer
i will read a hint if you
answer the question correctly before the hint
you get two points if you answer
correctly after
during the hint you get one point
here's my question you said if neither
locks it in you'll read the hint
now she had locked it yeah i
think i think it's okay if one
person looks at it okay answering correctly
you get nothing here's the question i
was once offered opium by a guy
with what clothing related nickname oh okay
a
um
i'm locked in i need the hint
um the hint is it's probably where
he kept his opium
okay
alright ready all right ready question one
what did the police officer give me
the third time i had an encounter
with him a trading trading card correct
alright right what is who's the hottest
simpsons character out of the bus i
guess to auto as well it's it's
part it's part that was like
it can't be botched but i was
a child when i watched that ah
your nation yeah you put away childish
things for my seventh birthday my mom
and my uncle threw me a party
with what unusual and boring theme and
your uncle uncle my gay uncle ah
tax-filing dirt manners and again it was
an an already are you walking around
with like books
on your hands we were and everyone's
dressed in a nice dress that's so
funny to point question what does my
grandma what my grandma always love receiving
there are two ah two gifts we
get one point for each correct answer
i said money and tief i said
flowers and candy know a hundred dollars
cash or a walgreens gift card
but yes money counts i only get
one point so money and a walgreens
gift card are the two answered all
the yeah she doesn't want candy of
the chocolate covered strawberries were too big
for six of them yeah i thought
it was the the amount like if
you give candy like m and m
she'd be like oh wow there's a
hundred of these
it didn't work that way okay and
then the guy who offered the opm
what was his clothing related nickname scott
george
pocket pockets pockets you think my friends
call me pockets they don't have any
i believe was the thing you said
to me write hey i didn't this
come up recently you probably alright okay
so i have three total i so
far have one and then we're gonna
do you locked it in though paulk
so you get two for that that
last
answers oh yeah yeah yeah so how
many do you have paul too i
think i've know you have three yeah
three okay so we're tied at three
lauren has one yeah so paul you
need to get an answer correct otherwise
all hell will break loose we will
be tied or in
less lauren gets more than two okay
you guys ready yeah alright
question one
scott once made out with a woman
yeah right
true false
halloween party and got makeup from his
costume all over her face what or
whom was scott dressed as shit what
was scott dressed as
this can't be right but it's funny
okay okay question two in high school
scott pretended to be interested in joining
the army in order to get what
from an army recruiter
okay okay okay question three when he
was a kid scott had to get
stitches in his face after attempting what
dangerous stunt i mean this is obvious
okay okay two point question scott once
boasted that his address was so secret
almost nobody knew it
what
name the two very cool not at
all all evil organizations that did know
it i e they sent mail to
his address with his name on it
oh yeah you get one point for
each you named correctly could you read
that last part of okay name the
two very cool not at all evil
organizations that did know the ads
address i e they sent mail to
his address with his actual name on
it
instead of the alias
very cool not evil
is that sarcasm i think it's well
i don't want to say okay
okay alright paul are you is there
a fifth question of course of course
dear okay some of you are wrapping
it up okay let's wrap it up
guys alright the locket in question
scott's former roommate
this is incorrect so i won't read
this part of it but scott's former
roommate who was roommates with the eye
of party's guy had what food related
nickname
i'm lucky you're locked in
alright lorin do you want the hint
yeah
this round food
it's what i was thinking is often
associated with new york city i mean
that just gives it away yeah it's
actually i was gonna guess okay alright
here we go ready
question one scott once made out with
a woman at a halloween party got
makeup from his costume all over face
whom or what was scott dress s
anyways
said the joker incorrect ace freely from
kiss i wouldn't ah right yes okay
in high school scott pretended to be
interested in joining the army in order
to get what from an army recruiter
i said a sticker a gift card
a hand job why no free
lunches free lunch eight free lunches yes
you took me out oh to me
because you would go like let's go
to lunch to talk about your future
and i kept stringing him along wow
eight times until finally not sure on
the eighth time he was like come
on man what are we doing here
i was like yeah i'm not eating
i guess it's time yeah that's a
lot
the army was short one person yeah
so just really gonna close this deal
okay question three when he was a
kid scott had to get stitches in
his face after attempting what dangerous stunt
riding a bike with his eyes closed
while wearing sunglasses yes but sunglasses doesn't
matter your eyes were closed that's the
stun
true but but the reason i was
doing it is because no one would
be able to tell my eyes were
closed because i was wearing mirrors even
dumber but i'll give it to you
thank you very much that's very um
alright question for two point questions scott
once boasted his address was so secret
almost nobody knew it named the it's
not a boast it's merely a fact
but okay
named the two very cool not at
all evil organizations that did know it
i e they sent mail to his
address with his name on it you
get one point each i'm gonna say
the fbi and the catholic church i
said the bank and scientology you get
one point for scientology scientology and the
republican party ah ah law
lock in question scott's former roommate the
party's guy had what food related nickname
paul you locked it in yes i
did and what is your answer bagel
bagel is correct pizza
it's just round in new york
i thought it was obvious but you
are right yeah really good pretty good
nickname wow yeah pizza i know i
was gonna be the person i said
isn't like a nickname and then when
you said i guess i was right
pizza alright do you want me to
say what the final totals are yeah
mine is too for ah tied for
second place
scott and lauren both hat both have
three points and first place paul has
six points the champion wow you got
three a piece for each of us
champion thank you nathan duffy for some
of the most questions
ooh my boy you know speaking of
nathan duffy speaking of him you see
his great artwork when i promote my
shows because he does all my show
posters and the latest one that he's
done is for um via tapia at
the bell house in brooklyn um
and of course we'll be selling the
posters at the show but that is
october fourteenth and fifteenth ten pm the
so the early shows are sold out
the ten pm shows still have tickets
ah and also ah november november i'll
be in charleston south carolina with maria
topa and that shows still
there needs to be sold out so
why don't you go get tickets to
that then let me tell you when
the date is that is the seventeenth
the seventeenth friday the seventeenth of november
charleston south carolina first time doing via
topa their go to paul f tompkins
dot com slash live for ticket links
great and
you can follow me on instagram at
laura mapquest and that's where you'll find
all my show updates i don't know
what i'm doing right now hi tom
really careful on a second well i
gotta tell people what we were going
to do a superhero wild horses show
right before lockdown yeah we were going
to improvise a murder mystery we didn't
get to do it
the other day i was like the
fuck why don't we do that show
again we're going to do it finally
oh my god tobar ninth at dynasty
typewriter both it's going to be an
in-person and live stream of shows it's
going to be a lot of fun
i can't wait to do this ah
so go to dynasty typewriter dot com
m for tickets to either the ah
in-person show or the livestream incredible and
october thirty first um was just going
to be scary this is very scary
i need suggestions for a father daughter
halloween costume so send these to lauren
and she'll pass them onto the road
the road yeah girl row these the
road oh i think i'm just like
a blacktop road yeah why don't you
go into the street just be three
and lay down in traffic oh wow
all right bye
ugh