three
oh yea yea yea yea yeah oh
yeah yeah she's bigger cheeseburger cheeseburger
hi everyone we're back it's us again
i'm across from the lady with the
goat on her sweater long wow so
woman's inside i'm across from a man
with just a white shirt and donald
ducking it that's right quack quack and
high
i am right across from this motherfucker
wearing two shirts steve bannon styes scott
aquaman steve bannon where one button down
with a t-shirt no yours two button
downs on top of egypt's the you
gotta look for buyers and fatigues and
so crazy i don't understand that's like
ah it sounds like a rich preppy
look it's yes some sort of naval
affectation i don't really know what it
is a naval affectation ah hi oh
wow i mean from from the navy
not to the belly button i hate
golf vacation from his belly button as
his mummy he looks like he's just
floating away in them welcome to the
show everyone
one this is the show where we
just talk about stuff yeah yeah tight
you just stay on it you just
saw it it's tiny it's time to
hate i dated someone without a belly
button what why was it patricia why
did she not have one or he
ah
thank you um because of some sort
of way ah that she was born
it was interesting because the way that
she was poor close enough to have
an umbilical cords is a sex no
you have to have an umbilical cord
it was it was through some other
it was not in that part of
her body or something it was interesting
you need to have more info it
doesn't wait a while ago i don't
recall the deets so as the tell
me was it weird it was i
mean it was there was nothing that
way
what's weirder is the fact that we
all have something there isn't it like
we all are but we all do
know it's no but you know what
i need to say her nude if
you ever did was it shocking or
was it more like you're just like
okay it would i mean it definitely
was ah it was interesting it was
definitely one of those things i'm like
oh this is your your brain doesn't
register it the right way of like
oh they're just there should be something
there but it certainly is you know
i would just have a hole somewhere
else that you saw like yeah but
when you know sex is your belly
button but it was on r but
like whether i'm just saying is there
a place where like you would you
would put the bicycle pump into bumper
up everyday
yeah come on guys like an adult
you like a duh you like a
dog what if i was in a
relationship with a sex doll i there
are people there are people like lars
or the real girl
there you have you watched like those
shows where it's like my strange sex
addiction or whatever no i saw one
about someone who a drywall oh yeah
well yeah my strange addiction that one
they are the woman who's like eight
couch and she just eats like the
saying i'm cash cow and a gesture
like find out the cheat and like
many cushions up to that point
like she would just swallow because she
would just like we shouldn't grab the
stuffing was she dreaming of eating a
marshmallow yeah she recently grabbed the like
the ripple stuffing know cotton but like
when it's like kind of coffee machine
you're seeing the cotton the fabric gorilla
nah yeah that the the lady way
drywall that was she would just sit
on the couch and she would like
reach into a hole that she had
like dug into her wall and then
she would just like but it's a
thing now under ca and it's when
you have hiker oh i've only read
it i think it's pica okay yeah
um it's when you have like a
desire for
something like that dirt or something which
has a lot of iphone you're actually
trying to fulfill a need that your
body has like when it happens to
pregnant women yeah and babies i like
kids like dome but they'll eat dirt
but it's interesting my my nephew who's
a baby to eats dirt and sand
like at the oh my god so
much like you go to the beach
and he's just like eating the sand
as it is he needs something he's
not getting what is the cause that
made me think about that when that
cigarette butts and yeah he loves he
loves the grubby means nicotine i love
when a baby eats dirt they like
grab the hell out of a potted
plant or something and then they have
that look on their face like ah
juliet like this isn't what i say
he likes it like say my hey
we all know that one yeah this
is usually the show where paul and
i know references that lauren does not
know and vice versa yep it's true
so i'm glad that we all found
common ground on this i know can
you think of a reference that we
definitely don't know yeah okay um here's
with it
okay actually i was gonna mention the
last episode but i was like let's
gonna go nowhere no i'm talking about
blaming whoa um do you know the
show wiener bill that was on nickelodeon
in the early nineties and it was
when i thought you might know it
because it was i'm assuming a comedian
who did the show like a a
man
man and he would be the it
would be his head when you were
describing the puppet that your dad made
me think of this okay it was
it would be his head and then
like a little body like he'd be
like a puppet of himself as nick
well i don't know the name of
the guy his name was mark wiener
oh okay i know the comedian is
but i know i didn't know about
the show interesting
he had a kid show he used
to do this on standup stages he
used to have like a little tiny
body yeah well he wouldn't also find
me on the mister show's yeah he
would do this right i sorta remember
this yeah like a little table and
then you would put because i think
he did this as a street performer
to rye he would have like a
little sort of black box on the
stage where he would make his fist
sed into a puppet on a puppet
head on a body yeah and do
little stuff and an interesting thing about
him was he was an orthodox jew
and he could not do saturday night
shows so it was always like that's
where the money is when he would
come to town we would get more
work because he couldn't do you know
the saturday show got to do like
if you were
working if you were the mc you
got to then be the feature and
was here big like people oh yeah
yeah yeah yes so this was a
big deal he got to show but
you didn't know about it back then
wouldn't watch that exactly you were refused
if you were a comedian and you
had any any sort of appearance on
tv it would be a big deal
when you came oh absolutely yeah i
know what i mean
these comedy on the road yeah mm
interesting that's cool
okay well i'll try to think of
another one um like ah like ah
you know what i heard the other
day was i guess dilly dilly is
a thing i don't know what that
is i don't i just saw something
about that i don't know and i
said that the other day and and
ah my friend was like yeah dilly
dilly everyone knows what daily joe winger
posted a picture yeah i'll fucking she
said delos was
i only know it from a bud
light camera that's what it's from that's
but they're right on everyone who says
it be furious i don't really why
where's the beef is it ironic oh
wait everyone i mean i don't know
i didn't i don't understand what it
means on the commercial okay it means
the best kind of person or thing
you rescue me when i was blackout
drunk did
daily oh so okay it was think
so
but it won't now
so it was a thing before this
bud light come no they can't be
from eczema or hot on eat to
that extent now i want you to
give a reference that i might not
know but not super hero comics really
excited wouldn't know about anyway okay okay
ah um from ah something from like
a commercial maybe yeah
from ah our child hi guy do
you remember that
that's my god that is so ancient
and shiny the weaker it was commercial
do you know that ancient chinese secret
i don't think so the calgon commercial
calgon first hallowed take me away many
things but hell is kelvin still around
yeah yeah they i feel but calgary
so calgon was a mendoza detergent
it was a dish soap and i
guess it was some sort of bath
i knew it was like saudi spray
it was also well there's ah there
was a commercial this ran for a
million years yeah where um this woman
goes into pick up her dry cleaning
and she says to the asian man
behind the counter how do you get
this stuff star stuff is so amaze
using yeah how do you how did
you how do you do and he
says ancient chinese secret yeah and then
she sees and no no he doesn't
see oh we cut to the back
of the dry cleaner this is from
the simpson there's the wow there's the
wife who says to the camera my
husband some hotshot oh right here's his
ancient chinese secret calgon and then we
talk about calgon and then um the
woman the white woman is about to
leave the store and pay a wife
that the asian wife appears from the
back and says in earshot of this
round guy we need more cal gone
and then the
white woman turns around and says ancient
chinese secret whoa wow i love it
yeah yeah and that and we saw
it so many times that i cannot
hear certain things without thinking ancient chinese
yeah for sure yeah that's good but
hi guys don't what thai guy for
hi guy was i cover what the
product was i guy it was like
an alcohol
sir yoda or something but there was
a guy would open his medicine cabinet
and there was another guy on the
other side it was like they shared
a medicine cat that's vaguely one of
those apartments oh i feel a little
oh hi yeah yeah play yeah sure
um side note i just watched jeopardy
yesterday and
like i never heard of bob ross
oh what a fuckin idiot oh what
a dumb douche are you doing
it makes everyone share the same absences
modern apartment so it's how you do
it i don't know if our roadside
knew well there was a series oh
okay huh sure just like the mr
microphone that's all about that regular right
guys if one jonah record there it
is wow well that's dilly dilly i
guess is exactly the same thing where
they
he said it was yeah they've said
it so much and now everyone says
it football players say it's like so
plays into everybody mad me too don't
you wish because that commercial is stupid
but isn't there part of you that
wishes you could write commercial job
i feel i think that would be
miserable it would be i just feel
like i could do it so much
better i but i think we're at
this point now where no one thinks
oh well i could go at this
point where they just show you the
most random thing just to get your
attention it has nothing to do with
anything it's totally rent and i have
any ma i haven't watched a commercial
in years i feel like been
because of streaming yeah d v r's
and stuff so i win stuff like
this happens i don't even know about
i don't even know that commercial though
that ideally i don't think i've watched
like a live event here's what it
is it's a bunch of people and
it looks like ah how much punish
what are we talking ah to
no it's like it's like a medieval
it's like it's like two hundred and
fifty probably yeah sure it's like a
medieval court but everyone is twenty five
years old and so there's a king
and queen at this banquet this long
for girls and there they are they're
so our vodka brandy think melky
fuck off i want to break know
oh wow okay cody oh my nars
airline broken that ah
actually i don't want to damage a
nut why do i feel like i
told you this story but there was
a kid i grew up with who
had escaped injury and lost or tricycle
oh no he's technically the one that
wonderful anomalous wonder yeah that's what i
called hitler
it was oh yeah and so what
do why do we know that didn't
slide like down his leg i don't
know what happened with it but i
just earned a nice i got twisted
and i got next i load it
there's no i think about what she
said that indicated i'm imagining his ball
sack got sliced open and just one
came when walnut just almost like an
aig just
you know like sweating down and then
he got a new article a new
to call
for topics what do you get your
dog's balls cut off well you can
get some fake balls so i don't
know any different yes and they're called
newtok literally i don't understand that right
over it like within yeah why one
hour or something over weight but do
they really want them um i don't
know why that's honestly i honestly don't
know why like the balls are not
the thing
ing that i'm like the proudest of
like oh we got rid of fun
guys
hi i just my balls
i gotta get in there i gotta
get out and boring i don't know
what the most like if if i
happen to be neutered or whatever you
know are chemically castrated whatever god willing
but if they were just like hey
you don't have balls anymore i wouldn't
be like gotta get some fake ones
down there i gotta say i feel
like it would be weird and what
do you think surprise do you think
look they're more trouble than they're worth
but i'd miss them if they were
gone do you think much like the
woman i dated without the belly button
she should have drawn like a little
like spiral underbelly yes every day pretended
she should have done it every way
you don't want cindy crawford with a
multi watch ninety day fiance know that's
the best show on tv um but
with one guy who is who had
a vasectomy fifteen years
before he was with this woman he
was he kept saying well you know
i've been fixed you know i was
finn yeah it's making me say was
a bob barker yeah yeah it was
now what the fuck are we talking
about what you are looking to me
we're gonna tell medieval tv about this
commercial yeah so people are bringing their
their apparently there
they've journeyed from other land bring gifts
they're bringing gifts to the king and
queen and so i'm offering this and
i brought that somebody brings but after
each gift is presented the king and
queen say dilly dilly and then everyone
in the court says daily so annoying
i like it now oh really i
certainly see you actually probably
when i was watching a commercial i
was like wow
i don't say oh you guys don't
do it don't do it today i
like to go in dilly bar from
dairy queen never had one and let
paul finish the story daily news oh
they're silly it sounds recounting the commercial
telling right story
he didn't believe me
but if you are a dad and
you only told like good night stories
just three counts those were all medieval
fucking old team okay so this brown
guy
so how's so so re frogged on
a brand
so someone brings about my head away
and they'll say that's the a dilly
dilly well he doesn't bring enough for
the everybody or something like that and
so he's beheaded or some shit but
what's weird about the commercial is you
feel like in the commercial this is
a reference to something else right and
i die read an article about it
and they just buried up for this
just made up for that they they
do admit
get that there is like maybe a
song in the du like thirty years
ago called daily daily or something but
it was just made up for that
i bet the guy who made that
up is like so he's just a
pussy hard i bet he's got all
his balls he's like baby believe it
i bet he like me talking about
poppy goes up to someone at a
bargain you ever see daily daily i
wrote that and the always boys or
girls jillian probably wrote that are you
okay yeah no no that means
since lauren are you watching the bachelor
yas i ah are you oh i
think about that with like people in
there having these first conversations with people
yes when i'm having a conversation with
someone i think about lauren watching the
same ah i watched last night i
don't know what i'm saying about it
but i
like you feel awkward you feel bad
that they're ahead they had these awkward
moments on film yeah well i guess
so but they also don't ever seem
to have normal i wish someone would
have a normal person conversation i know
well it's so insane like everyone's like
then they wouldn't be on the show
they know they're immediately approached kind of
like i watched you on your season
five years ago i feel like we
have a lot in common
my dad died and i'm like oh
my god still chilly
and then they're making out and it's
like really nasty ah i don't know
the first episode would you ever would
you ever make out with someone on
tv i i can't imagine what scenario
that would have in a rehabilitation news
oh yeah dallas raines and tonight we
have more lucas
making out with me point flathead face
oh ah
um yeah i'd be into that
get a self-tanning can you imagine i
remember i remember oh itself tanner would
rub off on my face yeah um
i don't know i once made out
with someone on halloween maybe i talked
about this always wearing makeup and it
rubbed off on her face well yeah
yeah because i made with a clown
and i was just like a guy
guy guy yeah um but but remember
i remember i'm big brother one
of the first couples to ever have
sex on that show and then i
saw her in person and i was
like there's that woo and sec like
it was the scarlet letter or something
like that i mean there's that harlot
on the bachelor it's a little different
because you don't see anything besides like
making out usually but i'm like real
world they would youtube people in bed
like in the fuzzy black and white
yeah you'd see there but they wouldn't
show that so crazy oh baby to
now like david come on my baby
tonight i watched the first season of
the real world and then i didn't
watch it again until that season i
was exactly the same oh yeah it
was yeah it's a formula was like
so data first out it is so
different round but then it turned a
corner now
oh it's just like now it's me
me me me me town but like
seasons three four five silly seventy until
he dilly dilly deal but i do
think that i feel weird when i
realised how much older i am than
everyone on the shit that happened that
happened to me i remember i was
watching the real world i was really
into it and they said hey do
you want to
apply for the real world i had
no interest in it by the way
yeah but that be said but shares
are they said are you between the
ages of eighteen and twenty five and
i was twenty six and i was
like i'm too old yeah oh here
and everyone on the bachelor there's a
lot of people whether they're like twenty
two well that's the thing i was
watching i was watching nationals the other
day and am
and you know part of the day
just walking down the street just the
other day and this kind of thing
that happened to too
but i you know some sometimes when
you're watching that show it's like okay
how would i act in this situation
yeah um and obviously i'm married i'm
never going to be in that situation
but you sort of like okay if
i were in this situation but then
seeing everyone be twenty two twenty three
or whatever i'm like i what if
there was bachelor but for old people
are like
oops oh i actually have been saying
this for years the bachelor should be
every season to be a brand new
person who's never been on the show
before there's no preconceived notions about what
they're like or what they're into or
what they did with the last person
and then it should be all people
who are ah of age or they
might actually really want to get married
yeah yeah because all the
the twenty two year old yeah just
looking to be on tv it's so
crazy so unlike the first season that
the that couple is still together and
they have kids and stuff and like
that has happened since then but they've
been together for like facebook computer talking
to ryan and tristan yeah season two
season two sorry who's he's one
the season one was this guy and
he was like they were they made
him seem so cold but i remember
this given i remember this vividly they
were on a horse and carriage in
new york city and the person had
a whip for the for the horse
snow and he he said he made
ah ah they might be giants song
reference where he was like meh
hg imo be awesome and i was
like this guy's just a dork yeah
nobody for that guy yes or not
because he's a normal guy but they
were making him out to be this
like super hunky so yeah you know
what was on the bachelor that i
didn't like the other night was when
the guys like i'm actually a nerd
hey
a dream and then and then the
woman goes i'm a nerd too and
it's like neither of your finer nerds
you saw is different you suck dick
you suck my what actually i'm really
totally a nerd what do you mean
you bit you're just oh i hate
that yeah i pay i lived through
a book once yeah i'm actually really
like a nerd like actually really liked
comics it's not even that they don't
even like it i heard scuttle follower
trying they're trying to say like i
you i don't even like going out
to bars
is all right i sometimes just like
to sit around at home watching like
i'm a nerd i love staying home
and you're like oh you're just a
funny score a phobic like a nerd
about it
like i know had different responses i
know everything about my house yeah we
need to take a break by
welcome back welcome back welcome back
mag do you know the white shadow
lauren know it was tv is it
a car
it's a good name for a god
it's not bad really good for why
did they name cars after they they
seem to name them after animals or
nonsense
you know like like acura or whatever
well you know what in japan i
i noticed that i'm sorry when they
show my japan i actually very obsessive
japan but one thing i loved was
that the cars alot of the cars
had names like carol like the design
would be like carol it was like
i would take picture because there was
like there
crazy like the jane or like it
would just be someone's name volkswagen made
a car called the thing oh i
remember very bright like that in the
seventy s it was a cool looking
i was sort of it was a
sort of shortened station wagon kind of
um and it was like a mushy
neck station wagon it was like two
mushrooms you think okay do you think
you could drive
like you would yes okay horse i
passed by law everything ah you would
drive on stv i have driven in
sep yeah i've i've driven us as
rental cars but i don't think i
would want to do it and i
liked being sort of taller than of
i always have a car that's taller
and i really liked that but i've
been thinking about getting a bigger car
ooh bigger
even bigger than tall really tall would
know much of a macro or everywhere
i love to hate like cars that
are unnecessarily huge like a hummer if
you if you were to pull up
to a valet here in l a
in a mack truck would they park
it for you who like now with
a trailer but just the yeah just
tabs guys like like
over the top style i could see
it would they park it or would
they say we're not gonna work that
thing they would say we're not going
to have to say they wouldn't participate
don't think they don't oh lysa hey
licensed to kill let's kill my mother
shortly this is to kill my mother
it was common
my mother what have you could buy
a license to kill your mother oh
and do it how i bought a
license to kill my mother you know
guys my mom's dead yeah she's dead
i'm dad to you know no parents
do you consider yourself to be left
no parents no service
do you consider your took my shirt
off your pants or do you consider
yourself to be an orphan or is
that something where you can only be
an orphan until you're eighteen
oh yeah or orphan means yeah you
got it or orphan as an adult
i don't play joked and i don't
like when when adults say i'm an
orphan sincerely just a hoof some people
say that all the time well because
their parents are yes but are they
talking about it of like they were
an orphan since they think that wouldn't
like sending like
uhm like their other parent dies then
and then they're like so that should
be like something when you're when you're
eighteen you can buy cigarettes you can
read a playboy yeah and you but
you have to stop saying okay ladybird
just i just don't like that but
i mean also do whatever you want
and take it back you know if
anyone's out there and they're like that's
how i cope
oops and i've never felt that your
judgmental person till right now really
i'm so nice
hey guys hey
i to talk to you about this
okay i watched the movie call me
by your name i want to see
that comment i your name and in
the towel may huh
share
in the movie
the the there's you know it's about
a love affair yeah um and it's
very
there's a lot of things a lot
of picks have you w sex and
it's it's a really it's a really
lovely beautiful movie and well-acted the the
love affairs between a seventeen year old
boy and a twenty four year old
young man yeah and i didn't realize
that before i started watching that they
were there
there was an age difference and it
was really difficult because armie hammer plays
the twenty four year old and he's
older than twenty four and he's older
than twenty four but he's also thirty
s he's thirty one okay but he's
also he's gigantic he's like a big
person it's like cut out a marble
yeah he's like cut out of a
slam i'm older than him
that is disgusting want to feel armie
hammer's younger than you i'm gay
but i i remember i remember i
had that about playboy playmates once i
remember like in my twenties sure you
they were all they were like well
you know like when i was when
i was in junior high or high
school it was like who will play
right i made they're all like these
they're like as old as your mother
writing and then then very similar to
real-world in my twenties i was like
oh
a visceral eighteen okay lose it all
when you're young age is like everything's
the same like someone is twenty two
is the same someone who's thirty five
not to interrupt people but he but
here's the thing yeah while i was
watching this because i'm so far away
from both of those ages i was
like wow this just we like is
that i honestly was trying to remember
is this
okay right you know what he mean
what does this feel weird at that
time because i'm looking at it from
this from the the the point of
view of like oh that twenty four
year old is taking advantage of that
seventeen year old yeah i and so
i totally forgot when i was seventeen
i had a twenty four year old
girlfriend ooh
ooh i completely forgot there's a weird
lead up to a brac well yeah
no because right yeah looking at it
from this i'm looking at it from
the standpoint of like oh no he
shouldn't be doing this with the young
kid right and i completely forgot i've
never never i never looked at it
from the standpoint of the younger person
right now but i wish you
i understand you're switching when i was
forty two i had a seventeen year
old girlfriend and i felt like i
you know this actually happened on terrace
house um that i'm karen welcome doing
now they're all terrorists yes okay i
don't wanna watch them well it was
a conversation about someone dating a girl
who's eleven years younger than him and
the girl keeps questionnaire she's like seventeen
eighteen and everyone else is going like
it's fine
as long as you think it's fine
or whatever and i was thinking about
zelda creator that i like to live
by yeah fine as long as i
think it's fucking crater upper i was
thinking about myself at that time though
and it was like to know what
i know now versus what i know
knew then and like the i i
had a couple sort of pseudo relationships
relationships people who are older
than me but it's like i don't
i look at that now and i'm
like that's weird of them i that's
exactly don't you think compiler j wanna
hang out you now think yours is
weird
i guess i don't because i can't
i can't separate my experience which was
that even though i was like a
you know very immature i was i
was mature in certain ways where i
never thought of her as being immature
like down on my level of course
i thought of myself
lf is up where she rides you
know right and it was when we
were together for a year you know
like moved in together and everything she
thought jimmy were you in six were
in school i was in the process
of dropping out of school and i
know this much even after i dropped
out but is this process when you
do drop out i dropped out after
a semester of college yeah yeah
yeah i just wait you were in
college at seventeen is that yeah because
i was my birthday's september so i
graduated at seventeen and then um i
guess going into eighteen i was okay
so you're almost eighteen yeah okay and
um i i had gotten a job
on south street in philadelphia downtown and
i was walking down the street
just yesterday the day with a with
a friend of mine who is similarly
dropping out of college a broad street
can say a it on cold um
and i saw this lady
oh yes good till we saw someone
in your life
it was such a wonderful place of
having forgotten that that existed now does
i'll never forget and so this this
girl was walking towards us um and
then i was like struck by her
she's very noisy
ooh yeah yeah you're struck by ah
you thought because he goes hey you
with a pan she hit me with
the pants now you're ridiculous lauren you
guessed it so she walked into the
store and i said to my friend
let's go into that store and so
i i i've never
ever i don't think i've done this
i hadn't done it before repay point
it's good it's good work and it's
working i just started talking to her
and she was really funny and um
and so i think i don't remember
i saw i went to my job
and then i think i would post
a job at the time i was
working at hats in the belfry oh
right
very famous stand-up exactly go check out
your album laboring under delusions i have
heard about this you've heard about yes
by watching your stocking hat
that's right the famous king had famous
king happy that's right yes and so
i would i would stop it in
the store and and then she would
stop at my store and then we
went out on a date but it
was like i never i never i
think it's the when did you want
to tell the only times did did
she ever think you were older and
did you have to say oh by
the way i'm only seventeen almost eight
eighteen why haven't seventeen going on eighteen
we must have had that okay with
you
i want to date you but i
don't care if you are too old
for me
okay can i talk to you rodgers
never seen her second this song love
the melody you like it love it
okay i like the general idea of
where you're going until you hear the
next three hundred eighty sorry i'm late
yeah cutie
booty bend it and let me be
flat
okay
maybe this wasn't such a good idea
huh i'm enjoying it so your personal
note to do this oh yeah oh
yeah for sure this is shutting down
his hand goodbye ah dilly dilly dilly
dally so wait so you must have
had a much better conversation but i
don't remember it it was obviously not
an issue because we kept dating yeah
interesting do you think that she
just like your personality or she she
had a thing for the young'uns or
was it just you mustache no i
did not interest i did not
was it a period of time in
your standup career without a mustache my
crack oh that's very true yeah yeah
it's also true um i don't think
i ever dated anyone with a moustache
with a mustache yeah so i don't
know they got rid of oh um
no one with a wide gap um
age wise
yeah high accelerating almost anyone with perfect
thigh gaps except for chua oh what's
your different you really made up for
it there because hey real may december
one two
well ten years old attempted just ah
actually it was six hundred ten
yeah i ah so like went on
some dates with someone who was pete
whole nine or ten years older than
me but yeah it was pete holmes
think give me a roll um was
there a teacher that had an affair
at your school we talked and we
talked we talked about this like a
person who isn't the play that yeah
oh yeah wait but who had ah
but there was another i forgot there
was another english language teacher who like
oh my god there's another one there
were there were
three two the teachers looked like by
the way they looked to like zooming
the hay they were it was like
they were friends and they were like
i like this guy's style and so
they looked like or yeah that's what
it was
great
or do you just mean physically like
they like genetically they physically they were
both shortish guys with the same haircut
and moustache and they were both they
were both italian so saratoga really as
well as genetic well all the teachers
kind of dressed exactly the same know
that because he was like yeah they
all wore like you
no dress shirts and dies and stuff
right right yeah yeah no our school
you could wear whatever what about the
teachers what were the two guys that's
why i mean the tutorial seemed like
i remember our english teacher came wearing
a bikini once which was no big
taught that didn't yeah i say well
hey where's the big talk where i'm
really yeah she was a teacher i've
talked about this way
watch oh that is fucking weird yeah
it was weird hurting mary kay something
we didn't have been tell the story
probably i'm assuming of what my hot
gym teacher who oh tell us she
was young i don't i mean uri
i know i knew her um she
was probably like twenty four maybe younger
so could've dated one of us really
um but then like she would be
very very flirtatious and the one of
the guys in my class slapped her
on this one day and wow him
and then he got in big trouble
but it was like this huge turning
point of like it can't go that
far
right oh good flirt but then she
would flirt i it was enough that
he thought it was okay to do
that which i mean actually think was
like it was happening like we all
witnessed it's happening and and then she
also i learned a very big lesson
from her which is always wear a
seatbelt and cabs because she was an
acat and it was a sudden stop
and her face went into the into
the
blasting and she buzzed shouts yes forever
hold black eyes and she was really
pretty in chia her whole face cup
i mean i'm sure it healed fine
but oh it's crazy yeah sure every
time i'm in a cab or car
backseat i think of that and i'm
like yeah i'm going to be that
person who's like too late did you
what ah did you ever have the
driving around in a pickup truck
in the back of a pickup no
we didn't do that we would do
that in church group sometimes it's like
down the freeway here in california so
crazy insane to me that i remember
it was a big thing where you'd
be like oh can i sit in
the back we totally wanna do that
now it's so dangerous i know i
can't even imagine so scary you'd feel
so on me
mord yeah i don't know yeah well
yeah well what happened to one of
those teachers have an affair with one
ah one of the teachers had an
affair um and i think he got
fired you're fired one by donald trump
hey they they they brought me down
to this high school
just so i could say oh she's
a philadelphia hired me um who does
a better job you're here here's my
hey i'm donald trump i don't trump
help me i'm still
that isn't going through a door
and you do like like a giant
dorna yeah the garage shed fucking picture
of him from new year's eve in
the tuxedo where he's just like he
looks like a whale but he's just
got his mouth open and this guy
really funny guy on twitter patrick monahan
just wrote
just like posting the picture that just
wrote duh
getting so perfect so sad like about
all the politics i just am like
at a point where i'm i wanted
to stop oh it's it's hugely demoralized
like i was i was talking to
this man what are the other day
him donald trump saying i'm i'm going
to give out my awards for early
on you know or are you
doing such an idiot just so sad
anyway i mean i don't like anyone
doesn't i like him i think he's
funny okay good we need someone speaking
together i think he's looking hilarious but
just fight on larry don't see you
guys he bothers you so get me
wrong i love him you guys can't
stop talking about him because he's doing
somewhere ah i hate that um oh
wait so but another
of the teacher he ran off with
the student it was a girl that
i went to this grade school was
what i was gonna say about you
and the twenty four year old and
there seems to be such a wide
swath of maturity but that movie it
didn't bother me call me by your
name because i don't think movies have
a responsibility to do the morally right
thing
and realise like i think it's less
like this this is the story that
happens yes story no i never felt
like the movie was at fault apr
is more like i didn't know how
to judge their religious yes it was
a thing well because it was always
this part of it you know what
i mean is it is the age
difference significant and is it part of
the story right and in a way
it is
is you know it's like but it's
it's more about you know this kid's
um you know experience and this um
this wonderful thing that happens it's like
that's romantic and it's sad and it's
frustrating and it's you know it's every
like lie it's like yeah but but
but i guess what i mean is
is there such
i've never quite understood that about like
teachers falling in love with students because
or at least until you get to
college because it doesn't seem like if
you're under eighteen well it's also what's
so crazy about it is it's the
one thing you absolutely are not supposed
i think that's like a lioness your
one job you had one job don't
fuck up
i know but i don't i think
to teach them i think about that
sometimes like relationships shop is not just
like fleece yeah can you get right
damn who cares if you just don't
fuck
but i think about relationships i had
in high school or whatever you know
like ah you know when i was
seventeen i was dating a sixteen year
old and it's like it's and you
think in in nowadays i go oh
is that weird though like to know
i said i think but when you're
a kid like and you're just it's
whoever is
is sort of at the same level
as you yeah but i think it's
not like if i were to see
if i would of saw thirty year
old i'd be like you're too old
for well it's just what's complicated i
think because when you see somebody in
a relationship like that and they act
like that's fine or whatever it's weird
because for me now i think that's
a child
like i'm thirty two and imo if
i'm gonna run a high school or
i'm like you're a little kid that
was my thing the idea of somebody
being into that yeah like dating you
on a peer level is confusing to
me and you don't but another because
i'm older than that even and i
want to know i'm thirty five years
old guy okay okay when i am
twenty nine
dilly dilly dally what do you want
scott are trying to bring back the
the jack benny lying about your age
jag
when i look at someone who's twenty
four i see that as so young
yeah so it's it was weird like
to to experience this movie where all
of us i but so much of
it i think was about the casting
because yeah it looks like such a
he looks like a middle aged man
like a great-looking mean i always thought
he was older than me like for
the last ten years
i'm surprised that way younger he's one
year young way you'll let me know
i sit next to him on a
plane across him armor
and like he's breathtaking input yeah did
you join the mile high club i
did i masturbated in the back i
probably would do if i were across
from ya i mean he was going
to shoot the lone ranger career was
going out new mexico was wearing the
mask weight was back then yeah we're
holding wow flying to new mexico where
the mask yes
yes on his ass
how could joseph put his pants on
me daily daily daily alright let's take
it let's take a break we'll be
right back
welcome back we're back we're back well
backwardness of the art on the show
where one of us bring something for
the other call it to the feature
the future yes so it's my turn
today feature and um i have this
game at home that i really like
called hypotheticals i told you about the
hypotheticals yeah it's a chuck
klosterman gay oh yes and it's these
hypothetical questions that are extreme to be
right fight club oh no that's chappelle
nook but he wrote sex drugs and
cocoa puffs
you mad
furious you may check bags and go
oh okay well here's one of his
questions it's a fun game okay can
you just answer it so you just
answer it however i want yeah and
we'll just talk about the question okay
you are offered a brain pill if
you swallow this pill you will become
ten percent more intelligent than you currently
are you will be more adept at
reading
comprehension logic and critical thinking however to
all other people you know and to
all future people you meet you will
seem twenty percent less intelligent in other
words you will immediately become smarter but
the rest of the world will perceive
you as dumber and there is no
way you can ever alter the universality
of that perception do you take this
pill
i think people think i'm dumb already
i don't think rarely do it yeah
you think you're dumb yeah i don't
i don't you seriously feel like people
yeah i'm always mispronouncing words like look
you know i i do think about
this sometimes i remember george w bush
you know how you would have a
lot of ah sort of
brain farts on tv yeah say things
wrong or whatever no i was making
fun of that once my dad said
don't call him no um i said
yeah he said will you try talking
that much and you'll have those kind
of things too and then i was
like yeah okay whatever point but then
being having podcasts it's like
i'm constantly saying stupid shit yeah so
i have come to sort of empathize
with that but that's also a whole
lot of sex also my dumb brain
it's also your dumb brain but it's
all but that's there's a difference between
that kind of talking and you know
bull shitting on a podcast you know
what i mean no but i mean
messing up syntax of words and
or sentences yeah but i don't know
i feel like yeah and also i
won't remember i've said something incorrectly and
then i'll listen back to a show
and say i have done that oh
wow i've totally got that on my
god wait i was doing this i
was recording an ad at home and
i was home alone no mike was
there my
boyfriend and i was recording the ad
i was like oh it's just so
fast we go and i was like
and you can find the link to
that in my instagram bio and that's
ok thanks bye and then he was
like it's so funny that it's so
cool that you can um like do
a character voice like fix something when
you mess up and i was like
what and he is like
what does neg would you say he
was being serious he was like you
couldn't you don't have to redo it
you like made it make sense and
i was like what and he was
like you said twitter bio and i
said no i said instagram and he
was like no you didn't and it's
like guess i did let's do it
back and i said you could get
that in my twitter bio i know
the guy said that
interest it was crazy i thought so
doubly talking about all the time it
was so weird though to hear i
thought i said something i was so
certain and then just to hear it
back and like that's not what i
said that was i mean it was
not even a word i was you
know the show gavin and stacey i
have yet to watch that but i
really wanna watch i love it but
i've i was talking about it somewhere
i
i'm on microphone and i kept calling
it ned and stacey which was that
tom chester miss joe but i didn't
know that and i said it several
times the incorrect way and um and
people started talking to me about it
assuming that i knew that i had
said the wrong thing and i didn't
i'm like what does everybody what are
these people saying are they
make vita me i had no idea
so weird i said the other day
um someone wondered what song was playing
and i said yeah and it was
the song can't stop the feeling and
i said oh it's can't fight the
feeling and she said yes that's it
and then all i could think about
was i said the wrong title to
this stranger she thinks i'm in it
idiot now because i said very confidently
it's catfight the feeling and i'm going
to remember this day for the rest
of my life huh
and you did i so wow she
i think that she she didn't notice
she she registered it as the correct
thing or higher or that was shot
early know and i know but it's
the kind of thing that i will
obsess about for the yeah well that's
weird i think i might like to
take the pill just to give it
all but forgotten think about the question
um because i think i feel like
it'd be so great to be able
to use i don't know and be
smarter than bill i feel like um
i'm assuming if i take the pill
that gives me more intelligence it will
also give him the ability to read
isn't out enough to not be upset
that every grey stupid because it would
i feel like it would that would
be over here getting frustrating i don't
care about my own personal knowledge i
care about what well that's things but
i for me it's like it's i
realised it would be less i think
because i'm a middle child it would
be less about
um what people thought about me but
that they wouldn't listen to me it
would be frustrating that i would be
perceived as someone whose opinion or input
did not matter matter tray looks like
i know i'm actually smarter than men
you wouldn't be able to use your
intelligence to help anyone does anything like
what do i do with that intelligence
if everyone assumes i'm an idiot did
you
could you write letters and people would
think they're smart like a progress report
or like just even a letter like
he's good on paper yeah i don't
know hey if you have to write
it anonymously
if you could go
got this letter ah but it's a
good idea and i can't read it
but you don't understand maybe you can
make heads or tails out of it
if if you could sometimes do you
ever have that fantasy of laika be
good to go back to college or
go back to high school yeah i'm
learn more you know like what if
they made high school learn or want
to fuck
one of them a prize i thought
it was to not be emotional ie
terrified all the time yeah i know
when i think of it now my
crush i just be having fun and
like doing well like oh i have
the opposite where it's like all i
did was have fun and i didn't
learn a single thing like no well
i mean i was having fun and
i guess my social life but i
i hated living
in the door my god so much
anxiety about like a lot of that
stuff and so i would enjoy to
not have that dormitory yeah did i
say dormitory no oh god oh we're
back to square one oh and one
more question yeah sure i was gonna
oh what we're gonna say i just
wondered if like they made high school
for people like us whereas like we
had to go for people outrage
you had to go and you had
to do it for years if you're
it'd be fun my god no no
that's your life and your careers waiting
for you when i didn't like being
a student yeah i think i'd like
it okay yes i haven't read it
yeah
think of someone who is your friend
do not select your moron do not
let your best friend when i think
about making jokes but make sure the
person is someone you would classify as
considerably more than an acquaintance ah okay
this friend is going to be attacked
by a grizzly bear okay now this
person will survive teaching my friend
this person will survive this bear attack
that is guaranteed there is a one
hundred percent chance that your friend will
live however the extent of his injuries
is unknown he might receive nothing but
a few superficial scratches but he might
also lose a limb or multiple limbs
he might recover completely in twenty four
hours with nothing but a great story
or he might spend the rest of
his life in a wheel
chair somehow you have the ability to
stop this attack from happening you can
magically save your friend from the bear
but his salvation will come at a
peculiar price if you choose to stop
the bear will always reign for the
rest of your life wherever you go
it will be raining sometimes it will
pour and sometimes it will drizzle but
it will never not be raining will
the friend know that we've saved but
it won't allow him
but it won't rant oh well then
frankly i'm saying it might slip but
it won't rain over the totality of
the earth nor will the hydraulic whole
cycle being destroyed disrupted okay these storm
clouds will be isolated and they will
focus entirely on your specific whereabouts you
will never see the sun again do
you stop the bear and accept a
lifetime of rain does the friend know
that i say they do because
you're stopping the bear you're stopping the
bear let's say they do what it
says magically so maybe your friend doesn't
know i don't know i say didn't
know would you not do it no
you would i would just let shit
happen but if they knew and that
was like guess what it's gonna rain
forever on me because i did that
and and they had to they had
to thank me for it oh man
you love
no i didn't know i was thinking
about my friend i was like oh
would i want a baird attacking i
heard a crazy story about a bear
attack recently i wish i'd remember the
details but i was telling cool off
about it about like ah woman attacked
by a bear in the home and
and it was a cr
a star but i don't remember the
details but it's just that's horrifying to
be yeah but then the idea that
they could maybe just get away with
nothing you don't know what's gonna happen
unknown when someone's attacked by a bear
yeah i would not want to take
that chance i would i would save
the friend meat i don't really care
cash i like the rain sort of
like a counselor hate rain i like
ryan like excess
i like huh
oh but yeah when i bought i
do feel like i zero j again
you said here do it hey you're
way more time for another one okay
let me just scroll through these because
it's the most wonderful saturday night live
music start playing dumb dumb dad him
letting us know it's out of time
what was that music that doesn't play
to let
you know it's okay of time it
plays at the end of the show
and yes saying goodbye but it's not
like play like an award show or
you get played on snell music okay
here we are in the middle of
a sketch suddenly like oh da da
dum da oh i guess we gotta
wrap this up i'd probably good every
skin
earth is about to be struck by
a mammoth meteor book though no one
knows exactly what will happen most scientists
assume life on earth will be totally
altered and potentially eliminated everyone on the
planet is freaking out suddenly you receive
a bizarre email the government demands that
you must fly to washington dc immediately
by order of the president the email
message fired
the email message and goodbye email message
includes your last plane ticket wow first
class i'm in okay once you arrive
no matter what this title here i
mean once you arrive at dulles airport
dulles i wanna find a reagan military
police confiscate yourself phone and wordlessly transport
you to a secret hangar that houses
ten massive space shuttles your escorted he
spelled hanger wrong inspiring we were escorted
onto one of the ship how do
you spell it like a clothes hanger
like e r yeah dumb shit nah
george clooney your garden one of the
ships not counting crew there are twenty
four equally confused people waiting on board
you recognize a few of these people
instantly bill gates the musician
prints and oprah winfrey toby praises balance
when the individuals you don't write princes
back i'm in i don't care what
it is when they do it's not
a box of prince spaghetti
when the individuals you don't recognize begin
talking and interacting with one another it
becomes clear that all of them are
brilliant scientists consequential artists or extremely wealthy
political figures yeah yeah the ship's caption
informs all of the passengers the space
shuttle will be leaving earth in two
hours he does not say where it's
going although he doesn't says that anyone
who wants
to remain on earth is free to
stay behind you are ninety percent certain
you've been selected for this trip by
mistake do remain onboard and if you
do they expect ten people for this
i if you do how will you
explain your presence to the other twenty
four passengers you have no idea if
admitting your choice you will die by
you from traveling
yeah you guys have i've seen your
cable pack along here if oprah was
on the thing i'd be on the
thing i'm beyond the thing i love
her she's my only celebrity i really
wanna meet i told you she was
springsteen on broadway with us right ah
no you hung out with her ah
no she just was sitting bias oh
that's good weather um
i thought i'd be wearing like a
sweet like ah sweet life was i
mean um private area but i don't
have any of my loved ones who
are the women well they're brilliant scientists
are not interested
the only names are like male celebrities
let's say who are the oh oprah
oh probably do you think of her
as a man compliment
aww she's so successful she high praise
high praise is still there the queen
is a cock blockers yeah i mean
i guess i'd probably say like am
i supposed to be here i would
admit and i would start asking around
for sure yeah i'd be like why
am i chosen i yeah i think
that's how you would find out as
you would ask someone why was i
selected for this and then see if
they know who you are yeah or
you would do that and not just
go this is a fuckin sweet deal
i always just say behind you couldn't
you have the option of just not
going it's time that buddy know earth
is tough because i don't even know
that i go into the limo or
i'm assuming it's a limo
i don't know if you ever mentioned
a level but no but there's a
nice stretch let's get today to switch
on first-class i don't know if i
get into it if i can't bring
you know yeah paul over here know
if i can bring cool up i'm
like what the earth is going to
and oh yeah now i'm not gonna
leave her i guess she calm you
know what that's exactly it is that
if if in this scenario if it's
just like i don't know it's it's
this desire is presuming university of a
shit about putting your life or celebrities
you're single and you're done today yeah
yeah yeah yeah shoot i
yes that must be democrat yes if
you're a single dumb dum imposter i
will probably talk to oprah for a
little bit and then stay behind i
know every last second yeah i love
hey i don't wanna go there but
you're gonna die do it by dave
winfield will be alone but don't you
but there's twenty four other people doing
think the will to live
is it if i was any yeah
it's just poor i don't know if
like everyone i loved was like we're
all going to die but then again
there is there also is denial where
yes we all know the meteor is
going to strike but the human brain
kind of goes like but what if
it misses yeah what if it's up
or no and then you stay behind
me i don't know i mean nobody's
gonna like donald trump president
um i would yeah i would stay
behind with my lovely wife yeah if
you could go with your wife or
if she said go and that's what
she said that's what she said that's
what they always say to you dilly
dilly dilly my due
deeley deeley go off with you now
now deliberately
um yeah i would not yeah i
would stay if they're in if i
don't get a plus one then forget
it yeah you gotta get a plus
one plus one i'd be so scared
to interact
with a dead prince so much going
on i will ok i was talking
to prince for awhile did you think
prince would you be nervous to meet
bill gaye know i'd be like hey
what's up who's yeah he's a famous
person you just wouldn't give a shit
about i wouldn't give a shit about
bill yeah we're not gonna have these
nice to me that's pretty cool great
awesome
they used to be popeye on the
book huh oh who's a prisoner in
popeye then it would not be like
it would not be impressive to meet
one who what a president president because
i honestly well i'm not impressed i
mean trump obviously but like before that
yeah i don't think i'd really care
about most of them because i don't
really i honestly i just don't care
that much i feel like for me
it was that bad no no i
feel like it would be a big
deal for me to be jimmy carter
but of gerald ford was still alive
it wouldn't be that excited if i
met obama i would like cry that
would be yeah he would be an
impressive yeah person to meet but that's
the only one and bill clinton and
hillary clinton i'd be excited to meet
but even like george w bush people
so
steven george bush i feel like it
would be crazy like oh my god
i'm meeting somebody who yeah yeah i
would think something of that yeah i
wouldn't i guess anyone who is a
president when i was alive i would
be feel somewhat intimidated or excited about
meeting dr nagao accept you enjoy i
don't share my patch on the mag
da dah
let him who cares he's dying do
you think
do you think prince in this situation
say he's still alive that's another qualifier
ah do you think prince there's only
twenty four people and we're going off
to another planet do you think he
like drops the act and you know
what i mean hang on he's just
like a regular guy because someone said
that about michael jackson where they were
saying like oh no when no one
is when the cameras aren't around he's
he drops this thing is just like
hey i'm michael how what
that's like gilbert godfrey
why lot nah no your mean michael
jackson said that was pretty good really
you think he do you believe that
someone said that i don't know so
they were just like yea it was
michael fascinated by i do think really
had those kids
i think he jerked off into something
yeah i will say a woman
is it a woman's gap um i
waited on him once when i worked
to tell her video was awesome yeah
yeah he came in with an ah
you know an entourage of like security
it wasn't the entourage no turtle oh
oh it wasn't oc memes care oh
maybe they invited me maybe they meant
to invite aqua yeah
wait what did they like instead of
aquaman jason momoa huh
oh shit we thought we invited awful
yeah it's got aquaman you're gonna get
that one right so i did get
it when i was a kid and
i would get really upset and then
as an adult i'm like they're calling
me a superhero like she doesn't even
exist when you're talking about weight so
you worked a tower video which is
like on tower records kind of yes
it was news the video from our
records and um it was just a
video
store um and i think it's a
bank now but it was it was
empty for a long time after it
closed yeah yeah um which always made
me happy um i dated i dated
someone who lived by it once and
data is in quotes um but i
remember i went over i went over
to her often again
i went over to her apartment and
just it was like hey let's get
together what are we going to do
i don't know just come over and
so i went over and was like
well what do you want to do
you wanna let's go rent a video
at ah at the tower video so
we walked the you know i don't
know two blocks to tower video rented
little big man is enemy yeah
yes absolutely yeah is dustin hoffman no
no no big man oh wait yes
little big man is dustin hoffman okay
yeah yes rented that took it back
to thing what does a big man
little man little man take the one
with jodie foster would know i loved
the one that did ah marlon wayans
did oh i don't either
maybe you're white chicks you're gonna watch
when he's a white baby by the
way yeah but put a pin in
your story because i'm sorry i put
a pin in yours that's alright um
i saw a little bit of white
chicks i'd never seen it ooh and
i saw a little bit of it
on tv the other day and i
didn't realize that in this in the
world of this movie the wayans
brothers are disguised as specific white chicks
that when everyone else looks at them
they see these women was like this
was like paris hilton they're yes they're
impersonating these two who went anyway example
yes in the world of so when
we see their p o v we
see the actresses playing know just the
year
yeah like hi lisa on your whatever
their names are they look so much
like that flawlessly know i sound like
be so insane and then you see
them at the end the women that
they're impersonating i didn't realize all the
various i've never said what have you
got classroom as that of like yeah
okay you get this part and you
realize you're playing someone who looks like
like marlon wayans with like dad with
white hounds face to the idea was
when people look at marlin in this
getup they see you yeah wait okay
so what was your stairway tower sorry
but i want to finish my story
we never we will get back to
my twitter we put the video when
we walked back to the we put
the video on and watch sixty seconds
was it because you were fucking yeah
there's no hotter movie a little big
man starring guy oh and he was
so crazy minute of that movie the
whole pretense of like picking a movie
and we both were like oh this
is interesting new and we were like
have you ever seen wayne was that
literally you actually just hooked up yeah
that is what all you do at
that point where it's like let's watch
a movie these will not
owing to the netflix thing is right
where people know netflix and chill it's
chill and they're literally put on anything
but i was just like why did
we have this half hour thing where
we were like deciding and rolling oh
no i've seen this so it's like
a dance of courtship yeah anyway okay
wait so you know michael jackson i
saw michael jackson although now that i
think about
it could have been anyone because he's
wearing a surgical mask and the mirrored
sunglasses and a hat has been any
like the the tendrils of hair creeping
out and um tendrils
that's an inside joke between the jewels
ah cool
thank you you dilly dilly yeah
yeah i reckon but he came in
with like three or four security people
um who established kind of a perimeter
around him as you browse through laser
discs when you thought you were gonna
break that never said a word if
you were to break that perimeter you're
a customer at the store you have
rights to go wherever you want i
think i think they were letting people
in
around but i think the idea was
they were being watchful they were they
were to say submission two hundred day
would maybe say like if you share
your tribal leicester then they would say
and he would say yes hey hey
i'll tell you so so what uncle
jackson so michael jackson would what did
he do then did he brought such
stuff and he left what are you
buying year about a bunch of laser
discs
cool that was that would be a
thing that you would see a lot
is like wealthy celebrities would come in
and just buy like a crate of
stuff yeah well john meanwhile in colin
hansen's colin hanks his documentary about tower
across streaming videos ah he would go
every single ah tuesday and just buy
every single record
that would come out yeah and he
would buy stacks like you would buy
multiple copies of them he said just
because he loved like going probably like
selling them yeah that's right emails john
was probably used selling them out of
his car for like a markup yes
exactly ah gosh we have to go
but before we go we do have
one thing to say it everyone and
that is daily
a dilly dilly thank you bye
uh this has been in year with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com