three
thanks
ah ball i um scott
you ever forget your name i just
forgot my name did you bank on
yourself for good
my my name is scott like you
know my name my name to like
a hate my name grown-up scott you
know what it's like it's such like
my name is such a lame name
like there's so many polls though you
can be like my ma another one
in a big long traditional pool is
there a lot of scots no four
hundred yeah i don't know if any
guy aka
her man scott speedman oh so now
you're talking about language this is the
company that i liked guy f scott
fitzgerald that's a minute hold on francis
scott key key oh say yeah yeah
ooh say
i'm training more scots i know there
are about holy scuffling i also found
out by the way speaking of names
and our and we were talking about
our parents on the last episode and
we're not talking about him they'll come
up again my brother whose name well
first of all his first name is
burt after my
father but he went by greg i
don't blame him what parts better really
you do think not back in the
bag of analogy now it's probably better
but um but he my dad fucked
up the name think it's a name
like my mom and dad had agreed
on
what the name was going to be
and then ah and it's not even
close to greg whan it was they
just like it was like some italy
or something and then they and then
they asked my dad what's his name
for the for the birth certificate anyway
greg this is out of left field
and then when my mom heard it
and this is this is you know
typical of my family instead of going
no it's knighted steve she was like
oh alright i guess that'll be fine
i know my place my main complaint
about it for years i have told
my story but it's similar in that
it was a last minute lauren was
like just a last minute thing where
the doctor accidentally called my name lauren
called my mom lauren called your mom
laura and she said it made her
feel pretty and then to now
your lawn is crazy she wanted to
fight or to think she was pretty
she just thought that's a pretty name
like that made me feel good like
she my name my daughter existential feel
pretty what's your mom's name trish trish
regime i've always liked name true yeah
she went by patti grandma she didn't
like that happy when she moved out
with trisha good yeah i mean
i will say that patty
it's got the hard ass and i
think we got t it's got that
solid paw
your mom has such a solid put
on suh you can't say she does
listen high lounge as we love you
dredge nice dance but anyways yeah i
feel like that it's very funny to
have that like random change i just
found that i just found that out
in christmas or something like that where
we were telling stories and my mom
told me that it was
like who is going i don't feel
like it's shocking to me cause i'm
like don't you have like a conviction
about the name of you feel like
i'm gonna name my baby this game
and like maybe you see them and
it feels different but it's like just
a set right settled on it and
just hear that my dad was like
go and rogue yeah just blurted something
out but also that there's so many
stores
is about like this about naming babies
where you get the impression that it
it's done under the gun like a
time limit you better tell us right
now or typing and i'm to way
out the door yeah to give this
to the government it really is a
lot of pressure it feels like from
those stories but yeah i believe that
to be true yeah you get good
at that either
easily had a conversation about that like
no we said steve remember yeah like
oh hey we said steve and they
go alright we'll change it i had
a discussion with my ah my thrilling
adventure our friends on our long-running text
thread ah now in it's seventh year
where do you find time to text
all these people because i'm on maybe
two or
three of your techs reds ah yeah
and you are usually the instigator on
them your your unit call me i
mean i will let it lie fallow
for months yeah and you're usually the
one to like get it all going
and i'll tell you why because i
think of things and then i think
of the people that i like as
nice but i want to share that
with we got one yesterday from you
about the lie
live action lilo and stitch that's a
movie like the point people yeah and
there's a picture there was a picture
floating around the internet of what of
the terrifying inch that is stanched yes
and a little caroline where real real
life yeah yes yeah that's why it
was a cartoon very cute mccarthy we
remake everything
oh now we're getting to the deep
philosophical stuff finally oh what i love
a good remake but we don't need
it for every single thing that's ever
been that's true but that disney seems
to be on that trajectory where they're
saying we're going to take all the
movies we've already made in cartoon form
and make them live validation makes it
all like if it's in two d
animation
i guess i like it if it's
two d they should upgraded to two
three d animation and then go live
action they're skipping a step if it's
three d they should make it forty
no but live action is that like
they're not like the one they said
a live action lion king banking was
one every single thing there would be
some actual humans in it right now
there should be there should be like
charlie chaplin the little tramp should just
come in suddenly yeah why not because
it looks beautiful but it is shot
for shot exactly what the original lion
king and it's just three d animation
yeah and then i heard something about
how like the original animators don't get
any sort of money for that even
though they came up with all of
those images well the now we're talking
about the long history of exploitation
and and media and wow talking about
the thing that i started talking yeah
what were you talking about you don't
even know i was yes oh yeah
like raw you were one of your
text threats yes your thrilling adventure i
was saying i had this realization of
like my name should not be paul
f tompkins it doesn't it doesn't work
yeah it's
very planned i'm glad i finally said
it i feel like the f really
makes it special but how about this
i really i worked it out and
i think that what my name should
be like if you saw a picture
of oh my god this is amazing
sure of me yeah with the way
i like all dressed up yeah mustache
the whole deal my name should be
dennis j peacock okay so you're basically
like a clue character yeah yeah aren't
i yeah yeah you are sort of
okay that's a fun game though but
yeah anyone can you only do it
about yourself i think you can only
do it about yeah because it's like
potentially offensive yes so i want to
do it for you
no of course you do but scratch
magoo ah dumb shit before i feel
like my noise
like my name should be like like
something like a little bit quirkier you
think because you have a i think
i just goofy i feel like it's
like so i could easily be like
danny or some i think lauren lucas
first of all the alliteration i like
the alliteration i like the things six
yeah six letters and each one would
you say six six six and six
six
six for the devil my favorite guy
but it's longer it's a nice shout
out it looks nice together i like
that yeah plus i d p k
but if we're making up last name
what about what about louis p k
i wanna know what about louise c
k
ah because it's just who i am
um i don't know i feel like
i could get away with with a
weirder name but like so if i
had gone by dorothea my whole life
i would been called daddy or something
but then i don't like how that
is with laccase i don't think that's
going to be lap cats yeah that
sounds like somebody that works what if
it was school
like ma body johnny layers what about
dorothea liguria daddy lie so she's talking
about drugstore when you're supposed to be
in class at one point i considered
just being lorne allegro as my last
name and seems to f know to
me it's too like pretty like it's
too like yeah i like what it
is i guess but yeah i don't
fucking know well but
it's like a big thing when you
think about like naming a person as
a huge to you and then that
person i guess my changing my life
i didn't like it yeah exactly i
think you have to as an exercise
think you have to look at a
picture of yourself where you feel like
the naked this picture where you feel
naked but you have to be making
when you're looking at the picture you
you must be new it should be
next with the body mass index yeah
that's right and police shot people who
look like you enough to where exactly
yeah actually have you heard about this
show um no game of clones on
mtv i just heard oh tv it's
thrones i think when each new absolut
not it's an mtv dating show where
the person has a type and then
they bring the people who are going
to compete for them are all identical
like it's like six men who don't
know each other who will happen to
have the exact same style and look
and apprehension they dressed some of the
same club casino no i just saw
the trailer wow and what is you're
supposed to then based on personality i
guess yeah but lie
like can you imagine if you walked
into room and there were six guys
who looked just like you yeah it's
additions i know
i think that's true too but like
like the idea that like yeah i
know what you're basically really look like
yes yes yes i will say right
now that i've said it on race
by t but if you tag me
in a picture of d j qual
ziploc you i've made fun of it
i've had fun with it yeah when
we talked about it i don't need
to ever bring it up hey you
know what the same yeah if you
do it your block if you tag
me in a picture of vehicles
yeah it's done i do think that
that hey you look like this twitter
is the worst twitter yeah i've i
get messages from like girls who were
like oh people say i look like
you and i can often see it
but it's like it's a weird thing
to even like respond to like yeah
because usually they're like totally telling me
i hope you're okay
yeah look we're all just you know
trapped in these bodies our parents give
us it's a meat sack trapped in
them until the day we die and
we wish that we could change names
back here's what's great tell you something
we're all disgusting yeah human beings essentially
are the most disgusting creature it's gross
it's gross
lauren what's up no i honestly don't
want to open the pandora's box of
what sort yeah but like and changing
your looks i yeah there's too much
to be said and and it's it's
just a big topic it's too it's
a huge topic i think so i
think you can get it i think
some people it's i think anyone should
do whatever they wanna do that's the
thing where here's for such a out
leaf candle we're here for such a
short time if someone wants to you
can you were talking on the last
episode about photos and we shouldn't be
looking at photos and i i've been
thinking that too well part of the
problem with doing shows like this is
like we have to take photos for
the show yeah and we have to
put them out and i know every
single time i put out a photo
for a show anytime i put out
a show
it's going to be a test to
a photo and i'm grey yet cracks
about my looks so it's like it
makes me go oh i don't want
to do shows anymore but like is
there a way to post something that
it's not that like what could you
post like is there a way to
post where it's just the guests there
should be oh i'm sure there is
sketch artist draws you really nicely
the the way that was the of
voice do the job what if that
was part of what kevin did does
here which by the way i don't
know the other parts but it just
works we just don't have to leave
at one because this is where one
part of it where he had to
sketch us while we did the show
that would be something kevin there's a
question why do they do courtroom sketches
like how long does it take
yeah that's the other thing let them
take photos why are they sitting there
sketching with like colors and stuff like
yeah get to the point where we've
just accepted a world where you're not
allowed to take photos in a courtroom
and people sit there with colored pencils
i guess it's less distracting than camera
but why because of a click although
i feel like i can feel it
when somebody draws me do you know
like have you ever like
gotten your drawing dental i guess the
street or something like a caricature yeah
yeah or like just one of those
guys who draws you on the streets
you know since after your house was
already creeps um no but like orange
sometimes they do like a pretty sketchy
pencil sketch like i did when i
was a teenager and like italy and
and they're like oh sweet my mom
had them do it from your you
know my so is so
not a caricature like a beautiful picture
yeah but i mean doesn't even look
like you in the head of course
but right i even caricature i feel
the pen moving on my head i
didn't see that one yesterday it's like
money i feel them doing it like
i feel like if i were in
a court case and i was crying
and someone was sketching me like i
need them to stop
please stop my head is itching with
you drawing that's lauren i've never heard
that i've never expressed it out loud
that's true i mean sounds like a
feeling of like someone like
putting their their hands on yours maybe
you are a drawing come to life
that means a lot of sense actually
because you do look to look like
something like a disney animator with you
on my machine my character psychologists that
i was like a disney princess slowdown
from the pusher are you from cool
world what's that that's a kim base
kissinger as a cartoon movie from nineteen
hundred and ninety three brad pitt i
guess someone here david bowie in the
theme so i didn't think you'd not
weird someone else out there relates to
this feeling and there's a diagnosis maybe
they do maybe it's my niece
my bike
it might be a thing where if
you know someone's drawing you it makes
you like self conscious or something yeah
yeah yeah interesting so do you how
many drawings do you have of yourself
at home um actually be honest probably
like six but some of them are
from fans and stuff i got that
when your people made amazing art i
think it's so cool and people do
that yeah
it's awesome for sure yeah i'm someone
them are that but like the ones
i've like commissioned myself i think i
have two and one is from a
car a caricature that was at a
bar mitzvah we have a silhouette wedding
and that commission that yeah there's someone's
doing silhouettes party yeah oh my god
i just got that done at magic
castle and i was so cool oh
wait it tells him about the magic
council would happen
and oh it was fine oh wait
are you talking about mike's house yeah
he's the magic so the mayor ah
my hole he likes free i go
to his house sometimes ah his he
had like a friend from college yeah
kygo yeah do you wanna just see
your house
his friend is a magician and his
friends machine is so cool yeah we
went to go see his friend performance
magic house loses friend give him a
shout i don't remember the name right
now magic friend um i don't remember
the amazing friend yeah amazing for amazing
mike's friend
so we got tickets because you know
you need to be invited to go
to the magic castle who doesn't live
in l a it's like a it's
like a castle that says magic but
there's you have to buy more stages
you have to be invited you have
to wear suits you have to wear
a hard shoe it's recused myself i
did a very hilarious routine okay yes
thank you stan i appreciate yeah so
women have to wear a dress i
believed to which i think is really
weird like i have a friend doesn't
like to wear that that's the thing
about dresses it's weird that it's clothing
where it's like open right where the
the pussy you know that's not the
reason why it's weird okay you know
like guys don't have that so like
it has a hole in the front
my guys are covering their buddies can
wear well and the wrong dog thinks
the ground but still
l and but it should have a
close it should be closed down chopper
born address yeah it's various things and
it's like gets comfortable bringing it's kinda
cool but you should just wear shorts
anyway i worry we should wear shorts
why do you want to wear shorts
i'm saying it's weird that they're short
right area here's the problem
is that women are not wearing shorts
enough and they should wear georgeson scores
and that's an hockey jersey here's a
real question for anywhere buddy o charge
jerseys where do i find good bike
shorts to wear under address that are
not athletic okay tell me that because
i've searched high they're not athlete meaning
you cannot get on a bike when
you cut but they're the i don't
want the texture of stretch sway
at wicking i don't want like waiting
in the woods what do you want
like a cotton biker like chi when
you're a kid but for a grown
woman like you could wear under a
summer dress yeah because who knows what's
gonna exactly a breeze with my cum
okay so you go to the magic
castle and a hot tray i was
actually it was beautiful i bought by
the way i have to say i
the last time i was there was
a couple of years
years ago i was with ah two
of the people that we were with
were ladies who do not wear dress
addresses and ah they have they have
adjusted their dress code oh good to
wear as long as you're dressed up
yeah cause i want to do this
was like maybe five years ago in
front of and like gotta dress yeah
she it even though she's like i
don't want yeah right yeah okay
yeah that's good that's good to know
yeah ok but men still have to
wear suits or can we wear dresses
you know i think manga wear dress
okay i mean you better look on
board way if they can't forbid people
wanting to wear whatever exactly exactly anyways
um so there's a couple rooms there's
like a close-up there's rooms with close-up
magic there's rooms with like purse like
private shows and then there's also like
the magicians who sit around and these
like more public spaces doing just tricks
river walks up and watches these guys
were one of the private rooms drank
a full forty hour it was like
the clothes already our man forty hour
forty minutes hourlong show i don't know
how long it was in the closeup
room it was not in that room
so yeah yeah i know it's a
coffee parlour maybe but it's one of
the
not the main room but the ones
they're kind of comical they did like
um it was kind of like a
comedy show with magic guys fun yeah
and then there was a man cutting
silhouettes um and it took him like
a minute it was like very cool
really stand in front of light and
he was like dude you're cutting it
freehand yeah wow like what looks more
like him than
i look like me but it's still
really cool we had that done at
a wedding they had a silhouette just
at a wedding ah that jane and
i went to and i was very
trepidation about doing it yeah it was
like if there's anything i hate it's
my profile i feel like i've one
good angle and i'm not thrilled about
that which one is your good ones
right
right down the road i feel much
better about my straight oh yes well
but this characteristic was very forgiving really
and she forgives you she forgive me
can you again we have we haven't
we framed it we have it on
display in our home but i was
astonished watching her do it because she
wasn't like the the
she didn't have the people against like
a screen or something to see the
shadows she just i'm doing it france
she just oh wow so it was
wild it was wide and it looks
like you yeah wow it looks i
mean yeah now looks enough like yeah
crazy if you walk if you order
out you know that's them people who
can do that i mean i took
our class
this is as a kid because i
wanted to be a cartoonist when i
grew up but and so i learned
various things about like you know make
everyone a shape or you know we
did the whole like turn draw something
upside down that will remove your perception
of it does that make sense like
if you see a horse you
have a perception of it as a
horse so you're trying to draw it
as a horse whatever your perception is
whereas if you like turn a picture
upside down and just draw it as
the shape it comes out more accurately
yeah it was if you see a
horse you take him down right away
yeah so you establish dominance over the
arms it's over you get on top
and it's upside down right
but and then nature takes it's course
and with that i'll see what i
was doing but that skill of just
being able to like how did you
figure out you're good at that did
someone turn to the side once and
you go i know how to do
that it feels old timey yeah maybe
they like resizing land or something like
oh gee artist yeah it was yeah
it was like a popular fad of
of a bygone era yeah right yeah
people why would people get so
silhouettes instead of just drawings of themselves
or i guess you could get both
it seems really bigotry i think the
novelty of it yeah it wasn't like
victorian era they had silhouettes and like
their name we had a ton of
your silhouette cameo we had a ton
of silhouettes growing up like my my
parents would buy pieces of art and
then they would all
and they would never change yeah yeah
you know they like most people so
we adam johnson silhouettes we in fact
when we are in tokyo or kyoto
actually recently i was looking through a
magazine of ah various things to do
in kyoto and there was a museum
and they had a picture of the
famous painting that was there i was
like that is a painting that was
on my wow
wow family room wall for decade and
you had no context and essentially it's
a fake well we had a print
of it yeah that my parents got
when they went to immune using israel
and ah sorry i didn't even get
a bid i hear ya i'm always
very disappointed it's time for you to
not engage in order to tell
well the story yeah it's true and
that's the way we that's three to
bay but i hated all those photos
because you would see them every single
day and get dire oeuvre painting you
get diarrhea you get diarrhea from them
i'd get a diorama from it as
a painting ever induce diarrhea absolutely because
music has you know the brown shade
if there's a certain shade of brown
if you just might it makes people
have diarrhea okay look we have a
break we'll be right back
alright we're back hello sure yeah i
don't i think i you my my
back i'll smile soon is so good
for you sleepwalk i used to really
yeah i don't know why i thought
of that but um i see
did as a child and i also
where would you sleep to where would
you walk my parents' room there's one
story where i was like well i
walked into their room and i was
just like standing there like a zombie
and i'm almost like go to bed
and i was like no
that will leave no beer yeah i
didn't having i realised this the other
day because i was in a meeting
and i and i it popped in
my head what we were talking about
and i brought it up but i've
been having i guess i i dream
about a certain place all the time
and i am real
you help to go one day we'll
place our lawyer a place i've never
been to oh it's the payoffs in
some crazy way in your life i
mean a certain house you think you'll
die in that house owner when you're
one hundred
oh thank you lauren i appreciate your
hundred but that's all you'll do no
but i know you walk and you'll
yeah just go your birthday surprise oh
my drew
no but i know the whole environment
i know the way out of it
i have several dreams over several years
i dream about it and it's not
like i i go to and i
go oh it's that house no i'm
just fine i'm in the middle of
another dream and suddenly i'm in that
house i'm like oh this is the
house dreaming oh that's going to be
like the the house you buy some
day and you know it's well it's
crazy
house i don't want to buy it
sorry it's like three weird levels it's
way too big and how long have
you dreamed of this years and years
and years and years and i've never
been to it so why it was
so what is it is it a
parallel dimension where i do have this
house could be i don't know now
that's what i mean don't you think
we exist on multiple planes no okay
fuck yes thanks
play
um i don't know that's the thing
is there a multiverse where we've made
different choices and our lives are fucking
crazy i think that there might be
because like the pain you feel isn't
inexplicable
meaning when someone draws you out do
you mean physical pain or emotional thing
i guess like you know like you
could feel like something is bigger than
you and i don't know i guess
i feel like that could be another
version of yourself do you think
or is it just that your so's
ah like you love yourself so much
that you think there must be endless
multy numbers to me everyone right i
i don't i i feel like i
was at ah a gathered recently where
people are talking about you know are
we in a simulation and i never
heard anybody talk about it
so sincerely as i did at this
i have i recently heard somebody talking
about this too and they're like yeah
i'm deaf i definitely believe that and
when i heard when i heard the
way they were saying it i realized
oh i don't at all i think
that this is just it and i
think that you know the thing
no sir where are you oh it's
easy somebody made a playlist of every
song we've ever mentioned on the show
it's great it's exhaustive if so an
exhausting yeah like us i think that
because because there's so much in life
that is random or unfair or inexplicable
or whatever we're always
trying to make sense of it yeah
and to me like somebody saying oh
this is a simulation sounded no different
to me then oh gosh there's control
talking about religion so in control of
it it's not pointless yeah anyway the
semi that we're in a simulation but
but i'm thinking like the multiple dimensions
is possible because that's like something that
people are
working to prove isn't that awesome yeah
i mean i'll say this i think
it's it's possible i don't i don't
think it's probable but i think it's
paul do you think it's not that
we're all existing with many different sliding
doors versions of ourselves but that when
you die you can go to another
dimension yeah know where you're in a
black hole and you don't even have
of existence but you're there well people
think i mean i know we've tapped
aspect i would buy your consciousness goes
somewhere i don't know we are kind
of dipping our toe but do you
think do you think there's ever been
someone who suddenly like they're acting way
different than they've like a good friend
or something and you're like they change
maybe it's like someone from their multi
the multiverse like took their play
case you know i don't buy that
you don't buy you don't think that
we able to access you don't think
we're able to so i don't think
anyone's coming into this one from you
or one zinc there's never been a
traveler from another divine there's been one
got bacula it's cut badly there's a
scott eric go yeah found it or
at least expected another dementia
yeah i don't know but ah do
you guys have recurring dreams that ah
i when i was a kid i
did i don't anymore
what are you trying to put there
like ah my dreams now i don't
i sleep pretty deeply the sleep of
the dead i think just
yeah obviously but the just i don't
i don't remember my dreams a lot
i have lately i've had a few
anxiety ish dreams really but they're like
so low level it's it's more annoying
than anything like why did i dream
about being anxious about that dumb thing
right but being late for something or
whatever but i used to have a
for the longest time i would have
longest time ah dreams
death longest time you imagine if it
isn't just life you are trying to
get through a sentence with and someone
did with people it is like this
is not stimulation this is how we've
tried to communicate so it's bad it's
so weird that he's like oh you
know i'll let a week go through
it where it's like
oh let this go on for a
little yeah but i'll just pick up
where like yeah huh it's psychotic you
feel really psychotic it makes no sense
you wouldn't do we act like this
off mike
no way not finally people finish for
the most finish
just finished um ah wait what and
exactly your dreams last time i would
have zombie zombie dreams where i was
in zombies
and they were great they were great
dr because i always you have the
freedom working people they were very yeah
finally there were very exciting yeah always
got away yeah i never died in
the dreams right it was fucking great
so i wake up and it was
like i was just in a movie
don't they say you can't die in
your dream well
that's okay you're true here's what i
found oh yeah here's what i found
is that when i'm dreaming i usually
have like an escape hatch for whatever
situation i'm in and anytime i've you
know how it's like you're like dreams
are sort of like improv were like
well if this then what so if
i'm ever
or in a situation where my brain
has gotten me into a thing where
i'm like i'm falling out of a
plane or whatever like too great a
height and i go oh shit there's
no side hatch for this i'm definitely
dead that's when i wake up right
you know where i go and it
just frightens me too much i'm like
oh no i'm no escape hatches here
there's no plan b here
i'm dead i've had that for sure
yeah but i've also had dreams where
i've died and i mean when you're
just then you're dead like i'm a
different person can we just say kevin's
silently leaving cause he has to go
and he just left this you have
to dry guess so he finally okay
let's check out the sword as a
perm lauren has a perm just
lauren oh i can't tell who is
who we all look like we're wearing
hardhats well i just polished off a
big glass of chocolate milk apparently
he used some coloured bag it's hard
hats it's the headphones oh okay well
did they ever we look like we're
in a construction site you get a
really great job lauren shirt like you
have anxiety dreams about real things in
your life when you said like yeah
oh yeah for sure i would have
worked dreams
seems when i was not the boss
now i'm the boss i have like
about your old jobs yeah you know
which ones i'm talking yeah yeah i
know funny i don't i haven't i
it's been a long long toss yelling
dream or a school dream i have
yeah old dreams alive or i'm back
in school and i'm not prepared or
wearing a half shirt and i wouldn't
do it like you're wearing a big
show but it's like covering my shirt
yeah i do still have the restaurant
dreams where i have too many tables
etc doesn't mean i haven't been i
haven't been a waiter in now twenty
years i still have them ah and
occasionally i'll have the ah this is
what happens to me a lot
is i'm supposed to go on stage
tonight and i've scheduled and i have
the schedule i have now but i
also on a lark agreed to be
in a play for the community college
or something oh yeah i've done plays
games that are like and within hamilton
and dream recently
i don't know but it was so
stressful but i've agreed to it and
the date is counting down and suddenly
i'm supposed to be on and i
realised i did not i either have
to cancel or have to be on
and learn all my lines yeah that
day and then i'm out on stage
and i'm like trying to feel it
out and trying to yeah figure you
know trying to just like
ad-lib through it and stuff like that
but it's usually all schedule and stress-related
where it's like i want to do
this fun thing but i've over-extended myself
yeah i've had dreams and it's infuriating
where the the the anxiety that the
way i'm communicating anxiety to myself is
i'll be in the fucking supermarket trying
to find something
in that i can't find so you're
lost in the supermarket know you're needing
an irony or new guys
to them i like red
a mark yes
and i wake up and i'm like
what ah that was a waste of
a dream yeah i want to do
fun stuff in my dream i'm gonna
have an anxiety dream at least make
an interesting well that's the thing about
these like i'm on stage and i
don't know any my lines why can't
i have a dream where i know
my lines and i'm in hamilton or
whatever and having a blast yeah and
like the audience loves it and i
get standing oh
those and i've had dreams like i've
had dreams where i was doing standup
and it's like a wake up and
it's absolutely nonsense but in the dream
and dream show like this layer shit
yeah yeah i've i've written jokes and
stuff like my dreams and i would
say ten percent of the time they
make sense if you remember i also
like some that are really funny or
it's like it feels amazing like he
wrote his main you're dreaming you're like
wake up you're like right danny like
that actually is good like that makes
sense i actually crazy because most of
the time it's like yeah me going
like oh i do do a lot
of like when you're writing you sort
of work out problems in the writing
through your dream that you can do
that ally were like you're thinking as
you're going to bed you're thinking about
a story prog
elam you're having and then it reveals
itself to you in the dream of
the solution so it's almost like you're
not wasting time while you're sleeping you
know now that i have that a
lot actually where like you wake up
and go oh my god that thing
that i was dreaming about i figured
it out and so there's so many
now i've figured it out with the
pencil and a pen and then so
but conversely i also have the thing
where i'm like going through an argument
with someone in my real life as
i'm going to bed and trying to
like you know you know how you
do that thing oh yeah where you're
trying to anticipate every single thing they
say and what you would about that
what you would say as a rejoinder
to us to do this god damnit
to do that all the time yeah
you have imaginary conversations with people instead
of just happening in bed yeah yeah
so just having the real conversation yeah
you know i feel like what even
are not having the conversation which is
like getting just getting over it i
feel like so like there's some people
who are really good at just going
like that doesn't matter i'm not going
to think about that well if it's
a work thing
things on the say that's what that's
what it's been like for me recently
where it's like a work thing and
you're like how having you're thinking about
it because like the the actual conversation
that you can have is days down
the line and so you're trying to
anticipate what to say and then that's
all you dream about is a stressful
the menu
get it just right when you actually
are in the moment right yeah you
know but i think like in terms
of like people where you're thinking about
something from your past were like you
you either like i wish i'd said
or like or if i could see
that person again i would say this
thing fuck da da se um but
then i like
i often think like well what a
waste of time that is to be
like thinking about something like re having
a fight or thinking about someone who
i don't see but then thinking like
okay well if i ever did want
to confront them about that what would
i say is people who have wronged
you or people that you have wronged
like both like i feel like it's
just like a mixed bag but whoever
pops up it's like it could be
anything but it's like has there
ever been someone where you think about
that a lot and go oh wow
if if i could just talk to
them again like isn't there someone you
could just reach out to and go
totally but then i go one thing
i was thinking about that is that
that person might not want to hear
from you like weather like like even
a nice up even if the apology
or just saying like let's forget everything
that ever happened
are like what put it all away
it's like i haven't with certain people
what's our centers to people don't want
to hear an apology from someone but
i'm saying i don't even know that
my thing is an apology necessarily with
the specific thing i'm thinking of it's
a friend from a long time ago
i don't know that the thing is
an apology so much as let's let
bygones be bygones like i don't know
who
who did what it's a long time
ago i don't even really know what
happened but for some reason we're not
friends anymore i just want you to
know i don't feel anything bad about
you or that i feel bad that
we're not friends but like but but
do we need to change it i
don't know it's like but i wonder
if that person is like you know
what you did yeah maybe you do
and i don't i've i've had that
with people where you know so
nobody that i was friends with and
we had a not like an announced
falling out but we definitely we waited
and send out the invite i didn't
knock out the light we ah we
yeah i'm not friends with we'd like
head it was like tension building and
and then we just kind of went
our separate ways and um yeah
years later ah reconnecting with them briefly
over something and saying like essentially like
saying like hey when i look at
when i look back at the past
i don't remember any of the bad
stuff i just remember that we had
a lot of fun together and the
person saying yes same here and it's
like it's nice yeah i say sometime
seems time just takes care of things
well somebody doesn't much like scars your
memories you just forget about the bad
stuff in a way yeah and then
i wonder those sometimes guard from lightning
just like scar yes just from the
live action lines you do you forget
because he was a bad thing you
only remember the fun i forgot about
scarring feel like we're sponsored by the
lion king somehow
yeah whoosh but here's the thing what
i feel is there's no the first
of all there's no statute of limitations
on apologies you can write i would
accept that from anyone anytime but also
when you're the person apologizing what you
have to what you really have to
feel in order for it to be
sincere is you you don't even have
to you came to worry about whether
it's gonna be accepted or not right
it's gotta be like you are owed
this apology whether whether you accepted or
not for sure you are owed an
apology and i'm gonna give you an
apology yeah and then you know the
rest is up but it's hard when
you also feel like they owe you
one too well that's a different story
yeah yeah actually my new year's resolution
this year was to apologize more
it's it's nice really yeah because i
noticed towards the end of last year
that if i were to if i
were to go to my defaults which
in my family is like you know
getting defensive and you know saying i
and if i could move past that
in a quicker manner and go you
know what this person is owed an
gee i'm just going to like instead
of just ignoring it i'm just going
to barrel through and give them one
i found that it just like ah
made so many situations so much better
it's a lesson that i learned and
it's still like you know the it's
still work to to put it in
practice a lot of the time but
it was such a relief when i
realized oh i don't have to it's
okay to be wrong
yeah and my the way from the
way i was raised to the how
i lived like the first half of
my life was like i have to
figure out how this is not my
fault and i have that exact make
it somebody else will because if i
if it's my fault that means i'm
bad i feel like my brother and
i were in a competition all the
time for who was to blame for
stuff and we would
get spanked you know depending on who
is to blame and so we were
always like lying about you know what
we did or we were always trying
to say like neuro this it originally
wasn't my fault you know arguments would
escalate to the point well who did
the original thing you know yeah and
so that's how i feel like my
life sort of is is like well
it's not my fault you don't know
no the situated you to look just
it's the situation yeah to the point
where like you can get to where
you just never apologize to anyone you're
just like well just deal with it
to everybody so yeah it's just when
you catch yourself saying when you catch
yourself starting to go through the excuses
of like this this and this and
you're like okay what does this really
about you know this is really about
i fucked up because of whatever
you know and and this and it's
not this person's fault and so after
apologize to them will also just even
if you were set off by something
the the person like just saying like
you know what i'm going to claim
responsibility for what i did even if
you feel like you're owed something just
like you know and even if you
never get anything back and just
like deescalate yeah i don't know yeah
nice try wanna do it more although
i do think the person if you're
going to apologize to them they have
to be at the same level as
you so leaning what meaning like they
never apologize an underling they can be
a subordinate they have to have like
the same i am db star meters
yeah like would you must check before
i think it's more like it's all
there anyways when you're giving apologies to
people who aren't like cleaner like your
meter is better than yours then always
zero
yeah pretty much yeah yes okay let's
take a break we'll be right back
welcome back to three am here we
are here we are sitting in a
room together that's right that's right meet
you you lolo over here do oh
la my robot oh yes lauren is
diana
name is a picture of you dressed
up a small wonder online anywhere ah
nobody can find it it's it's i
was small wonder for halloween in two
thousand it's yeah da costa great two
thousand and six hillary housing college oh
okay i wasn't universe
these university guys you know what time
it is what time is it like
well about one thirty scott
it's good that's according to the clock
ah but according to according to three-time
it's time for the feature oh let's
do a feature we got to feature
this one is called twenty one twenty
one twenty one yeah we're gonna is
the game show are you cheat this
is blackjack that's
this is a memory game where you
sup
you know like memory games i just
glanced ahead and yeah what okay oh
just start just start let's see what
we have and i haven't looked at
it yet so see explained to me
like i'm a dumb idiot well normally
would i'm gonna explain it to you
like i'm a dumb idiot okay this
is a memory game where you substitute
words for number
hours i'm already off board words for
numbers guys game go for speed if
you break the momentum than you are
penalized he with annoyed glares from the
other players and you want to sound
like you want to isolate that's all
we do yeah please avoid the noise
yeah that goes for all the games
just please please if annoyed were to
show up here
a bag of i misstated the group
forms a circle and starts counting one
person per number what one person found
multiples of seven the person who says
the number also makes a rule where
one number becomes a sound or a
word cousins have this one was going
to be easy yeah so the purse
austin lands on seven might say from
now on for is shazam well for
our purposes the lion king
then the counting continues and the person
who lands on fourteen might say the
number nine is now bob ross so
the so you're you're changing numbers to
words and we all have to remember
these we all count up from one
every time it comes down they'll say
the person on twenty one makes a
third rule in the counting starts over
at one with the new rules in
place got it oh okay the object
of the game is to get to
where all numbers have been replaced by
something else god whoever forgets to replace
a number is out and or drinks
so when you fucked so what are
we going should we plan on drinking
we changes drink during the show and
we honestly believe oh and so here
we go
we said we got this soviet stuff
maybe
let me just tell you to relax
yeah fun talk this game out we're
going to do coke did we say
so we're going to do that too
okay so i say one you say
to three and then i say four
you say five to six i say
seven which means i get to to
say any numbers right oh i see
so we're just saying numbers until the
multiple events
surely eventually every single thing twenty one
would start over yeah guy so let's
start okay one two three four five
six seven the number one is now
coop who lore sorry eight nine ten
eleven twelve thirteen fourteen and now the
number five is
a cockatoo ladoo fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen
nineteen twenty twenty one and now the
number eighteen is circle ok poop two
three four
kakadu told upi you came up with
that six seven eight weight seven seven
so the number um the number eight
is now kitty cat get cat nine
ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
the number
victor over and your sister you don't
remember numbers yea number will tell you
he's already been done ah three okay
is now ah kaboom
fifteen sixteen seventeen circle nineteen twenty twenty
one and now the number twenty is
cardboard poop
two
three no ah what is it kaboom
kaboom you're out i'm out kaboom
for cock a doodle doo
no no likes that's okay that was
a mistake but i was five so
you say six o six seven and
now you change it
the number two is now beer
alright
eight no
circle know
i don't even know i don't kitty
cat
okay someone i'm to get yeah i'm
gonna try to myself yeah do it
yourself do all the way
from poop poop beer kaboom
for cockatoo de lou six seven
hold on
no it's something you do know something
kitty cat
yeah nah it was ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen the circle
nineteen cardboard twenty one yes yeah but
we're supposed to get to having all
i know yeah that's pretty far too
stupid
already done sorry i don't remember that
there are more people also be better
at night when he won yeah why
don't we do a version where it's
four ten what okay yeah now we
do it on multiples of worry five
why don't we do it ten on
multiples of five okay fine but conaway
three three is more so we'll do
more three six
nine it would happen faster i know
but it's too much to remember right
you know and i'm sure start okay
one two three four five and number
one is now kleenex okay six seven
eight nine ten kleenex and no oh
sorry ah nine
is lamp clean x two three four
five five is racha two e six
seven
eight lamp
ten
number two is um spanking
one no
cleaning yeah speedy never heard of work
spanking ah three
am i still in yeah i don't
know think of it for kaboom
rolled
yeah this one's you are done we're
done this one's too hard but damn
done for a rose really fucking is
really tough that that one the way
are what was the one that we
did a few episodes ago where it
was a memory game and it seems
so much easy that was um the
minister's cat oh no the packing game
oh yeah not a trip yeah i'm
going i'm going on a trip
and i'm taking and that's a through
z yeah and but he was many
corresponded to the alphabet well let's do
that we're gonna get that let's do
it again ah let's do it let's
do it where does it i like
it okay i'm going on what if
we don't even say i'm going on
a trip i'm gonna just say a
letter with a word with the letter
a b and then you have
say ab then you'd say abc don't
want to do the trip just because
it drags it out so okay okay
let's do without the trip we know
we're gonna trip here's what we're bringing
all right i'm going to give me
give me a letter p p
potato
so now i say potato within q
yeah potato quilt potato quilt rat but
an l quilt raf sailboat potato quilt
rat sailboats terminator to the rise of
the machines potato quilts rat sailboat
terminator two terminator do rise of the
machines umbrella
potato quilt rat sailboat to terminator two
the rise of the machines umbrella
it violet
potato quilt rat sailboat terminator two by
the way i think it's judgment day
it is terminator two judgment day umbrella
violet zoe said violet um whisper that
i ruined it by taking the sentence
no i like potato quilt rat sailboat
terminator to rise on judgment judgment day
umbrella violet
shit what did you say yeah see
i'm out i was ah thinking about
you said it's you do it
you do it you do it your
turn
potato ah rat tattoo oh no you're
out you forgot quilts wow your next
ah i'm next week prove it do
it prove it okay to prove it
prove it potato quilts rats sailboats terminator
two judgment day
umbrella violet whisper xylophone the problem was
that i thought x came after v
and that's why i could remember what
that is the problem isn't it if
i'd really focused i would have realised
it was a w well you know
it's interest did we last time we
played started a all the time because
it seems harder to start in the
middle of the night
i think we started in the middle
did we really yeah let's play it
again it's gonna start you start i'll
start getting better give me a letter
three letter j
jpeg
jay peg
kitschy art jay peg art
lambrusco
jay peg kitschy art lambrusco that you
heard me
mnemonic
jay peg kitschy art lambrusco mnemonic
notary public
jay peg ah kitschy art lambrusco gnomonic
notary public oh face
since you're bringing on the trip
jay peg the troop has gone lauren
chips cow in another dimension now bring
whenever you want would bring that on
a trip the good guy guy fun
guy with franco so he's ready i'm
gonna forget jpeg kitschy art lambrusco mnemonic
notary public o face
pandora's box j peg kitschy art lambrusco
gnomonic ah notary public
oh face
ah fuck would you just say
your problem is you not listening to
the person right before you but i'm
thinking of what you're gonna know i
was i wasn't always gonna say i
was thinking something else
what i don't know um
what could it possibly be called on
what the fuck think of aerosmith
aerosmith and their big box set
there are multiple cns boxer oh man
you're a big aerospace
yeah why dare you
um what pandora's box um and um
at cliff
ah
gea pig
ah kitschy art lambrusco ah gnomonic notary
public oh face ah pandora's box ah
richard kind forgot you forgot q you
did
oh yeah i dare i did a
more out i'm always the first year
return alright jay peg kitschy arts lambrusco
gnomonic notary public o face pandora's box
quiff richard kind
salamanca some onca
what does that breaking okay um jay
peg kitschy art lambrusco mnemonic notary public
oh face pandora's box quipe richard chi
salah mundo salamanca da
no that is and then um
turtle shell okay i'm back in wow
hey hey yeah alright sure okay jay
peg kitschy arts fan briscoe mnemonic notary
public o face pandora's box qui f
richard kind salamanca turtle shell uvula jay
peg kitschy art um lambrusco
a mnemonic notary public o face pandora's
box quiff ah richard kind turtle shells
you're either way when i order dang
yeah i will not hold cheese
alright we gotta wrap it up don't
let's wrap it up guys this is
fun i enjoy some times use a
lifeline sorry for everything i apologize i
apologize to you guys so i apologize
i owe you an apology know either
reveal no no we're all good i
think so do guys want something from
me
i'm sorry i think not gonna give
it i think we're good
face
well yeah i think rory has an
own face i just scream oh we
got i we've got along like we
never had any ah tense moments on
the toy didn't know we didn't did
not i don't think so to everybody
time you
to ever give you the high hat
know i die we got along well
jump lido rp ah we always say
that at the end of every three
races toledo later risdon please
nicole napolitano
bye bye
a