yeah
um hi everyone well hey everyone welcome
hey everyone welcome and hi everyone welcome
my name is paul f tompkins my
name is scott f aquaman my name
is lorna f laugh kiss althea that
is and welcome to three dorothy yeah
thank you dora yeah dorothy oh wow
i don't want to talk about dorothea
yeager was just eating seaweed yeah ah
right
lower the shuttle
is she a woman is this lemony
snicket
it reminded me of my friend when
i was young ah my my new
friend in the third of the fourth
grade he was japanese and he really
thinks so
he was thinking some sort of knees
he was masturbating is that what that
means yes yeah i never knew yeah
now you know enjoy it even more
that suck that's how i felt when
i found wait why is it a
horrible idea about your horrible ideas correct
jesus christ what a fucked up song
yeah um but anyway he was japanese
and i was thinking about this the
other day and i was like
i wish that my parents and not
to roll it off on my parents
or blame them but i wish that
i had some sort of cultural sensitivity
training when i was young me too
because i remember my friend eating seaweed
for a snack and all of us
going like oh gross oh that sucks
you know and now i eat seaweed
occasionally it's
fine but i wish i could have
i wish someone would have said to
me like hey you're going to experience
someone who is not white or even
a white person who has who
who likes something not you know different
but i don't know when the seven
days hazing phrasing you're going to experience
someone who is not white i have
to say on the wiki for turning
japanese that song it says has seen
the songwriter says turning japanese is all
the cliches about bankston youth and turning
into something you didn't expect to know
codes but
anyway it's even good if it's not
about masturbation yeah no it's just a
weird thing to say i guess but
it's a catchy song it's a very
it's a very catchy i know i'm
never going to not like it i
had a friend when i was a
kid okay i also know i'm never
gonna not like
i love michael jackson songs i think
he's a monster poo
i can't get into this really it
into this when i was a kid
i had a friend i like me
laura lucas to oh i like to
cuddle laura okay
so you had a friend named sigmund
yeah and he was right of seaweed
really yeah he was a sea monster
i bet yes he was well yeah
that's that's we don't use that germany
oh okay goodness
he was a likeness yeah i don't
know but i have regret and why
am i still thinking about that of
forty years later oh i have so
many things like that from when i
was a kid that like you're just
a dumb and also when you're when
you're i was raised in a in
a place where like casual racism was
just yeah and fill it
sophia where'd you know casual racism was
just the order of the day and
you didn't and the people around me
and and the language of the used
and everything was just a part of
my life and it was not until
i got out in the world that
i realised oh guy was incorrect is
there any sort of ceremony to let
something like that go and i know
there is like a p
put it in a box and throw
it into the fire whatever save it
for anybody but you know what i
mean but do they work you know
like to like to absolve yourself of
yes sort of because anytime anytime i
see seaweed i think of that anytime
i see carl's junior french fries i
think of the ones that i snapped
at the guy that's like how you
let these things go thank you but
i
we we didn't have a conversation that
was adjacent please don't spank me i'm
not going to do it but chef
kevin stott here i know and i'm
not going to blame miami will play
but i didn't know this is this
is jason but it's i know the
angle i'm now the angle i'm taking
on it is is lauren you are
more why wouldn't even say you're spiritual
but you do
don't you do stuff like this sometimes
yeah to get rid of ah yes
to get rid of is there something
one can do i feel like with
that stuff it's really maybe therapy oh
there'll be able to live i guess
just found about bindon because i think
i started therapy this year or thank
two thousand and ah
god i know i know and i
know you've never been with herbs i've
never been oh and i always thought
it's not kind of cool but i
also always like i'm fine you know
like i was like i it i'm
fine and it has been great and
i've also found like the things that
i'll end up talking about will be
surprising it's like maybe something like that
where you're like oh i guess this
thing really does bother me
that i have this memory and it's
just kind of good to like get
it off your chest to somebody and
have them just be like an unbiased
sort of i don't know i believe
obsessing doesn't maria bamford say something about
if if you say it's than it
or then it's manageable or something like
they'll we're basically like comedy has helped
her so much with her
troubles because she can say it on
stage and it gives it less power
well i think that's true i think
like what without ever going to therapy
for ever my whole life anything that
i had that i was like thinking
about those upsetting to me it's unsafe
was just like i'm just over thinking
it in my head and then i
just it can become so big so
big
but then yeah and i'm saying the
first time you say it it's hard
yeah and then the fifteenth time you
say it it's like oh yeah this
yeah carrying things around like that is
terrible it's really terrible when it's just
it's just living inside your head yeah
that's why i don't think we should
be spanked that is what i'm trying
to say like the more times we
say something are real stories yes this
this is me trying to get out
of being spanked okay look i don't
want to thank you so i think
we're all fine i'm not gonna make
zig do it
that's to me is the hardest that
would be fun
why is it fine if kevin does
and it's not if if zig did
it i'd be like i'd feel sick
seems like a real person yeah kevin
wanted so bad and love he delights
and the license um wow but i
i view this show is my therapy
oh no oh yeah
you're not my friends my therapist is
sucks yeah yeah the new catchphrase for
three of this sucks
ah freedom this suck oh come on
i don't own one post negativity oh
the world good that's i'm glad you
said that because on that tip secret
visitors update there's a new parkinson's commercial
whoa where i because i think i
did you send it to me i
think i said it's your maybe i
did like a little bit
we've talked about it right
no i'm sure we talked about it
the commercial with um where the guy
sees i think on our last season
yeah we talked about it and we
needed t-shirt about it yeah of course
no no no well we talked about
the new wow we did where the
guy sees a dog and then he
sees two dogs and then one of
the dogs disappears so my question is
one of the dog doggy one of
the
dogs is real well that is he
seeing is he seeing no dog as
he's seeing is he seeing a two
dogs where there are no dogs resisting
two dogs whether they're one dog or
izzy should he be seen three dogs
three dogs and one is is
not suitable to him and then the
second one also becomes is there a
pack of basset hounds that he should
be see i just feel really upset
knowing that parkinson's has the side effect
of hallucination which i did not know
until these commercials mean i didn't know
that was a part of it i
mean it's really upsetting yeah the human
body sucks
source crazy all the things it can
do
waggling your eyebrows looking down winking various
ah human body has sang
secrets
crevices and clever so this is like
no other my shin cranny my mission
crannies i thomas' english muffins that phrase
when i was a kid i hated
it so much i think it was
the way the voice over but i
didn't like that either nooks is no
best it also sounded gross like i
would never eat it and it's also
yeah basically a bagel like i probably
would have liked it but as a
kid i was like huh it doesn't
granny love english muffins when i was
a kid they were like a real
treat with peanut butter yeah crannies is
so low still read your regular butter
i like i like em with regular
butter i like my opinion about i
don't like them with peanut butter crannies
is close to granny's and grannies have
crannies on their face yeah ah crazy
grannies and grandes and crannies yeah he's
grant
easy oh
yeah i can't i can't argue with
you something that to delight in my
life yeah that's what i do for
myself in the weekends i make myself
so today for example so for example
we're typing this on a saturday this
is not freedom thursday this is not
for no guy not even to be
three am thursday anymore it's what
sorry what have you heard well the
date that we discussed okay we'll talk
about this later we will talk about
this later because three of tuesday doesn't
work no sir
i make myself on the weekends on
saturdays and sundays maybe even be three
to monday but
i wish people cared about my little
tree do i do i do i
do what do you do i make
myself a breakfast sandwich i haven't eg
a canadian beacon what okay one egg
what how is that
sunnyside up it is here's what i
do cracking in the pan crack get
in the plane smash that yolk it's
my stay step on a good step
out of your eye when i flip
it over i put some cheese on
top of that let it melt on
the egg i'm out why i don't
like um you know i'm really
and cheese goes in things oh i
actually don't like being crannies of a
long-time kind of but i also like
cause like muscle basically like tosin tall
so i try to leave it out
of anything thank you yes so you
can finish a yea hey why don't
you just enjoy his story than trying
to like impose your lactose intolerance onto
his story on this
show before as as far as this
story goes i'm on time as far
as the story goes this is a
detailed story that is unpleasant for her
i get it okay so you guys
on again what happens the cheese are
used and this is step out of
your huge mouth the
i use ah velveeta cheese whoa so
you're really so like a philly style
ah cheese steak
oh that's is we don't know we
don't know where it's oh it's not
so it's not spray cheese no speeches
okay so it's like a singles okay
but she's taken the classic philly cheese
steak is with cheese so it was
invented like in like what the seventy
s when did cheese a cheese steak
sandwich i don't know what i mean
like yes i do yeah she is
isn't hasn't been around forever right
but there's a weird thing with people
put provolone a yeah that's what people
think a cheesecake is problem by the
way is not a good cheese for
sandwich right anyone anyway so you say
use slices avail via cheese yeah i
do and i'm proud on the bottom
of the egg on the top of
the egg well you've turned it over
didn't you say well you see the
bottom
now it's the top right like drake
said i can use to be about
enough i consider whatever wherever interesting about
eggs wherever it falls in the pan
first that's where it is that's how
we label i before i cracked i
turn the egg upside down
wait you know you skinny yeah me
on the day i just give you
the top okay but how much back
so then i was imagined and i
put it all on i put it
all on fifty yeah oh i put
it on a pretzel roll pretzel roll
holy shit okay oh good so what
does a pretzel roll
lol because everything right since roe v
redd yeah but what do you mean
slice round like two slices of pretzel
bro that's not a role a role
gotta gotta gotta this motherfucker it's as
if he'd i've had a borough where
i've had a burger on it no
i'm just gonna manage to slice out
of bread know i've had a burger
on a pretzel roll so now i'm
in i get it you know when
like you're growing up and your mom
would
have buns and stuff shoes brand yes
yeah she got bonhomme yeah like i
talked with like two pieces of bread
so that is such a weird unique
disappointing because you just get your me
we already planning to make it yeah
sure there's no bond yeah yeah like
yeah i like sometimes i'll put a
hot dog on a sandwich thin what's
a sandwich thin that's
you know instead of doing slices of
bread that because they're so fat and
there's so much carbs you can buy
sandwich things which are basically they look
like skinnier english muffins and so it's
like having less carbs kosher eating a
sandwich is it cool no it's not
yeah some of us have to worry
about things we don't look like an
upside down exclamation point oh much
the tdi private conversation
auras autor foe just looking at sandwich
then okay i'm trying to see what
it is and you know what i'm
interested yeah okay now you're into it
my description didn't do anything for it
which sounds good i know i'm not
into it you know why i'm not
because it looks like it looks like
a burnt muff english muffin and it
looks like looks like a burning wish
ma just like regular bread new and
good too
posted here's i'm telling you what it's
not as good as bread
alright of course it's not as good
as bread you're eating it because it's
not as good as bread okay you
know i feel this way about like
vegan cheeses like i have really come
around on a lot of them and
i'm really happy about them and that
they exist but like i my mom
would like think that was like so
wack like she would never want to
eat oh yeah i used to when
i was younger
i used to have the opinion
just just eat the normal thing you
know what i mean like e right
if you like peanut butter with nuts
in it eat the peanut butter with
nuts in it even though it's like
way more calories or whatever but that
that was when i was twenty right
i don't i don't feel that way
now i've i have a sensitive stomach
and i try to eat ah specifically
don't just go
around eaten whatever the fuck i want
you marie kondo your stomach yeah yeah
i do i only really because i
really feel horrible fates or do you
have do you have any food allergies
in addition to lactose intolerant no i
don't think so i had an allergy
test where they did all my back
you know like all those yeah yeah
i saw some food allergy yeah yeah
someone showed me there's
two nights ago well when i was
at that dinner where i shared the
deserves shared it with this person was
it in someone's home know who's that
a restaurant showed you their back and
they showed no no they showed me
a pic that looks like oh yeah
he got the shirt here you go
i did that until you ever done
that no i haven't i sort of
like you it's kind of awesome i
immediately started itching so bad and certain
things like it was kinda crazy yeah
they told me that they were on
fire yeah that night just that one
part of their back yeah so they
do they divided up into like fifty
or sixty spot and they learn way
they circle it this person had just
had it done just how well ahead
had done a couple of nights ago
and said that night they that one
part of their back where the one
thing that they were really super allergic
to was just on fire all night
but then minus because i'm not i
thought it was because of some food
that they were eating there was like
activated the oh no no patch yeah
yeah they put it wherever yeah they
basically put it in a needle or
something like that they have all these
different vials and they kind of like
poke yuen each with each
different vile and a member and then
they take a marker and they circle
it and then write what it is
that they've poked you on it so
yeah this thing is cats then you
get that as a tattoo yeah you
go right to the tattoo paw mine
that went really crazy was dust yeah
that's my it's olive trees all of
tree all
love tree trees but not um but
not all of oil i think cool
i've had acorn trees and nobody sold
this yeah yeah so we're yeah like
the trees themselves marketing jackson we were
talking about off mike just in an
allergy test and his allergic to a
million things you find so um it
may moping and find out something
yeah i mean it made me think
i want to do that because maybe
i could be feeling better than i
read all day today i wonder if
i because i know i'm allergic to
cats because i once dated a woman
who had who had a cat head
cat head jocelyn wilkerson body and her
name is babu barbuda
because duh um no shana cat and
i i the the first night i
ever stayed over with her i just
woke up in the middle of the
night my throat constricted and i was
like ah yeah sucking on
that's what
how dare you impugn the memory of
me sucking on her clin
i want to go home ah i
kind of want to set it i
know it so i have to ah
so i know cats but i i
don't think i'm allergic to food but
i don't know but it could be
interesting if you try to get now
maybe you aren't even still alert grapefruit
motherfucker
oh no i just can't have that
because of medication oh no oh but
it like activates something it'll activate the
whatever chemical in the medication or something
turn into a werewolf yeah my brain
explodes scanners
um but yeah but i forget that
because when people when people come by
you know a waiter will say do
you have any food allergies and i'm
not alerted to drake to grapefruit so
i always say no and then suddenly
they bring me grapefruit wow and they
call a fancy french name and then
you don't know because you're a bump
mom
shh yeah p me i'll have one
of those pamplemousse i love some of
that shit yeah give it some papel
mais um i want to learn just
catherine i was a kid but i'm
not naming you see i think some
people outgrow it yeah it was weird
weird though because i've had friends that
were really allergic to them and as
time goes on they're not a dermatologist
tell me once ah because i was
having
ng i was having an issue that
i thought was an allergy i get
ah ah ah excess buildup of yeast
on my skin oh cool well it's
very easy to make bread with that
butter sandwich thins but i get it
it's like it affects me behind my
ears and where you have like a
when behind your ear or something no
no no it's like
it's it's it's like it's one of
those like sort of sores that the
bumps oh you know what i mean
that kind of like gross shank www
yeah yeah google one of those have
fun google win and then put one
in between some sandwich thins shut up
but i get i get it causes
dry skin dry skin so like behind
my ears but it hurts it's like
parents doughnut
oh
and so five five media ah yes
look at one yes sure did i
thought that i was having an allergic
reaction to something right she said no
it's not this but she said i
remember i will never forget this allergy
she said allergies just happen any time
and they could you could stop being
alert something you could start being allergic
something
in anytime and it's like that sucks
oh my god one time when i
was living in new york i went
to i was just like at the
container store and my mouth started really
hurting and then like it was like
swelling and then i wow many dicks
worth in there only for only five
okay and i started
i went to look in the mirror
and my mouth had grown like doubled
insights like real layers this is awesome
and i was like i look so
fucking good
finally my faith we have a little
freebie girl chat finally my face made
sense um i was panicking those i
went to cv yeah when you say
gru what do you mean like yeah
it was it was swollen it was
swollen it was yes yes my lips
it was like something open all not
the opening where you said your mouth
grooves so my lips you're looking like
okay
a coming like really like swollen okay
and then i went to cbs and
like i got the pharmacist was like
give me some endorsing but i i
did not i you know i had
just graduated college i was living in
new york i didn't have a doctor
but i had a gynecologist i'd called
her and she told me what to
do but it was like she said
is it on your pussy because otherwise
i'm not allowed to say check she
was so nice
and like a mom basically but it
was like it was really late at
night i didn't know yeah and i
was really worried i was gonna like
have some problem right and then just
went away and i never interested could
just be an airborne allergy that's something
easy yeah were you making out with
some plastic containers you know that was
the weird thing i was like this
is the most like sterile and i
can't imagine what was in this place
yeah
that made me break out looking at
your container right now my container you're
looking at your water container was yeah
you were like looking at it like
longingly yeah you fuck water are you
meant to idea you're an objective sexual
hey
battle so
um anyway it was fucking weird i
had this thing power yet inflammation it
was fucking weird not to mention the
day the clown cried in two consecutive
episodes do it for you each and
every episode were you that that that
time we were going to do it
um he got shut down and got
shutdowns okay so little backstory patton oswald
will be had
um ah would do stage readings of
the script of the day the clown
cried because it's an oh yes i'm
i just that we've talked about and
so labour movie jerry lewis directed that
never saw the light of day and
i saw and it was the first
in a genre of concentration camp comedies
yeah and jerry lewis for a while
was saying there were rights issues but
then i saw him before his death
and he admitted he in an in
an interview then and in several other
interviews he's like no i did a
terrible job with it and he died
that's why yeah we always have to
remember anyways so fine we were doing
stage readings of it and i did
it over like a ten year period
i think like often on patent would
call you into service you're doing it
again yeah i missed a couple but
sometimes do anyway
so we did want over in in
santa monica at the powerhouse theatre yes
that's what it was called yeah and
um and the rightsholders to that ah
it was written about in the la
weekly so the rights holders to that
script came and gave patton a season
desist order and the weird
part about it as i recall patton
writes about it differently in his book
but um was that i recall patent
saying yeah we're not gonna we're not
going to
fuck this season assist we're still doing
the show right and then right as
we were going out on stage him
going hey so guys um so we
can't do the stage reading part of
it so we're just gonna go out
there and like an improv and and
do some stuff like literally as we're
going on stage right yeah so in
any case the other weird part about
that whole story
he is i'm standing backstage at the
powerhouse theatre i'm leaning i'm i'm on
these stairs waiting to go on and
i'm leaning against a rail a wooden
rail and it suddenly breaks and i
go crashing down into like i only
fall
i only fall three stairs or four
stairs or whatever but i forgot what
i crashed into but like juts into
my leg and like scrapes off a
bunch of my leg rice is so
anyway when i go do the show
i'm a professional now informed bleeding all
over the place i'm funny as hell
and they need ya on that
state stole the show but weirdly so
so then it was just like fucked
up for awhile and back then you
know none of us had any money
and so i couldn't go to a
doctor yeah so it's just kind of
fucked up and like never healing you
know what i mean but then um
the weird thing is is you would
just like come back everyone's would heal
for years it's fine and then just
suddenly lie
like suddenly it'll like get really dry
or something in like look all fucked
up again so wow yeah they were
in so i went to a german
now the now that i have you
know insurance and all that i like
went to a dermatologist is like oh
yeah that'll just like come back every
once in a while here's a cream
keep it for when it comes back
and it'll but it'll just like suddenly
i'll have like a big scab on
my
my leg because wow so because he's
just like it'll just come back every
once in a while yeah i'm not
a doctor you everywhere jul even ghosts
you've seen me in shorts yeah
and you loved it every day yeah
you talked about it a lot you're
right no but actually can't picture it
we were in hawaii together i swam
in a pool i remember that but
i'm saying like shorts like with yeah
sometimes i wear shorts with sneakers like
little sneakers yeah we'll see schedule c
schedule stay yours the trainers yeah do
you notice around the house yeah but
not not those our house sure if
i'm like do though
my health shorts if i'm doing like
errands or something if it's a really
hot day i'm i put on some
shorts it's interesting go out and calmly
nerve your style it's not it's not
my brother and shorts my brother i've
seen you in short jesus my brother
is a my younger brother is a
year-round shorts guy some people are really
shorts pete yeah yeah tell john
yeah that's right yeah you will never
see non insurance that's true like because
you can't get pants long enough
i can't remember him being invented that's
how often he wore shorts yeah i
literally cannot picture him and i officiate
his wedding and i am only seeing
him in shorts in my mind scott
come on now can't be so you
know he wore a tuxedo i imagine
you did but i can't see it
if he wore a tuxedo shorts they'd
be funny he also only
where's formal shorts he also wears shorts
and exclusively seems to wear my old
comedy death ray t-shirt with my face
on it man he wears a shirt
a lot he wears it everywhere including
when his baby was just born it's
treating the hospital the first picture he
while his baby was being born my
face was the first face that for
sure for sure that honestly is is
wrong
i'm like he shouldn't have done that
i shouldn't have to will you go
scold him yeah i mean like what
was his wife thinking during this moment
his wife well i didn't want to
just show you with like wow give
me drugs
i'm just thinking wouldn't she be like
why gotta look at she loves him
she loves me she loves him yeah
hey that's part of the you know
that's part of their thing that's part
of loving him yeah i love is
exactly anyone's that's comfortable feather wooden leg
i still love her right leg
i didn't know janie yoda wouldn't yeah
that's so weird isn't it i've never
seen her in shorts no and you
never will because of that reason that
relais yeah wow real housewives pirate peg
leg like um she was a fake
like one of the real housewives and
does anyone know yes it's ah like
a mystery they'll solve at the end
of the size of ships of the
housewives
has the fake leg different fee options
to wear with different shoes so she's
not totally real housewife
so when she was a kid they
went back to the scene of the
crime where the accident where it hell
happened what accident when she lost her
leg wax at it and everyone was
wide and she was at a i
don't know if she lived in a
barn or whatever but they are lived
with a bar you know she was
raised in a barn she's she was
she never close the door but i
don't think they were
playing she and her from are playing
in a barn where there was a
sort of giant machine that played foot
chop yeah they're putting foot chop
ya know i think what happened was
an appellee gonna get a little wrong
but she was playing on this machine
that was off and then it turned
out like a threshing machine like some
sort of crazy thing oh barring your
purposes horrible it's trope telling off and
her friend witnessed it oof isn't that
much goof horrifying i'd be so scary
but hey
it's that happens to people like who's
to say like we've here's one example
we've all we've all had had our
you know our limbs for as long
as we've had him but who's to
say like you know like next year
hey i don't want to think about
that because that is a that's just
reality that's just reality and the thing
is is like it just happens and
it never comes
back and actually i might as well
say right now there's a um there's
a go fund me for a comedian
who i know who fell through a
skylight yeah yeah yeah and if anyone
wants to go donate to him he's
recovering i'm gonna his name is jason
sands i s a e n z
and you can go finance google fund
me and donate five bucks because because
comedians don't have children
insurance is about to kick in and
about that's right and like among ah
after the accident happened he was supposed
to have a job with insurance oh
and that didn't happens in times so
he needs your five dollars that's the
thing i always feel like we're all
like to miss paychecks away from disaster
oh my god don't even yeah yeah
like every
american scout would okay but i've just
but you know what i mean like
it's sad how often this seems to
happen i know i think it's so
scary wish there was some solution no
well oh well let's take a break
let's take a break
movie be right back
where bag and in jail mrs so
very much well don't you love us
don't you wanna squeeze us and pinch
our cheeks if you see if you
see paul or lauren on the street
just pinch their cheeks hey you don't
love it if you do that to
me i will sue you
touching and you have deep pockets don't
i do and i'll go deep you
will make sure that you bury them
okay yards ago i did a cross
country train trip where i trained to
i trained from los angeles to philadelphia
to do a gig and i thought
i would make an event out of
it and so i put out a
little video pr
homeowner i said i'm traveling across the
country at the various stops i will
get off the train and meet me
at the train station i'll give you
a sticker how many stops well i
thought it's gonna be a lot of
stops but it was only like three
stops yeah i remember when i when
i went out to milwaukee was one
stop first chicago people met you and
you people met me in the transition
i give him a sticker that
said paul f tompkins looked at me
i love that that's how i met
real butcher whoa she was shiraishi she
was in chicago wow she came to
the station and you know she had
said i i i kind of remembered
her because she'd come to one of
my gigs and we took photo together
and she still has the sticker and
now she's one of my good friends
wow um but i um oh no
why did i bring it up oh
we talking about i think i'd say
there was a bad part of the
story now you had to tell trail
while you were talking about or why
we were taking our cheeks and get
your g g when people so i
said in the video like as a
joke i said
i'll shake hands with you
i will not i i something i
don't know what led to this but
i said i will not shake your
ears unless you give me permission and
one person's said would you shake my
ears so i took this one maybe
here's johnny sugar cranor brainwave out yeah
i have
i saw the story well that's what
she wanted to happen she was like
i just need to get a little
just need this out of here yeah
and i hate this in the brains
that pick me up and my brain
was like give me a sticker
it was a no sticker stickers are
for brains
what if you had to how did
you make those stickers oh just remind
me somewhere they would like to cheapest
things i just like the idea yeah
no it's not like there was a
there was a bunch of pre you
know come are you putting this temple
in your hand what you just did
that so strangely i squirted it into
my palm okay but then
you put no but anyone like that
in terms i say okay i have
some ah pure l i squirted it
into my palm which palms flat then
you put your hand and almost class
chiang mai tai's yeah that's not normal
it's not that strange to me why
would this not be normal if this
way it doesn't spill all over the
fucking place e okay you just don't
know shit
how do you do now okay we're
we're doing the pure oil challenge huh
we're seeing how we put okay and
then you see see what happened though
you turned your okay let me narrate
what lauren did
this is the problem so lauren took
the hero so i was like yeah
you did for show okay i made
it a little extreme and of course
nobody could see stream hero when she
pour the cheese courts into her problems
that guilty pleasure when george clapping well
yeah she started clapping that's why i
got you but what she
did she turn out dough do it
she turned her palm ah vertically instead
of horizontal before i do it before
she put her other palm into it
and it would be slipping down onto
the table
i put into my palm then i
sneak up on it that was like
a lotion commercial yeah i fake my
hand out like oh no not yet
yeah i got ya i put a
lad put it into my palm i
put my hand behind my back and
then i sneak my other hand around
so it doesn't see i put my
palm i put my hand up the
top of my head like this next
day they're healing this to go i
put my hand upon my
a hip oh yeah when ideal me
you did we did it was my
turn to go and was my turn
we do the the rule of threes
in this house my way makes more
way more sense in your way i
guess you're better than me oh lord
i didn't mean like i just you
came at me first and you will
make no sense for both use the
highway oh yeah you a
look we everyone's right oh we what
the right answer is just sanitize everyone's
right i ever get there but we
should do a commercial for pirro we
should pure alloy johnny basic material challenge
so i was already got on your
mouth it's you know it's just like
a little raindrop yeah and it's sorry
about it and it's not dirty it's
pure anyway i went to hot yoga
the other day and i
i was like commercial no i was
laying down in the middle of it
because it was really hot too hot
yeah yeah sometimes i i've only done
it twice and warm yoga i'd rather
do that it was ah it was
too hot i i just laid down
and then this guy next to me
was still doing all the movements and
his sweat flopped on lockdown
and you know what i didn't immediately
wipe it off because i felt like
no because i felt like if i
was rude or something but i also
was laying there going like it's right
there if that's working with parts of
your body i would my hell i'd
still be feeling it today yeah yeah
it was really gross
which ah and what what parts of
his body was the sweat from but
i can't say i'm assuming an arm
as he likes stood in linkedin thing
okay so armed arm not a huge
deal this is adjacent yeah one time
i was at the gymnasium i had
my water bottle which was a thermos
style like ah like
yours um smaller mouth of course but
it was a metal bottle reusable bottle
and i guess i had left it
with the lid off overnight and so
i filled up with water at home
and then i go to the gym
and then i'm on the machine and
i take a sip of water oh
and then i feel
something in my mouth no and now
it is a live spider oh
mdf superpowers now and so they sure
don't did you what did you do
scream run around i um i mean
it was so extreme imagery so extreme
and like a true nightmare and you
knew it was a spider there was
something in my mouth and i pulled
it out and it was moving it
was like
still alive yeah
so i oh my god that makes
me never want to leave my water
bottle with the top ah don't ever
yeah don't ever don't ever do that
top on always okay so i've like
flicked it off my hand and then
um i think i took like a
just a brief moment and then i
resumed my workout because i thought i
can't keep the candidate you believe that
thing of like you swallow a spider
every year like whatever oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
on my birthday did you want that
to be debugged i did by the
time your birthday forever swallows my birthday
i swallowed one for every year
really every birthday fifty this year yeah
it's all fifty spiders nice row number
fifty um i don't think about it
mostly and then every once in a
while i think about it and it's
weird yeah but i kind of fit
about every age a little bit like
once you pass thirty like i don't
know i'm thirty three and i think
thirty three when i was a kid
that sounded like an adult
well the fact that fifties very well
fifty is different than thirty three but
i'm just saying i still think you
i think about my age weirdly yes
the fact that you and i are
older than almost every traveling will barry
is bizarre what's a traveling wilburn you
mean how old they were when they
made the traveling overseas but boy do
they look much older they look so
old
old so the traveling bilberries here let
me send you a video i'm i've
heard of that name oh petty petty
orbits okay yeah yeah yeah you're also
more cherished than nature when
when they were in a bus x
okay so when did they do that
um they did it in the late
eighties or early nineties here but how
old are they but are you saying
you're older than they were when they
were when they made those they were
all like old rock people who band
together better random legendary rock people yeah
but they're all a lot
bob dylan it's roy orbison it's tom
petty i don't know this orbison must
be replay the video just been older
than them by know you're here
damn it i just to come through
now you're officially born yeah you're officially
okay i have learned a thing or
i tried to rick roller you see
them recalling that we got on twitter
yes yes very fully i knew something
was up with it but i was
like what's what's this going to someone
shows like rick ross looked like it
was l a times huh yeah i
checked us they checked our ego
yeah it was like l a times
dot com slash three now best moment
yeah thing no but i definitely really
think about us i know it's a
common thing of like wow they looked
so old but i think roy emerson
was fifty two he was the oldest
one or something like that wow but
um and then he was gone like
right after that yeah you know what
i mean so it's like he didn't
even get to volume
three guy um he was ah do
you swallow swallow a spider i think
the pretty woman's husband finally caught up
with
it was my wife and my work
what are you two why did you
kill i saw him right before he
died in liven korea later yes it
disneyland he kept his voice for an
hours time beautiful yet a heart attack
yet a heart attack yeah did you
ever see that black and white special
that he'd yeah loved it it was
great yeah that was so young same
no time around the time that i
saw him
i worked at disneyland and told you
that story and when i first met
you always die to portray shot and
you were talking you told that story
oh really okay i've always wondered the
first time i met you i thought
it was doing bang bang so you
asked me to do it oh did
i okay um but i saw i
was working at disneyland in theory the
only
the fund that grew up the only
fun yeah really
like the only seemingly fun thing you
would think about working at disneyland would
be that you would get to go
to disneyland for free occasionally but they
wouldn't let you you had when you
clocked out of your shift you had
ten minutes to get through the game
my god that's so right viciously you
hang out yeah know what you obviously
wouldn't want to hang out that off
and like you'd you'd want to go
home most yeah you wanna go home
most the time but they were like
if you don't if if if we
don't check you out of the guard
gate ten minutes after you play this
is for real this is crit and
you'll be you'll be warned first and
then fired right you know what's what
other business does this look enough said
yes it was very
one cheerful yeah it's like to say
anything out yeah and like it's kind
not getting paid that much like you
wanna know who's four twenty five it
was four twenty five an hour wow
so ca i but so so i
was there this summer of ninety that
minimum wage yeah okay that's time ah
so i was there the summer of
eighty eight i believe
cvs is the summer that i was
working and um it was the their
flashback summer where they were doing fifties
flashback um so they have this dance
club video palace which was like a
futuristic dance club with video screens that
would show videos and everyone those sorting
features yeah so because studio k over
it it's very far
damn that was their dogs candidate ketamine
but we would dress we would dress
up in trench coats maria okay and
they had fog machines and they would
play the cure sometimes and we would
like all you know how to do
this kind of dancing why would you
wear trench coats because we were gone
you were trying to be the cure
we were fucking gone way oh way
this was this was when you were
an employee of disney when i was
an okay so i was
to disney and eighty eight a welt
build video oculus probably eighty seven studio
k preceded it i was fifteen when
i've always see okay is when you
wear the trench coats this is how
you are performing at video apple no
no no okay apologies so video op
ellis i was to accept my own
i accepted i forgive but i never
forget
yeah yeah so anyway so i was
i ah at video apples this summer
of eighty eight i believe they had
um tons of like fifties whoever was
still alive from the fifties were performing
and they would perform every day right
so so roy orbison is doing three
shows a day at disneyland
right and i'm a huge roi was
amazing yeah and i'm a huge roy
orbison fan and so i'm like i
can't let my tenure disneyland go by
without like going to see roy orbison
but i'm not going to pay to
go see right and go to disneyland
so i broke the rules one day
and i um clocked out of my
shift and i
i ran over to video op list
when i knew his set was starting
i saw probably he probably did a
forty five minutes said i probably saw
thirty five minutes of it before it
was like i gotta get out of
here i'm never going to be able
to explain thirty five minutes or whatever
and then i like ran and got
out of the gate but it was
he was amazing were you right away
with it were you penalized or no
i think i was being like that
i also
so quit that job so soon after
that um that it was the worst
summer of my life just said you
had to go to the bathroom really
bad yeah i was just shitting forever
no one's going to want to argue
with that yeah that's true that's good
that's a good excuse there might be
a weirdo who wants
prove it move it walk me through
this if you if you can't shit
that means you're all out of shit
so try to shit right ah eat
this
it's just mean
oh why
there is a moment in that in
that concert the black white concert with
and if you haven't seen it it's
great bruce springsteen singing backups yeah ah
gabi lang bonnie raitt right diane warren
i think all-star baca lineup it's an
all-star lineup including tom waits for some
lingo she's still around wow she's still
around i think she's just really saleable
not that long she decided to go
upper case with her and that changed
naming yeah yeah no one knows where
to find her anymore so search the
clouds um but they're so looks great
actually she does she looks really great
tom waits for some reason as part
of this lineup and he's
on a little oregon and so it's
i think it's during ruby duby
they're going around will be dubious like
this rave up and one of the
woman roy orbison is like more uptempo
yes people are taking little solos and
stuff and they throw it over to
tom waits and he just like
he might as well have done the
thing where you put your fist through
piano lengthening strengthening but he does this
weird
like stupid thing like or like half-assed
organ solo or whatever was probably can't
play he's not a musician but he
is i mean he is because his
early on no no yes no i'm
agreeing with yeah his early albums his
early albums are very different than the
stuff he does now they're much more
like sort of seventy s two
troubadour kind of stuff than than the
weird character like you don't wait either
i budget and find a song you're
gonna like here let me send you
a video of what oh no but
the bet but the best part is
he does this he does this dumb
solo and then the reactions of the
other musicians like just looking at each
other like wow all right okay huh
important night for us
all but alright i felt like that
at this guy's wedding that i was
at we i was in a band
with my friend and everyone liked our
band but we everyone up in san
louis obispo and the guy who got
married was part of the san luis
obispo music sales naked postman i was
in no this was la vila matos
oh love this money
watch your hits yeah so so me
and my friend were in this band
lobby los molinos but we we neither
of us really played lead guitar he
was better at than i was but
i just played rhythm and but everyone
liked our band and so we went
to this guy's wedding who was in
the the slow music scene and um
the slow music san louis obispo and
so
yeah that was an important claire so
like what's this what's this movement so
we were all up there like like
oh seen babies love you we don't
believe that we're on the will we're
all up there doing the jams i
got invited up to ha researchers per
cancer and they pointed it at me
for a solo oboe and i just
went white
and and they're like yeah man and
looked really supportive i remember like going
okay here we go and i know
a little bit about guitar of how
to do it but i was just
like
no burn burke and the look on
his face of just
oh just has haunted me forever so
maybe you wanna hear a tom waits
and i think you might like yeah
alright she just do it this way
or should i link happy birthday
to you is there at cord alright
here is there an aw is there
an ox card
they're just pointing at ah the biggest
stack of chords i've ever seen my
oh i saw i see i see
it there any serious yeah but it
needs ah i just don't think it
needs a dongle dongle dongle do i
have one in here i have one
anyway here's a dongle oh this the
suspense that was killer just such an
occasion i was killing me alright here
we go
this is a tom waits song that
i will like okay oh shit where
to go
do you want to earn money from
home skip the ad
so far i like this await he
doesn't start saying wait isn't gonna
uh
don't you love that even that is
lock stock is fine yeah love the
trevor he got crazier
these videos you let him come back
sounds kinda nilsson ma wang korea easy
with vi like kids though
that is no this guy
uh
a
this to go in the streets
uh crazy right
yeah i found that too on the
tom waits oregon solo hello
that's the best part oh god
getting your dad
outlaw kid in the way
alright guys i remember these coming on
i love that by the way my
permission friend i was in the bandwidth
would have hated what you just did
which was just automatically like turned it
off cold i hate i hate that
he always had to turn it down
i will say i like i do
just do a fade-out i the br
up i loved it even if we
were at his own house he would
like
slowly turn a song down hey man
i like the abruptness because it's like
life changes just like that hey guess
what it has said now hey right
turns out i found the organ solo
here we go ready
don't go roaming not kill you
alright we need to take a break
come here aipac i'm cheering doesn't count
i'm furious
uh
managing lack of eyebrows ne
moving to the obi duby till you
figure heart will break and it did
because you did you originally
nah
alright cause more solos alright
bass solo because you want to play
bass alright come on come on tom
it's good that medida gotta do rock
and roll all night long tonight
springsteen soloing everyone's loving it to go
out of their minds we can play
with this legend
uh why i think the recorded version
of the song is one minute long
there comes
um that was it that was it
yeah great job
dbp then roy everson and this other
guitar guy look at each other like
ah okay we were forced to use
this guy big milb uzi rupel mean
viola nic bill to be linear of
him while that was happening i was
looking at a yo ram showing me
someone i went to high school with
was that a br
bridal shower where there was a michael
jackson impersonator oh dear what a crazy
combination of thing brides and moonwalks the
idea of inviting something like that into
your home and the close proximity is
very weird yeah and it's a really
strange look the whole deal the whole
deal we talked about this mister show
party
where they had a century verse was
so uncomfortable did he walk around just
talking there are three of them three
of them eating ones was the movie
of the year no no this was
well after well after chad movie had
been funny it was pretty funny concept
but then when you're actually there these
guys are walking around doing oh radiohead
and all that it's
like i wish this wasn't happening was
also in a revolving restaurants so revolving
everyone was getting way too like either
fucked up on alcohol or drug arrived
on drugs yeah and and and then
you're constantly slightly dizzy and ace ventura
is coming up to you and corey
feldman's band is those were two different
parties are you sure
and being in the revolving restaurant both
were in the revolving restaurant i went
to there were two in the revolving
restaurant and the first one had insurer
impersonators in the second one had corey
feldman's band lang truth movement the truth
movement yes i sat near corey feldman
at an event recently and it was
i was very hard to take my
eyes off him really was it an
auction know it
it was a um is that a
good guess it was a bad it
wasn't i guess it was a year
ago but it was um a screening
of jane goodall's documentary oh which i
hear is unusual yeah yeah and they
had philip glass those monkeys shutter graduation
the conduction conduction that's conducted philip glass
was conducted
thought without the word i'm looking for
they were doing the live score yeah
but whatever he was trying to say
i just like construction so long conducting
now i know but i had a
bunch of balloons and i'm going to
say orchestra
okay
those monkeys hated her the documentary sleep
i'm a i'm a jane goodall truther
the news great someone i saw posted
this thing about her ah that she
was it an interview and someone said
what do you what do you think
you'll next grade had been do you
think you'll have another great adventure like
that she's like like
this one at that temp ban band
the bumper
said death would be night her next
great adventure i hate when people say
shit like the hey man take it
or leave it i'll leave it leave
it all right i'll say will not
take it you're gonna take our deaths
i'm gonna take her death as being
her next great adventure okay do you
think that deaths will be an awfully
big adventure
yeah
i do
i feel like it'll be like you
think this episode this podcast will be
your legacy
yeah i do um unfortunately and i'm
really sad this will be your they'll
play this clip this year and more
airy yeah here's i wanna say this
right now if i ever die if
you don't play any clip where i'm
talking about dying or what i think
about it and don't
think about that okay thought what do
you want to ever die imo funny
what we've let's all go around first
what we don't want okay i'm going
to be alright fi ever die yeah
please don't just play a bunch of
clips me laughing yeah it's really good
but it's you having fun they want
to remember what is why what other
people i want clips of other people
having fun because of me yo other
people laughing at you i don't want
it to be like he was known
for enjoying things i would like it
to be that people if you're gonna
play a clip of
something i did it's something that other
people are laughing at yeah make me
toss something off for people losing their
fucking shit
you guys are so presumptuous to think
people are gonna be playing clips when
you die hey guess what what they
will
your face
if i died ah god made sure
i never do and if i do
i want to be ninety nine or
one hundred but only those if i
were to die before you play clip
i would okay what are you saying
you wouldn't play a clip if she
died you wanna play a clip of
paul died if i was still doing
are you fucking kidding me you wouldn't
play clip if i died
where do you think these clips are
being played at your funeral yeah everywhere
everywhere you would do it and i
do it for you i let me
just say only sir what do you
do it on race my tv listen
let's say hey we're doing great
let's say let's say you're right you're
right for the emmys again okay and
it's a year that i die you
better pray this has happened this has
happened to me actually yeah that's unfortunate
so did you get a clip of
harris in the in memoriam i we
all asked them
this is interesting i wanna know who's
in control of the memorial okay well
did my favorite producers say and that's
the best so we we they mentioned
it was done and we said can
we ask you questions like we felt
weird asking about a book is our
friend in there and we said yeah
he said who's your friend and we
said harris he's like oh yes definitely
he's in there
oh that's so here we go he
made the cut yeah because not everyone
who dies gets in the old memoria
i think that's wrong i think that
i think every single person who died
who ever worked whoever hasn't won i
am db credit should be in the
know but i think like there are
prolific people that you that don't make
it sometimes like why wasn't personally what
that's happened i know and i think
that's we
i think that there should be one
i've talked about this there should be
one award show there's too many award
shows just make one award show the
awardees is twenty four hours long give
it a better name no the awardees
or the authorities is twenty four hours
long we do the best music the
best in theater the best in film
the best in tv the best in
in web videos and all that and
then we knew and then we also
do one in memoriam and every single
person is in it and it's it's
probably two hours of the twenty four
so you're saying the webbys are also
folded into the old yes that's instagram
account would also be x but you're
but you're you're kind of making the
shorties right or there's others
i think there are two other weapons
and shortage different things fuck everything the
problem is that there's an in memoriam
for every category and they'd be too
many people i'd be like to it'd
be a two hour long here's the
big problem with the memoriam too is
there's these assholes who like have been
on stage on tv in movies and
also grammys and they suck up all
the ox
origin for all the other people because
they're an f during the grammys it's
during the tonys during the oscars during
the the emmys and they and the
golden gloves they're in all these memorials
and then there's nothing for the rest
of us i think that when people
cheer um for the people they care
about or clap for people to care
about in memoriam it makes you feel
about for the next person
and who pops up when they don't
some editor yeah i don't think that's
right we used to there's a group
of us used to go to movies
a lot and we would pick a
person to clap for during the credits
that's much like person we didn't know
were like let's let's clap for again
on this yeah whatever whatever credit we
picked beforehand
right and then we would do it
and it was very it was it
felt really satisfying for some reason yeah
i do like when you go see
a movie that's one of your friends
is in and everyone goes yeah you
like a person it's cute i remember
oh yeah i love you beth cooper
we went with paul rudd oh yeah
that was fun and he stood up
and did a dance his name a
ruin
alright look we have to do a
feature we don't have to get to
we get your bless this was sent
to us by a man named chef
kevin texted this to me and by
the way it's going to be said
right now if if we do die
and you play a clip it can't
be where we're saying you have to
play a clip oh
thank you thank you for catching that
but someone will catch this and here's
the thing i'm sure because i just
got this for everybody the way the
internet is i'm going to exist by
the time i date somebody like right
two thousand and ninety nine because i
have a show i have two or
more the year two thousand yeah anytime
anyone who is on my show passes
away i have to talk about it
on the show
oh my god sorry alright let's do
this feature you do have to talk
about on your show when people die
i know yeah bad is the head
that wears the crown i know sure
ah i know this is called remember
what to pack
oh my god remember what to pack
this is an alphabet sequence driven game
of memory and it's suitable for just
two players but more fun of several
are involved let's do the three of
us what do you say yeah let's
say it's also known by the name
going on a trip okay i know
this game okay begin by stating a
travel day
destination france for instance you know yes
play begins with the first person stating
for example i'm going on a trip
to france and i'm going to take
an apple i'm gonna use that the
next player makes wavering and why are
we getting to apple to france the
next person can't do that then i
throw it out yeah it's called the
city of apples reason the next player
must repay
eat the sequence and add an item
from the next letter in the alphabet
i'm going to trip to france i'm
going to take an apple and a
briefcase
the third player proceeds in turn i'm
going on a trip to france i'm
going to take an apple a briefcase
and a camera all right let's do
it okay anymore exam until so and
you can you can pick anywhere i'm
presuming and you can pick you can
start with any letter o saying you
did so i think the location has
no bearing on it was okay says
no bearing
i believe you can start in the
middle there's no newscaster yeah yeah trustee
the next yeah exactly so lauren you
start us off i'm going on a
trip to milwaukee
and i'm going to bring
a suitcase
i'm going on a trip to milwaukee
and i'm going to bring suitcase and
a tardigrade
i'm going on a trip to milwaukee
and i'm going to bring a suitcase
a tardigrade and my uvula i'm going
on a trip to milwaukee i'm gonna
bring a suitcase a tardigrade and my
uvula and a violin i'm going to
georgia lagi i'm bringing ah suitcase ah
tara gray
ah my uv of course ah a
violin and a watch imo call it
bar is my favorite candy
i'm going on a trip to milwaukee
guys whoa congrats thank you and i'm
gonna bring a suitcase a tardigrade my
uvula a violin a watch macaulay bar
my favorite candy and a xylophone i'm
going on a trip to milwaukee and
i'm going to bring a suitcase a
tartar grade a uvula a vibe
allin
a xylophone and i said xylophone but
you forgot watching the volleyball favorite candy
or his favorite candy i don't know
the elphaba huh
oh wait so what am i oh
you're out yeah but my sucks yeah
just raise ya through this sucks oh
i was in fifth
alright should i use i was telling
you and me did i tell you
i'm going on a trip to milwaukee
know yeah let me what you bringing
them right yeah give me the list
i know you're bringing nerd yeah you're
right turns out for that bringing a
suitcase or we you can start over
i thought oh i think oh i
think
can you start over no oh no
really we just go back into milwaukee
okay go ahead i think so okay
because that's where we were so rudely
interrupted yeah but you got well i'm
bringing my suitcase obviously yeah and then
in the suitcase i'm gonna pack separately
no no
actually i tell a lie i will
bring an empty suitcase to buy stuff
milwaukee souvenirs and of course to bring
echo
so suitcase to grade of course um
my uvula which are going to remove
from my throat and put in this
basement
ah um ah violin which are gonna
learn to play the plane right um
watch em call a bar my favorite
candy of course ah xylophone of course
because i wanna do all my bad
thing
um my young jeezy record
and i think that's all i got
so far yeah well you know that's
interesting because i'm going on a trip
to milwaukee what and i'm similarly bringing
a suitcase and a tardigrade my uvula
a violin watch mccullough bar your favorite
candy okay ah xylophone ah young jeezy
record but i'm also bringing a zither
because i thought maybe a two man
band kind of ooh
you're making me realize that if i'm
going to milwaukee and i'm bringing my
suitcase charter grade um uvula island
asylum
guess what you forgot what watch macaulay
guide
ah tardigrade what is a tardigrade it's
one of those weird it's that weird
little organism it's actually it's very cute
oh i'm looking at it is a
really funny looking yeah now put that
in between some sandwiches but it's like
that dude can live anywhere really yes
i think and leave in space i
don't like it
but it doesn't have to be their
kid a guy like yeah let's do
well let's do one more because i
feel like alright you start i'll start
the winner
whenever begins when i'm i guess i'm
in the big game the summer
so he hates it all of a
sudden
i'm going on a trip to new
zealand guys news en zed yeah wow
what are you bringing i'm bringing my
bible oh oh it's crazy because i'm
going on a trip to new zealand
and i'm bringing my bible and my
cat oh
this is gonna be tough for me
i'm going to zealand reading my bible
my dad and my dog oh no
oh well i'm going on a trip
to new zealand i'm bringing my bible
my cat my dog and my egg
poacher see i'm going on a trip
to new zealand and bring my bible
my cat my dog my egg poacher
and my frankfurter
i'm going to assume you're franklin vertigo
yeah i'm bringing my bible mcap my
dog mike poacher my frankfurter and my
grit america's family newspaper
well i'm going on a trip to
new zealand i'm bringing my bible my
cat my dog my egg poacher my
frankfurter my grid and i'm also bringing
my e haberdashery okay well i'm going
into a museum that i'm bringing my
bible my cat my dog my egg
poacher my frank and further my grit
my habitat
machinery and my intelligence oh
going to zoom and i'm bringing my
bible my rank pilcher referring her
my grandmother's family newspaper my haberdashery my
intelligence and
my jewish new year
i'm going to trip to new zealand
reading my bible my cat my dog
my poacher my frank converter my grit
america's family newspaper my haberdashery my intelligence
my jewish new year and my ku
klux klan outfit
okay that's so weird because i'm going
on a trip to new zealand i'm
bringing my bible my cat my dog
my egg poacher my frank and further
my grit america's favorite newspaper they have
a dashi my intelligence my jewish new
year my klu klux klan outfit and
um my lasso
going interested in bringing my bottle cat
dog thank butcher my frankfurter my grandmother's
robin the haberdashery my intelligence my new
year my ku klux klan outfit
my lasso and
it ah ah
my
manifest
i'm going on a trip to new
zealand and bringing my bible my cat
my dog my egg poacher my frankfurter
my great american family newspaper my haberdashery
my intelligence my jewish new year my
klux klux klan outfit my lasso my
manifest and my nose i'm going on
a trip to new zealand i'm bringing
my bible my cat my dog my
egg poacher my fr
bank and murder my grit america's favorite
newspaper my haberdashery my intelligence my jewish
new year my ku klux klan outfit
my last so my manifest and my
nose and my um octopus tail
i'm going on a trip to new
zealand bringing my bible my cat my
dog i'm bringing ma hey e e
yeah sorry i got a bus you
see
hey guys you know i tell you
was gonna help you i thought it
was going to quickly became my foe
yeah okay go i'm going on trip
to new zealand kinda snaps to life
because i remembered what it was i
brought my bible my cat my dog
my egg poacher my frankfurter my great
american family newspaper my haberdashery
my intelligence my jewish new year my
klu klux klan outfits my last sue
my manifest my nose my octopus tail
and my pussy a way i took
new zealand i'm bringing my bible my
cat my dog my egg poacher my
frank and further my grit america's families
america's favorite newspaper my haberdashery my intelligence
my jewish new year my ku klux
klan outfit my lasso my manifest my
nose my octopus tail my pussy and
my quilt i'm going a trip to
new zealand i'm bringing my bible my
cat my dog my egg poacher my
frankfurter my great american family
newspaper my haberdashery my intelligence my jewish
new year my klux klan outfit my
lasso manifest my nose my octopus tail
my pussy my quilt
and my rhubarb did you say quilt
yes oh boy a trip to new
zealand i am bringing
my bible my cat my dog my
egg poacher my frankfurter migrate america's favorite
newspaper my haberdashery my intelligence my jewish
new year my cookbooks klan outfit my
lasso my manifest my nose my octopus
tail my pussy my quilt my rhubarb
and my ce
snakes oil snake-oil i'm gonna trip to
new zealand i'm bringing my bike and
my cat my dog my aig poster
my frankfurter my great american family newspaper
my haberdashery my intelligence my jewish new
year my klux klan outfit my lasso
manifest my nose my octopus tail my
pussy my quilt my rhubarb my snake
oil and my tarantula
going on trips new zealand i'm bringing
my bible my cat my dog my
egg poacher my frankfurter my grandma cause
severe newspaper family newspaper my intelligence
i'm asked that you mesaba you forgot
haberdashery i went again
a i swear this must be like
a mentalist game or something this is
how like in and of itself like
what was based on the mentalist i
think this is how he remembers everyone's
job
you saw it right yeah yeah derrick
jones when you are you picturing all
this stuff no i read about how
you can do stuff like this but
you you already like an
every single seat in the audience to
a thing like like if you look
at each seed like this pig this
is donkey this you know what i
mean and then when you see everyone's
job you imagine a pig doing that
job a donkey doing that you like
if you memorize the first sequence then
you can memorize the other sequence and
it's a mental picture that comes up
in your ma
mind like the judge is a rooster
you know i me anyway okay guys
we gotta go i should not have
gotten high yeah it was honor that
was fun the judges rooster rooster next
time g
good to look guilty this sucks alright
well see ya hey
uh