three
hello everyone welcome to the shiny bang
bang sounds the same we need a
different intro yeah i'm sure
you started because you don't stay guys
go hey guys it's me lauren lab
guys and welcome back to another up
as well come back
hey y'all do hey guys it's me
paul f tompkins i hope everyone's feeling
great today i know we are we're
in the studio together ready to begin
a great show that we all like
to do because we like each other
and we like you fine
it has to be that intro every
single time oh god you'll never remember
that
hey everyone welcome to the show ah
yeah
it's hard without a title it is
hard without it is well welcome we're
glad you're here yes here's this show
is i'm i'm paul f tompkins hello
i'm scott ahriman you may know me
from coming back you know let me
start again oh i'm paul f tompkins
perhaps you remember me from there will
be blood
also i can kelly story i mean
megan too
ah he turned off
his head just tilted down myself pointed
at the ground either vacant
people will know you from bojack horseman
hey fellow jack horseman season
from april
you play mister peanut butter one word
that's correct is mister and peanut butter
one word no no mister and peanut
butter are two words peanut butter is
all one word so two words not
three that's correct that's correct and who
is this young lady
well ooh la la
a arby i'm laura lab the giant
rabbit
okay
um
i love kiss and you know me
from
ah orange is the new black and
you know me from comedy bang bang
and i don't know what else you
know me from i guess jurassic world
sure yeah jurassic world you play the
witch dinosaur do you play to which
dinosaur yeah that's not exactly exactly yeah
yeah why is that dinosaur room
they all had themes i don't know
if you noticed what was the christmas
boy in the halloween what if you're
watching jurassic world and then just suddenly
in the corner of the screen a
dinosaur when flying by auto brew so
happy
hey i would probably go yeah it
kind of makes sense and then one
character says did you guys see that
no one acknowledged everyone's like it's weird
enough we got dinosaurs back here who
cares if you're out who gives a
shit
welcome to the show everyone that it's
hard to do this without a title
we don't know what the title of
the show is oh let's explain first
of all why we want to do
at a show but then we'll talk
about the title and what we're gonna
do about that we should explain ourselves
yeah explain yourself well i will here's
the thing
scott lauren myself i'm not gonna lie
we have a good time together we
do we work together we've got to
admit it that's right it's a como
joan i hate you guys see that's
what he's like and that's why it's
fun but we i think probably this
this really stir
dated when we were on the tour
too is that two years ago oh
the year after year and half ago
yeah and obviously there's a lot of
time ah a lot of downtown downtime
where we're hanging like you're only on
stage for one two hours at night
two and a half hours that one
time yeah new york that was a
mistake oh but um we really had
a
good time together and and for for
an experience like that where it's it's
it can it verged on grueling that
tour where we were traveling a lot
it would be very easy to despise
the people that you're spending every day
with yeah i can see why some
people in band's breakup immediately never speak
to each other anymore i've never
thought of it like that but yeah
makes sense but we all really got
along really really missed each other after
the tour it's true that's right and
we missed hanging out with each other
and sometimes we go ah to places
together and we go we win vacation
together the summer why yeah that's true
and we said why not actually do
a show this actually also started when
when we were doing the tour recaps
episode yeah comedy bang bang yeah scott
you've had it to where the
yeah we did them all together and
we said you know what each of
our shows each of our shows varying
just a mess using our shows is
very difficult to do yes yes ah
both in booking and ah having to
do comedy the entire time yeah
yes yeah you have to like be
funny the whole time yeah and you
have to book one at least for
you at least one person for our
shows sometimes three sometimes four and even
not just the booking i have to
hope that they could can handle it
they have to improvise for an hour
and then people get very nervous that's
why you wear a t-shirt to every
recording says can
you handle it yeah and then if
they can't they walk right out and
what did they think your teachers saying
can you handle this like your actual
body honestly most episodes of my podcast
or them trying to figure out what
my t-shirts about and yeah it works
every time you believe i love your
show love it but we said why
not do a show where we just
kinda talk to each other we have
so much fun doing us all
so with comedy bang bang where laura
and i are doing characters you're kind
of doing carolina doing charger and i'm
having to do this kind of artificial
you know sarcastic you know ironic thing
so when i play like this dumb
guy ah hey polls don't do like
i can dupe an idiot that doesn't
get things
um and that's part of our relationship
on comedy bang bang which will not
be part of our relationship i just
shot because i actually like right you
don't actually like each other do you
remember the tv show carolyn maryland real
friends knows it carolyn marilyn no oh
it should have been and i think
they'd still be on the air today
if it was carolyn like sixty minutes
one person
than what we call our show real
friends
no marilyn marilyn and carolyn marilyn said
no what do we call it paul
scott and lauren no real friends yeah
we we were gonna vote a ten
we're gonna talk about the title your
title scott paul and lauren real friends
mm i like it a little yeah
there was a show there there was
these these tour and harold
in maryland they were carol and marilyn
and they were called the mommies and
i think they had a stage show
or thing yeah i sort of remember
them and then they they the stage
show i guess was yes and then
they were given a daytime talk show
yes where the gimmick was they were
actually friends i want to look this
up because everyone everyone in show business
is not friends anytime you're wa
watching a tv show a sitcom and
they're they're like hugging and going you
know what i learned they hate each
other they all ha cannot sleep think
we're the only three that likely actually
like each other out of any show
curious obey that your best friends with
everyone that you worked i think we
were like a family yeah every
once in a while it's true but
so rare that reminds me could you
bring back clip you know what every
day someone from brazil wants me to
bring bring back claps well you can
do that right now it's up to
me and i'm the person standing in
the way i want it back bad
you know but there's only so much
i wanted daddy i wasn't
i think he's a dodgy ah but
no our creators are very busy with
will and grace re boot
i did a and there's no one
right but
i did an episode of ah um
oh my god what's the show all
my children
yeah but i wish i wish all
my wish you one episode of all
my children i'm tears
family my mom taped ah all my
children on a v h s tape
every single day and then recorded over
it every single day and i have
wishy washy how much yes you can
after work every day she wouldn't just
tape over one she hadn't seen this
sale one yeah well he thought that
meant that there would be a whole
tape full of episodes um just rip
eat it over each other but no
i watched so much all my children
growing up did you actually watch that
show i've never watched that i watched
general hospital oh okay in the days
of ah luke and laura and the
ice princess and all this yes it
was like they tried to make it
the soap opera became sort of like
an anti bias kind of way yeah
looks like grasser like a james bond
yeah you don't know well yeah they
did eventually do other worldly stuff
like there was there were alien alien
thing yeah yeah do you think a
soap opera could ever be as important
as they were at that time because
no one cares now because there's so
many shows i i well i think
that the fact that they're all kind
of dying out is are they yeah
bunch of them have have gone off
the air i liked it i liked
it they still exist though yeah and
i hope they always do i think
that they will
i'll be more important
i think they'll be our most important
form of expression i think shows will
eventually be as biggest seinfeld again some
shows yes oh wait aqua teen hunger
force that's what i did an episode
okay and it was no soapy i
have no idea right after the boston
bombing and so there was i was
not good but it was that good
and they promote
noted the episode or it was like
coming back that new season they promoted
it by putting these sort of space
invader characters oh yeah just planting them
around all over yeah lumber city yeah
but they were bombs i remember that
everyone's so dumb so there's oh this
episode was making fun of people being
upset about that and so it never
aired
years later i had somebody on twitter
a guy on twitter was like when
will you release that episode and i
said i'll never really yeah i guess
so then other people started writing me
like why won't people want to see
it i'm like too bad i don't
know why i was put in charge
of this but i'll never let it
be seen
i love the way you interact with
your fans put them in quotes because
they're so often idiots who don't understand
what you're talking your fans are idiots
like why would they like your comedy
i think they're dumb oh i don't
think there's i think that there's people
that are fans and then there's people
that are like i was told this
account was funny or they saw
retweet and then they're like yeah huh
context thing i'm getting like i hate
watching people i hey i hate somebody
on twitter for the you're gonna find
that lauren hates a law as we
did onto her
take away yeah sheboygan shit that's more
low we all heard it says more
you're looking at it upside down yeah
i look at it dummy
but you think you're wearing a t-shirt
like more love come on give it
to me
give it to me
if you want to give it to
me
ah should we talk about the title
yeah i'm gonna do that now i
want to call from we look
i hate to bring the off mic
onto the on mike okay please do
though that's that's what this show is
the off mike onto the on my
luis
if it's anything that's the case the
off mike see out of the box
slide into my own oh like um
we had talked over when we were
on vacation i think which was the
july fourth holiday yes and it's fireworks
up very high around the same time
don't i say please that's right yeah
i remember everyone's birthday september nineteenth know
why
remember
it's not nine to it's weight you
know it's october it's tamar it's september
hold on hold on hold on no
it's september it's number twelve because it's
my friend mackenzie strimmer tofu that's what
and that's why i was september twelve
two thousand and eleven or two thousand
and three it was something else did
you hit that year i planned a
big birthday pa
arty right like it was i was
still at that age where it's like
i want everybody to come oh mah
yeah yeah and you're like i'm gonna
have a pie plate up okay okay
are you talking about wow
i felt that volume parts i right
on with it but everybody up
you were looking at me you were
looking at me with supreme confidence it
was like rotation like
i want you know that rotation no
look up the word rotation you'll know
what i'm talking about pterosaurs know what
i'm talking about gives me a look
it up and then a dismissive wave
okay
um do you remember and this i
don't know whether and forgive me if
i'm being sexist right off the bat
but it seemed it seemed to be
a thing that primarily women i knew
used to do but when they were
nine eleven yeah so when they were
female from like when they were graduating
college to like twenty seven or something
in their idea of a good birthday
was having dinner at a restaurant with
all their friends like they would get
all of their friends that is ah
that does feel like a female i
don't know why i feel it's maybe
just because i went to so many
with co-op i don't know i've done
a couple of those but i feel
like when i went around the time
when i was doing that everyone that
we knew was kind of doing it
that was a very common thing maybe
well going to dinner is silly yeah
so yeah i think that's italian yeah
we always did our birthdays right right
we always did barbara it's
but that one after that like it
was the day after nine eleven conway
yeah everyone came because everyone was like
yes i was like hey let's say
this isn't about my birthday anymore let's
all just see each other it was
weird it was still very weird and
did you get any gifts
i've always been replicas of the twins
guys get these for cheap weird to
say you had a cake with a
plane crashing into it come on it's
gonna get out when i was born
and you pick i wish i just
stuttered nighttime kiss know what this show
is about it's not we don't know
yet we don't know my thing about
me every episode it's all nine eleven
jokes um
so for the title you were saying
we had ah we were headed for
the show forth on july fourth we
had a discussion where like what should
be in the show and we kind
of bitch some ideas and now about
this this is simple because the whole
idea was to keep this as simple
as possible and we're like great kids
and we give it simple shithead
will be the new kids yep which
one do you want to be the
cat and one of us watch where
double makeup i'm the starting goalie three
i'm the star man and the ah
that would look insane both of those
things on top of each other they
would ruin it i think probably it
would ruin two great things i love
cancers so cool and thirty here the
gene simmons is so great he's so
cool i love that he does make
up
do you think someone does it for
him after these many years or z
like only i know how to do
the demon the idea of putting that
on over and over again is one
of the most depressing thoughts i did
you ever do theater where you you
have to do your own makeup and
yeah yeah looks like half hour at
least and if you're doing something even
more complicated you have to i did
kiss makeup for like one show
oh that i did for about five
weeks in a row my guy was
zhao yeah it's a lot yes it's
a lot so can you imagine being
him no that's whole life i remember
thinking i forget who i was talking
about with this of like getting ah
if you were in kiss and you
get a groupie back to your groove
back to your hotel room and then
you're like okay i just need some
time to
take off and you could like call
you over the bed like you're still
ending that's right i'm almost sorry you
just like go down on a girl
in there puts his all black and
white afterward
hey i didn't read huh
i did dress up yeah what's black
and white and red all over i
did reserve is ace freely for halloween
once and yeah
it's good i'm gonna i'm gonna it's
it's good i'm gonna go ahead
address his ace freely for halloween and
then started making out with a girl
at a party afterwards shabby she had
the reversed implementation of it honor famous
you're just mashing your head yeah well
she was a zombie halloween party and
i was i was like a dead
prom queen and i made out with
a guy who was a clown and
it was disgusting and then like later
when i thought about i was like
how gross must that have looked it's
just i don't even know how we
started kissing when you think about it
like sex in general is so gross
that people must really want to have
in order to to overcome there's a
large i'm just how awful is the
worst and the best right so weird
that
people do that
so for the title though we wanted
keep it simple shithead we wanted to
keep it's kish cave comparable shit comma
s yes hey i asked comma s
whenever their name was kiss they had
a little pause between the yes and
yes is that what is is their
kiss supposed to stand for something well
they said knights in satan's service was
supposedly what it was but the band
never said that because but they were
at the time there were parents that
thought they were satanic yeah it's almost
like it's
like a scooby doo cartoon they were
there there are people who think harry
potter is satanic that's me i always
forgive his i always forget that it's
like twitch plays witchcraft yes certainly you
must be a total slithering actually i
am yeah i know
never heard anybody say yeah i did
i don't care about harry potter much
at all but i did the harry
potter quiz on pottermore dot com which
is the official fucking we don't care
about harry potter right oh wow
i don't either but i didn't do
it which people talking and i was
like yeah me when i go to
potter just erin whitehead no actually i
should we've gone over me and aaron
just have talked about harry potter all
the time and how much she loves
and how much i don't care but
i was listening to a podcast and
the person was talking about how they
had done this online i was like
let me just see what i get
and i have leather and i was
really happy
e i really i wanna incite yeah
what are you i think i was
just off no no
i looked down but i know enough
to be insulted like you know enough
that it's insulting and i know enough
to be insulted oh we have no
basis yeah there's like a v randy
guy grip i think i was gryffindor
griffin would just like that's the vanilla
yogurt or regular you got into the
school yeah puff slither and what's the
other one ah
viceroy
vice magazine gryffindor hufflepuff i should vertigo
with that be vertigo ha hello what
is it raven raven law did you
know that you don't do you know
you'll pronounce the t hear your throat
before you i've taught been talking about
this it's true like i just told
paula lauren has inflicts
can you know about it but um
voldemort doesn't you don't pronounce the t
apparently yeah what do you mean i've
seen the movies yeah he's been talk
about them all the time
tell yourself that i read the first
four books and then i didn't read
anymore and then i saw the movies
and i didn't really pay attention to
entertain anything i didn't notice that they
said it differently and i saw on
twitter that it was different i saw
the first movie in the first book
and i read the first book and
then i was out and then the
movies as they went on started to
look better to me they started look
more intriguing but i
just couldn't make myself do it i
liked the third movie that ah harry
potter in the end harry potter and
the end he just likes waiting for
the end everybody by chops and he
seals off i don't ruin i'm off
to see the snow
wizard i don't know
i kind of go well let's talk
about this title alright okay what do
you want it to be
you're in the middle of saying something
i thought then we didn't talk about
it again until yesterday okay initially we
thought it would be called threesome yes
and then we pretend like type random
but three people and then we talked
about all the different ways it could
be spelled because we were talking about
the the number three and then dmb
and then we talked about t h
r e d oh yeah right right
and then that was pretty much it
and everyone we've than we were at
comic-con and we said hey we have
oh we also had another title which
was ah lakins man lakins man that
one's rough for me or tom what
was the other tom tom ken tommy
tom tom focus tom kiss me or
some already not good well we
we at comic-con we were doing a
panel when we said hey we're doing
a show and then we said it's
either going to be this title or
this time when we said both and
no one liked either everyone was like
we don't care we're pretty quiet throughout
that whole thing we thought this is
gonna win we drop this revelation on
their heads and they were like people
were excited about the show they were
like that
yeah no one likes either title so
then that's that's maybe been something that's
been standing in the way of us
even recording for while because we don't
have a real title yeah and it
seemed like people weren't into it
it was just the title so what
we decided to do i'm eating on
the podcast discussion wouldn't know that's what
this is the kind of show is
what we decided to do is we
decided to record the first episode and
we have our trusty assistant korean over
here and she is writing down things
that we say although she's not writing
a lot i have to say she's
is writing more than i thought there's
a lot of legend way more than
i expected she's got a david e
kelley legal pad in front of her
from dallas early a lot of people
don't know he used to write his
shows on illegal but he still doesn't
seem comfortable right writing on legal pads
because he's a lawyer what's more comfortable
than writing longhand entire scott
a tweet from i guess the writer
of bill and ted's excellent adventure and
it's was written like he found the
first pages of description was all written
on paper like that and i was
like do people do that like he
wrote it on paper i'm not trying
to be funny well anyways it accomplished
well lauren that's one thing if you're
listening to the show for the first
time maybe you're ah fan of one
of us but don't know the overall
which seems insane where's he going with
lauren is a little bit younger than
us what year were you born into
you mind saying or yeah i i
don't mind um i don't lie about
my age because i think that's lame
so did i until i crossed a
certain barrier oh honey it gets worse
ah
i always born in nineteen eighty five
zero born in eighty five so you're
a little bit younger than say to
me you're a little bit younger than
paul and i know so yeah let's
just say i'm shocked someone ever used
paper i know but i must say
as someone who wrote in the years
before computers in fact
my very first script i wrote on
a a type of computer where it
would only save twenty five pages you
could only let you print it and
then you had to print it and
copy it and then deleted all and
then write another daddy's name knots yeah
so i was writing at the time
when computers weren't around wow you know
everything was like typewriters before that
then i went so it was that
just really annoying to write on a
typewriter so it would just be lazy
burn yeah row plays on typewriter and
you're constantly making mistakes and having a
wide ow oh yeah like i remember
doing it for papers in school i
remember writing sketches in longhand i wrote
plays in longhand completely and then i
would type them later that's cool yeah
it's very good was really cool oh
my god
odd when people saw you doing it
looking at you go to dan and
gord you alright girdwood
do you think frank underwood was named
after the typewriter absolutely yeah ray i
feel like part of the story of
house of cards is that he used
to be a typewriter and then make
an anthropomorphic type right like the little
toaster i was thinking beauty and the
beast and the brave little toaster you
could turn into a real person no
but i wish he did yeah
what if he did i'd like to
shake his head for his bravery i
think there's maybe a few years ago
it was the slowest thing to movie
scene why
you're playing okay
that's a reference that only we know
oh great i'm glad i was cut
out of that you know you know
it you know i said thanks please
explain going down yeah i saw it
no i know it now i know
it now i know it not the
way until toaster is a movie yeah
it
one of my favorites when i was
little but it's usage as it was
boring i just rewatched it oh so
slow it helped me move anything that
i've rewatched from like my childhood is
basically so slow that i can't believe
and everything you used to like his
garbage yeah even up to like a
week ago okay hold on
no i love oh i love like
all my old stuff but when i
rewatched like some of those shows it's
like no sitcom could go as slow
as like elf went yeah just like
now glacier yeah it's crazy we don't
think about it so like everything is
so quick now supposedly you like when
you watch old stuff but it's even
it's gonna get even worse toward like
how fast
our sitcoms gonna be in the future
here's what's weird though i'm i'm rewatching
episodes of star trek the next generation
because i did a podcast where the
you know it's about rewatching that show
and i hadn't seen any in years
and so i watched an episode from
the first season and it was too
bad it was it was it was
a particularly bad episode of the show
yeah but then i was like i
really liked the show
oh so i started just kind of
skipping around episodes that i remembered and
and watching them again and it it
holds up pretty well but there are
certain episodes where they have these gigantic
ideas and they're trying to get to
them so quickly and it's like you
needed more time to talk about this
there there's one where ah scotty from
the original show
yo james do james doohan me up
of beam me up fame look at
my shirts up me beam
he he goes through some wormhole or
something being pretty good by the way
i noticed oh no me beam is
not bad we're gonna have to discuss
too by the way we're gonna powers
the three of us are going to
hear these suggestions later on in the
show and we're gonna talk about what
our favorites i guess then perhaps title
the show that's yes so he ends
up on
the the present day enterprise is like
hundreds of years in the future now
and they're like wow this is amazing
i look at this dude yeah remember
from beat me up fame first they're
up maybe they'll they'll pitch their teachers
oh is it off day for us
we're allowed to wear this so they
spend like the barest amount of time
being amazed that this person from not
just their history but like and noted
hit what would today be a notable
historical figure that would be like well
like if general lee came
not maybe not for everybody
so they they spend like a minute
on that like ah this is amazing
to see you and then ah bo
go better get your book you better
go better go better go better yeah
oh well it's know any better you
get you know emmys you better go
get your arm taken care of you
you broke your arm in the race
or anything fuckin wormhole wow when you
go you were on every single time
that seems impossible doesn't just suck you
in generally
julie tenderly gent generally generally take you
into your cemented real woman's thing to
get sucked through a wormhole and breaker
so he gets he goes sick bay
and they then he starts talking about
on my enterprise while this shit is
always good i went to he went
to sick bay sickbay oh god he
goes skip and i thought that was
like a
puristic style director and bay the sickbay
isn't well that any any ship has
sickbay what do you mean it's it's
like the doctor's office
it's like the principal's office but for
doctors any ship has sickbay that was
like a fake sentence it is true
that any ship has sickbay doesn't have
nothing any millage not a bad title
sick bay so anyway
they the rest of the episode is
him feeling like he's an old useless
man because he can't help on the
new enterprise and everyone is rude to
him people like ah yeah could you
do you mind we're trying to do
something here it's nice to meet you
please get the fuck out of his
sciences old yeah yeah yeah ok he
wants to tell stories
is everything so then the the birthday
and are they in the middle of
it like an emergency situation yes then
he shouldn't be telling stories no he
shouldn't be that's the thing is that
the plot of this episode becomes how
sad it is that we don't value
our old people and how old people
feel you know out of the way
but it's like maybe you shouldn't just
had a generic old person on the
show and not like a
a famous person from a couple of
centuries in the past that's all like
that studio sixty episode where the old
writers come back to the studio it's
actually because it turns out they're a
great race the new people that suck
right yeah right yeah um look to
tell you oh why don't we take
a break because we want us to
be short we want this to be
real
relatively short show we don't want to
do these longings we want to derail
one story per segment wait a matter
you were used to i was dumb
oh my god did you do you
feel like you needed more time to
tell that story was like the writers
know i didn't need more time i
was given too much time as a
result of all the detours yeah it
was a very it was not even
a story i'm shocked
i'm shot here's my panic about this
before we go to break yeah my
panic about moments like that is oh
no this has no payoff this is
just an observation i know okay wait
this has no pay off and now
i feel like will grow pretty good
title i have a question that's happened
yes when you said i'm shocked were
you quoting some
thing i was quoting you you said
it like a second earlier i don't
even remember him saying it i just
remember you say well because it sounded
like a story from my past and
telling you're quoting my past and i
really wait where you know the story
oh wait wait i mean is is
it related to a story that you
can tell internet yeah okay tell you
what we're gonna take a break
we come back we're going to hear
this story about lauren being shocked about
something or someone saying i'm shocked okay
there's someone's shocked okay but this is
very exciting just a shocking yes i
did we're gonna be right back we're
gonna come back with more upbeat beam
right after this more this has no
pay off we'll be right back after
this was no payoff is good
alright everyone welcome back this is scott
i'm paul and i'm lauren and lauren
before the break teased an incredible story
okay triggered my be in person by
me impersonating her triggered by ibm persian
triggered by vfw
hello everyone this episode has been triggered
by b m w zo i when
i was little when i was like
fifth grade we would roller blade my
friends and i or my brother and
i would roller blade to this candy
shit while it was never your brother
and your friends um no always separate
but i probably mostly went there with
my friend and we both would
roller blade there and it was this
deli that was really a sandwich shop
but it was the height oh no
that's right but yeah so it was
a deli but secretly a sandwich where
it's going is the part that doesn't
line up with it is that they
had so are most delhi's they don't
sell sandwiches new yorker they say a
deli and they kind of mean like
a bodega right right okay in evanston
illinois
it was literally a deli and it
was a sandwich shop and there was
a glass case with candy munchkin debt
until we would go with our our
change that we had saved to get
candy i'd ever had a sandwich there
and i would go and then the
guy who works there um for anyone
who's from evanston it's called als del
shout-out
davin and al's deli alice the dad
and then his son whose name i
never got but i did interact with
many times my childhood hell junior ah
worked there and he was this kind
of buttoned-up sort of guy with like
you sort of like he had on
a apron over his button-down you mind
a glass tie if i'm correct maybe
some glasses i might be making them
into more of a
ah coin dexter sure cara thought he
would have to go pick out all
our candies and we'd have like it'd
be it's probably annoying for him because
we'd stand there and be like i
want one six slits and i want
you know one you'd mix it up
and he would charge by the pound
but you would say no they were
just little individually priced packets like just
like god bulk candy
and then i ain't to me to
get shock tarts he would say i'm
shocked but he had no expression and
he never had any fun as far
as i could tell but that was
his joke and so we always would
quote him and then when you said
that i thought wait was he quoting
something and that was funny to him
but then no you were just quoting
me
i was just quoting here and i'd
probably said like him because yeah you
said oh so is this the only
time that al junior did a bit
was if you are the shock i'd
see only thing that he ever said
every time i'm shocked i remember the
first time that i ever ah figured
out that delhi's would make you
sandwiches and they were good sandwiches to
figured it out like i mean yes
i was seven i think i'm seventeen
years old and you know oh just
like any regular deli yeah yeah well
you know i i grown up and
my my mom had made my lunch
and made sandwiches and they are always
the same the way she made them
in my mom you know we make
saw other people eating sandwiches you're like
my mom made that
yeah i figured you know but i
never needed at home yeah i think
you had to go to a restaurant
or something to buy a sandwich done
some other way other than making it
at home and so i remember my
my friend we went into this deli
over next to the tasty freeze and
he was like oh yeah you can
buy a sandwich and it's like two
dollars four foot long sandwich with like
just incredible
a deli meats i don't ever i've
still never done that oh i've only
ever sucked on chili dogs
well it's from czech it's good on
gelato
guys debris oh yeah sorry mallika
suck it on chili chili no because
that's how he gets all shook it
off oh shit oh hey voltage i
welcome backstage you want to be second-home
i'm chilly oh i'll just tuck on
he just takes polaroids the girls sucking
cheetos
really stuck on it make a song
yeah welcome back to the episode um
paul is getting to give me some
water we don't well we don't know
what the title is destroying could be
up me beam that's very that's hard
to say that's yeah maybe oh maybe
i know pay off no payoff just
has no payoff
we've got to see what till yeah
yeah see guys i feel like i
got some good ones you have some
good ones i feel like but what
if korean didn't write him down did
you write them down i wrote down
oh and physically i wrote them tell
you it where on your phone my
telephone that's great this is gripping
so no this is gripping i'm holding
a bottle shocking um so one thing
that we were gonna do is we're
just going to talk about things that
happen to us of course and things
from our past and things from our
present maybe things from our future like
what are my dreams i've feel like
i'm gonna be in a grave my
name will be on it are you
going to be creative
or yeah that's a good question i
don't know i think about it a
lot i want to be cremated i
want to say i'm the oldest okay
i just want to say i think
about it too but i've said it
i've said it for twenty years i
want to be cremated i think graveyards
are weird i actually want to be
in a casket so that everyone could
come in look at me
like you're sure
more love but i think as i've
gotten older i'm more comfortable the idea
of cremation because it's ah kind of
pointless to keep making things i just
go underground yeah yeah i used to
think i wanted to be buried and
then after my parents died and i
never went to visit either of their
graves and i realised like
the grave like as they were being
buried like i'm never coming back here
really well yeah because i didn't feel
where where are they in third oh
yeah i didn't feel a sense of
connection to that spot you like i
know that they were gone and you
still have like a plaque or something
yeah if you work remains cremated or
a bench here's it's weird my dad
was cremated and he was buried next
to my mother wow
his ashes were put in in an
urn and then a box and then
buried wait a box like a coffin
sized box or just a no no
just a box okay a tasteful box
but he's taking up a coffin shaped
space well pretty much you can't stick
anybody else knows that's the weird part
you know like we're just gonna run
out of space on this are definitely
well actually every time i
drive into new york from the airport
there's that really big cemetery you know
i'm talking to yeah where you see
the skyline right behind it and it
just makes life seem so stupid like
you just see like all of these
these tombstones and then there's like hey
guys someone like they're all going into
that i hate that stretched so much
it's so weird it is real but
every time i see it
i'm like wow everything so pointless yeah
well that's what this show is going
to be about the pointlessness of anyway
catch-all rod crash who was already beat
home but hbo
i like how pointless things are in
my mouth i mean i kind of
that's kind of my whole approach to
life i feel that way about
i feel that way about the ocean
like the the idea of the ocean
making you feel small or space making
feel small i actually find that comforting
yeah it's that i'm just like a
tiny speck and oh that's interesting yeah
yeah sure like a dog that kind
of takes pressure off already likes it's
crate it likes to be talking love
that's great you should i'm gonna send
you this video and everyone can go
google it
it's called optimistic nihilism and on youtube
and it's this whole little thing that
kind of like expresses that idea in
a way that i really like in
a way that's and how is it
comforting though to know that nothing you
do will ever matter because that's it's
comforting it's comforting to know that that's
just the deal do you know what
i mean it's the same for
yeah he's made with the universe we
all just happen to be here and
it's you know we're all going through
the same stuff we're all we're all
having these feelings and right it's it's
very i feel like it connects me
more to the world than it makes
me feel um like a minuscule partisan
what is the point of everything yeah
fuck define no do it well is
it the effect that you have on
other people is it the i mean
that's yeah i think so to some
extent i mean that's why i like
doing podcasts and stuff even though it
can feel like it's pointless sometimes because
like why why are we doing one
but the idea that you could make
someone's day better is nice because there's
no point anything so if you're gonna
be sad and feel bad
it made me laugh a little bit
and then it's not just entertainers who
do that so it's not just yeah
trainers whose lives are worthwhile
i mean i like anyone anyone can
do that for other people and it's
yeah it's not just when we're doing
cornelia yeah i meant like why do
i choose the specific activity remember what
is meaningful but of course everyone's life
is meaningful and that's also the point
right all lives matter i understand yeah
that's what i've been trying to say
for years and i'm wearing shirts that
says ah
so understand what's happening in our world
right now though because it seems like
everyone's just doing horrible things for no
reason yeah we're all gonna die why
do you take away everyone's health care
why do you have to make it
so women can't have abortions i don't
understand well some of some of its
money because money everyone everyone wants more
money no regards dumb to yeah i
mean i wa
on it too but um yeah i
always talk about the way everything is
that i want it i was thinking
about aaron spelling the other day and
forgive me if anyone who knows aaron
spelling or their families out there but
i was thinking about like all the
money that he made right and supposedly
he doesn't give it to tori spelling
like tori spelling didn't get any of
it right yeah wow i know that's
nest or maybe she gets like a
tiny
any tiny sliver whatever thousand dollars our
terrible is alright it's time to read
the will one thousand of these workers
patch
now get at the throws better no
but i mean what's the point of
making all that money like more money
than he could ever spend right yeah
and i bet he loved the work
and that was maybe more employer you
know but um but why why make
all the money if you're not just
gonna give it to your loved ones
like what what i know i don't
i was thinking about that one with
jay leno recently you know we were
talking about how he he doesn't spend
his doesn't touch the tonight show he
lives he said this many times that
he lives off of his standup comedy
money again never touches let what what
the what he just put line the
bambi immersion when wagg goober goober when
was last education standup he he he
doesn't get it all the time he's
he would do it he make money
doing it yes yes yes yes remember
scott he would leave okay i would
leave the teenager show yes you tonight
show on friday afternoon do a whole
weekend of shows come back to the
tonight show hard he works really hard
but but
my address that way
roll up the sleeve wear full denim
our canadian tuxedo he's a hard worker
but my but my thing is is
he yeah he's made a lot of
monies never touching that money but is
he touching it now what does he
doing with it he's doesn't have kids
like yeah yeah that's like so weird
to not enjoy it or to give
it not to give it to be
i've just say i didn't i used
to the star wars prequels i was
like mad at george lucas like
a typical nerd like you ruined it
you ruined it and the day that
he sold star wars to disney for
a billion right and he gave it
all away to charity oh awesome yeah
i was like there you go that's
what you do that's what you do
with your money if you're not gonna
give it to you and and he's
he has a lot of kids yeah
he's adopted a lot how many kids
you have fifteen i love adoption i
don't know how many kids
was there all star wars characters do
it's like the cantina actors and resembles
know he has he's like a dot
he's adopted a lot of kids from
other countries and stuff like that but
but that's i don't know so no
i think that's true i feel that
way like i'm not rich like that
but like i like to feel like
like you're almost rich like look i
almost have billions of dollars i mean
i feel like i'm
in a place with my life where
i can afford the things i like
to do and that feels good but
i like to like give my family
gifts and my dream is able like
pay for my family's homes and things
like that would i would that's really
want to know what enforce all pay
for your family
but i feel like it would feel
so good to you that christmas gift
for us yeah okay great if you
want to would you take that yeah
you're giving it away but you buy
me a house i don't own a
house this is an interesting concept if
we did when when when i was
growing up we did a thing called
pollyanna which is some secret santa it's
where me and my because i come
from a family of six kids and
so we would ah the kids and
the parents would eat in the house
the house he doesn't know it is
enough and we would um with you
or your mom and dad gonna bone
ever thank you martin
bonin and they saw so this is
enough and they're like that really hits
home
i don't know ask him so iverson
know you're so delighted with yourself though
oh i'm not i'm lucy very happy
i'm not delighted i'm delighted in the
sense of almost every word i said
wrong
usually i'll get one wrong percent it's
true almost everyone this it's a real
hat-trick um we'd would you know it's
like secret santa you pick a name
and then you had to buy that
person a gift um so what
think where we had to buy each
other's families goodness oh that's i would
love that people we don't know i
try and it's just as hard as
buying something for someone you know yeah
yeah woo yeah because here i would
just know the general facts about them
and you'd be like what's something fun
they might like and that would be
easier than being like i know everything
about them they're going to have this
reaction that i honestly the people who
listen to conversations throughout the throughout the
year with people and their family and
then know what to buy them in
december like they make meantime love's i
can do that with with my wife
really i can do whatever what have
you bought your wife oh yeah i
have an idea like you want a
history yeah everything is something she said
and you like kept track of it
in your head and then did it
later oh
blanking now there's been a few things
though where she was and it's let
me tell you something the pay off
is so good anytime someone is doing
really nice campo you remember that yes
yeah it's it's the best yeah it's
the right one is i remember what
the place where i proposed to her
was a place where she took me
to her hometown
for the first time and she we
parked at this place she said i
always thought that would be exactly for
wedding reception and i remembered years later
that's the spot oh wow did you
have your wedding reception so i did
not because it was like that place
because fuck we already did some there
whatever
we we actually looked into it but
ah a friend of the family offered
their home oh that's right yeah perceptual
yeah that was yeah mutually yeah yeah
yeah that's cool she still demanded ten
thousand dollars she's she's still demanded ten
thousand yen in cash yeah right upfront
right i mean she locked the doors
and pretended he was halloween she turned
out all like it's my wife yeah
your wife demanded ten thousand to me
earlier to merrier it's a reverse diary
everyone's go to all right duh
river's diary diverse diary
we got around it
reverse diary
it is like a reverse eric were
just telling each other instead of ryan's
getting loud podcasts are like reverse diaries
in a sense yeah you're right no
reverse diary
you said that like like like we've
been saying it for the past like
that's the tight but i write shit
league does so you guys were saying
that could be the title or whatever
i said it like an announcement
okay i get it
what i was gonna say though is
one thing one thing let's just go
to a break oh wow we don't
want this to be doing let's go
to a break time when it's yeah
yeah when we said let's go break
when we come back we'll have more
of whatever this show is reverse diary
of me being this has no pay
off whatever it is and we'll talk
about titles in the next one will
be right back after this
this
hello everyone we're back this is scott
i'm paul and i'm lauren i hate
saying wow navy do you do you
still hear my name growing up i
just was tripping out my name the
other day in a texture with somebody
and i was like that's really my
name paul
i seem like a paw at all
it's almost like a ball it's almost
like that you know what tall it's
all
i hated my name and was always
like no one named otterman has ever
been famous o last name i hate
yeah well i hated both i hated
my first and last and i was
like i really couldn't stand it for
a while and then then i started
realising whole like arnold schwarzenegger's a dumb
name and he yeah it'll stay he
made it and so so i don't
know i felt better after that yeah
yeah i don't mind my name but
i don't it's like i'll often be
like wait my name's lauren like it
just feels weird but i like the
name lauren but i don't know what
do you make people call you a
bum
bum bum bum bum bum bum beat
up mom did you did your parents
have a nickname for you and your
little um i got a lot of
nicknames that weren't related to my name
right but like kitty cat or things
like that kitty down but i my
first name is dorothea my name is
dorothea lie like rice i always felt
some sort of like disconnection
from all of that if you decide
not to be called dorothea or i
was never called that is just my
rice that was really weird about my
brother to his he was ah bert
was a junior bert well he wasn't
even virginia because to be a junior
you have to have the exact same
middle name o rye or like george
w bush yes yeah exactly so ah
but
but i from what i know he
was older ah no one ever called
him bird they just called him by
his middle name greg i guess to
differentiate right yeah that wouldn't be the
same thing as you yeah but that
is something i feel like happens people
like passed on the name then don't
call them the name right that's an
interest as years pass down yeah yeah
my great grandma is dorothy
um then why why the twist greek
version i mean did you know her
at all or no no she was
dead before your yeah i sounded harsh
the ways i knew my great grandpa
that was my only great grandparent that
i knew i knew one great grandpa
i only my grandmother's i didn't know
my grandma they died before i was
around my grandfather's yeah you know your
grandparents i did do
do you ah they're gone we're all
dropping like flies okay in the old
wham on that note here's my segment
i want to introduce not gonna be
a recurring segments a one time only
game yeah we're gonna be doing segments
on the show that we surprise each
other with so in order for it
to not just be one long rambling
conversation yeah anyway what are you
this will be his called
it's called ah soccer league is i
read there there okay that's the name
of it it's called ah is a
really good yeah so okay i mean
how would you spell that like you
wouldn't say well you got it so
no one ever even try so what
the game is is that two of
us we'll improvise a boring uncomfortable conversation
and the third person will laugh and
find an excuse to leave the conversation
it's like a game yeah alright
okay what and who which one do
you want to be i wanna be
in the conversation i don't someone else
has to be the person leaving okay
i'll be the person leaving okay so
paul and i you we're all talking
together so we're all talking about zo
or paul and i'm talking first and
you approach or we're all talking but
you just kind of want to leave
okay i don't know how to get
out of it so you're gonna do
it right laugh and leave okay um
but nothing really
funny will happen to make that possible
okay great great got it yeah and
actually the traffic that i encountered was
so horrible where you're coming from the
west side i was going to the
east side but it was just so
long like i was just the same
route that you take all the time
er yeah i've always followed them
ah i um oh no i wasn't
a joke and it was funny to
do what's funny
i thought you were saying like oh
i always follow the map to le
dumb me i should just follow my
instagram you were making a joke i'm
sorry guys okay i got it okay
always go ahead an app so sometimes
the path will change yeah that does
change i have to um go over
what a rude guy
why leave i would have been better
have to go over
thing is the last time when i
went okay okay now you now we'll
find out well all three do it
sorry alright i'll go next cause i
don't feel confident that i'm gonna win
or anything
alright so we're all talking so um
i notice you have a rainbow tie
clip oh yeah some national coming out
day no i'm not but i i
have family friends that are in today's
national coming out day so let's race
to just how long has that been
around i don't know how old it
is actually i'm not sure but i
yeah i'll say while why would
i'm gonna not that long actually yeah
i mean it might be something that
we're that has been going on for
while that we're not aware of that
we've yeah that's become more aware of
recently yeah you know since people's you
know it's great i mean the i
mean the whole reason to make something
a day is to make it you
know have more awareness exactly so it's
so funny thank you
not really no no i wasn't i
thought you were saying something else i
missed oh would you only be sick
the whole point having yeah i gotta
go
i win okay now we've found a
loophole ah okay well wait one more
round yeah one more pause good okay
okay
so um where are you actually where
did you go last weekend i was
actually was in town i don't know
you're in town yeah maybe my train
i tried texting yeah oh well i
would still get it even if i
was out of town right right yeah
well that's true oh no guy golf
sir wait what
actually yeah
i get it that was a good
spot huh
looks like an extremely personal governments
well right in my head i knew
you
huh
challenge right that was i adored you
oh good good game good game good
game alright let's let fans good game
good game chancellor good
good game but alright ah we're just
about wrapping up should we do the
titles yeah let's do the title right
lot lord good segment thank you korean
or assistant has been writing furiously writing
down title she looks have about twenty
twenty five in there do we want
to announce what they are how do
you want to do a password pass
it around and
each say one or one person say
them
why don't we each do
five okay each to fry from the
list okay we'll pass the the pad
around are we going clockwise or or
counterclockwise i leave that up to you
scott let's go clockwise ah have you
texted whomever you were texting yes i
did it was email and it was
important okay
i'm reading one title you're reading five
nevermind wasn't listening at all
yeah okay tell him pause pause though
after them so we can discuss okay
i'm fully down guys i'm fully down
guys i'm fully dung and it's okay
it's cute but i never just sixty
percent i run tomatoes
a test balloon no
can you handle this too generic i
think yeah
paul scott and lauren real friends no
ma'am
ah it was that five that was
for oh um carolyn marilyn
no oh wait there's somewhere more love
more love now it's sweet you sweet
but no
so far the first one is okay
ah but but but papa
threesome which we've discussed we end up
with writing down titles we already have
their imprint theses on huh
no that's on the next one on
it oh i see okay there are
two options oh i see off mike
brought into the unmake ah off my
right into the unmik that's what about
off mike
off mic not bad because no one
would ever call there unless their name
was like jerry off
hey ma shows are my kinda like
handmaid's tale i'm willing to bet that
there is already already a thing called
off mike will do ah will do
all the research but not bad off
okay okay here we go how about
this all nine eleven jokes jesus
too bad that one's like look like
they would throw it all out there
and we said it you know he
didn't he said we don't eat like
we can't get corinne made that up
no no no that was us alright
k i s come s keep it
simple shithead
yes so stupid welcome back to k
s comments no one will ever find
it
on the app one of our own
v yeah looking for kiss on all
of our subscriptions for people who mistakenly
thought it was gonna be a podcast
about her my hand oh no you
did i thought it was a hard
hit i heard i felt it through
the table i smelled it
i put in
ah ah oh honey it gets worse
oh i like that oh honey oh
honey it gets so that's that's funny
love back about that was about of
course ah age when discussing age only
that i do and birthdays how many
did you do to three
four okay this is my fifth one
okay here we go what
that's one that's this one okay that
one's out with what with a question
mark oh okay i'm sorry was my
line read not obvious i
you have to do another one of
these alright the next episode is going
to also be trying to figure out
the name
ah ok i know it now he
i'm i feel like we
at one point there was no better
thing there was deliberation between who should
do this korean or kevin why i
volunteered kevin curran said why should it
be kevin yeah let me add it
yeah let me add on will keep
going because maybe ok she made kevin
cough sick today yeah he he's not
getting paid he's home pretending to call
yeah i take all day pretending
to call the predicting to bring bring
mom and calling someone he's not well
let me beam of course we'd discuss
of course go better you get you
oh god that's more of what we're
talking about though i like it
any ship has sick bay
the sickbay the singing today hate it
i don't i still know what it
means is it a room is an
area's roots like the medical facilities on
a ship okay you did tell me
that i just didn't hear
didn't retain ah i've done okay this
is five generally
that just gives the idea that we're
never going to talk about gender issues
thing which we never will however never
i don't know talk about um where
did we leave off generally i know
but it can um delete i'm shocked
i'm shocked too generic i feel this
has now
no pay off i mean so far
honestly i love that one pretty good
um or just no pay off is
another option i think this has no
pay off sounds more like a title
yeah sucking on chili dogs sucking on
shell it off so i'm gonna hit
it off so i'm gonna show you
know i'm so sad days three
standard okay
d let's try to emphasize hey welcome
back to sucking on show oh why
am i doing oh because i just
played that clip of the song instead
of saying chuck it on chili dogs
welcome back to southern tomatoes everything so
pointless
i don't remember that being said it's
my life motto oh that's right okay
reverse diary
it's interesting that i don't think ha
i have to go
ha i have to go
ah so many there that's not bad
let me take a look i'll see
the
hi this has no payoff might be
the best and most accurate description of
what we're doing yes now i also
awesome suggestions do you learn um no
i don't okay can i read my
all done let me let me write
down the ones that ah we thought
were okay put a checking mark now
yeah i'm putting in a checking mar
checking ah checking ah sorry sorry sorry
sorry put a blue
diamond like julian assange protector his name
on twitter ah this is because he's
got okay good what a weenie rebuilt
said okay i got five here that
we sort of responded to go ahead
okay what do you got we have
three them we have lakins man
this is a play on the three
amigos los trace friends
i like it's clever friend knows
right work friends
we're friends into the real friend just
work friends i like with yeah those
funny triple dip ripple dip i like
dripping i got the triple dip
turtle drip the magic number which is
which is three three measures number ah
tri klopp's
you all are not only oh scott
ah three easy three easy sleazy take
three easy sleazy three enough threes enough
and then these i think i had
a feeling they might be reflective of
how this was gonna go okay will
you just let me speak
you've had your turn ah
and this one i can come up
with while we were recording this is
frustrating ah okay yeah hey find a
great time you guys what was your
second one that you said that the
last three yeah you've had your turn
you've had your turn that's pretty good
that's pretty good okay
now ah let me let me ah
i'm not sure about the other ones
before that why should we trust you
using a dry erase marker to write
on paper but the fuck outta you
guys the town lunatic
the town ludicrous
three town should have a ludicrous yeah
it looks really hot and crispy
it's great yeah um okay so here's
what we have i'm fully down guys
know sounds too generic i feel like
of like hey i'm fully out guys
yeah off mike
okay i like it but it's priority
done this has no pay off i
love that love that struck it on
chill it oh veto
wow
haha i have to go
not bad that stuff it's not bad
it's not bad but you've had your
turn
ah no because it almost sounds um
mean antagonist yeah when we're really about
fun yeah um i said they're off
mike exists as a podcast we sound
to us that all across that out
okay so we have we didn't know
that both raised by tv until it
was too late so oh no really
everyone's telling me on twitter but guess
what
it's all too late it's all happening
what are you going to do we're
keeping it the day it was cleared
with those people oh really so they're
not doing it any longer doing it
but they're just they're aware of us
and they don't care they don't care
i guess ya know what they said
but it was cleared up so everyone
stopped telling me that okay
do you know there's another race by
tv okay you know
okay so your turn were between these
two this has no pay off okay
and haha have to go
i still think this has no pay
off as it's very clear i like
that one here's my reservation about it
is i feel like it's
so deprecating it's too sets that's true
because it does have a path it's
fun it's fun what about also what
podcast has a pay off what about
the ultimate pay off
i like the ultimate pillow i would
rather make a gigantic promise yeah until
people this is worth listening yeah the
ultimate payoff your ultimate that's good i
like the ultimate pay off
okay i like that it's very confident
we ultimate pay alright so it might
be that um and no you know
because you're listening to it yes ah
what would be really funny if it's
none of those which is also possible
and people are like no dummy yeah
um but we don't know that yet
um guys i think we
gotta wrap it up for this episode
um we're gonna try to do this
every week ah and we're gonna try
to not always the hard part though
well we're gonna do it we're gonna
try to bank a lot of them
yes so so we may not be
topical but maybe we'll be talking about
what you know that's what we wanna
do is we want to talk about
just whatever comes to us okay
you know whatever is affecting our lives
and you'll love it that's right as
of this recording you'll love it donald
trump has just been sworn in as
the president and i'm feeling good about
giving him a chance i love the
guy real tv guy great tv
um alright any parting words parting is
such sweet sorrow of course has the
immortal bard once said
anything either of you guys do we
should have a sign-off huh yeah but
the signup sign off and we got
three signing off signing off signing hawa
signing on signing off sending on signing
off signing on shining signing off so
okay this is signing on signing off
we'll see you next time
thanks bye
a this has been in year with
production executive produced by scott ackerman chris
bannon and colin anderson for more information
and content visit airwolf dot com