oh
wow
ah we did it right he did
it perfectly people are getting that we're
seeing three i don't think they're getting
it now i think they're getting it
yeah i think do we need to
explain it no no no no if
you know this but brett send us
an email saying he edits them so
you can hear three meme wow are
you fucking kidding i'm not kidding we
did not give you permission for the
that we didn't give him our email
addresses where did he get them how
does he know who i am
hey everyone welcome to three um three
that's right and um this is obviously
this little spinoff show of threesome where
i'm scott
i'm paul i'm lauren and that's only
on three meme are we these characters
um but ah this is where we
answer your voicemails and of course you
can leave us voicemails at hag claims
eight it's great doc dot com don't
put don't put don't go on the
phone trying to dial that high claims
eight dot com hack
i'm a dot com that said website
where you leave us a voicemail it's
such a good website it's so good
there's so much to do there like
leaving us a voice yeah they join
our gallery of the one button you
can click on it's actually it's like
it couldn't be simpler i think it
was beautifully designed whomever did it yeah
it's elegant in it's simplicity truly as
in it's terrible if you want
something complicated i'm yeah doing something yeah
lawrence gonna plug in her you can't
call a computer but i guess it's
an i-pad that she put a little
fun you can't really call it a
computer because it doesn't really compute anything
know i pads do not compute no
no that's not going to go butte
alright so we're going to listen to
some voicemails that you the listeners have
ah la force so are you guys
ready you want to listen to this
one i'm ready and i do wanna
listen to it all right here we
go um why wouldn't we at this
point you know what i mean why
are you stalling just press play when
he's radio because
it will not low alright here we
go we all know we will not
low three i'm getting my name is
chris i've been in practice i was
just listening to you all talking about
losing t getting baby tease out and
you're asking if you're reading the thing
it's like tying the string door and
getting a chewed out that way well
with my seven year old
just recently lost couple of teeth she
tied dental floss sugar to have been
to a remote controlled car and she
drove the car away from herself and
pulled out to home i've given twice
on two different teams it was really
cool to watch and i have a
video
give me back if you want to
do the video okay thanks can you
back two things guys lying about the
video you know what i can imagine
that nobody has ever even shot of
it we're supposed to hit him back
and then he scams us yeah it's
like oh yeah that video will play
on you know it's like if you
put your social security number yeah to
a note i've heard of this yeah
yeah this guy
is he's not even named chris i
bet i bet he's something like christopher
or something
ah he may not even have a
gig he might if he doesn't forget
i bet they don't have teeth well
you know what i love that story
that i love the un genuity their
expressed by new and used like a
roger new eddie
that was a wonderful story do you
think that that there are fish that
are good fathers like in finding nemo
where they care about i don't think
i think that about nature all the
time like is there a maternal instincts
i guess they always put it on
animals but i think they would kill
anyone for for a potato they don't
ah it's funny that they protect them
when they're little right and then they're
like you're on your own you can't
get out of here what are you
still doing here yeah i don't want
to be around you like cats don't
live together forever yeah i think that
about like sometimes i was like with
our dogs i was like
would it be because we know where
some of george's siblings are would it
be fun for them to see each
other i don't think it would mean
anything i know
um not to be around river butcher
ones posting you know river has a
dog named murph
ah who is a funny little guy
or for smurf or murphy
sure for murphy well that's really just
a couple short more oh no um
and one time he posted a picture
of the dog with another dog that
looked kind of like it's just said
murphy's mom
the talk when it visited his mother
i mean if i knew who fanny's
mom was i wouldn't can i wouldn't
definitely want to see like is there
any sort of you know yeah i
mean frannie was taken from a um
it was mostly a person left took
a bunch of puppies at a dog
groomer in like go like hey groomed
these for me pie
you want to grow a puppies and
then they were just free wow they
were all right there no one point
yeah i mean we through instagram i
believe we know who because of how
we got georgia so we know all
of and she was originally called fruity
pebbles oh that's really the you should've
kept them they were all named after
cereals so but but we we know
where some of them are i'm always
like what georgia care at all would
remember i was one named grape nuts
musa looks great that's a funny name
for a dog because they're nuts kinda
our new select so i think it's
usually huh
usually i heard this in a game
show floor last nine years i think
is what mucinex yeah that's not a
serial they pronounced it you could eat
a bowl of it though but you
are right it's mutually but but it
has an exit ah now there's mucilage
mucilage new slicks new slicks okay so
you're watching the floor i was going
a couple episodes of the floor can
stay away who i'm on it all
the tablo prob low i know
why fit fuckin you're rich already you
don't you're an actor just do just
act just great at it jesus christ
you're one of the best if you're
already famous you can't be a game
show host you should be hosting the
floor yeah i would host the shit
out of yeah all host the ceiling
you get the walls alright to the
window e hours of
power yep that's right yeah or blah
yeah they're the exact same show after
all do floor watch the walls i
want to host a game show okay
like it's you hosting a game show
i'm just you're on enough of them
i feel like i'm proving that i
can play i'm gonna choke
i don't think you can know i've
got a joke
oh so good job
hello players i've got a joke
ah it's a show that features no
editing
just wanting for five minutes straight
ah
look this is it i do think
i saw this pregnancy rhinitis thing it's
like i can't breathe you just want
to say that i'm also eating lutens
right now and i i just discovered
on the back they have watermelon i
mean that's so fucking good
oh watermelon in general or ah because
it's cherry lose while like wild cherry
lutens are classic and they're so good
plastic but the watermelon i'm like that's
probably so good that's a great candy
i've never thought about the watermelon cherry
combo before watermelon cherry it's my knowledge
are not a combo what am i
jerry i'm just like
like i've never thought of that combo
i wonder what it would be like
i wonder if anyone's ever thought of
it oh my no no one says
it patent it was a sex symbol
will own it you know and you
know what is good sparkling water i
discovered oh you little lincoln oh no
trader joes whatever who cares just there's
there br
brand yeah or have good com do
they call it like trader neptune no
really trader nope don't know things just
trader joe's did they figure presiding they
phased out trader jose and where they
sucked so like making everything yeah appropriation
or something yeah it seems like a
good i miss it i see it
seemed very
mild and i said i was just
thinking of video signed by those kind
of just yeah it's just it's not
for us to say and like it's
not for us to say but they
did not have like stereotypical drawings or
anything no on their packaging it was
just like get it get it it's
like a trader joe tow because it's
pasta sauce and then they still do
that
i will do trader joe's sort of
thing they do only the white yeah
blade country yeah yeah they're the last
to fall this woman traders bay so
that's like people magazine article yesterday that
was like some celebrity or actress or
something was like staying in a hotel
and she ordered room service and then
her husband later was like
using the wasn't like the food area
of like you know where they have
the buffet in the morning or something
there's like a communal fridge when he
saw that the stuff they ate was
like frozen trader joe's meals they had
ordered carbonara or something and it was
like it was oconto pepe and it
was like wow literally was frozen trader
joes wait how did he why would
that be stored in the common area
they were just
piles they had all these like tiki
tikka masala like all these different things
frozen the sound so good but was
that not a thing that you could
buy and you could heat up in
your room perhaps no she ordered it
was called like calming cult katu a
peppy and then it was twenty dollars
and it was a four dollar bag
of the charges sixteen for the heat
i'm suspicious of this
yeah i'm suspicious of this story i
feel like you're lying to all eyes
and i don't know why hey maybe
i am maybe some hotels you can
get like microwavable meals yeah it's not
ah okay okay but they didn't reveal
the hotel that's the part i was
suspicious and this was a celebrity and
this was the hotel
i'd never heard of her i don't
know you never heard of her and
the husband was the bloodhound in this
instance they showed a picture of the
room service being revealed and they showed
a picture of the stuff in the
fridge and it was the exact same
what they said the presentation was really
good and it was good
so were they complaining but no because
the hotel claimed to have all handmade
you know all you know someone's hand
made creations it's so true you know
god maybe you don't think a machine
made that lamb vindaloo from trader joe's
boy man if machines could make like
be chefs
like david chang right yeah zhang bot
j just there's jan you just want
him to be a machine no but
i mean he's so good at it
right but what if you could just
like program a machine with all it's
parts to do exactly what he would
definitely seems better i wouldn't be like
robots and stuff yeah and i'd buy
david cheng but i made david cheng
about i
wood by david chow macho day their
fifty thousand dollars oh but still like
sometimes advertise that's three meals a day
yeah would you buy david chang if
you could no i will not buy
a person really yeah if i could
i wouldn't just put us why you're
so great putting on record i would
not buy a human being i have
appreciate you
that's awesome thank you alright well that's
gonna do it for this episode yeah
so congrats to that little girl chris
his daughter yeah i think she's gotta
wear those adult teeth or baby teeth
with it sounded like baby teeth yeah
i hope it wasn't hurt does the
char was seven i think it would
hurt a lot more if it was
your idea
well um if you want to hear
your um you know whatever that was
if this just fired you why don't
you give us a call at the
website hag claims eight dot com and
you go to so many websites a
day why not visit this one at
least three times the price you go
to the same five websites every goddamn
m day mix it up go to
this one for once in your life
yeah there's so many websites that you
don't even go to you know when
you're on your phone and you go
through your three apps that you look
ahead and then go back to the
first one again yeah and you feel
disgusting just going ahead claims eight throw
that in the mix yes ah should
be an app oh my gosh we
don't have an out by the time
this episode comes out what are we
doing with our lads know i'm going
to i'm going to leave a message
right now and he claims eight yep
saying making me make this an app
bitch um alright well we're you're both
on your phone so i guess that
means this you die by