three
wow
oh did you hear a yellow different
day said it correct
yea hi guys welcome back this is
three meme surest got and this is
where we every other week we take
a voicemail from you guys that you
send to us via the popular website
hey claims a dotcom and we're gonna
do that right now we're gonna listen
to a voicemail and we're gonna talk
about it and these are real people
by the way these aren't actors that
are reenacting actual voicemails that people have
sent us i know that could still
happen yes we and we if that
does happen of course will be ashamed
but we will we promise you that
we will root out well we'll definitely
boys are doing that to us
yeah but there's a chance that we
will hire actors to read them because
we want to protect the identity of
somebody who sent it exactly then we
wouldn't be wouldn't be ashamed we would
be no wow we've become so if
we want to just give our friends
a little extra money sometimes we'll hire
actors to do stuff oh yeah i've
hired i've hired actors to our friends
virus yeah to do stuff around my
house sure yeah i've had actors just
be
me on this show a couple of
times if you can go through and
spot which time like i did that's
the freedom channel cause that's amazing active
you can tell when it's an actor
that's doing lauren well it's amazing impersonating
yeah yeah and of course there's access
to your bank account and stuff but
i just wanna be clear isn't acting
or is it impersonating yeah and i
mean that's actually the jamie foxx ray
jay
jamie foxx ray right jamie foxx ray
you know hey hi i'm jamie foxx
ray and i don't care jamie foxx
ray and i don't care if you
fuck say and i okay that is
acting to me fox is incredible as
ray you as an impersonation of ray
charles but if he was just talking
on a podcast as ray charles is
that acting or is it reacting to
to someone asking him to do it
and then doing thing that he wanted
to do when did doing the things
they see won't be de um okay
but if you are a reenactor of
like a civil war reenactor yeah that's
different you can of course leave us
whisper well that's just using yourself but
your job title is re-enact oh but
don't see an actual job don't hobby
should not be but don't be wearing
the uniform when you call us please
oh like an unless you're from the
good side yeah well we paul what
do you think is the good side
fuck here's what i have to say
i don't want anyone to be thinking
about i'm color blind so like i
don't want to think about uniforms they
are wearing while they're talking to us
i don't want them to think about
what they're wearing so if you are
wearing your reenactment costume don't don't
call us new code call us who
all this way are renewed but but
actually do call cells which are wearing
no no no don't ask us what
we're wearing don't don't tell us what
we're wearing yeah call and tell us
when and then we'll change into whatever
you want us to wear you ask
what we're wearing we say how high
were like paper dolls alright let's listen
to this
this superbowl people voicemail and i'm going
to turn back up i realised the
theme was too loud and all because
i turned up the voicemail oh man
the distortion was here we got a
ball i couldn't hear myself think hey
presto gang this has been a long
time yo cousin i'm yum
i wanted to see if there was
anything in your career whether it's like
on a podcaster and stand up or
anything that you wish you could redo
and i know that that's not a
good way to look at things but
i'm curious have you ever been a
sketch where you're like oh we didn't
really get what else trying to do
there or like a story you wish
you could tell again but
differently without you know getting spanked fiskars
alright love you i love you back
very nice question this is a good
question it's making me think about all
my failures yeah it's so tough to
because i think about it a lot
about oh man if only i knew
this then or if only i
i'd worked harder if only i had
not pursued this particular thing it's it
it is semi fruitless and in a
certain way but yeah maybe if it
informs the choices you're making now it's
worthwhile i don't know i would say
like very broadly macro i wish i'd
never smoked yeah and i wish i'd
go to therapy sooner
then like more thing like an actual
like a do over thing i wish
i had taped there was there was
a certain standard of our presence together
yeah together so this was one big
gift that would have been so good
i quit your gret i wish i'd
recorded i have an hour
austin of called you should have told
me that i wish i had done
later because i recorded it and then
i went on tour with it before
the recording came out yeah yeah yeah
and it's like i'm not i'm not
ashamed of it's recording tomorrow
and it will say like it'll i
mean it's what's the difference between that
and remastering albums you know what i
mean well because i can't remember the
song attitude well that's a problem yeah
then why should we
yeah i wish i never said this
i think so many things you can't
do you can't feel that way about
because that was your capability at the
time exactly as the thing your parents
you have to forgive them because that's
the best they could do at the
thai right i just i was just
listening to a podcast where this sort
of same thing was bro
caught up just sort of the idea
oh i wish i had known this
when i was eighteen we know and
why did i act this way when
i was nineteen nobel and that it
was a therapist was talking to this
person on the podcast and it was
about and she was saying
you know if you go back and
read like you're like a journal or
like an email from when you were
nineteen you would be like shocked by
oh damn you are basically like that
yeah she was just saying like she
was looking back at her old stuff
and she was like oh my god
i can't believe how much i didn't
know if you are just a kid
whatever not saying that's true about all
these things we're talking about but i
mean it
applies because i think it's just like
letting yourself give yourself grace for what
didn't go exactly right or using your
life or career whatever just things you
didn't achieve do as well as you
could have now but it's like you
couldn't just couldn't you didn't have that
i struggle know i struggle with that
a lot i struggle with time yeah
because i do i get um i
can get
very angry with my with my past
self yeah yeah yeah and it's like
i think about that a lot yeah
like why didn't i work harder why
didn't i know how to do this
thing that i now know how to
do if only i'd known how to
do it back then and then yeah
career would be different and i that
always makes me think of a story
that a friend of mine told about
being in therapy
he and the therapist saying to her
and if if you could if you
could talk to little amy what would
you say to her and her name
was not amy right
just don't touch lamy
choose point if you've just talked to
little amy
what would you say to her and
my friend said
thanks a fucking lot
i mean yeah
i definitely um i definitely have things
that i would look back i mean
because the question was about career which
is is lot but it's hard not
to apply to everything else but i
just look back and i'm like oh
that was a waste of time or
one night get those waste of time
or whatever it's like because you don't
know yeah anything exactly till you know
and then you experience the thing i'm
going to go oh that's how that
should have been yeah
a or i could have done that
job better if i had known this
sort of
brutal yeah yeah connection cause once you
see the answer you're like ah why
didn't i put that from the start
why didn't i just guess why didn't
know i guess those age rewind i
just start with rage
so it's a waste of time but
unfortunately we all can't help but think
of it all day every day
yeah we can only be consumed by
it every waking moment
yeah but um but you know then
again if if things had gone differently
i feel like i've lucked into some
many things in my life yeah and
it's true i always come back to
that though the timing of everything else
is basically everything else that happened like
yeah everything happens for a reason quote
unquote you can be sort of like
oh man
okay we were trying to have that
baby for ten years like
what if like what if my body
was ten years younger i was doing
the go on
it looked like the
oh but you know like it's so
difficult right you're like oh if we
just say this thing
if i but then but then it
wouldn't be i mean person wouldn't exist
yeah i always yeah back about that
of like if you went back and
relive your life the people in it
there's there's no way i ever would
have met cool up without all the
things happening exactly the way they have
because we just weren't not in the
same circles i would not have met
janie
had it not been for real time
with bill maher and icon but god
bless you bill maher rest in power
okay ooh yeah ooh yeah that make
you favor association sitcom clipped
yeah when it happened i remember i
remember loaf of bread but also welcome
to stick a butter clipped was a
pilot that got picked up and it
was a year until we shot the
scene and so we all became friends
over this year wow why why was
that i don't remember it was something
like that's very strange i know i
let because i
just i have to look back at
this and see what the reason yeah
please yeah i'm gonna check in your
files i don't know why it was
but anyways yeah but it was like
timing you know so if there's good
in your life be thankful that the
good is there because it unless you
did the exact things that you did
it never would have happened
ah you gotta make mistakes yeah you
simply got to yeah and like with
acting and stuff it's like a few
if i look back and i'm like
oh that's not that great when you
look back and you're like oh i
wish i had done that better but
it's like but you literally like you
can't even control which version they take
of what you shot so like maybe
you did do it but i mean
you know it's just the whole i
had an acting job
ah last week and i felt like
for the first time and i feel
like a long time i felt like
i did a good job but like
in the moment and i was like
man i didn't like that that much
and then we did a few more
takes and everything and i felt like
that's okay and then you know ah
the director like eventually
we finished the scene and i was
like if they're fine with it then
i'm fine with it you know i
mean like right you used to go
like that is what that was yeah
you're the weirdo movie ah i got
two takes and that was it and
i left going like either i was
terrible more i was so good it
only needed two takes then eventually i
just was like look it was a
low budget movie i'm
sure they only wanted to takes there's
no title but you can't help but
drive home going like saying the line
yeah in a different way hopefully it
stays that way and i watched the
movie and i'm fine i got a
lot that year i told you the
story about when i worked on modern
family and
like the director kept giving me i
don't think xo yes well because here's
why oh okay so i auditioned for
the i edition for them a million
times finally get this one part and
ah so i'm doing it and after
each take the director is coming to
me saying like he has this sort
of stress looking
this is like can you do it
like um like real big real big
and i'm like sure okay and so
i go real big and then you
come and go who is because you
could you could you do it like
just you like are you real asshole
just like you're the worst guy i'm
like ok do that and he goes
okay now um can you do it
like ah like ah like you really
hate this p
isn't like do it like that and
he's good but he's doing these directions
with this real stressed out look and
i'm like yeah this is not going
well and on the way back and
it was a fox of course so
i have a long drive home and
i was like that didn't feel good
yeah and then they replaced me oh
yeah yeah yeah
that's so hard though because it's like
it sounds like he didn't really know
what he wanted from me it was
not him but i think it's hard
as a director i went through that
the first season of my show where
the director just had the way of
talking where it was like it felt
like you were doing something wrong every
time anytime you gave a note and
then eventually i was like i left
that first season
going like i don't think i'm funny
at all and then and then we
had a discussion between seasons he was
like confirmed
you're not funny but it was like
no that was just the way he
was giving notes of like he's trying
to perfect it after the first take
and i'm like well this is comedy
let us like just kind of try
some stuff well some directors really can't
talk to actors yeah this is very
strange yeah something that i like had
to because early plays that i directed
i was always like doing the same
thing going like well what if you
did it this
way after just one yeah right and
it's like no give people a couple
of what i learned is like laugh
come over say that was really funny
yeah hey what and then maybe a
small adjustment and are like let's just
do it again like don't even give
a node after the first take and
just say let's just do it again
and then after the second one maybe
go like oh okay what if you
did this you know but it's like
such
a unique skill to like make an
actor in comedy i'm saying to make
an actor feel like comfortable enough where
they're like okay let's just you know
have fun yeah i feel like you
know ben maybe we got off topic
a little there we got back to
it we got back to it that's
gonna be it for this three visiting
we'll see in a couple of weeks
remember to leave these voicemails at hag
claims eight dot com yeah we'll see
on the flippy flap