freedom three
yeah
nah
um it's a three yeah you see
how i was acting like an agent
of chaus
i reworded my cross i was very
very scared about what was happening on
your end of the table was like
yeah i became a joker and a
smoker in a minute tour
most and that's something isn't that special
church lady lady when used to be
so easy comedy used to be so
easy i know honestly that sketch the
same thing every single time you would
get mad if he didn't say satan
and didn't say is especially sure to
add reverb on it it's okay look
we gotta change this up but we've
done this one thousand times
let's how about we had reverbed as
the word satan but we loved it
i loved it we loved it and
we folks he sounded like the cover
of people magazine as the church lady
within like a month really i got
see that i think i think not
not as the main cover but like
up in the oh okay it's the
stories falling apart and it wasn't people
it was person and he was dana
carvey k wow he he would get
the whole cover no but that's that
sucks it was on the cover i
think it was like i think it
was sid caesar that doesn't like rain
the pre dana carvey
the crazy woman yes
search grandma
those words put together didn't help narrow
down my search there's a lot of
church related things on the cover of
people magazine how about church lady people
magazine yeah that's what i wrote dana
carvey church lady people magazine yeah okay
i'm not too ah
i have it right here in front
of me first thing that popped up
wow it must be cool to be
you okay guess who is on the
cover guess who guess who is on
the cover you want to do a
twenty question they have a hat cover
they don't have a hat if that
helps narrow it down like the game
guess who do you ever play that
game oh no it seems like it
would be oh yeah yeah but you
just you so i've never played it
but i know what it is it's
pretty fun sounds fun
i saw a video well the game
is like you have the this board
with all these pictures of different characters
and then you're like an any of
a car that has one character on
it so you're like my person is
this person you have that person and
i'm trying to guess who yours is
and little down by like putting down
on my little tabs all the people
so i'm like does your person have
a hat and you go know that
i get down all the people who
do have a hat i get right
right right i saw people playing it
on instagram when they were like does
your person look like someone who would
talk to you at a bar about
like you and they just like make
it yes shaking like that's very that's
fun okay this person who's on the
cover of the people magazine that the
church lady has little top corner thing
i guess he and i have shared
something oh it's why
one person okay it's one of us
coke
maybe he and i have shared something
a lover perhaps you're gonna have to
guess and i'm not i'm not saying
guess what he and i've shared i'm
saying guess the person is it johnny
carson incorrect arnold schwartzenegger incorrect but what
have we shared in your opinion i
don't know what the hell
would i you know what he and
i've shared i know it yes
so i have to think of everything
that yeah everybody in other person yeah
a celebrity who would have been on
the cover of people magazine in nineteen
eighty six
the i'm just going with the celebrity
um because i can't
i think that everything possible to share
well it's not like paul rudd chachi
interesting because we share a name because
james chinese correct yes my name is
joshua scott
josh jackman um i'll nineteen eighty six
yeah
staying oscar winner oh and he's on
the cover because he's an oscar winner
tom hanks incorrect tom hanks did not
win until philadelphia nineteen ninety one um
he wanted to lumos oh ryan o'neal
incorrect
he and i shared a role oh
my name is michael k gold member
gold member go michael can i see
the picture yeah where you go is
be taking tibet porter then there's church
lady right up there don't you think
mike could address
messed up a little bit that's a
really like casual cover over you supercash
do you think that he that was
a shoot for the magazine who think
they just found a picture i don't
know because he's wearing like a tennis
warmer looks like he's pulling his shirt
down like a warm-up jacket but it's
it it is zip-up but he has
he's showing his chest hair too
to us intentionally it seems it's sexy
it's it's getting me around the bone
zone so hard to um okay this
is a gorged this is freemium where
we step tufa your right this is
three men where we play your e
or your voicemail like little said emails
player
emails oh no oh my god you
can't do that he's losing it um
he's giving me good days bad days
you you send us these via hag
claims a dot com that's right it's
bookmark this website yeah and it should
be your start page it should be
your main source of news hey claims
eight
i know you mainly get your news
from hudson news or other trusted news
sources yeah but
claims hey disagree i know you go
down to the corner i only go
to the airport talk to that guy
that's just a little shack it's freezing
cold he's got a cigar and the
watchmen are around there and the giant
squid is about this little boy reading
a comic book about what's happening right
pirates pirates oh yeah and guess what
you could skip that yeah turns out
it's never into
listing what what a good feeling that
is when you're reading watchmen and realised
it's like his this now what or
when you're rewatching the twin peaks showtime
episode you go oh wow i can
totally skip over the ducky scenes when
they do the doggy yeah yeah teach
me how to dougie yeah yeah um
okay so this i want to eat
you out to do that does ye
um here we go this is a
voicemail left by one of you
hey lauren paul scott
my name is delaney and i have
a delaney so paul you are on
the podcast recently where you describe yourself
as an easy laughter and that just
gave me so much joy and so
i was wondering if you could share
with all the other piss paintings what
it means to be an easy laughter
and why you consider yourself to be
one and then mourn and scott would
either have
you use that term to describe yourself
as an easy wow here's a good
question thanks i really like ever she
did yeah i like her name delaney
delaney i like a good name yeah
it's like dana delaney but backwards yeah
maybe your last name is dana with
no dana yeah yeah that's what that's
like
but we don't know their last name
is dana a good thing could be
delaney dana that would be delaying schama
dana that would be shocking i'm until
he made a bit um okay so
to me what an easy laffer means
is first of all i enjoy comedy
but
also i will laugh this is not
i will sometimes laugh not in a
professional capacity but in life
it's sometimes a laugh is people it's
just the intention of being funny you
know what i mean yeah like when
you're out and about in the world
and somebody makes some little oh yeah
something and it's like even though the
the joke itself is maybe not hilarious
but the idea that somebody's being kind
of um you know ah silly or
whatever that will i
i will enjoy that so it's like
it's weirdly like i'm laughing at the
intention of the person rather than what
they said now i think as a
woman
i'm not a woman you should okay
fine then i'll answer for myself no
okay good i think as a woman
i um laugh when i don't mean
it a lot because now with my
friends like someone needs but no in
public you have to do that right
i mean you don't have to but
it's like we're ingrained with this i
think
to show that you're i'm just a
nice shiny i mean i along with
it all and i don't mind that
you just made that comment i'm not
the biwa yeah in apartment twenty three
words i know but um so i
definitely put you polite laughter but i
think um with my friends i i
like to laugh a lot and then
but
if i'm watching something and i don't
think it's funny i don't really
yeah but it's it's not to be
rude it's just that i wait because
i'm gonna really is i'm like really
having fun like i went to see
we talked about this show gutenberg and
i was like laughing so hard and
it was like that's the best feeling
when you genuinely refined something so funny
that you're just like surprised by it
and the laugh is like
so authentic and i feel like for
me it's i i sort of just
like let it wash over me until
that happens i agree with that i
very rarely laugh at entertainment like like
a movie or tv show or something
so when it does make me laugh
out loud it's a huge thing yeah
wow that really caught me by far
like
i think you should leave or something
like yeah and then i'm just like
crying and i'm like that's the best
i get worried at live shows if
i go to see a friend show
because i i i have allowed laugh
and and to some people maybe a
distinctive laugh and i worry about ah
calling attention to myself yeah makes me
very self-conscious yeah and so
and i laugh and then i'll like
stop myself when i think there's that
thing too of like if you are
laughing really hard something and then you're
not then you stop yeah that's like
oh you don't like that one yeah
we're all aware of like what the
first allowed laffer is exactly yeah yeah
um scott what do you think do
you laugh i've ever seen that
have you ever left i don't know
what does it aw no it's officers
yeah it's haha um yeah i'm like
an easy laugh in a lot of
ways of something just tickles me like
cl always find very amusing when i
watched something like detroiters or
paul walter hauser and anything or you
know what i mean where i'm just
like sitting there laughing really hard and
she'll come into the room and be
like oh my god you're laughing really
nice because it's so so because you're
so miserable because you're such a prick
right and that's been three memes oh
god he's turning up his laptop oh
my god he slammed it shut she'll
show well um but yeah and i'm
around it so i'm i'm a really
easy and then you know just producing
that standup show for ten years i
was laughing a lot because
everything was so funny now i don't
find standup all that funny anymore so
when i because i just had to
be around it so much when hardy
what it is i think it's a
comedy fatigue yes yes so when i
do see something that i really like
a stand-up special that's super funny i'm
like oh i can still laugh and
santa yeah hey i had an experience
recently
the ah and i thought about it
it really made me think about live
performance i went to see a matinee
of a play and there was a
lot of humor in the play but
because it was a matinee it was
not hugely attended
there were lines that you you you
knew would usually get laughs yeah and
weren't getting laughs and it's not that
i didn't think they were funny but
it is a different crowd was different
women wow when you're in a crowd
and it's that's why comedy films are
so it's so important to watch with
the crowd it was important because it
just it just i mean i i
remember like
watching the naked gun on opening night
and just like laughing with tears rolling
down my face because everyone in the
crowd that's the best oh my god
we went to that scary movie premiere
that time what was it do you
remember that there was one of the
scary movies and we did yeah i
thought you were there yeah i don't
know did me a lot so because
we we like
walked up on the red carpet
by james woods i know that we've
been number two it was not me
but um and ah ah i so
it's it's a it's because prayer maybe
it was melanoma yeah yeah yeah it's
the premiere of this movie and so
everyone is laughing their fucking heads off
and i was too yeah and i'm
like
like if ah that's right it's like
it's like oh great time if i
saw this movie on cable or yeah
i'd say you own your house yeah
well sometimes i would see movies itself
by southwest and they would just be
so funny at south by southwest and
then you'd tell people like oh go
go see it and then you see
it it's just not it's kind of
laying there i was so relieved when
i saw br
kids maids maybe three weeks before it
came out and i was coming back
going dad everyone mean everyone will go
see brisbane and so we went to
like opening night at the dome and
um paul who directed was there actually
and i was like oh hey here
i am again i'm watching i brought
all my friends and then it just
kills you know yes just it's very
gratifying that
a movie i remember crying laugh like
laughing till i cried and also crying
at the emotional thing only i love
it i love to them but then
like i would get sometimes going to
the sunset five you'd get upset at
the certain type of theatre goer yes
like doing performative laughing like i'm smart
enough to get this joke but but
at the same time like
it is kind of a relationship especially
in a live performance it's a relationship
between you and the performer of like
trying to give them what they yes
i just i do feel if i'm
watching a comedian or comedy show up
in person i'm not withholding because i
wanted to feel like yeah like gary
we're here it's
conversation between you and the performers something
yes if it's a great way so
i think like when we go out
on tour it's great to hear the
laughs and it emboldens you and it's
not performative yeah in in some ways
but i don't know there are people
i mean depends on what you're watching
i think there's definitely those people where
they're laughing like huh i'm smart right
but i would i would
rather know as a performer i would
rather that than people just sitting there
going yeah show me something oh no
no it's much nicer that people do
like yeah but i went to a
rather comedy show in london of someone
who is very funny and
i was listening to some podcast recently
where they were talking about was it
you talking this oh my god where
he accused
the london audiences don't really laugh but
then they're like that was amazing ah
yes i was warned that before i
went to yeah for the first time
still very much more reserve was with
my parents and this song i was
there doing that movie and i might
so my parents can visit me and
we went to this standup or it
was a storytelling show somebody that i
really like and um
the and but i felt crazy because
i was like no one's laughing but
my parents and i were laughing but
it was like on like sort of
like it what's i couldn't tell what
was happening it was like it was
actually a really weird feeling because i
was like yo when you bring someone
to something in your like i hope
they like this yeah i'm going like
do they think this sucks because no
one's laughing but it's like
but it is entertaining and i'm like
and then they they did have a
good time but it was just like
so if laughter is truly involuntary than
why would it be a cultural thing
if people don't laugh
did that make do that thank you
fall asleep because i launched so rich
but you know what i mean like
like i don't know i just laughed
i hold ever really known that about
and then i had i don't know
if you said it or somebody else
said it but i was like oh
maybe that made me think of that
experience i was like oh is that
what happened there like it was like
the maybe they're being respectful or
like taking it in a different way
no laughter no it wasn't but but
it was it was it wasn't enthusiastic
laugh it was quiet yeah yeah yeah
i mean culturally and it was sold
out like if like they were excited
to be yeah that's like row
as a row fill right out oh
yeah i think that yeah i know
i know i think that we both
know i think
i think that ah culturally it makes
sense if you know expression of emotion
is so the is suppressed is more
private yeah yeah and so you're just
it's just ingrained in you let be
such a bummer to grow up with
parents who don't laugh at anything you
do or yeah
would it yeah wonder what that yeah
i wonder if it would have driven
me to show oh that's right
think about the other side of it
where i genuinely laugh at everything that
my daughter doesn't oh yeah i never
got that either alright well i've had
yeah perfect little girl both ways it's
all i'm saying right both sides um
delaney thank you so much thank you
delaney for that question question
and that's gonna do it for this
episode of three medium but yeah we'll
be back in a couple of weeks
two hundred don't be frightened puts a
magic top hat on our heads we'll
be back yes someday um i thought
that was a lids ville thing and
then i just realised it's frosty you
fucking idiot yeah good-bye see my next
one