three
my sister amy why did you do
it
a oh no okay what's your day
right
i said thrice you so ito
hi everyone welcome to three me m
v premium episodes of threesome where we
answer your phone call yes that's the
deal we may is the special episode
where you have a voice that's right
the only guest will ever have and
it's you that's a good way to
put it other than page doesn't pay
players
change back to us and reggie miller
so forget the red man um so
we're of course we get
blue blue blue god damn this guy
of course we get these voicemails left
to us at hag claims a dot
com wonderful website everyone's going to it's
actually like book market it crashed right
because everyone was leaving messages you guys
broke the internet congrats yeah or at
least like around web page
you erect it so we are going
the second ralph movie yeah he me
to direct the internet and that second
movie yeah they'll third ralph movie there's
no well he fixed it at the
end of the second one i know
you're saying like the third movie should
be ralph fixes what was the it
that he wrecked in the first movie
that's his character yeah i understand
character who wrecks all sorts of things
he would resurrect every building like a
donkey kong style building like a building
that looks like donkey kong yeah yeah
no i would wreck one too honestly
no funky kong is a menace
don't you think that this a rip
off of king kong don't you call
it what gives you that idea
you know we don't talk enough about
diddy kong and his racers or puffy
kong puffy
the recently disgraced puffy girl that's right
eighty's retiree lee made a murder happen
alright let's hear this voicemail here we
go
hey freedom gang this is buddy longtime
sneak first time this just wondering who
are some other comedians or shows or
movies that kind of shaped your sense
of humour growing up you know for
example i was online vs corn so
i feel like simpsons on a show
take my sense of humour or alternatively
if that's a stupid question we already
answered it have any of you ever
had any recurring dreams for life either
as adults or children were figuring yeah
hey thanks buddy and yeah right
we've talked about the dreams on several
episodes you know what it reminds me
though i had a great dream last
night what you have what you have
what you have would you go on
a dream i had a dream that
it was me and super super ego
and andy daly were putting on a
show in my childhood backyard ooh
and it was i i don't know
it just made me feel so good
that's really interesting it was really fun
and it reminded me that the thing
that i really like to do sometimes
this is like when i go to
sleep when i'm laying in bed before
i'm sleep i tried to mentally walk
through my childhood home oh yeah
i envision see all the rooms and
like it it's i don't know why
they haven't i have a vision of
each of your childhood homes from the
our conversation wow
that are very specific valid it goes
dash is it like mash where i
live in imagine and oh no i
think that this chanting yeah i thought
i thought you meant the shows and
i'm like i don't think so do
you live in a tent
put a match mash the master means
you have a homemade still know the
army show um no way your army
show with eva hornby show and marry
your house is in my mind you
had kind of like a quintessential like
seventy s almost like now my brady
bunch but like like
adjacent yeah a lot of browns oranges
well especially are we had terrible gold
carpet oh gold well terrible i had
tan in my head it was like
thick pile
gomer pyle yeah he was pretty thick
he was
and your house is more so i
put like philadelphia city so i have
more like there's wallpaper yeah in and
then like it's like that house in
darkness on the edge of town the
album cover can picture it i also
feel that the upstate it was more
narrow and that the rooms were like
tightly connected
you're describing a row home okay which
we did not have we lived in
an area that had more space a
neighbor called mount airy and so we'd
like we had a yard and stuff
haha
yeah i really got a sense of
that house
he got blind picking blinds and wallpaper
what else do you need to do
i remember we did have blinds in
one room when i was very little
i remember we had the old-fashioned venetian
blinds yeah um but like those always
have bent they always got bent and
i remember they fell were like we
were fucking around and they fell off
that so like paul
oh and they cut my cousin's arm
off off yeah completely wow just for
minibike yeah maybe not many blinds venetian
blinds oh yeah dance now um we
so it was a it was an
old stone house and there were floors
it was three floors oh it was
three floors we've got to be my
old memory that you've erased now when
i did picture there being three fours
because i was picturing a tall thin
how did i erase that memory because
you just said it wasn't a row
home and i guess it's been worth
three floors like now i'm imagined i'd
change the shape of the house the
house now you can stretch the house
yeah and you um also had your
your connecting closet to the wall of
somebody cousin yes because they were
on the other side that's right that's
why pictured is a row homes like
a jack hill now like ah it
was a jack and jill closet know
when it was like duplex it was
a duplex yeah we shared a wall
with my cousin towels yeah and so
we would i my my ingenious code
where i would knock on the wall
with a hammer where until one time
only two chapman b and c
so on and so forth man of
course i did hammer hold until
then you eat the drywall but i
love appeared on that show drywall leaders
and i won and won ten thousand
dollars was it worth it ah no
i had to go to the hospital
and i still have to go every
week yes i can be sure let's
be paying all the money that you
won oh and then some yeah yeah
yeah yeah
no i'm i'm i'm deep in debt
from eating tribal um the first question
was about things that influenced us oh
no yeah yeah yeah comics are you
know you don't know i do go
i was just gonna say um i
relate to the simpsons things i watched
a lot of simpsons but a lot
of that was just me looking to
see how back when my brother was
law
laughing oh bango like checking in to
be like was that funny was that
funny was ending and that was it
his laughs actually influenced a lot of
what i found funny when we watch
tv together right i just i remember
looking at him all the time just
being like usually they were live in
laugh track and i was while i
was going like is this something okay
huh
and what about the things you were
doing no no no just to be
like yep he was on the simpsons
it was probably funny yeah but like
i probably didn't get it right
yeah i remember laughing at steve martin
albums that i've for sure if there
was a lot of stuff i didn't
understand i mean yeah a lot of
it was great for kids because he
was just silly yeah but then there
were there were sometimes some jokes that
you had to be a grown up
together but i was still like the
grass oh yeah i remember my sister
for my birthday one year my sister
was gonna buy me a gift and
i said i want cruel shoes by
steve martin the book yes and she
did not want to buy it for
me because she thought you're not you're
too young you're not going to get
it and i was like i'm going
to get it yeah and then i
of course i read and i loved
it my name guy yeah still i
loved it i think it can be
aspirational when you don't get something like
i want to get that so i'll
go investigated and figured out exactly i've
told this story i'm sure but when
i was in seventh grade i was
reading jerry seinfeld's book signings and i'm
like
yeah i gave it to my funny
science teacher who i thought i had
a crush and i'm kind of probably
but i was like kill like this
because he's so funny and then he
never gave it back and i owe
many you owning two i was in
my mind i was loaning it oh
but you never said but i was
sure i wasn't clear at all about
how i handed over
this right the dude fell that i
think that happens to everybody at some
point where you loan something to someone
and they do not realize it's a
loner yeah they just keep it why
you know what i don't like those
when people loaned me books that i
didn't ask to read i this is
how yeah that's a different thing i
have your couple of myself from someone
where i'm like
i don't want to read it but
i need you i want to get
back with you and like i'm like
i feel like bad that i still
have it because it's been years now
but i feel like i should read
it but it's not my i have
a density i guess somebody loaned me
that i think is coming up on
ten years i have one to congratulate
that i what is it like it's
ah an orson
wells movie called it's all true oh
yeah the magic one yeah yeah oh
no that's fs fs fs perfect oh
this is like ah i think it's
like a recut of yeah something that
he did when he was young isn't
it on netflix or something it might
be you could probably give it back
and just go like i'm gonna watch
it on netflix not huh
well i finally feel like i gotta
wait even longer to give back because
it's gonna be funnier i still have
a copy of clinton's person's death open
lent me yeah oh by the way
i meant to get this bag t
hussey i feel like if you're relented
dvd it had to be ten years
ago so i'm like when did i
last have a deep i'm like right
so hey i have a copy of
clifford graham ryan my hairy dog no
and it's no it's actually not about
a big red dog it's about a
little
light boy bunny wears a little red
sweater does so i was very close
um did you watch her no i
have seen it yeah but i don't
think i don't even know if i
saw it ever from that dvd right
like i think
i need you sought from context clues
yeah there's a really funny scene that
i found on instagram that was really
making me laugh were just martin short
so funny but just like mocking charles
grey what a strange movie i know
i love it it's great i'm glad
it happened yeah when our world is
better for it it's not a movie
that i
that i i don't think i'll ever
watch it again you know what i
mean i just thought recently i know
you did honey how do you know
you know everything he hosted some shit
about it online
of course everything's a big event with
this guy who posts everyday just live
life was really nice so i talked
doing post he's always talking to the
camera going today many watching it and
post billion you posted you literally are
men you were in it paul o
duo is there is this true or
not true
every day scots like always talking to
the camera being like hey guys yeah
followers just waking up my day going
up to date sir have everyone's doing
my makeup day routine to get ready
making ready with me and once you
give your makeup routine like there's nothing
left right like you can't just go
like oh here's a new makeup routine
that's why yeah somebody yeah it means
they're gonna die
oh yeah if you give you make
there's always somebody playing and people are
like now i'm doing the almond routine
or like the strawberry makeup which there's
always fuck noisy new things like well
why did i watch your old one
it's always based around a small food
well there's a lot of them are
gonna be like my routine there's strawberry
to make up i saw it on
tiktok so i had to try it
you put it in
anyway and then they go like here's
the steps oh yeah you put it
on your face or does doing takes
to ah invisible camera
we all just take we don't know
they're taping three am to put clips
online no
here's i'm gonna this is a pet
peeve i'm gonna put out there right
now whoa mama see ya to people
mr ma ma ma ma se ma
ma sa ma ma coo sa i
didn't give you warning that we were
being filmed on newcomers so they'll say
they know i know by now yeah
that if you show up to that
fucking studio they're going to be okay
i look like shit and all
the video i'm like because i i
i don't really stop filming podcast get
ready stop filming what are the beauty
of podcast was that it didn't matter
what i looked like it does help
to promote podcast because people are much
more interested in watching a video people
talking than a video then making a
tv show let's make a tv show
that's a good point yeah thank
yes
from the mind of paul tomkins just
stop filming him yeah i hate it
okay i really don't want to be
filmed you guys can film yourself like
in the early days i remember just
yourself or me oh yeah before social
media or actually at the dawn of
social media when you would go do
a fucking
you like road gigs yet to go
do the rate local morning radio show
and it's like it's so antithetical to
a comedian's life yeah because you work
at night it's like yeah five am
and being like yeah who cares yeah
and you're trying to yeah you're just
stuck in the middle of the night
getting road beef yeah you're getting road
huh you fucking gross
you got a hamburgers lauren yeah and
please not hamper your fourth meal
and then they started taking pictures and
it's like no man fucking doing it
sam him yeah stop it stop it
ah suh ah well if if anyone's
interested i watched bob hope movies all
right that's gonna do it for this
three medium ah thank you buddy for
that for everybody and and look if
you want to leave us a message
of course you do it at hag
claims eight dot com bookmark that bitch
make it your home page every all
your it's your most trusted news source
yes oh my god we're gonna start
putting news on there yeah it's going
to be all about us
and we're going to investigate it it's
not going to be news you can
get from any other source it's the
news you can use yeah hey lose
yeah use it and lose ag choose
it if you want we don't give
you choice she ws you can use
it and lose it yeah the choice
in your mouth yours put it in
your mouth food in your mouth put
it in your mouth that's food
in your mouth you and you will
be older anyone have to wait soon
i'll tell you who to not shake
my sense of humor is the beach
boys i fucking well they were really
funny but just weren't a fan right
we can't we have to save something
for the episode they have the big
giant harmonica hated let's get let's see
was funny because on the put this
right
goodbye goodbye