three
i'm going to get it right i
know you are i'm gonna do anything
i can to get it right
mc right i'm doing wareham on a
roll hearing
yeah you didn't do it now i
do it oh my god oh my
god really panicked yeah really did but
you know what we still got here
you know and it's one thing i'm
learning is that if we say the
wrong word the show still goes on
yeah i'm taking a step back to
listen and learn yeah me too that's
right we're all
oh by the way on this episode
of three meme we're all just listening
to each other none of us are
going to talk yeah and no one's
gonna listen to them now let's get
interrupt and no one's gonna talk and
no one's gonna do anything but listen
mister gonna sit here staring at each
other listening to each other it's gonna
be amazing now let's roll that beautiful
bean footage
if you would like to call us
go to hag claims eight dot com
and leave a voice message on that
website hag claims dot com yeah like
a person did this person has ah
something that they want to ask us
the threesome three medium team what name
this person is well i think they're
gonna say it themselves so i don't
want to i want
to bury the lima was just told
me i'm in a loud environment you're
in a loud environment oh so met
up ya i'm decimal oh ninety are
we talking ninety decibels some lot we
do scream that's true we did scream
threesome yes and three me yeah screaming
does make that much co crazy screaming
makes the heart grow fonder
yeah so if anyone screams your watch
will tell you someone screaming good tip
well yeah they're like get away from
that screaming person's very passive aggressive about
it it says things are getting kind
of loud oh hey may wanna move
rooms just thought or go get help
you fucking asshole yeah sure i mean
we're honoring jenna vaizey situation
even if it were offering like should
i call nine one one for you
and then show like hold on one
one which one to save your ass
in it i believe in the u
k it's nine nine nine noi noi
annoying noi noi noi nine
alright this comes to us from someone
and they're gonna say what their name
is i think but let's list out
i hope so
hello yeah hello paul scott lauren this
is colin from phoenix arizona um i
would like to know if you guys
had to go to mcdonalds what you
might each get
um we talked about that a little
bit extra all i guess i don't
know if we actually said our goodbye
oh okay colin okay she says we
urge let us say goodbye to you
we're trying to talk here goodbye call
and goodbye to you um if i
had to go i don't think we
set our orders i think we said
which fast food place we would go
to that could be
true yes we would go
cool up cool up with order on
the was it the anniversary of harris's
death or was it his birthday it
might have been his birthday she would
order mcdonald's every year by the way
yeah everyone should die on their birthday
yes simplify just it's whatever year it
is just die alone i think just
what how about this year everyone dies
your
birthday is you will all do it
ah well let's all make a pack
everyone listening let's die on our birthdays
if your birthday is already passed die
right now
um
but we would we get we would
get his order which was like chicken
mcnuggets chicken thing and make no bigs
shut the fuck up well why can't
i make fun of that come on
mcnuggets is fun
chicken mcnuggets good i just love this
more but some that didn't funny and
obviously i'm a baby it's actually adorable
or a bit of a baby
um but she was all she can
make nuggets and she's very tribes
cheeseburger
the abominable dr fries ooh that sounds
like a good movie you just write
that i did mail it to the
vga really are you
juniors you go you go do what
else not i'm not doing cosby i'm
doing the what did you mean no
one was thinking you were you did
i did think i because he was
doing it i was just his eyes
lit up with bill cosby pictures in
his eyeballs
gotta be a bill cosby air
like what was your chicken mcnuggets it
was chicken mcnuggets schieber errors freebies
and maybe i can't remember what his
order was but but when i take
no there would never be a drink
involved but what i would order my
swingers elf you know what i would
love at mcdonalds zozo sundays oh yeah
oh sure ice cream machine broken yeah
always yeah classic hey hartford
sunday i i only if i eat
a burger from mcdonald's it's plain with
just a bud in the meat why
has the time been idiot my entire
life wow my mom likes it that
way and then i was trained to
like it for my mother and it's
good enough for me as a kid
i always ate it that way and
i i won't continue the way that
you like it but i will get
typically i'll get
chicken mcnuggets and i'll put the sauce
on the burger now put the sauce
on the nubs and i'll do put
the soil some of those ten piece
nowadays but six to ten weight on
your ham boob would you get ah
but like the contrasts thing at nothing
end of april much as i'm desc
gusted and it's untrue for other locations
like other other chains right there's just
no way about having donald's burger wow
but yeah i like mcnugget and i
like frames yeah and i love for
eps it's all gala oh i'll get
a six piece to attend peace depending
on my appetite and how
a large fry and make flurry if
i'm really feeling special wow and i
usually won't get that but that's if
a while i'll do fries and mc
flurry as just an order okay
it's just a great combo high cold
you have a lot i get the
same thing every time what's a double
quarter pounder with cheese yeah i'll get
the meal get the front and just
like a trainer or does that feel
too gluttonous it feels i feel i
feel like i'm not being glad if
i was a double quarter pounder right
yeah yeah have somebody i knew
we all know to have found you
have to do so much math in
your head every time you order can't
do it what am i beautiful mind
yeah yeah looking around seeing all those
equations just a dumb pewter powder weigh
half a pound knew it before cooking
before cooking after cooking always more yeah
because it's big and strong and they
put all that shit on it that
you don't like yeah get that out
here
what's the mc flurry when it was
first introduced i'm sure i've told this
before oh please tell us a story
you've told before when they give you
the show sportage comfort food you think
it's a straw because there's a big
hole yes and so i thought i'd
try drink this thing like it was
a drink no i almost like passed
out from either so
it's hard yeah right yeah just like
ice cream i don't i guess when
it starts to melt maybe or maybe
that's the suck up that huge amount
it's a prank was f a hole
in the that goes all the way
down yes yes yes yes yes there's
like a little tunnel through they know
it it should be they should fill
that with eminem's or whatever can
yeah put into it yes and have
it come through the spoon yeah have
come through the phantom of the come
through this book have that come through
this you know that book is at
fast food nation i don't remember but
where they talk about how um what
mcdonald's does is they they they have
it it's like scientific now you can
have an eyedropper and before i was
more religious
yeah yeah no but you can put
like one drop of a liquid on
a piece of paper and suddenly the
whole room smells like meat and that's
what they put on the fries you
can do that with any water in
any paper
do it right now just do it
right now you'll see no but that's
they they that's what they're using now
because it smells like meat and it
gets you hungry or whatever but it's
i'm getting angry it's all it's all
just chemicals this is making me want
mcdonald thirty eight in and out today
so i don't really want it right
now but in general i already had
a grilled cheese sandwich huh wow yeah
it was
vicious let's talk about what we eat
today okay what do we have for
breakfast i had a two body flip
yogurt
almond cocoa something it's like chocolate chips
cocoa niles almonds
and then i had to string cheeses
and a bag of pretzels
and then i had
a hamburger from in and out fries
and a seven up and then i
had half a bag of peanut m
and m's and two ritz peanut butter
crackers what about those cadbury mini eggs
and eight for cadbury mini eggs for
probably five
i had ah on earth
ah what's up an egg oh trader
joe's vegetarian sausage patty okay now also
had some cinnamon sugar serial that's organic
apparently it's good odds are gonna go
what's good for you um i have
some v eight juice oh some yeah
i didn't drink the whole bottle
i just bought myself a glass of
it because didn't use a come in
the little many things yeah they've still
does but when i get the big
bottle it's a very nineties beverage it
felt more like a seventies and eighties
to me i and the other classic
i kind of had a v eight
where you slap your own head yeah
but they still want a beta yes
no if any beverage that would that
would they
depict in the commercial somebody ordering some
dumb drink and then somebody next to
them like channel v eight and then
the person the first person will be
humiliated had one yes they're filled with
self photos too late then i had
grilled jesus and deutschen do you make
yeah my myself without what's your technique
what kind of bread using whatever breads
in the that's right makes the personality
and they're okay
it was some sweet bread from somewhere
deep butter the grain the side i
butter the bread the one side of
it both sides both sides dramas
trump does apple butter on both sides
of mines very fine butter on both
sides and ah and some pop chips
yeah it was a little gone like
many slices of cheese you put on
that three three and are they all
the same cheese they're all the same
cheese but merely something to mix it
up sure this is all the same
cheeses flavor of pop
rip ah seasalt nice um then i
had a couple spoonfuls of creamy peanut
butter not enough thighs my brand what
to call mera nafa mirage familiar with
this i'll be googling oh please you
gotta get into it what do you
eat then i had oh wow
oh he's still going pieces that i
had to cadbury mini eggs here right
and then a little ramekin of pretzels
okay all in all i'm done eating
for the rest of my life
yeah i finally caught up oh good
okay maranatha marin maric nah man nah
sir p na bay p nine being
let's see okay i will ask why
is maranatha peanut butter so good
ah why are you asking are you
guys from retail meat eat it why
is just cheated computers candy don't cry
because it's over smile because it happened
i always say yes okay what did
you okay i e first while my
coffee was brewing
i had a banana that whole bullshit
really okay you're right
i haven't eaten
you know hanging open land tipped you
off i knew you never had to
put down your life um banana and
then coffee with a little bit of
sugar-free hazelnut creamer
i forgot to say that i had
two cups of black coffee actually no
i three cups of black coffee oh
my god because janie went out for
breakfast she only had one cup of
coffee at home and i finished off
the pot whoa and then i still
felt exhausted interesting it's so you won't
be able to sleep tonight no um
ok
so then i had that banana then
i had what is the stuff that
okay cool ups been making it she
puts it in jar i know it's
like jelly it feels like a yogurt
kind of thing but okay it's a
little black chia yeah she it's chia
or something and then she made all
this you know i put strawberries in
it oh this sounds like
what steve and miranda would eat oh
they were doing their tv time yeah
thirdly home in brooklyn warehouse that's that
always looks fun the hell away he
says or chia they're watchable
so i have a cow nibs sent
up then what did i do but
okay go
i had some water dressing already counting
water yes no you didn't mention your
liar fuck i yes i took all
my pills yeah by putting um electrolytes
into my water hello law ran out
i didn't have many stay home wait
for electron just one but i was
using element elementi
have you ever smelled i think i've
had yeah yeah it's like oh colby
we okay enough with this with spelling
things that weigh up the vowel spellings
up spell all the regular way fuckin
spelled the regular way or come up
with a different name by grinder
put the e back in put otherwise
i would use you anymore i refused
to grind to tumble
okay hold on then i had ah
that i had not a question of
sweet kale with chicken salad well that
sounds fancy breakfast salad knows this breakfast
is long gone okay okay it was
lunchtime okay you just had a banana
for breakfast no and the gea in
the with strong yeah she chicha chicha
so then i
had the salad your champ
and then he hg i had one
cadbury what are they called me a
mini egg that lauren gave me i
huh and then i had that little
tiny bowl full of pretzels which were
terrible will you beat in the mini
acre
right when we doing alfred that's right
i love butler damn butler did that
line
but by the way when we're taping
this the day's only halfway through we
still got a whole half day of
eating to go oh i'm gonna be
eating a lot more this evening folks
and i'll update you all on every
single bite and why each step of
the uber called uber isn't a play
on anything like very fat yeah very
like uber like uber alice yes like
deutschland obr yes exactly yeah hitler shit
and lift i get you're getting you're
getting right although you know
it's the baby they should just it
should be l i f t yeah
yes can you imagine i imagine it
first or whoever was like hey maybe
we should spell these things different in
order to keep your copy was the
first one i don't know
i'm trying to think of any pizza
any pizza can you think of any
pizza right now paul ah pca caesars
little caesars
a little caesar implies the existence of
a big caesar had they steal caesar's
name we should start big sees i
guess favorite pieces fair use that's why
caesar can't sue them yes he's in
laura j honey we should start being
caesars and they are big pizzas yes
and we're like what are you going
to go to little caesars or they're
even small
cooler than little caesar yes but that's
a surprise no one knows yes fido
first day because we shoot them really
close up oh yeah look enormous and
we do force perception like a person
standing next to a grand canyon sized
pizza
is his big caesar's nose really big
no no nose yeah yeah it's like
a whole empty triangle yeah yeah yeah
it's an empty triangle yeah like the
guy and ah fall out
i don't know walton goggins walton google
e ma a an ad for that
they're making a fallout show based on
the video game i've seen that ad
it was starring very good sweet bitter
and then ah walton goggins playing sweet
do neural that's i can't remember her
name but we saw her that's what
we call her in our households because
she
in a show called sweet bitter
like oh sweet bidders in this oh
that's a cute name she's very cute
actress i can't remember her name but
she's very good during a lot of
stuff she's british
hello but she played americans allied oh
isn't that why unfair that's acting dear
boy it's unfair that's all you have
to do somebody said why don't you
try it to her and she said
ok well now she's doing an epstein
i beg your pardon or ella purchased
you have an island that pulls into
what's her name is zambrano do you
know what maybe
yes and she's also in yellow jackets
oh yep i recognize her from that
oh i've not seen either these things
first season of yellow jackets really fun
i fell off in the second season
so i can't speak to that i
did too i did too the first
one really got me hooked it was
fun she has a kind of captivating
look about it doesn't she
she's beautiful beautiful eyes shameful rice big
eyes great riffs huge risks ooh i
love those big fat wrists
thanks for listening three visiting don't forget
to leave us a message and a
hag claims eight dot com and you'll
get to hear everything that we ate
and that's the collin yes thank you
collin if finally your question fit into
what we always talk about which is
everything we eat for the day yes
and we'll see you
in a couple of weeks by