laredo
three yeah
ah um um it's called thredup um
get with it plum three to much
um it's a bit cramped house here
ya right down santa claus
a welcome to our special christmas episode
of oh that's right a's the day
where we exchanged gifts yeah it's christmas
in may is it me what month
is this i think right now is
april yeah when whenever there are timing
on a roll i'm just like i
know it's not like you know
i'm like you just know what it's
not like you don't know the table
but you know it's not june like
when i go when i go to
park on the street and like there's
like a crazy sign it's like thursday
from toe-to-toe well it's not thursday i
don't know what day it is i
don't know what time it is but
i know it's not thursday i don't
think this really does sound very specific
but i
i don't know that i've ever experienced
any relate to me it's okay if
you don't i mean usually if it's
ever said i was reliable
thank you to um if it's monday
if it's if the sign says monday
then i'll go like i know it's
not monday that's what i mean yeah
like i was literature last monday yes
back there were just thursdays a little
tougher i just did not sure yeah
yeah but i know when it's monday
because i've the day before scott said
i've had the holy sacrament of confession
and um i have taken the eucharist
ah and i have one giant meal
of lasagna yes i love lasagna sundays
you don't need it i'm manila girl
you know i eat it on mondays
like a real garfield
sir garfield hated mondays so much but
did he ever try eating the lasagna
on monday to me yeah he would
have to eat the the lasagna mondays
in order to feel normal just level
out you mean to feel you mean
to feel normal
yeah but i care about monday eat
the shit it's like you can make
your day sort of like why i'm
like every day you're like why didn't
he do because i'm like why is
like the early morning coming i've never
seen you this worked up i've just
i'm like every monday i'm like why
why is it like this why why
i like this garfield doesn't have a
job what does he care
yeah and also he hates john who
goes to work on mondays so we
give me happy yo finally that asshole
gene does his weekend acts john because
it's like you literally don't have lezana
you don't have a little box general
blanket you know any of this shit
without john does he hate john he
kind of well he has contempt for
sure
just kind of took that as a
given enough i don't know if i
don't despise him but he's not nice
tortured by the i don't think they're
cuddling the text of the sacred text
you don't think they're cuddling at night
i don't think so i think he
hates john but he still cuddles with
him i think he probably goes like
at his feet maybe you'll probably like
his feet whatever gets you through the
nih that's all right it's garfield
john lennon wrote that about garfield yeah
that is me he loved garfield one
hundred percent john lennon loved the funnies
he loved marmaduke he loved high and
low elo you know he did his
most of his if you send documentary
he gets all of its inspiration from
inspo from comics ratio who
are the beatles of the funnies garfield
obviously is john because he's sarcastic oh
wait we're gonna pluck characters from each
from demonstrate different doe ringo's stillbirth wait
wait wait because gilbert uses classes john
john from garfield not garfield no graphene
garfield garfield is john lennon oh okay
just sarcastic and he's biting and he's
funny and he's like you know very
musical and he's written so many great
songs i mean has there ever been
george and plovers bloggers no one even
knows that comment some people do i
think i think one of the
yeah yeah i can't argue with that
yeah it's right there i think one
of the cows from far side who
would they be they would be why
does one allow this was the ladies
ten eyeglasses yeah you you're going backwards
like shouldn't it be you think of
the beetle and then you think of
the comic but you're like your little
bailey
okay is all of them see he's
all of them all the characters from
beetle bailey or either of these already
know bally's rainbow because but i think
milhouse what was her name oh yes
the general secretary that he was always
ogling we got we got garfield is
john lennon yeah i'm gilbert is ringo
then who's left paul is fucker bean
yeah funky winker bean what about dagwood
big sandwiches is that george yeah i
think so
so and no one he can be
a tsar
because no one really wrote i mean
like i don't really think about brenda
starr what i wrote about prince valiant
who is thinking about it because he's
got that similar haircut yeah you know
what the beatles owe a lot to
prince valiant they really you know what
they should be what does that comic
where it's like they're like um the
people who have ah
sort of those hats with like tusks
on them
hagar the horrible there you go yeah
with what was his wife's name i
don't know
yeah me either i got well no
no no we can't live in a
world arena known this where we don't
know haig's wife's name i think any
letter like the second google's hell yeah
hell yeah merry hell colca marry you
couldn't be further off okay can i
just tell you i own i typed
in hagar but i will
is it hagar hagar yeah aim over
the a or like the slacks it
okay like the horribles whites people also
ask okay so people also what do
they ask about hae years but are
still alive what is it prickly seed
case what is his net worth what
is a prickly seed
what is before two poets who was
the shakespearian king can i go now
the password these these are all crossword
questions oh hey hagar must also be
a crossword question like isis why this
is coming yeah yeah yeah so is
that so are we to believe that
the claim to fame of hagar is
just that
they gotten a bunch of calm across
words and that's like not that's it
now because i'm looking mad up all
the searches all about crosswords there are
so many people who are in crosswords
all the time like fucking ken olin
constantly in crosswords just because of his
fucking weird ass name and i can't
get a single one
because you'd be the whole middle line
you're new to tangling and you're asking
too much if you want to be
the whole middle line did you know
that ken owen's name used to be
kin loin and it seemed a little
heroes so he changed it he anna
grimaced to ken lyon oh he missed
that one he wants to all in
that's too bad he went with lion
ken
yeah
ah yeah that's holding ken olin up
to the sun
lauren i've been looking into sun i
would love to see a new thirty
something with you in the lead i'd
love that absolutely one hundred percent yeah
but all the rest is the original
cast members yep
and they're pretending to be thirty
i would love that i would love
that so much um actually i just
watched while maybe i shouldn't get into
it but i just watched captain america
civil war for newcomers know ah saw
tom holland as spiderman for the first
time where and in the film
and yep haha and he was moving
image and talking himself and he was
a real teen which i liked because
i was just you know thinking about
how people were cast are often cast
older to play younger and he was
only eighteen or something when he oh
really i didn't know that you still
around that way that's what i've heard
yes around that age so twenty three
when you guys were when you guys
were younger and you were on yesterday
yeah yes of course when you are
working together on mister show and whatnot
and was there ever a time where
you traveled together and you shared a
hotel room know because we did not
overlap on miss yeah we did different
oh i know that's ever been said
different seasons just like the richard bachman
we have we ever wanted people to
guess it nobody guessed it and i
guess i just built the bean snail
scout sorry yeah yeah finally well yeah
we have that big contest going on
where people would be flown out ah
business class with yeah a friend and
they'd be fazed we would scream
even with floating yeah yeah like just
all the play oh day oh hey
and no one's one so and you've
given it away but that's okay alright
all the flow days has expired i
think the only time i had to
share was for some reason like the
third year of south by southwest
ah map ranga couldn't find a hotel
room and i was like not just
stay with me it's the only time
he shared i heard eight billion times
um i think women do that more
than men do ah is that because
they like to rub up navy maybe
not no no no i've shared with
actually men scott they do enjoy hair
yeah what's that were
it what would you say about my
hair would you whoo i didn't i
wasn't talking about your hair mr the
world revolves around my head but is
it what do you think of it
well looks really good under your hat
oh well i work with wearing hats
wouldn't you put a hat on i
wish i did my hooks like fucking
ass know you're hot
you can um i my my lovely
bride will often she has a girls
trip every year with the with the
group of ah of women that she's
friends with and they will often share
hotel room oh yeah well it's totally
fun with with your friends yeah um
wild horses we for many years we
would share every time we traveled anywhere
but then we got to a point
where we were like you know what
it'd be really great if we didn't
just to have that space yeah my
hope and p and do whatever you
wish yeah yeah we were talking about
hotel rooms while i was i was
an austin um ah for the last
few days yeah and we ah i
was i was so happy
api that not only was there a
door on the bathroom in this hotel
room even though i'm there by myself
but there was also a mirror shared
with aaron there was no door on
the bathroom even shower and everything i'm
like so if i was there's always
my way with a romantic partner ooh
i wouldn't necessarily
want to have this all open no
no but i've i've wondered that you
know like i've always gone there with
cool up but i've wondered that about
a couple who who is going away
for the first time together and suddenly
they have a base either a sliding
door with flats or you know or
no door it's like what do you
you know do you have do you
have to sketch
feel like oh i'm going to the
restaurant for a second and then you
go to
actually no i'm going to take a
shit i know a couple who were
performers on a cruise and they shared
a room obviously they were a couple
but they didn't like to poop near
each other so one of them they
would go poop in the public restrooms
on the cruise instead of doing oh
i know who you're talking about i
know yes
i do but then that means we
might i would be shocked can i
type it in the chat yeah i've
seen i can't even get the chat
by the way after last week's tobacco
i'm i'm on my phone now yeah
i'm cool it's cool scott is that
yeah you're a cool guy did you
see it in the chat paul know
i don't know who that is but
you know what shocking
i have i know ah the same
thing about another couple type it in
the dat type it in the chat
paul type it in the chat type
and chat da times it and the
chat i can't get my mouse to
turn on and connect i get okay
there it goes
oh my god alright my computer is
so far away from me when i
do these it is it is very
far away from you there are so
many songs like that that i think
about that then i learned i learned
in sunday school that i'd just go
through my head at random times all
the time that
do your ears hang low is one
that i yeah you guys ever seen
that one i did not know that
until i was an adult i knew
it as a child i thought as
an adult and i've since forgotten it
decides i'm gonna hit you in the
eye of africa ahead for my memory
um yeah but so many of those
songs are so weird there was one
about um ah
evolution that we sang at church which
was like i'm not made of a
monkey among he's not made of me
oh no
the earth is just five thousand years
old db bitty lately oh wait i'm
missing the chat oh okay oh you
gotta get on that chat about the
shit couple you don't even know about
who's pooping in the pudding there's multiple
people pooping in different places it's so
fantastic that's the thing is there's there's
poo
oop everywhere oh it's all over we're
swimming in it i mean look on
a cruise ship gcs is a bound
they're made of human shit and some
dolphin shit wow you really say that
with such disdain i like how you're
saying that
dolphin shit out of the out of
the blowhole or everything goes out of
the bottle everything every it just in
and out in and out we got
food we got we got water we
got shit use your ein
yeah mouth of theirs and then of
course the the fluid of of generations
so when they when they want to
have a baby dolphin they have to
like get that whole right up against
the lady and like yeah just take
it just take it you know we
don't think that much about the amount
of fish poop that's in the ocean
when we're swimming in it if i
remember see like when i first lay
learned that fish could shit like friends
had a um yeah when like a
little slayer neighbors hefty yeah neighbors had
a fish tank and like seeing that
line of garbage sick to me yeah
it's honestly really disgusting yeah and it's
actually not okay laura no you going
to
dude dissuade your child from ever you
know how this is where i got
my first goldfish was like i wanted
at a carnival yeah like oh yeah
awesome and then it's the worst fucking
patter you're gonna say like no no
no no jackie's definitely try to win
a fish at the farewell yeah that's
so fun it's like a childhood moment
i come home you name it it
die
dies to hold its
ah la da la but i would
get our fish for real i had
fish knows little i really enjoyed having
fish um and it was fun to
pick them out at the pet store
and think that's cute and it's like
a pretty easy pet the only problem
is cleaning the tank which i didn't
i don't pay ever did as just
gonna get dirty and dirty yeah fish
dies and then you flush
down the toilet i know my friend
has a um carnival fish that's been
going on six years now
ooh i had my carnival fish why
is that gross scott why are they
the worst bets i need to know
mike my carnival fish it had such
a dirty bowl that it while i
was sleeping it jumped out of the
bowl and onto me and it was
like kill me like you just wanted
thirty water please snuggle with me they're
just so grossing that i get that
i still can smell that smell of
the cleaning the tank and the shit
and yeah imagine if if like there
was such bad air pollution that you
killed yourself yeah you'd just like joe
duffy or i could drown i'm gonna
drown i'm going to go make the
ocean
this sucks
i wish you didn't think it was
ever jumped off the earth do you
think he would be so rad that
if you let me so dealer yom
you jumped in the air you go
to space probably there is that that
what's the thing about jumping like if
the elevator starts plunging oh yeah
right before you make a bomb joe
biden all the time when i know
it's not it's not for plunging it's
like you can do it when you're
um i mean it is for that
but don't do it as a fun
thing to feel like you're flying for
a second when the elevator is coming
to a i mean maybe it's something
that just works with your kid but
when the elevator is coming to a
halt at the floor right before it
does you go you
jump and then you are basically in
the air like an extra second but
paula
the the thing i'm talking about is
a thing where there's like an herb
you to know your god i know
the thing you're talking about it was
lauren that interrupted it i'm just sharing
other information
how dare you i'm born i want
to make sure that you didn't just
gloss over my thing and i never
wanted to ask questions about god i
never aware i never would gloss over
anything anyone says in the show i
don't want to skip ahead and or
and here's the idea here's here's the
full cost of your elders that if
let's say the elevator is it
it snaps it's cables and you're like
oh and then you go you know
what floor you got on you know
what floor when the cable snapped and
so all you have to do is
count just like guess the distance and
the velocity so it's like thunder lightning
sort of count the second verse and
then you get
to the bottom like right before you
get to the bottom just jump in
there and that's really supposed to stop
the damage from breaking your bones and
squishing into a size of a can
of soup exactly but what does it
what does the physics about it like
why would that work supposedly because you
are not hitting you're not hitting the
ground when the
thing is hitting the ground so it's
like you're not feeling the pressure of
that yeah but you're still gonna fall
to the ground one millisecond later yeah
we're crashing here with the same force
of yes you're also fully yeah i
also wonder if you would even be
able to jump because the velocity of
ah i'm sure you know and and
by the way you're so scare
hard you're not going i gotta jump
in eight seven sit no no no
i'm i'm wetting my pants and i'm
going mommy mommy mommy i love yeah
yeah although you're telling me though that
this conversation wouldn't flash into your mind
and you wouldn't just try it look
if it happened i would definitely have
this flash in my mind and i
definitely try it if i tried it
and i'm not saying that i did
but i lived whoa it's it's real
it's real and i tried at night
and i did not die and you
die wow yeah i'm dead guys did
you see that video of the guy
who jumped out of the plane and
his parachute didn't open yeah anyway cover
by peter gabriel oh no i'm talking
about a different thing actually
we know the one that i saw
was a guy who like his friend
was taping him falling to the ground
like oh yeah i'm going to tape
you parachuting out of this airplane but
the guy's chute didn't open and he
fell on the ground and the guy
then the guy taping him is like
holy shit oh no and runs up
to him and the guy gets up
and is like oh my god oh
my god i can't believe
i'm still alive oh my god and
he like gets up and walks away
from it that's insane no i saw
the i saw a video or not
the video i saw a picture of
the fucking video of but this news
story about this youtube guy who flew
a small plane crashed the pretended it
was crap it was
is malfunctioning and he jumped out of
it filming himself yeah and then i
see the plane just he did shit
it just fell into the fuckin mountains
ah but yeah for for this was
video he did this he faked please
wasn't problematic he had a ah full
of deviation lie
and all this stuff of like mayday
mayday it's crashing and all that kind
of stuff and then why didn't you
just all of that i think so
and then he parachuted out of it
um and videoed the whole thing for
youtube and then they figured out later
it was a stunt and he crashed
the plane intentionally and so they you
know revoked his license maybe he's going
to be rested i have no idea
he should be arrested because you could
i have heard someone yeah yeah of
course next plane could crashed into mount
rushmore
and i will be honest day because
it locked his beard off can you
imagine i think youtube should d monetize
his videos that's real punishment like he
should be paying us to watch his
videos yes and he has to do
and there's going to be ads where
he it's just him apologizing yeah to
us personally and like you get to
skip one
add but then the second i was
like guys you can't skip this one
i really am sorry
speaking of ah things that you have
to take for people how's your cameo
going oh my god okay we are
you living in a cameo mansion we
have to talk about this because cameo
last week we talked about how you
are gonna join and you are going
to do you're like um your bit
of saying when you were when you
were like me i'm i'm only gonna
charge fifty dollars right
i did say lowball i thought you
should get mine that i mean i
didn't want to i just had it's
all very new to me and i
looked at what some other people were
charging and i'm like oh well yeah
that person has to charge that because
otherwise they would be inundated with ah
with requests yeah and um and so
i started at fifty and then ah
i was
i was told by my person that
cameo ah that i were a broker
record yes oh freaking dumbest person to
ever join cameo yes they simply i
don't say yeah but it's hurtful to
hear we want to get into the
numbers jameson
really good for it too and then
when she said yeah you're the dumbest
person and i was like oh why
did you call me oh i'm busy
i was asleep
but there were so many people requesting
you in a very short amount time
that cameo had you raise the price
or they raised the price for yeah
they said i want to do yeah
they said you want to raise the
price and i was like yes yeah
because it's so much to do you'll
never have time if you don't you
know you have to kind of curb
the so now you're a slave to
cameo
where you have to do all these
things how many do you have to
do i have to do i think
two hundred and sixty oh my that's
so many it's been one lie wait
paul it's been one day it's been
it's been a couple of days it's
been it's been two days they aren't
they have slowed down obviously since because
now it's three hundred dollars yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah um
and still there's some most people get
it ah that like what the what
my format is some people are still
asking for specific requests i'm like i'm
waiting on those because i don't want
to like do them yeah that's pretty
much it um because i mean because
i'm not going to do it i'm
like people are asking for specific voices
whatever
like i'm just not going to do
that and i have a video that
explains here's what i'm gonna do right
but i think people just don't watch
the videos which would you do the
werner herzog voice right now for us
know will not do that come on
we love it no i keep people
vard i love world separate i keep
those worlds separate i'm just paul on
this show just
just good old paul put from philly
so no i'd rather you did a
character make me happy you're probably yeah
please voice yeah because when you do
the voice is so fine oh and
you were done the voice during sex
yeah where i sit in a chair
and then i turn around and i
say yes okay
your joke that you made yeah i
wait till i hear the noises of
sex that i like
yeah my wife is having with someone
else and then when it sounds good
to me i turn around to see
who it is that sounds good to
me that sounds great to me that
sounds fun to me but that sounds
neat to me so what does janie
bought a gun yeah she's got a
gucci handbag she bought a yacht no
yeah yeah yeah handbag that's too much
you know that's too much all it's
too much where did she get the
ya i'm really nervous for she got
it at the mall know the yamaha
yes actually but that next cheap yacht
that's not going to be a good
yacht it's still expensive next to the
the store where you you get but
a piano there's no need
sure that guys i mean she did
she buy a piano for the yacht
it's it's um it's i think it's
like plywood cheney's got out but she
worthy seaworthy wow well that's that's incredible
paul great shaun worthy thank you or
me paul is gonna be the next
cameo super trillionaire i don't think
if so hey i honestly don't think
so okay fine but making kids go
make nine you get something i'll get
him out i mean i'm happy to
to do that for sure yeah i
gotcha i just gotta knock out these
two hundred and sixty two requests in
the next five going he's getting good
so are you putting a time frame
on it you're looking for
this time someone do my cameos that
i'm gonna do my best my that
kind of like i was when i
was in austin i was just kind
of hanging out in the hotel and
i would do them as much as
i could you know and then take
a little break um and it still
wasn't enough it did not make much
of a dent so yeah i don't
know i i'm gonna figure it out
one way or another good okay good
alright well i'm gonna
by one thousand of them at three
hundred dollars a pop yeah scott i'm
someone that we're both friends with bought
one for you whoa fucking way that's
what in the chat know you wait
to woman for the job no no
no no no no you wanna wait
until we get it that's amazing that's
good
you have oren not gotten an already
it was not lorin
what if we give to the majeed
cameos for space so funny my god
he's still amazing that should be the
like the story on a situation comedy
honestly like the two people get each
other same cameo this fucking alert they
should do a skit on s l
and you should do is say should
do one skid on s and l
for once i get on that i
think a black lady sketch show should
do it it should last
shampoo in it and send it out
they should do a spoof of that
what's another sketch show are there any
i think it's more of our lampoon
idea
i don't know if there really are
any right now besides the ones we've
mentioned black lady sketch show us oh
and what else ah just is harvard
level and i think you should leave
of course i think you should leave
could you imagine tim robinson with his
trademark heightening of frustrations so that he
can really send it up he could
do a goof
on that that would be for the
ages how do we hold in a
skid on that where he had two
people get the same cameo for each
other and then they did that on
this show that'd be freaking bomb dude
i mean obviously we should be in
it well if they're yeah level we
gave him the idea put us in
in it please please me put us
in the lead on that tim i
need starting in this skit tim i'm
gonna start begging for shit you know
what i wanna be i wanna do
is test engine yeah yeah you wanna
you wanna host it or you want
to be on no i want to
be a contestant on it okay
it myself i it's this it's this
ah comedy game show in england they
did a season of it here but
it didn't take reggie hosted it yeah
which was that was a strange choice
now that i'm doing what now that
i've seen the original show is a
it is an and of course i
watched i watched the first episode of
the
the british version of the the american
version and it's so you can so
clearly see the difference between what they
think the american attention span is versus
anywhere else we think we're just a
bunch of dumb shits like we don't
like charm hot we're not most of
us are yes but so what
well gamers will help you what does
joe know for oath a thousand people
to watch your tv show come on
call so it's lauren i think you
would like it because really it's really
fun it's really funny um ah basically
it's it's five comedians have to complete
all these ah ah
odd tasks and um they are varying
degrees of challenging ah they they they
often will think of ah funny clever
workarounds for for ways to achieve the
tasks and um it's i've just been
like tearing like after hearing about it
for years and people recommending
it to me i have like i
watched a bunch on youtube and then
got the um the seasons that i
couldn't find off of itunes and i've
just been tearing through an mlm all
caught up and i'm mad that i
don't have any wow wow chat yeah
it's really for your own
yeah it's like when you run up
a sign just make it up yourself
it's like fucking do a camera like
oh no there's no more seasons of
you know lost or whatever just make
your own it's like what are you
waiting for i guess kind of a
yeah that's a great tim robinson show
what are you waiting for
tim put us on your show what
are you waiting for delete the companion
series too i think you should leave
what are you waiting for with your
not leaving action why don't you go
what are you waiting for oh it's
the prequel series what are you waiting
for and then i think you should
know it makes sense as the sql
i think you should live what are
you waiting what are you waiting
four oh good he left
it's a triptych
triptych tragic touch simply the freshest triptych
that was being restricted oh yeah go
ahead the three of us have to
take a break oh bye bye let's
take a trip pitch of breaks
and we're back and ah chevron just
gave us some horrible news and the
three of us are considering firing him
chavez went ape shit on wow and
he literally she was like i have
a recording in thirty minutes and i
don't know how
this is gonna work and he started
crying and he started screaming and he
was like i am the host of
the zoom this is kinda like everything
yeah yeah that's a good impression he
kept yelling how he was the host
of the zoom they're like no no
one was disputing up by yeah no
one but it's almost like it was
trying to make it like he was
the host of this podcast like yeah
troll shit
wait guys do you think that he
thinks when he hosted the zoom that
makes him the host of the show
i think he doesn't understand what that
means yeah i think he might mean
we do give him all the money
from all the ads we sell yeah
he does she may have done that
he does do a transcription of everything
we say and then he imitates the
three of us and he
put out a separate show where he
does all the voice calls me oh
there's the idea that he's good though
no but his show's called needham meta
up now yeah he's been doing the
whole time i've never once heard my
own voice on this recording it's all
kevin if you guys knew what i
actually sounded like you'd be disgusted i
have a terrible voice shocked i have
a terrible voice
i don't like lists i thought were
fighting the entire time you talk i
talk like the announcer lady from the
tic talks and the instagram videos i
don't know what that it's i why
oh is that the generated yeah when
it's like always sir whatever hey this
sound for your baby and see if
they don't dance
do you remember when those candy colored
hate it or even before the candy
color mix but the max that they
bought ah kam show okay alert the
candy colored max deep space to show
what's my boss all day but are
these mac macintosh computer like i said
what's a max they rented all these
computers restaurant from sfo
to write and we only use final
draft on it but yeah um but
when we found out that you there
was a program on it where you
could type something in and make the
computer say yes dirty words that it
was so selfless ap very fun course
who doesn't love that piss piss shit
but of course it was like shit
is
oregon trail course classic when you would
put in that um people's names you
know you've got to make up a
name in the game and you can
name your family and then um you
always put penis then at some point
penis gets killed by snakebite and then
it's like let's just say i never
played oregon trail that was after my
time and i'm not
quite sure it was just like a
text game right now i mean it
was there were visuals like i know
that you died of dysentery okay today
so like you have your family and
you have your covered wagon and you'd
see like an image of that and
then like you the wagons trying to
like do various things and you choose
what it's gonna do is going afford
the river or is it gonna cock
the wheel
rules are i don't know what there's
different things that i just learned from
the game and then you want to
do the thing and either fails or
succeeds and if like all of us
and then some of the things might
die and then you go hunting and
there's that's always the fun part you
get to use your little gun and
you shoot the bison and then there's
her squirrels and other things that are
worthless you know food points
and agreed you kill as many as
you can but then sometimes like the
you shot too much you can't carry
at all so you don't wanna be
wasteful with your bullets and um yeah
and then at the end you see
your group grave or you win i
don't recall ever succeeding honestly use this
crazy wave yeah it's so crazy you
can carry bullets and they're so light
but then the
things they kill are so heavy this
is so deep dude you should write
a book isn't it funny how abraham
lincoln was our tallest president but he's
on such a tiny little coin
dude oh my god dude that's fucking
isn't it insane how george washington was
three-dimensional and yet on the on the
darvill he's just flat it's like what's
that supposed to mean i do think
when i was a kid i used
to think that okay george washington was
the first president so he was on
the one dollar
or bill not means abraham lincoln was
our fifth president because i think i
thought that too at one point yeah
i think in some ways they should
have done that it makes more sense
like make a make a different bill
for every single president we have so
the sixteen dollar bill there'd be a
fully six dollar bill there was a
sixteen dollars just made me feel weird
inside how much is that sixteen dollars
oh
good like your sixteen dollar bill and
you were like legally obligated to carry
every and like one of each bill
everywhere legally high yeah there how much
that's how much money would that be
i mean it's already kind of sixteen
dollar bill then you have to replenish
a sixteen dollar bill yeah but that's
already ninety one
one dollars just with our two most
recent presidents but imagine wow you might
hundred and thirty imagine yeah imagine carrying
legalizing fifty one dollar bills it takes
up a lot of room yeah so
you shouldn't do that i'm saying you
shouldn't you will
if i were president this would be
my ticket huh hey you oh what
was the young of the folder first
what are you doing oh the lucky
you know oh yeah i do but
why were you what were you
again new york times text alerts that
are that are right in front of
your face and i want to see
your hill i'm crushing your kids a
holler coming back i'm very excited about
the day we've been coming back they
have any show yeah on amazon i
can't wait to see it do you
do you ever think your episode of
the characters will ever come back and
do ah another season yeah they're gonna
just do another bunch of stuff on
do you think you'll
more episodes of comedy bang bang the
tv show i you know it's such
a weird company that i did it
for it would not surprise me if
one day they were like hey ah
you're coming back and and they made
me do it and it also wouldn't
surprise me so whenever asked if no
one ever talked to me ever again
from there yeah the head of the
company or the head of the network
just
he left and sent an email earlier
on
left earth yeah she jumped off my
shoes i guess two already did it
she did it she's the first person
to do it but and she sent
everyone an email and i i sent
her back a nice email and but
i was just so so kind to
what she said was rude
she said because he was just like
there's still people there who worked there
um there's still people
now this company was raytheon is that
correct
halliburton
a lot of people don't know they
made the comedy tv show possible do
you know that there is one specific
person i think of whenever i hear
that albert who haley burton i can't
see it on the podcast oh god
it was it was a joke that's
so what else we know made at
the expense it's
oh okay put it in the chat
but i think of i think of
what whatever her name is from one
tree hill right in her name haley
burton or something on lore and stop
yawning or even the first time i've
young we can't call out yawns we
can't guys that's not the first time
and it's like dude i i
more go hard all day dude she
does go hard all day with that
goddamn so why do you schedule these
epi end of the day after you've
gone to us i literally have no
other time and then i'm leaving town
tomorrow at the crack of dawn chevron
says it's hilary burton
that's why i thought you were close
from one oil from one time i
didn't watch that program
very de to nagin from the walking
dead jeffrey dean morgan
i just saw brief clips from huh
seven that rounds up celebrity couples for
another episode of three-day but i just
had great clip from seventh heaven which
i used to watch a lot as
a kid there's an episode where the
mom admits that she's like the kids
i guess smoked pot or got into
it or something in the mom and
cheese smoked pot and she's like she
says it's so dramatically it's like the
funny
best thing ever
there's something i need to tell you
something express check every man in this
thing is the summer before i went
off to college i didn't want experimenting
myself experimenting yeah he's going
slower i'm trying to tell you you
can download music
i want you to know that
thanks
a puppy the stairs
ah is oh my god it's like
he's carried affairs they cut out and
he was just doesn't have fun okay
i know i love that show like
i didn't think i don't i don't
think i loved it as much as
my dawson's creek whatever but it was
it was ah right before after that
you know you just kind of settle
in for the night with one yeah
shows
but that is the most ridiculous way
of i just can't imagine every topic
they covered on that show with that
so they talked about it it's so
crazy do you remember i hate to
bring it back to currency but humor
when two dollar bills were like exciting
oh it's still exciting thrilling to me
i do receive them quite regularly because
my my family
early it is ah oh it's a
thing in the time where you guys
collect all this swing you know where
i would get them all the time
is universal studios parking anytime i would
go to citywalk and ah or go
to a movie there at universal studios
they would give it they would give
them his change because i think parking
was like eighteen dollars or whatever
riley just had stacks of two dollar
bills and i love that it's so
fun to get it to give it
out i always i'm afraid i mean
i saved them anyway but i i
wouldn't really want to use them cause
i feel like people don't notice it
when they're taking like an article it's
a to you know name yeah ugh
it's like i'm giving you something very
rare and unique and special and then
some people would look at him and
go like what am i
yes i do think that because i'll
shut up if you're working at a
store there's like a cash register that
has holes you know for each dollar
and they don't have a two dollar
hole no they don't when i worked
retail twenties are i put it with
the ones or sometimes at the bottom
put it under you put yeah here's
what an under don't know because if
you put it with the ones palsy
counts going to be off not so
loud pull the count will be off
what a lot of people don't know
is in the cash register you can
lift the black part out and then
underneath you can put flat things in
there if you want so like what
kind of stuff oh like a nobel
for example or maybe oh okay if
you ever got a hundred dollar bill
or
say you got a note that said
help help y huh
why oh my god way i forgot
the only person whoa why
it's so funny that i've had so
many jobs where they're like oh yeah
put twenty like keep one twenty in
the drawer and then put all the
rest of the twenty s underneath and
fifty so they won't stick well yeah
who is that there were fooled yeah
at airwolf basically when you know your
job you're off when you yeah you
behind the register at euro
yeah that was your first job there
right
you where i worked my way up
a podcast host
there's a greeter that i became a
guy songbird yeah and yeah we just
be taking jayce mandzukic his money when
he came in to pay to do
the show hey hey this guy
um by scott so there was a
yeah right oh yeah our internet went
out again as so it's great that
i am on the phone and co
op is asking me if she can
restart it
bop i'm saying i'm on the phone
so go ahead there we go wow
came back do you just speed do
you do speed tests ah my my
baby person comes by and does it
and yeah so like right i'll try
to fix it by the way they've
been out hundreds of times in the
last three months ah they come out
they fix it ah
my avi guy does a speed test
goes oh wow you're getting to fifty
over whatever and then they go or
that your blood pressure oh wow you
need to come and they go away
and within within six hours it all
slows down again so yeah you need
serious help and use ethernet yeah wow
yeah it's all it's all fucked up
it's all and they're the only place
that does this area so they have
a monopoly on it yeah and it
was the weirdest part is it was
good for two of the first two
years i lived here i did so
i did zooms you know the entire
pandemic love comedy bang bang you had
a great job done crystal glove dummy
was love being on zoom it was
greatest time in my life
life best one is twenty years of
my entire life to see the laughs
i've had during the pandemic oh my
god are you twenty greatest ever i
miss yeah i'm miss quarantine a little
bit yeah i know re
i love the closeness i loved being
the only person in the world you
remember like the first month of quarantine
you had to do so many zooms
with people who are like this is
so weird i don't get to see
any of my friends again yeah and
now it's like we'd never do it
anyway
i know well i mean it's still
what i feel like the world has
shifted in a different way where well
even now we're all homebodies now there's
a lot of there's a lot of
that and then there's also like now
that the work is picking up or
maybe it has been whole time everyone's
on different paths with this but that
like you prioritize your time so different
tlie like i feel like people aren't
filling their day going thing the thing
the thing it's like you're kind of
i don't know i that's what it
seems like my people in my world
are doing so you've they're doing their
whole day from thing to not a
thing no like it's more like think
they do fewer things during the day
when they did before the pandemic where
it was more like roadshow outside it's
not going from thing
to not a thing then to a
thing that i guess that is what
i mean oh yeah life i have
definitely in the way that a ah
fish grows to the size of its
bowl um my ah energy level has
shrunk to whatever it is that i
have to do so if i do
one thing in a day like one
errand or one
job or whatever it's exhaust i'm exhausted
after but that's that's what you have
the energy to do and after that
like you can't do anything else yeah
but if but if i have like
four things yeah you have all those
four things yeah i would do all
those four things then i would feel
the same way as i did if
i did one pain right so then
so then you would say like ok
they will schedule five things a day
and then you'll get more done yes
and now i'm i'm ah i'm gonna
collapse lawrence holding her jaw so she
doesn't yacht again i own twice already
i'm not going to yawn ever again
it may be gone talking about huh
yeah yeah everyone listening is yawning hey
if you're not yawning you're not paying
attention that's a bumper sticker says and
i'm the one who is up at
two in the morning till five thirty
why were you able to just wow
woke up got out of the dry
cool girls to sound weird oh no
just michael my hair very weird just
just woke up and was like well
i can't get back to sleep so
i did my word i'll send it
to you guys
and how long do you think how
long do you think we're all gonna
do wordle for on the chain you're
the one who wanted us to do
it me too i'm wondering how long
is it gonna go i don't know
i'm happy to keep sharing it i
think even if we don't share it
i'll still do it because i like
to have the little brain exercise i
also um i enjoy yeah that text
thread utilized
a lot of times we don't have
reasons to post to it that's true
though we've run out of things to
say to each other it's true and
it's nice to have this tenuous ah
thread that keeps us all together that
keeps us eating care about each like
this like yes they're ruining want to
or not i'm like wordle like a
mortal and then i have three chains
that i send it to
but i'm letting one of them slowly
drop off me cu wow wow only
have the one with you guys let's
see oh wow i have i have
three mortal chains as well and one
of them is just sort of it's
becoming more sporadic i think yeah with
with the other people i still send
them faithfully there's another
well we we started we've said this
a few times on our thread but
that framed game yeah um yeah here's
what happened because i there's other people
that i'm on a thread with that
play more and then we we realized
that we were not all getting the
same movie at the same time
really yeah and i'm like this guy
i don't like this game that much
anyway so i don't like it either
at one to kind of stress me
out and it was like i didn't
i feel like the reveals were ab
like the worst random picture ever seen
in your life yeah yeah it's like
say the movies batman they show a
picture of the joker for the first
one it's like come on this is
batman not the
joker i was like oh my gosh
this you know that's not scott you're
being silly because what they do already
paul will you forgive me was yes
of course honey i love you but
but for the for the batman like
it would be like you know a
picture of a tree or whatever and
it's like well i don't know what
that is never buy a tree well
there was
is that one scene in batman where
batman pulled over and pissed on the
tree yes he was like oh i
didn't time this outright this is this
is further away than i thought keep
the car running how to get his
dick out he had to take a
whole thing off oh that's like wearing
a jumpsuit yeah so you just might
got ass naked next to a tree
e yeah with all that let robot
who rubber suit just bunched up around
his ankles
fourteen nfl he gets tonight it's like
so horrible but he still got the
batman movie i want to see yes
i wanna see enough videos batman enough
with fighting the joker and all that
kind of stuff let's show him pissing
by a tree with his pants around
his ankles just in one batman movie
can we see him put his eye
makeup on plea ease with the brush
or the whatever it is smudge i
wanna see what facey makes if he
does like ah oh god mascara
because just once i think i tweeted
this once but i realized at a
certain point that when i brushed my
teeth i raised my eyebrows oh huh
and i was never aware of it
and then once i was aware of
it i stopped doing it here you
can stop
you can stop anytime you want i'm
not addicted to it
that's all well i'll be the judge
and i lost my job because i
kept raising my row when i brush
my teeth
my wife left me look alright we
should take a break leaving yeah we
got to take a break yeah so
ah god almighty kevin can go to
his next more important show meanwhile we
don't even know what we're gonna do
no but we don't but we're gonna
come back and we'll we'll figure something
out and we'll do with reacher i
hope we'll do it
on our own because god knows kevin
not going to help yeah alright ceo
lie
and we're back it's time for a
three cheer this is the time where
we play a fun three chair i
think it's like this guess would like
to introduce it ah who's the zoo
you move from cradle the balls stroke
to show
those i've reached figure weekly alright this
is my neighbor recorded the truck so
nice knows this is slice favorite game
it's called french toast we've played it
once before yes and here's how it
works its submitted by gina maiden one
player is the clue giver and thinks
of something that the other players will
guess at for example mount rushmore or
ghostbusters or chocolate
anything in the world the rest of
the players and no sugar orders yeah
rush marcos vs yeah yeah ah there
was a little but i was in
no particular order ask the clue giver
comparative questions in the form of is
it more like x or more like
y and the clue giver much to
the best of their ability to choose
the x or the y that it's
more like so in the first question
the game it has to be french
chose
so and all subsequent questions access whatever
the clue giver said was more like
the answer for example if question one
is is it more like french toast
or bass fishing and the clue giver
says it's more like bass fishing the
next question must begin with is it
more like bass fishing or blank and
the game ends when someone offers a
gas and guesses correctly yeah i got
wild horses into this and we had
so much when we did before our
show
recently and we got addicted we loved
it and there's also a fun thing
on it which maybe we could try
another time um where you basically think
of a celebrity and then the other
people ask um questions like what's there
what what food would they be what
shoe would they be what you know
it's like
and you just kind of start putting
together and it's really really fun right
um okay so we'll try that one
sometime but not now not now ah
okay so who wants to think of
the thing i will think of the
thing okay when you're ready tell us
yes let me go into my mind
palace
he's going wow look at him he's
getting small ago
but larry is getting larger ah leon
leon's getting larger i've only seen that
just nine months ago so i guess
so that guy was so fucking funny
guy so funny johnny um okay
okay go ahead is it more like
french toast or a flower more like
a flower is it more like a
flower or more like a car
more like a flower is more like
a flower or more like an umbrella
more like an umbrella
is more like an umbrella or more
like a jacket more like a jacket
is more like a jacket or more
like a raincoat
more like a raincoat
is it more like a raincoat or
more like a peacoat more like green
coat zipper like a raincoat monaco wetsuit
more like a raincoat
my like my leg my leg
my leg that is more like belinda
is it more like a raincoat or
more like a trenchcoat
very slim distinction i feel like um
yeah well one is used for weather
and
i'm gonna say more like a trenchcoat
it's like a trenchcoat more like a
blanket more like a trenchcoat
he's more like a trenchcoat or more
like a three piece suit more like
a trenchcoat is a manga trenchcoat or
more like a sweatshirt more like a
trenchcoat
is it more like a trenchcoat or
more like a private eyes ah glad
you know magnifying glass more like a
trenchcoat it's like a trenchcoat or more
like a um a if a um
boa like a fur feather boa more
like a trenchcoat is it more like
a
i'm trying to think of anything else
like a trenchcoat is it more like
a trello trench coat
judge further very
more like
trenchcoat are more like oh more like
more like a transcoder more like a
bathrobe more like a trenchcoat as a
moraga trench coat or more like a
briefcase more like
more like a trenchcoat or more like
a smoking jacket more like a trenchcoat
is like a trenchcoat or more like
a blazer more like a trenchcoat is
it more like a trenchcoat or more
like a house coat um
more like a trench coat is like
a trenchcoat or more like a um
what do you call like a tuxedo
jacket yeah oh more like a trenchcoat
it's more like a trench coat or
more word is ceasing to a meeting
more like a trying to think of
any other outerwear
ah more like ah a blazer i
don't know homes that is more like
a trenchcoat and more like a parka
more like a trenchcoat is is almost
gonna rapid fire is more like a
trenchcoat or more like a um a
zipper hoodie
like to go to isn't a trenchcoat
no i wouldn't have it at that
and ended is it more like a
coat or more like i was wearing
a trenchcoat or more like a table
you don't mean like are we talking
arena completely wrong know you're you're just
staying within one narrow groove okay it
is more like a trenchcoat than a
table okay
okay is it more like a trenchcoat
or more like address more like a
trench coat is more like a trench
coat or a jean jacket maybe it's
not moving i'm gonna say more like
a jean jacket i think it's ok
is it more like a jean jacket
or more like a monopoly game more
like a jean jacket is more like
a jean jacket or like
a windbreaker more like a jean jacket
is more like a jean jacket or
more like blue jean pants
given those two i would say more
like a jean jacket is it more
like a jean jacket or is it
more like
um a members only jack it's more
like a jean jacket is more like
a jean jacket or more like a
horse
it's more like a jean jacket but
it could be like ores i don't
use it to talk a little marine
jacket or i was like a fur
coat it's more like a jean jacket
is more like a jean jacket or
more like a six shooter
ooh ahh more like a jean jacket
is a monica jean jacket we're like
chaps
more like chaps
is it more like chaps
or more like a ball gag i
beg your pardon
it's more like check which of the
things that you own which i wasn't
looking around the room is it more
like shy guys are chosen or is
it more like a suede jacket with
fringe
more like a suede jacket with fringe
or more like a ah cowboy hat
it's a cowboy hat yes far a
chaps was a great guest job oh
overweight you get the credit i'm the
one who passed yeah ah i should
get there
buddy that's almost asked if it was
more like a hat at one point
and i didn't always begging for someone
who will like it because i thought
we decided it was definitely a jack
todd i would say was no like
ahead and i didn't hey now i'm
not crazy alright everybody we love you
so much thank you for always um
we are in followers say yeah
in a twitter instagram or an instagram
three m usa gmail dynamo say gmail
dot com and phone number for to
come to com t k for now
depending we've already recorded the outgoing greetings
so you know we're serious about this
we are serious we need this number
it's an aspirational outgoing greeting and if
you want to hear ad-free
episodes you can listen to stitcher premium
or at cb world dot com thanks
yeah summation goodbye yeah have only information
you need mister policeman we say ooze
a