hey everyone's got aquaman here and i'm
lauren lamkin i'm paul f tompkins and
we have a brand new podcast called
three-day oh musically the three of us
have a lot of fun conversations together
and we want to do a show
where we aren't playing characters so we
abandoned our individual podcast formats to discuss
each other the world and everything in
between although maybe
maybe we should have done all of
our podcast formats on top of each
other simultaneous like we should like friends
like that yeah like definitely yeah
looks good friends we are friends in
this limited series we try to figure
out what the show should be called
a test balloon no k i s
come s so stupid welcome back to
k s comment no one will ever
find it oh honey it gets worse
oh i like that we share weird
stories from our childhood
and i tried to flip over his
back and then we both just fell
and we both landed on the tops
of our god and we make fun
of each other a lot which is
kind of a bummer sometimes oh my
god not for all of us just
for one of us wait
one
so make sure she's like it's not
a bummer for me yeah i'm fun
i get my feelings hurt
oh wow now that is gonna get
people to listen make sure to check
out three to march twenty ninth on
stitcher premium or go fuck yourself