three
remember why we say the end we
either right
um
russian foreign for god totally forgot but
i said remember what we say at
the end you said yep
yeah
chimed in three-toed instead of freemium like
gay i want to and i looked
at you you were absolutely on autopilot
i was thinking about something useful for
miles oh intends your miles away
everyone it wasn't even something in history
thought i was like rehashing a thing
that i already own cookies been right
anyway welcome to our three meme episodes
we do these every other week and
it's where we respond to your voicemails
that you send us at hag claims
eight dot com yes this was your
idea and we are honoring it yep
you're welcome you made us do this
we did not want need us to
look what you made us do um
yeah so let's go to one of
these right i can here we go
what's preventing well it said it was
not available but now it is okay
here we go let's hear it
hello hello my name is andrea i'm
a really big fan of the show
i have a really important question for
you guys so for a little bit
of context ah earlier today i saw
what was probably the most beautiful cat
i've ever seen so that's awesome first
of all second of all i immediately
thought run all the way up a
tree like a cartoon and i really
liked this and i wanted to know
have you ever seen something happening that
you like thank you so much my
eyes this person sounds like anything be
like elise meyers i think his name
of this like instagram person has tons
of followers and is always telling stories
in a very similar voice and cadence
um
anyways um anytime i like yeah i've
seen a lot sure like um do
i wanna go first because i'll think
about you seen so much you should
give us ten examples ten things i
like yeah um okay i mean you
were just bragging about well how much
are something like yeah you're saying like
i've seen so much oh yeah we
were all
really intimidated by it's own alright i
think like art vienna museum like what
our degas degas i like take ah
da da da da da da da
da i saw the last time i
was in san francisco and i put
it the video of this on insta
mom um i saw the the famous
parents of san francisco oh yeah why
are they so famous they because they're
very loud
it seems like a bad thing to
be just forget i remember hearing the
story of how they ended up there
ah but they are there's this big
flock of of ah green pairs i
think telegraph hills were the angle but
i saw them in a tree and
they kept doing the same thing over
and over again where there they make
like a terrific tran leaf oh sorry
good
so they send the tree and they're
all talking to each other than they
all fuckin take off they fly like
you know a few yards away then
they swoop down and fly back as
a group the whole time back into
the tree and they're all chattering with
each other and they
just repeat this like over and over
again there's like some parrots on the
east side yeah ballet that are supposedly
a pet store burned down i think
that's i think that's urban legend it
sounds like yeah but we used to
get those parents in our neighborhood they
don't come anymore and it really bums
me out i loved it it sounds
like drastic park but yeah like the
the urban legend said a pet store
stubborn none of the parents were displaced
and
and they now are wild but it
is weird that they're there yeah that's
why we have so many goldfish all
over the place
i know those perished dino dna what
have you seen that you like who
man her mentioning the cat made me
remember something i saw i did not
like oh which was the prompt but
ok i know but i can't get
it out of my mind but i
was right i was driving in i
saw a cat
who get killed yes oh my oh
i was i was crying in my
car i was like no no don't
don't because recently yeah relatively oh actually
sad
when i was a kid we had
this um we had there was a
dead cat on the side of the
road who owns this cat
and we we would pass it every
day on our child lee walks and
we call every day and call the
black cat flatly and watch shamefully while
we watched it decompose for the entire
summer fun and it was entertaining always
remember it it was a family event
flat cat
so you're like it's like watching one
of those decomposing videos but in real
time yeah i mean it sounds really
gross now but it was on our
path to this to the beach and
so we'd go like oh it's there's
a why when i was in london
doing kelsey grammer resents sketch show i
always like how you call it that
we rehearsed we would rehearse and this
this is very common in tv there
we would rehearse them like this sort
of community center um in this hall
and um i remember looking out the
window and seeing a fox and i'd
never seen one in person before it's
very exciting and they get killed to
the fucks thinking meeting placing me me
me me to not get killed i
was trying to
to pull out of that i dive
that's amazing have you seen the holdovers
yeah i really like that i've really
liked that movie so now it's just
anything we've sold there's a fox and
that wasn't the oh was there too
i believe i think there was a
fox in there yeah it's chuck also
feedback talking about the actor who plays
the yoga he's so high he's foxy
he kind of reminds me of mike
minor you've heard that because my me
said it no my parents are the
two speaking of the holdovers from something
that i remember seeing when i was
a child we had um in in
back of our house one of our
neighbors was this man mister haynes mister
haynes remembers the heir to the underwear
fortune nike
only for undies yeah that's what you
call it i don't know what his
actual last name was but will
underpants um dirty soiled he was the
first dirty deed he had the first
glass i had ever seen he had
the first one ever yeah that i
had ever seen oh yeah but it
might have been the first one ever
far as i know he didn't brag
about it yeah
you could have i suppose but he
had um he had three huskies and
i was that's why i'm so fascinated
by them oh because i made a
breakthrough because i loved them so much
i thought they were the most amazing
dogs but one time they treed a
raccoon who's on top of the telephone
poll how what verb is that where
you
true when you treat something what does
it mean it means you force them
to go up a tree i don't
really yeah so he was sitting on
top of this telephone pole and the
raccoon and just like sitting there and
these dogs were going fucking crazy and
it was i remember it was i
had never seen anything like that before
like yeah real nature you like
that in a way you know what
i mean i don't think i've ever
seen a raccoon before oh we got
a lot of those in our trash
cans and yeah but there's there's a
first time you know what i'm saying
is don't i crazy it's like you
guys are trying to rob me of
this experience i know you would really
have i'm actually really happy for you
and my memory sightings there have been
many times where raccoon families would be
perched on the fence we look at
them at night when i was a
kid and like it'd be like mommy
and babies yeah and it was so
fun to watch them what were they
up to i saw them cross the
street i was driving home and i
saw them across the street my neighborhood
yes fancy other side presumably i mean
that's what they did right yeah dogs
going crazy
why okay so my dogs go crazy
for anyone passing by or delivering something
or any kind of kin from you
the house yes at a certain point
you think they'd be like okay we've
gone crazy
yeah one thousand five hundred times over
the last year and nothing has gone
wrong yeah i like yeah or we
are reacting talking to each i wish
my dog would understand that too it's
like it's fine everything's follow you want
them to go crazy when you need
them to your children even small dogs
are not gonna stop
you know i'm saying like them barking
and it is small dogs because you've
seen those videos of like larger dogs
that love the u p s guy
or whatever right my dog is half
two oh and i think that's a
lot of what's going on yes looks
like she's just your cares really wants
to talk about and i'm never getting
i never well my dog has eaten
talk about every meal for the last
ten years oh why what do you
yeah that's a lot chalupa yeah and
you're unused every meal your dog has
breakfast lunch and snacks of course healthy
snacks held these taco bell yeah it
just started to show it's also can
you get just tortilla chips at taco
bell i like
to to see you try i'd be
so he wanted to try it first
you changed in the middle yep i
did did they not do that a
full disclosure so yeah by the way
you need to give us full disclosure
right now because we've been doing so
many episodes of this and you haven't
confessed whatever it is you're right and
i'll give you full feeble trash only
in one thing from taco bell one
time in my entire life and
i was really isn't shero really all
i do because it's a stamper you
know i've been curious about touro curious
sure you never had it you've ever
been sure we should go we should
try that i don't want to go
do you know what i i usually
like taco bell like most people yeah
and then i did it for doughboys
a year or two
ago and it did not hold up
for me really well they're sponsor now
so it was even better
alright what sponsored i'll try i'll try
too many items we hope ah audrey
we hope that that answered your console
and your hold on a second we're
gonna talk to you in a second
is there any fast food that you
like you like but i don't even
anymore but i used to i grew
up loving mcdonald's lunch were wrong um
span and high school kinda pop over
there so it's kind of far away
swear aspect of the burgers appealed to
square s pick the fries and the
frosty fries in the frosty so good
um her there's so much of it
that i would love to eat all
the time but no but i i
do if i if i treat myself
to a fast food item at this
point
it would be mcdonald's
we used to have when i was
in philly there was a chain called
roy rogers yeah and that was that
was like the hangout near our high
school we had frost you eat fast
food now are foster threes rosters fees
i used to go over there every
day get a burger i was like
the only one to they can have
survived on that
there's a foster's free
you eat you are the only customer
they ever had it seemed like everything
was like i would go there every
single day and the guy would go
you'll want a burger and there's so
much better than like a fast food
burger because he's grilling it right in
front of like getting out oh in
and out like an urge in and
knock that the fries though i like
the fries well i got them well
done the other
day what's that you can request it
was but my friday virus codes and
i didn't know if that meant like
yeah yeah you covered in sli it
means making better nickelodeon style so they
they do it twice yeah and then
what happens they're crispier yeah i don't
need a crispy i like so i
actually like them soft i was yeah
alright okay com can you
they're all losing her while i was
at your first time doing well done
yeah and did you like it no
i actually i like it and our
fries may do but so if you
had to get fast food what are
you getting i probably mcdonald's although every
once in a while i get a
craving for kentucky fried chicken oh yeah
we see people in the listing that
i might feel sick well yeah yeah
um but but if
their sponsors we love them all we
love all of our sponsors all of
our sponsors i'll do ads for all
of them and i would eat it
again this is what i'm telling you
i've never been to a foster reason
there's one near my neighborhood really and
i always think like go today let's
go well fosters maybe i don't think
i really know what that is it's
like an ice cream place but i
also do
do barriers and stuff not to be
confused with the businessman who ran for
office and said that birth control was
putting an aspirin between your knees and
holding it there yeah mr freeze yeah
mister mister freeze and put aspirin between
your knees and hold the data that's
good thank you alright look audrey i
think we're doing this right before like
you want the booger
we do this right before lunch sorry
that we've segue to fast food but
hopefully that answered your question i hope
that shuts you up
yeah that's gonna be it for this
three medium episode and um you know
we'll be back in a couple of
weeks but listen to us every thursday
on freedom thursday to us every day
all the time by night