three
oh
for
three dome three domes dome theater nine
year boy three shots to the dome
um welcome to three results through the
door three shots to the doe little
loves to the door new jib new
jib or we just decided you know
what
we make three shots to the dad
come on throw shoe charm shoe charms
charm shoes are too tight shoes are
generic
welcome to three-day mime scott i ball
and learn
and that's who you guys are well
ah how what are we
i said oh that's what you guys
are turn on your goddamn original sound
so you can hear me turn on
your goddamn original sound whites so now
your god damn yeah why do i
do that see up at the top
word says oh my god are doing
town shop is the beginning of the
show buddy
where is it never mind top layer
top left of the screen and also
i don't care either hi paul hi
i'm actually not there okay i'm like
well you need to update your fucking
zoom guess what i don't care um
i gotta tell you guys a story
because last night i attended lorne topics
it's widely topics and i attended
prestigious award show via zoom and i
had a ball so i went to
ambien last night right you went to
the ami's ball and went to the
snowball microphone or there oh podcast yeah
podcast inside but um because
one of the top of the homo
just inside i attended the ami's to
represent three them because we were nominated
for best comedy podcasts everyone knows and
i think decided you're not old nor
i were dating would deign to do
it you both say i was dating
you you both did say you weren't
going to do it and i said
i'll do it
i'll do it and i know why
why would you do it and we
wouldn't because i guess i thought i'll
just be sitting around and i don't
care right yeah so and i felt
like you know and i'll do neither
of those things yeah i won't be
sitting around and i will care yeah
care a lot yeah um
so i i had to do like
a tech check like a couple of
weeks ago for this where i assume
weeks before that's a long long time
in between tech at least two weeks
so much can happen ahead to down
i know it's true and i had
to download this background they made for
me which had like a yellow sort
of background and like the freedom logo
and i had to put that
as my background and my tech check
was under three minutes i mean i
had it all ready to go very
bad now i'm very professional he didn't
say it was the fastest tech turkey
ever had
um then she is that is that
like sex where it's a bad thing
though yeah he was like i didn't
even come up for him it's like
i want this to go on
it was a rough they probably do
i mean they're getting paid by the
hour you would assume
i don't know
really don't think they get paid by
the tech check
one because dude is probably checked for
hundreds of people there tech checking because
when i logged into this award show
i mean the number of podcasts they
were referenced i've never heard of any
of them i mean hundreds of podcasts
you know there's so many um in
the awards alone obviously there's thousands and
thousands so i
i log into this zoom so first
of all they want me to dress
up they did tell me to dress
up as if i was going to
an award show i did not do
that i didn't brush my hair and
i was wearing whatever i had already
okay it was i saw i saw
the photo yeah i shot the photo
it was like neck up yeah you
can barely see me and and when
you actually when
we get to the part where you
actually see how much of me is
actually on screen for this thing if
i had put on makeup for this
i would have been i would have
to pay it just it would be
a waste of time so but let
me say also one of i watched
right before our category came up i
watched i started like a half hour
before so i caught yeah you know
half hour of it there was a
guy that was one of the
governors of the ambos that came out
in like a short sleeve shirt why
and they wanted people in their homes
to fuckin put on things that weren't
show didn't have a collar or was
it a shirt shape of the color
a color and if we know anything
about podcast one of the best things
about it is you don't have to
look good to do oh okay yes
so great
thank you so much so even without
makeup mueller so pretty you guys are
disgusting
yeah you have like a natural beauty
shot huh
this from within the hell you okay
so i'm sitting i logged in to
zoom and i'm i'm give us every
step i'm i'm going to let you
on how many times have you said
i logged into the zoo
so already like copy paste the password
i actually copied it about a hundred
times cause i was so confused because
i was admitted i was put into
this room where i was not able
to see myself but i was watching
a backstage greenroom like tech check of
other people so i was really confused
at camping like a man the wrong
place what's going on and so i
watched these people like silently do their
types
it was a super weird and
eventually i text bryan safi because i
was like am i in the right
place like are you looking at the
same thing i'm looking at he's like
yeah okay so then eventually we get
when we're watching the award show as
it's going onto and i have to
say cameron esposito was hosting it and
she did not have an easy job
because she's standing in a black void
in a room where there was like
twenty people in person wet cafe tables
with me
masks on who are laughing but it
just it seemed like this not your
ideal audience for no no that's the
only place i'll perform
exploited in twenty cafe tables by mouse
i love that for you like i
almost think it would've been easier for
her if she were at home like
yeah not standing up in front of
these people and having to like you
know standing up at home yeah but
anyway give her props for that because
that's a really hard job so
we're we're in the more houses by
the way every step of the way
and more pauses i'm in my pausing
that much i mean jesus okay so
we get so they get to our
category and they're doing the tech check
for our category it's me paul scheer
for how did this get made ah
tag for um don't ask tig bryan
safi for groceries
ah this podcast call i think the
breakfast club and then ah conan o'brien
which was represented by matt jukes was
there to write well in chinese culture
yeah yes okay snl yeah so i
was really happy to see everyone was
funny but also everyone was kind of
weird like it was it was just
like a weird like we're all kind
of looking at each other like
what was going on yeah and there
was this point where okay so first
of all we had done all these
extensive tech checks and then the tech
person is like alright everyone looks good
and i was like well it looks
like matt needs to flip his logo
because it's backwards and he'll probably want
to be facing the right way when
he wins
and then we all kind of laughed
a little bit about how he's gonna
win and whatever and he's like i
don't know how i got this position
because even he's going i know i'm
gonna win it's like it just was
like conan is a shoe in for
this award
then we have to watch the show
but silently so our are on i
don't i don't think were you on
camera the entire show for no no
no no one at home could see
us but we were on camera within
the zoom for the unlike a green
room and then they were playing the
show in the same green room unlike
another square but you
our mix were on so that the
second a winner was announced you wouldn't
have your mic off basic right right
but it kinda gave me this like
funeral feeling of like where you can't
laugh like i was like
i started getting kind of listening to
the story shut the fuck up
i did your dirty work by going
to the fucking amby yeah stop at
scotland yard said today i'm setting the
scene i also think it is worth
telling the behind the scenes of this
okay so they announced this next category
at it's best it's best podcast hosts
and they list
these podcasts and they they do it
like the oscars like where they said
the name and then they play an
audio clip from the show but it's
completely out of context i should just
be like for i'm like ah like
best host podcast of the podcast you
know this or that so with so
and so and then she'd be like
yeah i didn't even know what he
said and i never even thought and
then they go
so were they that short like yeah
absolutely there was one that was like
and that's when ruth bader ginsburg arrived
and i like there's no context for
charity oh shit i feel like a
parody of itself i started crying laughing
so my mic is on and i'm
like i was like turning red in
front of my yellow background and i
was like crying bridge and i could
see like ah my friends on the
zoom were like looking at me but
they couldn't tell why i was laughing
and it was making me laugh so
hard and then brian was texting me
i was texting him about why i
was laughing and i couldn't stop and
then like i started a compost
really fun like i was having a
great time and then i started coming
down and then the next thing that
pops up is this like ten year
old with his podcast oh yeah
a ten year old has a podcast
he was like yeah at least the
kids have podcast today they had remember
and i started crying again
i'm sorry i had to like duck
out of the frame and then we
come i come back and frame guitar
category within my kid have a podcast
by the way i don't think it's
probably a good idea for you to
be able to be old enough to
rent a car before you can have
a podcast i don't think it's up
to you i think that maybe twenty
five access
stuff they can have a podcast you
won't even know it paul you need
to stop defending everyone we talk against
okay yes that's right no more
stop devil's advocating hey let's just disband
or the literally go they they they
go okay now for best comedy podcast
nominees are and they put it to
our face you know they put our
logo on the screen how high up
is this category is it like you
know you know how it goes important
it was towards the end so it's
it's important okay so we were up
for an important award all
so i have to say that sometimes
they would lose the nominees and they
would show their faces and well whatever
but a lot of times earlier on
they would say here's the nominees for
best you know business podcast and then
would just be like five thousand zoom
podcast logos they wouldn't even send on
email
yeah wouldn't even say the names and
i like look everyone who's watching the
things on their phone you know when
it was a blip it was like
they'd be like yeah nominees they just
flash a bunch of logos like where
you could say them out loud like
at least give us the dignity so
i thought you were gonna present lauren
i thought it was true they didn't
they didn't know fellow yeah
yeah like everyone agreed lauren was gonna
present and then they just never brought
it up to you know and i
saw other they didn't have other people
presenting twain said no yeah because we
had too much kenan thompson presented our
category um
and so would they announce us and
then they use this dago and the
winner is kona needs a friend and
then i go
oh no and okay i thought you
could hear me i was so excited
because i thought it was really funny
but then policy you couldn't hear me
and so many on the coma laughing
as he wins because i was already
crying laughing from all the stuff that
was happening backstage that was only funny
to me i when it was announced
i first of all it like it
happened very fast like after keenan yeah
introduced everything it was like immediately and
the winner is and so i was
still looking for you i got my
phone to take a video and i
was looking for where you were so
i could say it was too it
was a millisecond yeah it really was
and so i will all i saw
was you just like so laughing and
nodding like
of course
oh man it really know what happens
in these award shows your category comes
up and then it's over and i
mean in my case i went up
to accept right to matt early i
remember when you remember when i was
nominated for an emmy and then you're
like jane lynch is gonna win so
just enjoy it i said fuck you
i felt bad but i also like
having gone through it a couple of
times yeah you start to get in
your head like i can when i
can win and then yeah you crash
right after because you can into yourself
in it and it makes you feel
bad and so i just kind of
wanted to say like hey this is
probably what's going to happen the person
in my dreams it was true but
no oh i'm not actually mad no
i mean it was true and it's
all accurate i'm
just saying you did tell me that
and it was true and now when
conan was nominated thought he's gonna win
and then he did and i mean
it does and makes it more as
your expectations thing because like especially if
like ah if you don't think you're
gonna win then it may and you
do it actually makes winning fun you
totally because i did go like well
what if we did win somehow right
now and
and i'm like what am i going
to say and then i only had
two seconds to really think about that
and then it was over so right
now it the the minute your category
comes up it flashes in your mind
like but wait i have a shot
at this yeah and if if it
only happens then then you only have
like twenty seconds before you don't win
it's better for your mental it's not
as big of a comedown i
yet at the the the one year
i went to the movies where it
was like i was like oh we're
not going to win we're not going
to win and then when it was
when that when they were reading like
and the winner is when that when
that was being said all of us
and i got so charged up like
i was full of electricity like wait
what
it happens and then it didn't happen
and it was right such as a
steep letdown yes so quickly yeah i
feel like i never i didn't think
about it until this one moment and
now i know yeah and i have
a party afterwards and yeah it's like
it's crazy it's it's nuts well we're
gonna say about matt
oh matt gave gourley gave a really
nice acceptance speech on on behalf of
the conan show and was one of
i think maybe jamie pointed this out
one of the only people we saw
if not the only who thanked the
listeners whoa i o one o oh
i was so shocked watching people think
a long list
most of like people with their podcasts
and not just have like a heartfelt
because i'm like yeah this doesn't if
we'd won would you have even thanked
josh i absolutely would not and i
hope that just yeah absolutely
but i'm but i did think like
oh
only because we're getting the common good
cats are we getting a chat from
joshua on that note no refunds oh
alright like in bed like i'm watching
this
ah fingers in his ears saying la
la la yeah that's only fair he's
okay but i did say why it
was thinking like is it because we're
comedy podcasts that my instinct would be
just to go like well i think
ourselves for being funny and like that
we really nailed it like whatever you
say i'm stupid because like everyone else
was
taking it so seriously then i was
like i guess they do like journalism
with their podcasts and stuff and so
then that's like a whole nother level
of what they're doing like we do
bullshit around and that is what's fun
about it and that's the kind of
podcast i like to listen to but
it's like most these categories where people
who are like with the stunning portrayal
of the wars in
wherever you digitas yeah exactly now they
show you the wars in the indigenous
what other what other current event words
are there it always bugs me because
they tell it they they coach you
when you're nominated for an award to
give a speech they say don't thank
everyone because you can do that later
after
the show like make a speech that
yeah the speeches given impact are the
ones where you say something personal or
you think wasn't in particular or something
and no one does it and so
both times that i want to just
went up and did a comedy speech
and everyone like really appreciated and i
saw jane lynch afterwards she's like i
loved your speech you know yeah like
over and over lauryn she doesn't know
who i am it's really boring to
watch people thank their agents i mean
i don't care like i understand that's
how it all came to be or
whatever thanks i'm like for the show
you're honest easy on how it all
came to be well know what i'm
saying like that's how the deal was
made yeah exactly i you're like their
thanks is your ten percent
yeah that's how it is
watch
from mad men oh yeah i've been
um watching orchards my whole life and
i love them so much but like
i feel like what i always loved
growing up was like when somebody would
be like this was always my dream
and like i'd say some things like
you wanna hear that i don't know
yeah or talk about the one person
who inspired you like you know like
ah
tom hanks is speech about his teacher
or where they could have gotten up
there and be like i really appreciate
how mark marron opened the door for
me to be able to voice exactly
exactly well it's yeah thank thank you
lauren for ah doing that for us
really appreciate you're welcome yes i was
ah when when it was finally happening
i was i really
arised oh this is a very nice
thing that lauren did for us as
a team yeah thanks i you know
i also was like this is kind
of fun like i mean it it
i enjoyed myself just by making myself
laugh so i can have fun anywhere
i guess but i had a great
time and i think you know about
yourself die yeah
would i hope we win an award
soon because i was like we needed
a long shot
yeah through best suit charm i yeah
yeah huge oil swag let's make a
shoe charm that isn't award yes it
rips off the whatever it's going to
have it does it and which rips
off the oscar and the api is
basically an oscar that's holding a microphone
over instead of sora yeah it's like
it's like it's like a
the midpoint between an emmy and an
oscar it is it's kind of a
swirly oscar it's better than the what
was one i like a steamy or
a webby or something like that it
was basically just like swirling i don't
know a lot of the words are
at your reward you don't i noticed
out you threw out
yes aesthetically this award goes in the
trash wow it was it felt like
it was tinfoil wrapped together why didn't
you put it in the loo
oh that's in the total doorstop what
would we had a we had a
comedy bang bang sketch about someone who
used his awards as doorstops but i
can't remember what it is it was
such a funny idea though but only
specific to people who knew that that
cliche of actors using supposedly using their
awards story his one is doing anything
funny with it i think everyone's got
it somewhere nice and that's that yeah
i think some people put it in
the in the bathroom or as a
doorstop or whatever really yeah i do
because getting so gross about it being
ah covered here theses what but
the faecal plume
the toilet what what bugs me about
that is they're not treating it with
that irreverence when they win the award
oh they're not saying this is going
right in my toilet versus going up
my house it's still it's still doing
that but it's still giving it reverence
by making it a joke in the
house yes exactly then everyone sees it
and then it's like a thing and
then you talk to me in houses
to be funny but they're acting like
i'm i get help you believe hilarious
that people can
inside the houses can be funny if
if they want to try wow house
is hilarious and the people are just
normally the people inside when you finally
say want to try what is the
funniest house in the womb and devi's
house and it says he was houses
of course funny but the wheelhouse the
winchester the peewee house is being fixed
up a little bit and there he
yeah i noticed i drove past it
is it a real house yeah and
pasadena it is anyways but inside it's
not like no i'm sure it's not
i go you goldberg
like i went to um see it
at one point like a couple of
years ago and it was kind of
messed up in the front and the
stairs were like kinda cracked and you
know it was you couldn't really turn
safely front and now it looks like
it looks a little like me yeah
also something it still looks it still
looks like the same colors and also
things like oh my god you guys
ah
um i'm gonna google it okay have
fun with that you can't have fun
everyone
ah wow what did you say every
time you googled anything could i kind
of verbal commitment you will do that
sure um you guys ah ever enjoy
looking at houses that were in movies
or do you not really care in
real life from yeah like in
i don't think i've ever been around
like you right now
even the brady bunch house i don't
think i've ever driven i winced in
front of it took a picture i
know random days you know to realize
like oh i heard that was over
here and then go find it my
friends and i lie on it my
friends hiked by the bat cave and
i've always kind of wanted to go
to that but literally like here when
i'm done yeah i don't know that
i've ever been outside of fw
famous like ah a famous like a
famous movie house or anything i don't
think i like the wonder years houses
around here i haven't been to that
when i want to go to that
i wouldn't know that if i tripped
over it wow you ever watch when
calls a giant i did watch one
two years but i don't remember what
their house won't cool you do know
would you do
would you think
i was using the uae two way
one moment oh yeah lily girl billy
lazy mirage it's whoa would you do
june would just turn up and walk
out on me where if you watch
it online if you watch um wonder
years i'm like hulu or whatever it's
on they put in like a weird
cover of that song oh right so
they did get the rights for the
other music i think because it was
that my friend had had a like
illegal copy of the wonder years that
i had forever because
cause you they because we want to
hear music well it had all the
music and like when they would never
air to reruns because there was some
issue with that or something i don't
know about you know old contracts they
never expected anyone to ever rewatch these
shows anywhere else so they they wouldn't
put that in anywhere so it's now
like when we did the ferns movie
every single thing we put
in it we had to get tells
movie
what my mouse movie oh that's right
yeah it's the difference between defers yeah
i'll have thompkins we had to get
every single every single piece of art
that was in it every single song
anything it had to be ah the
contract had to be across all mediums
that will ever be invented in perpetuity
through the end of time because they
never want to be situation
just to make shit up yeah why
don't you just like sing on just
about anybody dvd couldn't hurt
oh my god dare you literally dare
yo hey i can say that it's
my movie that's true um that was
a big problem with ah w caribbean
y w care p b um i
think it couldn't be so either syndicator
they couldn't sell a box they couldn't
do a box set of it because
of all the original
music that was in it because it
was you know sen radio station they
would use actual songs how could they
get away with that in the moment
maybe they had like a license like
you know hell yeah does snell does
it because they have the news license
i believe ah the like they're part
of what sports licenses are oh like
lot
so so basically you know live events
in sporting events that they televise the
the stadium will play a song and
you can hear it on the on
the event so they oh yes special
like news license that ah an s
and l is part of that so
they're able to use songs that they
can't then repeat on the show that's
why so many
like so many of their sketches are
taken off peacock and stuff right there
and people find this interesting know can
we do a vote what was more
interesting that or lauren story i'm the
story and obviously it was my story
so people you know yeah i'm a
person here's we barely talk about okay
true i haven't learnt the topic do
have time to take a break lawrence
top no we
we have time for one more december
one more laurence topic than gnome the
gnome was a huh
not instagram it's really what the comments
were flowing everyone thought it was so
funny the poll was many haha killing
it many haha the whole oh my
god okay the amount of haha is
first of all there's seven hundred thirty
seven comments on this like do understand
when you don't have that many listeners
like that's like really good game bajo
la
lots of people finding a hilarious classy
testicle and a hat um yeah there's
a range okay these are good comments
a classy testicle and a hat
and i then did a poll and
um yeah i will say the scott
side won the poll but it was
close because two yeah because the the
two votes were haha or i am
scott and i think a lot of
people could not resist the fun of
of pretending to be scott for
oh it's so fun to be me
that's so so just do it for
a day pretend to be me for
a day so it was like forty
something percent said all around your your
apartment few wattle yep
wobble things i need to veto in
batman returns diane de vito died
oh what am i a woman who
looked exactly like me not related named
diane de vito
real perlman and she was tall too
but she still looks like danny devito
burt all yes seventy eight made by
the way veto once ah huh go
ahead oh i want to say something
about being talked about i thought of
the other day it's so good
so when i was any inch in
oh it's my own part of restaurant
rounding lord was it called that because
you're so tall ever was looking at
your chin
um one of the one of the
waitresses was head of hating you know
should we say how it had a
friend who was who was who was
really tall and was getting her was
looking for a tall woman or it
was looking for a tall man to
date right and she's like how tall
is going there and she was like
how tall are you and i said
six
two and she's like ok she's six
one okay so that's good um let
me let me tell let me tell
her about you so i go okay
fine and she goes tells her about
her and then she comes back with
more questions to me it's like you're
still trying to narrow it down after
like you're six one and you're looking
for someone taller like no more no
more narrowing
if she's not allowed to have any
more standards other no being one is
you get whatever shitty boyfriend you're offered
no
but here was he was a circus
freak here's a question do you have
a hairy chest ooh la la i
was like no not really and then
it was off like a home goes
to la fucking qualification
i sincerely you don't fall further questions
she found her tall hairy chested man
they exist i guess that's true they
do yeah they do exist avoiding them
and i'm sorry if it doesn't exist
adam scott
alright we have to take a break
right back
we're back we're back i'm paul i'm
scott wood i'm laurie have to introduce
ourselves a young people know why not
right why not professor let's see what
every five minutes just in case people
forgets ooh
um ah would you do this weekend
paul well i'll tell you and i'll
tell you true tell tell it to
me good i want this story to
be good make it good ah
we have um
a bunch of friends who live in
our neighborhood and we were on a
text thread and it's pretty active and
how many texts per day
oh my god i'm gonna say two
to three woe is me as our
other one not counting the taxed oh
yeah that shouldn't be counted as texts
but no they shouldn't be they shouldn't
be but when you when you get
to your phone and there's like sometimes
with our text chain there are over
a hundred yet texts and it says
you have one hundred and
three new messages and fifty eight of
them are thumbs up or i should
be origin do like no gives us
the red the red circle with a
number for the amount of actual messages
and then like a purple circle with
um like a heart in it for
the amount of tax what's in a
circle i guess the number of numbers
or why is it that otherwise they're
circle
why i think should become yellow circle
it should be like the messages and
it says like you have twenty messages
and you have fifteen tax write i
think there should be also be a
yellow circle that will let you know
how many of them are worth your
time yeah they're nice and that should
be about every there should be some
sort of filter where like asks you
any questions about what you find nature's
how tall are you how
harry is your chest
yeah begins okay just just those two
by the way we should put out
a poll about that
what would the one idea you may
do i'll tell you how harry's oh
okay yeah those were those are the
two houses you can either vote out
all you or how hairy your chest
okay i'll put that up
ah so what once we were all
talking about getting vaccinated um and tracking
our progress i got five g
try to talk to each other what
is early hit their first really oh
it's already available dragon um i got
i realized like oh my god we're
all vaccinated then we can hang out
together indoors yeah and i made an
executive decision without checking with janie and
said we're going to have a party
um the city
feel about this the earliest she felt
great about it the i'm assuming thank
um where we're going to ah you
know let's we got to figure out
when everyone is completely in the clear
and then like as soon as we
can after that date let's all get
together and have a party at our
house and so one of the one
of the participants in the thread made
a chart
of when everyone was because we talked
about our schedules when everyone was getting
vaccinated first doe second dose and when
they were fully in the clear so
second dose third dose bunch that's right
clear and
how many doses are you going to
get guys i'm getting enough done i'm
gonna keep getting tomb i'm i keep
going until they tell me to stop
i want to get i want to
do it around the world and get
all the different vaccines yep i want
to go to india next oh i
was thinking like walgreens cbs rite aid
i just wanna see how they're different
um so we just had
it on saturday and it was we
were all like giddy yeah to be
hanging out together like everyone was at
a at a level that never stopped
throughout the entire evening and it was
really fun yeah and it i it
made me so happy like i forgot
that
ah that feeling of hosting a party
i hadn't we haven't had people over
in such a long time and i
was in the kitchen like you know
getting something to put out i'm sure
she was she wasn't there oh dinah
didn't come she was couples only it
was couples oh she's such an old
maid
she'll die a crone um so i
was in the kitchen getting stuff to
put out and i just looked over
because we have like an open plan
um you can see the living room
from the kitchen and i just looked
inside everybody is sitting around and talking
and it made me so happy i
was so happy it was
really i i could have lived in
that feeling forever it was it was
fantastic i have not had that experience
yet however my friends did go to
a wedding last weekend that was had
been pushed and rescheduled and you know
throughout the pandemic and now enough people
are vaccinated so everyone who's there was
vaccinated and heavily instagrammed with
it was and it was like i
haven't seen it um you don't have
to say i mean so yeah i
don't know if you know this person
um oh my jet anywhere she married
this guy been no jennifer lowe benefactor
j lo jennifer lopez jennifer lo
okay
yes yes she wanted the only people
with soapy fun is there a pez
dispenser of her yeah wow she's one
of the only below we've had isn't
her name she she deserves like can
you think of another celebrity with peasant
and i mean george lopez sure isn't
but someone with with not named lopez
with peasant their name ooh that's a
tall order my friend yeah and now
here
ah
but no my friend said that it
was just like really overwhelming like at
first i didn't want to go out
of her hotel room was kinda like
everyone's by the pool it's kind of
a thing and then she went out
and then everyone just got trashed and
have y'all bad thing yeah we went
through a lot of booze like the
the what i put the recycling out
the next day was a symphony of
clinics yeah
the people people are always like oh
it's gonna take me so long to
figure out how to talk to people
again or whatever it's like two minutes
and no i know that's not my
concern my concern is not social awkwardness
like how am i going to have
a conversation it's more like the getting
over the fear that being close to
someone is bad like
i feel like that's the part that's
hard for me to for like forget
like standing next to someone and being
not being worried at all seems weird
or not being obsessive about like you
know i'm washing my hands and after
i touched my mail
yeah you're but yeah i called my
but my mail because it's my most
male structure
can't even do squats but yeah it's
so ripped it looks like grass my
ass is jacked
your s a small it's a joke
the swell hard taped okay cakes i
haven't heard that one got a couple
of cake donuts back there
little
how many learn how many times have
you ever looked at a button went
nice but terrell bunch you kidding me
you guys like butts what did you
say scott did you say you say
it to yourself to yourself yeah okay
in your head you'll like i definitely
have never said it just to some
stranger um what about to a friend
see a great ass you're gonna notice
it i mean i've never said it
to someone but i've said it about
someone oh i've said it about people
i think um butts can be
great you know i think if someone
has a great but you should say
to their face
i'm sure anyone will be happy to
hear you say to there but they're
doing all the work
maybe rested just leave now nice job
hey bend over versa i just gotta
say if you hurt my mouth i'd
be
jesus you know what sucks but this
isn't it i know it doesn't suck
what is somebody because i just my
mom just started listening to three them
so no hundred i just got an
iphone and so it's kind of changed
the game with how easy it is
to access all these things i mean
i don't know is it became very
easy for her to find it so
what was she rockin before samsung galaxy
oh sure sure i had a lot
of android users in my family and
there's they're slowly turning i think i
only have one green text left some
people get very mad when you talk
about this yeah when you the end
it's look it's all fucking oh i
think it's a series i will say
i wanted to leave i'm so loser
yes many times i've almost gotten different
phones but then i just think i
really know how to use this one
and then yeah the whole thing and
then yeah because i know other phones
can be better um but you know
my name is mike had a google
phone for a minute and i really
liked it and we we both almost
turned completely to the highway will accept
any phones that anyone wants to give
us oh if you want to send
me a scotch scotch yeah answer
yes please just send us phones well
we'll don't say squads don't send us
ipods or ipads um god you know
scott people really is relatable please send
us first generation ipods
i still have to click or ipods
by the way they're grim sure you
do i have some problem here's a
word yeah here's the problem with the
touch screen i paused which i have
one but you can't fast forward while
you're looking at the road like if
like clicking something you can kill it
just but you can't just
like tap a screen and guess where
the fast forward button is like you're
trying to what fast-forward what just like
skip over a track or whatever you
can do that you could do that
god i'm saying yeah you gotta memorize
i knew this
oh you just you just want to
be contrary no it's actually that i
just am on my phone so much
that i can do a lot without
oh
yeah but it's oops
shit
how contrary did you guys have um
like a mentor when you were starting
out in comedy and someone was telling
about their mentor and i was thinking
let's call he had kept like a
document of um i mean i know
that i was upset
i didn't but i do i do
remember getting a lot of unsolicited advice
is that the same thing that's interesting
i didn't know i didn't have a
person like that i didn't have like
someone that i look to for nothing
i yeah i don't i don't think
that i did there would be that
i admired and everything but nobody kind
of took me under their wing in
that way or yeah not that i
thought mark did for me he was
very nice and
in he would come to all of
my shows he was some tiny nice
he would sometimes like say hey what
if i introduced it because he knew
that would be meaningful to the audience
you know wow so he would go
up and introduce it he would be
in some of the show he'd be
like hey even if you're nice think
this isn't funny i just wanna let
you know i'm going to stand up
here and introduce
maybe you'll it'll make you think maybe
it is funny i would count poppy
leave his mentors when i worked on
that show i mean sure you learn
a lot i learned so many but
they were they were very patient to
teachers in terms of comedy in terms
of like yeah you know like explaining
something rather than just saying this isn't
good enough
do it again it was like anyone
has their moments where they'll shoot something
down or or yes a caustic way
to shoot something down yeah but they
they were for the most part you'd
come in with an idea and they
would take it seriously and not schooling
that sucks yeah they would they would
take an hour sometimes to like go
yarwood and and route because and that
was all a reaction to s and
l
think yeah yeah bottles experience on it
absolutely yeah yeah i would say him
and i'm trying to think of any
restaurants that i oh boy
i was also thinking about the show
for y'all um mike and i just
did naomi paragon and andy beckman podcast
couples therapy and we and we were
telling one of the stories but when
we first were in the same room
as each other which i think i've
told on three-time which is when mike
broke garry shandling to u c oh
yeah and yes yes and and they
were like why would he go to
you cbn like he was just like
he he was a gary was so
cool like wanting to like see what
people were doing now and like keeping
you know keep up to date on
everything you do that a lot i
would see a mature and it's so
that's so cool because i think that's
like that is really rare like once
oh for sure i mean i feel
like i've been doing improv for like
i don't know
years now or something and i don't
really i know and i don't really
want to go see something you don't
i mean like i'm like i'm excited
to stay home and now that we've
had a year of staying home i
might feel a little differently but like
right i don't you see me now
yay yeah right right now i would
leave this and go do something but
but i feel like that's such a
cool trait to have
like someone who people admire that they
still go to the shows and or
i could good audience i would say
i would say one other person the
mentored me in a in a smaller
way definitely because bob was a big
one which would be jeff garlin in
a way like jeff would i saw
him verily very early on i went
to go see him up in san
francisco
i saw him fairly
early yonder he stood oh i'm about
yeah
i should write poems i wrote yeah
okay i'm no i went to i
went to see an amazon book yeah
yeah probably a book yeah well i
went to see him in san francisco
record is half hour hbo special or
something like that you saw me in
the crowd and like thanked me and
ever and ever since then you would
like ask me on every show he
did he put me in curb your
enthusiasm yeah
i didn't audition or anything you just
gave me a part and you were
a cop i was a cop yes
in the palace didion chicken emphasis um
but yeah i would say i would
say for him he he he would
do that he put me on like
shows with robin williams and stuff like
that and like he was he was
always very generous with yeah like robin
williams is another exam
apple where i feel like there's so
many stories of him showing up to
theaters and just like wanting to jump
in and yeah people and have fun
and like that's like the coolest thing
i mean for a young person in
pricing have a grumbling him show up
and want to do something i definitely
want to do that kind of thing
like i want to i was feeling
that very strongly
like right before the pandemic feeling like
i want to go just see shows
like i used to i used to
spend so much time watching shows yeah
i mean yeah go i go do
a show and then i just watch
whatever else happened after yeah yeah and
i really was feeling like i want
to feel that connection to the community
again i want to know who people
r i want to see what's happening
i agree oh yeah i was thinking
about my chicago days um where like
it was just the most fun to
just like stumble into the theater and
like see what was going on just
hanging out yeah i was drunk or
high i'm a little bit
some a lot of beds and the
kids i like you know there's you
just could show up at any point
and there's someone to hang out with
someone to talk to and like i
showed a watch and it's like something
to do any night and that's always
there it just like it as you
do longer and longer that becomes less
of a like thing you do with
your time but like it does in
an established way i'm like oh that
seems like a b
really nice yeah and i think he's
i think it's failing every time people
like you know jason bazookas to to
do a weekly show and stuff like
that i always i always enjoy that
yeah um we should we should do
huh to break time oh wow oh
hey do a breakdown where you can
see right through em shifter what are
you suggesting we do something
yeah was i don't know anything what
do you guys wanna do you wanna
put on a play we've been begging
you to do live stuff and you're
like now wow you are from the
computer and you're like what is that
pays eighteen
answers are watts who i've been on
tour with you guys what are you
talking about that was what you want
that's what you're suggesting boys i guess
you'd say now do it on zoom
or duh it's fun you know there's
plan we have a tie we've been
doing these on online shows
and it's been a really fun it's
just silly if you're invited that you
turn not not to those shows that's
still just being more oh no yes
but what have you
idea we want them to get what
they're paying you're invited to start your
own show and invite us to do
it no thank you
easy it would be for you you
just sit right where you are right
now i don't want to sit here
i barely want to sit here now
sit some place else then stupid my
guide i want to stand why did
you guys with a guy like do
get sad that we have to perform
on the computer i just know i
just don't like i have to do
it i've over the pandemic
but i've had to do it so
much yeah and i mean work on
you know doing working on bang bang
like a whole extra day now you
know working on the editing it together
and stuff is like i just i
just don't you know well you should
look better people um what i think
is that it makes her the show
all the time it makes yeah but
not i do the show some of
the time
we wouldn't have this problem um alright
i think that will do when you
know there's people watching it makes it
the the difference in the vibe like
there's a difference in the vibe from
like if you're just zooming with a
friend and it feels like after a
while it doesn't take long for it
to feel like this isn't this doesn't
feel that great you know what i
mean like
like it feels awkward then like the
thing that we're doing right now there
there there's a difference in vibe to
that where you feel a little more
charged up knowing that there's people going
to listen to this eventually yeah and
then there's the feeling of knowing that
people are watching live is like it's
i can't believe how much it feels
like a show like it really feels
fine
does really make you feel different and
like i feel like i'll be like
sweaty and like putting in you know
you have to put in a lot
of energy from your soul because you're
projecting something trying to be humorous through
a computer which is harder yeah um
there's no gauge on laughter and you
sound like a scientist yeah
ivan so you know look like one
doesn't pretty you're so oh my god
yeah alright let's go to a break
and we're back and guess what everyone
i don't know oh oh i forgot
he said i should've said everyone except
lauren and scott oh you want them
to guess yes but i also want
you don't know
look if you guys want to guess
you can guess okay i'm gonna guess
what
your guess is what yeah well the
answer is chicken but oh yes it
was nice but chicken know that chicken
is a nice change to fit my
face chicks on it's ass oh you
like chicken says do chickens fart when
the chickens who airs out of the
chloe what are you doing
a stock hold on a second if
you have information what do you do
with it then well i'm just wondering
because like do they have the parts
safari today ford parts what everything farts
every single thing worms don't fart i'm
sure you know anything that poops can
fart because air can you
what is the loudest parks you elephants
the loudest fart i'll google it
i'll see you guys later
paul actually left this my god it's
an auto-fill post actually want to know
that people want to know hippo farts
supposed to be little doubt among the
worldwide web that the loudest fart on
earth is the hippo fart accept it's
not one video is over twisted
hippo farts are virtually silent as people
who've seen hippos know what why is
it coming up in huge bold than
a tip of farts if it's not
okay but the loudest fart ever recorded
was one hundred and thirteen decibels think
wielded by the name you guys have
dear the name
by herkimer short
short this is favre gambler short guinness
book of world records wait it was
a guy
and his name is chore well you
i'd be a woman
i mean no i thought been be
an animal i thought i thought an
animal was coming and i thought herkimer
was just person who recorded it yeah
so whales a really big firsts sea
lions though the smelliest
okay i'm glad that's all squared away
and now it is thought herkimer short
has the loudest fart at a hundred
thirteen desk does he have a wikipedia
page he should be used to be
a lit limerick why does this happen
there once was a herkimer short
there once was a herkimer george you
wanted to record a loud fort so
he stuck his butt up in the
air sandwich wait herkimer chart let summer
break easily hear the rhyme scheme it's
not good to let out the world's
big meter oh it's okay
okay her commercial oh and there they
have the the image is like a
dude a fat dude holding his nose
like it's smelly is at him
oh my god i've refused to
it was the first person to fart
in the world this is literally wow
god
we answer today i think but i
had to tell roger it says born
joseph poo hole
okay come on
please guys
eighteen fifty six
what
before him
se o p u jus oh ooh
good stuff oh god
that's like ah that's like what google
is showing me it's not i'm on
some weird website this is why this
is a fact
alright paul so google is just showing
me websites i'm not on one
alright it's time for one of our
famous three cheers people talk about this
all the time they are constantly telling
our families that we're doing this um
and it's a little game that we
like to play and we get a
different game each time and they're submitted
by fans or josh so this is
a game called five seconds
honestly not a fan yeah actually he
does not like the show but he
keeps sending us games this game is
called five second rule submitted by tamer
tamer the object is to name three
things in five seconds player one comes
up with a question such as name
three famous jennifer's more of a command
player two has five seconds to answer
if they succeed they get a point
if they fail player three gets a
chance to answer the same question but
player three cannot reuse reuse the ones
that were already said they must come
up with three brand new answers you
keep alternating between players two and three
stills till someone wins a point so
okay this look
ks like we would take turns being
the person person giving the topics yes
um and then how many points to
win
ah that's a good question and something
you know if you're given point until
someone wins a point oh until someone
wins a point and then okay got
it right that's weird one point doesn't
seem like enough then let's say five
yeah because we're gonna get five seems
too much let's do three points three
for three dumb
three for three adam scott very poor
matchup i love you i got you
ben la oh okay okay ma'am alright
um who's counting the five seconds are
doing so that's like yeah yeah alright
whoever's whoever's the ah the moderator will
do that all right oh okay but
i would like to moderate a frenchie
moderate firm
first all moderate first that means i
have to think of things which is
the worst and we already know who
goes we'd go one at a time
yeah so it it it's you want
to go first lauren and i'll go
section share time okay
okay alright so lawrence first yeah yeah
okay okay lauren name three red fruits
apple strawberry pomegranate scott
ah name three playground ah things swing
set slide and the rings that you
ah the monkey bars lorin one point
a piece but to be over in
two things lorin name three things you
can see in the sky birds claw
louts airplane scott one airplane name three
famous boats titanic ah the one from
jaws and ah the one from lauren
name three famous boats um ah the
queen mary um the um a
yes yes yeah yeah they do yeah
i mean ok a minnow the minnow
the pinta the santa maria oh i
agree right there
it would have been good all right
what does the score am i really
learned about those boats a lot i
think we're too to the woolrich it
was very important that we knew the
names of those votes
alright um salon you can await doesn't
go to lauren first i think oh
no it goes dimino because she wasn't
able to do it looks like it
i can win oh okay okay i'll
be the first to three does she
get a chance to tie me at
three yeah we all do no i
don't think so i think it's either
gf sister don't you round after that
and then okay yes
yeah alright great alright scott name three
candy bars snickers three musketeers almond joy
alright then scott is the first to
three oh wow i think so yes
right isn't that what we just yeah
so now he's now to new ground
good yeah so i'm gonna say that
counts as one
point o like in the round you
wanna be the first to three and
then you earn one because then clemson
whoever gets to three so we venmo
robbins and paul has to do it
some more know that i'm gonna do
i'm gonna moderate know okay you guys
okay got it got it yes
because then it'll it'll be like the
it's like going to the super bowl
yeah
guys it's brackets ok his brack i
like brackets like a ten dollar six
guys like what scott like attending the
super bowl not as a player but
like watching know it's like brackets okay
got it okay yeah i'm all for
an established it's like brackets paul for
paul is gonna go first and i'm
going to say um
name three flavors of skittles
but blue red yellow
yeah okay scott named three flavors of
skittles bitch
tang e farts
i don't know slavers recital and watermelon
okay yeah who knows just kills my
eyes okay well that was a bus
okay um okay your category is paul
name three brands of a cv
oh chevy ah dodge other car manufacturers
not su vs
oh my god okay vain thoughts turn
tahoe that's all i can think yeah
bronco bronco i had a bronchitis ah
tahoe bronwyn you're running comeau j or
with them
oh my god okay
ah white bronco you did okay it
got stolen outside of kai yeah i
don't know how many times do we
know who stole our cars o j
simpson one hundred percent it's it's kind
of ridiculous okay um so so far
nobody has points that's my point i'm
doing a really good job as a
mater
editor actually ok you really shut us
down yeah okay now paul named three
apple products iphone i pod ah apple
tv you got it okay scott name
um three television networks
cbs abc fox okay making it easy
now everyone has a point um ok
paul
name three black and white animals a
cow a skunk ah tuxedo cat good
job okay paul has to um scott
name three animals that have green somewhere
on them somewhere on them ah
a frog a toad and ah hey
i can't i don't know ah a
ah now i can answer yes yeah
oh okay ah a turtle ah an
iguana ah a
a grasshopper good doe paul you got
three points okay seems you have a
point oh yeah he's got one big
point i've a point i'm a big
point paul has a big point okay
and now i got moderates everybody's got
a big point don and not me
alright are you guys reading dotting what
was the waiters his name in the
nps big adventure island small smile simone
who goes for lauren probably searching yeah
haven't gone awhile okay lauren named three
bands that start with our radiohead um
ah um um and man paul named
three bands start with our replacements r
e m re
wrestling field nah it's not bad that's
not a bad okay okay so now
lauren lauren name three things have cotton
in them cotton balls q tips um
tissue
just tissue of guy i don't know
just to have certain is tissue made
of cotton i don't like clean exes
let me look at you and me
look it up you should go to
the judges
alright our tissues timmy park
who is first tissue some are some
are okay great i got it okay
great
um paul hi name three words in
the constitution we the people
one of you are clearly trying to
help paul way laura names three constitutional
amendments oh right to bear arms
and the free speech um the right
turn right oh i think so too
fast yeah you're you started counting faster
you didn't know anyways no three constitutional
amendments no anyway your time huh yeah
repeal of prohibition ah
oh my guy now eat okay now
we gotta learn
lauren name
three presidents before nineteen eighty um ah
nixon abraham lincoln washington yes paul named
three presidents since nineteen eighty
ah william jefferson clinton ah donald j
trump barack hussein obama
alright laura name how many ways do
i have i think wait i don't
even know
shit yeah we haven't been okay too
in two josh said we'll just stay
tuned to oh just see josh should
be the one the old chuck hillary
alright so lauren you can win you
can win with ray alright here we
go lauren name three things in a
freezer popsicles ice pack
and
here you go you one with ah
we all have a big point of
peace okay he's had one big point
now yeah
okay this round this round is for
two big points okay okay and i'm
gonna moderate so whoever gets three in
this round gets ultimately two big points
yeah what are we and what are
we playing to three big point three
big points okay so if i win
i win but that is a bracket
systems and
the next person up against you and
then that we'd have to see you
got the three points and then we
got the final out about the bracket
scott okay okay all right no time
to do the bracket now is the
bradwell it's part of the frankly alright
the bracket is whoever gets between the
two of you whoever gets this okay
is going to the finals
okay great okay
um okay who's the five of the
joint funeral i'm going to scout for
seven paul first last time okay great
scott name three shakespearian plays othello hamlet
romeo and juliet great for my three
paul um name three woody allen films
manhattan midnight in paris annie hall create
each have one point
um scots
you'd be good again
it's got because you're so pretty and
then to shop
ah scott name three possible eye colors
for a human whoa brown black black
black oh my that's for demons alright
brown no you don't get the point
right i don't i don't think people
stop blaming things i don't think people
can have two people let me look
i think they're wearing black guys black
black guys i think they're dark brown
don't think you have put black and
your driver's license hold on
true black guys do not exist contrary
to popular belief will but my belief
was popular well that's that's something i
enjoy oh okay so just got our
paul name three eye colors that he
made he kept naming face so what
do i name it here can't name
any of those
do it i knew i didn't do
it in time and you'll we repeated
the who said hazel green gray i
said green i said he'll repeat the
ones you said yeah that was this
isn't well because you kept going after
you lost you kept going yeah def
he automatically gets a point
okay medically okay scott
name um now i have two points
scott has one point is that correct
yeah
scott name three things you can ride
a horse a bicycle a unicycle okay
paul named three things you see the
circus elephant ringmaster cloud
okay you got three points then you
got a big point i got the
phone back to a point to go
to the finals
do you have three years you're willing
to fight three big points away now
it should be between me and lauren
exactly so paul's paul's gonna moderate between
us and we'll see when whoever goes
into files he also moderates yeah ok
ok alright alright go first go to
learn first lauren name three animals you
can see in your neighbourhood a dog
coyote a um um cat okay scott
name three animals you can't see in
your neighborhood zebra lion jaguar
jaguar you each have one point okay
lauren names ie scary bugs beetle roach
spider those aren't scary you know i'm
scared
oh scary to you that's it up
scott yes
mame
name three types of rug
parisian ah the kind of latin flies
on and a toupee
you could think of metric
the kind of latin flies on it
hey guys i'll give you that you
each have two points okay give her
a hard one
lauren
name three colors that are not ah
that are not named in the roy
g biv spectrum turquoise sapphire um ruby
wow lauren you have three big you
have three big points oh my gosh
i'm going to lie
i know and that is just so
big okay cool sounds now
collagen can yeah whoever gets the first
point or whoever gets to three points
whatever because no it can't be the
first point over it's right doesn't make
sense ok whoever gets to three to
three but who we have to flip
a coin to see who goes first
because that person has even got if
that's a
ah do you have a coin jaw
show i don't have a cold yeah
i don't josh why don't you just
say like you josh picks a number
pick a number between one intent and
then whoever gets one one hundred one
hundred whoever gets the closest yeah okay
he's picked alright over but used to
be
closest yeah yeah whoever is between one
and one hundred right one in one
hundred yeah ninety nine sixty four well
you should just done ninety eight
okay who's closest
oren was closest it was eight so
okay i'll go first okay
alright here we go ready
name three books that you have in
your house um i have oh god
why can't my minor feelings ah d
transition back ding okay paul the holy
bible ah my favorite thing is monsters
as above so below you actually have
a bite
obl i do have a bible yeah
i was gonna say bible to i
don't know well yeah you know bible
bible they're fun
yeah it's so much fun finals so
much fun to ho fun it's so
funny too it's like centrally funny i
was fun and funny jesus was funny
like the stuff you and tony
alright paul you have one point thank
you all right and now i go
to lauren yes you do
lauren named three bands that start with
b the bangles the bds the beatles
very good paul name three bands that
start with w
the wellingtons the wasabi nut
i put our lord you have one
point i'm like tied up or tied
up and now we go to lauren
again okay well wait just to name
three three battles sorry yeah go ahead
yeah three bands start with w okay
the weepies um
whitney houston
alright so now we go to ah
yes alright paul name three things in
a sushi restaurant
california roll was saudi
layla right
sorry you did not beat the clock
i started i started answering before you
made that horrible noise but go ahead
okay alright already yep and go salmon
tuna waiters okay lauren you have two
points
alright paul you gotta get you gotta
get this guy game i gotta get
this to stay in the game alright
this is big yes name three types
of rocks
igneous geode
oh so close for a name three
types of rocks for the win okay
um canyon
yeah i paul you're lucky yeah
huh
alright paul
name
three things a gardener would use in
his in his job a hose a
hoe and a rake very good paul
you have two points lauren you can
win right now okay okay alright and
i would go up against you know
you will just don't even win the
whole thing oh
finals baby is the final
lauren named three football players
ah to toe mo alright and paul
you can win name three football players
go ron jaworski bill burgee jim brown
you bore you rig that to the
man would win you know i love
football
you could tell by the the choices
made no that wasn't really fair game
that was really awesome i like that
guy thought it was fun and i
liked the bracket system i mean i'm
the big loser and i'm still fun
or that's true
now it's not so fun
your your revenue is great i was
i was right guy alright a maintaining
alright well see ya later yeah well
keep listening to threesome yeah whenever he's
on you can usually tell because it's
like thursday and it comes yeah and
there's probably like a bell rings at
your town um but please do ah
review us and rate us and share
us and all that shit we love
you guys thank you so much
as for listening to our silly show
we really are happy to be able
to keep doing it by love you
by lie
a