three
really oh did you catch that yeah
three vm instead of three this third
one this is our first three meme
episode and excited so excited i'm tim
jazz i'm over the moon i'm scared
and i'm terrified i'm
you're shaking like like a leaf i'm
quivering in my book clearly have you
seen a leaf shiver and fork four
times yes wow yeah were you trying
to scare it intentionally know here's what
it is when the first day of
autumn yeah what i do is i
go out and pick a tree any
tree that has leaves and i stare
it's gotta be a tree with leaves
gotta be true beliefs
cause otherwise it's just a collection of
branches yeah i'm not gonna see a
leaf shiver if you don't stare at
elite it can't be coniferous yeah so
i will stare at this leafy tree
and just see if there's a leaf
that's ready to go yeah and then
i see one and it starts to
quiver and quake yeah and shiver and
shake it's actually kind of creepy i'm
going to watch this
all the way down to make me
feel powerful yeah that's yeah no you
feel powerful like a god right yeah
yeah yeah yeah wow that's really good
wait that's really cool how you say
i just realised that you know what
i think you're cool that's not a
you're a cool person thanks hey by
the way who are we we're cool
people who are we oh are you
woman wait is it going to me
is this a thing that people can
stumble upon i think so really yeah
my name is laurie lap i don't
know but lauren lamkin is over here
he
may know the star of the radio
song that's how you know me
and i just got aquaman i'm a
guy who watched the wrong miss yeah
he's known for that best i'm also
one of those guys that's cool thanks
for supporting me my movie your endeavors
yeah yeah and we have a show
called freedom and if you've stumbled upon
this this is our premium episode of
threesome called threesome yeah welcome bye yeah
goodbye oh wait no stay because we're
going
to answer your voicemails as usual you
can send us voicemails at hag claims
eight dot com don't use your phone
to dial the number no easier phone
to go to the website oh yes
go to a website with phone we
know you want to use your phone
to do one of these things everybody's
everybody knows they're so tiny day just
try
use your phone phone phone phone alright
what do you say let's get to
it let's hear let me say let's
hear this voicemail okay alright what we
got here tight metal gang my name
is andrew i'm a long time test
pig on i got my mom into
your podcast and now like i think
she's an even bigger mistake than i
o de la
love and whenever i talk to her
inevitably threesome comes up as a topic
of conversation so is my question is
what shows movies of fans etc etc
did you and your parents bond over
you also put on oh she's very
cute that's a really high this andrew's
mom
that's so nice of utilization answer say
hi to your mom for me yes
um do you think that an andrew's
mom maybe you're just a pure listener
but ah are you listening just because
you know your son likes it and
you want to bond with him oh
that's nice oh but nobody i'm thinking
andrew might be younger and that his
mom is more in the age range
where it's oh yeah normal for her
to listen to this i think andrew's
mom is younger than andrew yeah look
my mom also likes threesome is that
true yeah trish are you kidding me
a handful of my fellow members listen
to three what a handful now any
more than a handful is too much
yeah it might be two maybe two
two anvils maybe two people um well
that's an interesting question so is there
anything that you sort of bonded with
one of your parents my dad and
i had sctv oh nice we like
i say yes td so i did
i have the same std that'll bring
you together and i remember i came
home and i said dad i got
chlamydia and he goes guess what guess
we get it right yeah yeah you
were born with it manage to meet
ya
is a beautiful day for these terrible
thing it is really just a pretty
rare disease so i think wanted sing
a song about it or write a
song about it chlamydia with media i'm
never getting rid of yeah i said
you want to do i love you
that's beautiful yeah do you how much
it gets
we used to watch the um the
network ninety episodes that would come on
on friday nights after friday night videos
or whatever and they were ninety minutes
long and i would watch that was
the that was like the only thing
that my dad and i shared in
that way yeah and i remember we
said the kitchen table watched a little
tv and we would like
smug look at look at each other
laughing that's nice i mean yeah and
of course we were smoked together yeah
yeah i recall um when i was
growing up that my parents would watch
letterman and then they would call me
out of my room for the top
tanks they always like to wait so
you're sleeping and you know i just
like dude in my room and then
they like hey let's have the top
ten one
in the morning it wasn't on that
late this was oh wait this is
the cbs letterman yeah um because it's
sort of like eleven thirty five ten
thirty i would say oh in the
midwest was attending oh right okay yeah
um i like it and so i
would watch the top ten and i
was always fun but we went as
a family we watched and continue to
watch a lot of tv together
or so my mom and i have
bonded a lot over ninety day fiance
but i stopped watching more recently but
it's annoying because she still wants to
talk about it yeah we also both
watched the bachelor that kind of stuff
we like a lot of realities okay
yeah i would i had a different
upbringing where my parents were always suspicious
of anything that i
was watching so so but i i
will say like i think i remember
one time i was watching ah conan
i think late at night and my
dad got up um and came out
and i remember from where i got
it from his bedroom because it was
late because i mean this is like
running tv yeah this is well
i don't know if the rocket i
don't think it was because i was
listening to it or watching a pretty
softly but you're like an inch away
from the scratch now that i'm older
i realised like anything will wake you
up and you'll just yeah like be
puttering around the house at night so
he came out on top saying yeah
thank you so he came out and
watched it and then i remember this
very clearly andy richter came out and
he said
andy baby
your dad's yes because he knows he
knew he knew who he was and
he was like a museum like in
real life no just like he knew
him from pop culture like my nanny
baby handy baby yeah and then i
remember once ah he read news stories
about ah the marvel civil war
the event why and you said that
sounded pretty cool
but he didn't read it of course
because where would he have gone but
he was like so are you still
reading marvel comics i was like yeah
he goes oh yeah i read a
news story about civil war where the
heroes fight each other sounds pretty cool
i mean i i relate to that
because i hear i read stories about
war that are happening and i'm like
that's cool but i'm not gonna go
well the civil war itself
if the american civil war i read
stories but it's cool but i can't
cool i can't get there i'm not
gonna go back in time three original
texts yeah yeah
right next occasionally i would put on
a ray logs the smithereens were something
that was just straight ahead rock and
roll where i was watching a live
smithereens concert that was on mtv and
he he enjoyed that but i remember
once i put on an rpm record
and our aim is like as inoffensive
as you can get but they did
it was there besides
record in the in they started playing
king of the road and they were
changing the words and he got very
suspicious i remember because he's also the
devilish yes see so he was like
why are they saying it this way
and got very suspicious that i was
listening to the satan is now my
lord
i was laughing for christmas my dad
was watching zootopia with all of us
because all the little kids wister karachi
hero watching it special appearance yes and
i just was looking i was like
did you ever think you'd be sitting
here watching this tape
i just like so you think you
don't see yourself getting older and watching
worse you know you're just done watching
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's like i
don't have to watch this when he
was like kind of like take use
like really watching it i was like
this is hilarious did you shoot a
sick elephant said
the is it is it a fox
who is the lead of what does
the fox say anything toby no i'm
sorry i'm mixing up it was sing
we were watching o things and that
was funny because it's like these animals
singing really earnestly which is funny but
there's no way around just taking it
in and i'm like this rocks here's
what i remember
from zootopia i only ever seen the
trailer it's pretty good and i think
there's a fox right there's a fox
and jason jason bateman bunny from spank
jennifer goodwin the the fox physically somehow
reminded me strongly of drew tarver oh
yeah i can see that yeah yeah
he's he's
got drew tarver energy when he looks
identical to him yeah he looks cool
i thought it was drew drew his
funks we should mention that he is
a stone cold fox you guys i'm
reporting you to h r o know
why freemium over h r maybe i'm
here it's some o h e cio
hits chooses to play epa
tar licks yeah in some glasses okay
look andrew that's gonna be sunglasses hashi
every six am off in washington the
color purple was true i actually get
to see this isn't this how are
you going to see your fingers and
where they're at it's gonna come out
all blank blank you're gonna do it
andrew thank you so much for sending
us the voicemail
you and your mother it's so nice
your listeners yes thank you so much
and um that's ah that's what a
three minutes three medium is just like
that and and just like that
not genius and it's just like that
just like that um and it's if
you want to leave us a voicemail
go to hag claims a dot com
and you can be heard on these
three new maps just like andrew and
by proxy his mom were thanks um
um goodbye forever guy