three
right
ah we're back i really hope someone
in your neighborhood knows what this is
and they hear a scream on it's
back
thank god they're back
would be wonderful if someone liked us
so much nobody out of fat so
if there was a fan of freedom
lives here in beverly hills and they
were like i didn't know i lose
so close to scott aquaman beverly hills
that's where you want to be sure
yeah don't guide dog
oh
oh man she said gimme gimme gimme
gimme who is that by the way
who said wheeze huh it's kimmy gatewood
it's weaver's wife it's kimmy gatewood they
said say your own name on this
one kimmie candy
ah his word he starts please call
me mrs weezer
we're back welcome to the artist lee
episode back da weasel doe easer um
we're back and we're better than ever
and we're battle
in a backyard we make up for
months months is my car's origin story
call monthly goober
sister to bradley
yeah bradley cooper sr bookmark because because
bradley's or what what a month is
a month of bradley is a bread
used to hold papers together it's five
months don't you know what a bradley
is what bradlee goodbye boo so we've
been in here brian rose uma yeah
can't take it oh we're um we're
recording this in my backyard and that
is due to the fact that if
you are listening to this in the
future we are dead dead long dead
and andy of course you're aliens and
you're listening just to figure out what
human beings are like and we're all
like
this you found a boy robots under
the sea he wants to be real
ah you can make his mother live
for a day
and i always say we're at least
twelve feet apart yeah yeah at least
let's see i'm six feet so if
i were to lay down that's how
i'm wired i'm not kidding tallulah pictured
it i think i think you're twelve
for me and you're about fifteen can
i tell you something please i often
think of scott when i think of
the six foot distance yes i don't
know why
now you're the person that comes to
my mind your overshot all yeah it's
like at the at the grocery store
when they have like the the lines
on the side right so you figure
him dead aegon row
think about myself at an acre myself
when they have the lines i'm like
is that six feet and you're not
one of scarring it was lying down
those grocery line things are not six
feet i swear don't you think we
have don't talk about what covert here
we have not caught up about about
the grocery lines which i've not been
in a grocery
more since day three of cove really
i like so much probably i go
to target like once a month around
when you get your period for tank
i get my new tampons only my
studio wouldn't call by d
cooper
gov
ah please everyone this is new slang
yeah yeah my one fifth of a
bradley i was gonna say new slang
i was like are we ever gonna
stop
i feel like you obviously won't relate
to this but it took me a
long time of my life to realize
that i didn't need to buy one
box of tampons at a time i
could just but i'm gonna need more
i should bind right one of you
die lord that's true it's like i
wasted seven dollars million harold kumar exactly
to my beloved husband
may you always know what to do
with you if should you ever remarry
um by the way i'm scott
by the way i'm paul and by
the way i'm lauren and we are
recording in the backyard so if you
ever hear a plane or they're they're
working across the street at my neighbors
house you might hear a drill driller
saw real banana just say a lot
of people have been just getting together
and doing fucking podcasts in one room
and it makes me feel sick during
this time
will i be nervous watch makes you
feel like you have coven it does
basically like the show when i watched
the instagrams and they're like one foot
apart screaming i'm like why can't you
do the zoom can we talk about
my covert adventure ways i want to
hear about your adventure how many times
you play the jingle are covered and
then che eating deep
sidi bou said how many times have
we all been tested i've been tested
twice i've been tested since friday it
is now ah no yes it is
now friday since last friday i've been
tested five times five times five night
of baby yeah right let it ride
baby keep him keep
the good you do the thing with
double or nothing your partner is tested
you kind of assume you don't have
it we've both been tested at the
same time yeah times yeah so we've
gone separate issue and i might good
right now reich she told me chinese
so i assume she's telling the truth
and i should know your partner you
should always look at our jobs meaningless
show me yeah
here's what happened i got a job
working on a guest starring on a
sitcom a new show that's ah ah
there this is like the second episode
and part of it is mandatory accesses
out and has snoop dogg once it
did hopefully he will say again
um so i had to go in
a couple of days before work to
get tested i advise you yes please
pass me when is this show supposed
to air just out of curiosity you
have to say exact dates but like
month general likes i'm curious what the
timeline is working with the covert that's
a good question i know they finish
production can't finish
gotta pay for defender production around around
christmas i think oh okay it's probably
i mean it's you know what's taking
a lot not to get too deep
into production but color correction is taking
the longest time because you can't do
that over you like zoom you can't
oh the advantage over zoo
boom because like you can share screen
and look at the edits but the
color you can't do it in high
definition the way you have to sew
gives you along with a little dropper
yeah anyway so are in each person
i put some rosy cheeks on
mirror mirror
hello
why is he doing color corrected
um so you say you're on a
show so yeah so i get to
test the test is drive to um
this is a test to drive to
somewhere i had to drive kit and
if you can drive her to the
test take a driving test then they
made me think the jumper little park
yes i was great at it we
have we talked about the pointer wanting
to take the s a t's ago
and just to see how you would
do know i took i remember back
in the early two thousands they would
lure you into like take this free
i q test yeah and i was
like oh i want to see how
high my queue is now because i
heard it was really high when i
was young so i think i heard
it was really love it was like
i want to
here's keep in touch i just had
to go you know they told me
they told me i had a one
hundred and eighty icu but i couldn't
hop on one foot when i was
six days so they were like you've
said they were like you're bad at
baseball was nice yeah that's why my
parents okay yeah enrolled me in baseball
i'm like yeah all that kind of
somebody was like hand-in-hand like he's really
smart but he is almost you know
unable to do anything you basics like
einstein with the backward sweater but what
he wore backwards day was go cuckoos
and dumb shit i didn't know that
he was too smart to figure out
anything can cause you know it's going
to cover all his body exactly so
in those early two thousands they would
lure you into like
like hey take this free icu and
you a like websites these websites so
you you'd see like papa mad or
something oh yeah and this is before
you knew pop-up ads were bad you
had to pay attention to every pop
up bed when you say whoa what
do i do they might be little
facts so it would get you to
do
it would get you to deal plastic
like shoelaces called bagless
get you to answer thirty questions or
so when each one was another page
and so you've like been on this
website for a half hour and then
to get the results you would have
to pay yeah and you're selling pot
committed to removing that your icu is
low but yeah shit all of that
yes exactly
um so you had to go drive
to a test where was this lady
working out of universal studio yeah by
the way ah universal studios is an
unmatchable location where they give you a
look dollar was like everything is just
like one hundred universal plaza that's like
but it's a town really that goes
twenty eight days office yeah it does
inside it does so i finally find
the place and i'm all stressed out
and then then i realized like oh
i could have shown up here anytime
it's just you go to a parking
lot somebody comes down out of the
building they give you a kit um
oh this is a do it yourself
use is this the type you spit
in or no this was an austral
one it was
natural that you do yourself yes yes
yes so strange because i've done the
nostril one that someone else did and
heard which of your web blog posts
your brain it wouldn't i wouldn't have
done that to myself no you don't
you don't go that far okay you
like you you push it until you
feel like a decent resistance push a
real good right or you put a
real
and what's the resistance coming from ah
the inside of your nose
they should pass that typically yeah in
the one that that that cool up
and i got that was so horrible
yeah they it's it he goes hey
this isn't going to be painful it's
gonna be uncomfortable and i was like
well what's the fucking difference yeah like
there's a difference i use a different
lie got my i had a deviated
septum i like can try sixteen because
user
but yeah because i was still bleeding
like huge chunks hey guys yeah and
they had to put a little like
he put a light up my eye
i mean about i my nose like
a very thin ring basically the size
of a covert test capita oh and
it went up really easily in one
and then he couldn't get in at
all in the other
wow lately close now that's deviated baby
yeah and you're sure well they're open
you're sure it was a light and
it wasn't anything weird it was like
a lighter camera oh what did you
think it was nice it was as
thin as kobe tests
so so in this one you you
you did it yourself yes you got
negs i got y handed back to
them and then you have to get
download this app oh and so when
i when i got the results the
day i got the results the next
day and it was hilarious how many
steps i had to go through
to to get the results first they
send me a text saying hey we
sent you an email and i click
here or email dummy right you get
the email it says we got your
results click here click there it says
welcome to the portal sign in sign
of it now we have your results
click here you know all like i'm
ah the tension is mount yes
and then it was fine and then
so then i go to work everyone's
being very careful they have like a
ton of protocols in place everyone is
masked and shielded like all of the
crew directors everybody knew thing i want
to tell you about that i just
learned about is the shield from the
neck up it's a plastic it's like
ah that's where i got a check
on person had that one
check from an neko
one person dead have barely better for
like people doing makeup or something because
the droplet stay inside beans are looking
down yeah yeah so there was a
person that had that but then they
filled it with popcorn and they were
just wow
wow actually limit disneyworld disneyland i was
there with wild horses and we never
stop talking about it there was this
woman walking around with a popcorn bucket
just attached to her face chooses like
like a dog with a yeah daughter
she's just like nose stuck in a
trailer with butter i'm just thinking like
a horse with one of those bags
yeah she was in line for the
honey mansion just
it wasn't like trapped in it pumpkin
when i was
pumpkins and popcorn i am talking she
was eating a pumpkin
she's eating a whole raw pumpkin she
was just walking through the line with
his popcorn attached to her face like
robert robert was when you say attack
because it was like a handle on
the back that you put over the
back of her head i can't remember
how it stayed on just pure suction
just pure popcorn back during suction something
about the way the size of it
was perfect for her mouth
it's squalid
so okay get there the first day
i do a test um and ah
it's all fun so i don't get
the results till the next day um
the second day i'm there so you
have to get it the day before
you go in every each time every
de oh yes not the day before
today day off so before i got
i was it was couple days before
by the way that's one of l
a is famous helicopter who's traveling a
bird ah not really
i wish they'd leave us alone they're
always trying to get the scoop on
thredup the past i wish the paps
would leave us alone
savannah tenn i was working on and
i'm gonna keep it up yes oh
yeah the show show is i am
early show before i'm like so touched
to be interrupted again
i was working on this show lucifer
and we were shooting hotel scary ah
roof it was scary and a drone
paparazzi drone flew up i mean we're
up twenty stories to get pictures of
lucifer just this little thing just came
up a little bit of it and
was like hanging around right here pictures
of the set and every
thing is not creepy that's right too
and they want your sort of super
like oh i guess they care about
the show please face pitchfork yeah what
if it wasn't really someone getting to
get money from the picture is it's
like someone oh my god what if
it was the actual devil who's like
what are they what are they saying
about me not in my name is
the guy hot let me take a
look
so second day same as the first
little bit louder a little bit worse
um we're shooting shooting virginia we're almost
done we're almost done for the day
and then um we're between setups they're
they're turning around on the scene
and so i'm sitting in they have
a like a little room for the
three cast members that are working that
day mean little people and you're in
the same room as a little tiny
room we're sitting on top of each
other it was bad no it's it's
a small room but there's where spaced-apart
park and i saw some sets have
a partition between each person you're like
oh yeah we did not have that
if the but if the fennel
elation how to do anyway i know
how do you know what's right so
but we're we're massed between yeah as
soon as i get back on everything
so the ah one of the aides
comes in and says hey ah we're
gonna take like a thirty minute break
so you guys can go back to
your trailers
and so i follow him out and
then he says to the hair makeup
team which are in their area
hey um we're all going to ah
vacate to set we're all going to
vacate the studio we're just gonna walk
outside and i'm like okay this is
zelig a break wow so they they
they i didn't want to this i
just wanted to walk back but they
kept making me get in a van
and it's like a whole van where
it's just what it's just only
one person can sit in it so
it's and the driver and i'm like
it's not that far i can walk
and i feel better if you took
demand so i get in the van
none of them drawing pad it's like
fucking children of men people are supposed
to get wristbands to denote ah they're
clear status right yeah and so i
see scientology somebody
handy yeah exactly and you said david
miscavige just handing out these respects this
is kronos here's his wife and it
was like in the vanish like missing
out of no idea know the founder
she was fine
she was taking a nap in another
room ah yeah um it was really
spooky to see these people like getting
these wristbands and they were taking them
off or they were getting them on
people were putting them on the results
have just been given yes yes yes
yes and so i go back to
the trailer
or i'm sitting there for a little
bit and then trash the trailer of
course fuckin every time every time and
it makes me mad because they don't
say anything about i don't go back
the next day and i'm like wow
mo when partly when you hire a
paul f tompkins he's always gonna trash
the trailer and everytime he goes in
any poll of anyone i've really heard
this about people when i find to
be the weirdest thing that people
will trash the trailer i've heard this
about a couple very famous people rarely
i heard about one very famous person
and actually i know someone who got
in a lot of trouble for talking
about it so i really don't want
to say well but
um this person left her monthly cooper's
oh okay oh it's all over the
trailer like just lying around like just
like she'd been there a couple of
days and used tampons and then didn't
dispose of them properly well i mean
was there a trash can in the
trailer yeah and also if they're
was it i think you would figure
out a way to leave them lying
around yeah guessing interesting okay i gotta
hear that name afterwards yes yeah um
so yeah guys ah then the with
me ah i'm like alias so the
the base camp ah ah pay comes
to me and says um hey you're
up for the day and we're gonna
we'll finish this tomorrow can you come
in tomorrow morning and i was like
ah i guess oh and um also
why are they giving the results in
the middle of the day it fee
feels like that's the kind of info
you want before your i think they
i think they get them as soon
as they can get them they use
three different services so they can different
service they can be testing all the
time wow does carry freedom
three different services
hey hold on
ah here we go already three d
one printer says wait well oh i
gotta turn up
three two what freedom reserve is is
worth it
oh that's it we're not gonna tell
me all it up i turned it
down alright alright
our first edit um so ah i
it turns out i was one of
the one of the camera operators had
said that got a positive take on
a positive test so that unit that
like it was b camera so although
people up anyone who has been working
with yes yes yes yeah although technically
all the actors have been working with
well yeah
yeah but not quite as closely as
like these are right people that are
sitting in a clump all day yeah
the clumps the clumps it was the
clock
i didn't want to say name from
cod out noise of course i knew
it there so nutty
so so then i went back in
so then the schedule was changing every
like couple hours like when they were
going to bring me in um i
thought i was going to go in
in the morning yesterday then it was
like maybe in late in the afternoon
then they had me come in and
got two tests from two diff
different services um one where i administered
the test myself one where somebody else
administered it um the same test they're
in competition with each other yeah who
does it better to see yeah and
guess what i do a better um
so so i get the results the
one test was a rapid test that
i got the results in within a
half hour
they say ok we got your results
and then they bring me over to
the trailer where they're doing it mom
and they just shout negative who gives
a hay but it's like maybe because
then if you're in trouble and you
do have positive well be the same
treatment for everyone said it's not clear
they can't they can't legally they can't
give away your medical rules but here's
what they do they can give it
away to me here's what you do
this nurse comes to the door and
she says okay we got your results
back shouldering veneer alone yeah was there
there was an interesting question
is she um hooking up with ladies
in the new series i saw some
sort of trauma probably wise i watched
the first one i'll tell you all
about it okay um what's what's what's
a show called rat ratchet rachid yeah
like racha her name is chad right
her name is rachid yeah those ratchet
you know oh whole life if you're
thinking attack shit but i've been thinking
patton oswalt
i'm always thinking of patent law
what are you up to now patted
tuohy so do people ever say that's
pretty good he patted doing so zeros
comes to the door she says we
have your results and i say okay
and then she goes will you join
me over here and i go over
i go over to this area that
they've blocked off for results giving where
there's two
to like taped marks like a little
square that i stand in as she
stands in and then she opens it
up like why are we telling a
marie this is weird
marie and you are negative
i do
of dancing around but why they can't
keep doing this to people you can't
make them sweat and weighs all time
anyway yes pointing this room that were
run together like i mean yeah guys
so so far no code for me
good for you that's good none for
me
so far as far as i know
although i do none for me thanks
i was gonna say be pledged road
i do i was telling you guys
beforehand that i suspect that maybe i
hadn't february before anyone knew what was
going on but i don't know my
roses
from a million i know i do
think it's more rare here to have
had it right like i feel like
i thought in california that did they
suspect last round of people have it
hi i'm shawn ya nose
a yeah wow be good
a
ah but no i had the weirdest
sickness that everyone was just kind of
like wow we we think it's strep
or something yeah remember that anyway so
i don't know maybe i have the
antibodies but ah who knows well they're
probably gone by now sorry to say
anyway we are by the way we're
recording oh yeah we've we met your
one beauty little women reference
when she cuts her hair is is
this from just all of them or
the northern reason frankly i think it's
in the book i read
they they call they call her hair
her one beauty because she looks likely
after she gets it i mean according
to don't all women yeah your hair
better be dandy but
i don't watch the new little woman
but i would like to and i'm
home alone this weekend so it feels
like the perfect time to oh where's
my go in this is awesome oh
well i guess i've also invested i
mean it's i feel i guess it's
weird with covert that whatever you do
anything it can be so criticized yes
um so
l f consider cutting this out but
he's his friend is alone at his
parents' house in vegas has like best
friend from la so he got both
got tested in there hanging out at
that house telling people and it's fun
that's fine um yeah i think it's
fine to i but you know sometimes
people are really if people are working
on said i think going totally testing
yourself and hanging out yeah
yeah i think if you're taking precautions
there's there's nothing wrong with that yeah
yeah had to go take care of
my parents last week and so yeah
i was wondering we went i got
tested you mean they got test take
care of them yes put them down
they will be a problem
they're on a farm somewhere do it
because i really want to go home
for the holidays but i don't know
how to make this possible real nervous
well the the issue for use the
plane i would imagine because yeah you
will have to that is the base
because you drive he drove to vegas
and he just got tasted waited a
day you'll have you'll have to
fly to chicago quarantine get tested after
that it's like fancy wheels a month
yeah really want to do it but
not just seems like a fuck am
i doing exactly yeah it's so hard
we got we got tickets for um
christmas umm bye always wanted to see
that i i've never
i've seen christian i got fried chicken
to christmas i feel like i see
it advertised everywhere and it's like here
i got to
so you're going to north carolina and
spoiled for me south carolina sorry well
we're we're keeping an open that if
things still seem so bad we won't
go and we'll change the ticket or
whatever the tickets are cheap right i
mean tickets are cheap but also they've
there's never been a direct flight from
los angeles to charleston before i and
they're finally offering one
ben and janey really misses her mom
yeah her mom's all alone down there
oh yeah um so yeah we're kind
of keeping our fingers crossed that we'll
be able to do it but yeah
well i mean we want to be
smart about it like we don't want
to just i know it's so crazy
yeah it's also hard it's hard it's
tough but i think i think you
can do it i mean it's you
downgraded from
terrible the tough it's terror it's i
feel it's okay i think it's crazier
in a sense the i mean i
wouldn't want my whole family to fly
out here but it's easier in warm
weather because you can spend time outside
like i can't socially distanced hang out
with my family in the winter yeah
in chicago yeah it's like before i'm
quarantined you'll have to meet up
oh south carolina yeah yeah you'll have
to know that all of you don't
have it before yeah yeah i would
feel so nervous yeah but you know
it's only another two years huh
ah oh we don't want to make
our first show back ah depressing state
of the union on covert here oh
maybe we should've had a meeting well
when does this even come out because
october okay where did why you think
it'll be done by everywhere november so
be a fun retrospect i think by
the end of the episode
i just think god i love he's
so cool like it's gonna look a
little boy comes out next
god
no i'm just glad we're not too
far in advance as they only shout
extra extra when it was an extra
edition or is it that just like
no hey there's a paper out is
that is that kono it's like they
already printed it today but then there's
a good little extra digit well they
would do that in the news if
it's like something happens
in the news that people had to
know about it in the afternoon the
frame wasn't covered it was always an
extra edition but i don't know i
wonder if like extra extra just now
means like hey i have a paper
up until what point where they doing
that like printing a newspaper for an
extra news that you needed to interesting
march yeah probably and then covert happened
and they didn't break
but for that they were like we
didn't do it for this ah yeah
yeah
okay look we need to take a
break we'll be right back wait
did you guys see that video of
trump getting um booed and oh my
god i watched it last night and
i was in bed and i just
like was going through twitter and i
was smiling from ear to ear and
i started cackling
like a witch
it was a beautiful yeah yeah and
then he just had to stand there
i know take that in there think
about sierra now kind of voice that
you're against trump right now right this
is how oh ma i didn't know
we were back
are we talking okay i'll say it
oh we've been back i'll say it
well we stay back i don't i
mean i don't like his his tone
ah that's my biggest thing this whole
time like this can just change his
tone if he could store to changes
to everything and get on board i
wish she'd be more presidential you never
once in a while each
this is a thing and it's like
now he really became president in any
does he get he goes back to
not being president and then every once
in a while he reads a speech
said he's like the president now ah
the the the voting what is it
an election that's what they call it
that's coming up yeah we want to
encourage everyone to vote but not if
you're gonna vote for stupid people
look voting it's not i'm not excited
about it this time but ah where
are you going to do it or
you're going to do it in person
or you may win i think i
got her performances i think
yeah i'll just phone him and you
mail them and they take days oh
yeah yeah yeah the audience is like
what happened to me
on the show um i'm gonna do
the ah the mail-in ballot but i'm
probably going to drop it off when
i'm okay because also one thing i'm
confused about is that i'm already signed
up for mail-in ballots so i can't
change that right are you like permanent
mail-in i don't know you can change
it yeah oh okay because i just
figured well rather than
like messing up what i've already done
i'll just get that and go drop
it off at the proper location which
i don't like you to have mailing
it in the mail i know that
feels not enough me i want to
go into some point that it's like
meant for that there's also there's also
a service ah i think it's called
ballot tracks where you can track your
ballot oh yeah oh i think
i did that once yeah yeah cool
fun have you guys ballots going on
a little adventure learn if you've gotten
a haircut since i got one haircut
on my porch um wow porch cut
yes and it was stone yeah i
see that yeah you could see that
it was so necessary um because my
hair had gotten really dry
very long and just like chunk it
was just yeah it was like little
house on the prairie it was and
i cut off my one beauty
have you guys i get my myself
that one which i debuted the day
that the the three of us went
to the drive-in movie thanks right yeah
we haven't talked about on this show
we we went to a drive-in movie
on my birthday we saw jars it
was really fun to see drawers it
was fun to see yours and then
we were also going to see tremors
and then we all love we all
know
she was tired because we watched tremors
at home and probably is probably always
in the summer is that it doesn't
get dark until a thirty or so
or eighty five and then after jaws
it's ten forty five and weigh what
we're supposed to do stay up another
two and three hours and i just
had a sangha and i'm ready to
go to bed i had the best
time it was so fun
i was driving i felt like you
had ever mentioned i think i had
never been to address that oh i
guess would they not have them in
chicago or do they have them they
probably have something but i've i don't
think i'd ever been to one maybe
once but mike debt never had joined
i've never had like doc never had
any duck had never been as well
it was so new and it was
so truly it was because we hadn't
left the house in months it felt
like a vacation yeah we had to
dry when you know anyone wants to
throw forty five minutes we sat in
a big long line of cars yeah
we parked two spaces away from each
other we text each other constantly during
the mao tse yeah that was fun
that made peanut butter balls which were
oh god delicious and we had a
nice picture which we could maybe put
on the website of all of us
with masks i printed it and put
it in a frame oh yeah good
that now where are you printing these
pictures do you have a home photo
printer he has a kinko's like locations
i have a kinko's a starbucks ah
ah talk about express so wait you
pretty well know i'm toto printer yeah
i've photo paper and an ah in
a printer that prints photos i need
to do this yeah it's fun um
there's also this company that i ain't
gonna wait a minute kodak about my
haircut oh let's talk about his haircut
lower or you move onto your company
what about i
i got my first professional haircut since
covert lawn friday due to the ah
the the person that the ah shit
work did it know i went to
my regular style okay um and it
was handled very well where they made
you fill out a little thing before
you went in
um and then ah to show you
any symptoms right and then you're like
yeah this is crazy though be care
of a little covert this is like
what i went to the gun range
and oh yoy
i one time went to a shooting
range and i had to fill out
a format that i'm not mentally ill
and that i'm not on drugs it's
like okay yeah yeah great it's like
the the customs things like are you
a terrorist no yeah when i was
in there i kept thinking about how
simple that was and then there are
these young people who looked like they
were way too young but i'm
i don't know if they lied or
if they were just really young looking
and i was like this is the
most dangerous thing i've ever done to
stand next to people next to strangers
and we're all holding guns like it
is i hated it it isn't saying
that someone could just turn to you
and go oh by the way yeah
and it was it was so scary
i would never do to get wet
t-shirt contest motherfucker
ah it's terrified that what an epic
prank that was
adulation as you want
why would i when wet t-shirt contest
motherfucker
from something or you're just making this
an ice cubes oh okay
it's like the sandy terrain waves
i'll talk about being shy
it is being very generous well that's
what's so ah that's what's so funny
as in the nineties and early two
thousand they called everything a skit yeah
they so you'd see that in the
track listing if it's a skit i
think generally people refer to us and
i'll sketches skits if you went back
in time and say you had to
relive your life over again but
dude you still had your ah memories
from this life yes wow would you
be able to handle it without all
of modern conveniences i i was talking
about this very recently i had a
covert dream yeah everyone's dreams have been
crazy right yea so i had had
a covert dream i had a corvid
dream lydia
um i don't even know what that
is
from a representative fisher king
but what's so what's what's the song
i was saying i thought i saw
a dream on willy wonka three i
got lydia from gypsy yeah but when
what's oh yeah yeah he see oh
yeah yeah the funny yeah michael farnsworth
twelve vs on farms over but i
could look it up he died he
died yeah he was funny he was
funny
um anyway
go hey hey gang have fun with
those references see if you could piece
it all together what the fuck right
jeter michael g da derek jeter no
but both of the baseball hall of
fame is no longer enough i had
a dream lydia oh i hit a
home run lady yeah lawrence has taken
a break
opera huh because she cannot participate i'm
in they say um what were we
talking about we gotta covert the dream
i recovered dream where my consciousness traveled
back to two thousand and six okay
and so in the dream i was
like
this is great i know that there's
certain things that if i'm living my
life from this point forward this is
great because it's not that long it's
not like going back yeah high school
or something it's like it's ah it's
ah ah ah point of time where
i've already met my wife um we're
together um so there's all this
the other stout open marriage
i'll lay the groundwork for that
an open marriages that we know i
found out about too that i was
very surprised about during the good times
how many future divorces are about
just like friends that later i found
out oh they were in an open
marriage i got here when they were
in a marriage oh i know we
might know one that's the same okay
we'll have to get all these names
after the odd yes go ahead ah
um and i was so i was
like in the dream i was mapping
out like all the stuff you would
redo in your life yes it's like
okay so these points
i definitely want to do i would
definitely do these things the same oh
my god but other things are like
mistakes i made a wrong decisions or
whatever that i can correct you get
an early on that ah star wars
podcast before ah dude if only you
were in on that oh man but
i have a question with that with
that key
concept i mean in your dream i
don't know what the rules were whatever
but if you like do you believe
like in your mind like i like
one thing that stops me from feeling
really bad about things that i regret
is that the other things wouldn't have
happened if i didn't do those right
yeah well yeah that's something you'd have
to you'd have to really sit and
think like okay what what were the
repercussions of this
did anything good come out of this
wasn't just like sort of a push
in my life you know um or
yeah i know like if i thought
okay if i if i would approach
this differently maybe the show would have
lasted longer and i and out i
know what the notes were about this
i could change oh when i
like about oh i always think like
okay i'll work harder because all of
this stuff that i wasted my time
with i've already wasted my time with
it i've read the books or write
c d all so i hated all
hours so i did or or even
just like in my spare time like
hobbies and stuff oh i already already
did but then i think like how
many times you reread books and stuff
like that i'd probably just waste
the same amount of time i feel
like i would waste all this i
mean i think i have this thought
during this time while we have you
know there's this assumption that you have
a lot of free time which i
don't really feel is accurate i feel
very much like my free time as
i'm barely relaxed i'm not like it's
on vacation i'm like mentally stressed it's
something like not really free time because
you're you're constantly managing your anxiety yeah
that's getting a horrible virus yeah there's
all these things that that like we
just moved here about a year ago
and it's like i put these things
to unpack like when i have time
oh yes and it's like well maybe
you're never gonna get to it yes
like if you haven't during covert yeah
at the same time yeah
you're like constantly trying to figure out
just the world and and we're saying
i think heart health is happening during
an election year though now focused on
and that all all the horrible things
happening in the world and then you
have all the stress oh things are
going i have work but then i
think our business also really expects you
to keep going in this weird way
which
this is all unprecedented so it's whatever
but like there's so much self motivating
that you're supposed to do anyway but
then people are kind of going like
where's that thing why are you doing
away and then there's this pressure and
i feel like it's really bad sure
i think it's really bad like when
you watch a tv show and billy
joel's pressure comes on because the you
know the main characters under a lot
of pressure yeah i think i know
exactly what you're talking about yes okay
so but back to my original question
if you had to go back to
your own q yeah boom i had
to go back to this beginning of
your life what would you get the
most for
frustrated with in terms of like technology
like my loving having all the ones
you've already lived in oh so it's
like i but i but you retain
your memories so i it's the nineties
but i know that i'll eventually have
you're trying to say you were born
in the nineties no but i'm saying
if i wasn't cognizant of my life
before that i just wondered if
you had like a recent because i've
known people who have revised their ages
oh my god birth years i know
people like that too drives me nuts
but i know i yeah i live
in the eighties i was like a
little care so i wasn't aware of
what i did or did not have
but i'm saying no but you would
now like you you have your memories
from but having
both brain that's too much being a
little kid when there is essentially a
contract basis of some science fiction and
actually the current x-men comics this is
a subplot in it so wait my
question is if it's been a let's
say i'm ten yeah and so i'm
aware when i'm watching tv that i
could be on my phone and watching
tedious yeah this is what i'm getting
ah
we didn't just drive you insane to
have to watch tv worst of all
in the nineties i tell you with
with really small tds you know when
the internet was coming ah when chat
rooms and aol were thing i was
in like i was like so twelve
yeah and so it became a huge
obsession and my brother and i were
constantly sneaking to go
online which we we have like stolen
ah my uncle's internet information so somehow
we were routing it through our house
i don't know how my brother did
it honestly we were kids and we
were online and we ended up starting
a huge bill to my uncle oh
we didn't find out until later and
we got in trouble but we would
just go in his room lock the
door and just go online for hours
in the
phobic
yeah i mean if my mom picked
up she didn't understand yeah truly was
like we were getting away with something
and we were so obsessed and if
i couldn't be on it was stressful
like if we are going once we
go to a friend's house and they
had only been gone yeah so it's
like this huge obsession and i think
the second i had that i wanted
it all the time so i do
think if i knew i could be
on it was but but now if
he really
hard so so now if you were
to go back into the nineties and
still keep your consciousness than you would
first of all you would the internet
wouldn't be interesting because it would be
so slow compared to what you're used
to anyone would be like i'm just
going to wait until it catches up
like i think about when iphones were
first invented ten or so years
in twelve years ago or so um
um how slow they were then and
how late clunky they were like it
would just be so frustrating but you
seemed amazing so i wonder if i
wonder though also never like eight hundred
dollars or something stuff that's that was
on tv back down there were a
mere thousand say wait there's still that
much money but all the stuff that
was on tv back then you're not
in
listed in an a more so you
wouldn't rewatch it so you would spend
your time oh god i'd be bored
out of my fucking head but you
would spend your time doing interesting things
like do it like i don't know
writing or maybe more traveling or you
know what i mean like you wouldn't
be so but also wouldn't you have
to fuckin hide your adulthood like you
yeah well like
too hard with last grade a little
notice this is a quad in the
x-band but hey x man jesus really
want to come out good chris come
on over here here's my here's my
pitch on this question okay let's say
you go back in time to like
it's like back to the future and
you're you have your so going buddy
in time
yeah you're basically an adult in a
different era right so you know all
this shit like i think he was
stressed by that right well see i
think marty mcfly in my opinion
when he went back to the fifties
i don't know that that much was
different from the eighties to the fifties
other than like he couldn't get a
pepsi free you had to pay for
it um no didn't ask for a
tab tab if you gotta order something
if you want it by the way
no one was drinking tab by that
point and that was my impression from
my
entire tb to be in the movie
and then it was out of business
within a year right tab was huge
and my house was it with us
huh interesting i remember it from when
i was a little kid but then
i remember when it was it was
forced to go away because of no
my mom kept forever whatever was in
it and then switch to diet coke
but i think my dad was talking
about how nostalgia is
is sort of it's it's a trap
in a way because you feel very
ill like when you grow to get
old you feel nostalgic to wear to
the way things were when you were
young like how little traffic there was
compared to row or how less yielding
know at the time what it was
you couldn't roy yet but but if
you were
went back there now would it would
it be like wonderful of like oh
wow look there's no traffic like the
parts of it would be so cool
but then the other parts just just
be like if you tried to force
enjoyment of things now like this amount
of traffic if it gets better than
later than this i won't like it
but
this is fine when covered for starting
no tribe member driving around it was
beautiful it was like arena once upon
a time in hollywood no it's not
it's not back up to the normal
levels which no it's still good just
still good but but it wasn't like
back then where you could get anywhere
in ten minutes you think that there's
going to be a lot less traffic
in the future as people start to
do more things from home i hope
so
so i mean so oh yeah a
is is not back to the levels
it once was and i think like
there's kind of no i've always wondered
why everyone kept all these offices and
it's it's purely because like when i
worked at dreamworks animation they would schedule
you every hour to have a meeting
because they want they're paying you they
wanted you to to
to have meetings and they were always
a waste of time and i every
hour every hour you had to have
something on the books and so it
would be like ok we're going to
have a meeting with the storyboard ist
and it would be like well what
are why we don't we don't need
anything it was like well ah we
just need to schedule you for something
that sucks but that's the trap of
like everyone having
these offices i think people can work
you know smarter from home anyway we
yeah we need to take a break
oh you guys both went to board
them town where you were fiddling with
your stuff while i was talking well
you're the mayor important
alright we'll be right but it wasn't
what i was just disinterest i know
we're back and the third act of
our show is when we always go
to a feature or what we call
a thresher and that is to this
where one of us brings in a
fun little home we always do this
we owe have to always do this
we can't stop
what's with us and ah problem want
to acknowledge ah our producer josh who
helped us out with ah the lists
hello yes hello josh just as your
official acknowledgement
and so this is one called olu
yeah she would do an in memoriam
okay oh for kevin yeah kevin oh
my god ah vi yeah sevens this
the song that sarah mclachlan sings about
puppies are you guys alright i was
saying shoving because you're supposed to picture
a picture of kevin with the chef
kevin apron yeah right she have it
so i just said that over the
song that was part of the ma
chapter seven it just kevin one byob
if he does get into memoriam and
i hope there will be one for
podcast by the time i was saying
the other day when we were watching
the emmys i was i legitimately seriously
said i gotta get in this montage
you look i
do feel that if i'm not there
i do feel if i'm i don't
know memoriam i think it's fucked up
because yeah how much you have to
do in this world you gotta do
what you have to do what did
you do to be to get in
there what do i gotta do to
get into that dead person montage i
loved the cover on the memoriam of
um what's oh her did nothing compares
to you
yeah it was beautiful yeah i don't
think it's on spotify i was like
trying to wish you would put it
out yeah check that out check out
if you can watch it on youtube
her which is h period e period
our period definitely what i got out
of that the loving montage of people
who have passed away i wish you
would put that song out i really
wish shipping on spotify got to get
in touch that's my takeaway thought that
before then i
the chinese guys was actually more moving
than many ira i enjoyed this year's
emmy and the mean overall i thought
were really good i enjoyed them although
that was really fun i had a
great night honestly i was so happy
i mean like they know what winning
was a damper on my enjoyment of
likewise yeah well yeah bojack did not
wow oh right rick and morty
and best animator pro yeah yeah i
of course was not nominated um last
chance you blew it everyone that has
a chance you're doing a guest spot
right now let's be real um i
ah
i was so happy that catherine o'hara
and eugene levy one that was really
fun with the whole shits creek i
mean yeah i'm happy but i'm i'm
glad for the whole sweep i'm very
happy for those people but those two
because they meant so much to me
since i was a kid i agree
they're so easy and i was her
first emmy yeah yeah crazy yeah no
yeah yeah yeah really so good day
one i think they want writing emmys
for sctv one year okay when they
were doing those ninety minutes i think
shows were toronto emmys
what are those called pieces of shit
to remy oh ah remember what there
is the baftas of course there's some
awards for their knees i can't i
can't remember okay it's genie we gotta
play this three-tier okay this is called
someone they know if you guys are
going paul died we can't hear him
anymore
josh got acknowledged and not me this
is called one three five oh my
god morning confused okay wait slow down
it's mad
three people that's how many we are
okay guy guy and nine three people
improvise a conversational scene but one person
is allowed one word huh her response
one person must use three words and
one person must use five words in
response he wants to use a wants
to use thirty who wants to you
five oh let you guys pick i
want three you want
three but i'll take one who frequent
i'll take five who at who asks
what who asked was i was just
we do a scene which is a
conversation okay but you can only say
three words asks why you'd only say
three words each time paul you can
only say one word i have to
say five words okay
hi
hi guys what's going on you look
great thanks i feel great as well
good
i am hungry real well why don't
you eat because i can't why what
happened to you lauren my surgery tomorrow
oof
forgot about your
surgery
my butt surgery wow getting a new
hole huh
ah gotta have three
sure like a lot of ah
right
totally don't finish piercings is what i'm
saying agreed okay let's play
sure yes let's play our game cards
for everyone thanks i love playing go
fish
floors
none go fish
you have to draw those oh
you don't get it no shit i
fucked up
shit i fucked up is for
you don't get it you don't get
it that's three it's for you you
don't owe you fucked huh yeah wow
he's a new rule that we joined
yeah well that's something has to happen
okay okay so now you and me
right
paul where are you going home
i wish i could go yeah i
have no home what i wasn't done
i feel like paul should be saying
three words because it's hard to fuck
up wow no see we keep it
okay fine i'm fine alright is hard
to fuck up one alright you want
to switch to three three time
three words recruits started up ah all
the and i'm the engineer now yeah
oh god and now i gotta press
this alright and ready three years
three
fuck
up on the freeway so but it
should be i think we shouldn't give
any we feel one word three words
five words and that's the game and
that's the jingle friend yes please yes
okay so you're switching
alright just adding trying to play that
again modern diet a lot of pressure
yes i am
why can't i go there it's not
safe
what's going on there now real bad
things this scene is very fascinating
did something happen over there
oh yes baby tell me everything paul
tompkins oh boy
it's paul f
tell me paul f tompkins
okay you ready i think so okay
go this is bad
i'm ready whenever you are
heard of murder
i think i read somewhere
it happened there
at your house over there murder did
yes
you murdered someone or the
no i didn't
so the alternative then is i'm afraid
so
janey cup murdered the the time
okay i'm out or fucked up
ah alright let's see well i one
kids went clean again and will do
it someone transcribe that
she got murdered the time was played
again switching and let's do the theme
song like lauren wanted yeah yeah go
three two one one wow
three wow
alright i want one okay i'll tell
i'll take five okay i'll do three
again so you're taking a break already
yeah i'm leaving
hi
get out now whoa lauren know why
so angry because he can't
he can't why say is that why
not what did you do nothing nothing
come on oh the trade tell me
something
in the way she moves
attracts
seriously scott
seriously wow
tell paul everything please scott i'd like
that
guilty
wow so you admit it
paul you know
i had my suspicions okay
your suspicions correct
i'm happy and sad so yeah mixed
bag
sins
have you thought about confession
religion
no priest for you you need religion
scott
that was close disbelief
you don't believe in anything
agnostic oh one of those
speak more words me or scott are
you
talking to scott oh thought you meant
me nope i'm talking monosyllabic
you why did you save me mano
syllabic no you're not that's not monosyllabic
cheated
every word cheated more crimes with this
guy sorry
zahra don't feed the bulldog are you
ou
yes
friends
wow
but dying what lauren call an ambulance
stocker phone doesn't work oops well scott
you did
good night
you did you hear that did he
die
he died and ah noise so he's
out
he took himself out yes
nobody awakened oh he's back and worse
now oh he said awake dead again
ah
well that was nuts huh
now just us i know how are
you i'm okay sorta what's wrong tell
me now sleeping so rough why bad
dreams or something
what else were
oh ah bad food reaction
no not food or counting us
did i do oh ah bad food
reaction oh my god okay yeah know
a bad food reaction ah ya
where's your wife
she was murdered i guess jamie was
that okay you are fucked up
no i'm not excuse me
ah excuse account no shoes that was
shoes off character
lauren i don't want to
just say whatever i don't want to
fight i'm not fighting
then who is because ah it feels
tense that wasn't that worked out i
was
i also think we shouldn't be able
to just cut off in the middle
of a sentence if we misjudged it
and trailer that doesn't that's not a
good that's kind of good yeah you
can't sell it with acting you know
thing i mean you're selling it you're
one of america's greatest actors i feel
like we need to do it where
it's very much you finish your whole
sentence okay
so lauren one oh great congratulations wow
that really worked out you lost the
first one you you came back you
got vick payback i was awake and
okay back dinghy
well that was fun though i was
a great day wasn't one of our
best and now it's a first game
with a theme song that's right that's
right wow it really is we have
to wrap it up guys thank you
so much for listening to us again
so happy to be back yeah to
be back we're gonna be back every
week for the
the next foreseeable weeks for a long
time oh yeah so look out at
the weeks how many can you see
you see them stretching into the horizon
that's how many weeks we're gonna be
back for love that um listen to
us again subscribe ah lee tell your
friends tell your friends we're on twitter
it is
five-star review and three dm usa that's
right and send us ideas for three
cheers if you didn't like this one
and hashtag it and it's reacher like
this one tell us why you liked
it yeah positive comments only
alright we'll see you on the next
episode okay bye hey
uh