yeah
three
yeah wow great oh my god oh
my god wow yeah the grapes green
grapes oh the grace eps of viral
video issues yeah oops okay so i'm
thinking shapes where she's gaping shops i
gaping yeah and it irks me to
do move
he called holes yeah starring shia leboeuf
shot out of the blue shy ah
yeah love shy love give me a
shy deer because yeah i'm a shy
be another pizza that boof give me
a shine gameo john
hi she looked at me but you
give me a shock because i felt
you looking at me were all looking
at you because you're on your phone
because i get you all looking this
this picture of me and loki my
dear friend oh from disneyland yes i'm
from your friend i met when i
was lowkey these days because you know
his season ended on a bit of
a cliffhanger
or did you guys have a chance
to catch up we didn't watch loki
this show oh and but you knew
who he was because um we are
speaking of my podcast newcomers in case
you're unfamiliar um i knew who he
was because i've seen many films such
as thor i've seen him on the
great white way screamed his name
please take a picture would be i'm
a loser now did he was he
in the character did he say look
after you he did and i was
taking the smoking stuff to eat say
ah he was like hi i'm low-key
like i'm low-key hungry right now um
i took it i took a picture
thing i don't know what he said
initially he kind of was just speaking
in the general lingo and then i
was marvel's you and i was so
excited in the nighttime so you actually
i'm standing here with two children who
probably should be taking a photo with
him make sure you stay for the
credits so my nephews hey guys do
you want to take a picture with
loki and then one of them said
no and one of them said yes
and he's like one or two something
sort of like that i like and
then i forced them both to be
gay gordon for two yeah and then
they both ran it um wow yeah
great story yeah loki it i liked
it but i got to be loki
and i saw doctor strange
to me yeah you just saw doctor
strange you didn't get to me i
didn't speak to him we watched it
in my backyard and didn't invite you
to be the same thing as well
to be quite clear when i wouldn't
have come you wouldn't have come i
don't want to watch that you don't
want to watch it not at this
time i feel like i need to
get through my marvel work for my
podcast and then maybe i'll watch me
for
finally i'm adding him in now it's
unfortunate when you're doing a movie podcast
when it feels like work yeah it's
because because you should be watching them
for fun for sure and i think
that that's true pain i'm excited to
be done with the season only because
it means i don't have to watch
anything for quote unquote work anymore yeah
oh really okay i like watching this
for fun yes well i i've i've
taken to now because i i've been
watching so many shitty movies although some
good ones ah i know am forcing
myself to watch like legitimately good good
films instead of just like when i
have a break oh let me watch
something for fun
that's just that could be bad or
whatever i'm like no i should be
watching something good because i'm doing it
for women is running out and dogs
perth you have yeah you want to
fill your brain with the goods will
like something something deputy with the g
well has like somebody that i'm not
not maybe feeling of like oh god
this
is going to feel like work like
a french you know for sure you
know i mean like i'll force myself
to do it because is there anything
that feels more like a day at
a factory than a french film
oh my god
we're so elite we are the elite
were not reliable i don't care leafs
i don't care
lauren i'm looking at your water bottle
yeah and there's two fruits it looks
like cherries but they're not the color
of cherries maybe they're apples to fruits
and okay thirty two scoops huh
what's that tim cutbacks
tim cook things to do homework to
figure out what it's like a riddle
yeah what do you gollum
oh i know about that i know
you do so it's it's too perhaps
apples and orange one and a green
one i wouldn't say so yeah okay
chair what would you say their chairs
okay there are cherries but i've never
seen cherries that color when ripe and
unripe and cooking and one says look
and one seven mi share yeah now
what that means so i got this
a sticker at a store in tokyo
called b-side label where they sell amazing
stickers tokyo's they're all from there and
i love them so much it's the
most fun store ever um and these
are all stickers that you put onto
a water bottle yeah so is the
way let me ask there's one this
is mix
water well to be clear these are
his houses what if he's looking for
that and the hat county and california
state law fifty fifty if you guys
got the right to use it that's
right if you guys got divorced and
i hope you don't i mean we
don't do but to be honest it's
about fifty fifty which will or not
but if you were to get to
my studies say you could happen to
you yeah yeah
fifty fifty pop up um i'd be
shocked would you take that would you
say like look i got these stickers
i want the bottle this bottle i
would let him keep really even with
the stickers that you'd like some i
don't want to take care of him
you know even though we're getting divorced
i think he should have a nice
ice water bottle ice wow um
the hidden taxes and practices of the
rice method rice i see sir
i see say oh the cats is
goofing around these stickers do you know
a vis um instagram account called good
shirts no it is literally just photos
of funny t-shirts really and i gotta
say they are good we had to
for the between two ferns mu
ivvy ryan's sort of costume choice was
that he would always be wearing t-shirts
yeah but you know they called t-shirts
what's the good t-shirt good shirt shirts
is the name of the account so
we couldn't we couldn't do like real
t-shirts because they're all copyrighted so we
we made them
for yourselves is fun but the the
real trick was not making them too
funny we were like sb just so
you can still watch the scene and
not be re not be like why
is this show are laughing it was
shirt says so it was like we
it is interesting like how just odd
the shirts are and yeah i feel
like they're like have to go back
and watch it as the shortcut yeah
i can't even remember any examples but
it was just i can't remember them
either but they were just like not
funny but not i remember one there
was a big picture of a peanut
and then anita said peanut stew
four i remember when there's a picture
but that's the kind of thing it
would be
that's actually good shirt yeah i would
but hey let's make three in buddha
store shirts know store store such a
good inside joke from freedom only three
my class yeah i think you're against
us what why i'm not not say
more that's so no just right now
it's looking good what happened what happened
i got pissed
because i finally realized why this peanut
store is big enough for the three
of us so no room for one
per let's get rid of one peanut
so on the front picture of peanut
underneath peanut store on the back this
peanut stores and big enough for the
this peanuts isn't bigger than the three
b p a p
picture of a peanut and then it
should say peanuts store no no that's
too funny and us too funny come
on yeah that's what the problem is
p and u s bemis this shit
is peanuts p e a and u
ah guys come to three of my
calls
and we didn't say last episode either
we did scott did did you get
it wrong about three boyden say we
were i had my feet up i'm
trying really remember it because i'm trying
to err i really remember it you're
trying to help your little leg yeah
i'm trying to oh you're up to
air yeah i'm saying you've done i
mean you've done rest i've done right
you haven't you skipped
nice i today i skipped ice but
always damn nice let's see constrictions you
skip that and you just went to
elevate so you've been right to elevate
we've done enough to do them in
order r e o it's probably better
i thought you had to do them
in order so whatever one's deal for
them constricting them we've got to look
up on the tower this is my
case where this is a relaxing episode
at thredup i love only listen to
this don't listen to it on thursday
yeah doesn't do when you get off
for less what i like about our
show is it's relaxed it's conversational we're
just shooting the breeze and we're three
people know each other meanwhile kevin like
a sneak is trying to take pictures
and even like zeke there's there's a
shadow of a microphone stand over kevin's
face through the window and it looks
like he had a topknot and i
was like why did he put his
hair up and i was like oh
here we go grow enough hair for
this top guy oh my god i
was so surprised but so did you
think it was sexy though i do
think they think whether things are sexy
or not with people i'm working with
so anyone you're not working with you're
constantly judging if they're sexy
i do allow that tend to the
conversation yeah here's a question speaking of
something that i just reminded myself of
rod stewart famously has had the same
haircut for all rob the mod right
yeah it's sort of like a feathery
like it's kind of like it kind
of looks like the puppet from mister
rogers yeah madam whatever so no what's
her name you don't know what i'm
talking about bowlers lady elaine fairchild
yes but then ah but he said
it was the scary one right lady
lean he sort of looks like lady
lee that's what i mean more than
anything
because the shirt or the hair of
lady elaine
i know his other sort of like
that yeah his ears are like that
yeah well it's it's not not like
that you describe this haircut because it's
like he has bangs coming down but
then the back is sort of sticking
i would call it like a job
school mullet yeah a double mollet all
the weightings in the front what does
this mean feathers in the back
huh i'd call it a feathery lift
i've got a burt's bees what thirty
burt's bees i got a bird's broad
stewards and his famous burt's bees
will be coming down you know the
shop steward from hamster learning first food
yeah hello i'm telling i'm telling you
that i heard it as rod stewart
i was like the kids in your
neighborhood were double-dipping and the sharp aiming
and i just tell you a story
about burt's bees yeah of course when
i first moved to l a i
got um i had some friends through
so
lori pirates the theatre company i was
part of and i they i got
an offer to do like a day
one one day job that would pay
like i don't know must have been
a few hundred dollars because they feel
like it was pretty exciting and the
job was a burt's bees sponsored sort
of thing where we went to the
beach um speech i think we are
in venice beach possibly and we did
you see a muscle man without but
it was arnold schwarzenegger roll my tongue
backend so i couldn't even do the
job you see an old lady on
a skateboard definitely so we had to
wear third bees beards that were made
of yarn okay and we had to
wear like a yellow cap and like
a t-shirt and then we were riding
these bikes that were stationary bikes that
made smoothies you know like when you
ride and then we premier smoothies like
like you had to pedal and yeah
yes right and then handing those swings
and then handing out um burt's bees
lip balms and things
to people as some sort of promotes
you're like the bird species girls but
you were beards yeah to sort of
like tamp down the hey we're not
sexy yeah we just either burt's bees
girls it's like the budweiser girls who
like sure you know it was really
hot and i think people were really
excited like they were attracted to us
i mean at the time oh never
call the temperature i think it's freezing
cool tries
they were but it was super high
actually sexy and um it was men
and women and um it was a
memorable day and i what one reason
i remember it very well is that
i pocketed like ten burt's bees chapstick
and have been using them for years
i probably still have wow i probably
do
i thought you're gonna say you pocketed
money that you charge like you're like
oh these smoothies are a dollar then
huh i never cheat no no no
no no other than stealing our hearts
huh
i've done it and chewy on mike
yeah guess i got admitted i guess
shoot me shoot my husband oh my
gosh oh shit minute
isn't it always insane when you find
out someone to that it's oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah i mean i know
the person that we're
talking about the most famous i don't
know that it was
the most famous was not immediately clear
how few people that we know you
mean yeah oh yeah you know no
i don't
why no person i don't know oh
boo i don't know well talks about
early won't tell you yeah i like
to already know yeah people are being
disgusting i don't know anything about anyone's
personal life someone was asking me for
gossip the other day do i have
any
somebody who asked me for no not
again not me yeah um so i
have somebody who asks me for gossip
really like i don't have it i
never asked if they were like but
i feel like i should and also
don't know each other that well it's
like we don't know right so if
i ski yeah you don't know well
it's risky but it's also if i
have gossip i would have to explain
who the
people are not showing us although that
being said i'm i've been bingeing a
podcast called normal gosh oh yes yes
yes and it's very enjoyable it's literally
people call ah well the the woman
host has a guest and then it
hosted a host reads a story that
has been submitted that is you're sick
because gossip a gossip story
submitted by so you could literally write
in and tell the whole story then
she'll read out louder than the guest
kind of like says what they should
do what she thinks what the guest
things they would do whatever and it's
very very fun it's a really good
listen and one thing i'm surprised by
is that a lot of times there's
no resolution because it's just a story
that secondhand more third-hand but you still
feel like
it was fun to listen to because
it's like you've got a good juicy
little store see to it as it
goes a lot juicy tit tid and
as it goes along you're thinking what
would i do oh my god this
is so annoying you imagine it all
happening it's very fun well this person
said okay tomorrow we were getting dinner
because we are a weird cheating on
cup we are
for the third time we're getting there
and they were like ok for tomorrow
think about it take a day and
think about it and bring back some
juicy gossip so this is like a
homework assignment oh here's the other thing
this is a friend of cool ups
cool up tells her all the guys
right she cool up knows the gossip
i don't know the gossip yeah so
i read
really rack my brains and i and
all i had was something pleasant that
someone did ah it's very cause like
this person's had some good news recently
did you do it in a salacious
voice
i've got to tell you some height
really crazy i had nothing because i
don't know any
someone tells me some gossip out there
yeah yeah i mean hotshots and normal
gossip
yeah but who cares right
i mean i didn't say you're this
i do understand the appeal of that
because it's like every once in a
while i'll see that on instagram solomon
georgio would do it a lot because
hey i pass it also similar as
it's but the guest is sharing gossip
from their hometown yes oh yeah but
just seeing that like this there was
this
ah you know guy who worked at
my mom's bank who did whatever it's
like it is kind of fun i
think so because yeah there's something very
funny about the normalcy of it it's
just it just kind of how relatable
at all is yes everyone has heard
a story like this life and yeah
every once in a while someone that
we know like there will be big
huge breaking
in like oh yeah when shattering that's
when it's fucking crazy young that's winning
the kind that this person was asking
before and i was yeah know that
you would have already said it if
they oh does this person like wanted
hollywood gossip no no why gossip about
people we knew cheeses you would know
if it was like that and call
up would have told them yeah
yeah but the idea of like no
i really want you to think about
this yeah no i really wanna use
my desk tomorrow is grasping at straws
i had nothing i don't ask for
gossip but i feel like the good
stuff finds me want to have fun
yeah because you're willing receptacle receptacle
i'm i'm kind of divided cum dumpsters
mine is a street called compstat north
hollywood the worst street remember worst
comes in and checks in yes paul
thompson checks out i am oh yeah
sql
are you going in the extensive stay
by two days because this play in
st
because it comes in gets a meal
voucher because his flight was cast
um i'm divided on gossip because obviously
if if it's something that's kind of
um ah salacious about people that it's
sort of removed from you like it's
not like a friend of yours you
know but it's somebody that's maybe on
the outer edge of yours yeah like
on yeah somebody honestly
i'm somebody you don't care about it
feels right yeah yes yeah but i've
had it where somebody started to tell
me something and i've stopped i was
like you know what i don't want
that in my head yeah i don't
want to like i'm close to this
person i just don't that was the
thing about words sometimes it seems like
like i've had people tell me things
that are so personal yeah that it's
like i understand that
that in the context of this story
this person is bad or whatever but
it's like now you're telling me something
that is absolutely none of my business
yeah and i don't want to know
that's how i would feel about people's
dating situations to like if if two
people i know dated for awhile and
was then
they would break up and one would
complain about yeah yeah it would be
like i you know i don't really
care i don't know because people break
up people you know it has to
cross into a level of like oh
this person like majorly did a wrong
thing or yes something illegal or something
like that for me to like want
to hear that kind of stuff like
because it's true
ricky because it becomes kind of a
grey area where like so does that
mean i'm not supposed to be friends
with that person anymore because you told
me this well and don't think about
how they were in your relationship yeah
sometimes it feels like it's an active
campaign we had somebody that we knew
two friends that like brief so briefly
hooked up like it was a matter
of like a week or something right
huh and then after
it was over now it was pretty
hot week man that's perfect they were
fucking for a week i mean it's
a great amount to do it but
after after it was thrown for giving
their schedules one of one of them
who okay yeah one of those friday
night probably yeah well if the week
starts on sunday yeah they wait
until friday yeah and suddenly and then
it's over yeah one of them was
trying to like kind of get us
to not like the other one and
it's like that's not gonna happen like
in and and it felt like the
the the the bear he lead was
you are actually wrong yeah well that's
always sometimes you wouldn't someone that i
to people or date
i don't know well and when i
do know well and the one who
i this is like four people know
the one i don't know well i'm
gonna go know there's somebody you know
while there's someone you wish you knew
on someone whoa these are the people
that you meet in life there's one
you know well there's one you don't
know well some you do not know
well some you do know well oh
okay i see the difference in things
so like yeah good
a friend good friends good friend partner
that i don't friend partner good friends
partner that i don't really know all
that well tries to like jack bauer
you pick it good friends here now
could he ever date he's like a
good twenty four hours or days after
chapter twenty four he big bigot so
good friends partner will will they'll break
up and then
i'm good friends partner will try to
like say like hey you're on my
side about this right and even if
my good friend is in the wrong
it's like no i don't know you
ah yeah i find it odd though
sometimes where there's a breakup and then
pure people you know
do stay in contact with that person
almost more than they did before like
you'll find that you go oh so
i guess none of that landed
ah wuss ups yeah i think it's
kind of funny i think it's kind
of sad the dreams which i'm dying
are the best
so that's me so what we're going
to say out there is don't go
you weren't gonna say anything to know
i had nothing that don't don't also
and if you're if if you know
two people who are breaking up just
let people fuck and have fun and
then break up and it's like who
needs to judge anyone if you know
two people were breaking up let them
fucking near out there having a summer
of your life fucking around live it
up and now the next song goes
out to camberley on the west coast
generally i hope you're slugged it up
out there and having a great time
roller blading at venice beach right now
we wanna give a shout out if
you are seeing a dog in sunglasses
you're probably on venice beach right now
so have a great time and enjoyed
those burt's bees chapstick smoothie on a
skateboard and pushed into the ocean let's
hear it for the
yes you love
oh alright we'll be right back
and wonder back oh my god during
the break we talked about all the
gossip yeah i'd say sorry no juicy
kevin leaves it in instead of putting
in an atom so no it was
so useful we know we don't really
have ads i think well yeah sometimes
the things we advertised by the way
it's weird gossiping about their yeah the
it's coded in there yeah oh there's
gossip mix into all the leesa mattresses
one of the habit of them i'm
seeing hide nor hair of them i
mean these to be i used to
i used to have the name lisa
in my mouth every day i used
my phone i used to forget to
to talk about them on tour and
lauren would have to for you to
go oh i think you're thinking of
your friend lisa right now yeah
ooh
ooh la la la la la are
you excited for tour everyone should be
buying tickets sold out yet ah some
shows are just about sold out but
yes yeah i mean they're on there
and get your tickets are we about
to go i don't even know when
the show it's now is a good
time to buy them were about i
think maybe
it starts next week as far as
whenever this one is coming out or
or maybe we're in the middle of
it but yeah maybe who knows oh
i'd be in the middle of the
tour we might be in the middle
of it when this is really know
but in any case where's the
my snapchat good times if you remember
to bring that that be sad not
be there when we're we're gonna miss
you know such funding when it was
saying it's not gonna be the same
gonna be different in a better way
yeah i guess it's gonna be great
just what i'm yeah that's true now
if i really am gonna miss you
on the tour
me too and i'm i'm shooting a
movie in august so i won't be
there to explain yeah um and the
movie is the comedy bang bang tour
movies so that's weird that's really yeah
i'm i'm just making my own story
and kinda guys guys to fill in
to play you guys i think you'll
be happy we even asked playing me
um i think it's just why he's
like an unknown but he looks like
mora no
me yeah how's that possible um yeah
he's anonymous he doesn't have a name
he cheats anonymous with perfect data oh
my chinese will buy anonymous and you're
playing me and then somebody else you
are really good you impression and then
the me is played by christian sean
chelsea pretty
combined and they are they're switching off
scenes or the cgi i'm gonna get
a malaga mission oh faces incredible amalgamation
it's an incredible amalgamation that's what's called
wow i liked ah yeah i liked
that a lot an incredible amalgamation colon
the cvb tour twenty twenty two where
does this kind of stream up
your asshole i think okay right like
a good day
wow great
is that a stream stream as far
as i'm concerned has to be i
think a stream goes down but would
you call it a forceful gush if
you're if you're spraying a hose and
you turn it towards the sky it's
still a stream know what do you
call it then and a front three
to god oh shit god doesn't want
to be wet
maybe he does and that's why he
invented hoses you think he invented oses
he put them there to test us
like dinosaur bones every invention that man
sees these guys will spray me
oh isn't he what's bringing me
jose powerful those too short to spray
on god is it possible
oh lord oh paul scott
wait a bit yeah um yeah it's
going to be it's gonna be lonely
out there on the road without you
know what are you gonna do you're
gonna put in my place i mean
who who could fill my huge shoes
you do have huge shoes huge huge
but it's because your wiki feet it's
because you want to protect my well
my foot ego is gigantic yeah you
stuffed them with clean exes to like
with aloe aloe vera yeah i love
olive oh and we've done a show
on my ma we did it was
so much oh fine we have an
audience
once we finally were in front of
it wasn't really fun people clap yeah
they did didn't sound so funny it
was our first show with an audience
we've um how many shows that we'd
done now fifteen jesus selling like that
yeah and it was our first time
with an audience and it was so
different yeah and it was so much
fun i can't wait to again do
we laughed a lot yeah i think
i think we should do it in
september
that's nice yeah wake me up when
september ends oh okay i guess is
that from a song is jus
er yes yes i want my own
show we keep asking you to do
threesome live and you always say no
i do love freedom lie can just
busy didn't want it it was fun
too busy i think if you're really
good time yeah too busy to go
out one night we could do it
we could do it a dynasty tip
river and we could strap a str
i'm it to the world every hour
of the day is filled up huh
you liar lie
you're just afraid i'm afraid i'm afraid
of performing in front of people you're
scared little baby we gotta do it
it'd be so fun if everyone out
there wants us to do it come
into our latest instagram posts begging us
to yeah bag literally begged us but
look lauren you can't do it anyway
because you'll get a movie i'll get
i'll be able to do a one
night show
we did we did one my just
didn't do a movie and said oh
i passed yes what's movie did you
pass up it was called ah what
was cold titanic really really really skipped
over to maybe did too but it
wouldn't be o d o who it
did
it was a different boat or the
door the doors door that he lays
on there's a um there's a thread
doors in titanic two
titanic i want ah yeah god
that's it's it's own dated in the
weirdest way have a doors titanic movie
it makes
i mean the ireland wrong the doors
movie oliver stone came out and what
ninety two i really dislike tannin came
out ninety eight say it's not that
you dislike yeah i don't enjoy the
door but something underneath dank what if
they made a bunch of like ah
like any money types movies oh yeah
like the doors the fun doors
having adventures they're called the doors the
doors to reception yeah atlas huxley my
dear see dear i had ah they
had a good logo i will say
that yeah goodluck that's the thing about
bands if you get a good logo
use it on every one of your
shoe but you know it's kind of
crazy what some maybe you know van
halen duran light on this
this yeah target cells band t-shirts now
they're at nirvana rolling stone yes yeah
you know the notorious b i g
y ng r they able to do
but who did that the rolling stone
said target consoler shirts probably a company
mexico and that's why
wild and nirvana are either one company
makes them another running the licensing company
makes them oh and you know i
don't really want winning huh so one
company licensed either one either target buys
them all from one company and they
individually i would make some eggs and
that's probably the case or target is
out there like reaching out to various
teacher and cutaways going hey we have
their individual has loved to see nirvana
shirt in our stores what do you
say
the kids want the nineties now they
don't go talk to which nirvana races
nova selleck that's the one with his
fine band members the smiley guy yeah
they have it in baby sizes as
well oh what do you think about
that about do you put your baby
in things that you think are cool
um so far she doesn't really wear
logos of any kind she's pennzoil pretty
exclusively patterns that's the move yeah right
depends yeah scar rates yeah stp absolutely
um but i died i think i
would gladly do it i think i
just think baby clothes are so cute
with all their little kittens and patterns
they didn't have you know baby calls
you're cuter than like your musical tastes
yeah go on your butt yeah i
never it doesn't really do anything for
me like i don't think it doesn't
what about morning it's played out like
whenever that first was happening ratios that's
pretty funny like that fur remains ones
or whatever but now it's like no
you've got about a t-shirt with like
a funny saying i'm trying to think
of the baby ones that i've seen
kind of like like oops i in
hoops
thought it was a fart dirt out
it was issued that it was vargas
funded and it was shard thought it
was a sharp turned out it was
this is good
reclaiming my time okay go ahead i
guess that's a good start
yeah for a buddy oh buddy
my time do you put my one
holly i'm sure it says biden for
president ah don't put her in what
do you put her in like shirt
says i don't i don't put her
in funny shirts i really don't just
all floral you know just cute she's
just use just enough energy to fruits
and vegetables you got ghidorah clothes and
fetch some stripes i do buy her
a lot
boy clothes because i just think they
look really cute and there's you know
a whole world of patterns they don't
decide to share between jays that's for
sure no it's very steep especially like
what types of patterns like getting like
navy like the stripes are just more
quote unquote masculine color mix of striped
masculine that you will see like frederick
douglass poem
it's a stripe masculine but like it's
like and they also have different snaps
the boy's clothes have snazzy for shoulder
whereas the girls have snaps on the
back hand then it can i got
asked this one what's up with the
the the buttons being on opposite sides
for me i feel like i used
to know that and
i don't remember it doesn't throw you
off one because you don't often put
on a woman show no sign on
a man's shirt you don't know how
to do yeah your every need why
don't you go whoa everything should be
uniform you call your doctor why is
it different buttons i don't know jiggle
you only look to shop but look
it up because it deserves after doesn't
have anything to do with like
the hand strength or like like they
know men are jerking it so the
right hand is i mean stronger what
about so left-hand a man wears a
woman shirt i guess so and then
women are flicking the bean with the
left yeah ah yeah that checks out
that's exactly what it says here on
wikipedia yeah i'm fleeing nine i'm leaving
that right here yes who added that
i love it haha yeah well i
mean it doesn't make any sense and
why would it be even a thing
is it to deter people of other
genders from being in specific clothes or
call you
oh nothing no i felt learned was
looking at upside and just saw the
worst thing when i like it like
that's horrible would you say can't even
talk about it just bad news oh
yeah you know it's just all that
too i don't know i don't think
you saw i think i thought you
might have seen a different piece of
bad news this is just i think
i'd know which one to use oh
my god i will have to talk
later and i don't want to
anyone today here's what i've nuclear wars
what i've put you know it's it's
like it's not a news mine is
not a news story oh my nose
i was got put in wires which
nobody knows somebody who's something bad agito
yeah something that happened to me and
i texted it to lauren oh no
yeah happened to you well lauren could
tell you oh lauren what happened with
what
so i put it in the i
started to put in the words why
do women and will come right away
is why do women live longer why
do women wear hijabs and why do
women have periods
jesus chris
so which one why did women decide
this by the way this is a
women periods this is not a bad
three ter when we don't have anything
to talk about is to put it
in three words and then find out
the answer okay watch some of these
why do women's that leaves us that
leads us to why do women's nipples
hurt why do i mean period sink
snc di did you try to look
up why do why does victoria's secret
underwear have a pocket
um alright i don't think i've ever
so why do women house acutely red
shirts is not like doesn't come up
right away sure so you're just going
down why do women shirts button on
the left here we go oh then
we'll find out about the periods sinking
get a load of this shit okay
wow
wealthy women back then did not dress
themselves their ladies may did oh and
they needed it since most people right
handed this made it easier for someone
standing across me to button your dress
but that's why keep it going now
when we can't afford survey has so
many weird things like that in our
world that we just kept doing i
hate this country and world will please
please
only two two button on the dominant
hand i absolutely will promise me only
your dominant hand is the one the
button to woman holly to pass the
duchy panda left-hand side
pause touchy on the law who said
i said pause i want to fly
at me and i actually say please
spend more time to she loves you
but i want i feel that i
felt we did have a little connection
yeah ah the last year getting much
more um outwardly effect yet though but
she's like
found even today she was almost like
hugging me back more oh yeah lily
q shoes grabbing at my watch and
then she would like look at me
and she loves watch it so she'd
love that big face do you have
a special apic face wow on your
head it looks bigger moves regular but
it's just what you have in the
didn't you use to by having her
there is a case on on around
dna paul didn't used to buy watch
as a big watch guy didn't didn't
weren't we in a mall once and
the beverly center and you were looking
for watches yes i think so i
probably went to the foster family law
was a long have not that many
anymore you think lawyers don't throw them
in the trash just i smash them
with a hammer starting back mad hatters
gonna do it
let me try again i gave them
away because um janie got me an
apple watch and so i did not
i mostly read this yeah but i
have a i have a couple pocket
watches and i still have some ah
automatic watches which are um the kind
that are powered
buy your wrist movement what um yeah
what does that mean during to wind
it so it's like somebody's wearing me
i got to keep the time yeah
i guess i'll keep this going like
like the wrist movement kind of implies
it's being worn at the time no
and the energy know it energizes it
yes yeah yeah keep yes it makes
it run like right
it's like there's an evolution of your
it's the smoothies maybe by the birthday
guy that's how i can understand it
and i'm a couple mechanical watches better
where you have to wind them but
you have to wear a fake beard
the y just wear a winding i
find stressful why it just feels whole
stressful just feels like there's got to
be a better battery in here
i enjoy it but then what about
replacing the battery i like to do
i love to waste
but isn't that stress is that i
read online that you can don't you
can drop off old batteries and i
found such things at home depot they
have different garbage cans for each thing
yes okay so you should get and
then they take it to the landfill
yeah i mean yeah as long i
should hope that it's going somewhere appropriate
but i know i when when i've
read that they don't you yes fuck
the shit like the recycling in california
that is oh i don't believe in
i don't i don't recycling really it
all just goes right in the i
can't stand to how everything works why
does nobody care why is there not
a billionaire
or who's going let's fix a couple
of these things it makes no difference
to my bank account i do like
i do like the mark cuban is
doing the prescreen i love it although
you're right about him saying like we're
not spending a dollar on advertising maksim
said we should know what it is
right now because they yeah because maybe
no it's he started a company that
you can buy prescription drugs that like
the actual guys
yeah like yes yeah and so it's
like it's like the only time i've
ever heard about it you know when
you get something good for for anything
other than just like giving money away
and going you for charity but so
they did say they're not going to
directly helping a lot of people if
they hear they did say they're not
going to spend any money on it
but it's called cost plus
drugs yeah just cost plus what i
want to figure out how to get
all medical fun
yeah what what medications are you on
i'm not on any actually what um
you gotta be some you gotta take
care of some of your obvious sides
doe um
you searched a brand name or the
generic name and then it finds you
the call the item and what tells
you how much what what happens if
you put in diarrhea okay let's just
try picture of a baseball diamond
because you sliding yeah there's no medication
which baser you won't ah
and then we can tell you what
medications here
or did you feel a great big
a search by address you can get
it for for eighty come on guy
or one hundred and eighty dollars for
viagra don't need a boner say no
is four dollars four dollars and eighty
cents and you save how i do
have any eight dollar pill or a
bottle it retails for one hundred eighty
three dollars that's insanity thirty ten sam
thirty count is fall under
or five dollars instead of four not
to get that i gotta go i'm
gonna get some for later let's all
guys what if we took fiber right
before we were course let's see what
happens
you guys just fuck each other
and i go behind the glass to
heaven
and call the police
alright we go take a break huh
oh arabic
and we're back we're back we're back
now can't deny it here we don't
ever argue with us about being back
because we said we were back you're
listening to us that means we are
this is all i'm going to say
on this topic yeah we are back
period end of story end of story
you know i was
yo that commercial that you see on
probably hgtv where it's the property brothers
and he goes fact we all love
video camera yes there are video door
doors doorbells what does i do talking
about that it's not bad fucking fact
proper love it i have
what i wouldn't say i love it
yeah yeah i mean yeah hey it's
great i love it oh hell yeah
it sounds like an ad network
oh yeah the show was actually back
but look for twenty percent off a
doorbell you could just bring anybody else's
steal it because then i'm doing an
love and then the numbers it off
good a doorbells john door dash three
door work
but then the other the indoor property
brothers the property ones ones outdoor ones
indoor i'll take your word i think
it was kept in a crate that
everyone gets to run free no ones
the ones the guy selling the house
one chance to vulnerable to coyote construction
vs realty so indoor property brothers says
it's how he
he follows it up and he goes
goes personal voice assistants have changed the
way we do whatever right any but
but the implication is he's saying it's
a fact as well and that's not
that's not affect the yeah the tiny
amount of people use them we have
a personal voice assistant if you can
call it that right and
the only thing we use it for
is to turn the lights on and
off oh i use a personal voice
assistant on the ride some a lot
of timers when i'm cooking
cooking oh what this is huge news
because i did say what i really
would like this i have started cooking
and i'm going to commit to this
what did you knew um i've made
a few dishes tell us yeah ticks
to show the recipe it sounds more
tartary i wanna hear i made let's
see i made raw corn zucchini and
snap pea
salad with lemon vinaigrette that i also
made whoa yeah no shit was good
it was delicious i mean cut i
mean pink katu peppa like you may
let you pepe i did last night
yeah what's eating but simulants are pink
peppercorns whoa it was that good it
was really good i made soft scrambled
eggs with bharat
on toast with including your regular shine
now paragon i put tarragon on the
shit how did you do all this
i guess talking about too i also
don't know this sort of it sort
of a cookbook that i bought called
what's gaby cooking eat what you want
and it's god of the elkins book
and they're all really easy recipes and
i
wow did you have to buy i
would say ordered you talking did you
stock up like yes i did what
he said yes i did join you
i said no i said to mike
scott said his mom would buy the
ingredients for the week planning me so
i picked out three things i wanted
to make and i or i ordered
my groceries which i've been doing since
the pandemic anyway and i just put
in all the ingredients which made it
much easier because one of the things
that hold me up from cooking is
that i don't know what other things
are i'm like books tarragon yeah i
gotta google that at the grocery store
look around i fear what it looks
like right when i'm ordering groceries i
could just type it in and then
there it is so that made it
a lot easier for me yeah and
i have found that i'm really um
loving it and the
meals obviously are way better than everything
else i've been fuckin eating francis so
it's not as if you're not ordering
food to it's like not as high
uncertain oh completely and also it's like
i've been wasting so much money not
wasting because i it's been necessary and
having the baby i feel like ordering
became more of a thing because we're
just so busy fact we all love
ordering online but
not ordering we deleted postmates from our
phones wow that always work away with
you
people in our account so we don't
even get oh just like hillary told
you to yeah so that was that
was kinda crazy to me because i
have wanted to order things but i
have um not ordered anything and we're
also finding that we're just making we
have tons of groceries always that we're
ignoring because we're like it's easier just
to go yeah yeah i'm loving it
so far that's so
so proud of yeah thank you so
much and i'm going to make some
banana mum chacha muffins from her book
as well whoa i have plans this
week so you know this is all
it's all good alright there's something i
have to do as well yeah what
great book are you going to buy
well shitty food for assholes i saw
one cookbook
maybe it's the name of it but
the the picket the picture on the
cover was like a big bowl of
gummy bears and just a spoon and
somebody eating um so i know that
seems like right now i would like
to issue a correction a nucleus of
a new oh my god so i'm
doing comers correction on this show i
spent new-comers that i don't like
mochi but then i felt that i
was confusing i was talking about i
do like mochi i recently have been
having mochi and i actually love it
i never had it before when i
said that i didn't have a talk
with something else and i'd like it
a lot consider the nachos i was
thinking macho there you go yeah now
that actually sharing that right because i
couldn't figure it out and i was
waiting i'm thinking of green tea you
shouldn't make it sound so similar anyway
chevron has a voicemail for us and
let's hear it none of that was
an ad by the three i love
you guys quick question are you a
question if you could have your own
like disney world kind of theme park
what would it be what would the
different worlds the whoa the different sections
of the place vs what i mean
whoa
love love you it does i was
thinking about this regarding disneyland how crazy
that a guy's name guy's last name
is now synonymous with we we have
because i like i'm like laugh kiss
like if it just had a laugh
cause i absolutely fucked me here yeah
oh strange what would your world be
sex world i mean peep show i
me a haunted house again but i
would become a column
um i you know i don't know
i think disney world kinda nailed it
it's hard to think of something that
they haven't watched the new disney land
world be because they they've got the
future
then a lot of it is the
past like frontier land yeah star wars
the past so yeah the lounge the
best ancient oh so long ago yeah
yeah that's confusing to me but then
adventure land feels like the past because
no one's really having these types of
adventures anymore are they like jump happens
oh that's adventure land that's adventureland indiana
jones is the
past yeah i'm like yeah we went
in the cars land right yeah and
the share was the funniest fucking picture
my nephew looks so freaked out over
because they take it over the last
big crazy yeah yeah our nephew we
were there for years or so ago
and he was a little like i
don't want to do that again but
i'm wondering how oh no hell on
it now yeah buddy i think the
age
cause they had that too about a
few things they refused to go on
haunted mansion because they were they were
so three and six last time and
they were scared of it when we
went on but now they're six and
nine but i couldn't convince them never
in my life am i going to
go on that ah my nephews are
veterans of the gulf war oh
so they're scared of
um but yeah so what i mean
because the future just takes care of
everything so what in the past could
like they're they're they're all there could
be like like pyramids and stuff oh
no i don't think i really want
anything from the past i think i
just want something completely fake like
like really cute jello wowed all over
the place now rambo lin yeah and
everything's like really likes fluffy bunnies and
stuff so you like flood zones like
it's for girls no boys foods i
swear i you know what i would
like to do is something like meow
wolf does if you're familiar with me
i am i do know why
i'm no deer meow wolf it shouldn't
very new okay um but that's like
an immersive um experience in in new
mexico and i think they have one
in i want to see in colorado
now and and maybe in vegas and
laser tag no no it's like it's
sort of like an immersive art
thing where you walk around and see
all these different things
in marfa
or anywhere is it santa fe santa
fe yeah yeah marvin is in texas
no yeah i didn't mean no yeah
i did not say marfa
you're making shit up i say
shit that's my new routine like i
did not say that i think that
i just said to i didn't say
that that's not what i said no
you said mar you can't prove it
and i say
but something that has like a so
like the whole place has a story
to it that's a yawn what i
liked about it is you can go
through a museum scavenger hunt land yeah
actually that's a really good one yeah
oh she would have to be really
smart disney is going to pay me
a million dollars i'll never figure out
the scavenger hunt
oh way too much rabbit can get
involved badger abbott give a fuck now
when i think of scavengers i think
of like a sort of cormac mccarthy's
the road kind of sitopia yeah that's
what we need in a theme pan
when i started okay so i bought
that book i heard it was good
or whatever
is heard it was hilarious no i
just i forget where i saw it
like on a best of list or
whatever so i started reading that book
and when i was alone and i
was twenty pages into it and then
call up came home and my she
walked in and my face was ashen
oh and i was like i just
started this and this is the heaviest
book i have ever seen my fucking
intense intense
it's yeah they made a movie like
movies see that movie yeah it's nothing
i'm reading a book that i was
told will make me cry the bible
yeah because what they did and that
j ca hiss yeah
what book is that it's called crying
in h mart oh yeah yeah ah
it's by ah cabin systems up yeah
it's by yeah actually can't remember the
author's name because i know i've been
carrying it around michelle michelle's honor i
think it's about michelle zahner i think
michelle's honor yeah i'm pretty sure i'm
actually said that first was she
nathan card is how do i know
about this i don't know but um
maybe you don't get a lot of
talk about that book yeah oh she's
from japanese breakfast i don't know the
band i don't know she's the leasing
really she's leaving every manager also wrote
a great book yes this is this
unfairly it's not bad it's not good
that's awesome let's let's keep the
listen czech ladies yeah one can do
more than only it's like you just
we just started allowing you to do
one thing and now you want your
tales pen name
like j k rowling's yeah george sand
this book is by george sand it's
so good he writes women so well
i love george sand yes but but
i've heard that book is great i
i'm only on i just finished chapter
you and you'd like her band as
well well i know that i do
like japanese breakfast i didn't know that
she was an author well that song
she thinks about just like i'm the
author of crying an ice bar i'm
good around i wrote that book about
crying in h mart i
wrote that book about crying
learn is my thing the bass guitar
very many guitar and then the hand
went outward
gotta cut the bowl alright we have
to hold we have to play we
have to play a creature yeah we
do there's no way around it i
gotta go soon yeah because someone's calling
me that i gotta shoot location picked
up and what's going on oh we
could just end it all right this
is a creature
go to the light go to the
site three sure but submitted by mister
dirty randy oh jesus and it's called
in the manner of the word okay
two people decide on an adverb without
the third knowing lot of these games
involves subterfuge yeah the third player asked
the others to do tasks in the
manner of the word it could also
be done as the scene
the players carry out activities phone call
singing a breakup in the manner of
the adverb adverb chosen slyly stupidly yeah
we actually know what adverbs armley and
the third player has three guesses to
guess the word normally would be horrible
okay
wow how would anyone figure oh yeah
i'll make focus
two people decided the third does not
know okay yeah alright okay let's try
it who wants to um say it
again
yeah ok we're gonna i thought for
sure we'd have to call out a
little paul and i are going to
know paul guess there's an adverb that
you i'm guessing yeah you're gonna get
and then how to like no paul
gets this as opposed to jars and
and that was the best those the
best ever um there's an adverb you
know when everyone your head
i'm wearing one based on what am
i using to guess ah yes yeah
way we're something we're in the middle
of a scene we're going to do
a scene oh so i get you
to say it no we're we're going
to be doing everything in the style
of that adverb go yeah give us
a task if you say do this
in the manner of the word it
doesn't have to be a task i
should just
it was seen okay so a single
guys yeah this is a test right
now i haven't we haven't sent the
adverb yet oh i thought you were
supposed to do it in your mind
or the lights up in our mind
well you don't have to guess to
we're going to decide okay got it
got it right yeah we're both going
to do it steven d dead oh
i'm trying to think of any words
ah is really hard when you got
to think of anywhere i got to
work okay yes send it
daily li daily li da da la
di di di di di di li
li li li this is our waiting
for politics music okay
was gumby relatively
that's a blast to make it more
challenging yeah okay alright okay guys um
thank you so much for coming i'm
so glad i was able to hire
you both i need you to clean
my home um obviously that's why a
higher g or cleaning service there is
a lot of mess everywhere so if
you could just um
i guess hop to it
what's um yeah no yeah
no let's do it yeah wow what
a way to whatever we do what
we did sleepily
we didn't even yawn and you got
it
great okay yeah ty for me yeah
we went we were holding the yawns
and reserve i was like man i
could probably push this for a while
franca yawn
dope what we're gonna do me and
paul are gonna do one and then
i'll text him the word love it
love it you'll love it and love
it down daily lee delete a daily
daily lately ready
yeah yeah go hey guys um i
finally got my parents car so um
do we get in we'll get on
the road for this shore hey
ah are you guys okay are you
guys mad we're fine fine
we don't have to go if you're
the ones you want i really want
to go i just we just have
to go now if we're gonna go
because it's just not gonna happen otherwise
yeah i know you know what it
is already
here sadly no ah look
oh i'm slut
i don't know you're making me know
i got snacks just take them put
on a car
just put it in the corner what
we do but let's just do it
you guys i'm saying it's like what
are you waiting for god i i'm
i'm waiting for you guys to tell
me what's going on i mean i
obviously nothing you going on wow insulted
do you realize how your voices sound
right now yeah i taped i'd taped
you just saying that okay no things
going on why did you say that
whatever i sell my sound putting a
filter on that yeah like shit
that's someone who sounds like i don't
sound sepia what is it telling you
it's i mean you sound ah exasperatingly
we're not exasperatingly sound exasperatingly yeah you
sound ah ah oh you sounded no
definitely annoyed and
i wouldn't say that we're annoyed ah
this is a worst day of my
life
you sound i mean this is like
high hyperbolic oh i'm serious it is
definitely ah like seven which is just
over where your your
oh let me go through the words
in the dictionary
oh my god what a hardware why
would you do that instead of going
through the seven dwarfs oh um who
are the seven doors let's see she's
so grumpy rumbling yeah yes this isn't
a good game now doesn't know that
alright listen
right it's been great it's been great
we love him we love everything we
love everyone alright everybody send us a
voicemails we love your voice business has
been good that those kind of props
it's fun haha input and if you
have you know an advice situation you
need to deal with that's fun too
and if you want to follow us
on instagram or any other social media
is
it's at threesome usa that's correct righteous
three am usa gmail dot com and
if you want to hear ad-free episodes
of the show you can go to
series x m or cbt world dot
com yes and great also go fuck
yourself ok
wow thank you bye bye
uh