throw it here
three
i didn't know that
um swallows i don't think he knows
an idea yell and my own ears
you know
god that would be so great if
i could yell in my own ears
i love my lips could reach back
there here's what i do like get
off all day i'd take take the
garden hey hey hey scream into it
i bend it around to my ear
admirer remember that your barrel around you
remember that were you around your goggles
yes what is the oh what are
you talking they were
or a product that was sent to
us by the way hi welcome to
freedom yeah hi by the way hi
by the way we're doing a podcast
and it says lauren over here to
my right where we're outside over here
to my right and this is lauren
over here to my oreos i love
to scott
ah fucking assholes but which are high
on for both of you which harm
your right arm and what's my name
god say my name your name is
why didn't you ask me now it's
gone too long and you feel
you are twenty five years i'm finally
figuring out your name no one ever
says it around him
they're always introducing one's age this guy
who has two thumbs and has many
new standard eighties no introduction right
who has two thumbs and needs no
introduction that they pointed my age this
guy
it's
okay good okay so it was pretty
good
we should do it i mean look
we joke around a lot that's bad
that actually works we are outside by
the way yeah in case you hear
any ambient noise we're outside oh just
flew over me yes is that an
omen alan crabs tweeted that crows are
getting you know is it alan somebody
no alex bernie tweeted that crows are
getting too big
you agree cruiser gang oh okay to
use the alan mcleod of twitter in
my opinion yeah it's a very specific
you know i mean like if you
see what he tweets then you understand
that it makes sense when you look
weird as hell mcleod tweets but he's
not the allan mcleod he would anyway
i bet he feels bad about it
is the allan macleod of the icloud
i bet he true he is the
one and only high class home the
cloud is out there and he had
access to all of our icloud so
that would be stressful alan mccoy
i trust him i would trust him
with all that i feel like i
would i could trust alum i could
not trust outs for any with that
info no use yes i wish any
of you knew who these two guys
were i do well now i know
what you mean yeah the listener sure
we are outside they know who they
are so the listeners yeah
you know who you are you know
who you are if you're listening to
this you know who you are yeah
so the ear goggles were a product
sent to us at the mister show's
writers room i don't know why why
is it they were about to explain
it lol they were like i'm they
were like you
even losing my mind over here for
thinking i'm scared she's been fiddling in
our seats shaping and he's shaking shaking
like a chihuahua so they were like
you use glasses for your eyes don't
you yeah we'll use these for your
ears and they were basically like ah
it was almost like having headphones
but then they had plastic like half
cups that would go behind your ears
and point here more and points at
like yeah so you could hear things
from across the room they were things
that you weren't hearing before it was
like having a megaphone up to your
ears but why would you it's like
fertile didn't pee wee erwin do that
well it's like you know holding your
your cupping your your hand up to
your ear and saying like a pardon
me you know yeah we used to
wear em all the time and your
ears just stick out and you go
i actually did hear that
i bet you guys thought i wasn't
listening and it was just a weirdo
i can tell if i heard everything
you said i can't tell if they
were a novelty item like haha you'll
throw these away or if they were
trying to get these going novelty ohio
throw these away that's how i all
novelty items are made so you can
grow it out do you guys still
own any novelty items i run
yeah qa will be a mission for
sure
christian pressure is your excuse because you've
got a joy buzzer somewhere i think
scott oh my god reality recap yeah
someone on the bachelorette used on the
bachelor used a ah one of those
ring buzzers when she met the bachelor
was really funny but um i do
have a what because she and my
costume bucks your cost you're not using
it for a costume my prop
huh yeah prop bucks you don't have
one i bet i used to i
used to have a lot of props
and a lot of cops costumes for
doing live shows all the time like
stripper grams of course
my boom box was here
i got rid of a lot of
them like ah and recently i would
yeah it was like i'll just buy
whatever yeah that sounds like why do
i have this pile up at the
worst way if anyone's ever seen but
you know what i've been in that
situation where i know where you can
find it yes and it fucking sucks
sometimes but a specific thing in mind
and at the time i was doing
enough shows all the time where it
was like oh yeah i can use
this wig exam
likely i'll turn it around and do
it this way or whatever now shows
are over so what's the issue exactly
yeah entertainment is over this is not
entertainment by the way speak we know
we've never said it was we never
said why not but we're moving into
like infotainment
i did want to add health and
wellness i got a lot about vitamins
and a lot about crystals i want
to talk about okay did you know
william howard taft had to have a
special bathtub built for him that's info
that's info tainment way why because he
was a great big fat man like
use r fattest press though he had
a big tub made yet it had
accustomed tub made because of regular
tub would not fit him but about
back then everyone was so tight and
they all paths also back then they're
all to bend there wasn't enough mass
production on the scale where they could
go like well a little a little
justify us making three thousand of these
huge tubs because there were three thousand
people who advise wow they probably were
there probably were but they just didn't
know like where back then we want
a tammany
the hall supermarkets weren't even around then
so it's like where do you even
go to github just regular market regular
markets they were cheaper now they were
small you go in there and you'd
say what do you have any potatoes
and they say we just sold it
how good would you be on supermarket
sweep terrible and be fantastic i'd be
fantastic you have to know prices you
you sometimes do but you mostly have
to fill in the blank or something
when i was twenty five but with
words twenty five twentieth you have to
enjoy w i feel like
this this ah salad maker ah fuck
i can't even salad make let me
go back okay when the brand first
of all crash x me go like
rise and shine it's time for my
morning orange juice made by sunkist nago
and you got a point okay wait
really it doesn't have to be the
one you're thinking of you
no that was what i though that
was where okay good wow i was
happy enough happy accident um somebody told
me somebody told me i redd somebody
told me away told you had a
girl friend guy told me supermarket sweep
was coming back with lizzie jones know
leslie o gums i
would love more i p alright p
right i think so didn't she say
something before one of our tour shows
but didn't her voice come out yes
was that leslie ugh where was that
it was part of it was in
toronto maybe i don't remember we talk
about it in the actual episode yes
sharper your listeners if you wearing your
ear goggles notice
no lesbians might still be alive i
think she i'm researching this now thank
you more info yes vote for info
tv live and she's yeah me eight
years old god i'd love to hit
that
i'd love zero she's beautiful yeah i
love fred wesley jones i'd love for
her and leslie jones to do like
color and commentary yeah you know what
i mean supermarket color competition and what's
the other way by play play by
play yes that's right that's super who
would do who would do what like
i feel like leslie jones to do
color commentary yeah
and leslie albums we actually play my
work of leslie uh gms are you
kidding me or you maybe i haven't
i don't know getting us the more
famous person in the world you cannot
be serious who was that
ah you know well it was me
but i was i swear your letterman
i was pretending to be someone oh
more of this infotainment can unlock my
phone okay okay there we go again
unlock my phone what are you unlocking
your phone for you looking gladly yeah
i'm trying to look up leslie ago
she was an actress and she was
a singer i saw that oh
okay so now united saw that but
i didn't know what she's in she
was she id i don't even know
like deadpool oh yeah she was the
old lady haven't seen deadpool oh ok
we or you could say that examine
said poor guys the like the neighbor
of deadpool who's blind neighbor of deadpool
lol yes deadpool has a right to
say william shakespeare was due to deadpool
avenue our production of the neighbor of
deadpool will be postponed um leslee imams
also famous for the famous june is
busting out all for june is busting
out alo the way she would wish
some award show and she's supposed to
sing joonas bussiness
or she makes her way to the
stage ah but the ah teleprompter goes
down and so she just essentially makes
up that's it oh wait like she
is doing things that sound like words
do the two what year was this
ah if it was in the future
i'll ago because you know that aretha
franklin clark yeah i'm sorry narrate the
pet of the bell yeah yeah
oh oh and she's like i don't
know
the words honey but she kept doing
it i loved it as opposed to
mariah carey who just likes you know
age yeah exactly she doesn't have with
the the the leslie ugh gms the
great sea against the labelle the lapels
have yeah yeah ah absolutely gums is
great ah yeah
you you gotta you gotta check her
out check out her work i'm just
so good so right yeah million pool
don't be put off by the first
syllable in her name she's great lauren
can i say you you remind me
of deadpool
you are very reverent yeah you wear
a mask everywhere you go through i
won't show my true side your face
is just imaginable is that what is
facing yes and yours
his face is mash puppies played by
ryan reynolds arguably one of the hottest
people now tell me that is real
in itself and i guess that's funny
you think ryan reynolds is one of
the hottest people in the world i
think arguably people would say ryan reynolds
is one of the top people would
say i'm saying you would say he's
extremely attractive one of my first jobs
was that's where it ran routes what
did you do i do
yeah i did a bit on jimmy
kimmel with him where i got to
improvise with him for like a solid
seven minutes really yeah seven oh my
god long sketch it's really funny did
the whole thing err yes i don't
maybe you think it was probably seven
minutes yeah what part did you say
in the sketch i played okay so
don't miss
oh yeah the premise of the sketch
is that i'm ryan brown's biggest fan
right and i work at jimmy kimmel
and i and jimmy wants to fire
me this is so he had no
right to come into fire me said
it's i take it well yeah but
then i go crazy yes i have
seen this yeah i've never sued for
being seven minutes long
be live in two and a half
you fucking bow
i were leonard's laptop if that's running
tattoo it if it's closer to two
and a half than it is to
seven what will yeah what happens when
it happens i'll dip my toe in
the pool gives a shit let the
punishment fit the crime
you dipped your toe in that sketch
does the poll a good deal would
you dip your toe in you would
you hit that without would you hit
this pool it looks good to me
we thinks we should do one from
the pool
how can i find for an hour
which is new the fuckin hey get
all pruned up we should do one
from taps bathtub i wish some very
famous photo of the workmen yeah yeah
it was like for guys like comfortably
i would love to do that with
the two of you just do one
big job sick
huh watching nude but if we do
want in the shower
that's okay then what asian foods we
do an episode from the shower and
we we put on fancy suits oh
yeah like our fanciest clothes our fanciest
clothes oh my god what's with the
shower going that's so funny god you
guys would love it that's so funny
one time um did you see the
running time yet you're talking to me
i found an article about i'm trying
to
and a particle
from the old gray lady sketch a
real men performed jeff bezos washington post
i'm working on it people all right
did you want to tell your story
while you're when we phone him we
wanted to do multitask okay when i
wasn't um elementary school probably second grade
my friend and i decided we were
gonna swim in her stand-up shower that
had like a glass door you know
you start like a cartoon you could
fill it up wow so we put
a phone book over the um crack
what do you call it crack know
the part where the water goes down
the drain so yeah the drain so
little
and we've started fill it and it
started we've turned on the water and
we're just like soaking the phone and
then we got in trouble
how far up did it go ah
one millimeter
just made like a puddle in the
shower yeah but i really remember when
that phone book also i couldn't swim
so it was pretty bold thing to
be doing so anytime you call anyone
from that phone book would they sound
wet yeah they always thought soaking wet
weight did you oh do you remember
if your plan was to fill it
up to the top yeah we thought
we were going
to swim in it to the top
though not just so you could float
but to all the way all the
way up to the top to where
you would drown it i think i
think this has been removed from the
internet even though it was always their
scrabble entire life do you think ryan
reynolds had a screen i can't find
it yeah right ahead you slapped i'm
deadpool now i can't can't be out
funded
yeah i didn't like my wrong but
yeah hilarious woman i need men pro
partners like ah the selma hayek samuel
l jackson the rock was the moot
did we see that movie yes we
did unfortunately separate your wife's bodyguard right
here yes we did from this business
mr kirsten stop what you are you're
aware of the screen i was sitting
where you are
yeah yeah and you're you are the
screen so could you act it out
and we want an actor to this
oh it's just like yelling
i love that kind of comedy which
is like look ah what is comedy
is it screaming i'll do that yeah
sure no i think i've been there
article about it oh good we also
asked luka here which by the way
we watched luka my name cause we
were set to watch the green knight
and i had an accident with my
projector and so it was kind of
fun
gt up wag it so we went
my projector he was so embarrassed and
it's like it's not it happens to
every child so he decided to watch
something a little more low mate um
that didn't need a good picture by
the way we just watched the green
night and it would not have gone
over well known the backyard degree so
i'm glad we watched luca we had
a great time yeah okay and that
was a fun move
we watch a good backyard movie luka
video is now private private to jama
shy right to jimmy wasn't taking you
on friday city guillermo what was the
guy's army is it private
well we'll never know you guys until
i do think it was nine and
a half
just like those weeks minutes i spent
oh no i'm having sex with that
woman well you're safe from dipping your
toe in the pool this time
um wait what the fuck ah we're
talking here oh yeah are we talking
about luca luca luca operates house of
gucci operates on the same principle as
luca where it's italian people although no
it's not not notice an accent and
luke know they're not there but they
do occasionally throw in italian words yeah
yeah but house of goo
they are doing italian accents but they
also sometimes say italian words do you
float
j do you float in the pool
or you watched the movie did you
say a rebbe dare che yeah he
did
i let it slide this time we
watched it again we watched good burgers
loading in the pool one welcome to
a bigger home i bigger yes for
bigger bike for my nephew's birthday as
the movie guy and we and we'd
cover loading the pool and watch that
and it was a lot of fun
but that's mainly night should come back
this summer
are always welcome i love to come
to a movie night you you never
come i haven't yeah you've it's almost
as if you've had other stuff to
do you know don't want to do
it with the carpet and the bobby
cavett and the guy got gavin with
ya
around the damn easy yeah the eggs
and the milk and yea getting the
dentist goes in your mouth and he's
like whoop it up bottom lip
um so that's put it that's put
an end to paul's energy i'm just
i'm gathering now continue oh okay yes
i can't respond to these things i
need to gather my energy so i
can get past the wonderful i once
had a fight with ah with a
driver about bill cosby really
pro or con i was um against
um but i had a fight with
this man why well how would this
come up he was one of those
types people who just wanted to bring
up stuff that would just get you
like hot button topic was he like
hey what do you think about this
bill cosby going to jail like that
like he he was um a driver
on a film i was working on
transparency when you when you're when you
have
made made the leap from babysitting to
movie stars yes essentially when you're on
onset and needing to go from location
to location they will have drivers there
who drive you to and fro these
places because they too and fro they
first of all you should not be
expected to drive yourself but also they
don't trust you to drive yourself without
having an accident and then causing a
big insurance plan tell true do you
know
what is a quick sidebar i never
thought about this before but to and
fro is just an abbreviation of to
and from by one letter yeah it's
it's not faster though no yeah i
mean it same way tie me to
throw to and from timey to and
fro ma ma almost adds a syllable
we're ready to and from a whole
lot let me get my timer
okay alright ready lauren three two one
two and from ok point sixty six
oh six six six okay and so
you have to do at the same
pace okay three two one to and
fro i forgot to everest
yeah three two one to and fro
thirty six said yeah it's sure thirty
six seconds so much hour or much
faster i love that levy
let's try that let's try to get
sky yeah you don't need to start
with two and from two involve okay
three two one two and from fifty
six seconds your facet point fifty six
okay i keep saying okay
c smith doing
alright three two one to and fro
ah do it again
three to walk to and fro forty
forty forty yeah we love it we're
gonna time you know you're the one
who's skeptical years into and fro skeptic
i love this only amazing randi of
june fro i love our language and
how hard my love you to and
fro okay and love you so much
go to and from point seven five
seems like you were rushing them and
go to and fro i didn't stop
harder than you write right and go
to and fro i didn't do it
why do people keep pressing
this is just infotainment input and go
to and fro points out a new
debit boy seven
by so fast
point seven zero point seven blazing fast
and slow play we did point five
seven zero point seven zero yeah oh
it's just when we serve seven point
o seven i guess i was thinking
you know that doesn't make sense
she's as crawl your brain is making
her out anyway you did a great
job paul well what all this proves
is that to and fro is so
much faster and easier to say that
you're doing this why is anyone saying
two and five love it we lay
waste to and fro we love you
and desire deviation
those that aren't that chart but are
shorter well the famous jerry seinfeld one
was july to jewel ah well yeah
that one's famous permission i mean isn't
in the sense of he had a
big bit about june to jun zemlya
maybe that was the bathroom that might
have been the the bosh sunday
oh dude like how much these calendars
was like hi tom are you actually
saving you jan fab
oh i say i don't like jerry
seinfeld esper i sound like the guy
from ferris bueller yeah you sound like
allen right yeah doing norm ah yeah
peterson though there's an actor that i'm
thinking of okay yeah you asked a
question i answered it how much time
you actually saving my name is norm
peterson and i that sounds more like
god king of chicago
ego
the guise of you smile after you
said if you could be ferris bueller
for one day i'd party in that
parade but not that day that we
saw the movie oh it's different day
i didn't know what to do where
he actually goes to singing goes to
school
just dance fun yeah i'd probably have
sex with little girls yeah was he
nine hundred supposedly in school where he
was cool and know he was cool
and everyone loves the thing is he
was cool everywhere and he had no
problems isn't that a weird move and
i love ferris bueller well he but
he did have to get home before
he was dealing yeah but just got
a tight tight time his friends have
the problems he had no emotions
the problem that he had to get
over well he had one friend who
had problems and then amarin was the
girl that he has sex with sometimes
yeah but she he was pretend to
be her dad waiting outside of the
school that's a little weird but it
isn't it strange to have a movie
where a guy like the setup is
hey i'm cool and everyone likes me
and i want to do this thing
then he does it in the end
i'm sure there are
more examples of this well but it's
also the tension of is he going
to get caught early is downfall because
everywhere he goes it's like a thing
you shouldn't do well it's everyone's dream
to have a great day off yeah
that's so it's more go to the
senate better my fancy go to the
museum to see the american experience like
how about baby's day out i'm that
baby has been problems but fuckin crane
imo sits him
do you know what that baby knocked
off mr magoo yeah well we train
hit him no glasses ferris bueller has
no glasses he's mr mcgrew he's a
total mr mckew everyone who basically everyone
in ferris bueller by the way is
a total mistake everybody in the fast
far faster fast furious franchise there no
mister maybe they're all mr mccool many
people in the world
those cars like mr magoo my god
it's terrifying
contact lenses and one falls out are
you a mr magoo oh this is
a good question this is a trick
let's just call you if even if
you have contact lenses at all
you're mister magoo cause no glasses yeah
right ok wait we have a new
intern and he hasn't done anything yet
and i'm so which one is oh
satan oh yeah you would think maybe
he's busy
could he be check out our instagram
or knew our new yeah she hasn't
made a real post yet freedom usa
people voted but there was there was
bernard and then kimberley and the ambler
lee and then similarly voted overwhelmingly for
safe yeah it was pretty so busy
he's like tempting everyone all day every
day that's true
maybe he's too too he's out there
with chocolate cakes constantly going like hey
you also ask do you want something
i think you mean devil's food cake
abolition chavez chocolate k isn't it soon
you're not allowed to eat that i
want one i of course we all
want one but to eat one is
against god you know what devil's food
cake isn't offered enough no it's not
if they'll go double chocolate last time
hey not the same
nelson was my favorite growing up from
the box yes yeah yes yes yeah
i wanna make that shit restaurant roundup
by the way yeah when you are
serving like a big fancy dessert if
you didn't say it was sinful the
table was guaranteed to say it was
sinful oh this is sin are you
serious yeah every time one hundred percent
you were supposed to say
so here you're not sinful dessert know
you're not supposed to say that but
like when you would deliver it people
will go whoa and you gotta go
like yeah it's safe you didn't say
like if you were not like yeah
it's sinful isn't it people would go
this is sinful but now was that
phrase being used a lot of the
time or do you feel like ah
or was
this a religious restaurant
religious right right around huh yeah i
did work at a religious restaurant manifestation
we've never so first job we've never
talked about and say we have talked
about it briefly okay it was part
of the rounds that christian get into
it as much as i guess okay
let's try to have as many stories
move on christian yoga christian yogurt place
right right
yoga fired after six weeks religious yogurt
yeah ray well it had the yogurt
part of it this was nineteen eighty
five so yogurt was very very big
yeah like you know and yoghurt meaning
um yeah okay yes fro-yo so so
they were popping up everywhere and i
guess they were a relatively cheap way
to start a business and and with
a lot of like ah markup on
on how much you would spend and
rice so how much was a yoga
two dollars yeah it would be like
to back then it would be like
even a dollar fifty or whatever you
would probably spend twenty five cents on
on everything yeah that's that's a profit
so shark tank would like that and
people were like out the
door usually whatever the popular ones were
around so this guy said okay well
i'll start i'll start a frozen yogurt
business but he was so religious he
was part of our church and gave
me the job because my parents asked
him to write um but he was
so religious he couldn't fathom starting a
business without it being religious
like an having to appeal to christians
don't a lot of businesses have ah
bible verse quoted on the million dollar
bag like forever twenty one it would
say john three sixteen on the bag
that ever twenty nine jingle bible verse
i didn't know that that trend that
i've heard best transcends like rye is
that's absolutely ap
absolutely god so loved the world he
gave his only-begotten son yeah that whosoever
believeth in him should not perish but
have everlasting life it's good in any
content and then don't like to be
religious know put on forever twenty one
bags and you like throw those clothes
out in a week and they don't
because you're you'd turn twenty two yeah
well you should start going on your
twenty first birthday they last a year
a lot of people go on
our twenty first birthday like i got
to make this last yeah wow i
finally twenty one is what they should
have called it that's disgusting that's disgusting
anyway so he started this christian christian
yogurt place where it was like you
could go in and buy bibles away
it wasn't a franchise of an existing
place no no it was his own
creation okay what was it called the
manistee much like we are god's own
creation but what is manna stay shanna
from heaven is like a miracle that
happened a miracle as
in johnson said the israelites were wandering
through the desert at one point forty
years later god was like yeah so
here hey let's let's give him a
break i'm going to make food oh
yeah saying yogurt is like from heaven
he was saying like sustenance sustenance is
from heaven and come and get fed
it wasn't just yogurt too
who is like i think they had
some food items and you should never
do that and stuff like that should
never do that yeah she just made
yogurt place just maybe yogurt place or
food as well know it tarnish it
i mean it's like too much and
and i'm a prime example of that
where it was like anytime anyone had
to order anything other than yogurt he
was like how do i do this
stressful yeah
so things like wave grim boulay or
yeah shakes the last chateaubriand
turkish delight
turkish slight reminds me of um
but the lion the witch yeah water
and we used to watch that in
school and my drama class and we
would watch the pbx version of the
play oh yeah and then they had
the turkish slight and i always thought
that sounds good but then when you
see how to good to see turkish
delight you think they complain they complain
about it in the movie belfast which
by the way is really good i
can't wait to see it
yeah i was invited to the virtual
any movies that are so it looks
so that my to the last daughter
we watched code daughters great kota kota
the two we watch this week that
we really liked ricotta and but that's
what i wanna watch kota and i
don't even know anything about them but
i want i heard they're good yeah
to houston right where is kota available
to view
apple tv yeah plus were you fired
for bearing false witness against your neighbor
yes of course
i said that my neighbor fucked me
and that was false
you fucked him yes
now i go if i got fired
because ah well basically i i feel
like i've said this on the show
before but i hated doing windows that
was part of it the worst do
a windows like oh washing washing the
windows right what did you think you
meant like manning the drive fucking the
windows the trial okay whole yogurt shop
happen to you
to be well so i hated that
i hated like mopping the floor um
these are things that like i hated
at home too so it's not like
it was just hated it it worked
the worst part of jobs like that
i hated it retail when you had
to clean up yeah other space like
oh yeah like if hire someone else
to do the thing make that somebody's
job i'm here to do the
that's right the extremist but i cleaned
many people's homes so as a babysitter
i will say i was a fantastic
babysitter and that was part of the
job i love to clean you will
have to tidy i like to tywin
clean you a tidy write clean i
throw out only food i would do
a lot of things no no no
but when i when i say clean
the distill
ocean for me is like a strain
rag yeah doing when i show it
now i want be clean window for
die that's what i'm saying but i
would clean you tie up the space
you would tidy you will not ever
babysitter does that that's true at that
be no okay but admit that you
were tiny i was hiding
but sometimes we've done a killer she
ain't even safe so she can i
a counter she can wipe really good
wiping down the counter is cleaning i
think going i don't know i mean
hey okay anything next to a sink
that's that's not cleaning that's still out
of hiding because he has anything next
to a sink has to be why
wiped up you know what i mean
that's just part of lomas last time
you cleaned a toilet ah twenty minutes
before you got here
i take out the old you know
those scrub brushes that we get the
ones that self clean but i love
that one yeah yeah i don't know
this magical oh my god well kusa
from narnia i learned about yeah it's
july clean all the terms like coup
turkish delight toilet brush it's called lumi
toilet brushing it so it uses a
uv sir
sanitizing light said trump iowa man do
that too little poopy on there gets
dissolved by the light um and they're
always sold out let's see if they
revealed why why don't they shine and
this is only about two i have
three sites i like q three this
is akin to why don't they make
the whole plane out of the black
box but why don't they shine uv
light
it on everything so nothing is ever
dirty and agree the whole world my
new thing my newsday uv light just
show up what is filthy it sanitizes
it my new thing is is why
do you have to use coasters make
your table out of everything that the
coasters may yeah there was this on
something i don't know
but it drives me crazy coasters why
i do hate i hate roads i
hate rings do you know what what
about the lord of them
i have we have ah a nice
wooden dining table and one of my
great pleasures is to polish it every
week oh yeah buddy news pledge i
use some pledge would spray yeah yeah
i have something you could polish if
you were interested isn't a word yes
it is
oh my god can i just say
breastmilk stains everything is the weird lips
tested let me bring out my trying
to make me see i do a
bottle of breadsticks gusta and it leaks
over the side and there's and then
you put it down on i put
it on my wood floor there'll be
a white ring on the floor that
i will for
ever work with i have worked together
all over to stay in the ship
he loves it how's polishing searchable down
with breast milk and clean
not even yours or jamie's know people
just drop by
oh my god alright we have to
take a break huh
okay we're back and ah during the
break we heard something about the lumi
toilet brush lauren lauren this is earth-shattering
news and it almost feels like our
toilet correspondence but it's just part of
lawrence topic we have now debug
nct what i thought was true now
i it appears to toilet with gloomy
brush was available on amazon yeah bunking
toilet it appeared to me that let
me brush was available on amazon dot
com after clicking said link i found
that there is no lumi russian amazon
dot com now where is the link
to lumi their website does not seem
to exist anymore why always sold out
now all i see here is the
kickstarter for the lumi i don't take
this is a scam we could not
find it um i'm i'm extremely upset
asshole lumi thing how high up does
this go because one laser pointer on
a toilet brush and you fell for
it when kula talks about this odd
mark as his eyes i had to
get
at it now what i found was
stated whitehead no i like social media
they had no social media presence what
are you worried about there's four fingers
pointing back at her oh that's true
i'm looking at their kickstarters toilet brush
had no social media presence why zoe
what toilet brush doesn't have a social
media okay thousand dollar goal
and they've made seventy eight thousand five
oh and they are there but just
just calling it so were they selling
them as part of the kickstarter i
don't know but i know oh yeah
we got we have to i believe
yeah and i look at every week
and there's no germs
well you have to before you kick
it i get before i kick it
you don't want to get a ticket
wow click it or ticket guys that's
one thing this new year's eve by
the way kick it before the one
that's coming up again in eleven months
in ticket or clicking you get a
ticket make sure that you're safe out
there driving these because it's very ah
perilous out there sure is what was
covered we knows that'll be around in
eleven months but i mean this keebler
people here's what's happening and i've heard
this from a lot of people including
many friends of mine that i know
in real life people are getting the
booster and then they're freaking out behind
the wheel they're just going nuts they're
circling carved so far staring
we'll they're kicking the steering wheel like
they're punching trying to make the airbags
but people don't understand when you get
the booster you know they poke a
hole in your arm yeah or the
carbon gets in yeah if they don't
if they don't put the bandaid on
fast enough yeah suddenly covered whirlpool yeah
it's flagged for mississippi
marjorie taylor cream
you're just kidding where katie this is
satire we are but we're not a
comedy podcast know when your team should
we just write that info tainment no
this was tainment oh not in pho
got us we're good at this i
think we're great i'd say so guys
hi wow
sounds like had something you know we
mentioned i knew as soon as you
said like that was like yes nothing
yeah we speak we mentioned strippers earlier
triple gr yeah are you going to
be a stripper yeah here finally absolutely
good you're living the dream it's a
dream you're gonna live reach huh
huh if i went to a strip
club and then there was something pretty
ladies doing a dance than you did
which didn't buy it by the way
their title is going to i was
the person who gave you all the
money you absolutely were really why do
you think you weren't because coop thinks
that it was it was our house
person yeah that's going to see him
doing actually you know
oh you're right yeah that makes sense
to me yeah that's the thing he
would know i think you're right yeah
so then when you said you absolutely
were why did you say that i
absolutely want to share with you
i guess so
i still sort of think it was
you show me to be you corbyn
it could i know i could see
mark two maybe we both did yeah
i think you both that sounds reasonable
that's a compromise but i was going
to say if you came out next
i don't know what i would think
so next it's coed strip club where
it's like they don't even tell you
no one announces anything about it there
you think you're going to see pretty
ladies i do
and then i do and then you
come out
what scenario would this be what do
you mean i feel like a job
at a strip club but i think
that strip clubs either men or women
are they co-lead yeah easter monday ration
to somewhere to say should yeah we
should open it but they were saying
yeah they were excited that you were
a well-known man who wants to
brown man so they were like kidding
like besides you at the strip club
is say hey it's full of talks
look at that well-known man the way
people know about the real non man's
but it's got a weird body for
a stripper usually look like this guy
i think i'd be very fascinating okay
so here's so try to make it
happen a job i'm trying to do
a chris farley thing
here's something that that we were talking
about this summer in this very pool
with some people okay so was it
the thing that i was trying to
bring up now which was what was
which was what did you think i
mentioned super crabs as like a conversational
jumping yeah
well you're the king of i bring
something up it's to give you guys
top but yeah you just reminded me
of something okay so serious person
so like when when i went home
and my roommate knows i like it
we stay in the moment and there's
no looking back
and my roommate reminiscence a wham and
my second roommate ram anissa whom i've
talked to a ram and nasa
etc
ah rent ah hired a stripper thousand
and twenty one thousand six hundred thousand
five thousand twenty five thousand size bows
and i was to a moment i
liked it
tick thousand ticketek thousand tick tick tick
duh
say they hired a stripper i can't
remember why but she came and remember
why i got i can't remember whose
case why to see some today was
a tuesday so i think i think
two came over i can't remember and
then one was like my my party's
roommate was trying to go look who's
to around
um and party with this ah you
know after she was off the clock
and she's like oh yeah you know
i have another one i have to
get to this is my first experience
with this by the way oh i
have another one i have another show
i have to go get to but
it's five pm right now but i'm
gonna come back afterwards right yeah but
but maybe i'll come back afterwards is
like
oh yeah okay now that's a total
lie birdie it's a total lie in
it's align i have come to figure
out yeah that they give of like
you know as to not go oh
don't know what they want and then
they won't get hurt by you yes
exactly yeah exactly and how did you
come to figure out that this was
a lie by trial and error by
geh
older and smarter every time they said
that they never actually did come back
um which by the way we she
was a cashier at a place when
we were in there once and we
were so embarrassed that that that we
just kind of like and she was
the only cashier we couldn't go to
another line was just thinking she recognize
you i don't know that she recognized
us
but we were so embarrassed it was
bullies yeah we're over here i can't
believe they saw where the horny guys
were so we also buy things you'd
ever take back we kept a candle
in the window we look like losers
we put a yellow ribbon around the
tree in the yard and our next
but then i was talking to we
jerked off
i was talking to some women who
hired a male stripper okay and he
said he's gonna come back and it
said please vote yes practically i'm going
to come back he was like can
i come back later oh let's get
the fuck and he like gave him
the card it was like calm and
and got one of their numbers or
whatever and was like hey and was
texting like hey are you guys still
partying
can i come back and and basically
i'm still nude these women these women
were like done with him after three
men of course essentially riding on something
and you're like we got those so
i wonder if there's ever been a
female stripper who's come back to a
male party or some females have been
like yes please come back to a
male stripper i'm gonna say no to
the
first and most simply a second we're
losing luann ah de la supps on
real housewives of new york okay the
counter salary cap yeah she's brought up
a stripper that appeared to the party
that was shazam an add on and
which on another show and she was
a he was really good looking i
really like yeah yeah so she would
want him to come back um i
always go
to say because you said stripper gram
and will eventually get back to what
you want to talk about it reminded
me that in high school we had
this thing called valid grams and what
isn't let's try to guess oh oil
you would give kids value because the
valentine things you there were a couple
things that happened you could hire or
basic audioslave
well and you say who you want
to get into and you would pay
and that sounds like me then you
would either deliver a shitty delivers which
is a shame yeah no they would
just come in and you get handed
out all your lollipops that you got
i hate you and a yea i
know but you kind of like it
too you know going wow wow yeah
if you're well liked but i were
just remembered that
there was also this um love quiz
you could take and they would tell
you who your best match was at
school yeah list like our lives were
like oh my god not that guy
or whatever you know like that's very
weird that shouldn't be something that is
i can understand the school trying to
raise money so doing the the first
thing but the second thing is strange
old
were you i was probably seventeen
still not good i wish i had
that paper i bet i do somewhere
i always save every i wonder if
you could look them up now maybe
they would be good matches for actually
mike was on my list huh hello
yeah paul tell us about your stripper
yeah what do you say when i
worked on kelsey grammer resents the sketch
show in two thousand and four drop
the peak awesome it's more accurate ah
there was this very nice young lady
who was what was her job she'd
like our scriptures judge judy
very nice young lady judge judy lost
her job she was presiding over us
by the way dude over the sketchy
have you guys seen hot bench high
bench hot benches crazy what's that it's
steve hurry no it's a quarter with
three judges hot passion and i can't
figure out why there's three judges that
will make it a hot bench i
don't know why luke calls mass movement
but it was and is
it's like a sort of daytime tv
show or a nighttime to stay time
and it doesn't you're pitching know it
was on and we were trying to
reach her cool off and we're trying
to figure it out because because we
got ben we got dropped in you
know five minutes into it so the
premise was already explained and then we
were watching and were like why or
why is this judge talking now why
are there three judges ice like one
one
basically like decided we thought and then
two more got to talk so we're
trying to fit and then why is
it called hot bench we couldn't figure
it out and then we got have
something to do we never saw the
right options how this many popular court
shows are on tv how can the
genre improve how about using a three
judge panel that's the concept of hot
bench created by judge judy scheindlin
after hearing each case the judges discuss
it amongst themselves before rendering a verdict
the jurists but are not civil litigator
blah blah but they should have that
in real life considering how bad some
of these judges are out there can
you imagine three judges trying to come
to some sort of consensus if it
wasn't for money what when they get
money well i mean the
ones on tv get paid wow am
i right i'm i'm sorry so it's
like worth it to them to not
just roll over sometimes be like i
don't fucking give judges should be two
people judges should be two people i
always say what about stripper grams so
this young lady by the way hot
bench how much we were three-tier today
we were gonna have an idea how
to do it
okay good we were confused by it
we didn't know what it was and
then we watched i don't know if
you guys watch how to john wilson
great see i love that shows their
season there were in the middle of
the second show and one i loved
it and ah we were watching this
week and ah suddenly he pops up
on hot bench what
it's like we're like hotbeds it was
the most perfect we just found out
about it a day before we were
so used by how to they showed
that things from they showed him in
the past being on hot pinch created
no i don't want to spoil the
time okay so this young lady ah
who is a very um fine young
lady she was a fine young business
young lady was a fun young lady
she's a very foolishly she was kind
of like i had a sort of
meek quiet demeanor like she was she
was very nice but she was you
know sort of like you you you
could say she was like bookish you
know what i mean she did not
look like somebody's low ponytail but if
she were to take off those glasses
and shake her hair out
yeah she'd be even uglier she was
just lovely young lady but she was
not somebody that you would think let's
hire a stripper for her but it
was her birthday one day and so
after work they it just happened to
be your birthday one day well that
happens everyone just happened it's crazy
that's seen some of the crew hired
a stripper for her and so we
were in the canteen of the studio
and everyone who do have it canned
meaning a bar or something in in
england like it's like a cafeteria kind
oh yeah and they only have drinks
there to for after hours yeah we
should lie it's fucking great so if
i serve
have drinks during the show would you
guys drink yes i want yeah why
would i know are you going to
do this good alright
for the next episode i mean i
think that's what's been missing guys pretty
sure so they hired the stripper and
she has to of course sit on
a chair while this guy grinds honor
and everybody's like oooh nice
mortifying at work you could tell she
was like trying to be game about
it but was neither would would prefer
this wasn't happening the guy went on
for so long and it got so
raw raunchy you could feel it go
out of the room like whatever sort
of high jinks people were enjoying kelsey
grammer come up on stage to be
like oh
right this is enough he could not
have been further away physically yeah i
think i'm sure i've told you this
that he can always very far away
he came to london for the pilot
and he always tried to be on
the exact opposite end of the earth
hand he did um he came to
london he was in the pilot and
then when the series got picked up
we went
just got a telegram that said fuck
this
not even that we went to london
and we lived there for a couple
months and then when we came back
the day after we flew back the
morning after we flew back transatlantic flight
next day have to get up at
six it was like a seven am
call to shoot sketches with kelsey some
of which we'd already shot without him
like with one of us playing oh
right because they couldn't decide which ones
kelsey was going to be when buddy
whatever he would spark oh yea i
want to be in this if this
one speaks to our place her arson
i think this i like this one
where i'm lying down in the bed
that's the dream i always love wages
at the end of your story that
was the story it was just got
really okay it was grim to watch
it it was really bad yeah like
the tv show grimm it was like
this guy was like a fairytale it
was one else rich german it was
wonderful what of prince charming became prince
charmless
this is like a twilight zone once
upon a time meets twilight zone this
is a show and i was trying
to do like a dateline meet stateline
of course yeah but why did he
get so raunchy and for how long
till of dateline know my wife does
do you love love love i don't
watch it i enjoyed it oh that's
the guy i was imitating for dateline
guy why
why would you smile yeah right the
way the other guy haired guy yeah
no keith morrison no not me keith
morrison the oh yeah morrow john quinonez
no no no not maybe not oh
it's one of the mankiewicz um what
but why that guy who's a boy
but why is it something yeah no
i can't picture you know that's that's
exactly what using my name popped in
my head my wife went out to
dinner with him when josh mankiewicz yes
i've heard should go out to she's
a big fan she and our friend
casey started talking to him online like
joking back you told us that he's
like let's we're gonna go out to
dinner there
i went to jar hey let's go
get a lovely dinner that's the kind
of set the pandemic is stealing from
us yes i would be going to
jar every night with a different ideal
with jai and goods twenty times i
have coping
i have coffee look by the way
if if you've seen the the video
of the police woman giving her like
superior officer a lap dance at a
party it's also very vital she like
got disciplined for it she like well
i thought it was a party and
and but it's just mortifying to ever
have stricto ranged to ever have a
strip that you
and just don't do that no put
it in somebody's house put it in
somebody's house and no one can report
it alright we have to take a
break but why
a and guess what everybody get out
your champagne and your party poppers because
in your paper and your regular yeah
yeah imo metroparks because his side to
relax rectum and we're gonna do a
three ch are everybody's favorite yeah
this feature was submitted to us by
a tv show called hotbed judge judy
scheindlin here's our technically here's how it's
going to be one person will be
the ah the the plaintiff and to
defend it
the other two people will be three
judges now one person has one judge
and the other person is two judges
that don't agree with each other i
love okay and we're going to go
clockwise with it right oh yes as
we always do so yeah paul doesn't
like clockwise i do but i i
i feel like i can't it's someone
grantham blocked in the air and then
when i looked down here i lose
it it's own grammy now from playing
clock on the floor every every board
game little mind is happening to me
every board game when you're young is
clockwise so it's like i don't even
think to suggest counterclockwise anymore it's just
like oh clockwise but do you know
why don't you say go to the
lab was five i think
saying clockwise is really confusing when you're
a kid i remember when i didn't
know how to tell time do you
oh yes any daily and i share
a thing that we did not learn
how to knit both of us did
not learn how to tell time until
we were in seventh grade oh that's
pretty late i think i was in
it it was terrifying maybe no second
or third grade i think this is
back when there there were clock
x there was nothing about claw yeah
clocks so you would just drop into
a circle with your left in damon
i did not know how to do
the math of the clock yeah and
it's not easy tried to teach me
and i just couldn't get it i
think i would get anxious about it
and i couldn't get it and then
for seventh and when i was in
seventh grade for christmas my mom got
me a watch and i looked at
an instant
can delta whoa just already like together
it just was like it was a
magical show somebody threw a boomerang at
me in the face and then it
hit me in the face again that
was back to your way around the
world to go back to the guy's
throat exactly instead it went around the
world him how long did it take
twenty four hours oh and you
just stood there you've moved as fast
as i thought i was looking around
to see who did it yeah for
twenty or so son desperately does the
sun move does the sun rotate oh
my god i don't i don't mean
it's the sun moving around us i'm
saying yes we're all moving around the
sun but does the sun actually rotate
yes when you look up in the
sky at night and it's white that's
the cool side of the sun why
don't you stare at god
don says stupid shit
alright so who's gonna do what on
this person alright i'll be you guys
be the judges although the plaintiff and
the defendant okay in which which okay
now you judges you one of the
you have to give me you so
scott and lauren you each have to
give me yeah ah something that the
plaintiff is plain to think about and
why the defendant
and okay ok defensive got it okay
so the plaintiff so you are you
going to be the two judges and
i'll be the one sure okay the
plaintiff is um oh but you give
that then okay
please all rise please please all rise
please i'm rising i'm rising whoa i
don't want arise but you don't have
to dear you're the judge you don't
have to week we get to just
sit our faxes right here on the
bench when i decided to talk one
judge didn't want to
arise but the other one do yeah
that should i get onto i'm still
mad at you by the way show
oh okay hi sir yeah you are
the plaintiff i am the point if
that's correct and it says i made
a funny yeah we don't address the
bench until as your own right very
good so sir you're the plane to
wait the other two didn't williams that
means i can't do it i
i would prefer if you didn't but
i like that you did or majority
rule
so you could see what i have
to put up with so i can't
but so mister rogers are you the
famous mister rogers know i'm alive can
you see him judge i'm aaron rodger
you're not you are wearing a sweater
though instead of a secluded here i
think it's nice
you don't have to disagree on everything
okay just because you're the the plaintiff
to find like the sweater i don't
and you don't have to disagree on
everything either okay not okay just
okay anyway so it says here mister
rogers that you're suing the defendant mister
mcfeely
no relation
you are a mailman though yes but
still you're suing him for not delivering
your mail and your mail specifically that's
correct he would go to other houses
i would see him do it through
my window i look at my window
all day long and i would see
him go deliver mail to the other
houses and not to my house okay
now i must be getting mailed bills
and anything oh
okay and what is this what kind
of wreckage upon your life is this
well my services keep getting shut off
services what services what do you mean
gas electric water this is very bad
this is really bad i actually agree
your owners if i may know we
haven't gotten to you mister mcfeely haha
you fucking asshole were
still talking to me rogers here jack
tion with the john gerald wrote no
so mister rogers why would you have
any evidence that you were not receiving
mail yes i have not received mail
oh yeah it sounds open and shut
to me can you show us how
you haven't received a proven are gonna
yes ah so exhibit a i've brought
my mailbox as you could see it
as empty wo is not a thing
inside and that's crazy let me drop
to drink when when he blows through
that see if there's a
oh and the bear came back and
hit me under the side it certainly
is empty weight but one little piece
of mail fellow what i told you
for me was what the fuck
let's open this up and read and
read what it says mister rogers alright
yeah i'm i'm unaccustomed to public speaking
so just know that that's okay well
do you realize cameras have been on
you this tiny what this judge has
a magnifying glass you could use your
oh thank you oh thank you very
much your honor why do you have
a magnifying glasses a hat okamoto
to read does my man everything have
you seen emily and paris emma lee
and belly yes i like the first
season but that might just been because
of carbon
okay we're not talking to mister mcfeely
feel left out three the letters alright
here it is here it is dear
cheese i love you i love the
idea of you i want you to
be in my tummy tummy tummy you're
all i dream about all day long
my favorite food no my reason for
living please please please choose
is cheese cheese come and be inside
me so i can be the happiest
little misty mouse in the whole wicked
world love me alright mister mouse come
up to the bench please approach the
bench scuttle scuttle scuttle did you write
this to mister rogers or to the
concept of cheese i wrote it to
the cheese so your honour therefore
does not my mail i have not
received my mail i'm suing you me
this is a prison suit with your
suit this is inception suit doesn't cheese
live inside your house i mean i
have cheese in my house she's you
have in your house mister rogers have
forty pounds forty pounds is that a
lie
checked over rules since guys know hey
that doesn't mean i would deserve male
wow why do you have so much
cheese mister rogers in case people come
over how what when are people coming
over to ya how often do you
have people coming over to europe well
people coming over all the time these
other people in my neighborhoods okay so
like name name that people coming i
don't know they're there like the
people that i meet when i'm walking
down the street sure there's the people
that i seen each day yes like
the mail carrier the mail carriers a
person in my neighborhood has he in
my neighborhood has he ever come my
neighborhood has he ever come by to
one of your parties
oh i has he ever left you
something like a gift at one of
these parties that you have you thought
it was a gift i um
i'm ashamed to say i've never invited
mister mcfeely to one of my parties
oh why is that sir can i
talk now alright mister mcfeely approach the
bench thank you runners mouse listen wow
did the mouse get next to us
i thought the mouse judge waring road
little doge
code is a weak on okays kid
i'll allow it or allow it i'm
hungry so your honors i wasn't trying
to not deliver his mail what happened
he would get mail right right and
my job is to deliver it right
we're with you so far i haven't
gotten to speak enough for yolngu you're
one of the judges
he put a hole on his mail
six years ago and he never took
it off he put a hole on
his mail behold a whole you according
to love super fan you hear what
you wanna hear it gets so yeah
how am i gonna live through this
yeah he got his mail held and
he never took the hold off
sarah mister rogers stand up
that happening
exciting old-timer you say i'm not very
tall you're standing really yes this is
as tall as i get really you
wait you're not still growing i am
technically still if i were to invite
you back here in a year you
would not be taller oh no i'll
come back in a year i'll definitely
come back time passes one year goes
by alright
yeah doctor
hey per may john chow dog sep
oct nov deaths j jad alright next
up on the docket is ah mister
rogers for a visit yeah yeah i
just wanted to check back in with
you i remember you yeah seven
fat talk yes i had a spurt
and oh you are so tall yeah
you're like a giant now you're like
a regular dicamba matomo oh no i'm
not what's up with your finger
hey remember a year ago when we
won that lawsuit and we awarded you
with um eight hundred pieces of mail
yeah i remember was ah january sixth
um and then that later that day
i just see some sites here in
the capital oh no you're one of
those
ezee alright i know i think i
think the judge is really thinking
i think that might be it certainly
isn't time for more well we'll probably
play that again will definitely play like
wow that was not banned gente centralist
by judge judy scheindlin twenty twenty two
is gonna be amazing oh my god
guys we want to thank you for
listening ah was as we mentioned before
go to that instagram
ram wherever it is i don't even
follow it but you guys should you
love the family room know i've i've
a very specific social media rule which
is i follow whatever accounts when the
when you sign up for one of
the social media accounts says can we
find out who in your mailbox has
one right and then i follow those
people and i never added anyone
else really because otherwise i'll just spend
all day reading every single person i
knows social media so i'm not taking
on any more new titter titter claims
god why it's well i'm not taking
any new twitter clients i'm very sorry
if you want to be one of
my clients i'm all full up i'm
obsessed with however i don't know if
this
social media by the time that i
sign up for it that's my own
advice day but um three m usa
go follow it right um three to
me you say on twitter where nothing
happens and three mio say gmail dot
com if you would like to send
us a three cheer like yeah judge
judy did judge judy thank you so
much and then also if you want
to hear this show ad free
every week the day it comes out
you can do that either on stitcher
premium or at cb world dot com
and if you never have please do
check out leslie ugh search leslie algoma
zuloaga june is busting out all over
you'll have enough and then patti labelle
is as well yeah what song did
she do it was a christmas song
this christmas i think this christmas
yeah yeah yeah yeah but search out
both of those have a last she's
still crushes it even while she's saying
yes yeah i can wear my backups
and she's got this grey is she's
great at it also check out that
video of that guy singing along with
thank you for being a friend the
golden girls theme sigh yeah why not
check out ryan reynolds in learn laugh
guests
doing a two and a half mad
private video videos at least we're talking
to jimmy right if you can hack
into that if you can if you
can believe it it was at least
six minutes jimmy watch your video tell
us how long it was i mean
we know you're listening oh jimmy you
come to me on my daughter's wedding
you watch you make a video pray
these
tell me like the philosophy
what are you house of gucci it's
the house of gucci i gotta go
oh okay bye
uh