three
yeah
nah wow scott honey are you sure
you're okay you sound like a goblin
i got a piercing headache right as
we pressed record oh no it's a
symptom from the recording you have recording
sickness
when you record for tools like the
benz
yeah it's already podcast burial jimmy graham
yes benjamin grimm it's covered time my
dogs are both h and j lo
time
yeah dr markarian doesn't work all day
yeah
hi everyone welcome to freedom the show
where we say hi to everyone and
i'm paul and i say hi everyone
my name is laura and i say
hello to everyone oh mix it up
do and what i want i'm a
crazy bitch
thank god you sell it and take
it as ninety however many episodes into
hey come on all three matches were
all crazy
that's another nickname for us the crazy
bitches then three two boys to presto
gang the crazy crazy i don't know
that i like this one we have
already talked about how we are recording
some of these episodes and advance yeah
so this will come as no surprise
when ah the sounds very late but
the noma is on sale okay the
gnome is on sale it's a dollar
fee
she's with the gnome was on sale
a month ago if you may essay
and you're listening to this go get
yourself a gnome if you don't know
about this it means you don't follow
the freedom account and you need to
follow the freedom account but it is
on sale for a dollar fifty off
that's fifteen percent off and i did
a poll in the stories asking if
people are going to buy the gnome
now that it's on sale and let
me tell you okay sure sixty one
percent said no i am dumb sure
sixty one percent said that thirty nine
percent said i will buy it but
you know what that is that's actually
pretty good numbers that's twelve hundred people
who said that they would buy their
ny can i make a confession yeah
i said i would
buy it but i'm never going to
buy that thing i just want to
see the real liability and i want
eight hundred and ninety nine times sky
to your gerrymandering you have so many
instagram accounts
that there's anything wrong with it
ah well i really want to sell
out the gnomes so that target sees
our power and that they feel our
strength our purchasing power yeah we're just
like add to cart essentially yes yes
add to cart has changed lions it's
really thinking with add to cart yeah
i recently was recommended on add to
cart
some charcoal toothpaste and i and and
i asked the question my wife and
i me and my wife both asked
the question does it taste like charcoal
and the host of the show one
of the hosts of the show said
niche one just tastes put em on
blast i'm not gonna put out a
lot and let me tell you something
i order that jungle and it tastes
like fuck
even charcoal that's so gross so we're
like the anti add to cart were
removed from cart but here's the thing
it's very effective it is effective like
i've noticed this is a podcast where
we listened to add to cart and
talk shit about the things that they
want us to buy and we supply
them which i also did on add
to cart raw so yeah i learn
so
it tastes bad but it works tell
me it's it's a whitening toothpaste and
light it's black how can it wait
i know it's it's a conundrum as
it's a toothpaste conundrum to my caught
on drum i know do another two
boys conundrum but it really it really
does it has made a difference then
i heard
that is actually dentist do not recommend
to use charcoal toothpastes so i figure
i'm going to use it until my
upcoming dental appointment next month and then
pretend i haven't been using it
is this your dentist pride because you
want to know just to be proud
of you and how white your teeth
i need the dentist to be proud
i look i really did not i
did the the minimum dental care during
quarantine so did i and by the
way i went for the first time
and almost two years because of quarantine
yeah and i was just like alright
let's do this what's going on
and they have tooth cancer they definitely
is everything and they're like alright good
to go by no see i i
always go every six months sometimes even
more frequently y mucho even during quarantine
i i just i took the chance
and dentists because i chose to change
but because i already had my eyes
open there
my mouth is open there yeah i
know that's it's pretty nice yeah that's
the place to get it that's the
big that's the biggest place you can
get it is when your mouth is
open i know but in the little
cove perhaps can get there with pregnancy
my gums have gotten very inflamed which
is a such a common thing that
happens but really and it when they
hurt or or
sting they're like just big they go
down there earlier than typical you know
i usually have healthy gums or just
like a little more other they're thinner
they like going between my teeth morning
aggie should be higher up but to
most other proceeding yes and other they're
like going down d yeah they're like
almost covering your entire teeth yeah like
oh my whole teeth are just pink
and then as mike like that yeah
he loves that comey blow job and
yesterday i was getting at
oh thanks scott when she cleaned my
teeth with this with this affliction
it hurts so fucking bad it was
crazy yeah it was horrible and then
she told me i should be pushing
my gums with this little gum pusher
tool no i don't like using because
it whoa of course well the one
i was trying to post a floss
to to where it does hurt because
that's what activates the gums i know
but i it's like it's gone to
pay
painful yeah we're talking about you're not
supposed to just floss to get rid
of food in between you need to
go up but taste wow up and
into the gum and try to like
make it hurt almost no data it
activates the gums no i agree i
really feel like i've lost i lost
a lot because ever since i didn't
invisalign looking for additional description
of this episode by the way
well i used to not really know
us and then once i didn't fizzle
and you have to floss invisalign or
it's really gross right and so i
was flossing all the time and now
it's a habit but i really hate
it when you actually get up in
between the gums how they do it
to the dentist oh and so i
literally i don't know why i like
it but it hurts but you kind
of like it
one of those deals yeah yeah like
well it's kinda like how you love
being spanked in
only in bed
so my god what's being spanked in
bed sky you gotta listen to add
to
ah talk about that high end car
wow what a cool i've just made
shit up about your add to cart
never came she didn't feel everything spanked
but she did say this a nearly
things i refuse to do that scott
wants me to do looks get seen
yeah yeah um when when you said
we had a lot to talk about
laura and this is it nones and
i'll tell ya that no
that's the main thing yeah we had
a ton to get into the gnomes
when we think flossing gnomes ah flossing
flossing nones yeah yes that's it so
say yeah right before we start the
show lowers like we got a lot
to talk about yeah lost immediately into
the gnomes which lead us i thought
the gnomes might be a bigger topic
for you guys
want to move on
since then that happened months ago when
this drops
the thing hey you bought oh my
god everyone shut
well one of my fears about the
gnome is that people aren't going to
buy it because it says it needs
to be shipped with a thirty five
dollar order because it's you know i
don't know why is it less than
thirty five dollars i find that hard
to believe that gnome is eight fifty
that's very reasonable is that the sale
price or is that regulates the sale
price ten dollars is regular and they
also had nine
they have a nine incher now good
for you guys oh but not on
the do on the website description it
says you could choose between seven feet
and nine feet they used the wrong
indicator oh i love it so much
a lot the word feet right they
just know a good yeah with if
i had a seven foot fucking huge
nome with just ahead
in my yard oh my god i
actually think you would buy something like
yeah i would be more inclined to
buy it then yeah seven feet that's
really an event
i'd invite people over yeah for the
unveiling got huge know right yeah exactly
yeah that was the sound of the
cape being pulled i'd hire a publicist
yeah that'd be great for one month
only just exactly like this one thing
around my neighborhood
wonderful public if you could hire a
publicist and say i don't want you
to go to media outlets i just
want you to tell everyone in my
neighborhood some yes would you go door
to door would they do it by
feel like we need them i don't
know i mean for that money or
expensive yeah exactly exactly they are nana
dua there to do
ooh ah hornpipe if i ask him
to for that money hey i do
have i tell him me do what
have you hired a publicist to spin
a sign in front of your house
to promote your projects that sounds great
this is a very targeted approach
um i did want to ah i
didn't choose this guy's ministers yes oh
god topics yeah um i want to
tell you the harrowing story of saturday
oh my god we have to hear
the whole story so right the hfs
let's hear it yeah tell us from
the begin
and okay leave out a single detail
but like i told about the ami's
i mean just give the the headline
this is the story of one of
our dogs escaping and being missing so
trigger warning for people who have dead
dogs t w colon okay so ah
saturday the medallion the dozen very happy
and a sad ending you happy but
it's origins reveal his true feelings about
the dog something has a happy ending
i mean sad
sad when duh yeah to the dog
okay ga by the way would bark
at paul every morning as if he
was a new guy because less and
less but that last day she still
got a couple in yeah my dog
does not like men it takes her
more time georgia to to what sam
my dog but i
one last night um because he came
over in georgia was barking at him
too and i was like it's just
all men you know you know it's
yeah not all men's and not all
know yeah but um but like i
don't know like what was it
like what is it about is it
their full you know hatred it's weird
because wilks appeal of masks on now
so looks like it's another level of
it where i'm like there's something happening
but she's had like the other day
i had to have somebody come into
my house to set up some equipment
for a livestream thing and she did
not like this guy i mean it
was like it was more
than i've seen her go crazy at
anyone like she was going for something
she didn't like disk yeah couldn't even
couldn't even hear what he was saying
she was barking so much right in
my ear as we were opening the
door and so i had to lock
her up much like hillary lock her
up yeah i know what did you
were you holding the dog is that
why she was she
with her no i mean she was
just right behind around feel high but
the but the barks were piercing and
the guy was like she commits a
fine you know and i was like
she i was like she does all
time lie she literally hates you i
always feel embarrassed if anyone comes over
to fix something or you know directv
or whatever and the dog
dogs are barking and i would say
not ninety percent of the time they're
so nice about it they're like oh
i'm used to it yeah what must
be done a crazy and engage with
the dog if i if it were
me i would be like look that
dog up before i get in here
i think with dogs you just have
to ignore them for the most part
unless they're particularly gnarly vicious okay so
tell us what hap i would
please no please no no no before
before before but i just i just
i like like around my neighborhood there's
a lot of dogs and even if
they're barking at me i like to
see them do you know what i
mean like if they're behind a fence
and they're just going crazy i think
it's kind of cute that they're like
defending their homes yeah anyway good so
so what's so to do okay so
there we we found there is a
gap in between our backyard fence and
the neighbor's backyard well that's convenient for
shopping
you're like barbara streisand it's more of
a baby gap yes the barbara streisand
thing is so crazy have we talked
about she has like a mall in
her basement shout em all interfaces isn't
well it's like it's like she wasn't
basemap a mall but it's not really
a that at that point it's not
a basement if you have a mall
do you know what i think we
talked about this ten hour
ten hundred years ago to go yeah
but it was when i went to
versailles they said marie antoinette also had
the same kind of was a marie-antoinette
have the same kind of thing where
branching out and take your age yeah
she had a fake so people would
act weird around her so that she
could just stroll through and everyone was
told to ignore her and that's the
same thing that barbra streisand had and
the like
that is actually crazier like it's like
i'd be thinking everyone here is pretending
they don't see me how often did
barbara streisand go to the mall before
she got famous and did she have
to buy things there in the mall
in her house and was she like
digging for change out of her purse
going oh she just like your things
orange yeah it's been real
the these are real questions that we'd
never do she like i've never seen
her do they ring stuff up and
go that'll be eleven eighty three and
then she just points at her face
and goes come on she's like i
own the small i own you
do you think she has play money
nice yeah it's a plastic coin just
go through like a whole charade she
uses mcdonalds money yeah and they'll give
her mcdonald's food instead of clothes no
matter what restaurant or yeah that's your
mistake oh yeah she does have a
food court did her mall yes she
can just stay
can they just leave donald de na
julius
hot dog on a stick i like
to watch them make the stuff it's
fun i looked it up yes um
so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes
so there's ah there's a gap in
the gate and ah hey we gotta
wish it was like god it's like
you love holos
lacoste
there was a cost in the game
but two lacrosse sweaters and canada the
first time i ever went up there
and i thought they were french and
i did drive back they only sell
this year and i told you i
was i was stopped at the border
and interrogated when i was going up
there because i was i was proposing
to cool up and i bought two
lacoste why they interrogate just wanting and
i was
coming back down and i was freaking
out again because i had just been
interrogated and they were doing the routine
questions and it was like did you
buy anything while you were here and
i was like two sweaters yeah and
the guy goes get out of here
ah good tip if you're trying to
smuggle stuff across the border
just say two sweaters so sweaters sweater
so a lot of ah when i
was in high school i always would
go to this thrift store for a
lot of my clothes and you could
get lacoste polos and a little boys
section and they were so cool
when i was young twelve lacrosse that's
when the lacoste started it's sort of
thing and it was super popular and
everyone had everyone in my school dress
like a preppy with lacoste t-shirts are
not t-shirts i guess but pelosi with
it with a the collars turned up
and all that kind of stuff and
so when i
went to new york for my first
big like family trip there was a
guy selling a white lacoste sweater on
a street corner and i think it
was five dollars and i had like
maybe ten dollars that my parents had
given me to spend in new york
and i i spent the five dollars
on this white they gave you a
ten to spend to do your good
luck i mean they went to
tiny paper my food and everything else
we were doing they're just like little
samurai money yeah so i spoke in
a pet so i spent five of
it on this white lacoste sweater and
i think it was a fake to
um oh you think the thing they
were selling on the street was a
fake
making the cost for five dollars was
not real i don't think cos just
had too much they didn't even have
room in their store and they like
go out on the street and sell
stuff
and so i was in shop class
would work working class and i wore
it and the teachers are you sure
you want to wear that white sweater
in woodworking class and some guy had
a brush paintbrush full of stain and
no and got it on the sweater
on purpose yeah it was the first
day all the
not no not on purpose oh right
still the first day where he just
bowed he bumped into me and so
and we tried to bleach and we
tried i mean you were like this
was five dollars five of my dollars
i shit on my shoe i took
woodworking in high school and it was
so ah weird that i did that
i should have taken
oh man yeah it was the biggest
waste of time like i don't we
had to take woodworking metal shop and
drafting and well i should tell back
to we had to make like pancakes
and shit yeah that was crazy i
wish that i'd been offered in my
school i don't think we had a
whole mk program there was like a
um ah it was called
vo tech vocational technical training where it
was like that was working in cars
and stuff like that and but that
was like a whole other world in
my right like that was yeah everybody
together and you know there is an
auto thing at my school too and
i didn't know where that was either
and it was very mysterious but for
us it was a simp
the choice you could either take homesick
or wood shop classes like hey there
man so you are yeoman bolton for
a guy to take home ek right
of course like if you had taken
homework you you would have been made
fun of you know media or email
you learned how to do like woodshop
and like never use any of those
exact any of it and i failed
metal shop
i think it was like why would
you be good at that report card
i was like i don't give a
shit about this but it was a
big problem with my dad they should
just i mean that's just crafting they
should make everybody take home heck yeah
that's that's because you'll you will girls
unless you unless you're like hey i
really am interested in a vocation of
of shock yes exactly
you know what i mean yeah like
and and there should be barely anyone
who signs up for that i want
to take us a sewing class i
don't know how to sew a button
oh actually i showed her i said
hello i i did a pillow when
i was in fifth grade aw i
made i made a pair of pants
when i was in fifth grade my
friend's house can i wear how to
sew no buttons obviously
yeah they were elastic waist pajama pants
i can sew buttons i can do
like emergency so you should i think
if you're with honestly with your fashion
lifestyle you need to know how to
sew but you need to know campus
to true girl when it with me
i'm like i don't even iron i
just put water on the wrinkles and
let it dry it works i can
rip out rank
yeah exactly i do that and honestly
it works
i got all the shit i got
a steamer i had a seamer i
left on the side of a road
i was like i'm never going to
use this fuck on the side of
the road like after you bought it
what am i doing
and i was like i've never used
this and i just put it on
the street and of course somebody on
the street people like when you put
something on the street because they take
it right away but um i i
use the steamer not not a lot
but when i do it's very handy
like to just like steam out some
wrinkles of a suit that i haven't
worn a while um and i
also use it to clean ah some
of my hats well on an add
to cart casi st onge i think
it's ac case norway she had ah
she talks about a product that was
this is an add to cart recap
podcast that's okay well we know we're
going to talk about why the product
is bad this is removed from current
this is
exactly yeah this this was a a
basically a dummy of a body it's
an inflatable man's upper torso and you
put the shirt are dummy and it
like inflates and like steam's it so
that it is perfect and then you
can take it in the carpool lane
yeah and you can do a lot
with
with it too i remember her talking
about that and i absolutely could not
picture it in like yeah i'll had
to look it up yeah it's weird
and it was also the one who
recommended that toothbrush that i rejected that
that's the toothbrush size up the iconic
one but yeah i haven't haven't opened
yet okay you need to try and
tell me what this is because everyone
like they
i'm talking about how their teeth feel
like la yes glass like glue up
and suit channeling to feel like he's
like like they're ah i don't know
steel i want my teeth to feel
like sandpaper
i want my teeth to feel like
that shaggy capa to show i do
i make you horny
okay so the dog got out there
was a gap in the
ah
beps
well anyway it was about ten minutes
or so i was oh here's here's
the bit of background that um maybe
it'll be interest um i had taken
the shingles vaccine the day before and
my my doctor said you're gonna want
to stay at home take it easy
answers yeah yeah yeah because you may
may get ah you know some pretty
severe symptoms and i talked to you
paul and you were like i didn't
get any symptoms and i talked to
my reminder i had shingles horrible around
yeah so you have symptoms i talked
to my mom and she had horrible
symptoms for like three days so i
was like expecting something in there from
the week aquaman jesus right if you
have had shing
eagles you can or cannot get the
vaccine question i'm not a doctor i
think that you can because i think
that the it's like a thing that
you get every ten years a year
yeah yeah yeah so if you had
shingles well this i don't even want
to speculate you're somebody that spent ten
years ago you're probably
good but i don't know but i
wanna look at it because you can
get shingles three times relax yeah i
think it's kind of like like asking
a question from a phoenix on a
bridge yeah guys i don't know what
is it a troll under a bridge
while there's a troll under a bridge
but isn't there someone on top of
actually i just yeah china trying to
pass i just played trivial per
pursuit ah yesterday and i won not
to brag but with huh mike was
there not a jelly should
let's make a dewy um and my
my friend joy greer and i won
and um but there was a question
about who you ask riddles to in
greek mythology those pleasant greek oh it
was this thing so ap too i
meant not phoenix i was thinking of
the x oh silly
re sphinx sphinx what has three legs
of the you know four legs in
the morning two legs in the afternoon
three legs of ny right illuminating fucked
oh lorin sorry
there was a gap in the fence
i swear to god if you don't
go to the next sentence ah okay
so i had taken the shingles vaccine
and so i was i was inside
ah cool i was having a sort
of a get together with some friends
in the back i heard it was
a party yeah more of a get
together swim together and i was i
was taking it easy i was watching
ah star trek voyager and i did
not really feel any symptoms really but
i was like i'm still gonna just
you know take it easy and not
be in the backyard yeah right suddenly
cool app comes bounding up saying she
can't find georgia
it had been about ten minutes and
ah she got nowt and so everyone
at this get together mobilized and went
up and down the hills and i
counted my steps afterwards and it was
ten thousand steps at least and just
going up and you just went in
your head anyway one to fetch
four five six seven eight yeah i
think it was an unused to that
forever i think i did ten thousand
i think i did i was counting
yes i mean i guess i don't
good i probably did like on ten
thousand steps
i do i do want to three
four hundred ten eleven hundred so ten
thousand my nephew got this watch that's
a phone i'm scott this is how
the show works we talk and then
just backing off from the dog story
whoa the dog story will take the
tab i'm just back in i'm ok
okay on the mic like i want
to hear lawrence story my nephew
got this for this watch that's a
phone it's a timex it's like it's
a family connect thing for a kid
basically and then he could call me
through the watch and on the it
was it's so cute he's he's called
me a bunch it's really i love
it so much and he called me
and said i took i've already taken
a thousand steps today because the watch
tells him right so then i was
it's so funny for a little kid
to be like ah looking at their
steps like i know my cholesterol
oh my triglycerides em up well i
think during during quarantine i mean it's
you know how they say you need
ten thousand steps every day which is
like we tried it one day it's
impossible unless you're taking like my god
during an hour long hike every single
day your nine steps have gone to
oblivion in the fucking quarantine it's like
rather but i'm not going to
thousand a day like two thousand if
i if i go exercise yes i
got a walk while we we walk
the dog so it's like i get
to two thousand every day but ten
thousand is insane and especially going up
and down the hills i was thank
god i had no symptoms because it
was literally two and a half hours
of hiking
that i was doing oh my god
and down the hills up and down
the hills calling for her and um
everyone was really great casey wilson and
matt mcconkey in casey's husbands and laura
kindred like they all made flyers and
they started posting them up all around
the neighbor this is all in the
space of two and a half hours
um
buddy was a lot like our friend
kevin sessions dog who got away a
couple years ago the day after christmas
um and that was a little more
dire because we we found out it
happened at like twelve thirty p m
button during christmas it gets dark at
five and yeah all the coyotes likes
yeah success so he can crawl into
your nose jimmy under the cover of
day find him so we were
going up and down the hills or
sexist her you know the other one's
dog is a woman yes her okay
you think every other dog is every
other gender lawyer douglas georgia shower girl
and next one i'd be a boy
so so we were really under a
time crunch with that we were andy
was a it was a big big
area to cover and we were just
an and the owner kevin was out
of town that's the other part so
he couldn't pay off so he's like
frantically sending us voice messages that we
can play on our phones of him
calling you know
am not about i remember this yeah
yeah and ah and i was stung
by a bee about an hour in
ever i never mentioned it because i
wanted wow you're smart light to be
on the the missing dog now
um but that was that was again
it was around like an hour to
you start going like
okay this is bad ah either someone
immediately picked her up ah and because
she has no colorado right now doesn't
know what to do and hopefully will
take it to a vet to get
the chip you know the microchip thing
right but or something terrible has happened
right
so it's it just feels inconsistent no
honestly no everytime i want some god
now this it's like they're dead it's
over so thanks so hard to imagine
that so in coop is is just
inconsolable in the how kind of sticking
by the house in case you know
ga comes back and really nicely put
on social media and and you guys
re-tweeted it and stuff but really nicely
you also some people wrote some tips
which were the two that i did
were put a pile of dirty clothes
by the entrance to your house which
we put by backed by the gate
that she got out of and you're
like no problem already there
ah but where we live like pigs
got it
she'll find us
and that's because if she's lost she
can't she it's able she's able to
to find her way back because that's
really that's so sweet yeah and then
the other was get her favorite toy
so i got a squeaky toy because
she goes crazy for toys and throwing
balls and stuff and i was just
wandering all over the neighborhood squeaking
and going charge ya
yeah and out of bounds like is
the worst cover of the song i've
ever heard
joe joe oh joe
yeah cool instrument man go huh
so so we we you know she
got lucid three and it gets dark
now during the summer like eight so
that's like saying it doesn't come we
still we still had some time but
at at five thirty i was just
like ah this is this is bad
this is going to have a bad
ending and but i
you give up and i was exhausted
like i felt like aged like obama
during the entire experience um and i
was just wanting very well
you're going so hard at the end
so i said you know what i'm
gonna go i'm gonna go back into
the sort of like alley paul that
you pointed the birds ad when we're
typing in the backyard like ah bird
alley i call it yeah bird alley
where there's bushes and stuff and i
was like never killed there maybe there's
a difference opening
so that she got out into another
area or some things so i'm just
squeaking the toy calling george oh here's
the other weird part
we kept kind of hearing her we
thought oh we love we kept kind
of thinking that we were hearing her
bark that she barks when like she
wants you to throw the toy in
the pool so she can jump in
like the excited like yeah i'm kind
of like really high pitched yap and
i heard it first time like i
swear i hear her and then
casey and matt were like yeah we
think we do and then our neighbor
got involved that was me was like
was it the nice neighbor the one
who bite who yelled at you nice
neighbor who was like she's she was
like i think i hear it too
but then two houses down from us
there were these kids jumping in the
pool and and kind of squealing so
we're like maybe that's it did you
go oh shut up i'm trying to
hear my dog bark
but i was backed by the i
was backed by the fence and i'm
just like calling out across the entire
neighborhood squeaking the thing going ga ga
and i looked to my right and
she's her head is over the foe
just like looking at me going
wow i'm looking at the toy and
i'm like georgia and i swear i
thought she had been hiding the whole
time or something i was like georgia
where have you been yeah and when
she's going to happen to walk what
happened to walk out right at that
moment was like jaw and and she
ran and she was just like squeaking
the toy let's play with ray like
that
it's why going back so she's like
that's so great yeah really focused on
the toy so we shut the gate
shut again and we clean lock the
gates as a matter of fact and
um alright i was like just been
here the whole time what is going
on and we checked our camera and
it's really cute we have like two
cameras on it you can see her
just
like run into the into the the
backyard and like try to find me
oh because you are gone away and
she's like jumping up and trying to
find me and then she finally sees
me um but yeah so our our
theory is that i guess dogs when
they get lost and they can't figure
out where they are
are they just sort of hunker down
and hide yeah in a place know
i think i took a look at
the camera and it looks like she
came from up the street which only
has like five houses up the street
up the hill and i think she
just wandered into the backyard of one
of them and then couldn't fit in
and probably when we were calling her
was yelping like i can't figure out
how to get out yeah
and there's definitely i was just squeaking
it so much she'd like was going
crazy ones like backend die and figured
away out and just like smashed girl
wow
like many time my cat has gotten
out she's always been really close by
like yeah you don't run you don't
know but like then once you find
them like she's she'll just be hiding
in a bush like next door or
like in and someone's little like patio
like she's always like really close and
recently it happened and she was in
the backyard but it freaked
me out so much because i was
like if you just went the other
way it's over like it's just it's
crazy georgia had gone down the hill
and actually did i don't know but
i did take a look at the
camera and she appeared to be coming
from uphill just down the hills where
all the traffic is do you think
for the animal it's like i just
wanted to go here that's i know
there is
this disease my cat recently when she
got out this was it was an
it was scary for me but was
only a it was a quick thing
because i've looked out the window and
saw her in the backyard so i
was like okay again but when i
went out and like called to her
she looked back and she ran straight
to me like i've had a feeling
she was like overwhelmed like yeah georgia
doesn't like to be away from us
but she but she also has an
adventurous spirit
where she like you know smell something
and wants to go check it out
or it's their name maybe she heard
the the kids playing a couple doors
down and was like oh so there's
playing over there great let's go over
there you know and then just got
turned around this is why i don't
have pets anymore because i had a
dog who smelled a pie that was
baking like several doors down flow
noted in the air and i never
saw him again he just yeah the
pie why that wasn't that's dogs will
do the whole don't so that's what
i always say people need to close
their windows and they make a pie
unless they want to you know steal
somebody yeah but that's how smells like
pie well how is that a bad
thing i know i tried to make
a pilot like lure the dog back
apparently it doesn't
work and now those people survivor dog
yeah i tried to make a reverse
lie and i got to one of
the questions on the top hydra these
reverse ingredients and um and now they
have the dog and and i see
the dog in their yard and it's
it's heartbreaking
oh my god you know i've got
to say um started highs so many
people thinking you want the dog back
and i know he's got a fat
fatty yeah i received a pie as
always thank you good i received a
pie as a thank you i received
a pie pies a thing you gift
wait hold on i wanna hear this
but i want to take a break
lyrics let's hype this up this is
an amaze
king story we guys aren't going to
believe what went die that lauren received
as a thank you gift okay we'll
be right back
and we're back and okay one thing
before we get to lawrence story one
thing i should mention is i i
forgot to close the loop on the
previous dog story which was that dog
was a runner when the when the
person that had been hired to walk
the dog from a dog-walking service was
not supposed to open the door was
just supposed to open the door a
crack but just open the door and
the dog immediately ran out and went
into the neighborhood and was gone and
so that dog was not that close
by but gone up the hill and
was just we found two and a
half hours later the same thing where
it was like oh my god we're
an hour away from darkness just not
respond
to any calls just like sitting in
someone's front yard just smile yeah and
our our cousin dinah ah finally like
we have been going up and down
that street too but finally like looked
in the yard just right at that
you know we have been going up
and demonstrate thinking the dog would make
noise but it was just sitting there
yeah and and a woman who owned
the house was like oh hey yeah
at some point i was gonna call
someone about that
anyway at some point i'm like well
your station which was walking down your
street caller i was walking down the
street this was like tell us you
have a dog you're already done the
street yeah when did this other day
i guess early in panic oops it
was early in pandemic time and i
i was just going for a walk
and there was this dog that was
the most fucked up looking
the dog i've ever seen in my
life it looked like a drawing that
kid made like it was like it
was all askew and it was literally
this dog it was so it was
honestly really disturbing like i actually felt
i felt really weird looking at it
i was like oh and it was
like sitting on the grass just nowhere
you know and it was just like
it looked it
looks like it wasn't right you know
what i mean like something was wrong
with this dog from day one yeah
and it was sitting there home like
it's it's eyes were like different levels
like it was really it was so
odd looking
and make an error like ooh what's
up with this dog and then we
were like are we going to have
to deal with this dog and like
help it get wherever it's going and
we we literally just walked a little
bit further look back never saw it
again i don't know where it went
i don't know what happened maybe it
wasn't dog it's someone was weird it
was maybe an alien so you think
dogs that ugly should be put to
death no i really was but
i was really like whose dog is
this where it was sitting there kind
of like low like it just it
just looked weird i was like what
is the story i don't like anytime
i see a dog a loose dog
i start to mobilize and i'm like
let you know i started i'm driving
by usually and i start to park
the car and i get out of
the car and then it's
just like then you see an owner
walking i know well this happened to
be like it's not on leash and
you're like what the fuck are you
doing with your dough you know and
shy running around i swear i've i've
followed chihuahuas around the neighborhood a couple
different times and then they hopped through
fencing in there like i think you
live there like i don't know like
there's just this like hard like there
they can go wherever they want or
something i don't know okay
tell one story about a missing dog
but yeah people are worried about the
this is your missing dog story okay
so but this is not a dog
i knew but we removed it says
mix it up okay so we were
driving and we we find a loose
dog and we pull over and we
call it over and it lie
like you know sometimes loose dogs run
away from you this one like leapt
into our arms and we look at
the collar and there's ah the owner's
phone number on it so we call
expecting of course the owner to pick
up immediately or something rings and rings
and rings and finally an answering you
know a phone voicemail thing comes
up and we say hey we found
the dog's name where parked at the
corner of this and this and we'll
wait for you or call us back
or something we wait for like ten
minutes and we're like okay i don't
think anyone's coming no one's calling us
back let's i guess go back to
our house and wait for them there
we were like roy
ready to abandon our plans essentially we
were like ok let's go back to
our house and just wait for the
person to call suddenly i see from
down the street a guy on the
phone like holding up his hand
and i go i think i think
some guy is like trying to flag
us down this is probably the guy
so i get out of the car
i have the dog the guys coming
towards the cities and in the middle
of a phone conversation and he's not
looking at us and i go oh
i've i've messed up this is just
a guy who was stretching right he
he so
back in the car he finally comes
over to us grabs the dog doesn't
never interrupts his phone conversation and just
turns around and walks away that's insane
insanity that's insane
decides not to call us just like
just trots out grabs the dog can't
can't interrupt his business deal what was
it i will say we hear anything
because the cnsc had a major motion
picture oh my gosh same zappos jay
roach
i will say my neighbor who ah
basically accused me of calling animal control
on her oh yeah has not spoken
to me since i mean we haven't
we haven't been like ida i said
we've been across the street from each
other we have not said hello um
but because you're too shy too late
um but i still think she kind
of thinks we did it yeah so
anyways i mean i tried a book
called the way they did it work
yeah all right a full of holes
if i didn't i would call the
number
take a picture of yourself for the
jacket
some of this pies wanna talk about
his pie for oh this is exciting
okay we talked about this before the
break previously on three i got a
pi as a thank you gift that
was the clip that was played back
and now the thrilling conclusion to think
i got a pie in the mail
as a thank you gift from gen
spiral slash spira i'm not sure how
to
renounce her last name um but she's
very funny her book is called big
time and it's it's very it's it's
honestly hilarious it's all these like short
essays anytime anyone says honestly they're not
being honest no but i am i
am because i usually say it when
i am yes what honestly i think
that they're always lying
you know that's the opposite of what's
true so i read two of them
and they were so funny that's why
i agreed to do it and um
and she sent me this pie from
milk bar as a thank you oh
wow now i was really delighted to
receive a pile of pies i just
i don't i don't see i don't
love pie is actually old pies i
don't remember
i was like yeah i don't love
a fruit pie i don't like a
lot of things and i usually i
usually talk about a nice cherry pie
with ice cream i don't like um
hot fruit why you know what lauren
i used to be like that too
but now i like apple pie apple
i've never tried apple pie or apple
actually it's good it works never interested
reasons i understand your reasons but i
think you would like it i've been
afraid of time we needed a new
tastes challenge that people i would love
that i actually don't like it because
it's me really swishy mike um he
but i then i was like this
pie is so good this was the
original milk bar pie yeah and i
was high i don't think i don't
have as cold crack pie i would
try
to figure this out it's like slang
for it like people just go they
know they have one that is called
crack pie i don't know if this
is called that it's like a it's
like a gooey sort of their signature
it might be my fist gooey i
bet managed the crack pipe okay well
it's fucking good and i've now sent
it to two different people as a
gift and i just wanted to throw
that out there this is
for a gift this is my add
to cart honestly so then on add
to cart they should talk about why
crack pies are bad okay great that
would be great to restore balance in
the universe but i sent one to
my dad for father's day sam which
has my home so i'm really curious
if he's gonna like it but i
think that's going to be exciting because
it's shaped like a thai yeah because
you know what
you know what i'm so sick of
that shit of the eighteen father's day
cards are kind of hard to buy
because they all kind of assume you
have a relationship with your dad were
young guns tools
right right right that they all they
all are sort of like hey thanks
dad when that might not be the
sentiment i know there's there's never like
a neutral enough tar and happy father's
day
why are you so remote wishing you
the best
ah
what do you do yeah honestly that's
it that's i don't know like you
janie has that recipe and she's made
that crack pie if you really yes
and it's so good it's so um
i have a question what do you
send or give somebody when you want
to appreciate them
ooh i'm usually spare ipads
letter engraved to you crew jackets ah
i gotta say it why is it
so hard to make a good-looking crew
jacket i thought between two ferns ones
were good though i wouldn't know oh
i liked i wore that in a
store um i um we didn't get
far
oh no you fucking um actually orange
is the new black the first season
they gave these messenger bags as the
um i could now i have one
of those i was even let show
you do know oh
huh and i gave it to my
dad and he used it as his
briefcase for years that's actually not okay
memorization start to pass on like crew
gifts to your parents because they'll actually
be proud of it like yeah for
the between two ferns one deputy had
the we had this public access logo
on it which doesn't mean anything to
anyone and then netflix insisted on putting
net
flicks on it and so we have
them ah we haven't put it under
the back hood i was glad about
that because sometimes it's so hard to
wear those things when they're really corny
because it says like like i worked
really big yeah when you're walking around
yeah exactly um i like to give
people i like to send flowers i
think flowers are nice if sent my
mom now says
i don't ever send me flowers again
why because she just doesn't like her
it's too much work or whatever she's
just like look you've been sending me
flowers just don't send him to me
ever again i think sending flowers is
actually so nice i might cost a
little bit opposed to it at first
when i when i did it like
one of the first few times and
then it's like i now i'm like
i don't care what
anyone says it's a nice thing to
get like it's just like it's a
sunny day yeah i'm sure i would
listen i'll never send flowers to that
bitch
she's done one of those bitches
but it's it's it's nice because it's
so easy like i think it's you
can find there's always a coupon by
the way i mean this is my
big thing with like anything like that
you gotta search for a coupon you
can always get fifteen percent off at
least off of any i mean you
found it for the gnome i'm saying
that no deal while i was looking
at well the reason i found the
the deal on the gnome is that
i was looking for a new gnome
you want a new know what i
want going on only yourself we've very
high in here i wanted more gnomes
but i'm telling you i have not
found one i like like i just
don't know and it's it's coming it's
almost here i'm i'm very same person
i'm looking at yeah i'm really curious
about the quality um i can't wait
can i say the more expensive it
was more expensive
so i got a break in here
yes oh my god there's some there's
some late breaking news from one of
our threesome listeners oh god
now this is on twitter ah w
t f cathy why would you pick
that name w tf kathy did she
work on w t f just looked
at cf maybe it's about the cartoon
okay that's true um she says by
the way scott ackerman on last week's
ep pretty sure the test you had
the one the one i talks about
for when i had the the bladder
infection and you guys are having fun
of me
ah that's the only part i remember
i make fun of you pretty sure
the test you had is called avoiding
sisto re three graham vcu g i
own it is it is unfortunately very
common and horrible it's to check for
urine backing up into the kidneys and
the child has to pee in front
of strangers on a tape
gl oh now i remember that yeah
we were like you just spray it
all over the you spray it all
over the place and she does this
very common and and and that's what
it was so that's good to know
thank you so much shows really wondered
i just have that memory of having
to pee in front of everyone and
not knowing why and they're like oh
it's just something you have to do
and so now i know i may
have to do it's coming of age
it's good to know because i've become
a child again when you when you're
dating everyone has to do this
okay go on about flowers i think
another thing is if you know people
that drink i think wine is a
good yeah yeah a bottle of scotch
i think like stealing the mail well
i mean here's the thing is it
really the mail like when you say
you got the pie in the mail
was
is it usbs or was it like
a delivery service it was males but
it was really these new persons in
the mail never get it mill far
sends the um the ah probably sad
i send it anywhere yeah yeah but
but i mean i mean it's it's
but it's gotta be stored in some
sort of you have to eat it
within like you have to put it
in the fridge put it in dry
ice right yeah yeah yeah right but
yeah that's usbs you can do that
through uspto's yeah i didn't know that
i did not lie did not know
that weird wild male i think the
usbs now can do anything that u
p s or fedex can do
do yeah and we should be talking
about sam do i can do better
also you know what if you want
to splurge like a gold belly thing
if you can single buddies oh gall
it's like oh lauren hold on to
this is this is a nice thing
that jenny did this for my birthday
she got me you can get you
can get food from anywhere sent anywhere
oh and giant snakes for my birthday
which was really nice goal it's like
if you if there's some if there's
some restaurant that like say you had
people visiting you and they're like oh
we loved that restaurant when we were
there you can send them stuff from
there but how on earth does that
work well i don't know but the
rest are so big
bang theory was was formed in two
thousand molecules crashed into one another and
suddenly we're here
wait so like if i was like
um i want you to send me
burger lords to chicago or whatever like
like how do they get the food
i don't understand like i want you
to send these two burger lords to
chicago are you already there i'm involved
i guess i'm worried that it's gonna
taste like a no it doesn't no
it doesn't it's great it's like reddit
you get it and it's ready
it's great
but but but but but but but
but you know need to be so
nervous lauren but how do did make
it to go in the mail they
put it in whatever packaging you would
use for the new to cooking food
um i yeah hot when it gets
to you later fuse them out oh
you weren't they weren't things up but
it's every detail they have d
detailed instructions of all restaurants that are
involved are like we have our gold
belly system which yeah yeah yeah so
i've yeah i've done it sometimes and
they give you a detailed thing of
like okay you know put it in
the oven for this long at this
temperature and then you know it's like
very detailed so it tastes exactly the
way that they want it always starts
don't touch the oven the oven is
hot
yeah okay so because they don't know
there's no age limit like kids can
order this
alright i'm into this i mean this
it's a really cool thing like if
you know if you know somebody that's
from us specific place you can send
them like yeah you're famous show like
if you missed chicago pizza or whatever
yeah you used to eat there my
parents tend to yeah illuminati is gift
card which is literally what
you don't need to admit that it's
doing a west l o u space
no no no they found out they
data for poison
ah alright we have to take a
break
and we're back and it's time for
three church
and this one was submitted by cartoons
underscore plural and it's called audiobook grant
here's here's how it works we have
engineer ryan over here on the ones
and twos keeping us honest and we
ask him not verbally put it in
the chat ryan
right we ask him for a genre
and a i guess subject matter or
topic for for a book yeah and
then one person's the narrator and the
other to voice characters doing the dialogue
anytime the narrator so say sander when
tastic um so ah
ryan if you would my man first
of all who wants to be narrator
i'll be the narrator okay okay paulo
will be narrator and ryan will give
you the what was it as if
the
genre topic oh genre genre new title
i actually we could do title actually
what might be better is just title
that would be sure right yeah why
don't we do that ryan just dry
and just playing title had dirt again
or put anything into the chat because
ryan just type into the chat when
you're all alone
yeah ok listen ryan ryan jesse ryan
just put in horror slash skeletons
oh yeah that'll be the title i
guess horror slash skeletons yeah look tough
alright here we go paul
start us up
or slash skeletons a novel by richard
abernathy on chapter one
oh no
loop
is that the narrator saying food well
that's exactly right yes
so it's now the first character um
yeah so you guys just lay out
i'll take this
alright bye see ya chapter one
the door creaked open slowly and a
figure entered the room it opened it's
mouth and spake oh my god it's
ding dong what's the player ding dong
replied
hey i'm looking for my skeleton it
left my body
that's horrible and the other copies
suddenly the lights went out
don't worry ding dong i'm mostly strong
man and i'm going to protect you
said the tiny guy
the tiny guy looked around the room
and found a stub of candle and
then a match he struck the match
across ting dogs scratchy forehead oh
the magic knighted and he lit the
candle
thank god your forehead seems to be
made of sandpaper in fact your entire
face is just really rough you have
skin problems when loja
pass another man had entered the room
it was ding dongs husband was a
husband
ah hey dig dug i heard what
you ah first of all what's up
plays but i heard what you just
said to that man and i'm a
little upset that i was actually saying
it to you well then let's get
to it
ah
sandpaper race
ding dong ker like maybe maybe
why
thanks
what did you say
you can dig babies
it's slowly eating
just then the lights came back on
ooh
and for the first time the tiny
guy was seeing ding dongs husband mister
wasa players for the first time ah
hey what's going on dude ah i
didn't turn out these lights you don't
look at me
he's not lying mister wasa players did
look at him
oh you tiny tiny piece of shit
i do believe i will engage you
in a physical altercation no ding dong
stood ran between them holding out her
arms and protecting the tiny guy no
no don't do it don't do it
he's just a little thing
the tiny guy got a little offended
at this guy i mean ding dong
we've known each other a long time
i don't know it's a little dry
you see me you can't even lift
a key
i'm lifting one right now we're looking
at me lift one everyone stop we
need to focus on what's most important
finding my skeleton slash horror
suddenly ding-dong skeleton walked into the room
oh god ding dong very well let
me get inside you said said ding
dongs husband
don't say that i've missed you hey
come over here what do you want
to say well um i've just been
out there walking around and i've seen
the world and it's very frightening to
you know take a look at the
world from this point of view so
i'd rather do it from inside of
you so i'm gonna get in there
probably dive right in through your mouth
here we go
ding-dong scream so loud that the skeleton
was repelled out the window hey that
didn't work
when he goes so over the top
i spoke up
look this has taught me a valuable
lesson by he also jumped out the
window ah then it was just ding
dong and her husband mr whalley is
we never learn what that looks like
same time and so did i
note to reader doing dialogue when you
hear this it's all of us at
the same time it's not a mistake
alright well we've been talking about having
gone to jump out the window anyway
so early time
oh right i guess you're able to
save your anniversary
the end it's a one chapter book
ah that was such a good story
when i listen to fall asleep every
night
so good do we have time for
another or what's going on i think
we have time for one more okay
who's going to be a narrator i'll
narrow it okay okay ryan you gotta
give us give us a title this
i know that well okay just do
whatever i just don't ever do anything
you want in the chat ryan ryan
this is your time
to be a freak
let your freak flag shine ryan let
your freak flag shine
we are waiting for ryan to me
to be there anymore
really
oh my know oh oh burning the
burning it's a question the genres question
mark burning is burning
ah
in the dusty dunes of the indiana
planes
two young men climbed a mountain in
the blazing blazing hot sun lady sided
probably best to remove their shirts and
tie them around their heads
boy i sure could use to drink
water oh the shirt is so heavy
i don't know if i can lift
it up my head my mind linen
which is lucky mine's a bulletproof shirt
the eleanor talked first decided that he
was still having enough energy
e so he should carry the other
man i got you just leave it
to me kevlar i'll pick you up
and carry you the rest of the
way up the dusty dune do you
want me to jump into your arms
no that's actually going to mess me
up let me just scoop you okay
scoop me like you're a chip and
i'm salsa
he sounded like he was far away
but was just still right there caviar
yeah
from up high he could see something
nobody else could see check this out
check this out well for me okay
you get up here i'll live up
your me first oh okay no pick
me up alright oh do you see
what i see yeah i do it's
freaky
they kept singing that christmas song but
making up words to tell us what
they saw
ah city or city standing on a
hill and it's burning up and needs
water with some smoke that climbs through
the sky
boom boom boom boom boom
they kept walking knowing that they were
the only ones who could save this
city as clearly all the people had
fled
hey we gotta save the city no
one's around we got damage her firefighter
so this is a good plan yeah
we do it because we love it
not for the money yeah but they
are fighters who get paid to do
it or sell outs volunteer firefighters we
are amateur firefighters we want to be
professionals no one will hire
they thought now is a good time
to talk about their relationship a little
more in depth and how they got
to where they were hey you remember
when we met in ski-doo yeah it's
ten minutes ago
and we knew right away we'd be
best friends forever and we got to
climb that mountain right next to the
school yeah this is the first time
ever cut class yep a wonderful get
in trouble probably not we'll be heroes
after we save the town from the
burning oh that's right and our school
is burning up yeah back at the
school but the school the
a teacher was giving one last assignment
everyone sit down and shut up i
want you to read all of huckleberry
finn backwards i'm bored and i've been
here for too long all right i'll
start and the
good
oh
but i've stopped disrupting the class i'm
not just writing you stupid bitch i'm
alive
whereas all the smoke coming from who's
doing this the principal walked in with
a cigarette blaze hey what's up it's
made a cool principle you guys wanna
smoke with me hell yeah i do
alright fuck you teacher i'm taking the
kids smoke to the smoke about privacy
sorry cool thanks guys
ah what's this other smoke though
the principal looked out the window oh
it looks like there's a big fire
on cool dudes
he did a banksy or she left
though and i did work he did
a backflip and left the room see
yours
look at him go
just then the bell rang
it was time to go home
what was was
everyone filed out
alright guess it's time to go home
yeah in size order
yeah i wish i didn't have to
go home at the end of every
school day a limit to it's the
best i wish i could stay here
forever the kids who love the school
looked at the window and saw their
old classmates walking up that hill hey
what's gonna do best friends yeah
remember when they met i was electric
for all of us we zoom in
there would be other fancy zoom in
divorce of state rex
alright i think i figured out how
we're going to put the fire out
here here's here's okay i think are
you thinking what i'm thinking because here's
what i think you're thinking let's say
at the same time okay here we
agree to one we're gonna honor our
pistols and those water tanks and have
them leak out
out onto the school so parallel thinking
yeah i mean you just said water
yeah that's not really a plan
you got me there this is our
first bite
well i'm tired of you me me
to you let's say said hey each
try our different plans yeah you go
try your plan of water
you go apply try your plan of
i can't remember it was so long
yeah well okay you say both walked
off in different directions marching angrily
ten hours passed and neither of them
found the thing they were looking for
they both died and became horror slash
skeletons
and the burning took over and killed
them all
we became one slow still slash guys
of the last oh boy you said
whores i love course at first oh
there why do they make the word
horse and horrors so similar and horror
guy no
well that was great that was great
how he declared that it was great
and that we enjoyed it and you
enjoy the most well but the most
important thing is that we enjoyed it
first because if we don't enjoy it
how can you enjoy it you the
listener enjoyed it so much on i
thought it was so fun um all
right that's gonna do it for this
episode
i hope you enjoyed the harrowing tale
of georgia getting loose happy endings for
both dogs and the third dog as
well whose name i don't recall and
whose hipster owner ah doesn't deserve to
own them but um if you have
bought a gnome please tag us in
the picture and we'll make a collage
and if you ny
ease if you know the names of
any of our ah medical procedures that
we've described that we don't know the
name of please let us know those
as well you're in related only thank
you um you're in now makes me
think of ah the movie where what's
her name rosamund pike is like helping
o t
evangel old people oh i care a
lot i have nice yeah she she's
great the whole time and then one
word her accent is not perfect and
she goes he's lying in a pool
of his own urine your eye or
something yeah yeah he's he's lying in
a pool of his own urine urine
yeah i remember that that doesn't sell
strange to me though your in your
urine urine oh you're a year in
your url yeah okay alright that's very
exciting bill be sure to tune in
next week yes we adore you ah
we are twitter ah wait no we
are we're three years later we have
freedom usa on twitter and instagram
power jack aren't you so yeah i
don't like to admit it but yes
i'm jack from twitter i don't care
about your complaints um we and three
m usa gmail dot com if you
would like to send a three cheer
thank you very much we love you
and will be back next week by
bay urine
and you're on your own
uh