nah
right huh
three huh
boink boink do duo boy
wow wow oh wow three months show
where we make noise for the first
minute we're back and it feels so
good i'm in love and it feels
so good wow congrats what is it
that's from the bachelor i know hey
sorry wake up late and sometimes from
a song
clayton clayton clayton clayton clayton or take
time just so retreated sorry to do
retiring in clayton but some people were
calling on clayton no it was either
clayton or people going clayton clayton clayton
he literally is the worst bachelor we've
ever had what makes him so bad
explain it to me like i'm five
oh okay ah goo ga ga i'm
fine i'm assuming you've not learned how
to twine a man thousand liberal overhearing
women on tv and tells them he's
in love with them and then has
sex with two of them which is
when the man pants playing on this
other woman's vagina oh man wanted to
have sex vagina okay hold on
take this with a third thirty
a third asked him if he had
sex with the other yeah he was
about to steal you along with me
said yes i told them i was
love them and that i and they
had sex with them and then she
was like well i'm out of here
and then dennis miller style z like
crossed off everything hundred pages and then
the two women he told them i
had sex with both of you and
i told you both i'm in love
with you and that hurt both of
them immense
only because they thought they were the
only one of course and then he
planned but stick around but stick around
i mean she left for six acre
oh and then there's unprompted yeah yeah
basically had to do it unprompted and
then because he realized he should just
be truthful with them because susie was
so disturbed by it that maybe other
people would also be disturbed so i
told them it was like stick around
meet my parents so awkward
met they met his parents then at
the end of meetings parents is like
yeah like the other one the most
and so he broke up with both
of them together the other one this
one didn't have say one left okay
he made a come back any he
goes into the room and breaks up
with two women at once he's like
yeah it's not going i'm still in
my studio and they're both like can
you treat us like individuals you said
you you're in love with each of
us now you're telling us over to
both of us
the same and now then susie ends
up coming back and and is with
him now and then they were at
the tel or whatever and the after
these my mom she was like i
love you clayton's mamane i love you
i love you but they're like they're
like she's like really stupid they're like
are you in love with him and
i love you love you no really
no way am i do
love you my man which is like
i love you so she's doing like
a little voice yeah well no she's
she's southern right yeah but you went
like oh i love you all of
you she kind of made it kind
of a joke and then i was
like you should she's already yes she's
the one who's saying clayton clayton and
she's with him now and they're working
it out and i just think it's
a disaster and then they said that
way it's over right yes it tells
the show
oh yeah yeah and the two women
who were rejected slash rejected him are
now the bachelor bachelor skyler i really
liked both of them especially the one
who was like gabby gabby who broke
him down when he broke up with
but he was like here's your problem
you i wanted to break up after
you told us all that and you
begged me to stay because you wanted
it to be your decision not mine
you wanted all the power you know
she just like expertly she was to
kill it about the whole situation and
it was objects i would've been like
euro dick head
your head is maybe isaac hot but
i wish that the idea of them
being double bachelorette i sort of feel
like could get dicey if they're dating
the same pool of men they say
the creator says that's not gonna happen
okay because i want them to have
two separate houses with different men and
then they supposed divided cannot stand the
women sleep in the same house between
the two
houses and kind of recap and help
each other and coach oh like like
one divorce couples buy they get one
house that's where the child lives yeah
and then they take turns living there
yeah what an interesting idea that is
definitely true what a piece of work
is
there was a there was a producer
who pitched me the idea for a
movie that he wanted me to write
robert evans this is remind me yes
it was robert evan i can't remember
who it is but it was the
craziest pitch i'd ever heard he was
like alright so you know how reality
tv is really sounds like a producer
i'm doing virtual reality seems a bit
like alright here we let me take
my
go around okay i'm also from the
east coast if you can't good let
me take my val choices up from
becky's reality tv very big so he's
like okay so there are there are
shoes there were two houses alright and
the the movies called three hundred i
think this is before oh no
must be called two hundred know it
had to be three one hundred but
if it's doi her and this is
before the movie three hundred oh he
must have been pissed okay so was
it three it must be three high
recall that
so to help you figure it out
so he's like alright there's two houses
maybe it was doing anyway let's go
huh i'll just keep saying that the
plot day will come where i will
jump into the pool
so it's ah so it's two houses
and in one house there's three hundred
people and they're all divorced and they're
always in one kid in one house
it's people who are who all weigh
one hundred pounds what and then in
the other house it's all people who
weigh three hundred per
pounds what does this idea and then
the goal is for them to lose
it's it was ten people right so
maybe it was a thousand so it
was like the goal is for all
for all of them to either lose
or gain as close to a thousand
pounds oh yeah obviously it was called
a thousand so it's probably i
no and had a weird guy it
was the weirdest close-ups i'm like movie
as a movie and he's like an
obviously like they they have relationships i
honestly and i was like so you're
trying to get actors some actors are
going to be putting on that suits
and then some are going to be
taking off that sue is that what
you're it was the craziest idea i'd
ever heard
id like he hadn't thought it out
at all i don't i don't know
if it's would you watch i'm writing
it right now and it's really really
yeah but see here's one of the
themes or humanity oh great relationships here's
what i discovered is that i liked
you guys telling me the bachelor without
my having to watch it please watch
my instagram stories and we're all goes
i can't do that oh but i
count
sorry too many dots that's the dots
oh
duh
fair fair fair but i'm always worried
about turning soviet words like the three
dots make you know what i learned
about that and then i felt kind
of sickened by the idea of like
i've like having a phobia of tryptophan
yeah well i've had the thought when
i've seen something and i've been kind
of like i guess i see why
that's gross and waiting for the dogs
dogs are walking by were waving to
them and nearly three year ga
is interested in what we do there
are three dogs this time benny visitor
area my buddy he's just rotting away
he's very funny he's the he's a
dog who anytime he pees poos he
like does the kickback of a um
which seems psychotic to me if my
dog does not lollipop guild yeah
ah i also like the idea of
ah of ah of really being a
movie and yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
get over with two hours mr moody
filler this was a movie you'd yeah
yeah he was not pitching an actual
reality now that's what i thought but
then i just got confused yeah wow
i love the bylaws kid i love
the bachelor just to be a movie
one time and then it's over yeah
yeah narrative to like fake and it's
all fake yeah they'd be great as
you know start it sucks that i'm
locked into watching this rest of my
life but what am i going to
feel that way well i like it
it's something i like it well i
like it and i hate it you
know it's like yeah every time it
starts up again i think oh no
it's already back because you know it's
gonna be back sooner than you even
realised yeah i don't think so because
hey they haven't even started ah filming
it so yeah it will be it's
gonna be me and that's already it's
around the corner you know i mean
i have one reality show that we
watch and just southern
charm oh yeah because it's set in
charleston by the way i told you
about another rock the block is said
yes gotcha watch my rock the block
i must catch up
but we don't like it it's not
good yeah i'm sure people are just
boring shit i can't watch it for
the local color or the scenery or
we that's when we started watching it
for was because we were writing something
that was set in charleston right in
in south carolina and we and it
was terrible but
it was they had a writing yeah
and the proof is in the pudding
no one wanted to do oh it
was terrible
we had to watch a show instead
that's actually we did get we did
sell a script but nobody wanted to
buy the yeah the pilot sorry um
what noise that happens you know what
i mean it's only a little bit
the hoops the hoops i know the
hoops are on fire we don't need
no hoops i launched there's like a
whole fuckin ton of of bravo that
i won't
watch oh southern time i won't watch
below deck yeah i draw the line
you know i saw the same just
one formula yeah below the deck blow
the deck blow that oh yeah needed
to blow the dick but it's
when we first started there was a
there was a person on the meeting
kevin
kevin bailey charging us hello kevin and
his bag yeah he hasn't brought his
spanking pension seventy k kevin aka chef
kevin he's back in charge of us
again josh hasta la vista
had better things to do we brought
josh he's watching better things
oh joy i could i confuse better
things in stranger things all the time
while they're extremely different he should be
the same yes i know i know
the stranger better things and combine them
ah what if what if pamela adlon
pawlyn padawan outlet what if she had
the same teeth as that one kid
that'd be awesome
rich kid what do you kid who
has like the gums and the braces
or whatever the the mickey dolan is
looking kid yeah mickey jones looking kid
yeah why don't you cut your hair
this
i just anytime i think mcdonalds i
think him banging on that snare drum
singing that song yeah ma'am
you got two and of course i
think about him coming into jin and
eating with his daughter amy ah she's
out of control she is she was
that day i remember the commercial that
like the trailer for that movie i
remember seeing it on tv yeah zelda
control which starred tony danza ronnie danza
as a dad is her dad yeah
who's who's amy
a daughter meaning man cleaning man like
god who's the boss was he when
he was a housekeeper
oh i think made murderer
the cleaner the cleaner angels going to
be with his body
hey angela who's the boss hey the
different who's the boss who is like
the accent was on who's yeah who's
the boss yes the boss who's up
who's v boss yeah
um and then his daughter is as
blossoming into a young woman and there
were lie there was a scene of
high t ma her name was tina
lie and there was a scene of
her of course this was at an
age when this would be burned into
my brain yeah of her run urging
the the ocean yeah and like she's
holly berry skin super
her hot like it's wild like that
was the this was not a movie
for kids i don't that's how battleship
was it was it's fucking razor sexualized
like blame it on rio it was
the it's not andre the giant what's
the french country three thousand
home
on three hours oh wait thousand whole
time easy but this is why i
think he's onto a trey muse the
guy he he he was in green
card with andie macdowell oh yeah wow
yeah daniel do he had one with
like katherine heigl where she's like yeah
teen yeah my guy row my dad
toto my father
either they hear my father the hero
insanity yeah yeah and then and then
you write the blame it on rio
one i was just doing research on
it because i think i saw that
instead of a movie that we watch
for my other show ah the the
girl in that is seventeen and had
to get a special dispensation from the
courts to be nude in it no
yeah
that court is wild
i have a laugh riot talking about
sophie's choice ah yeah it was it
was it was funny i was doing
last night oh yeah yeah it was
good i mean it was a while
i've never seen it i've ever seen
that movie and i assumed the same
thing that you did about it but
yes really sad know that well all
set in a concentration camp but looks
like it's all set in and i
guess i should watch you know war
time germany don't know if you showed
her but she's great in it i'd
like to see it too emotional i
have to cross my lips because i
watch any movie that has a character
named stinky oh yes sting
or sting or sting ghosting being it
sting go steve ow sting yeah moe
any of the jackass so i watch
everything with oprah sting
yes and so you haven't seen the
color purple jackass so if he's no
i have i i oh i suddenly
saw this movie that's all i'm collecting
them all you have a pretty good
match to watch with those names pretty
good bad remedies new batch i watch
any batch yeah
what are the other batch movies the
bachelor the bachelor ones absolute yes can't
wait for the next i can't wait
did you know that abraham abraham lincoln
was the first bachelor
well that's what they based the bachelor
tv about is his like trouble sleeping
away lincoln
who was james buchanan who was the
gay president who's oh it was the
bachelor his sister was the first lady
to have you heard that let that
like kind of underground belief that like
every president was gay every everyone no
i have not heard that
and that's how they get the job
like to present day i made it
up
that's a good one there's some there
a secret inauguration where they have to
suck a dick
but they'd want to they get it
yeah yeah yeah they're allowed to yes
in front of everyone's gotta be a
good one for the pray and ask
any good old i mean they don't
think damn someone they like pick of
the litter
kevin do not make that title do
not make that man god damnit kevin
apparently on our last episode we all
told stories we've told before who cares
yeah okay i mean fuck this is
what happens with friendship yeah but you
hear people's stories again and then you
free guys everyone close to us now
because look i actually didn't remember that
they totally in those stories and i
remember that i told mine so i
also don't know if we've told them
all on this podcast or
this other podcast yeah okay yeah oh
you and i got the new phone
oh i yeah you gotta to me
too
no you'll get the same way this
is a twin didn't even talk you
get the thirteen i got the third
distal yeah i do every other gentlemen
spams i haven't done one
spams calling spam spam hello
if you put the speaker genius i
did spam hung up you you they
hung up on me you gotta be
so lame they're upside down
loser hurts anyway i love this phone
um the picture quality fantastic i haven't
gotten one in like four years and
and mine was fine until the other
day ah i was ah exiting my
bathroom and it slipped out of my
hands and was plunging towards the toilet
and i batted it away
a like a like a baseball player
i was not paying attention for sucking
your dick yes my yeah yeah bad
music one hundred and twelve yeah anyone
flying across the room and and broke
the screen well that's own that's a
blessing for you because you got the
good new one yeah so i got
the good new one and they just
smashed my phone get a new phone
yeah well
well i was able to trade mine
and get like four hundred bucks back
i showed the pieces i wasn't mine
was cracked so i was yeah we
go back my my phone carrier will
always tell me you're up for an
upgrade and then when i see what
the upgrade is like that's not really
an upgrade yeah i know that's always
like bullshit yeah an upgrade is like
you know a sweet instead of a
hotel i think it's the next
the newer model of the phone yeah
right like not not the newest yep
not necessarily the newest yeah if it's
just newer than the one that yeah
i don't think that's good you have
to you with these phones you'll say
oh nice same phone we got good
for dispatching k what's the difference did
you get the wallet that slaps onto
the back of the magnet
the wet mike up a wallet that
slaps onto the back when yep this
can hold magnets and you can put
the roll a little ma'am wallet and
slap it i don't have a wallet
that slim i have too much you
have to buy and it's has puts
credit cards and oh credit cards ended
okay i okay i need
need all my credit cards i need
my license i need my aaa card
i need my sag card i need
my dga card any my insurer use
medical and dental i need my santee
card and i'm a director do you
both carry folded thick wallets no no
no ah i i go very slimline
these days because
nice guy oh i took a little
money boston so i have two credit
cards my life doesn't clone my money
my cat and i yeah it hasn't
a monogram on the back don't mind
if i do you have to ask
all laughing you simply have to ah
it has to be thin because i
carried in the front pocket because i
used to carry my wallet in the
back pocket
and i read a thing of that
fucks your backup really bad effects your
backup it's easier to pick pocketed yeah
but from just oh because you're sitting
on it and stuff yes yeah genius
well i'm like how does it fall
into your bag because it's so heavy
you're walking like who the director oh
my ass meanwhile if it's at the
front have like george constanza his wallets
fatter than you remember
her and then the wallet exploded and
do you remember when seinfeld would say
what's the deal with and so forth
and so on such and such and
you and you remember and do you
remember when he made a movie about
the invention of pop tart and do
you do all you going think it's
coming out yeah you're gonna start it
all the nice thing about all of
a sudden after think about all the
movies that are not getting made but
that is good eyesight emily gordon writing
a plato movie yeah so that's great
i'm happy for she's hilarious but i'm
thinking this means that every i p
in the world every product is fodder
for something no i think battleship on
the door can be like whoa
oh thanks girl can become something yeah
yeah yeah gumby for instance can be
oh what if they cross over if
we finally go into gumby gumby is
made out of plato oh my god
do you think he's made out well
what the fuck do you play it
was always going to be gumby gumby
i made him out of class right
exactly great but when you watch gumby
gumby yummy okay
right that's established as fact it's stuck
let's make sure we always did that
gumby is great i love coffee i
love oh he's a piece of know
i love you i love camila poco
of the woman one i love em
all but when you see it now
it's weird it's very weird it's like
soviet feeling yeah it's so yeah it's
very it's very bleak and yeah
i'm like gray and yeah odd when
i was having fifteen they gumby just
became a thing again i remember yeah
so i think because like eddie murphy
i'm going to be dead weight out
from the past i think yeah i'll
see what i was doing my childhood
it was very funny because no one
had ever talked about gumby but you
but then a few
years later must talk about gumby we
all pretended it didn't happen but we
knew that it did few years later
whoever owned the gumby thing started making
t-shirts and stuff and started yeah and
started selling them again yeah and so
i got a gumby i got a
gumby t-shirt and i'm like i don't
even it's yeah it was a stroke
of irony lucky yeah hop culture i
don't even like as a kid you're
like one of my doing
fifteen year old boy doesn't mean he
wants to be a man someday i
have a gumby and pokey miniature in
my minis collection your minis collection have
a collection of miniatures oh mister expansive
um that's ironic yeah yeah yeah it's
it's also anything anything sm
small i collect my sonny angel dolls
anything worse my sonny angel don't lose
again which are these little dogs that
are this tall um compared to something
i don't know okay yeah one cho
showed up
it looks like a choke just the
size of a penny angel those but
the size of a joke a little
cherubic little enjoy enjoy huh and they
have they have animal heads on a
very charming and funny and making human
bodies with animal hits yeah they have
animal like um like just really new
genus oh and
and the vagina next you know and
make an i found them in ohio
first but then we thought that was
something we just found in a random
store and then we started seeing them
in a random stores in different places
we traveled and so we realised okay
these are we have we would only
allow ourselves to buy two one v
one each every time we would see
them because there's an you don't know
what's in the blind box
oh i like ten and so yeah
but you can blink like to yeah
topps baseball cards yeah tops shift and
so now we have a pretty good
collection choose a collaboration top chef tops
chefs where you have to make the
bubble gum yes every recipe is bubblegum
sounds or has bubble gum in it
hello chefs today
they were making pink and here's your
special ingredient oh i bet it's bubblegum
i can't really yeah hard gum oh
yeah absolutely oh the harder the better
ones yet to come the tighter the
sweater but anyways the whole collection of
miniatures of all different types of how
many do you have and how much
spaces to take i have one shelf
dedicated to this and i would say
i have
probably somewhere around sixty miniatures and i
probably have forty or more sonny angel
dolls that's gotta you're looking to swap
out dvds for these cho dolls
i started selling a lot of my
old stuff ah times are tough leaning
out towels i mean cleaning out ah
times are tough and i don't want
a website or how are you doing
it ah the electronic bay i believe
now they ebay that people float in
on and so do you have someone
like doing it for you kind of
like upload
and things ah no it takes about
nine hours of my day every day
but yeah
oh yeah i'm doing it full time
job my book no benefits some of
the some of those some some toys
and games some yeah just a bunch
of stuff just getting rid of ah
clearing space you know and try not
to buy as much stuff yeah i'm
trying to buy more stuff lately
tryna make myself buy things there's something
i want to buy now but used
to give me so much joy but
now there's nothing i know i'm so
sorry you don't do retail therapy anymore
no there's nothing i want i can't
even buy clothes because i never go
anywhere
just underwear it's all i ever use
anymore baba says it's the year of
bold underwear yeah and bomba really does
thank you bombus we thank you for
these blessing god bless you obama signed
an ad they don't i don't think
they've ever done an ad for us
but yeah every show i do love
their song i like their socks to
mambas i had the
out of spam box from the bahamas
which were great oh baby oh are
they fucking adorable they're really easy to
have a lot of styles i would
like them to send me more please
you must ah do you fight off
the urge to just continually by holly
clay i do i what i have
done when i really want to do
that is i buy things for when
she's big i need
yeah well that was before don't ever
grow these clothes you'll be my light
clothes for the sunny angel dolls which
people make if you go searching on
etsy i wish i was so excited
about but this was all before yeah
that american girls store we've must um
yeah we've talked but we hit oh
yeah right bye bye but i'll definitely
take her there when the time comes
oh yeah
two american girls to hand down to
her um how lots of things for
them um and they don't make mine
anymore so it's like really exciting oh
wow they've branched out so much they
don't even make these but but but
i was going to say i whenever
i want to buy things for hollywood
buy things for when she's bigger yeah
i got her like a coke so
and she's like
four but it's so cute i got
her a maternity he was like a
splurge but i was like i need
this but if i buy it for
her right now some porthole wear it
and
anyways
i try to your suffering chief yeah
yeah studying up for bifocals well time
capsule it's great oh and this one
you're old yeah great stuff love it
it would be ah yeah i can
only imagine especially with like cool up
in our previous dog rocky of course
dear sweet rocky when she bought him
like thirty
one hollowed-out outfit for the entire month
of october yes i get it can
just be very tempted so fun i
really had to hollywood costumes she was
it's like you can't really hold back
you know it's yeah st patrick's only
she didn't have the same patrick by
the time well by the time she's
like thirteen or whatever will be over
yeah it's a you only get so
many times and we got like when
i get to control
even better please remember it's wild to
me to think of these kids i
think about this a lot when i
see my friends baby pictures that they
are going to have this vast archive
of their live show are you looking
at baby pictures of your friend
i want ny
all jokes aside i think that i
would know it by losing baby pictures
of my friends
i would love to see that but
it is true it's like we you
know you have a limited amount of
fun because i i think you meant
like your friends pictures of their baby
yeah that is yeah yeah okay great
i'm just explaining but you know what
i once i tweeted once because somebody
tweeted this your tweet i tweeted once
and so i was like i don't
get it oh he
wrote i remembered this to get i
remember that tweet that like i wish
that was my only this tweet that
stayed with me for a while somebody
tweeted something about um ah how cool
it would be to hold your friends
as babies oh yeah we've talked about
this well i'm on my own if
you want my rebel video if you
want to feel compassion for someone you
should should hold them
as a baby that's why the way
he blew go back and kill hitler
as a baby they can't do it
because he's so fucking cute with that
little tiny mustache
but today tweet about the reaction that
people have that it was weird yeah
maybe you just talked about this now
and whatever one yeah everyone was like
oh you're looking weirdo who wants to
hold your most people were like this
is very sweet and some people were
like this is disturbing i'm like why
is it disturbed they don't have a
adult head or something it's like they're
naturally what oh what people people were
simple likes
people with baby bodies and adult people
were saying it's a consent issue like
to hold your friend says i'm like
two-page fucking dirty their parents would give
you consent baby likes to be held
but it's like the idea was if
you go if you could go back
in time it's like oh so you
some weirdo goes back in time and
hold this this stranger baby i'm like
no you introduce yourself to their parents
you say you're
time traveler how about a friend of
theirs in the future yes may i
hold your baby like in the scenario
why wouldn't you assume that that is
i'll take that yeah yeah expect you
know what i mean why do you
assume like you you break into someone's
house like fuck is wrong murdered the
parents yeah you hold the data for
two seconds but back in the crib
i don't think i tell my body
i don't think anyone has a
a ah issue with the fact that
they were held by various people when
they were a baby if yes you're
just being held exactly i was there's
a family friend of ours who used
to tickle me when i would go
well that's a consent and that because
your name was elmo yeah then you
actually interesting point
but it it used to drive me
fucking crazy and i still had eighteen
ethical no that's not good would do
it to the extent where i would
be crying and and like weeping and
i would just be like oh come
on perverted that's yeah that sounds like
it's not perverted it's like sounds good
it's not good i just i just
felt like i feel like if a
kid is saying
hey you like i thought like this
even even like hey i don't like
to hug strangers you should be like
no totally do you instead of parents
going like go hug this person or
whatever it's like hey do you want
to hug this person now see that
yeah that to me i like i
think that's a good thing that we're
now doing where we're not making kids
do a thing they don't want to
do yeah
yeah but if they're a little blob
of course they're awesome around yeah i
mean well you can show some really
on a lazy susan friends with little
kids when they're like stop tickling with
a new stop and they're like wanting
you to do it one yeah yeah
because they like it it's like that's
different like there's some kids really hate
it when i was that this was
when my friends had a
a ah he was like a toddler
at this point we were in a
car driving somewhere and i was in
the backseat with this little boy who's
very precious and adorable he's he's a
great big fellow now he's like really
knowledge and ship whoa but he had
a little stuffed ah pokemon toy i
think this from the pokemon world poly
world it was like this little idea
little blue dude and i was saying
who is that and he had say
it's polyol i was pretending to get
the name wrong and he would correct
me and he was like laughing at
first and then i we were doing
it for awhile and then at one
point he fucking started crying like out
of frustration like it's bob
ali whirl and i like the shift
was so fast from this dude this
dumb dude doesn't know the name correctly
using and now it's like i got
big her who is this fucking door
say his name on mike
because we got to shame him mark
zuckerberg mark supper supper huh
supper birth mark zuckerberg
wow um we take a break we
gotta take a break we'll be right
back did you say polywood pile up
oh holly world will be right back
oop i wouldn't move there ooh
amor back and ah over the break
we we had a meal break we
have thanksgiving dinner irl but the break
we had a meal there yeah heard
my heel over the break are you
doing it anyway it's better it's better
yeah yeah a little bruise i put
some balm on
oh and some salve um mid-south by
the way everybody not solved it's not
south it's not solved too many i've
been hearing this more and more yeah
there are too many times that say
so many words that are just too
confusing
how many do away with them there's
at least three yeah that's fair number
three words today's world threw me for
a loop actual oh i got it
in three bro team trying to get
an accent on the last letter yeah
do you know what until for me
i'm like spilling what's a french word
to so and that's why it's also
home that's part of it i'm going
this isn't even all right
three thousand i will
i mean and they had another one
recently that was possibly not english and
really are no i can remember what
it was today's was saute everyone which
i in my mind thought was spelled
with two e's me too and that
was part of why it was when
i was going is is one of
those and i just guessed yeah right
then i googled it and i was
like wow
but i didn't know that and were
my guest right before that was saw
me too which is like another food
word and mine before it was ah
ha hot oh how do you say
la la totally toronto queen yeah which
is another french word that you wear
out but wow
oh andre yeah
anyway we all play world every day
ever since the anyway took over butts
but there are changed so in our
in our text of attack shane of
a people one person never writes anything
yeah ever ever another person can only
tell the truth one person is always
sitting but then too so so she
it's no surprise she's not going
but then there are two su no
surprise she was playing every day she'd
exact tell us doesn't tell us but
then there are two who refused to
play like they're above it all i
know my now my stomach yeah i
think they sickened me isn't it annoying
to get our updates every day if
you don't even play why don't you
play when you can get a response
from the
lurker on your text thread oh it
is a brig day um really they'll
learn to go to call him actually
texted me privately one time i was
completely shocked that credible i'll see her
in person every oh it's a herb
oh i see she did she say
please take me off the texture yeah
she was like i really hate hearing
from paul and scott so huh
ah i i said i understand but
you have to stay it's things like
couples thing so text so text threads
obviously were a lifeline to people when
the pandemic happen where we couldn't see
people and again ah but are they
going to continue my lifeline becomes my
deadline
metallica
what's the thing that when you think
of the beginning of the pandemic that
you think of most about her personal
existence like what like for me i
think about how i was like i
got onto subscription box of like random
vegetables because for some reason oh i
was like roasting them all the time
i was always eating roasted vegetables remember
how how hard it was to
toilet paper and then there was a
local restaurant and restaurants local restaurants were
like oh shit no one's ever gonna
come in and they were like trying
to figure out ways to yeah to
to get money and so this one
local restaurant was like hey we've ah
you know for three hundred dollars or
something we're gonna we have all of
the ingredients for stuff and we'll give
you this care package of eggs and
no eggs
milk or really eggs especially were very
hardy so we're gonna give you eggs
and milk and toilet paper and then
meats and then cheeses and then a
suit of clothes of wine right and
a guy to cook it so so
the package me i wanna live with
you and we're like okay we need
toilet paper we need eggs let's let's
get this
and then it was like one roll
of toilet paper no like one meat
six eggs one cut of me right
and then like three hundred dollars and
you committed fifteen bottles of wine oh
my it was like they were just
trying to clear out there weinstein which
does make sense i remember leading mostly
what i remember about korans he was
is treating half a bottle of wine
every night yeah yeah i also ordered
toilet paper from office depot and so
i had a giant size roll that
i was working through for a long
time like i got i gave one
i had six of them and besides
like the back like a wheel of
cheese save a one way and then
i went through the rest of them
i just kept going i've got to
ask speaking of toilet paper bill this
is going
and now you have to ask this
yes so how do you use it
and do you wipe
yeah because i use you just lose
my bone neat about whaling god oh
my yeah oh no okay so he's
that an ad car you could at
least have said the dogs so this
is an issue going on for us
right now why do they make the
this thin toilet paper it has no
use it for cheapskates or for plot
bad plumbing
oh you see it and you have
like which if you have a plumbing
because you're cheapskate but if you have
that thing where it doesn't you don't
flush a normal toilet yeah you have
to use that but but but but
you see it okay so nobody's ever
more awkward everybody it's everywhere it's everywhere
and then we we get a whole
we got like us a twenty four
pack of toy
the paper or something like that open
it up and much to our chagrin
it's all super super fuckin yeah it's
just not usable don't you know make
my favorite brand should i say it
now is yeah well we want we
want thomas why is it risky because
if another toy paper wants to have
but but ads for let them compete
for it okay could my favorite my
fav
everett toilet paper i've after trying it
i'm trying them all shit wipers cottonelle
ribbed toilet paper over her pleasure yeah
wow um it's so good it's so
such because you know of some other
brands are a little bit dusty with
how thick they are it's like almost
like nasty yeah yeah yeah these are
very well-made do you ever
have this like you go to blow
your nose and you accidentally inhale the
tissue dusty oh i've never thought about
it but i'm sure it's happened tissue
dust because it's just been sitting there
like like no like the fibres of
the tissue some tissue has like yeah
real white dust right yeah interesting well
i mean this is my plea stop
making it stop disguising it so that
you people
accidentally buy it in the store like
or call it extra thin as it'll
yeah there's some like chair yeah yeah
i'm saying i really thin tissue and
then i i sometimes i like that
and sometimes it gets really annoying i
can't wait to finish the box i
can use a good box i remember
when i was broke like stealing toilet
paper from work house yeah yeah
oh you've got to steal it oh
yeah but off it was that super
mister show i think the paper yeah
sure but if you're stealing it it
doesn't matter know exactly it's great it
was just thank god you're here yeah
yeah yeah but it was when you
have money from starbucks a few times
oh well that's that's a crime against
humanity yeah because the next person doesn't
have any
people will know i mean they were
the starbucks employees going to steal they
come to my house they do a
coffee oh that's weird
they want the good stuff yeah not
starbucks um but i and i feel
like i've done it relatively recently like
why like within the last seven years
like you are like oh wow we're
like oh i just need this i
don't really get blackout i don't remember
what situation it was but i remember
being in a starbucks and going like
well i guess i gotta steal this
toilet paper yes it's like you couldn't
walk gorda cbs i can't remember what
situation i was in maybe this was
i was going through like terrible times
back in like two thousand and two
so maybe it was his long long
time ago compared to seven years yeah
no but yeah maybe it just feels
like seven but yeah it's terrible time
usually seven
doesn't to all of my work dried
up and then every every company that
i did have worked with wouldn't pay
me and they just would not pay
me for a year sometimes that's trying
to remember i hate fighting i had
a terrible time like that and i
remember like asking my management for money
i like you give me a loan
somehow and they're like lee don't do
that my manager okay very nicely my
manager did give me alone which got
me out of certain situations i manage
but but it was it was one
of those situations where it was like
the wwe ga the writers guild of
america you need to pay us ah
this money or else we are not
releasing your check
check to you and i was like
but i need the check to pay
you and they're like yeah well sorry
you're gonna have to find takeaway out
of the check yes you hold all
the power yes but it's really dumb
i remember i had to lean i'm
sorry go oh no go ahead i
believe it on my finances because i'm
like oh yeah i have never paid
tax liens because i never had money
ah
it's like why also the government can't
make you what is that called on
attitude recently gone i go saying i
did but i read there there is
a certain group of like libertarianism oh
yes like there's no such thing as
tax there's no such thing as taxes
that that in fact like speeding tickets
and stuff like that they can't make
you do that right um
there was one that i saw there
was like ah when the officer gives
you a ticket they need to say
that they're a collection agency ah and
if they don't do that then then
legally you are not allowed to pay
like all these fucking weird wackos who
think that here's what i think yeah
is that speeding tickets yes there's there
should be a ticket for that like
that's dangerous right you're in
injuring people yeah parking ticket unless it's
like urine like like by a hydrant
every parking ticket should be ten bucks
you'd i feel like you'd make so
much more much our parking but then
people there like seventy dollars sometimes but
that's partly why people depend on what
the what the thing is you know
well here's because it was ten everyone
would just be doing an old yeah
exactly but they make more money here's
the theory that people say is like
would you pay
an eighty dollars to park wherever you
wanted right in the city anytime right
and we'll just never pay for a
meter and you'll get like four parking
tickets a year and ah but so
that's two eighty per year yeah it's
like two dollars two hundred and eighty
dollars to park where ever you want
in the city for free yeah i
mean it adds up here
it's the most it does yeah and
now you you it's not free on
saturdays and well the signs are always
like not after tuesday but don't look
down if you see a sign the
new got
yeah hey wednesday tuesday like what there
were never make sense so many years
where i had so many parking tickets
that went into collection the parking tickets
speeding tickets that when i would be
pulled over by a cop i would
just like start sweating because i knew
if they ran my license i'd be
going to jail and like everything would
be impounded i would just be like
everything the car me like comic books
and i and i feel like i'm
pounded together to be fun use your
cum you use your car you are
i just drive right all over him
doing donuts in the jail cell
ah but oh yeah so but two
thousand and two was terrible my car
was ah repossessed repossessed twice first time
i got it back second time they
were like we're not giving this back
to you and then it cost me
thirty thousand dollars to have it repossessed
that's so much money yeah and then
it was it was at a point
where i was like i remember my
dad was over visiting me i was
like
oh man the del taco ninety nine
cent menu is it's so good because
you can get this this you know
it's like a thirty two year old
and he was like he's like yeah
what are you doing with your life
is this show business thing where yeah
hey turn it around that's right you
turn it around bright eyes turn yeah
now that i get a little below
lu i got it out wow
nevada
ooh la la la la la la
la la da da da
a da
i like that song it's a great
simon right so it's a classic jim
steinman absolutely the drama the stein man
it's absolutely fantastic yeah
it's so good it's maybe the best
thing ever written
what's some good tv you watch right
now i'll give you one that drop
out what is that oh the drama
and to see frida as elizabeth holmes
oh yeah yeah like we need to
figure out thoroughness i wish to figure
out how to kill thanos
i audition for that film you don't
get that that's i don't is it
is it from ah don't worry okay
you'll find oh oh hey i would
like maybe the kids don't understand what
the kids are gonna love it wow
okay whatever kids don't expect kids are
gonna love us back to the oh
you're not ready for that for those
kids are gonna learn kids are gonna
love cousin marv
that's one of those things where it's
like this joke isn't worth it it's
not worth no logic what's ah the
back to the future oh yeah it
was great it's your cousin marvin berry
this is the new sound you've been
looking for of it i hate it
i hated it loved it i sat
there just holding my belly but you
are a child and now
your child must put away childish things
wait was it to tell me that
joke and i'll show you how much
i laugh at it right now oh
okay so he's playing johnny b goode
marty mcfly right there maybe remain today
email you and your name your new
domain name to me baby baby dang
thing there's a young black man off
to the side hey he
is it the time in which he
lives judy herrell do now much better
today doo doo doo he picks up
the phone all lose yes oh totally
bearings you've had about he said hey
chuck it's your cousin marvin marvin berry
you know that new sound you've been
looking for well listen to this
ah you've already heard this joke before
yeah i love it that was so
sad
this is me just retelling a debate
even busy
oh yeah i actually laughed like oh
i don't think maybe i've ever been
in a theater where people are laughing
they have like very specific in an
annoying irritating laffey yes i have sometimes
i've been the one on stage you
actually talking about sometimes that they are
calling something yeah allergies do you do
eject them
if you're recording it oh yeah i
stop everything down and all secure caddy
stop having fun there was a certain
con okay what would do what was
your role that he should run the
dropout oh well i i later saw
it being played by this actor william
h macy
disgraced actor ah william h he was
barely disgraced helping me grady go to
jail because he let his wife take
things on one of those calls i
remember that very vividly at least one
of those talk about famous but but
but but but it's true we'll never
get them as guess that's so funny
addition for that yeah why did they
do that i don't know if they're
looking for
backup if they can't afford the person
they actually want and then i tried
to do the i know that it's
just far and wide it's up but
if if the if your starting point
is william h macy or whatever a
few people who are very very famous
you before you get to me like
ok i guess remember when absolutely everyone
but marilyn mers-cov is the wife where
it's like
that would be a great pairing shy
i think so i would have had
a ball being her husband on that
show life men didn't like me dead
live i'm so sorry remember when famous
people would turn down roles and were
choosy now yeah exactly now they get
and then roles were like available for
people like yeah and hell they now
they take anything yeah because everything is
everything is only five episode everything five
episodes there's no um judgment about doing
tv like they're yeah exactly exactly yeah
i texted you guys about that ah
the pinocchio movie oh yeah that i
got this this was you were gonna
play the nose
i got an idea
ah what did i want to be
a real pizza um i got i
got this additional quarantine to play jiminy
cricket in the new version of pinocchio
and i was like and and the
notes were so specific it's like we're
trying to match the voice of the
nineteen forties pinocchio jiminy cricket and
um here's what it sounds like the
center of this reference and you know
like i do impressions and like i
did a pretty good job and i
even sang the song which was not
a requirement issue which i can do
pretty well still and then i'm finally
like i was like whatever happened with
that right and i looked it up
and it's joseph gordon levitt yeah
well the audition process was rigorous but
he made it through he made it
i count to hear that i had
an audition too i'm sure will be
exactly what they asked for i had
an addition to two for the voice
of a character the actress had passed
away who did this character i'm not
going to talk about what it was
we've we've talked about go ahead personally
no show did i say things good
i know i think we've talked about
oh i don't personally hand and give
us those juicy deets here it's better
than just telling a story again is
it better than here for five hundred
oh yeah i don't know i mean
i anyways it was like an iconic
character and i really worked hard on
the on the impression i and i
think i did a really good job
and that was doc brown some for
the person who got it is really
why is it blindly established voice actor
and not not like super famous and
that way but super famous in the
voice right yeah i was like that
one makes sense yeah she really really
really good yes um i was working
on it really hard but i would
have been more way more nervous yeah
two
achieve that's a very specific thing where
you say oh yeah of course that
makes sense yeah that one person does
that was one where i was like
okay yeah you know i mean like
sometimes they just drive you insane though
when you see what it is and
it's just like wow why was i
sending this into the void yes exactly
yeah exactly sometimes i feel like i
i don't get hired for stuff because
i have too many
he just too many requirements for that
like i i you know offer only
i won't learn lines
um you need to be propped up
by eighty number one on the call
sheet no matter what be carried in
on a litter and be carried in
ah what's this phase we can bernie
style yeah have to pretend to be
dead yes you have some glasses on
me and you had just up and
down
alright we have to take a break
we'll be right back
and we're back and and do people
like when paul tells us the rules
of three years
oh my god and remembers them after
he tells them to us to people
like that part of the show that
was one of the funniest things it
was very fun it was very fun
i thought i was going to burst
a blood again in my defence it
was very hard to have to keep
going back and looking up the rules
again when you would close it i
wouldn't call it well because i would
just go to another i had to
go but the funny i keep going
back and forth between traps it's impossible
to write three things for each topic
but you were you'd any letter you
want it's like well no i'm i'm
one or three movies and timewise i
didn't mean
i think i didn't think it was
possible to think of three women's names
did you find a game yeah i
did okay tell us like i always
do i call it games this gets
three loren loren people love this shut
your damn mouth it's everyone's favorite it's
the three cheer that gets
not a game what's your headline it's
a wooden japanese that like it makes
oh i tell you i like to
think yeah just cute thanks it's cute
with cao cao three the games just
have to use my mouse josh satomi
like he's going to josh safdie as
my mursi as my mouse this is
a three cheer okaka ah
and so on cause you don't know
what the encore yeah the heading of
this doc is unused games on ios
game guys guys yeah yeah i was
kevin barr tells news when he wrote
like j josh richman was miami's or
onca on us guy and he's right
this is called let's try that again
so no guidance for india's job
so it is really hard to get
highlights to say guys josh boone space
for news games this is called let's
try that again submitted by nick oh
did you two ferries go through the
door at the window
we're on the set of perry's no
he didn't say fairies what was the
pixies pixies right picks up jud the
pixies go true to dora trudeau window
out the door to the window out
we are on the set of a
huge hollywood blockbuster each player is assigned
the role of either the star the
director or the studio executive the star
decides on a phrase or line of
dialogue
ugh that they are going to deliver
example i'm mad as hell and i'm
not gonna take it anymore class on
each reading the studio executive picks a
celebrity that they would like the star
to emulate in their reading they communicate
this to the director through text and
it's the job of the director to
coach the star into reading their line
in the style of that celebrity what
the direct
you may read that part over just
that part what just that part just
just start over way
join me treating the studio executive picks
a celebrity that they would like to
star to emulate in their reading okay
they communicate this to the director too
who then has to hear how do
they go through text got it um
it's wine wednesday guys and it's the
job of the director to coach the
star into reading the line in the
style of that celebrity without mentioning who
the celebrity is or yes the director
has to get has to say reddit
more okay this way so the studios
negative tells the director i want to
like this and then and then the
director directs the star to try to
get them to say it and the
impact without using that person's dapper yes
exactly the director must only instruct the
star in the way they are saying
that piece of dial
log try a lower tone but a
bit more nasal yeah read it like
you've been smoking one hundred cigarettes a
day and slower the star should piece
together this celebrity's identity and only through
only through those commands the director cannot
give hints to their identity and every
other matter so you can't say like
reverend jim from taxi yeah yeah okay
great let's do it who wants the
aim of the games for the star
to figure out which celeb
charity they're being coached to resemble them
the studio executive picks another or the
rolls rotate okay yeah we're gonna row
to join to be the the whatever
who wants to be what i'll be
the i'll be the director okay i'll
be the star okay i'll be the
studio executive former babysitter yeah okay so
you text okay
you and you you're the director i
start yeah you come up and challenge
scott you're the director and then lions
gosh well i think the executive should
also give the line it's more to
do well good point okay yeah yeah
good paint okay give give ah learn
her lines studio executive the line is
oh is it a is it a
line that exists or it can be
it can be when you make it
up the line exists i'll never forget
you and i'll always be in your
heart okay okay and you've got those
stars named person eating an itex the
star to scott rice yeah
so practice your line for i'll never
forget you and you'll always be in
my heart that's good cooler off book
but yeah i worked in it for
weeks thanks to my grouchy mold oh
okay yeah what's your i mean what's
your motivation just i'll never forget them
and i'll always be in my heart
well that's yeah that's yeah motivation yeah
that line yeah in particular yeah yeah
yeah okay it's sold on
in this ah you give her some
direction or something yeah do you could
you say more like a man-child kind
of ah yeah a little bit another
ah i'll never i'll never forget you
but you'll always be my heart less
that sounds a little too new york
could you make it back east
east but more of a boston kind
of i'll never forget ya but you'll
always be in my heart okay little
more high pitched i'll know if i
get chat which i'll always be in
my head but sounding like a like
a ah baby who has mental problems
and as i live i live forget
yeah let's do three yeah adam sandler
yeah yeah baby yeah he's actually my
first guess but i couldn't figure out
what i was doing and i was
like i'll just try to get there
um ok okay we know yeah scott
r paul's the star scott's the studios
director and okay and so you text
me and you tell paul align okay
paul i want you to say oh
my god this earthquake is making the
earth shake oh my god this earthquake
is
making the earth shake that's great oh
let me just confer president if you
could just work on that a little
bit the earthquake oh my god this
earthquake is making the earth shake i
love that this earthquake is mickey i
love that could use tip yeah okay
um paul who hires yes no i
did it's ok he's fantastic he's
it's easy approval though
we're going to have it by the
end of the day so it's the
end of the day this is the
first shot mark you the studio yeah
okay approve it sorry paul i don't
can go back to video village watch
this we work together yeah afford video
we've worked together so many times i
watch the ah yes um can you
say the line again oh my god
this earthquake is making the earth shake
i love that can you do it
like you're older oh my god this
earthquake is making the earth shake more
of a woman oh my god this
earthquake is making the earth shake and
keep your teeth closer together oh my
god this earthquake is making the earth
shake and get a little shaky
with it oh my god this earthquake
is making the earth shake and keep
your teeth close together oh my god
this is craig is making the urge
yeah this is getting really good is
it katherine hepburn no um a little
sillier oh my god there's jake yeah
is it jerry lou no um give
me time to keep my teeth closed
right i think it sounds really good
how you doing maybe yeah keep those
s h sounds going so let's kind
of hear that oh my god this
earthquake is really the sri that's really
good this week is really the earth
sure yeah older older old yeah
okay i'll tell all being direct oh
sorry oh please oh god this earthquake
is very much
and miller and give it real competence
oh
she shaky but confident yeah and you're
shaky is just from your age oh
god is this earthquake issue make easy
earth to shoot and really give it
to give it to your scene partner
louder louder definitely louder you could open
your mouth a little bit
but keep the teeth kind of wanting
to come close to o la earthquake
is you have a chic you're really
nailing it i mean give any more
guesses and hook cartman right try to
list for just even more
lizard esses yeah
more like you have um your tongue
and cheek or kindness yeah your dentures
are coming yeah and coming had this
earthquake if making me hey is it
zelda rubinstein from poltergeist no no she
did we just say oh yeah i'd
have no idea carol channing you really
saw like but if you
told me to stretch it out a
little bit oh my good earthquake yeah
baking he urged hey maybe replaced a
shake maybe a death i was trying
to lead you yeah yeah and i
think i didn't agree yeah you do
yeah he's great a lot like like
yeah yeah okay so now paulist director
scott star i get to tex paul
a celebrity and utah
scott align okay now you're you're the
producer right so yeah it's almost anyone
oh i tell you yeah okay i
tell paul who is going to be
and the answer is
meanwhile i'm here trying to learn okay
and the line is i wish i
could get this plant to grow okay
i wish i could get this plant
to grow i wish i could get
this plant to grow i wish i
could get this plant to grow that's
great that's great i have yeah let's
try this yeah um more
laid back i wish i could get
this plant to grow okay more like
that level of laid-back more plants grow
more thoughtful i wish i could get
this plant to grow know oh okay
sorry um seems like that's what you're
going maybe not
thoughtful but almost wistful like laid-back wistful
wish i could get this plant to
grow is that wistful
grow um but but you're not sad
i wish i could get this plant
to grow that's better that's been yeah
now i want i wanna give it
a little bit of ah ah sort
of ah ah panhandle flavor like um
like a little ah little texas
wish i could get this plant to
grow ah wish i could get this
plant to grow sorry that's a direct
that's yeah can you kind of i'm
the director yeah i'm talking to you
who's yeah who's this well sorry i
knew a studio executive who butted in
and i remember the director shut him
down so hard and do you want
me to try know
okay um thank you so not recruiting
your yeah that's a little too southern
moral texas like you know like we
always trying to get this plant to
grow
yeah but but no that that that's
better but remember like think like george
w bush is you know it's texas
you know
but don't come with george come on
over here hammy you don't don't hear
me that was actually closer that was
that was close we get this planting
but remember laid back okay you're you're
thinking fondly about this place i want
every outhouse every ah small tommy lee
jones sure yeah sort of like every
smaller house
small house every big house every outhouse
so that's accent think of that for
the accent okay then again laid back
i wish i could get this plant
to grow and then director i just
have even more slow it down we
take your time i could get this
plant to grow director i have a
tip that i think is okay i'm
not i didn't think that was our
relationship but go ahead because i actually
used to be a director
just like a few minutes ago right
what were you drinking i remember you
ago i feel like i remember you're
the one in the story when the
when the the the studio executive buttered
in yeah and you stopped him right
yeah because it was not his turn
to happen now that i'm gonna sue
you actually understand you see a lot
of ah it's fine i'd like to
be a studio i'm gonna actually put
out i'm gonna put out great okay
i wish i could get this plant
to grow slow it down ah wish
your get you're getting a little southern
now it's like ooh yeah don't do
that don't do the wish i could
get this plant to grow get remember
texas you have that i mean that
yes shimmy high on your shoes i
wish i could get this plant
to grow a wish i could get
this plant be younger be younger a
wish i could get this plant to
grow not more energetic no but that's
doing so i wish i could get
this plant to grow
wish i could get this plant to
say no say it like giving guesses
no say it like it's the most
like it's a it's a wild thing
that you're thinking about
i wish i could get this plant
to grow but like take the energy
down a wish shocking get this plant
to grow
give it give it a little give
it a little wow in your mind
i wish i could get this plant
to grow that's good it's good wish
i could get this plant to grow
do you want to join please suggest
something yeah keep your mouth really tight
wish i could get this plant to
grow are you happy yeah you know
what this just needs one other person
who can guess
who can guess it from that impress
oh yeah and showed me i can
barely hear it when i'm doing yeah
okay what if the what if we
do one round where the director comes
up with the the person and then
the producer is trying to get and
then the producer wins when the producer
goes by the way who am i
owen wilson oh wow wish i could
get this plant to grow
wow um where the producer is basically
like no don't do it like owen
wilson and that means they went oh
you know what i mean okay okay
one round like that okay yeah i'll
be the i'll be the the purdue
i'll be the producer since we started
there okay you're the star okay and
then you're the director okay okay
so you you are you have you
come up with the name the person
in your mind and you also give
me the line and then i can
give you the line okay i will
give me more to do and then
you you come up in your minds
and your steering her towards that okay
okay so the line is um who
put this cat in the basement
we all know he's an attic cat
who put this cat in the basement
we all know he's an addict cat
okay um is you say
i'm gonna say huh it's good
make it like that's good first of
all thanks um i think for this
character budget personally i would i'd say
like let's shoot how about a little
more ah hesitant at times
but this cat in the basement okay
and then like sort of um a
deeper voice who put this cat in
the basement when we all know it's
an attic cat
that's good and more um
make it sort of like you're you're
you're realizing the words as you're saying
them who put this cat in the
not like christopher walken know this is
i didn't think those oh okay alright
alright this is an attic cat
now a drew barrymore either no i
didn't think that was like okay right
and so that's great and then add
in a little um excitement a little
ah like random excitement who put this
cat and the basement this this is
an adult cat okay not so much
excitement as wonder who put
this cat in the basement this isn't
don't do it like nicole kidman in
that amc ad yes please don't do
that i would say um you can
be with your halting you can you
can be even stammering a little bit
who put through who put this cat
in in the basement this
this isn't an attic
this is really coming along yeah i
like this a lot okay except i
feel like it's too much like ah
oh man it does sound like drew
barrymore it's me i know i think
it is ah who put this ah
no one more i guess more you
know and what do you guys kristin
stewart know i would
not even begin to know what that
sounds like interesting okay i keep going
when all right so when on a
writer know you you your your um
your voice is ah is deep that's
good ah sorts of halting stammering um
a little bit of wonder your your
sort of excited
to be discovering these words as you're
saying them who put this cat in
in the basement this isn't added cat
okay i like that geez this is
tough i don't know i mean it
sounds like something i don't think i've
ever made who is it jeff goldblum
ah says
yeah who who who who who who
who
that hoo hoo boo that he isn't
happy this this is just somatic cat
foo who put this cat this cat
basement this is an attic cat yeah
that's yeah that's good yeah i love
him so much yeah he's fantastic i
always think like when i see him
in a thing i always think i'm
not going to like it like i
know a shtick or whatever yeah but
then i always end up really what
does that old movie that i watched
the first time a few years those
are easy know it's um wherever why
it's like a group of friends and
a big shoe yeah i loved it
it's good movie you know like the
movie ah that's not i'm no fan
of that one but um janey loves
them
i learned i love zach trophy oh
yeah heard it through the grape band
that soundtrack ouzo at the like when
i was a kid when that movie
came out that soundtrack got so played
out one of the people who played
it out was me i had the
soundtrack and i played it like for
whatever the songs on it it's like
my girl i'm like ain't too proud
the bag
hers is a great sign for whores
the great bad all those all those
golden oldies yeah and then it's got
to the point where like i can't
hear those songs anymore now there to
play yeah yeah but it's always fun
alright wow we did it gain yes
it i was fun that's our reacher
that's our show thank you for listening
we're freedom usa at gmail and ah
on twitter and instagram and you want
to hear ad-free versions go to stitcher
premium or cvb world dot com and
we'll be back next week with more
definitely be back this week there's no
but this cat in the basement this
is an an attic cat cat um
we'll see next time woo
uh