for da for ya i love getting
out early
just wow
fuck i think he's put his feet
up oh yeah
you have so much time to hang
out oh my god i had the
best time how can i wow all
got here early and he also said
all three three his early were you
last in the pool for the whole
song yes yeah yeah all hell how
early did you arrive to the high
early did you arrive put it at
ninety minutes
it's it's just noting that the door
was locked door was locked we got
the book which you sent me an
irritated text knock knock
no it was irritated because i take
everything every text as your ah that
tells ella were you doing at ten
am that you couldn't just do an
episode with him
shoot of at least spaces for you
to talk yeah yeah yeah wow does
ah we should do one like that
where one of us is scripted and
the other is not like are we
never say who would write i think
i'd be really clear
how can you see the shuffling of
papers yeah that would be actually clue
i kind of do like that idea
oh thank you so much script the
whole episode and not tell people that
that is granted yes i don't like
that idea that sounds like work oh
yeah what if we just record one
write it all out and then re-record
it reading lines
i'm sorry that's huh
but only in a very stilted oh
do as best you can i think
i've done that several times with rob
buble and tom lennon you've done what
that idea where they reenact the conversation
they have on the first episode come
right back really from just from a
transcript from a transcript so sick of
my ideas being done alright i know
but
just did it but what if we
what if we did it like we're
reading court transcripts yeah yeah and we
say yeah paul yeah we share names
before we say our lines we say
our names before we say yeah yeah
laugh during your portrait paul you don't
laugh during it some people probably do
after a court transcript lawrence the funniest
card
transport for oh there is the one
good guy that's like that juggling guy
jumped off and i got a look
at a crocodile's mouth and he farted
on his way down i gotta look
at that there's a great one
whenever i hear the true crime buff
i love well because i watched dateline
i don't really anymore you know did
you i used to like dateline a
lot and i don't know what changed
but mike really doesn't care for that
kind of true crime and so that's
part of it
what kind is he like well i
don't think he's really into like the
bite-size husband killed wife storylines i say
you know like sort of like like
things he'd like some more he doesn't
listen to treat to what is it
called true crime and just start almost
scenario life but he listens more like
last podcast on the left but they
get into like stuff like that but
then they'll delve very deeply sure he
doesn't just lie
listen to like chess moves he does
do over and over he watches channel
coupon three literally i don't know what's
going on he's very excited because one
of his guys is in the world
cup whose guys yeah which is in
what world chess oh guys magnet and
he would laugh as magnet man
yes i had the one name that
i'd have to read out loud i
had dinner with my cash alas you
did how much cash we had a
wonderful he said he had a great
time yeah it was really i thought
i was gonna text you and say
you're going to stand them up because
um you've been avoiding joyous space times
every time yes but that would have
been epic yeah everyone in africa for
sure
well i like the around sometimes i
do fuck when a girl seduces me
and tells me all of these from
donald sterling's trying to be fail tells
me how much she wants to suck
okay there there's lockup there's a really
funny there's guy i'm just looking for
some time did you enjoy the food
but that was in him was it
no that was someone reading it do
you know i did enjoy the food
oh here only okay can i say
more on that later okay well i
fool around sometimes i do when a
girl seduces me and tells me all
of these hot stove every dirty thing
now that you want to talk about
what we talked about the funniest corn
transit is acting as if it's you
doing ah so a girl seduces me
and tell
as me all of these hot stories
and dirty things and tells me how
much he wants to suck on me
and takes my shoes right likes my
feet and touches me i'm one wants
to suck on me just say take
my shoes off and lick my feet
tennis say yeah when i'm in a
limousine she takes off know all over
herself donald sterling's toes the limo driver
said what is going on
eat though and she started sucking me
on the way to mr doesn't mean
and i thank her i thank her
for making me feel good i'm saying
she's sucking me sir the question was
is this your handwriting however you know
that's really no
what a freak i've i feel remiss
because i don't think i've thanked enough
of my sexual partners for the sex
from yeah one year later once why
i think you should always say thank
you for someone like me everyone i've
ever had sex with
mr getting me up here i appreciate
it for getting right ya didn't even
help me getting up here i just
appreciate it so before i'm saying no
well yeah so yes i like the
mood it was it was very rich
i had a very rich ah cavatelli
with lamb ragu without naming this restaurant
i just don't feel like um they
do have a menu that's half
handwritten and the lighting is very dark
now i find those to be issued
well okay what's worse dark handwritten menu
or qr code menu at that point
you got have a qr i'm kind
of sorry or i'm sick yours but
i'd rather that than read ah shaky
handwritten in the dark i also went
to place the other day that didn't
even say anything they just sat you
down there was a little tiny thing
on the table that if you weren't
looking rolf yeah on a ship hey
joe was marco
you are cool as a little pimp
it was just a little tiny thing
that you could miss if you weren't
looking for it and then no one
ever came by for another ten minutes
and it was like oh i guess
here's that they never said like there's
a k they need to say because
also qr codes prepayment emic were like
something you had completely ignored and they
want hundred yeah maybe like enter a
sweep ca absolut
last thing i'm gonna do yeah my
phone i'm not doing that feature now
it's like we're expected to ever fucking
bay and i don't know why but
you know what i like is like
i don't want looking at my phone
when i'm with a friend so if
i'm looking at the menu on the
phone it feels like yeah it feels
something else because then you love doing
switch over to instagram i started liking
checking yeah yeah
my ear buds in yeah jim caviezel
in his intros for that movie he
just did because he's cabal how's ray
ah we gotta do it we're gonna
cure it um he's like okay i
know this is such a another christ
he's like you you wonder how to
get involved and help out i know
this is why
weird i know it's weird to do
in a theater but just take out
your phone and pointed at this qr
code down here at the bottom i
know it's a strange thing to do
but you can it's okay to do
it strange what where's this happening you
know that a movie theater yeah the
movie just put out like the the
q movie i don't know but
not a cute movie yeah know boy
oh boy is this real yeah boy
oh boy and i made like one
hundred million dollars israel yes did he
do this with one friend mel gibson
i don't know what this is it's
a movie about a documentary no it's
a it's a fictional movie about and
pardon me if i get any of
these details wrong pardon me it's i'll
excuse you it's about a ah it's
about a real life person who in
the movie he goes around saving
children from child trafficking oh and in
in real life the person didn't do
any of that okay and ah but
ah but it's it's it's a cute
movie that's meant to ah traumatize people
to child trafficking so much that they
get involved in q and on essentially
yeah and they just start shooting people
all over the place exactly so but
anyway
he he didn't in real life he
did not save children but he did
traffic children yes something like that yes
nice guy who who allies was the
biggest investor in this well allegedly people
who sure people hide in plain sight
it happens all the time i'm hiding
in plain sight right now and you
guys are looking right well i found
you you know my i started watching
recently which is almost
the true crime doc was the sort
of docu series about glee and the
sort of like the curse of the
cat occurs of the cast of glee
has more than one person died yes
yeah how many three three yeah it
is a curse yeah what are your
papers i mean wow mother had dinner
with lesnar yeah of course you did
yeah and how was that it was
very good with joey greer
the food is very rich yeah every
time so it was very rich afterwards
went to see a show you did
he came home yes ah chris smith
ah very funny you think you're i
did this show called acting for times
such as this yeah i'm sorry posts
and i really want to see this
that guy's really funny i just shows
wall-to-wall laughs
and i was laughing so like deep
laughing so much that i always throw
up that's the best ever because of
the the dinner and i'm like oh
i do here because i'm not sure
how funny it was no it was
funny but usually i can find things
funny without funding plus i get every
but i was really like what what
do i do here because i am
still enjoying the show yeah what how
is there a way i can curb
this feeling so tragedy plus time equals
comedy yeah comedy plus dinner equals vomit
yeah wow makes son so tragedy plus
time plus dinner equals vomit
what paul you're probably asleep
wake up we got weird crew for
a week of poe pulling
he was going oh my god am
i still asleep ou is where your
friends from your during the talking hey
you look like scott and look what
i'm doing usually knows from you drank
because you can only imagine skimming come
when you know yeah who else you
know look like bem who else do
you know anyone west
i named janie na name one hundred
people you know no i don't know
him though i don't love him the
way
your week whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
your raison of the christ save yourself
he woke up singing passion of the
christ again
stop doing it normal do you want
stream sounds normal so q who is
normal she's the grey cat from garfield
yeah i didn't know normal had a
gender and airmiles his girlfriend going to
look up normals gender talking about lorien
get it get the facts going normal
is the is the cutest cat that
garfield's gel
alice mail
normally small grey hey tommy hayes let
me see with thick eyelash showing me
the picture there's no picture this is
words there's no picture you want picture
this just words google google didn't serve
up a picture shopping your fellow man
our field has been converted to
worse sorry that looks like a romantic
image with tiger comic strip will from
now on just be jim davis writing
down what he thinks happens to garfield
not funny either just in general thanks
normal a male cat who has gone
i lost weight we were right there
sweaters are this is the live read
comics this is huge this is huge
what his dick yeah yeah some fans
have mistaken normal for a female kitten
because of his eyelids
one right here his seemingly feminine personality
and the feminine sounding tone of his
voice on garfield and friends oh okay
how many signs do we need hold
on jim davis often gives younger characters
eyelashes including garfield himself in the garfield
segment of garfield his nine lives and
orson at the beginning of the u
s acres comic strip okay the ga
airfield segment of garfield
yeah the latin american dub of garfield
and friends this is maybe what you
were watching normal renamed telmo and his
gender changed to female after season one
telmo was changed back to normal despite
this normals gender only changed back to
male near the end of this series
okay the interesting thing there is the
reason why not the timeline why did
they jay yeah why did they change
it back because the eyelashes have been
because people were just like who is
like dating a guy they were like
that's telmo okay yeah that's tell ma
it's not normal i think it should
be illegal firm rules for normal to
change to tell normal also
and vice versa no na normal to
me and our moza woman's name yeah
it's a beautiful name it's stunning i
love it you're almost you almost named
holly normal i almost did but then
i learned in the future that it
was actually a boy cat and i
thought that my oh right i just
didn't and then you memory wiped yourself
yeah right now
but you have so fluid nowadays i
think normal could be ah okay whatever
he wants to remove or she or
they well yeah but i yeah i
think you know what what it is
is as a child when i'm watching
a show they're showing a long eyelash
cat that looks female and was watching
a show i see a long eyelash
cat ice house
female yeah there is a long reddit
thread normals gender debate yeah well google
solved it in one fell swoop but
what do they say do that google
solves and says i'll swoop see what
comes up keep the conversation civil though
no downloading no downloading you should be
allowed to downvote you can
just say it's a bad opinion
i refuse to believe normal as a
boy boy this is there's a lot
of things i'm getting on there later
the six most wet gendered characters on
tv and it was this written pat
okay this is three months ago the
six most mis gendered characters on tv
okay okay oh only six months ago
um who do you think is in
there cudi bluey blue hoodie what do
you think bluey is bluey is female
but that's very easy to call bluey
male because because dog blue is a
male
color to blue dog yeah and she's
easy okay tails in sonic the hedgehog
is a measure i don't know
ah so they don't tell you what
it is i don't know don draper
people just make the mistake but he
does not think it's don draper don
draper
okay is is her full name don
draper don draper don draper why what
that's seventy more like hundred per oh
it's a beautiful name is hello entrepreneur
the voyage of the dripper your close
blue in blues clues is i don't
know oh he's attractive girl puppy it
doesn't have like facts about it underneath
it's a religion does not list which
gender is a mad article spot in
tn
gee no one does it that is
the cat of date oh sure oh
yeah that kind is often mis gendered
tweety bird huh honey bird is female
at the end of the day tweety
bird is a male canary and and
i just did what happens before the
end of the day i just did
that bluey from blu-ray whoa thank you
louise gender has never addressed but make
no mistakes there is a girl and
so is her saturday dressed up and
say
hey often will say oh oh guess
she needs to he's over there bubble
button and i go i miss gendering
louis does holly known just holly say
mom your i hate you know you
know i don't think she is on
that level yet are you worried about
that when she's gonna be like thirteen
although it hurt my feelings a lot
but you know it's gonna be like
how many damn indoors how many times
have you told your parents you hate
them i actually don't think that i
ever did i don't know that i
ever said i hate you i don't
think they have i wasn't really punished
in a way where i didn't mean
that someone makes
did you ever let them know i
think i let them you should tell
them on their deathbeds yeah i hate
you who is willing to tell you
i've never really said it but
i know we don't talk about this
but feelings i despise you goodbye i
think ever i think if you parent
right they'll never say yeah um interesting
theory yeah if you do it perfectly
if you do have it you just
gotta do a perfect game should be
good yeah how hard could it be
because you just remember the things that
you didn't like about being a kid
and you're like well
i will never do that exciting and
then your child walk no problem and
nothing you do could be annoying to
them yeah yeah i mean you know
can you picture a day when ah
when emmys screaming at you and saying
give me the fucking case of the
car dad not gonna let her drive
like martin luther king did he did
i see a day
when emi is yelling zen the second
most famous quote you give me the
fucking keys yeah or can you see
the day yeah
ah well i'll be crazy guys have
to tell you where reality recap yeah
oh i've got some updates over there
we just finished ah season for vanderpump
rule god you're doing it god you're
really cranking them out for people i
don't i can't remember if i've talked
about this or not
todd william tigers season four i can
remember the last time we recorded me
neither and we may not have been
watching it then but friends urged us
to okay so here's what we know
about present day vanderpump all we know
is there's a scandal it's referred to
as scam duvall so we have an
idea of one person that's
involved you really missed all of the
we miserable we had no idea well
i didn't know who you are but
i know a lot of what happens
in scandals in general will eventually be
called scandals yeah absolutely because this one's
so just easier to say yeah so
we don't know what the scandal is
we want to keep it that way
we're excited that we don't know want
to keep it that way do i
want to keep it that way
i do
i don't know the scandal and i
want to give it that we do
yeah nobody nobody tell him so we
are watching the show we have a
few people buy it we aren't tears
my news you you you and stuff
right before you he talks before you
talk there's people you are i was
trying to get him back on yeah
corrupting you i was track i don't
know you
great but you have friends who watched
it who are guiding you a little
bit or telling your checking that's literally
what i was about to say but
i know but i'm gonna ask you
something you because some people might want
to know what scandal is so you
can look for the signs earlier like
mister rogers so is that something that
looked for the help or i'm sorry
oh no we are that's exactly
what we're doing so you're trying to
figure out what it is yes but
what you don't want to know because
it because some people might think if
you knew the details that's more fun
because then you can watch no no
we want to be the subtle we
want to feel the full impact of
it okay yeah yeah all we know
is like for longtime watchers of the
show it rocked there you are you
putting
guesses in and into like sealed envelopes
you know what yeah of course we
are but mainly literally we actually don't
we have not discussed what we think
it is and we don't really like
as we're watching the show we don't
say wonder if it has to do
with that we we are just i
think that james is probably doing the
same thing i am which is why
wondering internally like does this have to
there's been like a few things were
like is just the beginning of it
and then we'll know but of course
we have no idea because it's been
so long time ago yeah yeah for
sorry that you know the famous quote
that's a bitcoin already that i don't
mind looking forward to i don't know
that i fuckin
so much cheese he's truly terrible um
and it's weird that we're okay so
we've been bingeing this show and i
don't think you're supposed to watch reality
tv this way because it feels disgusting
it feels disgusting that we are into
it and then we keep watching it
yeah it feels disgusting to discuss the
key
characters' motives when they're doing something as
if it's all real life it feels
bad yeah and it feels bad that
we we are sucked into it yeah
so so also deeply i find that
i find it very thank you but
yeah we're still gonna really sorry you're
going we're still gonna i know i
know the early seasons from what i
hear are all
about people who work at the same
place which i think is fine then
it becomes like none of them work
there anymore they're all influencers and then
it becomes the friend group in quotes
alright even though none of them told
me too much or have i really
well yeah yeah i think you are
saying you when you go and then
it becomes then it becomes well no
no what what i'm trying to become
yeah i'm trying to say is is
like this is every
reality show these days is i started
out with console yeah they called and
this is all of the housewives is
they call themselves the friend group when
it's they don't know you're not a
friend group they are people who have
been put together on a tv show
and they've been told they have startled
themselves even now and in c at
the end of season four where they
are all still working in the same
place except for like one two
two people i think don't work there
anymore um they're using the term friend
group right and the the really funny
thing of the one true king monster
saying including don't kick each other i'm
not kicking her i'm kicking his lead
servers like liz i don't care who
started guys just do a pulsating so
stupid yeah
um the one steroid monster named jacks
who said i'm the number one guy
sat back and like you're the new
guy in this group i'm the number
one guy which isn't really funny way
to think about yourself oh yeah who's
the number one has president that's like
hot well to me
okay yeah giving main character and are
ah alright we have to say break
and we're back
and ah i want to say i
went to a dodger game the other
day paul fans of baseball will be
interested in this i'm one i went
to dodger game recently really which one
oh number eight play how many games
the dodgers play played the play children
seventy five games a year
how many eventually
and what how many like how many
total have they kept track of that
the dodgers have played i think it's
half a billion games is true if
your channel current if you're counting brooklyn's
currency oh lord i gotta look at
how many games have the dodgers won
no i just want to say play
and then says
this season no i just want in
history in history yes
um hey lauren what are you doing
noticed i noticed somebody may shoot i
don't think there's anyone who's taken her
shoe off she's rooting around in it
because like i kind of notice there's
this like piece of fabric and the
one hundred and forty seasons
there's there's no information regarding this no
one has ever counted this we could
be the first one that's in pot
so no one has found it somebody
out there has a thing where they
count them that's their thing yes oh
hey louis okay there people are free
yeah their record is eleven thousand three
hundred and ten to nine thousand eight
hundred and eighty nine so that so
i mean it's like there's about twenty
thousand games
so which one did you go to
like twenty thousand and rose was also
on say something like oh so i
so i go to play the game
and don't look only on the basis
we own the basal i didn't know
what was going on at all literally
like let's let's stick the whole i
couldn't understand the fuckin score sign i
was like stenson it's too it is
too complicated now i
i was looking for just the score
when i know i was like where
i am there's so much information on
it but it didn't used to be
like that because i was like oh
i remember going to games growing up
and not being confused and explore i
would come out he would take the
card off but another card on but
the score was always pretty prominent in
the old days where yeah and then
there were a few things above it
now it's a
ton of info that you're just trying
so many number and hey can also
don't give you started the ads i
can't even i like when all the
the um lcd screens like switch over
to one ad and it's for forest
lawn cemetery the cemetery well in case
people don't know but also that's crazy
you mean i don't
an ad for a cemetery i'll make
you're an asshole once i'm there i'm
very close everyone's gonna figure out where
they need to go and that's going
on do you like i would bet
baseball is the sport with the oldest
fanbase
probably i don't know if
but i mean you have to be
like olden we're talking means we're talking
means we're talking baby let's go law
nobody you have to be rich and
but most people aren't rich until they're
old while there's generational wealth sure from
those old rich people at the polo
game
that's exactly right so there must be
a lotta young people there who's plan
i mean those are the people playing
it's rich it's it's literally originals how
old is the average
hello fan
forty seven
ah polo magazine offers
the average pelosi is my old is
the average baseball fan
thirty five to forty four that makes
sense
oh no sorry twenty five to thirty
four for twenty five to thirty four
twenty five m l b has the
oldest fans among the major sports with
the average age of fifty seven that's
what i'm leaning god is before you
know what they are learn to separate
facts from fiction just heard three different
takes so those are the top three
respond this doesn't tell the responses are
every
age of an adult elba as the
oldest student happened ah the avarage suitable
and when i'm doing can be doing
okay in nba oh four oh yeah
that thing that that john quinonez or
whatever that not not him but guy
from new and not him the guy
from the eighties who's like
oh what in this unsolved mystery didn't
happen that you talking about when it's
like hey it's all those keeps whatever's
no no it's like jonathan frakes okay
oh yeah beyond both of fat beyond
belief fact or fiction i always love
it i've seen that there's like a
super super cut of yeah it's great
it's just so funny when it's like
a meme and nba is
forty two for any channel is forty
nine and ffl is fifty m l
b fifty seven yeah i call it
you did call it wow thank you
and polo forty seven according to paulo
massa young man's sport it's almost our
birthdays it is almost coming right now
but i've never gotten to my store
where september babies you have a bird
it was dory when i was at
a baseball game
oh no what happened well i want
to say
i didn't know we were allowed to
say i never got to my store
all the same i never got to
my servant reality tv who i've let
so many go yeah i didn't realize
on low you'll be interested in this
sailing way it's not even a story
lazy way too that's what i call
orinoco flow and that's what i call
spread bear was a compilation cd
that's what i call orinoco flow it
was just that song volume seventy
this person doesn't know about the repeat
button
this
they think they have a compilation but
they don't it's like i give this
compilation of one song it's just to
see these i think it's the same
thing repeat now that's like oh you're
like wow
she loves it so much easier this
baggage is called tracks of oreo i
feel like now that what i call
series is disingenuous because you would feel
like the first volume would be it
it's like now that's what i call
music but but who's right
well exactly because they're not odd are
these supposed to god so he's doing
it because i mean i'm like no
that's what i call this show started
with like
no j to date so you could
teach
do you did
yeah
but
so you're at the baseball game so
and then wow huh some other baseball
eating is going what may happen i'm
at the baseball game and i'm sitting
in my seat like oh my oh
boy you could you could spare some
details yeah god whoa are you wearing
jeans and a teacher i'm ah watching
the game
with my eyes occasionally blink a ah
great i'm happy for you then what
ah one of you with i was
with okay this is unnecessary
i was with okay so we so
cool up was supposed to buy five
tickets and chanted okay only buying for
overall mass yeah that's was supposed to
buy the tickets yeah right so and
we and luckily i was like hey
where are we sitting the night before
and she goes oh let me look
at the tickets otherwise we would have
all off
i've sort of arrived oh no the
ah at the place so i stayed
home so her sister stayed home it's
like our nephew ah it was her
nephew and co-op's mother oh cool okay
the four of us core four core
four and this comes into play because
i i much like baseball so that's
not
necessary information i bought the ah this
is a side story about the woodie
call hotdogs know that you know that
the slurpee fifty tickets a fifty fifty
sure about that mean ah where they
keep half the money and they give
half the money to have whoever wins
but it's like an instant lottery
athena team who wins i'm like why
would they get the money you know
she's cool
no you pay raise the additional twenty
five thousand dollars for unders you pay
ten dollars you get five tickets and
then okay ah the the the team
keeps five dollars and the and whoever
wins gets the the other half of
the pot yes exactly so i was
like if i won
when i was going to split it
up and then i realised oh that
would be unfair to the sister who
was gonna come who didn't have the
tickets i was like alright i'll split
this five ways yeah the odds of
you winning are oh i didn't know
my goal and then i started to
think my decision worthy of king solomon
himself then i start to think should
cool up and i take one for
herself only one chair i would say
say you're a house yeah i don't
know anyway i'm twenty one a polit
a five-way oh it was fifty two
thousand dollars wow i guess so i
was like oh five ways but it
would make more sense for you to
keep one and split four ways though
at fifty two then you're talking to
what what is that no i think
fourteen thousand anyway i don't care so
so i'm ah i order from a
concessions person please one of the no
do they sell hotdogs by the dodgers
game know by hand walking or i
don't think they do walking around hot
dog i don't think so they only
sell leads to idle stationery right yeah
you have to go get a hot
dog but i think you can get
european ups hot dogs don't come to
you you go to them in raja
then you're going like i need rela
shiny meals like they used to be
okay yes they did use yeah those
were good days those were the good
old days i'd love to have a
hotdog at the dodgers game right now
what if
i have some hotdogs upstairs what if
what if all and i look upstairs
wrestle while you eat a hotdog sure
you're just saying i wanna eat a
hotdog while i watch a sport yeah
oh okay okay okay okay okay so
then why do you have like the
hatch because this was a tangent so
what was the main so the main
is that that i there's a concessions
gentlemen who have you done this before
who has the ah as a delicious
tangent i would say if you get
four tangents by the way i fuckin
that has to be over now what
shared plates hold i went to a
restaurant the other day for the first
time and and they're like have you
ever dined with us before i'm like
here we go and of course they're
talking about tops and he's like ok
this is chef andreas who
revolutionize the topics in america and and
all of these i don't know who
to believe all of these are meant
to be of course to be shared
and and they recommend ah one one
appetizer per person plus one plate and
then omit to mains plus a plate
and it's like i looked down at
the prices and everything is like
forty nine dollars everything full probably because
she's sharing prices now fuck yeah hey
i do have a place that i'm
enjoying lately that is a shared plate
what's nice you don't wanna blow up
this kind of blow it up i'll
just tell you tell us yeah off
mike but i've been enjoying i go
there with two people about once a
month we're actually switching our location next
month but
we liked the same things you don't
mean to it's easy if you're going
i also want that same place with
two people where one had different dietary
restrictions and that mess up the whole
situ elevating the oh yeah shit all
eating like don't eat grapefruit motherfucker i
want to know we always say that
everyone but what's weird is we we
can't have grapefruit because of both cool
and i are both on ah staten
which is a cholesterol drug and it
inhibits the enzyme in your ah in
your balls it gets the hose again
yes so but but it's pretty common
i think but what's weird is is
everyone ah you go to a restaurant
they'll say like do you have any
dietary restrictions we will say oh grapefruit
and everyone looks at us like we're
cr
crazy like that you that you both
are like no great food it's like
it's a little specific no gleeful and
how common is it in a dish
side rom but i think it's a
common drug but now out of apple
tail but people don't know yes because
i'm saying i never heard it that
toe right now but now we're yeah
but the things you don't know it
could fill a fucking book hey
oh nah nah nah nah nah nah
hey goodbye yeah i'm in my car
like okay my dad's lived to citrus
so my whole life i've been aware
of that but grapefruit only that and
i'm just saying that if you work
in the restaurant business i think it
would be a common thing people go
like oh i kind of grapefruit because
a lot of people around this drug
does there's also other drugs it's not
like grapefruit is not allowed to be
used in cooking
like jat know they had the last
restaurant we were at they had one
grape of thing and they were like
oh yeah well there's a desert that
has great prudent other than that we
don't you know but most of the
time we get like grapefruit away so
yeah i always kind of want to
be the person who like eat to
have a great fruit at breakfast but
i just really can't do it i
used to yeah
before the sugar on it
you know sometimes i would yeah okay
so you're at wrestling and you're eating
a grapefruit what happened
so i ordered listener i order an
ice cream sandwich from the oh that's
fun and yeah i've flagged going to
get dipping dogs ice cream in the
future i fucking love dip and dodge
anyway i love the way they feel
in my mouth at what point i
was able to ice cream the pal
the way they feel in my knife
is there
just canceled they're almost done they're almost
done yeah like you know you'll like
the day they do you'll see a
dip adult station it's not functional you
know it's that kind of stuff i
think they took it out of the
universal city amc i don't i really
if i were to go to the
movies and the dip and dots i'd
be so happy they tore down my
uncle's house to make room for different
dots factory wow wow and now
oh the places abandoned no it was
such a cure all she knew back
in yeah should be fun little bit
of factory it will oh my god
especially dip and dots factor could be
really silly yeah it could be really
silly i mean if there's any dip
and slept over he could roll around
on them or likes or maybe he'd
trip and fall and like you know
kind of slip oh my god
so i order an ice cream sandwich
it's more like tripping nuts and i
do manipulator shit daily
trip and odds so i i've never
been more thankful but you've never been
more thankful than what you're gonna say
ah but but i pay for it
using a car by the way you
and if we went through and you're
like nah no but but now one
nine tulip still doesn't no no it's
probably four dollars let's be realistic
now is more i think it was
more six oh yeah fuckin ice cream
bar yeah probably special cream i could
see it being ten bucks i can
see they jacked the price inflation is
just so good now control but they
they now it says like tip you
know like mts ten so i'm always
like tip and datsun yep i'm always
not
for this reason but i'm always like
yes of course tip and i've never
been more thankful because i he hands
me the card back and goes in
front of god and everyone goes oh
by the way i'm a piss pig
wow
yeah he's listening right now he's listening
now hello jim oh wow what can
i say heard this story get derailed
a mill aiki is like you're talking
like yeah wade okay wow what kind
of ice cream bar was it
i don't know was it like classic
ice for you amiel yeah i think
it was gossip it was an ice
cream sandwich dear he said ice cream
sandwich at the beginning vanilla chocolate yeah
classic okay
i just feel like he was saying
either remember where
but i just started laughing and and
you know ah cool up and her
family also were laughing because it's the
first because they didn't know what it
meant well now i also have started
to feel like okay i used to
only get recognized within like one square
block over there like over by amoeba
records you know basically any business in
that area you recognize that i listened
to podcasts
yes but now i'm starting to feel
like i'm recognized everywhere they just have
never had anything to say to me
until now right saying i'm a piss
pigs really concise yes way to say
hello it's a thing people are dying
to say yeah you wanna say they
are one yes i meet them frequently
dynasty typewriter i'm always happy to meet
in pittsburgh it's true meacham gentlemen at
work i thought that was very funny
to be yeah i'm in front of
all of the other amateurs
yeah it may be there was a
funny thing i had this big another
day that was like i don't mean
to sound bragging that someone recognized me
but this was a i was at
ah one of those happy returns places
at fedex or whatever where you can
you can like return something that you
bought online from any store but then
it's like you take it without a
box and you just take it right
yes okay
then like the lady was like we
were just having a normal interaction and
she's like i can say this because
i just quit i'm a fan or
whatever like you just quit i love
that she's like shiny in the middle
of your conversation just so she could
say that yeah i'd be worth it
by the way paul what you said
reminded me then another person as he
was walking by i feel like i
contributed yeah as he was walking by
when
let's go piss pigs know what that's
next level that's to start a group
chat and nobody knows what it means
and then people start brawling and it's
to be do you consider piss to
be a curse word i think piss
pig is it sounds really derogatory yeah
it's going to be yelling it at
a you know public space
i just think punches could be thrown
yeah while they're little careful be careful
yeah yeah anyway so two two interactions
at the baseball game i absolutely love
it can i talk about the rowdy
screening oh i love to hear about
this i saw one story that looked
fun yes it was it was really
a lot of fun this is scott
scott hasn't seen mamma mia
yes mamma mia two here we go
a game on me too did a
rowdy screening at the dynasty typewriter theater
paul was our special guest you say
the role of andrew lloyd webber that's
right i love to put on a
multilayered costume in the dead of summer
huh didn't wear it really hours before
the hurricane yeah that's my guide
hurricane boats and yeah but oh man
while they were doing him a cat
there were two great chance that happened
okay ah character is revealed to be
pregnant and people started chanting pregnant brag
brag that and then mere seconds later
another care
character was revealed to be pregnant i
don't remember about that and then the
chant went up also pray that ah
ha also i was really really funny
so it's it's the it's amanda c
fringe character is is as well as
ah euler's but yes lily anyone like
her mom meryl streep z o e
james
oh it's oh it's the past before
we go to a break it was
really fun back and forth between the
past for i've only seen that one
because it was very fun before we
go to a break meet me too
by the way yeah what's your new
frazier theme song y'all know how this
goes oh no
hey baby i hear the blues call
samsung salads and scrambled casey lying in
bed was always singing and maybe i
seem a bit confused this morning but
i got you pegged
i pick you but i don't know
what to do with those tossed salads
and scrambled eggs
frazier has re entered the bill oh
no yeah what do i know what
they should say that at the end
i think it should just be the
collin again well this is for the
teaser trailer right now but it's not
that's not the theme it is but
i think he's saying frazier's reentered the
building to be like i understand i'm
coming back but i'm saying i don't
think you understand i think
re-recording the theme is fun enough for
enough for now he's gone and it's
enough yes financially get ahead on a
hat although i have to say a
hat on a hat would look cool
this is this if you put in
quality yeah on the comedy huh saying
it's a hat on a hat you're
saying that's too far to go but
how know how it is funny it's
funny i know why we've not want
to do that can you imagine being
in a
comic farce
like frazier yeah like frazier and entering
and there's a hat on your hat
at the audience would die if that
audience kind of lose their mind my
hat gets cold it needs a ha
yeah and i'm not trying to be
funny and i just want my hat
to be worn yes it's little kid
lost my hat gets cold it happens
what if that happened it's cold now
i need to know
about how frasier himself ended up singing
the song because when in the reality
of the shadows singer ah no he's
not known to me as a singer
so when did the neither frazier nor
kelsey kelsey grammer i mean i mean
both but i'm saying so the reality
of the show there's there's a prequel
episode that discussed
is how he actually came to sing
this hall no well in the reality
show where's the song coming from can
the people hear it because usually it
would be over it's over the end
credits will the recovery episode of sigh
here every episode there's a little there's
a little ah silent vignette that's happen
every episode of frasier happens the thirty
minutes
for he just happens to sing that
song so whatever whatever the thirty minutes
before he sings that song is that's
an episode but because i raise your
episodes are in real time at the
same time good senses but the song
has nothing to do with the premise
know so then it's like okay the
actor is singing a random song about
tossed salad and scrambled eggs which by
the way
i enjoy the song okay i'll be
oh you're i mean even first in
line to see a concert hello i
love now that's what i crave yeah
tossed salad and scrambled eggs every single
track but my feeling is when did
they go kelsey you want to sing
it like when does that happen in
the producers number asked him well he
goes i have a great idea for
a song what it's like
what's going on i could see that
happening did he write it or did
someone else write oh me guglielmi guo
road gatsby frazier gang song right letto
from bruce miller that movie show the
sword show look here's a whole article
the story behind the frazier theme song
guys so yes all of our questions
it's an oral history i look we
have to take a break i'll read
the article and try to encapsulate it
okay
okay we're back and this is what
the composer bruce miller essentially says is
they want something jazzy eclectic but they
need to avoid any references to specifics
of frazier so stay away from words
about psychiatry radio shows the name frazier
eh
anything so don't need daddy he wrote
the music niles
death on the nile with enough champagne
so they were just like nah here's
what's it about it's about don't say
anything about that don't say anything about
that so he wrote the lyrics and
then he's like anything it has sorry
he wrote the music than he needed
lyrics so he called his friend darryl
fantasy who's really talented and really smart
or was before this this is the
assignment that broken i can't mention psychiatry
at all
but he hadn't then he wrote a
song he was like i'm a little
girl with hearts for eyes and they
were like that works too you didn't
mention any of the things like whoa
what it could be getting
i live in a fire hydrant
he called back with the idea of
tossed salads and scrambled eggs and the
guy wrote the music is like what
are you talking about he goes well
these are things that are mixed up
like fraser's patience
oh no she's calling people crazy yeah
he's also not a psychiatrist anymore he
he's a radio host he's he's an
entertainer he yeah he's yeah he gives
advice he's basically carries podcast does he
get exactly does he oh moment does
he only do the show or does
he also treat patients no he doesn't
have a practice anymore niles
as a practice okay but frazier is
exclusively a radio host practice makes perfect
so anyway they made they made that
title for a very very shy guys
dress
our lawyers think the guy who wrote
this on doctors and their last name
is perfect
practice makes perfect okay yes hello second
can you believe they're they and this
is a new show with a great
guy skyler aston but great guy ah
yeah what does everyone so help me
todd they're still doing shows where they're
like it putting a curator zoe happening
yeah in yeah call me rachel
wasn't a fire all that dia but
they do a lot of them the
only way you can name a show
so help me tavis if it has
a theme song like the nanny or
something like that and there's an actual
corps of so duh every night i
pray to my god da se
he's an actual god and this scenario
yeah and it's like you could still
say so help me god it's like
no we're trying to differentiate tits thai
yeah max marijuana swallow law uranium ra
how does psi obey todd so to
answer your question paul vi guy who
wrote the song wanted mel torme to
sing it as
and the producers wanted kelsey to sing
it sure told you producers told you
producers
will you say that when the strike
is over i producer producers you knew
ivy i assumed it was kelsey's idea
to sing it yeah probably why producers
were i could sing it well i
wouldn't know i've been known to just
getting a tune once if mail says
no why good thing it can be
do with reacher yeah yeah well
well you said you had one so
lying if you'd like to show me
some creature you can write to three
dm usa gmail dot com they aren't
sure is called mad libs and i
you know mike and i bought this
on a whim when we were on
a little trip recently how much it
cost oh let's find out um for
ninety nine so you're paying so you're
able
to just spend four ninety nine on
a whim i can just throw it
and not even care i should mad
libs cos when we were kids i
don't have twenty five cents or something
you'd get them through the scholastic like
the elastic book club yeah oh i
loved it dynamite magazine so i thought
me really close early werewolf during the
hurricane i did i didn't want every
cooler
wherefore yeah i got my three ah
prescription glasses during the hurricane i did
one with cool up on our texts
thread which i don't know if you
were paying attention to because it's probably
really annoying i went it was so
funny because i was trying to i
was like cleaning something up around the
house is
you will hear this and i have
a problem every morning i have to
clean up every morning i clean up
all my peers and anyways with the
hot rod constant buzzing constant bug yeah
and it's not important that all i
know the adjective all i had seen
was you say wanna do math
lib i was like i guess that
mad libs happening yeah okay so who
wants to go first mate okay i'll
go so then you will just will
each person will hold the paper and
control yes for the other person okay
so i'm not going to go to
the call
so paper control verb
ah um get shake yeah have fun
with it are we are we alternating
no number because it's gonna be his
madlib and then oh wow two thousand
and five adjective
briny
adjective
burpee noun
caboose adjective
um slot like plural noun
um because zoo's a place this is
going to be crazy narnia
adjective
um bloody
plural noun
barnacles person in the room scott
verb no animal plural um by but
but but pippi bats verb ending an
i n g
i'm going to zap fucking ah high
five and type of food plural
mashed potatoes
noun two servings of mashed potatoes i
consider mashed potatoes to be singular it's
done so in the end no noun
can you eat one mashed potato yeah
i can i could give you with
me
potato
and sorry mashed potato
essex
um active ah crummy really wasteful to
make one mesh but they get all
the mill what if it's all you
have that's true yeah crumbly known chrome
yeah um dream noun
um the the bit barry okay too
many it's done
mad libs title is amadeus mad lips
happening by paul f tompkins happening wow
run don't shake to join two thousand
and five of your closest friends at
the greatest briny outdoor musical experience of
our burpee generation this once in a
caboose event is guaranteed to provide a
salon like weekend filled with music peace
loving zoos in the picturesque setting of
narnia batch
fans such as the bloody barnacles scott
and the bats
like so fucking mashed potatoes i and
many more will be rocking the mashed
potato oh my la this crumbly happening
will take place rain or crumb so
dream accordingly it's sure to be a
legendary barry
wow that's good that takes me back
i know to ones to control do
you do scott
okay put on my spectacles okay oh
those are prescription yellows
yeah that's fun to it did you
have i used this marker it's just
chunky monkey just use it you can
use anymore you don't have to use
that chunky monkey it's true i'm gonna
leave and chunky it's chunky monkey is
everyone loving this
when he picks the pen
i think that is going on there
all the same just scribble it i'm
just trying to find one with a
better point now it looks good thank
you thank you dear okay it's got
to turn go for it alright scott
give me an adjective
yeah
gosh so many in the world how
about one
ah rafi
okay adjective braddy
person in room
let me think please me please oh
oh shit
yes
fucking out ink in the trash
ah plural noun
um
your tridents gonna have to go a
little faster
were you just trying to control my
oh yeah okay play it slow as
you want caddy my adverb
what's an perfect
that's what's happening ending in l y
o right right um
sweetly
gross
adjective
did i say baddie already know baddie
plural noun
yeah
waves
not the verb now
leaflet
plural noun
cardboards
type of liquid
tussling try to give them the next
one while you're writing that one and
it'll just help it along down
electric vehicle
adjective
let's see baddie caddy oh my god
um adjective
corpulent adverb
wonderfully
plural noun
knobs
burglar alarms plural noun
is dubois just too quick for me
um forty five rpm records now
refrigerator
um person in room oh let me
think not mean something i mean no
boring
adjective
um fetching
okay mr darcy
alright ooh it's done oh boy here
we go as a lot of pressure
what's the title world peace and other
promises by scott alckmin copyright two thousand
and nine by penguin random house oh
so you got published oh nice our
schools are voting for this year's ratty
president let's listen in as the brady
candidate paul makes his final campaign speech
my fellow tridents i know the caddy
changes you want and just readily deserve
if elected i promised to put an
end to batty homeward and pop waves
i will expand the lunch menu to
include leaflet burgers and cheese stuffed cardboards
i will fill every drinking fountain with
chocolate gasoline i will see to it
that the only acceptable exercise in gym
class is dodge electric vehicle oh gee
finally for every corpulent student in detention
i wonderfully swear to make video knobs
comic burglar alarms and wide-screen
the fuck is that
let me see
you don't know what he said wide-screen
i can't remember i said whereas it
ah wide-screen up
yeah he's pretty good glasses are up
rimmer purse yeah up remembers o rpm
record rpm record forty five rpm record
available and attention refrigerator so remember a
vote for lauren today is a vote
for a fetching school tomorrow why isn't
a different person i don't know
i would i would elect him okay
i love it great job thank you
know it's my turn alright lauren are
you ready yeah oh my gosh
here we go i'm gonna need an
adjective
sexy okay
going to need another adjective um horny
going to need another adjective i need
to go in my car
what getting me crazy lucid
yeah
plural noun um but plural nouns is
old school as this days today's got
in trouble for doing this when i
was young yeah i should think so
adjective um breasts practicals practicals
oh hey that's a adjective wow now
hello yes i do okay thank you
put a to i'll switch these okay
adjective adjective um smooth smooth okay
ah verb ending i n g um
um pogo sticking pogo sticking
okay noun um butt hole
article of clothing plural
boxer briefs
boxers or briefs
ah noun did not um tit
plural noun dicks this is like your
origin story type of liquid i wonder
how you discovered a cover
for bending nie je sucky
adjective
tasty
and noun um marital bed
mero ben marital marrow marital bed
okay here we go
this is called happy campers when life
gets too sexy there's no better antidote
than to forget the horny grind and
go camping with some loose friends
with the moon and butts twinkling overhead
and the sound of tidies chirping in
the woods sitting around the campfire and
singing a smooth chorus or two of
she'll be coming round the testicles or
i've been pogo sticking on the railroad
is a great way to restore peace
to your inner buttle
or if you choose you can scare
the boxer briefs off of everyone with
tit stories
ah just sit quietly toasting dicks and
sipping mugs of steaming piss persistent twinkling
into your sucking bag
it's yes there's nothing better than the
tasty outdoors to guarantee a good night's
marital bed days we did is and
that's easy madelyn that ain't as a
feature now look we also in addition
to accepting emails from you if you
want to phone call us then we
take a phone call
and you quickly with the voicemail we
had our number hag claims ached hag
claims eight and if you wanna hear
ad-free episodes of this maybe you already
are currently go to cb world dot
com that's where ad-free episodes can be
heard and also ah there was one
other thing right and follow us on
instagram three
mm usa yes ah any shows coming
up anybody nope well i have newcomers
we have a new season coming out
we're gonna be nicole and i are
gonna be what nicole byer and i'll
be watching all of batman and so
far it's been i'm gonna say so
far it's been what it is you
have to live your life turns out
to be like as of this recording
how many are you in i have
watched
ched the third assignment so it's the
second i mean yeah when stood the
assign yeah i won't even say i
guess which movies yeah they are because
that's part of fun yeah so yeah
um but it's been it's been ah
it's been a time i'll say yeah
i'm sure it hasn't um you have
a show coming up huh yes ah
where are we in this
comes out thursday shit then i have
to tell you that um tonight um
ah super ego and i we are
doing our forgotten classics show where we
take a book a famous book that
none of us has ever read and
we take the first line the last
line of the book and the character
names we improvise
guys what we think it is or
should be about love i'm sure i
like you guys doing what it should
be yeah yeah this is i'm gonna
do should be like the original authors
that fucking idiot
i mean that's not for me to
say yeah we'll find out ah but
that is ah going to be live
tonight at dynasty typewriter i think ah
tickets were close to selling out so
as of this recording um if you
can't be there you can watch it
on the livestream we are live streaming
it to the world seven thirty eight
yeah so
civic time um in the book we're
doing is ulysses which famously has a
last sentence of four thousand words so
we'll see i handle that how you
gonna read that i don't fucking know
why um so yeah that's gonna be
a lot of fun ah please do
check that out and then um september
tenth at la
a room in highland park of myself
and nicole parker doing our first two
person variety shows something for everyone it
was called please do get tickets for
that yes well that's it we'll see
around these parts next week so folks
hold onto your hats and glasses
folks alright bye-bye bike
uh