three
ah
oh um hey little darlin woo wow
my name is not scott aquaman my
name is not lauren lucas my name
is paul f tompkins fuck and that's
why
this is the paul f tompkins show
global liftoff to shoot the ball at
tommy joe were all named paul f
tompkins that's why this is the paul
f tompkins show what a beautiful world
that would be would that be what
if it was everyone was named paul
f tompkins he was just the inflection
told you what the difference between yeah
so that's what i'm saying that's what
i want yeah paul would you
want to clone yourself for any reason
oh no not even to live forever
but i wouldn't be living forever you
mean for for like spare parts ah
yeah well what situation would there be
where you would clone yourself and be
okay with it umm i can't think
of any even if it was just
like here's a you with a perfect
organs already to go and came to
oregon that's already for us thank you
so much
my brain that's right my answer is
orbis yeah well they always get job
that would your epidermis is showing oh
show paul what if you have you
ever wanted to be two places at
the same time
in a multiplicity kind of situation i
don't think that i have you don't
know i don't want to be in
one place at one time but i
would even have but then that's not
really you're not being two places your
clone is being one point know but
but like what if what if you
could be two places at the same
time and your consciousness you could see
both places at the same
in time like in a split screen
like dr manhattan and you're operating on
a higher level of being and you
are existing within two locations having equally
good time in both i guess i
would like to be a higher level
of being if i'm having a good
time yes well you're having a bad
time in both well it's possible
that you get in a fight in
one of them but you're having a
good time with the other oh yeah
what if i what if i like
getting the fight because i'm a messy
bitch who loves drama oh my god
do you do you don't tell me
what it was but have you had
a fight recently like in your life
like a fist fight know like a
fight like not like not like an
argument with janie but like just someone
hoping
oh well because that's different that's not
really what i mean like i mean
like jane is the only version ball
seen in a year but like with
a fray i know a parking lot
or something no it's been i think
it's been quite a while since i've
had any kind of like you know
verbal argument with somebody yeah yeah maybe
it's a message that's a silver
or lighting to the pandemic fewer arguments
i think the thing that's true i
think the pandemic there was a period
of adjustment at the beginning where it
was like oh no we need to
figure our lives out while we're doing
this and the way we were living
our lives is not the way we
have to live our
lives now so it led to a
couple of arguments where it was like
just like about day-to-day stuff like you
know like people being like you're not
following the rules or that kind of
thing or just like what are the
rules anymore like we need to figure
that out like oh if we're the
only people we're gonna see what are
the rules like what are we doing
here so it led to a lead
to a couple of arguments oh you
men
do you mean in in your household
you don't mean like the world is
the society um yeah we had we
definitely had some tense moments where it
was like but but i will give
us credit that we recognized it instantly
for what it was yeah which is
like we're not supposed to be seeing
because you're just mush you i just
said it last night to mike i
was like normally
we are a part like three months
probably total a year like we're we're
traveling and doing other things not sure
yeah just from all the time i
spent three months are shitting you know
just crazy huh i'm outside he take
shitting it a year adds up to
three months three months of years
and then for urine and then six
months per year of sleeping yeah you
only really get three months is that
when i sleep six months of sleeping
no no you know it's probably it's
for it's four months of sleeping probably
but what did they say you spend
a third of your life was your
dad's
it's a third of your day so
today's your day is made up of
your life is made up of days
four months of sleeping three months of
shitting that gives you five months of
like awake non shitting yeah go time
then that's pissing that's true then why
do you have left you spend her
jobs eight months a year pissing
some of that overlaps with the shitting
and the sleeping oh yeah that's unfortunate
oh boy
right off the jump right off the
jump drive we aren't watching ah lauren
would you clone yourself no i mean
i don't know it seems like clones
are always dumb or annoying and i'm
already both in what it is like
again fiction it feels like they're always
like the clones
i was doing something either evil or
annoying and you're like oh well he's
gonna make some where there and do
this thing and it's gonna look like
i'm saying that well she say the
clone doesn't have your memories or anything
like that it's like true a true
clone like you know how their classroom
and stuff like that is true comments
of course hey there's the title um
but you know it's like
where suddenly like there's a clone of
view but it's a baby right wow
and it's gonna grow up and have
it's own memories and life and all
that nbc and it's own babies it's
own club babies but it is a
clone of view it's not like a
purely like it's not a child that
you have born if you know that's
weird
like baby i don't think i would
want that because then it's like you
would you would have such a hard
time not laying your own shit onto
that baby because it's like like hey
don't get loose because actually like me
and i'd be like oh no now
you're gonna be making all the same
mistakes and it'll be hard to watch
i'd be like hey here's what
happened to me in my life like
physically here are your challenges to try
to stay away from this because you're
like because of all your shame want
to beat you up you have the
same genetics as me here's what you're
gonna go through don't take off your
underwear in front of anyone
oh
i would say like if i were
talking to myself anyone anyone at all
like myself and in middle school or
something i'd be like start working out
and like yeah i'm like do things
that are athletic and just i would
tell myself to get over a lot
of the things that i'm kind of
like that took me too long to
come around too well that yeah i
don't
don't think that i had any idea
of how like the body worked in
a way of like okay so when
i was growing up i was razor
thin like i had a super high
metabolism skinny as a needle and exams
like a twenty five or twenty six
at all slowed down and it was
like and i didn't know that this
happened to people
and i was like wait i was
going to be super six hundred pound
man and you've got that yesterday about
you and then every picture of me
having your photo shot on those motorcycles
every picture me my twin is just
out of frame
but we're well i'm on a motorcycle
in every picture if you've noticed i
would i i wish that i never
smoked i would definitely tell myself to
not to stick to my guns because
why not what high school i was
like smoking is stupid right then when
i got out in the world and
i was trying to be older than
i was um i started smoking
ng and i would i would tell
myself no you're right stick to your
guns don't know what do it what
if young you was like this old
guy's stupid i'm not gonna listen to
him would you physically like slap cigarettes
out of his hand like would you
follow him around and
what am i the old me or
the young me now you're old you
what i slap no i'm not going
to slapped what
okay so i'm assuming the situation is
the young version of me knows who
i am
i'm not some old man well yeah
hard to not put it together right
yeah well yeah you know what for
me i yeah did you look like
you looked as a kid like i
don't feel like i mean i think
in elementary school i started to look
like me but like up until before
that i don't think people would say
that was me if they saw a
picture of me i don't know if
if you look like you if twenty
one year old me saw me now
i don't think he would be like
is that me
yeah it's kinda my point i guess
like it's like i still just think
that was some lady but i may
do you eat do you ever look
at somebody who people tell you you
look like and say if they hadn't
told you that would you say hey
that looks like me may i gotta
say hey you look like this ugly
person twitter is the worst
hi i'm like what happens in real
life that's the best
yeah oh um but no no the
kid knows who you are you're you're
let's even say you're the kid's dad
like you've taken him on as a
parent and you're sneezing at him and
your
show him what he's in store for
yeah but so but but did you
listen everything your dad said no so
this kid wouldn't let anything this kid
wouldn't listen to you either would you
just tell him once like oh hey
by the way smoking stupid but scott
it's entirely different
to have your dad say something give
you advice or whatever then your dad
and your future your future self to
say look i've been there here's what
you shouldn't do that's so different because
they're going like but you're further all
the things happening to your body when
you start doing this and all the
things haven't your brain and i'm all
the time to try to quit
and bubble blah and then you might
go look i i think if my
future self told me that to do
something i might listen yeah right but
you're saying it's not time travel you're
saying it's just a clone that it's
being ruined that i'm a bass the
same dna as you so like technically
nothing happened to you that you know
of from smoking other than just
you know you have no effects right
so you can't even say no but
i did i did i did rank
you know and it's also so cute
colossal waste of money it sure shocks
but i mean it's all the stuff
that we know about his kids right
yeah we all we all know that
kind of stuff and yet people still
smoke so so i think it would
be interesting if like someone got cancer
acer from something and said hey you
are one of the one in your
or three in ten people who is
going to get you know lung cancer
from this so you need to stay
away from it then i would go
oh okay great good tip well that's
you i'm saying it does i think
it also depends what age you're talking
we arguing clone
i want you to fight
morin you ain't going to be financed
finance yes that's why i asked about
the fines anyone had a vey recently
do you want to have one now
over a lot of room
hello a little bit of the above
i think it would also depend on
the age at which you're telling the
clone all these things that if they're
fifteen they're probably not going to fucking
listen to you even if it right
you from the windows of your clone
listened to you i think i think
maybe in your in the early
twenties maybe you could you could get
through to them and say look i
have to tell you this now this
is the this year's what happened here's
what happened in my body and so
you're gonna get to like take care
of this exactly i think it should
be earlier because it's like hey you
know what here's how to wash your
face correctly like er here's how you
don't get like bags
under your eyes different though that's it's
okay
you know what i mean like yes
i think there's a lot as everyone
else everyone thinks when they're young oh
that's never going to happen to me
and then than it does right so
it's like hey at around ah you
know forty five you're gonna start getting
bags under your eyes so here's a
way to take care of it before
then which is teenage blood yes and
that's why you're lead even that blurred
and
your eyes yeah you put it right
in your eyes
i it it's an eyewash station but
it's all blood it's all teenage blood
so cool
lauren what would you tell your clone
i mean i do think ah exercise
would be a big one but i
think like i just delayed that for
a long time than i liked exercising
once actually started doing it when i
was thirty and i liked the results
and i thought it was it felt
good for me and then i was
like why did i never do this
like
i bet you i was naturally skinny
yeah and i mean
look i still am but i like
having muscles and if if you could
be one of those bodybuilder types who's
in the string bikinis with the huge
muscles with you
yeah and you know what i would
i would almost have my pandemic my
current self tell my beginning of pandemic
self some stuff because i feel like
that would yeah oh yeah yeah just
like hey don't abandon everything you know
and like like it's like we are
but we already knew that and it's
like my feeling about i'm finally at
a place where i'm
i'm i'm lodi
what does that mean
does it mean simply discussed what
ignored heavily discussed here yard acknowledge accept
it i'll extend um i was i
finally got to a place where i
was like look you're just fucking doing
the best you can you can't like
of course there's a million things that
i wish that i had the i
wish i had the emotional strength to
do
do during this last year but i
just didn't i just yeah and you
know and so i don't know that
like already knew all the things i
should have done you know or that
would have been beneficial for me yeah
and i mean i just couldn't watch
what's happening it's true because i was
like i if i could just do
this and i'd be good and i
was like can't do it even like
one
day i want to do at the
beginning i was like i'm gonna learn
how to do the splits cause a
lot of people were posting like this
this like
thirty day stretch thing to learn how
to do the splits and i was
like i'll do that i did like
two days and i just stopped with
you as a thirty days right now
probably before of course i do it's
i'm not going to do it it's
i want to see you do this
yeah it only want to see an
audience yeah but like even just things
like that where it's like
like oh i if i just did
this five minute thing every day i
would have something to show for it
which is a five minute thing that
you could do every day and still
have some like even you know what
i mean like when i hear something
like that i'm like oh if you
do this just five minutes a day
this will happen there's nothing right even
exercising if you do something five minutes
a day is nothing
gonna happen or even like something like
if you were placed one bad snack
with a good snack once a day
for five like for like just a
simple way of doing it where it's
not like a full overhaul or expecting
yourself to do a hundred different things
but but that's but my point is
is you you like i don't think
there's anything you can do for just
five minutes a day
i think it's gotta be at least
a half hour like you you're practicing
guitar or exercising or anything like that
like it's gotta you gotta take a
half hour a day and then you
can get better at something but usually
it's like hours and hours you gotta
like the people who are amazing at
guitar spent their entire teenage years sitting
in their in their bedrooms just practising
scales over and
over and over and over and over
you know yeah i mean it's it's
really just a matter if i think
saying five minute today is just a
way to get yourself to do it
and once you actually start liking the
thing are getting better you would naturally
dedicate more time to it like when
i started my piano app for two
weeks that i did during the pandemic
which i'm really proud of for the
time that lasted
i was doing ten minutes but then
it would grow and grow to like
thirty or forty minutes i'm like oh
so much time has passed i just
was playing the song and then i
think like oh that was like it
felt like i actually did something and
it was good for my brain and
then i just stopped you know because
depression is not you the idea is
not you only do it for five
minutes it's like do at least five
minutes
no there's there are things out there
like exercising where it's like if you
just do this five minutes a day
you'll lose thirty pounds it's like well
what does what does
there's no one pound of your body
ah
i don't know i mean scott what
do you want to tell your your
clone yeah i wear know about the
ebags i was yeah i will serious
for you i would say smile shit
listen to me you grabbed me by
the shoulders
oh my bad you're gonna regret it
buy some concealer it's preventative measures now
that this is in a case where
their personality is whatever it is this
isn't like a person who's gonna undergo
my own experiences and all that so
it's just like purely a like hey
you put your you probably like okay
so you're fifteen right now go hang
out in the in the
the the gym at your high school
and i mean we all know more
oh it also like you don't have
to drink like soda every day and
milk every day like there's better ways
to eat although we all know that
stuff now way better than we did
back when the opponent probably know that
yeah the clone would know all that
so it's just like you know what
probably know that
your your your ah don't be too
hard on yourself your family has a
history of depression ah don't
emotional stuff for sure for sure you
know but it goes because when you
when i was a kid the only
kind of thing that anyone ever said
towards that was one day you won't
care about this and it's like that
doesn't do me any good now but
if i could if i could figure
out a way to to talk about
feelings like to teach myself skills to
deal with my feelings um you know
i'd like i would go to therapy
sooner i would have you know so
i would develop like a taste for
vegetable sooner than i did yeah there's
a lot of slow they're so gross
paul nationals
ah you're going indie you know but
i spent years and years eating fast
food every day and i yeah i
don't know that i even regret it
and think it was fine i do
you know that all of our me
you would
that is one thing where it was
like literally until i was twenty seven
twenty eight i think i ate fast
food every meal and it was over
that it was pretty extreme it was
literally like a burger and coke and
fries for every single meal and then
i remember like even the breakfast
best sandwich for browse no no but
you know what i mean i would
like cycle through taco bell and burger
places like for every single meal but
see it's so much more fun when
they're a tree yeah well now i
don't have you my little nephew is
turning five and he wants to have
mcdonalds at his birthday for everyone else
and then i
thought i need to get mcdonald's on
his birthday so that i can have
it too and feel like oh wow
yeah
yeah and he also wanted to buy
a present for everyone who is coming
and an l has idea i mean
it's like my parents and you know
it's the the immediate family but all
of his ideas were like i pad
like you to get like oh i
gotta know you know micah i'll send
him oh my god you shit you
know what appreciate that children yeah i'm
that was wild
to me when i when i started
hearing about modern birthday parties and i
guess this started one of the star
maybe in the nineties when people started
having kids that you would buy presents
for all of the kids at the
birthday party that was like nah i
don't remember that being a thing when
i was like it but not like
um gif like party fave
i don't think so guys i remember
like sort of party favor stuff but
but but literally buying a gift like
a birthday present for p yeah who'd
come to a birthday party that was
that sets seems like a rich person
in sane thing i've ever might have
been party favors it might have been
like you know those blow horn things
and yes actually pretty bad
eggs every kid gets a saxophone mo
every kid guesses next week so like
do you know people with like do
you know like rich people with kids
who are having like full-on everyone here
gets like a great gift yes i've
heard about tell me something that you've
heard it's just a who it's it's
it seems so extravagant that
these that the every first of all
is a million people right um right
coming here sawyer and all the parents
are there yeah that's that's that's a
weird one to me i yeah and
when i was a babysitter famously i
always had to go to these events
and things and or even just play
dates after school with the other
or nanny and it's like normally you
just get dropped off at someone's house
and yeah plan and those parents are
kind of the point yeah is that
you don't have to watch and talk
to birthday party for kids though is
is a lot of times an excuse
for the parents to see other parents
and hang out with them and it's
wine o'clock baby let me die feels
new slot
rich people yeah yeah to me i
feel like maybe it's not rich people
but i see a lot of it
on reality tv which is why i
have that idea but i feel like
when i was growing up the idea
is that you get a respite
an arrest from the kids
that you get to be away from
them yeah and they go to a
party for three hours and you've got
them up but but i think that's
so that's what i mean by some
birthday parties it's like okay the kids
are all being entertained over here by
the whatever and meanwhile all of the
adults are just kind of hanging out
talking amongst themselves it's more like a
split party if that makes it sounds
kind of fun as
as an die the way split partner
i think that's something if you learned
how to do it we can have
a split party over at your house
well i'd love it if everyone so
do i like drama forum am i
just getting up and doing the splits
for you realise is gonna do that
and then we watch the movie split
open
what it should be is that we
each have sixty days when i extend
the challenge to learn how to do
the splits i only have a sigh
and then we never drop a spell
that's why it's funny and then we
have parties why it's fun each always
says the best knish yeah
this this was always yeah that actually
is really it would be really funny
to judge work everyone would take out
a tape measure to see how close
their balls were to you you have
to you you will work on it
you stretch every day so it's not
going to be your go to the
hospital you just slamming your balls into
the daughter we nude yes
well no you're in c from you
know nude from the waist down because
we oh actually your crutches go into
the upstairs shirts on yeah because some
people might wear really baggy pants that
are like sagging down in there it
looks like their splits look better yeah
yeah i'd wear my juicy ripens
this was always my lie to me
though though in being in musical theater
is is like i i'm not ah
very dexterous in that way like i
have long legs but they they are
no and they don't bend that way
and so anytime you chopstick anytime you
would have to like that doesn't have
all those anytime you would have to
spread
your legs and like stretch or or
do dances where it's like you're doing
the splits or whatever i'd be like
i just can't bend that way and
it's fair but but for the swiss
party you're going to have to work
on it every day for five minutes
for sixty days okay so in sixty
days from today we're having to split
party over
yeah and i'm going to get a
platform built um for it so it's
gonna be i'll figure out who the
telus person coming is and then i
will platform from foot to foot yeah
of what if we did a think
perfect split going straight down not the
tallest person but the person with the
longest legs and i see yeah could
be an unfinished piece of wood so
that
it will be difficult to theirs you
can't slide on it because you can't
put a good face to enter without
split exactly so if like if tall
john's gonna come though his legs are
probably longer than yours nobody wins i'd
love to go leg to leg with
him will be you know there it
seems so isn't it funny when you
have friends who have
like where your proportions are totally different
like your very different heights but then
when you sit down you're the same
height or whatever because a long torso
yeah it's always funny it's so fun
hearing a tray a true fun guys
whereas this poly trends hours of polls
trends yeah heard oh so someone put
that to me
um when baby showers started to become
parties yeah it was not just like
an afternoon thing where here's all the
expensive baby shit that you need when
it became like hey come on over
we're gonna have one we're gonna dance
and all this shit and it's like
no i don't i don't want another
thing to have to
like another mandatory thing that i have
to get up to yeah i also
think baby showers they should just do
away with it just give the gifts
yeah stuff also just just if you
really need stopped off at the house
if you really need stuff to go
do like you know a one day
a week thing on a sitcom or
whatever and just buy them yourself you
know like or just just
a guest spot on something know what
you should still allow you okay i
always do it on purpose even if
you have a guest spy just still
some your artwork however this is forty
just some of your audience people are
like these insanely wealthy people with vanity
businesses and the dad needed money it's
like what are we gonna do it's
like well what are your lives
i don't remember that part of this
well they had yeah our brooks was
paul rudd's dad and he was like
kind of a deadbeat and ah he
was trying he had like an original
john lennon fuckin doodle or something and
our book is like why don't you
just sell that and give me the
money give me the money he had
and paul rebecca had his own record
hadley mccoy bomb vinyl record v me
up ignore and not really judging and
she had what she had a boutique
leslie mann have like some boutique the
oh i remember that part paul's ignoring
the mayor the entire plot this is
forty
said anything about the story
this is just the circumstance to tell
the somoza movies i feel like that
are like i like that people just
watch chen and there's like no explanation
yeah everyone's just rich yeah it's more
fun i get that it's fun to
watch people be rich on screen like
it's it's lot it's entertaining i love
watching people being richland school to to
look at sumptuous scenery is yeah you
know is enjoyable but then if those
people have problems that i'm supposed to
care about it makes it very difficult
yeah
i just remember that beginning of the
movie where he's like something but his
asshole
huh
do you do you guys any over
because asshole
is this real i don't play asshole
over and over
remember his asshole his asshole who doesn't
remember his asshole polaroids asshole i think
that was like a plot point in
the first five minutes and then i
don't remember anything else i don't know
wasn't the movie about a guy with
his asshole problems
you call this is forty do you
guys know anyone who for real looking
up asshole problems yes it's a hemorrhoid
yeah all of a sudden there's a
light on on lawrence space yeah i'm
like like like like i wrote paul
redbud whole this is forty
and then there's a video of this
image hemorrhoid and he got his legs
splayed in the error like a split
party
the first split party you guys know
anyone who seriously has had a gender
reveal party no um
no i don't that seems to me
like a person just looking for excuses
to have parties yeah i think so
and i think you know it kind
of connect citing two ways learning bit
where
like people who are just living their
lives it's a nice day to get
a lot of attention and i understand
it for that reason like it's a
fun celebration to get together and have
that moment and it's a celebration bitches
but
do you definitely don't need pyrotechnics yeah
i mean i feel like it's i
think it's proof i get why we're
we're moving on from them in general
but i also think like well if
you want to cut a cake that
has a color inside it doesn't really
drive me crazy as long as there's
no fireworks in the cake yeah i
don't want to eat fireworks and frosting
i think that we've talked about this
before about wedding stuff like it's like
party things are real it's a real
racket like they're inventing things yeah so
that they can sell shit we'll talk
about how the woman who invented gender
reveal parties regrets it yeah yes yes
yeah here's something i was thinking of
yesterday because she got the wrong gender
um
okay so i think the yearly cycle
that discussed yesterday thoughts this is my
yesterday yes today yea i had a
thought yesterday um i think the yearly
cycle that we're on for events is
too short okay i think
the game more days birthdays your what
if it gotta be like
you know like can we have them
eighteen months apart you know what i
mean like valentine's day two you're saying
don't have or don't have a birthday
every year but don't you you got
yes just no i don't i don't
agree with your yesterday it's not because
i think that it should be once
a year because it's nice to feel
the passage of time in that so
like science it's the one exception i
was going to make was christmas because
it's seasonal and you like if you
have that every eighteen months suddenly you'd
be in the summer i know our
australian friends they all do it that
way but but you know about that
enough by the way don't you think
we don't do they ever complain about
that they never complain there they just
sit there and take it what's he
doing playing about the santa
on a surfboard everywhere you look anybody
a jingle bell table
christmas that is connected with snow so
much i know well that yeah that's
the thing but but here's my point
is like okay so valentine's day suddenly
i got to think of something special
to do it just fucking happened twelve
months ago give me a sixty give
me another six element times is stupid
it's stupid but birthdays too like suddenly
i have
to think of some to buy you
birthdays are smart now lauren we live
in los angeles and there's no snow
i know but i but i did
grow up in a place where there
was snow so it's a little it's
a little chillier paul you have to
give us says you have to you
have to give snow chillier i like
i did it didn't really grow on
me how people decorate for cr
isthmus out here and it's like it
fits very cute the sort of warm
air but the christmas lights are you
a robot yeah and i also my
biggest pet peeve in the whole world
is that people don't take down their
christmas lights after christmas is over and
they're hanging year-round and a my belief
is that if you're gonna leave your
fucking christmas lights up
all year round you better turn them
on every night yeah might as well
right yeah i want some joy if
i'm gonna see these dangling lights every
day i would not mind if somebody
in the neighborhood had a permanent christmas
house where it's chris it would be
fun oh it clearly just lights are
including santa and snowman are all all
of it like you put up you
put up the christmas day
operations they never come down i don't
know i mean you ever passed by
santa claus lane over there every day
the one one freeway really where you
you go to santa barbara every day
every single day oh my god i
love i love holidays i love that
they happen every twelve months i like
the tradition and i like putting up
a decoration for every single holiday and
taking it down the second
in the holidays over that is fun
to me
but but i think there's some holidays
to do away with right now like
watch when you go get valentine's day
get rid of all the times they
please get rid of it it's so
close after christmas
wow it's a month it's it's in
a month and a half after chris's
forty five fifty days after christmas kid
that's really needed the most to understand
or so low from not having christmas
and new years anymore and we need
symbols okay well this is a true
battle of the sexes yeah obviously lauren
you like it i like julia
as a man going like a eleven
i don't get anything for valentine's day
and i don't care i do ask
i do request that we write cards
even that is too much for me
no it's not one of the big
holiday you okay so pandora you have
new year's new year's eve that's one
that i that's one that look it's
right there in the title go ahead
and have it every year
okay so you're giving us that there's
no presence to buy it's just merely
a celebration of the passage of time
we love it i actually like new
year's eve and i like not going
anywhere yeah this is scott's holiday roundup
by the way this is holiday roundup
okay so then we have um then
then we go a whole forty five
days or forty four
days before forty five yeah before we
get to valentine's day and that's our
next big holiday i'm not counting groundhogs
day and stuff like that no that's
not a holiday i'm going to say
get rid of that i say get
rid of valentine get rid of valentine's
day lawrence i keep it sorry okay
alright alright you're outmoded so we're getting
exciting at school it's exciting whatever fine
gone i think it's too nerve wracking
for people it is but isn't that
fun it's like those are memories what
no sir
is ah what if they don't like
me oh they didn't
i definitely have a view are we
are we counting stuff like ah president's
day and all that are we no
no no okay holidays with people celebrate
we take the ones where you get
off work okay so then we go
to mother's day no you skip st
patrick's day but i don't people do
it in chicago it's huge yeah see
in patrick's day can go to who
can go that can i agree i
don't care about drinking okay wait i
love drinking and i still say get
rid of it you could drink any
day you um before and i do
have a problem before mother's day easter
easter i think mother's day and father's
day mother names you combine them not
i'm buying them but they should be
a week apart i think i think
having them like you have to go
to this your parents two weeks in
a row no thank you you don't
have to yeah i do that easter
i think what we would we jumped
ahead too much i think easter is
good because he's your term is like
you have excuse to see your
a family in the spring german put
on a nice outfit by the way
really britain here's my here's my other
opinion on this for kids it can
be once a year stuff like christmas
and easter and stuff like that because
a lot of these holidays are for
kids you know what i mean and
be able to take easter so we're
also kind of lumping and things that
aren't really that's why i think easter
should go back to being solely a
religious holiday
and it should not if you're not
religious you can't celebrate it if you're
not religious can celebrate it but you
have to take a religious purity test
yeah it shouldn't be a corporate like
about like how you know how how
so commercial like how yes exactly bank
isn't eggs and everyone yeah so present
okay oh representation should be christ on
on the cross arising from death
okay so okay mother's day and father's
day make them on the same day
and they'll get this exactly six months
away from from christmas so that if
you only have to visit your parents
twice a year i haven't amendment okay
make make mother's and father's day on
a saturday and sunday so ok want
to get a weekend go home for
if you if you visit
family you go home for a weekend
okay no i'm i'm an upper pitch
okay mother's day and father's day should
be um decided on by the individual
families because not everyone has a mother
or father and we don't need to
make it a national thing where everyone
feels bad about themselves okay and instead
if you want to celebrate that you
go every year in our family we
do mother's day on july third
or whatever and they just okay to
add to this make it on their
burrows america is our father so the
next day is america's birthday exactly make
it on their birthdays their mothers and
fathers birthdays because they get two days
or once you become a parent your
birthday is now mother's day father's day
exactly and and then you have
have to celebrate your birthday six months
away from christmas so that it's like
june twenty fifth
june twenty fourth and twenty fifth the
moms and the dads get those and
they have to change their birthdays to
that
so then it's just you are making
those days actual holidays and then your
birthday is what changes yes exactly you
should then a gigantic portion of the
population will now all have birthdays in
june yes and what a wonderful month
to have a birthday you can spend
it outside in the park
alright so we have her day but
really it's the dead of winter it's
true we have independence day july fourth
i'm gonna say i'm skipping ahead to
memorial day okay i think memorial memorial
day for four that's in may that's
me that's me ah so what ah
no we don't care about memorial day
memorial day also by the way
a too close to mother's day for
comfort
i'm gonna say memorial day is more
is a more important thing to observe
and because it's so similar to fourth
of july in terms of you like
switch the fireworks over to memorial day
i'm saying kind of fold them into
each other you get rid of or
or we move memorial day
to the fourth of july and we
celebrate memorial day on this is better
and so that orange day memorial day
presidents day for the july august one
yes because like the the the fourth
of july celebrations that you go to
that are like official ones like i
used to go to to ones on
the national guard base that my dad
was stationed at they fold memorial day
stuff into it
where it's not just like hey we're
all proud of our country they're all
let us now remember our unit yeah
so exactly make that one thing any
of those sort of ah america america
holidays should all be one day right
but here's here's where it gets really
hairy because now we've got a huge
dead zone between july through good
we need breaks so far but let's
see what happens as we keep going
we have labor day because guess what
holiday labor days yes it's a day
off work fuck that nobody should be
not unskilled work and nobody should be
celebrating it you shouldn't have to do
something on labor day you should just
enjoy not having to go to work
yes it shouldn't
be a an activity day yes i'm
gonna say this thanksgiving too close to
christmas is yeah move it up no
but it sees yeah move it up
a little but what about halloween timber
what about allowing halloween's perfect where it
is october thirty first i can't think
of a scare your date well yeah
well here say boo shilling no thanks
giving in september
he okay what about when when halloween
is too close to ah daylight savings
day though and so you have those
weird halloween's words light outside but that
was always fun when you'd have halloween
when you go to a party on
halloween night in the neck it would
be daylight savings at two am and
you gain an hour yeah also kids
have
have extra time to go trick or
treating that's a good ah when there's
more daylight so you think thanksgiving in
september what changes like the food is
it the food is seasonal think oh
you know can still be the same
the food's the same and would it
would the food grow everywhere in the
world you know the same like
you can jump in and she's covering
you can can have it or we
can have that oh your man was
not meant to play god but he
does it because he wasn't meant to
do it so september you're saying like
after labor day we have thanksgiving than
a month later yeah labor day is
just a day off is just a
day off and we have thanksgiving then
a month later we have halloween
mean and then we get a nice
mum fifty five day break until christmas
yeah i don't know it's not bad
i like yeah
okay i think to have that break
in november would be really nice to
not have to worry about anything you
also that then y'all it's also not
like jump jamming up to family holidays
so close to each other and just
get rid of thanksgiving all together because
yeah why reasons related to history but
also the foods on even that good
good i like the food i i
like the getting together with family i
think we need to rehabilitate thanksgiving and
make it about ah first of all
columbus family family needs needs to go
away right somebody needs to go away
thanksgiving needs to be a celebration of
indigenous people ah where we all we
gather with family and
we are thankful for the fact that
we exist here um and we have
to also acknowledge that we reside on
stolen land etc etc um but it
should be a celebration of bitches the
the first people in america rather than
ah just like ah of that's all
like the sole the sole focus
how do we america how do we
celebrate the indigenous people like you want
it to be as big as as
fourth of july fireworks like something like
fireworks or what how do you you
know i'm saying like i think i
think to be a moment of silence
i think that feels like you're just
having your own holiday and like giving
a cursory nod to
do it yeah well i mean memorial
day what are people doing like you
can turn on the tv and see
ah you know moments of silence various
places by firing hands yeah but real
life people are like grilling outside and
shit you know yeah so i think
that i think that there's many ah
native american traditions that we could research
that we could oh yeah like what
bring
to the truth
oh oh you said that we can
research okay
like what
what's your your research einstein ah okay
look that would be i think there
should be a a a yearly you
know observance from and tribute to native
man we could call it even we
could even call it like instead of
thanksgiving we could call it like history
day where we you know like
where honestly reflect yeah you know history
like past present and future day where
we think about the past we think
about the present with our family and
then we give a nod to the
future when we're all going to be
gone and our descendants will rule the
earth it's so christmassy okay that's there's
already i know there's already a movement
to rename
i'm columbus day indigenous peoples yes but
i'm saying get rid of columbus day
all together while google calendar did that
oh really or at least they added
it i don't know if it also
was renamed google calendar got rid of
it or the ad actually it's yes
october that changed columbus day and indigenous
peoples wow you get rid of columbus
day
look at irish people italian people i'm
both of you i don't want to
badger say and i don't want columbus
day get rid of both of them
sorry rehabilitate thanksgiving is scholars that froze
well we've to take a break anyway
so we can he froze incredulously
we'll be right back
and we're back i can we're back
and we're back and we're back hope
you enjoyed the holiday talk was at
holiday talkers i was shot holidays scots
yesterday thought we remember rica
i remember yesterday fosters a separate step
i was a separate thing yesterday i
had a thought yesterday and it wouldn't
go away lauren i don't think you
need to hold up that chord really
i don't think it's doing anything i
think jerry we're hearing through your computer
mike i think yeah really yeah that's
hard you couldn't tell me
that a million years ago i tried
to but then you talked about your
system well hold on
is this part of the show is
this year now tap it because i
don't think it's what nope it's not
gonna we're not hearing shit we're just
hearing it through your computer mike hold
on hold on the shopping this should
not be part of the show no
no people like the sky oh let's
play like it no it's exciting is
it exciting yeah oh and let's have
a
conversation while lauren figures this out if
you had three heroes and they were
getting together to do their heroic business
yeah and then one of them had
a ear bud make that didn't work
wouldn't you be fascinated hello no no
why isn't it doing it by the
way the listeners not hearing any change
because
she's recording yourself through an actual mike
it's the one we're hearing her off
so she sounds great to you i'm
echoing now oh no it was oh
no oh no oh illness it's fine
the way oh no can i tell
ya na that that people have to
stop using that song now i know
obviously we used i don't know what
song it is but it's used in
so many videos and reels and things
like that it was used to perfection
in that gordon ramsay prank that we
talked about oh yes the timing of
it was perfect you're not the way
step one send us your videos of
you doing the gordon ramsay prank on
gordon ramsay's your onboarding room yes he
fostered everything yep send us your videos
perhaps this time the egg will disappear
or i guess on your parents are
genuinely confused why it's not joe or
a lorena's send us videos smashing eggs
on your parents' heads yeah or any
videos of you doing anything we want
to see any video i'm starved for
entertainment there's not enough videos online
we need videos need thirty more videos
to make
oh no i was thinking of something
i was thinking of something that when
we were talking earlier about
about what my parents would say to
me okay so when i was growing
up they i guess were they did
not like the way that i was
eating food or something because they would
say like your table manners are horrible
um and this was the carrot that
they were dangling not the stick of
course but they were saying like what's
going to happen
when you get older and you go
out on a date and you have
terrible dinner matters like this you don't
get that snap yeah there there you
you won't smash
you want to smash don't she told
you what is best
well but i don't think that the
manners were that bad it was purely
like how i'm holding a fork and
a knife
it wasn't like ah you know what
i mean yeah it was only it
wasn't like i was chewing with my
mouth open or anything like that it
was purely the the one how did
you hold him well like this like
you'd have yeah just double burden it
just hurts
maybe you looked at him for tape
to my middle fingers like edward scissorhands
edward silverware hands sure
no it was i mean i don't
know it was probably like
you know i mean i mean first
of all i held a pencil and
a pen in a different way than
most kids do same with me and
i've actually been called out on it
from between two firms day with me
and the teachers tried tried to to
cure me of it and my point
was i was always drawing comics and
comic book
xxx and doing the the word balloons
really tiny and it's easier to do
that if you hold the pencil or
a pen like this that was my
excuse too and it was really no
okay i held my weirder and i
remember someone like some teachers aide like
trying to grip my hand like make
it go and i was like yeah
i still just hold it weird and
i don't care and i have good
handwriting yeah who cares well i have
tears
well handwriting but i hold my i'm
right handed but i hold my pen
like a left-hander right
yeah i do it like this too
we're all holding our fingers but i
i do it like this too when
i want to write really small when
i when i'm doing cursive i can
do it you know the other thing
but like writing really small it's easier
to do it like this actually i
can't
oh interesting one and people if you
watch between two ferns which may be
scott you've seen it um too many
times paul's movie
oh by the way had a really
funny writing with hall had a really
funny line in the between two ferns
movie and zack made me cut it
out i just want to say jealous
just no because it was abraham lincoln
one yeah it was maybe too off
color or something and zach said no
that shouldn't be in the movie but
i that was my first choice and
email was it something it's
like i'm sorry we have to take
five hundred points away from roger because
he abraham lincoln was in fact assassinated
he did not dynasty or something like
that yeah and somehow that was a
hot button topic for zack so but
i think it was that or maybe
that one made it in i can't
remember but whatever i wanna made a
jon benet ramsey joke ah
i can't remember but yeah but whatever
oh maybe it was that that she
didn't die in her sleep i don't
know ah that's worse anyway but um
but anyway i'm hilarious yeah hilarious stuff
a fun day hearing paul riff ah
back from colorful tompkins paul riffs tompkins
of course my day was your ten
seconds of screentime
ah i got zero seconds of screen
time so what are you're you're planning
on having your screen dry me saying
i should put myself in it i
was like no one wants to see
me well what are you complaining about
what are you complaining about everyone was
begging you to be in it please
god please me the movie
sophie in the movie keeps going
oh hey new year you're the director
you can be even if he wants
to be you could be the beginning
of this character mean i make a
movie buyer you could be the wipe
across the screen between every scene would
have been though
same way to me cartwheeling it raced
across the screen with that noise saying
we every edit every yeah
but eric wouldn't do it
it goes to the river angle way
well please will someone please when boise
one scene for the between two ferns
movie
ah
oh but okay lauren have you ever
been on a date and someone had
terrible table manners and it turned you
off i remember going on a date
with someone who was had had anxiety
about ordering
and like paralyzed by choice or by
low light menu through famine oh wow
and i found it somewhat charming because
they were older than me and i
was more poised in the situation that
they were um looking back i think
um
that later became later became a problem
for me
i'm picturing like somebody that is totally
at ease talking with you at the
table and then when the server goes
over huh i just went oh i
don't know i don't really remember how
it's an upper chiefs but it was
kind of like that it was like
more like um just discomfort and and
later it became an issue because it
continued to be a problem
anytime you'd go out to a restaurant
yeah but also like i feel like
i was one of those things where
i eventually taught him and i feel
like um my younger self thought that
was cool in a way that my
older self doesn't find interesting right right
where i would rather have be with
someone who was comfortable
well it's because it's not just shame
anyone for their show but i understand
it's like if you there is there's
a sort of thing where it's like
an i don't want to shame anybody
either but it's like if you recognize
you have an issue but you're not
you're just not doing anything about it
you're just saying like this is my
problem
the end is like you can there's
gotta be something you can do to
you to mitigate it a little bit
to to make it so that it's
more comfortable for for you yourself i
don't know i wanna i wanna i
don't wanna give a shout out my
point is more is like yeah it
was more indicative of other things than
i was able to tell
at the time right but it's like
red flag you know it's like not
it's not things like that aren't always
a red flag but in i feel
like sitting in this case it was
a red flag i want to give
a shout out to all the people
who have guided anyone in life through
a first-time experience that may have been
uncomfortable for the other person but did
it with patience and taught
i'm something that they didn't know in
a way that didn't make them feel
stupid and that's what i did how
bout it yes and i was great
and i was other than lauren sorry
let me finish
lauren accepted
but you know like like for instance
like i remember the first time i
ever ate sushi and the person i
was with ah said oh okay while
you take the wasabi and you know
what it means like anyone who is
not like i'm telling you've never eaten
suit yeah i know it's not what
you're talking about okay i'm just making
clear why didn't i thought too
iowa saying no no no i thought
it was what you're talking about so
this is actually helpful me okay um
i but i agree that i had
i'm lucky that i had some people
be very patient with me over the
years because i was a late bloomer
about a lot of things just like
i didn't know about how to do
shit in the world and i had
people who were um
very kind and and friends who are
extremely ah patient with my personal issues
like um that i'm sure i did
not express well or whatever but people
that were that were very empathic or
empathetic i should say right they're not
they can't read minds
no they're not raven of the teen
titans she doesn't read mine she was
an empath she was an empath meaning
she felt this emotion smokies like deanna
troi counsel jameel the emotion the other
person is experiencing let me say this
about table manners is that they're largely
just made up you're not doing anything
wrong
rude if you hold your knife or
fork in a strong way yeah exactly
a big one is elbows on the
table like that's who gives a shit
that's just like the elbows on the
table that was a big one yes
oh but elbows on the tables like
you care at all
adults do it all the fucking yes
you did it feels like you're like
body on my elbows on yes exact
right now yes it's like whatever makes
your body comfortable she yeah yes exactly
you're just likely going to do that
one does you shouldn't look too at
ease at the table you're supposed to
be sitting with your back attached to
the back of the chair yeah
yeah tens i also feel like there's
some of this is growing up as
the son of a military person you
know who oh sure what you know
because i had like making bed ah
you know a certain way type of
thing about you wanna be like yeah
exactly literally guy it was like bouncing
quarter off of it and do you
think you would be like that with
your kid like being like no because
i don't care i'd stop why should
they
it's like i don't know i mean
if stuff i mean look i had
a very messy room when i was
a kid and a messy desk all
my teachers like basically anytime i was
done with something i would throw it
into a pile and then it would
just sit there for months and months
right so that would drive me insane
yes if i were to go back
and do stuff again i would probably
you do that differently you know one
thing i was thinking about is is
i would probably learn to ask more
questions about people from other backgrounds like
i had a a japanese friend who
i was thinking about the other day
when i was eight through you know
high school or whatever and i was
like you know i never really
dug in deep about you know him
coming from japan and what it was
like was life was like i was
just more concerned about my own stuff
you know i mean i feel like
a lot of kids are like that
though yeah yeah i guess but i'm
not i was i should essentially be
arrested yeah you're a bad guy
ah
my kids don't always know too that
it's okay to ask them things too
yeah yeah sometimes kids feel self-conscious about
asking so i think if i think
if i were ever to be a
parent i would say like hey learn
to be interested in other people's lives
and ask ask questions instead of talking
about yourself that's a good that's a
lot that's kind of
used for a lot of people but
a lot of adults yes yeah but
i think also it said it's tough
for kids to ask questions because that's
ah that's a thing that's like there's
a certain curiosity you develop as you
get older and you have more lived
experience that makes you more curious about
other things does that make sense yeah
right you you because
cause you you know you're so familiar
with your own experience by that point
by the time you're you've lived on
earth for a certain amount of time
that you become just naturally more interested
in a certain amount of time as
well because willing letting your time easy
lawn please easy la z love you
guys and take me to the moon
taking me
personally to the u c see gc
grimes is alien scars back tattoo yeah
hey whatever makes your thinking she got
an entire bag tattoo of alien scars
alien scarves yeah scarves yeah i remember
getting movie alien where this really big
fancy scarf around her neck like a
danda
yeah um alien scars like an alien
scratched her up yeah wow
why i don't know it's pretty fun
right scott loves that he was like
whatever floats my boat whatever floats my
personal vote
speaking of boats we have to take
a break that's oh breaking the water
i didn't do it paul there is
no segue there is no through-line in
that segway we do have to take
a break we'll be right back
and we're back and guess what gang
it's time for one of our amazing
three germain three cher's oh yeah
paul you pick this out didn't you
call me paulie this is your choice
right this is my choice but it
was submitted by a listener who stole
it from someone else this is submitted
by this is called hitting the post
and submitted by john com dot who
credits date shall not com stop podcasting
yourself for the idea and i texted
day
dave and said hey can we do
this game of yours and he said
i don't know what you're talking about
but okay and then i showed on
the description he said oh yeah i
think we did that with comedian john
doerr and then he said it was
fine for us to do it hey
john doe are super nice guy john
doe are super nice super funny
okay here's the game one person chooses
a song and plays it from their
phone without saying what it is another
person has to improvise over the beginning
of the song like a radio host
right up until the lyrics start the
closer the improviser times the natural end
of their monologue to the beginning the
lyrics the better if the improviser steps
on the lyrics
if they lose okay so this is
a thing that d j zoo where
they are always are trying to figure
out like what's the latest i can
talk until the lyrics start yes no
one wants them to do this no
but it's fun for them presumably i
used to by the way because i
used to like to tape record my
own d j ah shows when i
was
fuck yeah
i used to take songs off the
radio wanting to play a song from
looney tunes we can have some popeye
coming up right now a few minutes
but first but i used to hate
it when a d j would talk
over a song because i wanted a
song i wanted the song clean so
i would yeah the best was when
it was a little could talk
yes so it would be like kiss
fm and then the song would start
clean and then go all the way
to the end that was like gold
whenever i would get one of those
yeah yeah alright so i have a
song i've i've put my i-tunes on
rent or my phone apple music on
random so i have a song so
who wants to play who wants to
be the d j on this song
i'll go first you'll go first
it's alright here we go i'm gonna
hold it up to the mike and
here we go ready three two one
and that's when the hunter competitions going
to take off and everyone better be
there because it's only one fourth of
july happening this summer next year we
go back to the eighteen months rule
as everyone knows so i hope we
all have a great time salute
in the flag i myself will be
celebrating with my family and friends on
the beach but before we do that
this rock song from the alien band
coming live from you
from edu
double dip above
it was a little longer than you
thought it would be it was love
that was ambrosia life beyond law that
was fun oh great now i want
to be the d j okay who's
the rapper
hey mister deja vu the kids you
want me to go i'll do that
i'll do the song if you if
if you want okay i'll do the
song oh okay sure that's a new
song you know you got it okay
cool i couldn't tell you were singing
so i couldn't tell if you knew
i'm i'm i but i feel like
i need to pick a song that
i don't but i don't know if
it starts quickly or not but i
guess that's
to the point where that's kinda the
point yeah so just patting me
shh hey everybody more tunes coming your
way but first don't forget our contest
is still going on you have to
be the eighteenth color to win that
x-box one guy you went over
i went over my lost close though
klaus and of course that was clint
eastwood by gorillaz yes paul davis was
you have a song for me wrong
yes i do it's a fun game
okay here we go
i can hear that perfectly by the
way okay no i don't know whether
mine was softer majors but i don't
know
and alright i paused taking a song
yeah unfortunately i have a lot of
sound effects in my library
that you like to listen to i
love listener hi hi
i love what's going on in a
car and my way oh yeah
that's why drivetime oh heavens i love
to drive the pca like
different different types of machinery ah
okay ah shit all right all right
something that's not a sound effect i
feel like i'm singing all the songs
i'm afraid that you know them okay
doesn't it doesn't matter that you know
them so well okay yeah so i
know so well that i'll be able
to cut off yeah here's a good
one here we go alright here we
go
hey everyone just want to tell you
i am guilty of murder and this
happened approximately twenty five years ago and
coming up after this i'll tell you
where they're buried like this
really gay zada against the wind that
was against written by bob seger the
silver bullet band bob seger okay let's
do another our buddies on the road
lauren ah this this is ah you
right yeah are you ready alright here
we go and
yes my husband did leave me
oh he's starts he immediately
ah you
good d j
heard that other radio
yes right has been did leave me
a lot out huh
ah that was frank black fast man
hey guys it's paul's turn
okay
what's up everybody i had those nightmares
bad again last night there were bats
in the room and i could not
escape now you know what you have
to do in that situation you have
to stand up and you have to
yell get away bats get away get
away and now here's a song you've
all been dying to hear it's a
song that i love and it's all
my debt
okay to all bats who are real
not the fake ones from my terrible
dreams
yeah i think i count that yeah
yeah that was good i didn't know
his lyrics whatsoever i think it's alright
does that's gratitude by big red machine
i love the song wait oh yeah
big red machine's hold on you the
song yeah
a looks good shit
ah yeah me and my wedding party
we danced down the aisle to this
instead of just talking here like the
asshole better not fuck this up
go put it up but that isn't
good enough fuck this so really if
that was your wedding zone well i
bet enough for photoshop all right scott
are you ready that is a good
thing so actually would be pretty cool
alright here we go where did it
go here we go alright
this song is a dedication from listener
jenny beth who writes hey sister you're
my sister and i want to let
you all
thank you
ah
never no longer
ah what wrong was that
it's called the song by dick careless
said that solid was called so cold
i can't find it anymore oh belongs
to you alright let's see one more
round because this is yeah i really
am enjoying this
alright so lauren you ready yes here
we go
and of course the winner of our
contest is named dick careless the number
one guy to win this prize he
gets a fifty dollar gift card to
best buy when we say that over
to via email so watch out for
that dick careless
nice i preempted it a little bit
but that is scorpions pictured life
dick carlos has a son named i'm
excited about airless um
okay palm yeah
hey everybody don't forget i seventeen is
closed for a big party that's right
my parents are celebrating their seventy fifth
anniversary they have closed off a highway
and they're gonna have an old fashioned
bath there's gonna be four kegs
ah the end yes
ah that was really good ladies that
is the dream to close off the
entire highway yeah right so so nothing
seventy fifth wedding anniversary oh that's people
are always alright alright guy you're ready
yep
ah um okay i'm gonna make sure
this song has words song has words
lot of instrumentals and sound effects in
paul's i don't like the human voice
okay alright alright okay
okay alright here we go alright any
second now it's gonna happen it's gonna
happen huh okay here it comes nope
nope it's not going
is in fact retreating
i'm like seeing all these songs that
start with lyrics right away
alright but alright let's just see what
happens here alright here we go
ah hey everyone just wanted to let
you know that every time i look
in a mirror i can't see my
own reflection plus i really lust for
the taste of blood i think there
may be something wrong with me
ah
i think there's anything wrong with me
sway three
was that elvis costello sweet dream that
was elvis costello frova the album almost
blows that was fun that was a
blast let's jump guy came on board
who submitted it i can't remember his
name oh and i gave it up
for one second if it was sunny
it was caught on com dot jon
com dot
who owns com dot dot com john
kompromat yeah ha hope he has john
combat dot com i hope he does
if he doesn't squarespace can help you
out that's fuckin good
promo code bang day alright listen we
are ah threesome usa on twitter and
instagram and we appreciate you listening thank
you for sending in your ideas for
three cheers um i think you could
send him to threesome usa at gmail
dot com unless that's right i don't
log into that i don't either why
to give the information while the song
plays
you know and remember if you want
to give us a free church just
send an email to freedom usa at
gmail dot com
ah no sorry another one
hey everybody don't forget
rid of usa gmail dot com oh
man can i take a late start
i could honestly do an entire planet
i want to try one do you
want to try one okay alright here
we go ready and
and if you want your game to
be featured on thredup be sure to
send an email to three m usa
at gmail dot com and josh will
read it and then he will pass
on the ones that are worth telling
us about we are protected by josh
and this instance you are not emailing
us directly
we won't know what you said unless
josh
wants to tell us a little over
but i was good wonderful guys thank
you so much for listening and guys
thank you so much for doing the
show it was fun we thank each
other and it was seasons in the
sun we'll see you next week goodbye
forever
hi
uh