three
friends
oh that's the way i like it
what what way do you think he's
talking about what he's saying that i'm
reading like like grinder hips like bets
the way
you don't think it's about eggs i
don't think so what how many songs
do you think are about eggs i
would say there's very legal will go
around the table i would say ninety
percent of love songs are about eggs
the eggs in a woman's wow what
are your bags in a woman's body
will give me your egg basket
i want to add to it i
wanna make your eggs into babies i
wanna make your eggs into sons
manly sons
guys have a bigger announce oh let's
start the show with a big announcement
from baldwin change shit instagram name to
alec baldwin insta and he announced it
with a photo of himself and he
says my new instagram account name hello
baldwin and chairs no one and you
don't have to tell us that you
changed it was
because still find you baby
because it was because it used to
be the ab fab er seine nets
charity or whatever and he just he
just wants to get paid to distance
himself from his charity so you can
be an asshole who starts their own
charity charity people i guess whatever tickles
question this is it's so self-centered well
what's funny is the i've i
no i've seen people like celebrities have
started charities where that's like there's already
a thing for that yeah well that's
what they say it's like his as
you would one use his name because
then it gets more immediate notoriety like
oh i know what that is i
mean i don't know what they do
ab foundation i get it i don't
know what they do i have no
idea what the alec baldwin from what
i've read there there already are charities
where my
more of your money will go to
the thing that you want basically what
he's doing is the red cross yeah
he's liking part of it and not
giving it all well know the overheads
ourselves mandates
ah yeah the ab foundation he sells
bandaids and ab blood it's so strange
i'm just telling you charity you have
to buy it hey guys so i
was like some point i'll know what's
a joke and went through
guys what blood type are you i
need to know in case anything ever
happens to um you really wanna know
is it okay to share i don't
know yes okay my four we do
this yeah this a good idea i
don't know but does it come kill
us or something i don't know i
know like say was humorous i'll tell
you how could someone use this against
you telling my my blood type okay
i will tell you the blood type
of my japanese pen pal from when
i was a kid because she wrote
it to me alright ideal okay
these terms are fair equitable trade they
will all do that okay okay yeah
my japanese pen pal was blood type
o o and she wrote me like
i still remember i still have it
she wrote like a very long ofo
song
what is it your name i'll see
ya know i see jersey yeah right
hey ya dorothea otay ya lauren liga
but also it's not actually whatever i'm
i'm gonna explain anything to you people
would would anyone ever call you this
no so you're japanese female called lauren
yeah
great and i got her because my
my i had a bunch of pen
pals all around the world my mom
and took my my brother to the
post office for like a tour lower
kicking and it was very cool and
then they sign up for thing where
you got to have pen pals and
so she was one of mine and
she wrote me like her first letter
was like kind of a survey about
herself
self and she included her blood type
and that's the only thing about it
i remember because it's that that's just
so weird but then she was the
first person to send me she sent
me like cool japanese stuff and i
sent her a giga pet because they
were actually really hard to get there
at the time they were so popular
right oh wow and do and you've
had their made there
although they're probably in china right i
don't know and at what point did
i didn't look at the back i
just had a little monkey that was
pooping himself and dying in oh no
how long did you like it don't
fill over and over again how long
can you keep the pen pal going
i'm not that long with that one
i had others that i was more
in touch with but but you didn't
know
their blood types know so she was
actually moving my closest friend okay so
now let's go now we'll each tell
the story of your pen pal and
her my lord japanese pen pal wrote
to me and told me her blood
type was a positive wow is that
a blood
type a positive i don't think so
it is is it really yeah oh
so what does it are there negatives
i can't remember why i don't know
i i know it's like be either
negative or positive be positive v negative
omega omega's oh yea db supposed to
be eighty three they'll always be but
now see
closing you think that he on the
set of glengarry glen ross got confused
on the abc was like alec a
alec b baldwin one hundred per parody
i mean foundation that gives me idea
a bad one my blood type is
the universal donor universal life church universal
donor with that easily close okay be
a way is it oh what is
that i can't remember any universal receiver
really oh so you can get any
kind of blood but
but don't the donor that you can
type thing i can give it to
anybody anybody in they'll take and they
have to take today nope it's be
nope is it ab nope it's be
paused be negative nope be positive i
don't know but negative nope oh nope
a oh oh no
what nope is it nope well how
are we not said it yet
ah that's what i'm asking you what
have we we've done a we've done
every combination because was all gay plus
a a plus a hey buzz
a minor okay a positive though a
negative stop a i'm supposed to just
stop yeah let's go in order okay
a positive no a no a negative
o be positive be no being negative
o positive o negative c
baby no
ab pause yes oh sick yeah
a a be positive hey that's right
that's what i do if i'm bleeding
out somewhere hey
eat bugs and they're like he's so
inspirational like knows my blood type it
seems like blood types were such a
big deal of of media in the
seventies or eighties or it's like what
blood diapers i know i didn't know
until like when i was like old
you know because people would always be
good you know have gunshots or whatever
we need someone with his blood type
like on tv shows yeah exactly no
he was in battlegrounds
all the time
it's really battlegrounds all the time in
ufc
i don't even know my blood type
i have to admit you gotta know
it why because you got white snake's
blood
whitesnake david coverdale
as they want an accusation tiny contains
let's i just pictured it as pure
white blood flow
hey come on now
i really got to know it i
can't remember color or not the race
what are you why do you know
it because when when you're when you're
in an accident people go up blood
type busy yeah i guess check lot
of accidents kill me just check like
just like a dip a finger in
there little ladybugs pretty sweet do you
think blood tastes different depending on what
type it is
i can guarantee that it does yeah
like if you worked if you were
a vampire i'm like i gotta have
that oh
your o face yeah as a vampire
blood type oh he's just like oh
oh oh oh should we give that
joke away to someone who's doing a
vampire comedy yeah we should give it
away to someone who's doing a vampire
version of office space yeah well but
i mean it's a funny reference
office space if a vampire's drinking if
he like is b bison somebody's like
he's like oh positive luciano face oh
oh yeah so it's like an oman
and oh mah oh and lush let
me show my o face then he
was like a bebe
as undersea i could say the dumbest
thing you did it what if vampire
could only drink a certain type of
blood that they had or whatever or
but they but then they could do
a b wagon of whatever universal giver
what is the one with face
oh three years yeah
you are totally sure vampires aren't real
what if you want if unicorns had
to sharpen their horns against a rock
be so crazy because as i know
them now it's just really pointing naturally
what does the animal is it is
it rat rats i guess have to
nonstop or other time just real paul
they're from harry potter lanes they have
to rub their white they have to
knock
their dicks against what yeah my dick
allen will have to put on sweatpants
with no underwear go on the subway
networks um they have to non stuff
because their teeth will keep growing or
maybe that's beavers are both rats or
this stuff ever told you this story
about a rat oh boy
let's see heaven
you told me lifetime you told me
five ret stories is that so let's
see that's not true i probably have
five but one of them is that
when i was living in chicago my
apartment building had three floors and the
the washing machine was in the basement
but you had to go down like
back steps outside like you know on
the building to get to it and
then you would pass by all
yeah chicago and so during the winter
that was yeah mr yeah right yes
god damn i was during the summer
really miserable to um so there was
there were like these three trash can
or no it was a big dumpster
type thing or whatever it was but
it was just filling lorne is mining
all of these things trash cans dumpsters
she's doing dimensions
race make a biggish answer you had
to walk past it and there's tight
thing and like there were always rats
in there and so it was very
little you could like hear most you
know whatever and one time i was
um taking out the kitty litter and
i had dumped the whole thing of
the kitty litter into a trash bag
like start over and i like took
the
is really heavy and i took it
downstairs and opened the the trash and
threw it like so thought i saw
something but you know you always think
there's a rat in there seems like
you just do everything really fast and
i just like throw it in and
i shut it and it was going
like i like crushed it with the
key litter
oh you're sure he wasn't happy it
was like oh this kitty litter was
scream what is this christmas oh i
never forgot wow i had a rat
in my old condo for i thought
i saw one on one franklin yeah
the one on wow
on franklin know the one over into
lookalike okay um i know which one
you're talking about ah that was an
apartment apartment okay yeah i'm the roommate
and that one no ice thought i
saw i walked into my office and
i swear i saw a rat and
then it ran away and i was
like i must it was i think
it was late at night or something
i was like i must
be hallucinating or something alright would have
stayed
i was just like i couldn't have
seen a rat and then like three
weeks went by nothing and then i
saw it again i was like i
definitely saw a rat and so then
it became oh it became this thing
of like how do i get the
rat and i put out the glue
stuff yeah oh yeah main glue stuff
i saw them in trapped in those
on the dumpster thing where they'd be
like stuck to
ooh it and all i saw all
i saw were just footprints i was
like oh it's a big rat that
doesn't get stuck in this so i
had to i got a giant trap
and just put peanut butter in it
and oh you mean like a trap
trap you like snap traps snap trap
and then just like waited put it
out there and then just one night
like ff
four in the morning i heard was
j g and i am and i
cool up as over there and i
was just in and i think she
doesn't wake up for anything so i
was just like oh that's it okay
and i eating and i went out
there and there it was and i
guy i had a big garbage how
big bag it was giant like wow
it was like like
as a raccoon it was like so
starting yeah what are you to it
he saw yes because because it's so
it's one
yes small rat ever
so i just i had a garbage
bag ready i didn't want to pick
it up or touch it or anything
so i did it like a dog
poop bag yeah where i grabbed it
and turned inside out and then tie
it up feel it and tied up
the bag and then went outside to
our dumpster put it in the dumpster
make you really feel like this zero
like a loaf of bread he's laughing
because i'm holding up my hands just
in normal rats or normal right-sized yes
about that yeah that's crazy from tip
to taint it was mainly about yeah
and they had a tale of course
but this i'm just measuring it's taint
here
yeah it was big it was and
i never saw another rat again i
don't know why that was your life
in my thought was the only route
i've ever seen oh my god wait
two things one place i was living
in la in my backyard i had
an orange tree and then i started
noticing that the orange peels would be
on the ground like fully formed but
without an orange inside like like a
row
feel like there'd be a whole like
a magic trick yeah and i was
like well what's eat nose and then
i one time was out there and
i was face to face with a
rat that was on the tree and
there i learned that their thing called
tree rats which is really just rats
oh yeah they would like to be
intrigued and they like citrus and so
they love orange trees yeah and then
like these guys came in like chop
on every branch of my tree and
then like they just kept coming back
it was discussing oh we have a
lemon tree and i worry about that
about tree rats yeah but we haven't
seen one yet and i've heard it's
really common out here yeah really it
was really gross and then another place
i lived there were it seemed all
fine and then like i found like
a little piece of poop in like
a cabinet in the wall and i
was like
that's not mine i was like i
didn't poop there is money that's really
small and they i called one years
a really big if i mean they're
not bigger than the size of a
pencil eraser um yeah
your diet tell me what there's decides
yeah yeah yeah just because your dick
well think about how dirty the show
would be if you weren't here to
mitigate
my mitigating probably guys holding yeah yes
so just looking at you i stop
saying she really
yeah i feel like you guys are
dragon v no because you've said some
shit i couldn't believe i mean
oh yeah i just wanna say i
found this poop and then i told
my landlord and they sent someone to
come see and it turned out there
all these rats living in the walls
and they had to come they gave
it a lifetime guarantee they came and
like setup they covered his lifetime the
rats yeah oh yeah i get you
yeah no they like put the covered
every little hole because a rat can
fit
it through the smallest hole because they
have no sir skelton can smush yeah
they're fucking skeleton yeah they like can
really get really small like a like
collapse and they gotta you gotta give
it up to him i mean me
i'm sick day or they are fucking
survivor rats and cockroaches co but the
idea of them like because it was
a t
any whole like i mean the size
of a size of a nickel okay
your dick and dingle the size of
a nickel and they had come in
that way it was the only way
they could've gotten in wow did they
get in that is so discussing saying
it's you don't feel safe because it's
like well there's probably a hole like
that they're probably crawling all over you
i we had ants at our at
the place where now
the first couple of weeks we had
i would wake up in the morning
and kind of go like oh i
feel itchy i'd grab my aw grab
my phone making me feel like yeah
yeah grab my phone put turn the
light on and just see ants all
over it and then i go in
and look at my pillow and ants
all over the pillow like so many
and i was like we have to
move yeah that's like me just got
here we've been here two weeks i'm
not because we did not have ants
in in our old place other than
one time when i did this thing
on jimmy pardo is ah all night
ah a podcast on yeah where i
where i made it you sally
just letting you go
i did this thing unto my photos
and i mean yeah i really do
that's fine i did this bit where
i did a cooking demonstration i had
like a bunch of crisco and chocolate
syrup and all day yeah and i
and i got home and i just
like i was so tired because it
was late at night and i just
like put the stuff down on the
ground or whatever and just
from that wake up in the morning
and there's ants all over the all
over the place that kind of thing
always surprised to neck if i spill
something i don't clean up in those
ants like you're hiding for yeah your
you know where are you so that
was how closer yeah and you're just
like waiting just hovering like yeah god
i hope they spill so that was
the only time i'd ever had ants
in the old place we just never
had it
so i was like if this is
what this place is like i cannot
live here but we found a really
great ah person who came in took
a look around and was like oh
yeah we can do this and within
a day just and he was like
it guarantees for two years he's like
you'll never see another aunt in here
for two years and it's humane with
pads and all that it was great
and then two years later years later
thought we did call them back because
suddenly i in our bathroom there were
a few ants i was like i
haven't seen anson here for like hours
and sure enough yeah but that's so
those guys who i mean exterminators are
like so impressive i think they were
just like cron under the house and
like they're going right and they bring
out oh and this other part of
the story with the when the reds
went through the wall they pulled out
a bunch of dead
ones and live ones from oh sh
and the guy crawled under the house
and then was like collecting them and
he's just cool isn't xl yes that's
holding us back well he had a
whole body suit oh yeah and he's
like and then they all came out
he was like he just came out
like how many bag and i was
like i think you know i didn't
want to like look because there's just
like a big bag full of albia
moving back yeah
oh they were dead i think actually
all because they come at nights they
pay your old debts and yeah midnight
we have ants right now
hey boring your own store yeah we
have i will tell you why i'm
yawning and it's like wow because you
said night we met
yeah yeah yeah big cat by stub
of a candle you threw up the
sash we ah because we had we
just had another heatwave like a crazy
yeah he looks you guys in in
our neighborhood so everyone went order a
neighborhood like the heat has again rizzo
hot that the ants come
in looking yeah yeah yeah yeah it's
cool but it's happy we like all
of a sudden they were just all
there yeah and then we got rid
of him and so that was like
how i forget when that last heat
snap was but it was yeah like
a month ago or something it depends
on when you're listening to this and
then and where you live and then
it happened and then it happened again
this past this past week
weak um in a different room oh
um and so we're just i hate
the idea of things crawling on you
while you sleep when you're most vulnerable
they're not in the bedroom i if
i think about that too much about
just like lighting in the house yeah
i would jump out a fucking well
the fact that there are bugs crawling
all over our face
the time it doesn't say okay don't
talk about that but then microscopic or
macroscopic but they're like a linear eyebrow
i know leave them vomit garbage got
in there and they're like it's yesterday
for me
i love it i love i broke
garbage shit
alright look we have to take a
break we'll be right back
we're back barry now let me tell
you i'm so tired and sleepy okay
tell us and by the way the
second episode we do is gonna be
insane so okay enjoy listeners of next
week's episode yeah from your ah my
ah lovely wife had a ah commercial
shoot last night
it was a night shoot on a
night shoot and we also have a
house guest who went out on a
date so i felt like oh i
have the house to myself and i
had a total so i'll just king
of the bachelor nights what do you
do i played video games until two
thirty in the morning ah you do
that yeah i've done it
those devices i've done that a long
kind of games ah violent games games
violence violence gets women that time this
time
right now the price you like video
games i yeah i do definitely do
it doesn't feel like you wouldn't be
into that everyone is always surprised okay
because it's not like a nineteen forties
nineteen fifties yeah yeah because i'm not
riding a bicycle with one giant wheel
um that's fun so two thirty and
then you just wake up at the
normal time anyway well i have set
an alarm because we recorded oh any
backpack yeah yeah yeah and so i
got not as much the plasma would
have cared for man i got a
ton last night i was so happy
for you i was so high and
i took a nap in the afternoon
right before too
two jan two hour nap yesterday and
then eight hours last night i couldn't
believe wow look at you you're all
caught up i'm all caught up yeah
no need to sleep anymore
now janie got in at five thirty
am and slept for three hours and
then woke up she woke up and
i woke up to shift to go
somewhere and she didn't know she just
couldn't get back to sleep yeah so
hard so we were i like to
binge-watch sleep
like cool
you've been to watch her sleeping yes
i just i'll just like watch eight
hours of sleep in a row
so she says she woke up ah
way too early and then before i
came here we watched and i'm so
mad about this a man at this
state of our lives we watched part
two of the southern charm reunion show
i don't know what i don't watch
southern charm but it's it's in my
wheelhouse i just had to set ah
draw a line you know and yeah
and at a certain point yeah like
i can only do so much i
don't i don't watch any of these
things but sure watches it it's yeah
it's reality show set in charleston we
started watching because of charleston and because
we had an idea for a project
we wanted to set in charleston were
like let's watch this to make sure
show for your character and stuff like
that
and so we start watching it and
then we just ended up watching the
whole thing and we're now all caught
up on five years worth of this
our bush you started late like you
waylaid way late i always wonder about
that with reality shows because it's kind
of unnecessary like you can just jump
into and yeah anytime plan it all
i know but we i don't know
why no the relationships and like why
y'all hate each other well because we
had watched it from we watched the
when it premiered and we instantly dismissed
it because we don't want to twitter
that people like what are they're just
dumb assholes who drink all the time
gonna fight i want to watch the
original season of the bachelor now and
see how much it's changed
jd over time and become more like
with exhalation with the goober from the
yeah well yeah i mean remember the
the fantasy suites in the first season
it was it was like someone turned
one down with saying like what are
you trying oh wow that's amazing what
do you try to do yeah they're
like why is catch up is this
ah yeah i think so yeah
ah there there just like what this
is some sort of trick you're trying
to play on tv to me like
of course i'm gonna be doing really
was just on the show yeah yeah
she was like turned it down flat
yeah that makes wow because you'd just
be like you've never heard of this
and it sounds gross the dude in
the first have i talked to you
about this before oh what a whipping
yes
if you think i have great yeah
because you want to win right
so we'll put away the pen
and i've said multiple times that i
think it's fine that he did that
lucy as a fucking personality yes i
guess so like a little initial i
just feel like all these guys have
no interests or anything like they're all
just like so boring getting ah yeah
i've that two years is the bachelor
the thing about watching those shows reality
shows whatever
is that the people themselves i don't
find interesting yeah and the the most
interesting person on southern charm is somebody
who i think was supposed to be
the villain on the show early on
and has now become the hero that
has become the hero and it has
just been on long enough it's like
oh but also it's a person who
started on the show when they were
twenty two yeah gone
became a mother and now is a
recovering addict and like huge transformation absolutely
everyone else is exactly the same they're
exactly the real housewives of new york
is getting really good right now yeah
roney they went book wowed yellow medical
workers now luann is sober and she's
trying she's in
recovery issue and this is just louie
yes she did blackface performances diana ross
she got a lot of things that
are not great but she got she
got a dui and then turn it
over to police that she was gonna
kill them wow i'm gonna kill you
let me out of here and that's
when she went to rehab and now
she's like
like now she's back within like there's
this other woman dorinda i really wanna
do a character of dorinda because it's
listener oh yeah tests it's really she
she's i really like her when she
gets drunk and she's like masti and
like evil and like just says she
has no sense of how drunk she
is so luann was like
okay like she was being kind of
mean to luana and i was like
it's ok you're drinking like you know
maybe and she was like yeah i'm
not the one with a mug shot
she's like i'm not the woman the
mug shot i'm i'm not able to
do it right now actually it's okay
you're doing good now which is like
i'm not the womb of the mugshot
i'm not the one who did that
you did that you did that there
no one who got i'm not though
you gotta go to rehab going and
gallery she's just like this just sounds
like you yeah now it's
really close yeah i have to work
on it though it's better when i
can just hear when you hear yeah
but anyway she's just sown evil and
like saying all this stuff that was
like so she's like you're not the
countess anymore and like all this stuff
you're not the countess anyone whose account
i was even to another because she
was just chopping her down for no
reason okay and luann left and thanked
her room
hey real talk paul yeah if janey
woke up every wage so are watching
this thing oh i remembered ah the
thing that i wanted to say because
cheney because she she got in so
late she woke when she woke up
she still had kind of the residue
of makeup around her eyes oh so
at one point were swear on the
couch and she
is explaining something to me about the
show and i look over at her
and she just she looks like she's
been awake for a week like just
watching this show like you because she's
mad at him and when he's doing
the same thing that she's accusing him
up and she just looked it saying
like she been like whoring over this
show bruce them
what's that who's the banana that's something
that my friend said when i worked
at marie calendar's we had to we
go we we used to be corleone
is i don't care what does
oh wait not carry out what was
the cordell catholic ordeal which a corny
yeah some interesting someone just sent to
me they went out of business and
so should you stop working narrowly and
have enough help
years ago joining him high and dry
um so when i worked at marie
calendar's we used to be able to
do whatever we want it was the
craziest i it was my first guess
was like you were taking home a
crate of pies a shift yeah i
was taking over the lines around each
other no
they like managers would disappear with girls
in the private rooms and make out
with them some managers would put up
with like we would stay there till
five in the morning drinking debris it
would put up a champagne room
that seems strange but they had you
know those like off the beaten path
rooms that would have a curtain sometimes
where if you want dinner whatever you
wanted to kill somebody yeah so like
managers would put torn on the big
screen go on what yeah like if
like they would close the bar they
would put on a porn wow watch
a porn
oh it's so crazy it's not a
group it's not a game activity oh
weird so do you wanna come over
my house and watch support it's great
so we use but we used to
party there we were all friends and
we used a party there all night
but i'm departing and we use articles
i all night and then we we
suddenly had a new manager there who
came who got transferred from another store
and she hated me
and she was the one who lie
caught me drink because she didn't she
wanted to whip us all into shape
or whatever sure like bad know i
was good waiter you want people people
you're like please mummy
i need whipping
my bum wants to be wrecked i
tell you the adolf hitler thing
what oh what did he do now
doing something with this guy now we
have these we have these things that
marie calendar's where we they had the
muscular dystrophy association i think like have
these shamrocks that you could buy for
dollars put your name on it and
it was to raise money for early
and so and we posted them all
around the restaurants i think i know
so we went up that said from
the wonderful heart of ada
we just put it up in the
middle of these things and everyone's in
a rare while someone would see it
should come over and say like look
what is up there with adolf hitler
that's not a funny joke what does
that doing up here customer a customer
yeah and we'd go oh my god
that's so crit okay i have
to get imaginative but we'll take this
down don't worry then we just leave
it yeah i can't take it down
in front of you for somebody
i'm not authorized to recoup any of
these youtube they say adolf hitler because
one of those just a coincidence and
everyone deserves that there's shamrock up on
the wall taking the dog that's right
so yeah we would do stuff like
that so maybe it wasn't all that
great simply but but i mean we
were all buddies and we were all
like constantly partying there every single night
and so she came in and she
was she was really upset with us
about stuff like that i guess but
and she started enforcing all of the
rules that we none of us ever
followed and but the irony of it
zen she had a crush on a
regular customer who would drink there every
night a regular old customs yeah just
you know because it had a bar
yeah description when your server everyone else's
just a regular old customer i mean
regularizing a lot yeah literally every night
and get in and get it at
first either like oh of
course i just some regular old guy
because it was a bar um you
would get people would be there every
single night and be in the exact
same spot um and she fours norm
which i agree i went to a
bar with him george went and the
minute he walked in everyone said and
it was a bard never been to
every shouted nor know any waved sir
sat down and someone slid him over
a beer yeah and drink for free
all night but he's not paid for
he i think he said he hasn't
been for a beer since that show
it's amazing um so she fell in
love with this guy and so then
she would get super drunk every single
night and and then be like drunk
after the bar would close and be
like why doesn't he like me
me and she'd be oh yeah and
so one night this happened and she
had just met sarah running down her
face like black mascara fuck but she
was wearing um a yellow sweatshirt and
yellow pants and my friend walked over
and said who brews the banana it's
just
stuck in my head but you said
we would know thirty years can i
tell that story though but it's just
something i say anytime anyone has makeup
running even if they're not wearing yellow
because she knows the banana that's a
funny line she must have been how
old she was okay i was eighteen
she must have been thirty five
oh jesus that's really good i thought
yeah somebody really old yeah she seemed
old to me but she was probably
only thirty five anyway she she she
got me in the bartender fired because
you didn't invite her to do the
play
but i was drinking one night after
the bar had closed right and i
mentioned that i mentioned i was classic
eighty eight and she was like heraldry
like this would have been in my
file and she's like how wait what
year and then suddenly the bartender she
disappeared the bartender came over poured out
my drink and said you're under age
and i didn't know that and poured
out the drink and then we button
then we both got fired that night
oh yeah i had my twenty first
birthday like the bartender trying to sell
it so what's the issue i know
when i call him and tell him
to choose me young man you've deceived
me and i shoot thinking too much
to my credit i called him and
was like i'm so sorry i didn't
mean to and he was like fuck
her i should look for another job
anyway
cause the whole place has changed the
culture of it oh the culture but
the culture of it was crazy like
then i went to another restaurant job
and it's insane what they what we
would do were you gonna say twenty
first birthday my twenty first birthday i
i had my party at a bar
that i'd been like three years parties
and and so they and they were
all like how old are you yeah
then they're like oh ah did you
have a fake id no but it
was one of those dive bars in
chicago we're like much money it's all
older people yeah just it was like
it was not a place but then
they started checking ideas at a certain
point but we had the whole hey
come home to me the whole
fake id thing for us you would
say what we knew the guy because
it was like all improvisers who would
go there and all my friends were
over twenty one so i was just
like come on come on out and
get in there was maybe one time
writing it in i loved being under
original bar is yeah love the freedom
space did you have a fake id
no i never did the only because
the only places i ever
got carded in philly were places that
i didn't want to go to anyway
it was always like weird bad vibey
places but i i went wasn't an
ideal time yeah because it seems like
in the city like in chicago or
philly you can get away with yeah
yes and no though because like some
places are more strict because like it's
the vice cops are out around them
if they go against the law
the first also the there i love
the idea of bars that cater almost
exclusively to under-age clientele yeah because the
first time i got drunk was at
a college bar where there was no
the like oh yeah the top age
there would have been twenty one yeah
you know but everybody there was like
my age maybe a year older and
this was like a
just a year out of high school
and i got i got shit faced
drunk for the like before then i
had a beer you know enemy yeah
and and said no no thank you
i will not take another oh i
was i'm farming yeah
oh yeah the last before a yummy
yummy that was yummy for my tummy
thank you but no thank you it
was twelve ounces of beer how old
were you when you got shit faced
i must have been eighteen seventeen or
eighteen when i was seventy ah gotcha
for the first time and we were
drinking ah
like ice cold ice cold pitchers you
can do linkedin dune please pitchers don't
hurt and they didn't
i got so drunk and i threw
up in the bathroom of the bar
and um i got i got dragged
out by my friends like arms draped
over their shoulders with the the toes
of my shoes dragging ah classic oh
yeah yeah with birds flying around your
head and then i was i was
hung over for two days oh
but i stayed in my friend's dorm
room and i couldn't move i hate
throwing public no and i hate being
that short i've only had that happen
a couple times but it was both
after i was twenty one i think
i felt like now i can really
do it like i was always hiding
my drinking in the bar yeah um
but i yeah i know i remember
a couple of times it was just
so horrible but i would hate to
have to experience that again
i got drunk in a at brian
zane's new years party once and we
walked to a denny's and then i
just like threw up in the denny's
bathroom and then just passed out in
the stall for an hour it was
just so gross but up on fake
ideas we used to have fake ideas
and we used to like you know
all of our friends who was you
know their old ideas pic
idees those a guy who kind of
looked like yeah it was we would
try to make it look like you
had a fake id oh no i
never fake i know yeah okay but
i once went to an el cerrito
with my friend tracy who gave me
his idee because he had he had
just turned twenty one and got a
new one and but i and so
i went with him and i was
trying to make my
myself look like him because he had
a big bottom lip so i was
like going like oh no by putting
on my top lip and always remember
the bouncer goes no i want your
id not his idea because he was
hearing there was there oh we were
like as if faces are that vey
a
you don't know and then
and then i was with him i
was constantly being pulled over by the
cops i think i told you and
and and i was didn't know that
you could say to the cops no
you can't search my car that's how
they get used they say do you
mind if we search your car like
it's an order but yeah they're really
asking you so it's like yeah yeah
sure i was constantly like hiding the
id under the seat or something
they would find it and go excuse
me who's id why do you have
someone's ideas like come on guy my
friend le carr yeah god i'm so
glad i'm old enough to drink too
accessible legally best i can do whatever
you want throw up all night from
drinking the last throw from drinking was
after my it was thanksgiving after my
mom died
died and i was at my cousin's
house because i was the traditional readers
we go over there first it started
um where we would trade off one
house um ah one year would be
their house when europea our house and
then when we both have big families
six in my family and cev eight
days this mailbox is a spanking ten
and territories are not the neighbors know
these are different neighbors okay no that
was they had seven my neighbors right
next door this is on my dad's
side okay eight and we would and
it was just the fact that you
were talking about how many siblings you
add that is pretty spread and territory
i know you guys want to see
because things will never go yeah i
mean ever have
yeah we're going to get him someday
right all right
seven just winked including of course his
signature nod into the microphone um and
i used to look forward to it
every i loved it i love my
cousins we had a great time and
it was just like it was a
huge celebration and um bitches celebrates your
celebration bitches and then ah
and then later years it just got
to be too much because i remember
my mother saying one year um because
it was a pain in the ass
yeah you have to cook for so
many people and even with people bringing
things it was so many oh yeah
because yeah at least the main protein
you you have a main protein i
hate it when people call me two
things proteins it's like what are you
going to use for
your protein yeah want just come home
and eat what i want to eat
leave me alone alien i need a
protein you need main rotate so we
so my mother said this was supposed
to be like when people grew up
and started their own families they would
they would do thanksgiving right yeah now
stay like everybody's still coming over adding
people yeah guy
but it was it was especially when
we got older and we would see
the little kids now act the way
we acted they would just lose their
fucking minds like just literally running around
and screaming yeah um so the last
time i was i i was over
there not the very last time but
this is like the second last time
was right out
my mom died and i stayed there
drinking with my cousins on because we
would as i got older we would
just be there until dawn drinking beer
and talking and and like that would
get down to like a few people
that would that were willing that were
committed on either committed pot committed um
and then i just got
wasted because i was you know going
through an emotional trauma and are you
recognizing it at the time or yeah
it was you know what it was
one of those experiences where i was
like i know what's going on here
and i'm gonna keep on going yeah
this is what needs to happen right
now and what but the difference was
is that janie
and i were together by this point
and so she had gone back ah
galley to know she's still in philadelphia
but we were staying at my um
her brother and sister-in-law's house because he
coincidentally married somebody who lived in my
old neighborhood so she's back there she
she had stayed for a good long
while and so i was gone the
entire night and did not communicate that
to her at a certain point because
i stopped looking at my phone then
did not plug my phone in so
the next day i wake up after
having like thrown up and was in
a horrible horrible stay
date and ah you know plug my
phone in too late so by the
time she was able to reach me
it's like my cousin's husband knocking on
the door saying hey um your phone
keeps buzzing in the living room oh
is also always plugged in huh yeah
wow and she had been worried ah
so yeah no idea what happened to
me it was
bad news and she still references it
does she just she hold that over
you or like don't do that to
me she she did for a while
it was like is this going to
be like that time like no this
is not going to be like that
and we it's like what's it ever
been like that time since zendo okay
no it's one of those very specific
it's very like saudis and why you
are like we
yes we would have the same exchange
every time i would say it's going
to be like time that was extraordinary
circumstances yeah
oh we were both saying the same
thing by rote yeah is this gonna
be like that time that you say
they're all like no it's not gonna
be like getting back to my question
about janey yeah if she if she
woke up every single morning going ah
would you still be with her
for how long it's just that noise
it's just that for how long o
how long meaning how how long did
you ever size yes it never stops
your whole life yes great well yeah
answer be free to say no if
your whole life equal yeah yeah really
yeah yes well it's like does she
haunt me after
she didn't oh no it stops right
when she dies yeah i can do
i guess i could do it you're
pot committed yeah alright we need to
get all anything why did you ask
i did popped in my head and
i just didn't want to leave that
thread dangling fucking about doing that i
thought you were asking it like that
happens to you no no up wings
no i just i thought about it
this morning when she woke up
on the alarm like if she had
just screamed because of the alarm after
three hours of sta
i was like what if she did
that every morning forgot alright we need
to take a break we'll be right
back
welcome back we're here it's time for
a future lauren what do you got
okay so we have a tweet from
tyler barnard and durden straight low rider
s t r eight l o a
cayenne and he suggested that what am
i thinking game you used to play
on comedy bang bang yeah we played
that a long time yeah
yeah i'm scott just explained it to
me but it also sounds like the
improv game mind meld but the idea
is each person starts just thinks of
a word than at the same time
ago three two one and we all
say that word yeah and we keep
saying a new word trying to get
to the same word where we say
the in and the word went and
three people can play at the same
time or just yeah okay
so so so we're all gonna say
a different word at what point does
it just get absurdly you know you're
supposed to play i think two or
three but i think in a circle
you could do two and then like
you get it down and then that
person can play with someone else like
okay this was like a human but
we can do it with three yeah
yeah okay so we all were all
obviously going to say a different word
at the in the first
word you don't know that although we
have we have said the same word
occasionally because we're looking at something like
me up will like be driving and
we'll see like hill and we'll say
hill you do want your driving yeah
we would do it while we're driving
oh that seems like a bad idea
really you're right i should try to
dry completely you shouldn't talk while you
drive i shouldn't think of a word
i forbid people to speak to me
in the car so
we're all gonna say a different word
but then the next word that we
say is we're trying to find the
either commonality or a word that's directly
in between or a word that reminds
us based on all three of the
word if i said chicken and you
said man and you say chicken and
you say man chicken chicken and egg
and then we all start to say
and i would like farm
her and you might say chef and
then i'm like okay what's a farmer
what's in between a farmer shove yes
so we're so and so will have
three words just will have three words
to deal with so so we all
think of a separate word and then
we say three to one and then
we say the word at the same
time okay already faced hold on think
of a word i'm gonna think of
were other phones to think of a
word yeah
i got mine i got alarmed by
its around
alright ready and three two one bus
i said blue i said penn i
said drugs blue drugs and pin he
said pen pen pen okay ready for
blue pen drugs blue pen drugs okay
yeah blue pen drugs i
blue pen and drugs three to one
when i had heroin heroin walter whitey
too weird to say drugs yeah yeah
i said drugs but that's okay we're
still saying heroin walter white and drugs
okay alright alright ready three two one
dad what do you think i said
meth use it breaking bad so bad
you said bad so breaking bad and
bad very close breaking bad and mess
can we do more than one well
because it was like a thing what
can we do more than one wet
word at a time so if they
just get it it's a thing like
bugs bunny like you were gonna say
bugs bunny is a thing he's looking
like a snack like
amanda moore
oh fuck books born of these alright
okay so breaking bad bad and meth
what is the commonality okay of all
of that okay ready and three two
one cranston isn't show i said dealer
uses bryan cranston you said show yeah
okay ready let's the commonality of that
okay
three two one
i said aaron paul you serve in
the malcolm in the middle what did
you say hey mc amc i want
to send box i didn't know what
channel that was on it it might
be too hard to do with three
people okay let's start over we that
was our tests those tests were getting
really crazy okay let's just let's say
it can only be one word ok
like
yeah but can't but you need to
be able to say things like breaking
and then like we would know what
i meant okay alright okay ah okay
ah yep alright ready three two one
she's shy to say you didn't say
anything alright so lorna and i are
playing okay sunshine and sunshine okay
sheaf and sunshine ah okay ready three
two one like guard okay god and
life oh i see guy interesting god
and lifeguard okay okay ready um yeah
i guess can't think you heard three
two one paseo okay beside an angel
okay
a three to one mermaid what did
you greek greek and mermaid okay ah
greek and mermaid alright ah three to
one wonder wonder an ocean ah wonder
notion okay three two one whale whoa
eat it
okay the wonders of the ocean of
our site or the wales okay now
let's try it again with three or
you're just yeah you're right you are
you ready for this or un paule
do it and we and then we'll
try three is like the final round
while i'll do youtube man paul alright
so me and paul ready you gotta
wear no
sorry do what i did to look
on twitter and just look for words
look do when i did work on
twitch i just thought look it's and
i thought well we've talked to us
i mean like you just thought you
thought son o looking at a yellow
king okay ready three two one science
course in science okay no no okay
yeah you can do
what is it a try what's like
in-between horse and just whatever you think
of from the cafe
it would make no sense i know
it's okay it's just whatever that leads
you to think of ready three two
one veteran airline okay frankenstein and veterinarian
that's good okay ready like i know
what it is right there's not a
right answer
alright frankenstein and and and veterinarian yeah
ready three two one racer paul auster
an operation okay doctor and operation ready
three two one hammer to me
pick a crazy weight laboratory have been
texting me one ready three two one
escalation her operation and scar do we
already see operation no we go okay
okay operation and scar three two one
stitches yeah you cheated okay
round you and me paul ho track
and i was still okay
reading through your mind look on twitter
just look at anything you're just gonna
be big suitcase that are in the
room but you can't think of anything
that's not in this room will you
thought of the sun like it's hard
to think okay so barbara
oh okay three two one space space
end funny funny three two one spaceballs
say zero
that's the funniest space thing that's exist
it was the most obvious one okay
this was already a thing that exists
two three alright let's do three alright
okay let me look on twitter but
see here's i'm wondering how much does
how much do you think looking at
the person has to do with it
do you think anything or nothing i
don't know
helpful to focus yeah i don't believe
that we're sending a psychic message to
each other don't you well maybe that's
fine thanks okay slit your eyes in
two years
wrangle boy are you okay alright ready
got one yeah three two one lizard
lizard vegetables lizard to me today so
did you did it we both thought
of eyes going another way because wrangell
wrangell was this is spooky this is
now tell me we're not sending psychic
messages that was cr
crazy right so lizard and vegetable okay
lizard and vegetable all right ready three
two one silly yeah celery green and
lettuce okay three what's three two one
produtos cucumber produce and round cucumber produce
round ready three two one
orange zucchini and pickle pickle orange zucchini
and pickle ready three two one sell
it i yell it out i said
salad when did you say sell this
at supermarket supermarket salad alright three two
one bay i was gonna say sweet
buffet lunch lunch and sweep okay buffet
a lunch and sweep ready three three
two one cheese shakeel janitor janitor hershey
keep shakya janitor eat eat shakes janitor
he does now it has to be
nouns right yeah just word no just
words like shakya janitor and eat shakes
janitor and eat
three two one hayes pizza hungry and
what keys keys
wait oh is it pizza hungry and
keys okay pizza hungry and keys thirty
two on the dollar ah dominoes door
and ah say again i'm going to
and the way datos and door door
and ah three two
one locker lock manager order order lock
manager order three to one close phone
phone you both said phone phone in
close three two one lawn catalog catalog
amazon and flip ok three two trump
police guy even say that to say
i buy and trade like bisexual ok
and trampoline i accidentally said bye bye
and trampoline alright ready okay three two
one
order present president bounce order present order
present bow okay three two one assessment
i didn't say anything check in christmas
we're still going check in christmas okay
three two one
grandma grandma presence in poor because it
is bouncing a check grandma presence and
poor three
there's original we're never going to lie
we have two brothers original car and
gift was that right yeah where there's
original car and gift ready three two
one k loan we said candy we
bust a candidate who said alone candy
alone candy like okay i got it
candy hello
clone three one lonnie allowance penny and
box allowance penny in box three to
one
i said pig pig piggy bank and
coin first softbox
but like okay
look it's happening billfold pig piggy banking
coin per line okay we got it
focus okay certainly you want wo money
well it and pillow yeah but you
know why like i'm the crazy one
he's that billow
zealous i'm a pro he said you're
looking at me like what your brain
does it work way what was it
wow wallet hello wallet hello and money
will ah yeah paul okay okay wow
here in money wallet in pillow red
one three weeks to one lisa yes
per savings and lisa first savings and
lisa okay okay ready three two one
hundred eighty hours of freedom for
alright we gotta call it that's it
we'll see next i'm on three day
four thirty p m vi
a