three
ah
i welcome three dah welcome to sweden
come to three i'm the home of
the three
home of the three land of the
three home of the bray
land of the three it takes so
much less time to say home of
the brave than it does home of
the brave i think the last letter
of every word should just be chopped
off like how many words with no
really oh by now yeah exactly to
and from we've already proven yes but
you know what i mean like pick
any word put it on the refrigerator
um refrigerator gray one graveyard
refrigerator of your graveyard graveyard yeah great
graveyard yeah tombstone tombstone tube so have
some awesome tubes to pizza to tips
to p hey
he is
a piece i like seats for pizza
p t give me a slice please
give me a size p i wanna
size a piss i actually think spit
slate i don't mean slice a p
obviously but like a slice of pee
period to abbreviate pizza dog that could
that could be popular kind of speed
if i started a pizza restaurant i
call it p
his yeah yeah i bet you would
you've always struck me as that type
and i think if you start wanting
to call it p dot yeah i
know but paul he'll never start what
i call paul's pizza oh that's too
long no one's ever gonna go my
pizza of tomkins no but we sir
pdf tamiya like paul f tompkins as
a name gets more things like that
than any other name you've ever heard
in your entire life and people will
make it makes sense somehow with paul
tomkins well scott almost as with his
name but it was a thing that
he started well that's
that's different i think then i feel
like that's an inside joke basically this
feels like you're like oh well we
graduate people are laughing yes who yeah
exactly they will want to yes your
name do you feel ah yeah i
see it every day but you invited
no you don't it's like a vampire
i don't
actually don't to vampire of jokes you're
the vampire of jokes like mistake three
what's wrong with you oh okay oh
noes oh okay good news say it
no like what okay vampire of jokes
think of it so vampiric jokes so
damn weak no no no no no
it's not it's the lyrics vampire yeah
she's from the x-men nineties and it's
is it bare niggardly know it's a
vampire of draw smashing pumpkins and i'm
thinking vampire
jokes yeah of am pain yeah you
didn't like my billy corgan now i
was trying to perfect it and i
think i got further away huh
right
the sweetness of bilbo yeah
my sweetest friend what does that from
my suite is and everything i have
goes away andy yeah they can dang
de ne ne yam pah of it
oh my empire of dirt nine inch
nails her scirocco and then she feels
her
vampire of japan pair joke i'm pam
power of jokes you can have it
paul laugh tom kids
you gotta admit though it's better than
janie like what happens to janie with
janey you mean what happens to me
with you
people like doing that irl the time
no they're not their shots they have
to have been why they did when
that song came nineteen eighty seven yeah
yeah yeah and then stopped in eighty
eight some people did
how could they how could they stop
that's insanity also like its pringles and
her name is janey not jane her
middle name is jane and people are
like oh it's a very dirty other
it's very southern thing a lot of
people in the south go by their
middle names as we know so do
i but that's not really her
best is craig i wanna hear more
choice on the south side of chicago
nah so bad his part of town
i wanna know more choice or what
i mean undoubtedly she could have chosen
to say no call me no my
first name at a certain point but
it was at a certain point we
she like please call me janie or
had people been calling for choice been
janie yeah right yeah
yeah she's always been some people in
the south give people first names they
never expect them to use ah in
some southern places yes and oh this
is my queen you tell me what
her first name and we're like yeah
i'll tell ya whining but you don't
and will you tell me her social
security number yes i will okay on
my
actually memorize said
do you don't memorize your spouse's social
security number right and i can barely
remember what you guys are weird this
what i'm doing is normal do you
know there are you know her phone
number i do know if i don't
know her social security okay i do
her no no yes i was going
backwards probably one of the few phone
numbers that i still know but yeah
i think i know that
don't i used to know everyone's phone
number me too yeah everybody had to
ask me anyone in the world i'd
be like bap bap bap it that
they you had to like people to
think those are nothing i was recently
on a phone in a scene where
it's takes place in the eighties and
i was aged eighty phone see i
was taping on i was typing my
number and i did a number that
israel do you do that when you
type
it's a fake no huh no i
j gibb or if i have to
type something all gibberish if i've to
dial a number all gibberish because i
don't want anyone like slowing down the
frame and figuring out like a real
yeah i dread having to do any
scenes where i have to type because
i'm such a terrible typist and people
will know that i'm not typing
i once was because if i type
the way i actually type you'd be
like what's wrong with this guy oh
do you think wow i'm like god
do you think much like your driving
you will eventually be a great typist
no
it's something you can improve i could
probably take a typing class again but
the first time i did it didn't
work out and i loved typing class
i loved it the quick brown fox
jumped over the lazy giants cool at
school oh at school and it's cool
it's cool it's it's cool ten times
it's cool typing i was a big
campaign i was a kid to make
typing cool yeah nancy reagan came out
was like i love she went to
every class when she visited our class
guy who nancy reagan came to our
class talks oh
oh my god first of all a
secret secret service frist to all of
us we were kids yeah no you
wouldn't have anything one of the kids
had gone wow
was janey zip gun yeah we went
to school together we've known each other
all our lives that's where that's all
yes
janie had a zip gun
yeah i think she also got jane
says by jane's getting serious james she's
just tweezers probably a lesser extent yeah
yeah no jane's house was more popular
i got nothing there's no songs about
scots i once spent hours now
napster and limewire trying to find a
song about a lord lot and i
did find one yeah what song was
it was a sort of euro ah
techno song about a crush on someone
named lauren or something i have to
admit i wrote that
normally is essential crush i want to
find your face and brush yes cool
anyway i found one song but there's
not there's not a lot of lauren
tunneling oh do you remember i probably
some lorries i can't remember how it
went what about lolo but laurie is
not my name i know but i'm
saying it's quite a low low there's
no songs about lowers no song even
close to scout susan
what about susan aren't there any susan
songs i'm sure i could see around
soo good suits by morrissey run around
run around susan codes
hey hey hum dubois hey those people
let me tell you about runaround around
susan
oh you've sunk so far down in
your chair this is how you think
it'll be on stage if we have
comfortable chairs and it never is
what do we get to do live
through my legs crossed at least well
okay twenty twenty paul can't even do
his own shows i know suddenly we're
supposed to i could team up i
don't know when people are hearing this
but i have a show coming up
in march that i hope i can
still keep yeah well ah from what
they say look i'm not gonna say
this on mike right because i'll be
proven wrong but they
did say it'll crest by the tow
bill cress but maybe by the time
this is released people will be like
do you think crest put out that
information too yeah i guess i wrote
yeah just remember they will do anything
to go viral crest is a ruthless
toothpaste company guys did you have in
halloween did you have the local dentist
who would give you crap
yes in halloween we held in a
hell
like there was a dentist who lived
on your street yeah not on the
next street over who basically like you
would just go you would approach it
and kids would be coming back going
like don't bother because it would just
be like a toothbrush and some crest
and a lot of free toothbrush huh
i actually don't mind that because kids
are i understand the momentary disappointment kids
are getting
but i think it's i think it's
okay to give them a little reminder
ah fuck without eye candy i don't
really think it's okay you think it's
okay together where reminder i watched you
slip him a business card so get
lost you know what i mean like
the kids aren't going to be the
kids will forget it instantly you know
such a bigger initial outrage was a
moment of stuff having fun
on kids yeah you go all in
or don't go or don't i guess
it's sort of like memento mori kind
of thing like remember youtube shall get
cavity never forget your teeth will fall
out which by the way i've never
gotten a single cavity so fuck him
really fuck you but also let me
say this before your permanent teeth come
in who gives a shit yeah like
kids rock their teeth out that's why
yeah people should be eating candy up
the watch zooey should be stuffing candy
up there as is your right oh
my god i saw a thing on
instagram that was like this should be
every school and it was a it
was a diet and sort of like
they had a can of each type
of drink and then the bag with
the amount of sugar in each drink
underneath it
oh really daughter's empty bag and then
all the way up to coca cola
which was like a big old pound
bag of sugar out of out a
pound but you know how everyone's sugar
right yeah and they just show red
bull and all these different drinks and
juice and whatnot and you're supposed to
think as a kid while everyone that
i drink coke so much as a
kid i love basically oh yeah i
don't recall drinking lot
oh so much better before nineteen eighty
four or whatever to when i worked
at in general there was a time
there's a period where i was about
why that was the general store where
everything was general themed right yeah like
the general
everything was about what was going on
internally in a general
that's going on internally in general
i would on my way to work
i got in this habit for a
brief time not brief enough though road
by a six pack of coke and
i would drink the entire six-pack over
the course of my shift yeah and
it got to the point where six
i couldn't taste it anymore it was
just cold wet that was all that
i love my cold wet i remember
who talked before about my cold
wet on mister show like going to
the office i remember we would stop
at seven eleven and i would get
like one of those packets of many
doughnuts and just like a giant coffee
and just pouring creamer and sugar into
it and didn't i had no idea
that was bad for me wow sick
fuck i was a freak
i got a freak of nature right
out of p t barnum's freak shows
yep the great showman jersey petit manan
vohra yeah you know this in hell
what yea still with us know yeah
pd i don't have it so people
will go to hell are always willing
to pilgrims be out
the restaurant p t anderson gms i
love videogames able to shit hanging on
the wall this is where they're mean
to you yeah they have a unicycle
the staff insults you it's great learn
if you come i have all my
birthdays there learn if you wanna move
that umbrella why don't you we'll cover
for you while you okay i don't
know where you could possibly move to
but ah alright
a little spaghetti arms are gonna even
push it an inch yeah you fuckin
you little weak leak
ah lawrence pretending she has on high
heels right now and she's walking all
sexy borders for some reason
lord suga catalog sort of struts she's
like a pirate era banksy smiling right
now for several thanks surmising tyra banks's
hi thanks she is that anything kinda
yeah i do like okay great there
yo let roll it roll it roll
why don't you go roll it roll
that bella over umbrella
i'm like if it were to go
by the way we should be we
should be doing play-by-play and commentary for
this to play by plane you do
yeah mentor lauren is trying to move
this umbrella she's finally found a place
that she thinks it will work yeah
remember when i used to move umbrellas
ah it's not like it is now
you know in the old days you
had to move the umbrella you had
to you had to get permission you
had to
wait of course he did but now
she now she's she sat back down
and figured out that it is not
giving her any protection at all shadow
i'm trying to figure out where it
should go
it actually should go further towards me
yeah to remember and and the last
daughter when he put that umbrella oh
my god such a good scene when
he put that umbrella well he put
that umbrella i was like oh no
lauren seems to have found a place
that she thinks my word yeah even
a modicum one of one texture that
hasn't changed is that umbrellas when you
move them ah you think it's not
going to work but a lot of
times it does thanks so much i'm
giving the thumbs-up sign to my friendly
person over here ah ghost
that go oh hey maybe you seem
to read and you seem to and
lawrence back and she's back on my
post in your neighborhood casbah in your
neighborhood casper ania neighbor casbah who is
the ghost cashman they were ahead casbah
in your neighborhood casper in your neighborhood
jasper that also works for mattresses
this or he looks sore nor weinberger
or purple hauser kaspar hauser whatever we
lisa
alisa hauser we all know her
anyway guys oh my god
oh my god look at that butt
and she's like one of those oh
hey you guys know she looks like
one of those rap guys girlfriends but
who understands those guys i want to
stroll friend went up for karaoke to
do baby got back and this is
before i really like
maybe i'd heard it four times or
whatever it was organized at one party
is a very well-known so you come
over to my sir mix alot listening
party we're going to hear what the
rap guy says there's a very well
known this is like ten years after
it came out very well known song
sure and i just thought it would
be funny to to like mumble baby
got back with
out knowing it all that well as
you'd think i don't know and people
got so offended because they were like
excited to hear baby got back and
then someone came up and grabbed the
mike from me and then just did
it correctly like from memory yeah and
i was like i would describe that
as annoying i was like wow that's
what i was doing know what he
is actually
hey you but then i'd be annoyed
that that guy got off and i'd
say absolutely my place is like coven
becomes a thing
book my players is like if you're
going out to a bar and wanna
hear god god's my rights if you
wanna hear the regular song go to
a bar that has a jukebox yeah
hey if you want you don't complain
during karaoke it is what it is
yeah she get exactly some people are
bad some are good some are nuts
you would bird some people will
whatever they already forgotten josh mankiewicz josh
mankiewicz just make forgetting so people could
see this as named josh mccoy who's
the man koo wrote citizen kane joseph
joseph l mankiewicz joseph l mankiewicz yeah
manque because they called him yeah and
you know the rank they called a
radius yes by by what by blah
yeah he's a very blood in their
bodies they're related by what else could
they be related
my marriage know they're related just like
grandson or grand w or something like
that yeah
fucking dummy they're related by being his
grandnephew so wow so he did before
he drank himself to death which i'm
assuming happened maybe it was that movie
i didn't see the end that really
long one i had food poison i
think when mike was watching that it's
black and white was that the one
i started caring thank watched mike garry
old man as a guy who launched
shut up yeah i think that was
it we were in germany and i
had food poisoning and i was heaving
into the toilet and he was then
i was recovering on the bed but
he was watching bank i think for
about twenty four hours are likely to
make i think well i mean because
it was just like you can watch
a movie i'm just so over here
barfi zandi come coming there and hold
my hair i'm sure
have to watch a movie about barfi
sands are doing it for themselves i
know i will hold my only no
man to hold my hair while i
barf i don't need no manque
no mary graded au manque i ain't
afraid to know my manque busters yeah
this is a thing someone drunk enable
hood you gonna call my boss huh
if you live in a hotel in
the middle of nowhere and your neighbor
is make you buster
wait was made that movie by yeah
yeah fincher david fincher know who did
the one that came out a couple
years ago there's only one manque with
the director with the big glasses woody
allen know the director with the big
glasses stop the black glasses
the black roy orbison
scorsese it's remarkably slow scorsese i knew
it feels it or him to be
the guy with the glasses not the
guy with the big eyebrows but the
guy with the big glass what movie
did he do a couple of years
ago that was so bad the irish
man he was watching when he like
railed against superhero movies that he does
one
yeah that's what he was watching the
irishman
i gotta see it has the power
to da only the face
only to face only only only only
damage my face a little walk around
like an old glasses guy he does
wear glasses yeah but but i don't
think he's known for his i wouldn't
say like if i were saying hey
let's go see a scorsese film and
i've couldn't remember his name i would
go the guy with the glasses i
would say like the guy who did
raging bull like i was in chepstow
over goodfellow
ella's guy who is in short deal
of course
does he have glasses in churchill god
that's a good quit do you mean
did they draw his character with glassy
he was mister magoo did his did
have big bushy eyebrows he did yeah
although they were scales big bushy scales
because he was a fish yeah you're
kind of fish was he he was
a puffer fish as i recall nice
did you watch all of the friendly
boys
tough with him no i watched zero
percent of it i loved it i
saw one minute of it and i
guess i'm a real dump mister magoo
yeah i liked it would you describe
her as somebody who wears glasses no
why is that because she's a woman
yeah women don't
no i feel like she's aware of
them that often
went on camera maybe not right and
that's where i see her when she's
reading one of her famous cigarette poems
then yes
i don't even think cartoonists would draw
her with glasses okay if you are
a cartoonist what would you draw if
i were her know just in general
not about she's not a cartoonist i'm
saying if you are a cartoonist well
we would you draw yesterday i do
see a picture for drawn with classes
so yeah it goes to fifty fifty
she's glasses or no glasses every picture
i see did you have
there's sort of a draw i would
draw i would love come on yeah
i had to release the air i
would draw people i would draw and
nature trees would you draw trees i
would draw a house i would you
draw a fire hydrant no but probably
not know what if i paid you
thirty dollars right
i'm good oh right now yeah ten
just draw a little i'm capable you
would have to be up to my
i'll do it for twenty i'll do
it for thirty give me peace paper
for twenty but if you didn't do
it up to my standards i wouldn't
pay that's fine can i appease paper
depends
i'll do it for twenty i'm drying
your stuff dry i'm gonna draw in
the draw part of the text messages
and i'll send it to you okay
but again that fucking thing if i
were ceo whenever i use it on
purpose it's only ever backed yeah you're
like send a big swipe if i
receive it yeah and i say this
glowing line if i received it i
say this is not up to my
standards you
can't argue you just have to accept
i accept that if it's up to
my standards i'll give you thirty digital
touch what's called okay um you gotta
bad my digit oh yeah bid
yeah take anybody but digital touch ya
hey to but defo heart i did
my best i'll do oh okay i
received this text i will give it
i will and i will not telling
you what my standards are but i
will give it a very fair shake
when you were kids did you
doodle did you draw a lot i
did yeah i love your jaw when
i was like did you have characters
that you would draw over and over
again i had a character i created
we've talked to about this and i
talked about different scouts fucking looks like
zorro
fire hydrant yes i'm gonna need to
see that this is ideal so you
should do okay good this is not
up to my standards i'll try again
so pick the right color
i had a character named irving that
i created
he had big eyeballs like garfield the
eyeballs were definitely were definitely influenced by
garfield
but
the way i could draw him right
now by the way i said no
you said another one that looks like
a cairn like a rock cairn
okay there's three four so yes it's
just four circles mondavi i'm sorry these
how do you do that because i'll
draw irving for you how do you
how do you do the draw thing
in this hadi we're all on our
phones right now recording a five-year how
do you draw on on the text
someone talked to me no
look under the little apps under the
the the the window the dialog window
that's by the way paul yours is
good but it looks more like a
knight a knight's helmet fuck off fuck
off fuck off where where is it
you have to do scroll through digital
touch there yes digital touch here we
go i'm gonna draw irving okay so
he has um
eyes like garfield but then he didn't
have eyes like what his eyes were
on the top of his face was
the little thing that i
did what does this tombstone paul just
sent
oh this one's scary it was always
hearing a polo shirt because i wear
polo shirts when i created him and
this is irving guys and i'm sending
into your right now and you should
i would draw comic strips that had
the basically like the the punt like
my punchlines were i think as good
as it looks like you
they were as good as like you
know ah sunday cartoon my punchlines are
my punchlines aren't great they're as good
as george carlin
i was just like this kid is
your observational i'll show you the dog
i always a job okay show me
i wanna make get big okay there
we go and listeners we want to
know what would you draw when you
were a kid now okay everyone who's
ever drawn something in their life here's
what i drew fire hydrants are hard
we figured out i'm going to try
to do it for you
um these were characters they were like
little aliens called snort snorts snorts you
you name them snore geezer one noise
and then years later the sn orcs
became a thing yeah starks the snow
works were thing okay so now lorna
sense this is ah would you say
it's a dog you'll see it's very
clearly a dog
that's cute little ah as a little
poochy with ah big jowls for laying
a little voodoo with the gels i
think this is good podcast like digital
touch art that you did very well
with both of you guys do with
digital slush mine were these they were
almost like mike from other like microsoft's
keep my existing months
she's sure that she's all that for
me two eyes that were on soldering
sawing springy things bringing stocks and what
did you want to do with this
i just would draw little cartoons with
them and they do every year since
they had adventures and stuff did you
give them away
did i give the question you heard
them all i hoarded all of them
um my mom probably um saved them
i might have some drawings of them
in a box somewhere in her coffin
yeah she's she's took fewer grades she
saved them in her coffin i've dug
up her grave many times
because you're always forgetting stuff yeah oh
shit what i leave your shit an
oversized coffin it was so you could
take all our junk with like taft
like taft huh can't a regular taft
coffin yeah yeah
i'm going to be cremated of course
of course and by the way you've
not told janey about that that's our
responsibility to make sure that you have
to tell her she thinks i'm gonna
live forever jamie's got ah stream um
what ah is there anything else that
you want you want to be cremated
i want to be cremated so anything
else you want anything else you
want that i can get really thought
about the concept of a last meal
to her referencing something person was being
executed was given a last meal yeah
what their last meal was and it's
like did we talk about last meals
on this yeah i think so but
ah we talked about what we would
eat but to me it's like where
would you eat it's such a depressing
whenever i think about it now i
think like well what to eat from
last me
well it makes me so sad yeah
because you know things good enough do
you not want to know what your
last meal is
that that should be on people's death
certificate what their last meal was no
but but yes but what do you
mean you don't want to know what
i mean like like do you do
you not want to know like
like do we not want to walk
out of a restaurant somebody said that's
the last meal you ever gonna eat
your last meal a steak and then
you're like great i'm going to have
a steak and then that's any steak
i ever eat i think if you
made a deal with god much like
kate bush finally could
and you said okay my last meal
will and god just came down said
hey what would you like your last
meal to be cut down yeah it's
only a voiceover my hand he actually
shows up makes chinese she's charged with
gay
hey do you want to know your
last meals no no not do you
want to know hey don't freak out
don't freak out this is like a
real monkey's paw situation says like well
i don't want your monkey's paw says
hey yuck what would you like your
last meal to be grizzly man you
say whatever it was that we decided
what they were like steak or whatever
and then and then god says the
next time you eat it it will
be
your last meal
then would you stay away from it
for the rest of thai i probably
would yeah but it's something you love
yeah but if it's if it's going
to be the last thing every meeting
i will sure i'm somehow i must
die after that or right maybe i'll
just be in a situation where i
can't eat food anymore but i get
i get fed through a tube yeah
and that still sucks so you but
you would know
no what i that cake i take
one sec what they ate cake cake
what a geek but once what if
god what if you finally are ready
to accept your fate and you know
you eat one man if god was
one of us first of all okay
that'd be crazy slob like one of
us yeah the stranger of the
plus so you finally eat the meal
it's like eighty years later you finally
i'm an old man i'm like i'm
ready to die the pain is too
much away eighty years from now you're
a hundred and thirty yeah wow we've
uploaded your young yes lorraine batteries into
a into a computer but it's such
an old computer at that point that
it's like re
rusty and and all right but i'm
still alive yeah but your consciousness is
you're you're in a computer but it's
like it's like being one of those
candy-colored imac to take on the saturday
yes but i mean i can't eat
if i'm my consciousness jandy co they
figured they figured out a way to
digitize meals
candy coated rain job
they figured out a way to digitize
meals so you find steed you finally
say i want out of this computer
and you eat the digital meal and
then god comes down and says when
you eat the digital meals like this
people hoping oh no i didn't buy
all those ones here i come down
says now you never need to eat
again i wasn't going to kill you
you just never need to
eat again you could have eaten that
at any point in your life i
would say this is less sexy
i like eating yeah
that's the reason why when you tell
me that that's the point though that's
the parable that is what okay so
god comes down and gives me very
little information yeah but gives me misleading
information for sure yes it's like a
trick and the parable is what was
the what should i have done trust
god above all else
so so god was just saying if
you eat this you never need to
eat again that that's what he that's
what he was going to say if
you had taken him up on his
offer what i mean his offer his
offer to for you to eat this
i thought he was just telling me
that well that's your problem you didn't
trust god and communicating with him well
that's the point way he's gonna be
okay
well that's impossible do you think this
because he's god yeah very convenient do
you think this terrible will be taught
in seminary yeah for sure
popularized here as variable valley la de
jesus tells us in three dungeons for
fifty two we have to take a
break okay
and we're back but lauren did you
draw did you draw cartoons with dialogue
and stuff or no you just did
did take cartooning class at my high
school why was this hippy dippy high
school that evanston township high school we
had cartooning class as a possibility for
art and when you could choose your
elective
and i took it and i really
liked it my teacher's name was miss
z i don't remember what her real
full name was and i didn't do
a bunch of comedy grips
c misdemeanor elliott yeah i did a
handful of comics and then i i
still enjoy doing that from time to
time the last time i did that
was probably over six years ago but
i did draw a comic neil campbell
drew a weekly comic strip i think
every week when i first got to
know him i mean i'm not a
good artist really i could do a
a couple little things and then that'll
what i always use the same sort
of thing you know weird where did
he do this he did he put
them up online
it was called my naked dad and
it was all about like oh that
was like his his email for a
while yeah yeah it was about a
family who had a dad who was
naked and and you'll come on come
on neil that's dirty that's deepest tommy
doesn't do that but you could do
some crazy stuff that dog is you
huge was he
huger than a normal dogar was were
they trying to intimate that he was
as big as a person when i
saw that big clifford shit and you
thought it was gross yeah
i was never how i didn't come
i brought it up now
ah that was arm was marvin d
was a great game but was he
where they were they trying to say
who is it like you know eleven
to ten scale or something or where
he was just regularly regular when i
was growing on my neighbors had two
great danes and ah that was a
very exciting thing when you're shorter than
a great day yeah it's very thrilling
love so exciting yeah it's kinda crazy
it's so sad because it's just short
lifespans yeah dumb little or they live
they don't i think they live a
little shorter than most dogs three days
that's pretty short and they get really
huge would you go back to back
with a great dane every day wondering
if you're taller ah yeah every day
i would do that
stand on your eyelids
let me go back to back with
you lords is fully on her phone
i know great dane life span oh
it's pertinent this is part of our
infotainment great dane life span take a
wild guess how long they live okay
okay who is it price is right
rules yeah closest without going over great
one too
horrible rules try again though price is
right rules ten closest and general give
it a span tell him you know
it's something to something like roughly ah
one to two hundred yeah if you
okay
fucking idiots
i would say what are you saying
a span of like eight to ten
years okay yeah okay i'm gonna go
seven to nine it's eight to ten
you win wow see isn't it fun
when you play by the rules because
you can be spot on don't watch
i hate our teacher what a pris
she's so mean to us if she
talks down to us we're grown men
yeah where are we in class i'm
fifty three years old i'm
up there ah when you go on
a trip and you see that it's
gonna rain to pack an umbrella or
do you just say fuck it let's
see what happens i sure don't but
i should
i have i've ah travel umbrella j
and i got these travel umbrellas that
are like top of the line when
you said java libre what do you
mean it collapsed shortly dude yeah wx
davis yeah they're good umbrellas but you
gotta remember brigham yeah i often i'll
bring mine and then not use it
and i feel like oh that was
wasted space it's better to have and
not need the need or not
has trisha to have luggage which like
a transformer folds into an umbrella right
before your eyes yeah
what you know how so the luggage
becomes an umbrella and umbrella so it's
natural citizen umbrella it becomes bigger now
it's national de la national state is
the luggage and then like where does
all the rest of it go what
am i a fucking scientists see i'm
the idea guy scott as really bad
i need to see a prototype
oh really
id you would never use it i
was all mad with love it because
he's always forgetting these fucking umbrella admittedly
i would love it but i need
to see a prototype i would never
want to wendy want it i mean
as soon as i can okay later
i brought one oh shit oh no
this is short tanker with you patting
your pockets you know what i'll go
home and over yeah okay
oh girl stay here i had a
shark tank idea actually other night was
it to create your tank do you
want to hear what it was okay
the ideas for calendar this is for
people who are trying to do something
everyday like if you have a new
goal that you want to do every
single day like see if you wanna
eat food you want you want to
not drink you want to not have
a cigarette you want to work out
you want to do something ever
the single day right but you write
a book but you like a little
reward okay litter fresh-cut and it's a
calendar and i wait lauren read a
book for fucking know this exists i
haven't googled it it's a calendar that
is made of bubble wrap so then
you can pop the day see a
little more away
ward
so the reward is like oh thank
god i did this thing i got
targets about my thing and if you
don't pop your thing it'll if you're
insane like lauren it'll bug you yeah
every day also and how big is
this counter it's huge like the size
of a wall
no it's like the dots are like
regular but it would still be like
kind of ah it become padding but
here's the thing the satisfaction means the
thickness not the width it's got me
think this yeah yeah the in she
has a sickness yeah i'm down with
the thickness yeah um and but to
me the the satisfying thing about bubble
wrap
ap is popping multiples at the same
time you don't get to but popping
just one is not okay you you
can wait all we can do for
your ideas good why do you think
i'm gonna improve on it
every day every square is like a
is is like four inches by four
inches so every day is foreign guys
exists wow right this is bananas it's
called the advent cal i cannot believe
that the world is like this right
now i cannot believe the
that is a heavy statement just that
every idea you have is already an
idea but you know what you could
they can't copyright that you could create
it i don't want to create it
and that's why i'm gonna pitch dragon's
den in the us as a tv
show
um i have a idea for counter
where every day is a winding road
and yeah that a picture of shower
crow yeah like a different picture just
the same picture same picture so every
day's different winding roads so it's like
every day is like ah du du
du du da like the kind of
the wiley cody would run into a
wall because you think it's a row
oh wait so what about what about
the calendar that instead of calendars are
so boring because it's grizz oh boring
and it's like this day this day
just stay this day what about like
never go to new york city almost
like candyland where it's just like winding
everywhere it's like it's like then it
makes you feel like your life is
an adventure yeah you know anyway i'm
i'm stuck in the swamp today yes
yeah i loved the princess and that
game and i
creased that card in candyland the princess
you would get it yeah you little
cheat sheet and i also crease maria
and guess who because she was the
pretty one
dora taya electoral loren lapis reversing lounger
think our spending typically reverse
so you would cheat at games and
you're young just trying to get the
good card it wasn't really cheating like
and guess who like you could be
the same person every time you're only
tricking though you know the other person
still so guess
so guess who is the game where
yeah i don't know it's a bunch
of different faces and you have to
say is your personal glasses flipped down
every person in his classes she only
have ten did people catch on that
you were always the same person people
would be like my brother and you
probably are using dss again or whatever
yeah exactly um ah what is the
game where you have to
match the people ah tinder what do
you mean match you have to ah
yeah it's like a memory game so
you see like a guy with a
beard and glasses and then you have
to find him again somewhere else yeah
i don't know that game
i don't know it's official name but
it's i'm at astounded by this power
account it looks humongous let me see
how big this is well that okay
so my my addition to it is
each square is bigger so that you
can pop twenty things yeah now this
is a big calendar
i mean do you like the idea
though yeah i love it i son
was so excited about his twenty twenty
calendar and that he is going to
pop the dates each day so he
doesn't have to achieve anything yeah it's
just purely a like okay so mad
about kids says great idea for bubble
poppers are those who rely on touch
you know idea for bubble poppers a
bubble
shoppers might say that's no moon for
ten fun i mean it's more about
i had this idea i could be
getting you you would gild the lily
you were you were gonna make it
about achievements you needed to lily doesn't
need that i still say that now
doesn't i see that now when you
were a kid would you get a
calendar and was the worst gift you
whatever i loved getting account
and i kind of love getting account
and everyone's gonna day-by-day calendar too and
i love how we get day by
days and you know how long it
would last january third oh i love
to rebuy day i did too i
got them in like high school it
would be like war today or something
like that okay yeah whatever data yeah
but sometimes i would let it go
for a few months then you rip
off a big thick gummy chung
yeah and that's fun too well i
mean when we would go away to
like our european home of course see
back for three months yes and then
to dribble three months at a time
as what about luggage turns into calendar
perfect if it's notable rap calendar i
made and what about bum rba luggage
follow reblog
this is perfect fun for people who
work in the airport because they can
throw it in it pops yeah that
would be so they'd be like throwing
the luggage suddenly go pat pat pat
and you wouldn't mind that they throw
your luggage you can be protected when
you see that out the window it's
wild it's going to do they're just
awesome that shit and they're like oh
if you had to do that job
that's what you would do
yeah and i like gatto fully one
hundred percent yeah one of the things
you'll ever make it like a machine
that just like lifts lifts hopefully hopefully
every job will be illimitable you know
what i think yup they need to
store wheelchairs more safely i've seen many
stories of leaves were too yeah she's
ruining yeah yeah chairs mean people are
stuck because you don't have a mode
of transportation it's thirteen fucked
bananas that they would do that yeah
why do they take care of them
so poorly i don't know like they
know what they're doing i'm sure they're
under some pressure to get things done
quickly and they're like a way to
strap it into its doesn't not knocking
around all over the place and it's
probably it is probably like an amazon
thing where they're like under quota or
like a time thing or it's awful
yeah i mean it's not everything is
like determine
lol wherever one who works at an
airport is jolly and wonderful to each
other i'm sure it's like if you
had to live at an airport which
ones you pick this is a good
question here's the phyllis
i picked the hawaii airport john wayne
you'd pick hawaii look out and see
hawaii yeah plus it's it's very chill
if you had told that little one
that's like sm yeah yeah yeah you
know that one yeah it's like outdoorsy
and yeah nice yeah like the kawaii
airport yeah i picked that one yeah
i mean if i had to live
one ran and maybe it would rain
too much in the in our immediate
area i guess i would have to
choose l a x if
i'm just living there's a lot of
restaurants like choose the genre so terminal
i gotta go what about j f
k though like that giant part of
j f k i do like the
j f k has a shake shack
as to shake shack yeah but you
die only in the delta place you
get sick of that soon
don't fall i wouldn't eat them every
day but i like it as an
option all right you're right she said
it would be a hurry it would
be trying to control my life in
the alpha and delta swarovski crystals every
day
i'd probably go to that bobby van's
restaurant would probably be difficult to eat
healthy if you had to live in
an airport wouldn't yeah you don't like
jersey mike's you would but i mean
you're likely to show so why not
live it up you'd probably figure out
a way to do it though i'll
be so drunk i would be just
like a fan if you weren't a
mess if you
work at the airport and then you
have to eat lunch the airport it's
so expensive that's unfair that's why you
brown bag it i mean i would
imagine people get discounts i should hope
so or bring their their lunch from
home but that's more their wife comes
and drops it off for them
holy and you forgot this and all
these play or they work at the
restaurant they just eat it off the
out of the troughs yeah yeah awesome
people's plates oh wait
tempus loud he may have it sample
some along some sort of little islam
alright we need to look beyond sugar
for the minnesota september looks oh time
for this let's take a break let's
take a break blog please oh
alright welcome back and guys it's time
for three
yeah yeah sunsets here in the west
here's the game hung sets in the
way the game is called junk chump
it's submitted by mike vieira and stare
someone down see if the thing of
junk premier penis players one and two
are sellers at a flea market at
adjacent tables player three as a buyer
browsing both tables at once great preparation
player two texts three what one's item
is and player one tex three what
twos
item is play player three asks one
and two alternating questions about their item
went into guess what their item is
after each question they are asked yep
god winning whoever guesses their item wins
got it and maybe after ten incorrect
guesses from each player three wins okay
so i'm not gonna lie i spaced
out dude i don't know what was
bad so it's basically
the lauren is what lawrence at a
swap meet flea market well we're we
both have competing tables right next to
each other okay i'm gonna texture what
you're selling you're gonna texture what i'm
selling okay and then we have to
guess what we're selling god it yeah
yes all right so i'm gay
into text loren something very funny right
now in fact i'm waiting for mine
is gonna be droll
i'm waiting
i'm waiting right now
and i'm stan i'm sent it
stu waiting and paul wasn't still waiting
we do yeah but back to season
one hundred yeah stew why i'm not
getting it hello hello phones low phone
i'm talking into you
there we go got three things at
once hello saxophone i'm trying to make
you make sound i know what paul
is selling and i know what scott
is selling alright alright and away we
go a little over the football hey
baby the woman over here like oh
okay oh okay maybe your table for
zarqawi sure and i look at you
i was talking to i was talking
to you hey ms jacks oh this
item is interesting how long have you
had this oh this is so bit
of my family for many generations les
hate to part with it well it
seems like somebody already did
yes somebody in my family already did
and now we party with it okay
to sell ten how much is this
going for you never gonna to believe
it is gonna be such a low
price going to be like oil i
actually do believe that for that item
really yeah because it's only gonna cost
you one hundred dollars oh it should
be much less than that i mean
honey yeah can i talk to you
call me up please
what can i help you with i
tell you secret yeah that's not his
voice he's doing a voice for you
alright that's not my list i find
that some people find charming and like
to center okay and what are useful
still like it even though you know
he's doing how much is this piece
right here oh my god ah it's
three dollars that's heavy it's three taxes
three dollars is known to be a
heavy item yeah
yeah thank you so much yours is
incredibly light it's incredibly light only a
hundred dollars but i could i could
probably go out of fifty dollars so
you think i should charge more though
for that yeah the material itself is
probably worth way more okay yeah i'll
charge four dollars okay um i'll buy
it but do you box set up
um i can wear do
puts it in my house um i
think you should the trash can maybe
no it's okay it's very special now
this item you could probably put your
house anywhere i think i could but
i might make people a little uncomfortable
well but also you could put it
anywhere you like it's a little stinky
for my taste wow
oh usual because a lot of people
enjoy the smell for well you can't
really tell what it is this is
not sticky though no it's not are
you saying i can't you can't tell
what it is because it's so specific
yeah okay that's what i was afraid
of i mean it's i can't tell
what it is because it's clear oh
okay well mine isn't clear and my
oh it's not very
special and belongs in a wonderful place
in your could be in a museum
i think so yeah say abuse i
mean it's it's it's like a monet
painting not quite but i mean seventy
room with one isn't really in a
room with one i agree with you
there's yeah there's my item so clear
that it's visible it isn't visible building
containers not i don't think you can
call so
nothing invisible if it's not visible
the containers the containers visible it but
is the container su familia de to
you the original product itself is not
ever opaque right the potato is not
supposed to my mine you can see
though so i think i think if
you buy something you want to see
it that is you do you want
to see it if you buy it
right
want to see it so you can
see this i can see that and
it could see me yeah are you
saying there's no place of your home
that you think people would appreciate seeing
this ah maybe the bathroom okay isn't
a divisible piece of shit yeah close
isn't just be no
yeah it's this is not a lifestyle
protocols you're close it's what your clothes
so it's it's an container it's shit
in a box not shit
you know it smells bad though
i'm just trying to do a little
technology on the person i'm selling it
so i'm just going to be what
did he what else could be as
a family has been my family for
a long time and it's been passed
down from today yes it has and
what is it it is something that
you would like well i mean yeah
poo it's not pee so you'll look
get a usb wouldn't i can't see
it in there you can't see it
in the potato now containers see through
yes but you can't see it though
is it a foreign yes it is
don't you know no you what do
you have over here look i'm not
like this weirdo next basement selling his
own farts at jar i was a
little but you said they were passed
down yes that's right who farted oh
that's the eternal question
but um this is alive obviously red
faced laughing at himself so happy you're
happy i'm not saying
i've been searched this whole time why
do you have here so this is
a lot sweetie pie here it's a
lie honey it would be in a
room with a monet what could be
in a room with him oh no
what would it really well in theory
you can put anything in any room
with any other thing and amazing yeah
what do you see in a museum
besides paintings well yeah definitely a statue
yeah and this is a statue of
an annum
or or i mean when i when
i said i'm you know a human
being yeah but not a whole body
yeah like ah a face obviously yeah
because you said it could see you
yeah with it's ah it's ah has
made a jump ball material yeah essentially
and it's made out of wonderful wonderful
ah stone yes ah al
and it's ah a stone bust of
a very famous person it is someone
we've talked about recently yeah it's ryan
reynolds you guys play deadpool no no
no i think i was only too
ah well we're not having an affair
but that's it this is not roleplaying
i come to this this flea market
to buy things and buy things own
early and did you get conversations about
things i just want to know why
but no gd i've never seen you
in a spouse
i need your side to our farts
i want you to admit that you're
holding a bazaar of a famous person
that i can't sink of this whole
new game in this she's got her
own show scott around jo ellen no
time other today we talked about renee
obviously she's got her own show
i know who this yeah she's got
her own show i mean a woman
on the show a woman with a
show you'll imagine that is so murphy
brown
remember the dan quayle he's got a
joke tools she's got a job of
being on tv with our job is
is part of the show yeah as
you know as i know did you
make this i did yeah and what
it's ah would anyone fight about it
in a court of law um i
doubt it because
cause um i own it and i
have all the paperwork okay gotta be
receipts oh shit it's very important i
don't have the receipt yeah see the
thing you made know that this bust
of judge judy i do not see
a yeah do do do do do
does
do do do do we have time
for one more i'm doing the real
time with bill maher theme okay i'm
one person and who wants to be
the dude i'll be the gossamer i
want to be the customer we're doing
another and i will text scott what
paul is selling okay and you're the
customer i'm the customer yeah this of
kill some time
i will take what will kill time
you being the customer in what way
i know you
i know you as well i know
you when i'm you're the customer so
i'm texting you as well yeah it
takes me lorna sailing and lauren you
text me what paul was selling
and that will be how we start
the game
okay i have what paul is selling
and i'm i heard a sound
okay great
hi guys hey hey all welcome to
the fair like you saw your elbows
welcome here when we travel is this
a renaissance fair yes it is renaissance
fair we got a couple of tables
and things to sell okay so this
is all stuff was ok
hear what happened to you i don't
know so this is all stuff that
would be sold during medieval times doesn't
so i think it is actually i
don't know i mean certainly some things
you could buy like but i think
both of these things are things that
you could buy well the customer's always
right so i don't know this guy
this definitely fits what do you think
buddies like what i have what do
you like wow yeah but what yeah
what i think what you have is
i i feel like i've seen something
like this before is yeah some cause
it's famous ah no it's definitely not
famous but i just i i used
to work at a swap meet at
like a flea market and
marble bust of judge judy no no
no nothing like that but your things
sir yes is incredible that a circular
light is so large like well it's
logic of course the price is a
little bit high because of the size
i understand that if it were smaller
it would definitely be less yes but
i would just like what does that
just said oder what do you mean
the odor of the the the item
in question five videos along i can't
smell what does it smell it naughty
boy it feels like your friend did
something on that
feels like my friends did something you
didn't know your friend there that you
have there oh this guy yeah
it's he he's got a lot of
people think he's really oh i thought
that was a real cad oh no
oh okay okay so then why does
this something he says you smell the
aroma of cat yeah certain certain part
of what a cat does yes like
a hairball no no no other
end the pupil no no maybe he's
yeah yeah so let's get pissed yeah
it's like yeah what does it look
like when you're like well it looks
beautiful i mean really looks like something
that would be around and hanging on
a wall and medieval time like a
beautiful earned no no like a petty
no not even like a pickup
banner i mean very close but like
a ural nah no less close yeah
the very close a tapestry that smells
like campus just like it wouldn't be
evil times i'll give you that right
it's it's a tapestry of a cat
pillow so now's like hairpins it's a
rug that smells like it smells like
yeah but as for you
you what are you selling this i
this is very close to what
the guy who had the next table
over sold something very much like i've
got a place where i used to
work what are you talking about are
the ah i'm i'm i guess yeah
shit
the box is shit can i open
it up and sure ooh diary garlicky
oh area
bad breath in a box very glad
it is that yeah he voted the
jar not in a bad breath in
it how is it a ya it's
not hell ptosis i mean it's like
it's just basically someone ate something and
vomit no no it's not ahmed know
someone ate something
and and regurgitated a little bit there
but
a not in a jar mad i'm
not in a box opener purple clog
it's in ah it's obviously in a
different kind of container that burp in
a tv that you
you would get out of grocery store
or even a bag yes but what
type of bag obviously bag paper bag
oh no the baby good tote bag
yes but not over usable bag yeah
sort of yeah i'll give you that
bourbon were usable toe a bourbon burlap
bag
a hammer pepper that back up or
bynum burleigh for summer left to be
fair i was two burps and yes
he said perps to sack little bit
of a bag
you demeaning me in that way
why would you do that to her
what would you do that do that
do show up and now i see
what a folly it was yeah you've
learned an important lesson here yeah well
guys that was a fun we had
a bluhm three term but it's getting
a little chilly here in the backyard
like oops we we the show is
governed by the weather and so
so we have to get out of
here as a plane flies overhead door
to door that daughter hey thanks for
listening everybody we love you and really
shameless yeah happy birthday happy birthday
contagious with the ha ha
yeah happy birthday and we are three-day
them yes your birthday by the way
you're very lucky because that has never
happened if your list no one has
ever listened to the episode on their
birthdays right now and let us know
yeah if it's your birthday you're listening
on your birthday let us know let
us know and we'll definitely respond yeah
books spoiled it for rumors about for
where three m usa on instagram and
twitter freedom usa at gmail dot com
if you wanna send us a reacher
ah who says this one
ah that's lost to time but i
yeah i had the message say it
okay did say yeah alright and hey
if you want to listen to this
ah you know anywhere you get podcasts
please subscribe that's great and if you
want to hear it ad-free the week
it comes out listen to it on
stitcher premium or cvb world dot com
can i say that cbp world dot
calm is a good deal i just
listened to tim bosses ah self cvb
presents where he was randy snouts it
was hilarious um i love i'm loving
the bonus nancy's podcast some good stuff
on there not a good stuff lot
of good stuff and i might be
doing something yeah maybe in the next
few yes yeah yeah i've
very fun idea yes so guys lawrence
putting on her coat i've never seen
that before i've never seen lauren wear
a coat and my lo my god
this is crazy surely your jacket
yea yea yea guys we love you
we'll have to see you next week
though until then spend the next how
many how many hours do they have
until we come back ah twenty four
yeah where every day now what now
there's seventy two is three savannah huh
forty four
time so a hundred in the plans
sixty so about one hundred and sixty
five hours from now we'll see you
and we'll be seeing you and you'll
be listening to us but we'll be
seeing you lie go to each other
be good to each other forever goodbye
uh