huh
ah
ah gah gah gah gah i was
acting like i was lifting a great
big rock that god couldn't even lift
i barely gave any energy to it
and lauren let's ask what he did
go ahead what did you doing do
you do i sang it normal oh
a little bit of grid on it
that's nice yeah just little bit of
grit just a little bit just a
little bit jews lose
great room does the work what song
is that a little bit of christmas
just a little bit just a little
bit of bloom and luck oh i
think it's from mo just obey for
me luck my fair lady but it's
making me think of this cartoon called
lil bits that was on nickelodeon
and i'm trying to think how the
theme song went okay hit us with
it three two one
where the little bits
just like a little bit of blue
man luck or lauren i can't help
but notice that you mentioned a lack
of energy yes i did because what
is going on with you lauren you're
right your yahoo will have corona virus
in covina
ian nineteen the carving neuro novel coronavirus
corona i got the carving idea get
the comment after after two plus years
of washing my hands wearing my mask
and why didn't you stop by during
your hands where i am wearing here
okay hannibal
i didn't stop any of my practices
and yet i got covered nineteen you've
done it um as did my entire
family so it was it's been a
wild week which is why we're on
zoom last week but it's just a
question if they're fresh i haven't actually
tested and tested positive when we recorded
last week so i was still holding
out hope that i would be negative
but no i got it you were
the
lower one in your household i was
which made me feel a little better
because you and i had done a
show just days before a little bit
i was worried that i would have
infected you but i didn't test positive
for days so it was pretty safe
to say that i wasn't worried about
it until you did mention after you
tested positive that you had had a
sore throat for days
well monday was my sore throat started
oh okay during the show oh show
yeah show a saturday or sunday sunday
sunday shows after church mike did test
positive on monday though but then i
was like i booted him out of
the house you want to stay at
a good friend etc
v that was mt showed over the
brand yeah and then um i was
wearing a mask with holly and then
it turned out hollywood's positive and then
i still was trying to wear a
mask and um but then i tested
positive a couple days later after wearing
mask doing it all by myself for
a couple of days it was futile
because i got the
cobb and priority had it but then
at least your disease husband could come
back home and help you that was
better yeah who who did he get
it because he got it first right
he did i don't remember this code
is the kissing disease and i won't
say i don't blame him and could
happen to me just as much as
it could that he's not in trouble
i'm just saying that no one should
be me
mad at mike other than fans of
this show he was massless and in
a space where there was a lot
of space between each person was found
in a giant warehouse with ten feet
at least between each person and huge
ceilings and yeah but it it got
them nonetheless yeah
um and so we're we've been holed
up and it's been horrible we both
got super sick it's socked it's been
bad it isn't i would not say
it was mild for us it was
very mild for hollywood think god it
feels like the people that are getting
it now from what i've heard it's
it's not like oh it felt like
nothing like this actually feels like you're
sick yeah we were knocked
on our asses and so it worked
out actually the timing that the fact
that i got it a couple of
days delayed really worked out because he
was when he was sequestered at the
air bnb he was able to just
like sleep all day and not worry
about taking care of baby and stuff
and then by the time i was
feeling really shitty he was back home
so i was able to lay in
bed oh but it sucked and i
feel i still don't don't
feel great it's been over a week
what about the babby how does that
how's the babby do she's doing great
she was really great after just like
i would say it lasted for her
probably like thirty six hours she was
sick definitely sick and wanting to be
held all the time and crying and
feeling bad and oh lol i never
got cold
and then i took to the doctor
they checked her out everything was okay
and they said it's typically been mild
what they've been seeing was then smiled
for babies and she was a situation
where that was the case thankfully end
she was much better on the next
day and was like totally energized not
made it a little hard because we
were dries yeah
i showed her her first movie though
i've never shown on tv before whoa
what did she think and when bobby
turns movie i'm sorry one moment with
scott doing an impression of a baby
being energized yes i'm starting what does
that sound like ie something like that
i don't know why we're like a
maid is like a mechanical sound well
i mean
it's it's a cross between honestly energizing
sounds like a cross between mechanical sound
and like pixie dust right no you're
right um anyhoo no no watched and
contoh and quietly and we both loved
it she kept turning around it was
so cute she kept turning around and
smiling at me when we were watching
it she was like really happy yeah
wow she loved
we watched one hour one day then
we watched the other hour the next
day and then when she was feeling
better she has no patience to sit
and watch a movie so that was
kind of cute
did she that's crunchy clock like that
it was the same movie you think
or i think so because i put
on a different movie or the only
one she's ever seen so it was
like she was less than me but
then i watched turning red have you
seen that no i've heard it's good
oh my god it made me cry
at the end and i loved it
contoh they are both fantastic
did you read that review that they
that they eventually took down i forget
where it appeared what were like i
was like how can i relate to
this yes religious unreliable and it's like
what do you think movies are like
every story exactly to me yeah all
movies are unreliable right i mean it's
like but the movie is related but
they're just they're just as relatable as
they are
unrelated that's funny it's like yeah you
could say that about anything yeah but
it's it's very i found it very
relatable and even at the end they
have like a moral that's like we
all experience this thing so good that
i was like how are you only
the only movie that's relatable for me
as captain america because i have a
really good body but so you don't
really start where he was a little
twerp no don't like
that your head is so much bigger
than your body
i've only see the first ten minutes
so i don't know you turned it
off in disgust that's good for students
really looks like
i this movie about a hero
well that i'm sorry to hear about
your covert gas it's sucks it sucks
i'm glad your feeling better though you're
in the mirror to think almost out
of the woods i never gave it
to us need thank you it's also
supposed to see you monday and that
was the day mike tested positive so
thankfully i didn't mean literally you were
honest with us
i know i could sell some over
there is somebody in our household who
has extreme covert fear and is convinced
that either myself or they have coded
every single day well that was me
for literally this entire time i'm always
saying i have coven and i didn't
know oh my god i always am
like my throw type kobe like i
just for two
years and makes until even when i
wanted to give my test he was
like fine like because because i am
always saying it and then it was
positive and we were both shocked shocked
i don't think i have it until
my roommate starts trying to talk me
into it yeah come on get code
and then i'm like
okay you're starting to make me think
it's a problem that i get offed
once yeah yeah um yeah yeah know
goes over lining though i guess the
whole carpet situation of getting the convent
and having and getting through it and
be ok is like that i can
um not worry as much for like
a couple months there you have it
there you go so that's good
cool up to co-op experience the feeling
of a little bit of freedom after
the idea i don't know i think
so i mean we both just went
to the doctor and got our anti
bodies tested oh so mine are off
the charts baby you you have antibodies
you know you didn't
have it yeah from the from the
vaccine vaccines from the vaccine but that's
why you didn't get it maybe er
no i heard that word we don't
know i don't think so but we
ah but maybe yeah i don't know
yeah they also seem to think that
maybe co-ops vaccine processed her body process
the virus so well that she wasn't
giving it off she was shouting it
at also but yeah devilish does that
mean she's an alien maybe yeah it
could be yeah like her body's like
zeroes and ones
more ones than zeroes you know i
mean oh i do not
but bought all what
modern-day by like the ballet la legge
di balik dah
i thought i got my toaster you
got your toaster great paul know anywhere
double boozer booster because i'm older finally
paid off huh that's great
scholar know so got the same letter
because he had jay and jay and
they are alone oh oh really because
there's so bad i guess i can
just i don't know topic just get
a million of em yeah yeah you
want you want extra we're gonna give
you some taiko ones
where are you going to ask me
how are you going to get it's
got ah my doctor suggested currently to
wait because my antibody levels are really
super high so any kind of way
too high why like you're going to
link then i get high all the
time i get this guy yeah no
just there there there's it's a scale
of one to one
fifty if you have one than you
have antibodies essentially and minor above one
fifty like they were so you're off
the chart so they he said literally
you know just wait a few months
and will tested again and see how
your antibody levels answer your life's hard
enough to say you're like an ohio
one sixty surely law
one fifth yeah with an oakland booty
of course
that's separately but that's what happens when
body starts lapping yeah i guess so
doing the wild
i used to do that as a
reporter all the bodies start slapping well
ah that's what's happens when body starts
slap when you played a reporter in
a movie
oh i wish i could play a
reporter of the movie i've just been
done and been a movie in the
movie call him the two armed bandit
one in condo the only movie that
i'm losing that's what holly things yeah
she's like man they should make another
one that was good emanated that movie
the whole thing oh with the big
flat black thing
thing that's against the wall every day
i love picturing her turning around like
to see with this are you getting
this yes but i had a mask
on when also bummed me out because
i was like only like celebrate with
her you know maybe she was happy
because she she thought you were a
different person yeah she thought i would
just like avoid please stay that loser
normally with never let
if you watch any of these guys
i like this new person
and how is is mike feeling better
he's still feels pretty crappy but but
better we're we're both much better but
it's just coughing a bit and i
might cough is basically gone but i
just feel very how's your senses hey
east good he did get me well
why don't you shit
yes i guess it was bad
he gave me a donut on ah
he got me into it on my
first really bad day but i couldn't
realise it oh no i just had
a kind of doughnut sprinkles was my
favorite it's um just a ah when
he caught a doughnut with chocolate frosting
but like not a kick on it
i love cake donuts but it was
a fluffy
i'm just don't old the chocolate frosted
doughnuts yeah yes so good i love
chocolate doughnuts you ah yes i do
absolutely do you know what i used
i used to love every once in
awhile after church we would go to
dunkin donuts and get a dozen dads
and the um the cream filled ones
but not now
not boston cream they were white powdered
ones with cream inside and those are
my favorite i hate when there's cream
inside newly know we talked about this
before because there was something that your
brother got you to eat well i
had a tragic time when my dad
got me a boston kreme and dunkin
donuts and i didn't know it was
boston cream and i bit into it
it was shy
shocking and disgusting and what my brother
did recently get me a macho doughnut
that i may yeah but i didn't
know there was much inside but then
i don't like it yeah but i'm
more open to a cream puff now
but as a child and certainly not
no i remember cream puffs being disappointing
when i was a kid like it
was yeah technically it was a sweet
thing what's so i was i would
eat it yeah but it just
like the is too thin the yeah
cream is too much it's like the
proportions are off yeah when i was
like where i lacked vocabulary obviously when
i was working on destruct show we
would slightly less talk about you want
to talk about when you were going
to mister show
stop have a seven eleven every single
day on the way and and this
is we had to be there at
eleven thirty this is at like eleven
get a giant thing of coffee where
we would just like poor cream and
sugar into it and then buy a
full packet of chocolate donuts those eight
packs of the mini donuts yes yes
eat that every single
day on the way it sounds kind
of fun that the time in your
life good for you know what this
feels like yeah have diarrhea but yeah
at the time i feel like my
stomach was well in some ways i
could eat crazy things but then i
had a period of time where it
was like just anything would just be
pure diarrhea central but then i i
move past that
i think just from having a better
diet speaking of eating thing you don't
know my area no i do believe
me but off off my
off like i want to talk about
it for three hours
there was a period of my life
where i was ordering um a cheese
steak sandwich every day from this place
the philly steak depot in hollywood fucking
disgusting i well of course i grew
up with the sandwiches and i loved
them and this was not entirely
yeah it was the closest that i'd
found at that point yeah to an
actual philly cheese steak and of course
there was a minimum for delivery inside
ordered them two at a time oh
and i i did this every day
for a long time enough so that
the delivery guy knew me by name
and we would chat a little bit
at the door ever say you can
we can change it so you can
just get one no he never said
that nor did he ever say you
should stop doing this to every day
you ate too i would eat not
every days i would eat like one
and then we did the other one
the next day um hey well that
night though but i
would get yeah sure yeah so yeah
boy today well no no no not
always not always i would not eat
like one for lunch and then one
for dinner
i'm on mondays and wednesday yes but
sometimes i would order i would order
a cheese steak and a chicken cheese
steak and then i'll eat half and
chickadee cheese steak the cheese takes chicken
yes exactly exactly drumstick and the clock
starts ticking cause i like sting i'm
getting tend to watch x-files no lights
on yeah
don la maison i hope the smoking
man's in this one like harrison ford
i'm getting ten or i'm getting franchise
thanks harrison ford got tantric like snickers
oh my god i'm imagining that when
i feel i'll email you used to
know that whole thing right i did
i did i still do know a
lot of bother somebody with it you
know
no and i love barenaked ladies there
was somebody who would do it for
it it would drive them crazy um
mister i don't know but i'm sure
that's true that might be another friend
of mine oh okay because i do
know i think it just drives anyone
crazy
anyone would sing that or know it
or and it feels like an almost
like an an activation of a sleeper
cell thing that if you if you
see it to someone yet they might
feel like i'm not control of my
own body and mind but i remember
the first time i heard that song
and i was riding in the backseat
of my friend's car her dad was
driving and i thought it was amazing
it was like so fast i was
like wow are they saying all this
stuff and then to remember it's very
fun i just wanted to talk about
how you know the memorized it note
for me to memorize oh and later
yeah um they probably are reading it
the whole time um i would know
that part of the concert where they
pulled out a crumpled up piece of
paper and they're like
try not to change things in the
studio they like couldn't record until they
finally all memorized it
on this right guys
wait it's not tick tock about some
people some people listen to music and
hear lyrics and some people hear the
melody which i guess i under i've
always understood that there's literally a study
about brains and helping some people's oh
no don't do that but i think
we all hear the lyric study my
brain i well i feel like i'm
a lyric person because i like
lyrics or all your ex people know
i'm not everybody is i sometimes are
because we know lyrics just a fuck
up what i am i think but
i suppose when you what you sort
of what what draws you to a
song more and some people are driven
more by melody and some people are
driven more by lyrics um it's like
what you hear
ear when you listen no okay but
that's not what i'm talking about and
that's what i'm talking about from the
tick tock but look i haven't seen
this tick tock i haven't a chance
to read it but i will say
this
i have enjoyed songs where i have
like a squeezed song or something where
i had no idea what the fuck
they were saying oh yeah i'm totally
settled by the fruit of another that's
one of the easier ones to figure
out yeah but like pulling mussels from
the shell they are slipping serenely difficult
yes because really pulling muscles from michelle
is like
i feel like he's talking about maid
marian at one point i think yeah
i've thought that fate that gave me
what i think we're saying not is
that is what he's saying yes he's
saying maid marian yes may with regard
to the tiktok like from from robin
hood or just someone knows somebody he
knows
i mean someone made marion do a
thing you know no no no it
is it is m i a d
marian okay i couldn't even tell you
what that song's about robin does not
get mentioned it's about one thing not
that the people who hear the lyrics
isis dance song passes the bechdel test
they don't always understand lyrics but they
hear the lyrics i think some people
don't even hear it more and get
off this i
ah suffering to brainwash us funding right
yeah you're right paul at me i
don't give a r t
this is cta you're trying to say
if i don't hear the melody i'm
a racist again
i mean hey
i mean i mean hey yeah yeah
yeah her what are the lyrics to
that song i wake up i look
out i say my house i'm life
is still trying to get up the
grippy you love hope for understood irish
heard we saying that the speech laura
and i saying
teach together we did with the throwing
shade bryan safi aaron gibson and coal
guy really wants me to be a
part of stratagem family stress no houser
cola schools or colescott la police school
law school call um one more and
you said oh and then you cough
what did you want to get us
our attention for that coffee nope okay
i definitely didn't scott because usually a
lot of people cough to get attention
i'm doing because i have a nineteen
it's a way to succeed in what
if what if you cough to get
our attention so we could hear your
covert cough
god you know you you wouldn't wanna
hear it when it's bad is
i hope you don't get coven it
really hurt my throat thank you i
do not want to get it it
sucks i need this nice and lubricated
i don't want to hurt it i
was on a sec ah last couple
days and um this was a ah
movie um and i had a sm
small part in it and so the
day that i got i got there
on a friday for work and they
i heard in the the hair and
makeup trailer which is where you hear
all the gossip
that the day before oh no this
one went for my wardrobe fittings so
we were away from set and the
wardrobe people were telling me the day
before nobody had masks on like because
they were shooting outside nobody was wearing
masks and that seems weird for the
crew to not have them it feels
like yeah exactly at a risk absolutely
and then the so the the pair
aren't corporation awe of his production found
out and said um no everyone has
to wear masks all the time and
so then when by the time i
got to set the crew was wearing
them but a lot of the actors
were just leaving them off you know
between takes between setups and loosey goosey
out here it's gone
jacuzzi enough for me baby i was
yeah fuckin putting that thing back on
i just feel like people are getting
a little too comfy i know so
many people who have covered right now
yeah i feel like i've heard a
lot of people that i know got
us so it's just like it's not
done it sucks to get it it's
worth it to not get it i
know once and we we tried
nazi guys wanna be very clear that
no of course just for the listener
you weren't out there in these streets
i didn't do anything even fun my
gym makes me a little nervous but
the area where i work out has
a great bible by the way hey
thank you so sick
in the good way right yes body
is sick q it's nice to hear
it from friends but i have a
sick body your body don't sick
ah like harrison ford you're getting tantric
so funny to me he's so tantric
oh my god harrison ford is so
jatra and sting is so frantic the
the always like what should i record
yeah i do wrong i know everybody
i don't know
should i re-record every breath
everybody take it with me god wanted
i wanna know how get it out
of the way you laugh poverty did
a re-recording album not too recently d
really yeah did he just redo all
of them with a loot
it's just purely loot
and he did it for the loot
once you get to go back to
his real name was his record orden
yeah what what's going on gordon again
trust the gardens fisherman yeah it was
what he was doing these fishermen
well that's the tea of course we
we know that right oh gordon's yes
shit but still he should be that
he's turning that corner wearing the bikini
from doe if we're in the bikini
from doing but with a rain slicker
and reset oh man you and this
liquor is open you could see the
dune bikini it's like everybody's knee gordon
ah
made some changes and i hope you
like this is my new and all
of this andre like sea shanties throw
sand at the audience i mean the
ccna part is sort of what he's
been doing lately did y'all see dune
no no we watched it i guess
you had to watch it on the
big screen i guess he had to
either yeah to watch it i guess
you had to be in it
i had to be a sandworms i
do i do want to go to
the movies and i want to see
everything everything everywhere on was yeah oh
good i gotta do that dang we
saw it i cried like a baby
it was great it truly was everything
it was funny there was great action
in it it was poignant
was fucking it was thought provoking i
loved it i've heard it just fantastic
the four things yeah that's the alternate
title of this show when mary helen
comes home she never coming on this
why would you even tease people like
that she has never coming on the
show the only guess we will ever
have is paige davis that's right i
forgot
okay we're almost out but it's i
think it's good to reiterate the call
though paige davis if you're listening people
know you're listening page page please please
come be our guest on freedom we're
not going to make fun of you
we just want you on your just
gonna shoot the shit with us we'll
talk about whatever page we're not we're
not doing anything weird
it just came to this point where
you are the only person we've said
we'll have on we are not impractical
jokers we are good guys no speaking
of trutv gabrielson adam pelley have a
show that looks really fun i seen
that what is it it's them they
go to travel to a hundred places
and party in them and tell you
all about what to do
how did they swing this i know
it's like what about if we just
go we have fun and you filmed
it
i mean we don't have to do
any tasks we don't have to build
anything it's literally just going get fucked
up and eat food that's found in
some niac used to be right i
love yeah i feel like i leave
to tell huh yeah that show was
so good it was yeah david tell
and he would go out after hours
just different towns and how simple this
happening
and it was really fascinating it was
great did you happen to read that
amy schumer since she had named her
child after david tell his middle name
was a tell but then after having
the name for a while she realised
with his first name being gene that
it's kind of like genital genital oh
interesting and so she changed it to
david she
changed the middle name middle though he
changed to david dale
jean david toe
no you get your question no not
read them so yeah sweet babies i
gotta ask about that show that's on
netflix i can't remember what it's called
but i watched two episodes and i
know you guys oh what's it called
it's called like grownup or something it's
called old enough old enough oh my
god it's so cute while you watched
it yet it's when the little japanese
these kids are sent on errands with
oh i saw trailer for this yeah
watched two episodes and it was so
cute did you watch all of it's
got no i just watched the first
two but oh when i go into
scott shane this is crazy they send
a two year old task in town
like to go a mile there in
a mile back walking picks crossing the
onyx and then
brings them home we're talking like a
toddler two tours in years nine my
have to watch this and the second
one the kids like three or four
but he's such a liar it's so
funny and he's like you spent on
doing a task when he he keeps
lying and saying he's doing it but
he's not
kids lying is so funny to me
little kids when they discover what like
oh you can just say a thing
that's not true when i'm gonna do
it all the time
i don't know what you mean maybe
she lied about liking that movie yeah
she was pretending she kept saying she
wanted to work with lin manuel at
some point phase oh she like when
she was watching tv big scowl on
her face how do you like mom
hey this is going great
now there's no there's like dangerous not
a component right now i mean there's
real danger but it does feel dangerous
because the first kid is walking along
the street it's like it just feels
crazy
i don't know but yeah you assume
that there's people behind the you can't
see that are kind of guiding communicate
think that occasionally you do see hope
so but but yeah it's it did
it did feel more danger when you
know how like lax filming standards are
there it does feel like slightly more
dangerous than it then it would be
around areas they wouldn't know whenever do
it here
i will never ever ever have this
is a big question determines whether or
not i will watch this please tell
me it is not scored like any
cute baby video that you see on
instagram it's a little bit scored oh
no it's more like it's more like
america's funniest home video it's like okay
it's a lot like due to do
but you did it and it hasn't
huh
narrator much like bob sang saying like
hey little baby what are you doing
oh no in english or in japanese
in japanese and is perfect i love
it so i posted like a video
someone tagged me in like ah pizza
vending machine in japan yes you can
get a full pie which we also
saw in italy i think we talked
about it gotta be loud to magical
but it looks fantastic and then there's
like a part where like step three
is like return the the metal grate
to the in this hole and i
was like that's our country we would
never return the metal piece i never
it would never go to grounds probably
yeah yeah i'm sure it would never
go right and it would be like
we can't have that we can't have
it's very when i think about stuff
like that it's
very dispiriting to know that oh yeah
somebody would just trash this just for
no reason we do live in possibly
one of the worst countries like for
some reasons but it's horrible for when
i was like twenty five i went
on a date and one of the
first questions she asked me was that
it took you that long yeah that's
embarrassing dude
before then i just fucked boy guy
bay wow i was like let's slow
this down a little bit ah what
have you asked me some question but
one of the first questions she asked
me was was when you got to
a movie
do you throw your trash on the
ground or do you pick it up
and we're going to a movie or
she's not asking this she was just
asking me this as like a getting
to know you question and i i
it was the first time i mean
when i grew up that's what like
i mean you see that madman scene
where there they go on a picnic
and made yes
trash on the ground you know that's
sort of the vibe of when i
grew up is like you know everyone
who went to the movies is like
oh no just put it on the
floor because they cleaned it up yeah
um and so i was like oh
you just put it on the floor
right and she's like it's so disrespectful
to the the people who work there
and like gave me a lecture essentially
on our first date was wow
um but i think about that all
that now i'm like consciously always pick
up my stuff and throw it away
because course yeah you should well the
idea that because there's certain there's certain
people to think first of all i
don't think it's disrespectful to leave it
on the ground because yes that is
their job so like was like saying
if i was yeah like back in
the day
but it was like a treat for
you in a way is essentially leave
all your stuff and walk so it's
not that it's disrespectful it just helps
them out if you if you pick
up your own shit and put it
in the trash can you're going to
say it helps them out if you
leave it so they have something to
do no but they learned the satisfaction
of earning i know people people to
sit there and it's like no nobody
nobody would ever
or complain if you did part of
their job for them they they wouldn't
be like oh there's no engineer i
would love it if you guys picked
up the slack for me on this
show we pick up the trash all
the time do you don't even realize
it yeah
so here's a question for you if
you're staying somewhere this just came to
me if you were seeing somewhere that
there was a this is just what
came to you holy shit yeah you're
really going hotel now the women brainwashed
like it's like just thoughts that come
and i can't explain where or how
but then i have things i want
to say and if you were in
a hotel and there was like a
ghost rumored to be
i've been in a hotel where there
is supposedly me to go ahead now
do you spend much over those vampire
okay do you spend the whole battling
your room thinking there's a ghost or
looking for the ghost or thinking you
hear ghost or do you kind of
forget about do you know what i
stayed in the stanley hotel which was
the inspiration for the overlook
hotel in the shining whereas that's in
in colorado estes park colorado colorado excuse
me and that of course it is
supposed to be yet colorado colorado colorado
and nevada colorado colorado i've never heard
this in my life you will hear
it from people from colorado
colorado colorado why won't you come to
your shoes um so of course that
is supposed to be extremely haunted they
love telling you that right um and
you can take a tour and you
know they'll tell you shit like you
know these flowerpots were set up here
and
then the night before and then this
morning like they were all moved around
or whatever and it's like i just
to me i just hear that and
i say well that's not true but
you're just you're just your plea playing
it up and in that hotel i
would think that's not true yeah and
so i know there are hotels definitely
true i never feel oh yeah other
hotels are haunted as fuck yeah well
other hotels where it's like
less of a big story like the
shining is like such a big story
that i feel like that's that's what
we're talking about right the shining yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah there's a hotel
i like and that is awesome that's
where i stayed yeah that that content
so yeah and i only heard it
from the bartender it wasn't a thing
where they talk about it or make
a big deal about it the bartender
just like told me stories like oh
yeah this
the place is haunted and then told
me a story about it but that
was it was it a good story
and tell it well well the more
it went on the more i realised
it was he was just telling me
the plot of the sixth sense where
he was the boy know what and
he was in a tent hey it
takes skill to tell a good you
probably thought i was a ghost or
something yeah i'm not
but but guess what my best friend
ruth schwab i will say this about
the the the the stanley hotel one
thing it was haunted by it was
the tour group that started outside my
door every day
oh wow wait stay with family based
on stanley kubrick i think it's telling
tucci yeah thay yeah the the the
the the movie is based on the
hotel and the hotel is based on
stanley kubrick and so it's in the
shape of his body doesn't like him
shaped exactly like it
exactly i stayed in the neck
but they also have on two tds
in the bar they have both versions
both filmed versions of the shining playing
on a loop right so they have
the standard number one yeah the steven
weber tv version which was what three
nights and do they sync up ever
they sync up all the time all
the time and then bartender rebel and
everybody gets free shots wow that's fun
yeah it's real fun alright we have
to start doing speaking of fun speaking
of fun and shots we have to
take off two shots we have to
take a break guy okay anyway this
is the break let's take one right
now don't record this part we're in
the break
and we're back black lord you got
me um i hate shots and even
with my content i was trying to
do oh trendy shots of um these
wellness vials you know some sort of
little capsules from
wherever the fuck whole foods so it's
not just alcohol it is just the
the the process of taking a little
bit of liquid and tricky why if
it tastes bad sure so i don't
like how these shots taste these wellness
shots and i cannot i will sip
it's accept i can't throw a shot
down and just drink i have to
like sip i have to like tasted
the entire thing i don't know how
to just go straight back do you
like get so essentially you get into
your mouth first and then swallow yeah
too i suppose i can just like
throw it back with you swallow the
whole thing and then just ease little
drops of it into your throat or
do you sit why like you dre
think the hope the whole thing uncle
sheikh jassim your cheeks ago go sam
you open your throat a little sim
cringe
repeat that's so cringe
laura and you just talked about cringe
fml
when i smoked i realized one i
became conscious at one point of that
i wouldn't inhale it directly i would
sort of sort of gulp the smoke
into my mouth and then like inhale
it from there as opposed to just
like breathing through the cigarette which is
not like a french inhale
all of like it was almost yeah
it was almost like a french inhale
accepted so it stays in there yeah
and that would you know was that
would cause me to get hiccups a
lot as i say it seems that
that would be bad for various reasons
it was it sucked and i don't
recommend it do you love not smoking
anymore i man i love it so
much and i
still whenever i have a dream about
smoking it is an anxiety dream it
is not like i'm not enjoying again
it is always like that where it's
like it's in my hand and i'm
like oh no
i started yeah i take a dragon
then i go oh i store all
mice perfect streep was draino this is
like once when scott's internet went down
and he lost some of his peloton
oh your listener okay i was i
was our number season i broke my
my wordle streak and i was so
mad i was lucky
my coven made me have a fucking
axe out of six i almost killed
the phone i was doing so good
i had such a good streak going
with synthetic sorry guys
it's not cool at all
i don't know how i feel about
this the screen filmo what is it
called film filml no it's called framed
framed yeah yeah yeah that one i
don't know if it's like i guess
i'm just bull shitting when i get
it right i'm just fucking around i
don't i don't know movies from a
single frame but doing line it five
at least five things per
second how are we supposed to know
like it's like the one today was
the exorcist and i've never seen that
but i got it because i'm like
well it's a creepy lady sitting in
a bed i'm like yeah you know
i want i got that one on
the second guess wow it was the
first station what's the first thing she
was like a um there's like inside
someone said it's always a fucking sunset
there's
so many sunset every taping into vietnam
and hope a movie pops up every
son said i've just learned to read
just title yeah the turn a lot
of movies hey bill via you know
i love but what movie is good
morning vietnam sedin what movie olivia good
morning vietnam city that's what i just
fucking
ng meant that there isn't movie was
vietnam right okay did you hear what
you said and then we repeated back
no what i'm saying i searched good
morning vietnam yeah and that sure wasn't
oh yeah
what what happened wow huh you said
what movie is good morning vietnam said
in all right this is what i
mean like it's all i've got anyway
um what what movie is good for
hello you said it because i'm saying
you said there are no movies that
was vietnam and the ten i said
well what movie is good morning vietnam
setting
when you say yes
to say we're
wait tell me more about how it's
wrong what i'm saying okay
in fact you want to me what
the movie's called the good morning movie
good morning vietnam is cool i actually
i actually do mean what i'm saying
what movie is good morning vietnam set
in said in stay yeah oh wow
i am glad we kept talking because
you wouldn't say kept talking about how
i'm so fucking stupid
and i actually did say something that
made sense you did but it was
your addiction my dear i'm afraid to
go back to finishing school it's good
you simply
yeah is to blame in watching me
is good so any feeling sets in
ah great you're right what movie you're
no okay now sure that makes sense
maybe my answer would be vietnam vietnam
and the tyto yeah rare arrests and
are you saying good morning vietnam was
not in the approved list it wasn't
even though i tried to guess it
a bunch of times because big guys
luis cabrera is calling me should i
answer yeah
i have no idea oh i like
when it's a name yeah as opposed
to just like you asked pham khoi
people will have a name within it's
like whoever pays the bill then i'm
like this is tm i like it
you know and but it's someone i'm
working with or something for example they're
calling me and then it says like
you know
jonathan reiki is calling you and then
i'm like i answered and it's like
a little girl right nikki or whatever
you know but it's like don't do
that well but do you think that
they should list every single person who's
in a household on it it's just
a phone number and the okay and
i think there's someone's name i think
it should pop you're like you're saying
there's no back
color har i think it should talk
if you're already and then the one
that's calling should blink you think the
color your onus should be on the
caller to press like two four this
is the person that's calling exactly exactly
i think only thing on the call
just didn't say a name because it
throws you for a loop well like
at our
our household cool op's name is on
the bill like in the middle of
your street hold you guess she is
the bill because i i yeah people
people will say like cool up oh
go oh no no it's seeing the
land is capable of us i don't
think that's good because they're getting their
expectations they set the bar very high
they think oh i wanna speak to
cool up now
if we're going to have this great
conversation about what's in her cart and
then you're on the other end and
you're just like
how many bing bong ma would you
go what are you up to right
now and keep a cool applicable and
just wanted to i was just feeling
lonely i wanted to talk on the
phone so we're gonna turn off your
service if you don't pay this bill
also it's cool
goodbye huh
ah i don't need to be talked
to like this by the likes of
you
are you talking to the guy on
the phone talking to me off off
mike we were talking about how paul
and i have both been independently going
through our closets to purge clothing yeah
i haven't fun doing that no i
for me it's always a very shameful
experience because i buy things is it
a size oh isn't it it's like
i never bought this i never never
for where i never wore this thing
or size note the size i am
a size queen and so i'm it's
all my crowns that don't fit um
i am ah i've i've gone through
like the side stuff already after my
ah weight loss but now i feel
better i have shipped this what's that
makes me feel
you have tags on things side of
tags on things for no i don't
have tags on things oh i'm gonna
wear this and then i don't but
i owe you tag it off yeah
well it's the same thing yeah have
a tag on there you know a
handful things i've tagged and they're things
that make it through every time someone
well it says the tag on it
and then i thought last night i
just was really fucking ruthless and i
want you know what i bought that
i'm fucking
two thousand and eighteen yeah i did
not wear it all of these years
i do not want to wear it
and now i probably can't wear it
so fuck this shy to me i
just picture the waste of money you
know yeah i hate that makes me
sick
it puts me it puts me in
a bad mood here's here's what i'll
make sure yours will make you feel
better oh okay and unleash in addition
to buying these clothes that you naturally
buy when we all do we all
buy clothes the all buy clothes you
crumple up two hundred dollars a day
and throw it in the trash oh
and you'll feel better you'll feel worse
about that than the clothes thing after
a while
okay i get that logic
it just feels so bad it feels
it feels before the waste phillies fo
i have tried to sell but that's
such a fuckin there's no way it's
not a hassle if there's no way
it's it's always yeah it's always like
getting all these different parties involved it's
like you have to take all the
measurements you have to take pictures you
know all the shit um measure so
i don't
team i just donate things but yeah
you have to you have to take
first you have to take a nude
picture then you take a picture of
the clothes on then you take a
picture of yourself nude holding the clothes
next to you how much do you
think like goodwill and places like that
will cole the things that are given
because i feel like it's like i
know i'll deal
sent i'd also heard that from somebody
that worked at goodwill years ago that
i used to know that the the
way that's done is not it's not
because they just put like entirely fair
well they they keep good stuff for
themselves or whatever and you know i
know it's not dumb and then they
sell stuff well um yeah it's not
democratic the store is not good
vote it should be a meritocracy yeah
so on everyone should hold they should
hold up each item that's that's donated
and then everyone should vote on which
employees should get to take it home
yeah who it's most like or who
it's most for and then anything that
doesn't get voted on can stay and
they can sell it yeah organ will
should be just an auction house and
you go in there and they have
auctions every hour you go in there
they auction the stuff off and then
whatever doesn't get sold you can have
that if you're an employee like how
often does goodwill donate a you know
five thousand shirts to like homeless people
or something yeah i know it's like
that every like every hour usually
i don't know if they're there i
don't know like the the extent of
the goodwill operation i believe it's just
that's it it's the store so it's
it's it's for people to get inexpensive
clothing they don't think and go to
a place to get an expensive but
i will say i feel like in
l a it's not cheap goodwill no
it doesn't the prices are not low
enough they're not as those they
should be up isn't goodwill also a
charitable organization so yeah i'd say it's
like bad or something i don't know
with all the ins and outs yeah
i don't i don't know i haven't
googled it myself or like it's like
how weight loss is problematic in some
ways and you people always third year
that there's a name of there like
the name of charity they're the name
of altruism but then you find out
they stuck just like
everything else but i do there are
there are when i have suits i
will donate them to this company that
um to this organization that gives suits
to ah homeless people who are trying
to get jobs i love that i
love when i can donate to overly
specific cause where i yeah ok this
will actually get used and will just
go in some pile and yes this
is their whole thing yeah yeah
yeah that's nice yeah yeah well i'm
a big ass donation because i'm going
crazy getting rid of some i'm feeling
so good about it it feels great
i'm just like because i've been shoving
clothes in my closet and then going
i don't wear any of this and
it makes me feel bad about myself
to see it all and feel like
i'm in a lot of that a
lot of it i have worn a
lot it's just you know the
pandemic kind of changed my style and
all that stuff so i feel like
my entire closet is aspirational like ok
i'll get back oh i'll get back
to that yeah some point
so true but then i was thinking
that was not making me feel good
so i know i was getting so
close to that that place of like
there were a couple of things are
like oh i'm almost there and then
the holidays came and i gained a
bunch of fuckin weight back and now
i'm trying to take that off and
i'm trying but that's the main thing
is trying not to feel bad about
it
yeah bro i'm trying to feel yeah
but i think that's good because then
i was like you know what i
just have to like buy jeans that
fit me right now and that's where
living and then feel good about that
and then that's making me feel more
excited and then i'm like whatever happens
next i'll get new jeans you know
wearing clothes that fit you as opposed
to wearing clothes that almost fit you
in so
it's feels so much better yeah it's
great like diana just literal better and
yeah we should we should buy each
other it's a tailor sessions we should
buy each other wardrobes and just see
what kind of style i want they
should give each other five thousand dollars
okay this is a good idea it's
this other great idea
it's a great way let's just eat
each other five thousand dollars to do
whatever we want with yeah nobody has
any money but we feel like we're
gonna get emergency alert oh i have
those off i guess i'm not getting
thing endangered elderly oh no no silver
law details that i'm not gonna click
on those unless the unless the elderly
wanders through my
house
i'm not going to see them i
would absolutely did a fascinating they're here
yeah i would click on that i
have information leading to the capture of
this ultrasonic ever surrender arrest
catch and release
i have a ton of like i
have probably a hundred podcast shirts because
anytime we would make a shirt i
would get lane and it's like ooh
and i'm never gonna wear them because
i don't want to be the person
wearing your own shirt i know but
i but i want to honor the
native yeah yes what you make it
quilt oh we recently that from my
dad with some
old shirts from his travels and it's
that whole night i love that that's
my mom my mom donated the shirts
and he was like fine with them
being he was like okay it's time
i'm gonna just do you want me
to make a quilt for your dad
yeah of all your podcasts i just
sent you my podcast shirts too cause
i have a lot of shirts like
that and i was like it'd be
cool to
or like from like shows or like
you know things done that yeah is
really hard to part with i find
i think it as a cute way
to to have it i think it's
like i think looks like kind of
special and you can just also fold
it up into one box so i
have a suit made of all that
oh yeah i've already so comfortable what
a comfortable suit yeah you
could you feel like pajamas maybe i'll
just make pajamas how about that
pajamas paul i would like i would
like to see you wearing pajamas in
the shape of suits and i know
they have to make them right like
three piece but oh i'm sure they
do i'm sure heidi race i'm sure
they do
i had a pair of years ago
um somebody made me a pair of
double breasted pajamas um but they never
quite fit right um but they were
they were very cool they were like
stamps like a prairie club to your
dramas yeah they looked really nice snapple
chested pajamas cbl gras
double doable i'm the hamburgers label label
label double business as double toil and
lawyers barry blinky birkin lubin
yeah that definitely does that yeah dev
no i thought it was down
this week's offspring song oh they they
imitate it why would they be offspring
come on yeah never but i was
in a rush ridiculous but it's dumb
i know dumb you don't get you
know it's the first time i thought
the offspring wasn't the smartest band the
heads like if you if you hosted
a variety show and at the end
you tugged you
or ear every time it's like this
new marshall group that epic that they
did that like i don't know it
i mean it was a big hit
it's so epic because it would look
ok when offspring did it with starving
to death lever did it did osprey
come out and play i believe alright
so the one where they yell or
keep them separated
it might only a mop and loma
is it why don't you get a
job i don't know well i'm sure
someone knows they are tweeting us that
guy one i'm thinking about them now
that guy just he just yelled right
he just extra harlan dexter hades he's
got a doctorate in something so oil
smartest
frontmen in rock what oils is a
doctor
well what did the doctor when people
have chemistry or cps he's like yeah
gotta keep em separated
repeat i'm talking about generals yeah i
believe i went to is already on
your son did you really i think
so i think i did you into
his wife put your bag huh
but you go to the bedroom and
thought you were telling janie went because
she was still going through clothes and
that's how i talked to my wife
how dare you talk to janey like
dexter holland sings at us
alright we have to take okay good
alright well we'll be right back with
the three right
can we're back to any were singing
about i'm liza he is um the
hands on me
and i will never be free
oh what song is this the guest
pooh these eyes cry i don't have
any guesses just tell me scott this
is fun it puts me in mind
of abbott and his friend castello i
believe i did this with on a
certain show where i was talking about
the band that sang american woman yeah
wouldn't be suppressed
sounds like you um alright it's time
for three-tier guys it truly is and
i'm ready and scott i can even
read ah this one you and lauren
yeah go ahead that would be absolutely
splendid laura thank you here it comes
this was submitted by elliott mattson does
he turn into jam know that
a different man by the name of
the bateson bateson this is called sitcom
heart-to-heart and the theme song goes like
this lauren
sick cum heart to heart it's time
to share your part don't let out
a fart because it's a sitcom heart
to heart perfect thank you players one
and two
players want to play i was like
just keep going just keep going
players wanting to play the parental figures
of a late eighties early nineties era
sitcom they go into player three's bedroom
player throws the child to have a
heart to heart talk with them about
something that happened that day this is
classic sitcom stuff the parental figures determine
what the scenario is ahead of time
to discuss with the child and through
their
chat condolences admonishment the child has to
figure out what it is exactly that
they did great so okay the people
or the parents will text each other
and agree upon what the event was
and then the third person has to
figure it out so lauren whom she'll
be the child lauren and i will
be parents you're looking i a child
and the child is we all know
his father
to the man i'm texting you lauren
okay great
here we go and sense all right
there we go i hey hey putting
hey mom hey honey can you end
up to mind yeah do you mind
putting that down on a yeah sorry
what is it what are you playing
with um you know playing a game
that's your penis is out what are
you doing was playing a sex game
and thought it was a song
no i have my phone next to
my penis to play the game for
like two to compare sizes honey we're
getting back here we have to focus
on what's okay we're not here to
punish you for whatever weird sex we
didn't even know you're doing that will
punish you for that later i guess
yeah paul um yeah we heard about
what happened
yeah we heard you did huh yeah
they called they were none too pleased
they called you yeah ooh they called
it well they texted first and then
and then cool it was too many
texts you know back and forth so
we're just like let's just pick up
the phone and which one called
principi drax principal drax yeah and he
told us what the what the people
in charge of the whole thing said
what do you call them the
i don't know the terminology i don't
know there are many this hobby of
yours but paul this you know and
you know who's in charge and you
know what you did and i mean
we just we think you're way too
talented for that you're too talented smart
you can't do this put i mean
put to this anything positive
well i mean they said well they
had yeah all they have to say
is positive things other than what you
did you could have over your tone
i thought something was wrong well well
the one thing that you did wrong
is really wrong but i mean it's
so mean to service to yourself into
us yeah well it's a disservice to
us because we're the ones who trained
you
and we put all the money into
this yeah what did the it's a
lot of money paul it's expensive for
you get your dorky glasses in your
stupid outfit yeah
and and the the the the actual
you know the board ain't cheap you
know what i mean board the little
whores the board green did that what
did they tell you that i did
well what do you think you did
for us into
that way i know i was there
with my dorky glasses and my stupid
outfit and the bore and there was
the board and i don't know i
guess i just got nervous i don't
think it's you got nervous i think
you were trying to help someone less
fortunate or less intelligent than you and
that's maybe not right i saw this
person and
and that made me nervous
and so i thought i got to
help why are you nervous to see
you see this person every single day
at school this is your
no yeah relationship to them you know
what it is i don't want to
sort of label on it but it's
my classmate i think yeah but a
little more than a classmate yeah i
mean my friend yeah yeah but a
little more than i mean you know
like my status event yeah exactly wesley
exact you know he's part of our
family but i know you guys love
wesley sometimes i think
like more than me we don't and
we actually we might start we might
start loving him more than you if
you let him continue to let him
excel in this area
yeah i know but i guess i
felt bad for him because my best
friend and all and thought like maybe
i should let him excel in this
area instead of me for a change
but you're the gte you're the genius
i know that's why i wanted him
to feel like it like he doesn't
even he doesn't even know what the
horses called the i know but
i told him it's that's the night
and you just imagine a night riding
on him and and and he rides
all of it chessboard then he talked
about david hasselhoff in knight rider for
like four and i'm like no that's
not olivia that's not on me
i mean that shows reruns so we
see it i guess so kit all
that yeah um the whole thing but
look you get you we put we
pay the money so you can go
out there and prove it to schools
that you're a genius i know but
i thought you know my friend wesley
never gets a chance to do this
so i gave him my outfit
my stupid glasses and i let them
impersonate me and the big chess match
well that was the weird part that
we didn't hear about oh shit nobody
told us forget i said that so
you're just swapping outfits with what he
really wants to view that video of
you doing where you need after you
gave him the outfit
well are you saying mom that video
i saw of you doing the six
flags dance like that old man yeah
they didn't ten ten ten twenty or
whatever the song is and then ten
ten and there's no data no that
was me when i was putting the
camera so wait so you gave you
gave wesley your outfit yeah and you
dressed up like the old man and
the signal that pity is that videos
old videos old but doesn't worry i
just got tiktok okay but look the
my mom's on tick toggle new way
to see my dance no mom everybody's
talking about the way that it was
yeah
we'll call these things are these things
are important because if you get if
you get noticed if you get noticed
by winning these it can open up
colleges you know i mean you can't
just do what you did you know
and okay leslie right so that's that's
what you're mad about i let wesley
impersonate me for the gesture no
oh we didn't know about the impersonate
that parts of weird were mad at
you because you let him win
or we're just saying it oh i
thought he already did say it but
he isn't
i love you when you forfeited you
through the you through the whole thing
well but differ good reason whom it
was it doesn't feel so morn so
what level of us more for change
are you going to cry
little boogie
raise a pussy yeah i did
thank you
you also married one
oh yeah too bad the nexus sitcom
whatever it was with these friend was
filmed before a live studio audience this
show is yellow was well he's hardly
in it
talk about why it's spin off but
it's like i don't think i actually
said it i think i was close
but but scott did i think just
let me know what what it was
yeah and then i did too yeah
you confirmed it i mean i was
dancing around your data that is talking
about
everybody's talking about i got i just
got just got a text excuse me
i'm eileen is this mister jason's phone
number mister jason obviously yes what does
she's calling jason momoa o j sa
ma ma you could pretend to be
him it's me oh c'mon ninny
kangana seventeen days
alright so now do you want to
do it again i don't know one
let's do one more struggling more let's
make it a little tighter and um
i do want to rest my old
papers who wants to be the child
i'll be the child okay okay god
bless you text you want to text
me the thing yes god i do
oh boy lauren
was ah i have a daughter lauren
hey lauren um oh your dad your
dad and i ah we need to
talk to you about something lower and
we got to talk to you what
i mean there was something what are
you doing it's not what you did
before is it no i'm recording chose
over your favorite home videos
what we shouldn't do that recording your
own i'm like cowering like dawson's creek
onto a tape that has your precious
home videos no not dawson's creek regionals
where i'm from listen honey we have
to talk to you about something very
important what is it well it's your
behavior yeah mine
mine eat rocks hey we don't say
that and the cells go anyway because
it doesn't really make need a refresher
go out front and read the sign
what doesn't make sense because you wouldn't
eat rocks because they don't taste good
yeah no one would eat rocks so
did you notice on you that's i
think the first thing i think is
how they would break your teeth i
don't even think about the taste but
they probably would also
taste very bad
listen no more you goddamn money
we have talked you know sit there
shut up shut the fuck up fine
what
did you remember what you did on
on sunday what when ate all halloween
candy and then barbed it up into
your closet you did that on sunday
i don't know what day it was
i'm just a kid i don't have
a calendar will you know you know
what you did on sunday because sunday
is why you did it
oh yeah it happened on sunday church
yeah yeah exactly and boy oh boy
did you ever not want to go
to church yeah you let everyone know
it well so you ruin church for
everyone
ah why because i eat the eucharist
no harden on this on the state
i think it was a little bit
bigger than you it was bigger than
you going up on stage at church
oh wait what because i got up
on the cross and then did my
little like dance know did that to
thank god knows i don't really worry
about that yes
well then what did i do i
mean what what was this answer you
know when i got in the pews
and and and use my knees to
kind of walk like i was going
down the pew little like bench thing
know people like that actually okay i
actually was because we yeah but before
the tragedy we start guessing stuff guessing
for a second honey and let me
let me just talk to you
you know when i was about your
age i did something that got everybody
so mad at me i thought no
one would ever like me again what
did you do
oh i stabbed the guy in the
bank but when i confessed whereas the
bank the bank on fifth oh oh
oh you mean inside a bit oh
okay yeah no i want to say
the bank and i stabbed one of
the oh i thought you when you
said stabbed him in the bank i
thought sounds like you guys have something
to work out and you think that
that's weird but we'll talk about it
later cool
new hip slang term for like a
no real thing hey huh oh don't
ever cause it we don't close doors
in this house i'll take it off
the goddamn it just you should to
close doors cause everytime you take a
shit fucking saw you should close doors
you should to close doors oh yeah
i'm sound like a fool anyway
after i confessed what i'd done
people were mad but they forgave me
and i realized what i did was
wrong even ho person that you stepped
forgave you know he didn't make it
and i confess okay it's yeah i
mean your father your father only did
that to one person you did it
to everyone i drink the wine and
stole the money from the basket this
is getting worse and worse worse and
worse before what you did arguably a
hint which thing i'm supposed to talk
talk about you it's fucking maniac
that the biggest thing that's everyone's is
huge and you can't remember it when
i wides listen now no one will
ever be able to go to church
again and we're never gonna say around
in churchtown yes you dumb little creep
so what your nightmare carry guns to
have first everyone was inside but they
didn't die yes yeah you're a mass
murderer that's a really bad thing i
did we're actually one of the way
are you confessing you're not dad and
dad well we are but we're also
caused yeah we've been working out
undercover the whole life waiting for me
to do something but we had a
bad feeling about you we started going
to the police academy at secret and
we just got our badges oh wait
you actually when i just watched police
academy same thing i mean yeah you
really want to go down like give
me the badge yeah they give you
a fuckin badgett a gun yeah anyway
hold anyways you're under arrest
cuff me up daddy you're gonna be
tried like an adult but i do
too too too too too hard ah
that was fun that was fun i
found one i loved it was it
was great to see you lauren feels
better soon i hope so if there's
not another episode next week
eek it's because lauren parrish because it's
not she's scared to say like that
at all no no no no no
if if ores you like with it
because she perished maybe it's true someone
who has could die at any moment
yeah nothing is promised alright everybody stop
listening now but before you do
do please know that we love you
and that we are threesome usa on
on twitter and instagram and three m
usa gmail dot com if you would
like to send us a fuckin feature
ideal thanks for listening and if you
want to hear ad-free versions or the
archive head over to stitcher premium or
cbp wells dot com and go
in peace to love and serve the
lord bye bye bye