yeah
my mama
no
oh welcome back to three dogs were
three of them were freedom that's always
used to say say hi that's so
quicker to say hi fifa it's so
dark in here hi freedom friends sat
back i'm so scared her throat and
friends were three of them were your
friends we are your
friends we are deejays were definitely d
j were club deejays and we are
your friends we specialize in mashups we
love to do mashups like um happy
birthday in the alphabet happy birthday a
g f g um la la mine
he goes paul f tompkins my name
goes lorne lab my name is you
guys scott ackerman you're so boring and
conventional oh don't judge me man that's
my lifestyle that's just who i am
that's just too that's just who i
yeah that's the way you
a news that's the way it is
with songs that celine dion oh man
you want it to most yeah yeah
yeah woo okay i do know that
yeah yeah yeah heard that
news that's the way it is boots
i would see her in concert yeah
you know that'd be good i bet
it will be a great you go
to vegas and go see her i
just all want to do is go
to vegas and see a crazy big
show that's doing i never slide in
and show wow no i haven't i
haven't either i only go to trash
shithole rochelle i'm saying about that
i wanna see a good show mom
you know i really wanna see a
share i want to see share bad
li i love cher i just was
listening yesterday to a wonderful cover of
walking meme walking in memphis by share
oh yeah was it like that yeah
yeah even walk into males na
oh and my own food she does
a great cover of it play it
i saw a great cover of her
voice on this commercial it was like
sin ten different singers it was so
good wow what like you're lying
i of it i can't place it
i can't place there's a new commercial
outward people are just saying that's a
walking memphis yeah
kudo ma lose weight to lose body
i love it thanks to d j
e scorpio da calm down
this comes to us from d j
scorpio dot com this is the official
music video you see have remember for
your video so slightly older scorpio dot
com this is from a few years
back i don't see i guess class
ticket
ooh us girls can be
any male force member falls backwards
you need to beetle
because i'm thinking ostrich
oliver she's great
please
yeah
alright how that's a scar get in
there his shit fuck yeah oh god
this is the final episode goodbye oh
no what if you spelled your name
s k eighteen you said it's pronounced
scott i would ah it's sky i
love ska music my name is scott
my name is scott
was funny happened on the tour that
we forgot to talk about we talked
about that goddamn cookie cake yeah we
talked about we did not talk about
paul okay here's a postscript to our
ah st paul episodes so the wicked
child who was across from paul that's
right
was bothering aw aw a yes this
is perfect and so so i our
second show and i tell the story
so you may not know alright going
please tell it so
we're leaving we're going we we finished
our second show in st paul the
next day we are flying tobacco chicago
chicago yeah sweet home chicago chicago suis
we say okay we're gonna we'll walk
nine thirty in the morning to go
i'm thirty was our lobby calls we
all all get into the cabs and
go to the arrow i said ok
now one of the things that i
love in an hotel is when they
have the card where you can fill
it your breakfast order and hanging on
the door for a specific time yes
love it i've done it i will
do it every time it's available every
time and do you not wake up
until it gets
there or d i usually will some
alarm ten minutes before sometimes i'll send
those i don't want to be new
when i sometimes while i open the
door i will but i'll bring i
sleep in the buff paper ivory sleep
nude i bring pajamas so you you're
fine opening the door in pajamas to
his yeah i feel like
i don't live there here's my question
all stranger about your plan yeah having
them a wake you up oh no
huh so sometimes i will send alarm
but if i if it's late as
it was that night
i'm going to my planet to get
as much sleep as possible because you
have a half hour window for that
delivery and so i feel like if
you're setting your alarm ten minutes before
the half hour and they don't show
up for until the end of the
half hour i'm racing forty minutes exactly
so i let them wake me up
and then i crawl into bed i
open the door how
many times they said oh you were
not awake sir sorry never having to
say my name so they said
because i'm opening the door
there are no times if they said
whoa i'll come back they're not like
giving the law like sarkozy by the
way i have to say sweet home
chicago i'm in the room for approximately
fifteen minutes
suddenly the the housekeeper bursts in no
knock nothing just like you wow opens
the door i'm like what the fuck
and on and accept they were like
oh sorry like but no like nothing
anyway so i do this plan i'm
gonna get as much sleep as i
can love it when a plan comes
together i love it and then i
put a cigar in my mouth
i say like monica lewinsky just like
bill cosby
wow clinton bill cosby clinton
did not have sexual relations with a
woman
i'd have wanted but it depends on
the definition of ziz so
i am awakened in the morning not
by knock-knock dog breakfast is here mister
tompkins i love you but they say
i love you every time it's so
sweet why do you write about you
check i write on the card i
say please i will not accept this
unless you tell me how i know
it's really my breakfast okay because it
could be in his acid exactly i'm
waking not buy love
mr tomkins but by the fucking old
lady across from me and this is
where the wicked child was running in
an hour wake of the doma style
of the wicked shot a wig shop
but we'd also do not talk about
the elderly people who had to have
an opportunity if we could change conversation
about everything in the hallway yeah when
they came or went any
nowhere i just can't believe i missed
all of that in my room and
i was only a few doors i
know they were right across the hall
from me so and i believe they
were closer to chef shaven chef kevin
rogers have chef so i go and
i looked through the people in there
leaving they got a luggage rack they're
having this big discussion about whatever it's
so irritating when people leave hotel
lz they should be quiet because people
are sleeping but everyone just thinks when
they walk out of a hotel room
they're like well i no longer am
a human being anymore but i don't
see anyone around here so i'll just
yell yeah everyone else is on the
same schedule i am yeah there are
no ones in these rooms exactly so
i go up to the people look
out and i like bang on the
door
that's oval mad because i think they're
waking me up early yes before my
breakfast is cold for breakfast has come
and then i'm not sure what time
it is and i think where's the
breakfast and i look i opened the
door crack to see you and your
bike yeah it's my nature but i
kept stub of candle
i think we made this joke two
episodes sure
and then i ah i see that
the breakfast card is still on the
door amazing and now i'm like oh
now i do not know what time
it is i don't know how long
i've slept and i go pick up
i look at the clock and i
see what time it is pick up
the phone see classic same time it
is procedure i see missed calls i
see uh
um you know texts what did not
happen and what had happened earlier what
had happened was was that no one
called up to my room so i
did and don't think they didn't put
the call i didn't put that but
but i heard it ring see this
is what's so odd to me way
here's the other side of of what
happened which was
does ah we were all down there
at nine thirty and no answer from
paul i sent one cab off and
i'm like okay well you know another
one still is taking fifteen minutes to
arrive so paul will just get in
this one nothing i went up to
the desk i had them call your
room all sorts of stuff i bet
they called the wrong room yeah
might have and i was and i
was so i was really mad at
that because that of course would have
woken me up and and your cell
phone would not have woken you up
because it was on silent executive but
sleepy tired sleepy sleepy town so the
wicked child saved the day the wicked
child's fail because you just made it
to the airport for our two hour
delay
that's right well you got there right
before we're gonna start boarding yeah they
literally two two minutes before you're boarding
and you said do i have time
to get some to eat and i
said no they're boarding then immediately they
said oh by the way you have
time to get something to eat paul
so then i was able to get
extreme i love you mr tompkins sweet
again but yeah i
and i guess i'll never do that
again which sucks because i really liked
it as a plan well it could
work can i here's here's the question
that i can't trust maybe you need
to like leave your phone here's a
question i have was there something on
the menu card that said you have
to leave it before this time or
pick it up because sometimes they have
words that's on the cardano and before
miller know i had it on
because they didn't pick it up the
night before and i thought like oh
because i had the do not disturb
sign over it so i used the
same card that same day so it
was absolutely it was out there for
twenty four hours yeah all day long
okay yeah okay if they didn't pick
it up the night before i maybe
would have set an alarm
well but i thought i thought the
problem was they couldn't see it right
because either do not disturb sign over
it right still and then that's probably
what it was no this time that
thing was outfront i think this was
their phone this was there by the
way the other thing chevron just er
chef kevin reminds me of is
is that there was a big problem
with the with getting the rooms and
there was like an additional form that
i need to fill out once we
got there with the credit card that
was not my credit card it was
it was my assistance credit card and
they're like well if you don't have
this form then we can't accept payment
it's got us stealing his sister's identity
and i was like but their rooms
or paid for already you know all
sorts of stuff and then at a
certain point i was getting so frustrated
and i said why is this more
complicated than any other hotel we've been
to and the the woman said we're
downtown huh
she did that wasn't i made no
sense it all happens here we're downtown
so i guess downtown is the excuse
for why they don't pick up the
menu cards or anything i tell you
what happened to me in chicago where
i want to puke again no i
went to sweet green and i told
you a free monster okay you know
i'll projectile patty over here was the
next day i went to sweetgreen marine
a great restaurant if you haven't there's
one right over here buy your own
i just had it today so i
was in line i ah you know
someone was checking out when i was
there then i get i go to
the end of the counter start ordering
my process you know we all know
how this word i go i get
to the fr
front and they say twenty five dollars
now and i die and i thought
that's a lot but i'm i guess
maybe it's airport price i yeah it
was like i don't even know why
i just going with it and i
was like okay like they know what
the shirt twenty five dollars for a
salad whatever it doesn't make sense but
i was just like not thinking that
hard you're traveling and so you're just
convinced with everything this is the color
teacher here and also shit is so
expensive in l a yeah yeah yeah
i'm pretty much everything yeah and yeah
it is it is fourteen dollars the
other woman who made my salad said
no way she only got that one
thing and then the woman checking juncos
know your friend said you were paying
for her and i was like huh
but she goes that girl who just
loves she said you
yeah he's got this this isn't i
was a i don't know who that
wasn't i know i'm not with anyone
and then they're like what and they
were freaking out and they were like
oh my god like perfect granny my
god i just like let her go
i believe that she was with you
and i didn't charge her and whoa
yeah and then i came back for
bench next day and they remembered me
and i thought that was nice
and what did they say when they
remember you think about this is the
girl that happened to yesterday i love
you guys i was so crazy they
thought it was a good story it's
a great story and even better in
the telling you are aware look i
know we're all storytellers but you are
exceptional at it you know what i
can't wait to try
a i actually i know you're kidding
and i also think i'm a horrible
storyteller really i think you're good i
think that i i'm getting better but
i think i used to just go
here's what happened at the end now
let me walk you home but that's
actually sometimes i prefer that because i'll
tell you that the way and and
this comes up in pitches when you
pit shows a lot of people
like to like to never tell you
what you're about to hear they just
started the beginning and then and that
leaves the listener sitting there going like
what is this store oh wait so
yeah what is what and then suddenly
something happens that you can latch onto
where it's like they get to the
subject matter and and the listener picks
up and goes oh okay so this
is a story about a birthday cake
no it's about treasures oh yeah yeah
he's getting to the treasures into birthday
cake a form of treasure oh no
mike and i have to say you're
both very dumb the pentel pen was
a hope that were sent to us
by our listener are absolutely amazing loving
them and i actually think it's might
be my new brand penn tells your
newborn
chantelle i'll wear a jacket that has
pinto all over it every day the
rest of my life and you'll drive
a race car because pentel pentel get
at us these we we want you
to advertise nascar sponsors are great gel
pens and yeah remember how i asked
you guys what load brand you would
wear for you i don't remember that
i remember but i don't remember what
i said i don't
member you go back and listen to
previous episodes i'll veto it would be
censored on tuesday i think mine was
mine was driscoll strawberries
look we can sit here rehashing old
episodes they're still doing okay we didn't
we don't remember anything do you remember
episode one no remember your president nixon
that's a song it's song i saw
a meme that was like that picture
of bjork where she has her hands
in front of her mouth it's like
an iconic kind of poe from the
it's so so quiet it's maybe it's
like i'm covered no single cover but
but or maybe yeah maybe surfer just
like a picture i don't know but
ah somebody wrote on it
it like someone wrote a meme that
was like i don't know who is
who this is but she is vibing
or whatever and i was like like
who is who is this woman what's
her deal she's vibing or something and
i was like
just maddening to think that like there's
someone doesn't know like like yeah yosef
is and you're just like thinking it's
like a cool picture of someone like
i don't know it's just weird sorry
to this woman i loved that interview
but did you watch that no what
does that kiki palmer did um what
is it called a lie detector test
for vanity fair and then they show
her with subject matter
anything is they have a bunch of
celebrities doing detectors horrifying it's actually pretty
fun to watch okay but she ah
sees a picture of dick cheney and
she's like i don't know who this
man is yeah right let's see if
there's that part i might have actually
made it separate it's she's right behind
me isn't she yeah all rounder armed
prone to irritation
than was disgusting and yeah it's basic
army close-up of an underarm
okay we're gonna get down just to
admit that the
oh yeah good daddy did you did
that oh no it's too long they've
been kind of pointing to meme now
i also watched a really great thing
i don't know what you're talking about
so she's she's hooked up to a
lie lie detector she's looking at a
picture of dick cheney says i don't
know who this is right i'm so
i don't know who this anyway and
here here to the service shut
to say that true jackson vp was
a better vp than dick cheney
it was
well y'all really tested me awesome stuff
that i i hate to say it
i hope it'll sound ridiculous i don't
know who this man is i mean
we walked down the street that wouldn't
i wouldn't know what they sorry to
this man she telling the truth so
now everyone's saying sorry to this man
i was okay that is also like
she's so young but she
she's saying it like she's an elderly
yes like she's very proper about it
i i hope i don't sound ridiculous
yeah sorry to this man i love
it i did an episode of true
jackson vp day yeah she was fucking
great yeah i do that or was
of andy gordon the rock sounding word
to big thing i don't know who
kiki palmer is sorry to that woman
oh well she was
trudy rejecting vp what is now actually
now actually a host of a morning
show she's like morning really yes um
she's like good morning america or something
oh wow
what's morning he is doing let's go
morning
let's repeat yourself we call that doing
stuff yeah she's a good boy tangerine
and our side tech show host good
morning america with michael strahan and sara
henke oh wow which i think is
a great boost of energy and youthfulness
in the show you did vibrancy it
brings a lifeblood that day was three
to four missing okay if you ate
a whole
most are like be one of the
personalities on a morning show would you
want it to be like ryan and
kelly where they're like two people in
chairs like and they just talk about
their lives and kind of like bringing
gas or we wanna be like the
view where you like to talk about
hot topics and share opinions or would
you want to be like good morning
america where you like do activities with
like random people cooking this now and
we're doing
want to be like this show where
it's the three of us but in
the morning really early wow i would
like it to be i actually did
a pilot that was a sensibly a
comedy show but also kind of a
real thing for a morning show huh
and the gimmick was it would happen
very late at night so it could
be called the first
morning show so it would come along
like well one yeah exactly yeah yeah
and ah it was a weird experience
it was not um they were trying
to find a co-host and they for
some reason like asked me for a
list of people that i would like
to coast with a completely ignored that
amazing yeah
they said what about this one person
said i don't i don't think she's
like great and they're like okay great
it's gonna be her
it's gonna be hard then um the
the and i kept asking these were
guys that i knew that were doing
and i kept asking like are we
gonna look bringing it into people that
i had suggestions to like do a
test or whatever and they just wouldn't
respond to me it was so weird
that's maddening and then so then we
did the pilot and
and ah you know it didn't get
picked up then they tried to sell
it to another network did not mention
it to me at all um and
ah try to sell it with somebody
else the network didn't somebody else in
place of you yes now the network
didn't like that guy but they had
already said no to me because they
saw
pilot right the one who'd still called
me up still asked if i would
audition again for this new network that
already said they didn't want me
it was so embarrassed it was like
the most funky request i ever got
docs like what do you think is
going to happen what what happens accept
i'm humiliated now on this show was
it real or scripted there were real
interviews and also like their scripted bits
but then the interviews were were real
were very much like a
one show interview so who but yeah
would i still want to know your
answer the show was a mess well
but i still don't know what i
would do i would do a show
like that yeah i thought that's the
show that i would do yeah i
think it'd be fun would you ever
do that scott i thought look my
eric potential job prospects are few and
far between so yeah do anything
yeah yeah very self-deprecating lately what this
about your ashes you're anxious about the
film maybe baby i don't know but
i think doing a morning show i
was thinking about this the other day
because i was like
you know when i first started doing
comedy van gang ah i was sort
of thinking like ah because my friend
had the morning show at indy one
of three i was like it would
be fun to do the morning show
and indie one or three and i
think just like it would maybe be
fun for a week i think it
would be like a fun thing to
do to guest for a week but
to
do it every day i just can't
imagine doing the well the kelly lee
or whatever no me neither but kelly
ripa the quest the question was if
you had if you had to do
a type of show horses gunpoint which
type would you want to do okay
i would probably like to do i
do a mixture of talking to people
in hot topics the view is
what okay that's you okay great i
do that but do i have to
have other people i have to do
it with like yes
i have to do with whoopi gold
nobody's playing me would be for just
being here on the view for men
or men with varying personalities and opinions
ah that seems dicey to me i
wouldn't like them dice will be their
dice will be there i'm in
the iceman cometh i always think i
would enjoy being a host on the
view um or eugene like i think
maybe have some finally was jingling michelle
collins did it you know michelle yeah
i know michelle yeah i loved her
on it but she was almost too
funny for it it's like yeah they
can deal with it yeah whereas although
i will say the cafe no kelly
ritchie
yeah cathy rigby
the kelly ripa show that seems a
little more like you can have your
personality and age it's a little more
singular and they talk about their own
lives a lot like don't be like
i just was watching yesterday and the
hotel was getting ready and it was
like um she's like telling this long
story that was really boring and i
was like i know the feeling luckily
you and i are yummy
chris saved the day it just was
so weird cause i was like wow
she just has this platform she can
just talk about anything and like they
had to fill hours so obviously i'm
gonna be gold yeah and i also
know i feel very you know what
i'm not this slam on you it's
a slam on everything we show yeah
it's true it's true it's true strew
oh
you still like them all and i
think it's a fun it takes a
lot of energy and a lot of
personality or if you could if you
could i think you would have to
choose one or the other either having
a show like that for death or
or being like an actress oh i'd
be an actress you'd be an actress
why is it way more fun i
want to be acting more fun than
you'd then yeah but i mean this
is a form of that is it
not it is but um don't you
prefer i mean i've referred play character
about you paul i like playing characters
i do like interviewing people but it
can get um ah tedious you can
get tedious to because not every constantly
interested in other people
well yeah because lotta not everyone meets
you halfway yeah so kenny loggins would
he would always be driveway but then
he'll take you to the danger zone
yeah that's true that's the price you
pay but it's true like when even
when you're doing a podcast and someone
like doesn't really hold up their end
of the conversation yeah like this isn't
fun anymore
yeah yeah yeah the drag i think
that they're doing a late night talk
show it used to be something that
i really wanted to do but then
it just seems boring to me now
having to talk to all these randoms
yeah i think that's something that i
that's definitely something that i used to
want to do but i don't think
i wanna do that anymore i think
it was just i wanted to be
a comedian because that's where yeah he
was yeah man you know someone
it was a variety show man that's
what i wanna do yeah man variety
that is what you should do and
that is what would be a that
is what you will do and that
is what we'll have tomorrow why don't
executives listen to our show and give
us away
if you think do you think like
anyone in the industry listens to this
executives like people in charge of like
networks and stuff like even care about
entertainment like they wouldn't listen to their
favorite podcasts and i think i'd be
so inundated with stuff all the time
that they're like not then seeking it
out in their free time i think
every time i go into it any
kind of meeting someone says i love
the rpm show awesome
really yeah so i think that symbol
do listen to podcasts no not this
one that is where a highway wow
we are outside of it as well
and people do listen to the show
and you can't if you shit on
yourself you're shitting on me bro and
i don't want that right i'll just
show it's okay because oh me hey
yeah no yeah
i like a snake saying don't shit
on me does the snake get shit
on a lot if you're gonna tread
on you're probably gonna shit on yeah
i wonder if a snake does get
shit on a lot
like a snake is down there on
the ground solicitor it's just around jody
run under like shit is going to
drop not everyone shits and toilets at
a certain point that is true at
a certain point someone's going to shit
and a snake will be underneath what
do you what do you mean someone
someone something somewhere
somehow are you talking about birds i'm
talking about birds talking about wolves i'm
talking about people i'm talking about anything
that shits is gonna eventually shit on
a snake and the snake's gonna be
like hey what about me i think
i i would bet that shaped snakes
do not get shit on as much
as you think they do i but
okay theres they're long and thin so
i
we'll give you yeah it would be
easier miss them eve hard target i
also think that your god i also
think that they're not about so much
about sneaking up on animals that are
larger than themselves yeah so that to
catch an animal unawares in that way
where the animals just like did to
it too this is a good place
to shit no snakes around
i think it's very rare i think
that they're not looking at each other
i think that the things shitting the
hume the human the mammal whatever it
is shitting is not thinking about a
snake is just merely shitting than the
snake is merely going about it's business
and boom collide you're listening to time
it's like a person walking in front
of a bill
building in somebody dumped something out of
the building yes exactly which is what
you've been shit on by a bird
have united course i yeah many times
in your life once just once yeah
that seems i think the credit whoa
that i know
you do have a dripping down your
background but i was ah wasn't remember
maybe i've just been shit on by
birds more because we're called ah yep
it's easier to reach me you've been
you've been shooting a bunch i don't
even know if i have once growing
up not no not really no but
i think my elementary tomba bird
birds my elementary school i think there
were a lot of segal's or what
are the pigeons i don't know but
always like hanging around or they dancer
although like you know but what do
you mean you don't know you know
the difference between pigeon steals they're both
whites they both know they're not they
both speak bird
bird tower dong than the dance this
one's by the sea we weren't by
the sea so it couldn't have been
probably pigeon that is probably the sea
so are you by them this wasn't
cso
i'm just saying there were a lot
of birds who were constantly shitting and
so people would get shit on alright
fair yeah that makes sense i mean
if you're in a in a concentrated
bird area yeah i guess you would
get shit on but that's i i
would think that everyone's elementary school there
would be a lot of birds is
what are you because there's so much
food
food lawn july by the lunch table
was first of all we like doors
high because we've seen this is the
difference i'm saying i grew up in
california and everyone ate trying to be
outside equalling more time to get shit
on why wouldn't you eat inside because
no one need they had lockers outside
too you should have eaten inside you
wouldn't get shit on by
bird so much why didn't you think
twice in six years ally i thought
it was all the time all yeah
no story changing people he wants the
birds to shit on him he did
that interview playboy where he was like
yes my wife and i would understanding
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah guys i went to a party
everyone was wearing masks and shitting on
each other
wow his birds as birds there's a
party full of birds they're wearing people
masks i was one once a bird
shit upon my my very bare head
and so people called me shithead for
awhile that was not because of that
yeah just a shithead and i did
i simply just said hey my dude
you just shithead okay let's say yeah
should hook you should ah the lovely
yeah my job is what ab should
have you have should they have had
you come to me like i tell
ya
ah for literature they can't refuse yes
it is the head sake of god
leave the coalition has since hunter that
shithead knows best
a slow the bug
again my shit had the bug me
this shit in my head the bug
made a shit in my head it
did day we gotta take a break
oh okay
i think that's been proven alright well
they're back with more of this more
of this you know you owe this
now
we're back and we are in the
present corner the part of the day
that has to be in the middle
of the show for various reasons we
received artwork from an amazing artist i
don't have the name because it wasn't
attached this portrait but they did tag
us on instagram as well and it's
three
them big dog got a bark really
beautiful art of three wolves howling as
well i think it's absolutely this one
it depicts us as the as the
mythical servers the three-headed dog now here's
some personalized bibs that came from richard
bachelor they each have our name and
the namely said we are on the
episode so
so scott has paul and parentheses um
lauren scott of freedom fame and will
wear them in the photo so you'll
see that waste episode walk me through
the scenario where these okay there might
know we could do it explained it
to me lauren i guess on an
episode we said this and i said
i was kevin
yeah okay well these are good presence
it happened in episode twenty five cactus
who's so that's when it thank you
and we also received um some some
shocking pens and i'm certainly shocked and
we received a chicken in the corn
this is like gibberish to me that
you're talking the other shocking pins
just as a joke pen yes you
try it is going gonna shock me
yeah is it like it's like a
joy buzzer yeah
so you you press
and then somebody made us threesome hats
these are from anna coffin that was
so sweet and jesus someone ah really
bad it's all amy to see someone
said this hate the game which i'm
really into into and i think we
should be illegal the packaging on here
is amazing we also received a bot
a whole pouch full of bibs from
ah another i'm on it
i'm honestly saying it's bibs did we
say something about bibs scott begged her
bibs i guess i'm honestly sorry so
think how on maiko how is this
legal baby but to do this sean
works at a custom print party supply
show called sand scripts party bibs dot
com most popular party says are custom
print party bib
so i often print these bibs while
working at the end of the episode
thirty fifth god said send us bibs
so if you found my boss and
i'm i need all of our weirdest
orders from real bachelor parties weddings birthdays
and other events pick them up and
send them to you hope you enjoy
it's i don't know how they can
this can be a real thing i
was so scared to touch it wow
you
myself out over hacking oh look at
this jerry you recipe this one looks
like a man's tits
oh man this and they're all about
people's marriages and stuff and and that's
pretty all the old people's marriages like
people like i say babes for their
names why like
if you had lobster at your wedding
on there like marriage is messy okay
that's what i want be very sorry
but that's to catch up with this
doesn't make any sense i don't know
i think it's insane that ah we
received these are so interesting marriages messi's
but this one says as well must
become and they had a barbecue
like i said if you're going to
have like a big lobster fry
okay tell you what the fuck did
i tell you okay and we're gonna
tell you we got bibs and i
also want to thank ah you know
people call in for the nice card
and gift and thank you everyone and
that wraps up the present corner yes
those very nice have also raised so
much great present corner loin it's a
lot for me to present
these gifts with ah with ah you
know great explanation succinct fashion just leave
me alone well everyone's saying good things
like everyone said it's you our present
corner twisting this into usable twisted sick
individual your twisted sister
and we're not gonna take it oh
no no we're not gonna take an
a take it that's what else is
up in your lives yeah well we
also invite to aragon clayton's wedding which
we missed we got the invitation too
late oh sorry guys clayton hope you
are still married hap happy returns to
you i'm miss your way
day do you know i ran into
a friend that i had not seen
a really long time we're into each
other at the supermarket parking lot really
it yeah and have you not seen
each other because of distance or because
of just circumstance a lot of people
in lhasa circumstance yeah we hadn't been
in the same circles in a while
okay ah yes the supermarket
it brings everyone from all walks of
life together can i tell you it
was sure fred belford fred belford i've
seen him and relatively recently moved from
a very funny comedian and um so
we were just catching a very briefly
and he has a he's married now
as a stepchild and ah
a normal child
a redhead um and he's and i
said oh congratulations and ah how's janey
and i said she's good and ah
there was like a moment i there
was like a moment of hesitation then
we talked about how it is if
you haven't seen someone so weird questionnaire
so yeah i'd say how is the
person you're married to i don't ask
you to people who've been married for
for a week i mean a year
you know something something sure i don't
ask anyone about anything about their lives
i haven't seen the the significant other
in a while and they have been
posting or something yeah and they're not
with them you better believe that exactly
imo but it's technically it's not rude
to ask because the last time you
saw someone they were married know used
to be a very normal quest
oh yeah and technically and and even
if the person is divorced the the
person should be able to say like
oh no we were not together anymore
it wouldn't be chicken shamed
it's sad they failed yes in the
it's a sin me bro they broke
the holy compact yeah i don't know
you failed being miserable for the rest
of your life don't ever tell you
this story yeah when i ran into
this guy on the train to comicon
no wait it's a little it's scratching
an itch but yeah it's it's along
these lines yeah i had i worked
with this guy on a pilot
ah well no we we did the
series together oh and an ana animated
series for mtv years ago hadn't seen
him in forever and i ran into
on the train to comic-con a few
years ago and he was it was
you know like eleven am and he
was drunk okay and i was like
oh maybe he's just partying
boss yeah joining like yeah whatever i've
had just drinking in the old days
partying like you're alone on that train
he's just party was the alone on
the trainer i think it was with
other people and he was coming back
from the bathroom okay and he saw
me it's like hey paul tom kids
i mean out down i will say
that is one of the good things
about being on a train is like
hey i'm not driving i can drink
absolutely
claims to it but drunk there was
on one of those flights that we
took for the tour the woman sitting
next to me had three gin and
tonics but seemed to be perfectly normal
do you know what i mean yeah
that was like not doing anything to
her she was not like oh i'm
terrified of flying she's right she's right
yeah you know what i'm doing
agenda topic wow very casual went on
i want i wish the morning i
went on a plane with someone i'll
tell you who later who like ordered
for jack and cokes immediate immediate was
like i'm gonna order for jack and
cokes if that's okay you can just
bring them to the same time yeah
it was just because of being nervous
about flying now just like this day-to-day
life this is my day
tendency for our one yeah can i
i'm a alcohol like i need for
jack and it seemed like it was
almost an admission of like this is
what i need to yeah get back
yeah yeah um so he sits down
and talk with me and i'm like
oh he's kinda drunk and so he's
not able to hold up a conversation
very well and so um a one
point we just had this lower just
like staring at me and smiling
and i went um i i've never
asked this question of anyone and ah
will you sign my day as soon
you never want asked that
oh so but i see please i
begged them if you're not busy
a security will you um i said
how's your personal life oh as soon
as i asked a quantum word as
soon as i asked the question i
was like skies drunk at eliminate oh
what's he gonna tell me like well
i got divorced and i was like
i'm sorry it's like no it's good
it's good
but oh he kept mining like i
like shout out i'm like oh you've
got me copper then he um went
back in the bathroom and then all
of a sudden it smells like cigarettes
and the train and then he ran
back up where his seats were there
was an ounce with the capon very
interesting you may not smoke on the
train wow
he was having a day i know
what it is i bet i would
be very surprised okay but you you
guess you ah mine is an all
guys who yours is why when we
take a break alright how recent was
yours ah three years okay it's not
someone that you know personally all of
that i should have fun guessing okay
why are you yawning right into my
i
haven't talked in awhile ah focus not
on me ah story about paul
it's just yeah
that's the
lorna you doing anything for christmas okay
i'm going away for thanksgiving where are
you playing oh i don't want to
tell you guys oh hi hey oh
can you mime it i want to
tell you guys but yeah i know
ah you know i don't trust anyone
yeah yeah i get it well with
in-depth during the break conversation yeah lots
of about lots of things
i'll tell you everything you wanna know
we'll tell you everything you want to
look silly
what's the silliest thing you can think
of okay
the philly fanatic right oh boy like
okay riding a cow that has two
heads with um streamers for a tail
and it is jumping over the moon
which is made of cheese it actually
looks like scott's scots
very silly can i change one thing
so silly yeah because the two hits
makes me scared yeah it's very frightening
in the middle of the city with
the heads are like emoji's and they're
like well alright yeah i'm making bomb
back on board bombard their three d
emoji's three d e's of the cow's
head i guess
the only silly thing i can think
of would be a couch which has
real human legs instead of couch legs
and his shaving those lays well collects
the hair and eats the hair by
putting it underneath the couch cushion unless
silly it's getting it's not silly it's
getting buggy while it's happening he's like
ooh
alright alright hey do you want to
come sit on my face hey me
it would be the silliest thing safe
comedy ah thank you for saying finally
it's been said yes yes qui a
queen yes
wow really anyone zed to the queen
of england yes queen oh i hope
cardi b or someone says to her
it would be so funny to be
so funny shoe soles going to even
get it
what if broad was what broad city
met the queen i wish they would
oh man what means do you think
the queen is aware of
bond james bond
me the original name
everyone just decided that was a thing
everyone was gonna say
the original mean um i mean they
decided the original even probably was some
fucked up like amos and andy shit
yeah probably what are some memes lauren
you're jacked into the memes i can
has cheezburger i even as cheese do
you think the queen of england is
aware of i can has cheezburger know
do you
i think the qui ms aware of
keyboard cat before yeah maybe maybe keyboard
cat maybe maybe but they don't really
use social media right so like they
don't have like the the royals do
you think of queens she is a
grandma and probably when those kids were
the kids that are married now no
but i'm saying they were i don't
know but they would be online
line they'd be right and looking at
shit it would be boring to be
the queen because you wouldn't have a
phone
you wouldn't have twitter
seriously you wanna play value on life
the show twitter i'm so i'd actually
i hate my brain like i feel
like yeah i'm i'm constantly chinese my
phone less and failing miserably and i'll
give myself excuses like when we're going
on tour i'm like well i don't
want to set limits on it because
i'm going to be like board a
lot it's like yeah on planes and
trains non-wood
bows and then i should be thinking
no how about you just set the
timer and you don't go on that
anymore and you have to read or
think or just listen to a podcast
yeah what would you read books i
read books you read books you will
read books i bet i bet you
ah i bet you read like a
nice fat book every eight
months
like what do you have a boner
does that feel accurate and i beg
you read this book every eight months
yeah rah rah rah okay when i
go on vacation i like to read
yeah remember your reading vacations fun yeah
what did i read you remember it
was about twin peaks i think oh
that twin peaks book yeah i did
read that i read a different book
it was fun
look reading is fundamental it when you
pair it with writing and arithmetic
you're covered but yeah
i'm going to ask you guys a
question on this hot seat box okay
plea but this is not counting as
a feature if you had a meeting
call what would it be i think
it would be plea
oh so kitty
please just look
okay what would okay but you know
when it was interesting about this game
i actually changed it said if i
had a meeting call what would it
be and i made it if you
oh okay but i guess it's i
guess i'm supposed to it's always about
you i don't know because they're always
directed at the reader i know you
liked this gallery we want how would
i spend my life if i were
given two weeks to live
live two weeks to live you would
eat a bunch of garbage and wash
reality television you definitely oh man
what
would you this is a weird why
think if i were given two weeks
to live would you spend it with
your loved ones or would you say
immediately within the first minute goodbye loved
ones i have other stuff i have
to do it spend it with them
just talking just talking about what about
life and life their lives i mean
that's what i've learned and what i
do
would you record everything that you in
podcast form while you were doing it
in order to pass it down do
you hope should you ever have children
and ah we're not saying if that's
something that you want or whether it's
something that you don't want ah haha
but do you hope that they listen
to this show in particular
her and i guess this episode or
any episode and say wow i really
got to know mom you know i
think that's kind of neat at some
point for them to listen but i
imagine that would only become interesting to
them once they're in their like twenties
or thirties i don't think young kids
would care about that or think like
it's cool that you do this you
know
i do wonder about the children of
people who have a who have art
that's out there for the public consumption
whether they legitimately are interested in ah
for instance i was talking to someone
yesterday who told me that they were
on a ah they had one acting
job in their life when they were
in in high school and they
iran like a teen soap opera and
that's the only thing they've ever done
this was like i've known this person
for a while and it was like
shocking to me ah that they did
two seasons on a teen soap opera
and i was like well do your
children know and it's like no they
don't know yet but i think it
would be interesting to know that about
you know yeah well they'll be crazy
reveal if i found out my
mom had been on a team so
powerful but you didn't tell me until
i was like nineteen right i'd be
like why don't i know this well
you just said they that this show
shouldn't be listened to until know i
just imagined they won't care to hear
ah there was their model talking about
like stuff that yeah that is relevant
to them at that age right maybe
they'd be more interesting i think young
kids
don't really care what their parents do
for a living i would lie to
my children and tell them that i
did a really cool thing yeah too
i would tell them i was the
first man to walk on the moon
and see how long it would take
and they would go to school and
they would be like my dad is
an astronaut and was the first man
to walk on the people would be
like no i don't think so just
see how long i could get away
with this
what have you set my children up
for pain and failure have you heard
of greta thunberg that yeah sixteen year
old activist yeah no climate change and
oh yeah yeah she's really awesome and
she there was this great interview with
her on the daily show recently which
i think everyone should watch but she
um she more of a jon stewart
is in the middle ah well yeah
but it's more about what she's say
ng is what i i'm more of
a bill maher guy
but she says she's not doing the
ah flying strike because it hasn't so
that is one of the biggest cum
tributes to climate change so she's not
flying she just took a no emissions
boat ride from um i believe sweet
into new york or something and she's
only sixteen and her mom is an
opera singer
her and her mom had also is
doing this flight strike and and now
changed her career to be doing musical
theatre instead of opera and trevor noah
was like because because she wouldn't fly
for it and trevor noah i was
like oh how do you feel about
your mom changing her job for you
know these this belief and she was
like i don't really care about my
mom's job she is
aspergers it's also kind of rather oh
so that's how we all really feel
but i think it's true that when
you're like a teen you're like i
don't care but if you were a
problem yeah like if you gotta show
it's i guess i'm not a famous
parent would you care i think i
think half the kids would be like
that's so awesome i want to be
like my parent and half of them
be like oh god i'm so embarrassed
by my yeah yeah i
yeah i think about that a lot
like what it's like to be the
child of a famous person and how
you would resist that pull to want
to do what they'd right i mean
because it probably looks great you know
i mean yeah it probably looks really
cool yeah april
maybe they would and maybe the parents
are only showing the perks and they're
trying to hide the bad stuff you
know from the kids mostly are trying
to show them the bad stuff and
it's not working out right yeah only
sees the perks it's like yeah you
seem to complain a lot but your
life seems pretty great to me yeah
nah i guess being a kid is
is you're constantly like in so much
fear
ir and worried about judgement and stuff
and then to cease people coming true
for everyone while children are a cowardly
superstitious but seeing people come up to
your parents and saying like hey you're
great is something that maybe wouldn't happen
for a lot of kids like right
because the constant hey you're great you're
great you know i mean sure you
had a very happy childhood lauren
but i was also full of worry
and fear yeah i was i related
to you but i was just saying
i bet there are kids who would
be like i wasn't the only that
stuff right but just to see people
at the end even if it just
seems surface level constantly so you know
it's giving people praise and adulation yeah
it must seem very alluring
two kids but they you know the
downside of it ah
you guys are both lucky i think
it was yeah pulling off the sticker
i sing to you i'm just drawing
a little doodle you have the spotlight
scarlets here well yeah wants direct eye
contact the whole podcast time how do
you like this yeah like right like
wow look away look away ruby say
goodbye
welcome back to three dom and it's
time for the reacher it's time for
reacher and what is this one going
to be
paul because lauren's mouth is still full
well i'm gonna tell you came back
to sim um we were sent this
game hot seat that we mentioned earlier
and we decided to sit and write
the fuck here yeah let's play let's
play hotseat it's a party game okay
i don't know
work says each round writing enter to
the question pretending to be the player
in the hotseat points are awarded to
the players who get the hot seat
players answer correctly because they have to
answer three full players into guessing their
answer what but what flat why does
this hot see i see why
it is this is each player on
it i give each player an andy
iago is my name
please don't fire me from any more
voiceover jobs it's all i got that
was not a good i did not
do a good gilbert please don't fire
me from any it's tough i yeah
i'm able to do it i know
okay the problem with this game is
that we need more
people but we're gonna have kevin participate
oh yeah okay ah allowed this one
but it's not ford um it's more
like boredom mom said we have to
let kevin player game with us so
the player in the hotseat draws three
cards and reads them privately the player
in the
hc chooses one card to play one
to give to another player and one
to discard if given a card the
player keeps it face down and must
play it on their next turn okay
there's so many rules everyone including the
player in the hot seat writes and
answer to the card in play on
their answer pad from the perspective of
the player in the hot seat does
kevin know how to play already the
player the huntsman collects the answers and
resold them out loud moving
clockwise each player guesses which answer was
written by the player in the hot
seat okay it's too obvious if we
only have two people i think we
need all three i mean four yeah
okay um
everyone gets a beautiful pentel pen i
want blue too hard to find right
now how a purple no
gary
too hard to know but everyone over
color we have them gotta be color
no matter because the person reading it
knows which one they made like the
hotseat person
you'll understand what happens but we all
yeah but we can also see what
color the people have no but it
doesn't matter because
they're gonna read all the quests they're
gonna read all the responses in youtube
like okay let's say i'm in the
hot seat okay you're lucky i read
the question everyone answers it as as
me and then i'll read all four
responses and i will show mercy and
i'll know my i was right anyway
you don't mean like okay here we
can pink it doesn't matter mr pink
what historical
event mr brown mr shit what historical
event would i have loved to be
a part of it i do love
that movie what historical event would you
lauren lap cus have love love to
have been a part of
and we're trying to guess what you
would actually say but we'll probably pull
up these silences and oh this is
like the dictionary game and all that
yeah and yeah you might make a
joke or two okay oh i don't
know that's a lot of pressure um
alright i'm just trying to fill the
time but as we're writing
ng but i have to say that
i have written my answer and i
am tearing it off and um give
nude over to little miss lowered laughed
is okay and she's going to read
it out loud
and are you ready and are you
ready and are you ready okay
right now i'm going to don't look
please know i'm going to go look
okay these are what what historical event
when i've loved to be a part
of woodstock
assassination of j f k princess di's
wedding woodstock okay okay okay we all
i think i see what's going on
here we all know it it is
it's princess di's wedding got to be
princess di's wedding
chev
what do you think
yes i think it's princess that's what
the answer was woodstock and paul got
it right yeah yes wholly sure but
the other answers were great i would
have let paul you okay be assessed
that was my yeah obviously it was
right in wrong and so paul and
weird part is is you
wrote woodstock yeah and you still thought
one of us row would suck the
odds of that are so astronomical that's
true the noun the god bless you
yeah crazy okay paul pick a card
i'm paul i pick a card this
i guess they all flipped over co
recipe box yeah if i were a
car it
interesting interesting what model would i be
if i were emily ratajkowski for a
car
claudia schiffer
if i were a car what modest
a fun game okay anita ekberg i
needed a hill and joe biden
clarence thomas oh and i have to
write one down to write yeah that's
great and right answer queen yes queen
you must write went down queen
and i this game
okay
now mix them all up however you
like paul look this is your time
to shine
didn't we play something like this in
palm springs anyway
here we go oh no we did
that we we wrote yeah you were
invited fuck yeah okay here we go
hotseat okay
if i were a car what model
would i be t bird
model t
a t theme model t wu and
rolls royce okay so do i vote
first or what are we going clockwise
let's go clockwise i think it's easier
to in the ways of the clock
okay so the chances are that you
said t-birds it's a fifty fifty chance
that you said t bird but i
actually
think you're a rolls royce guy so
i'm gonna say rolls-royce alright t-birds model
t
answer it was rolls-royce wow who says
subtlety i don't know but fuck y'all
i did sorry i guess i meant
yeah but you met on on t
you also meant model t i meant
because it's a fifty fifty chance that
it's model t because you said model
t twice wrote he did the same
i will take no no i sell
cambridge okay great picks hard so are
we scoring points model t's it's like
ah it's like the original it's like
classy it's like it's like it's like
cool and has a hurry score in
the game there's nothing cooler than a
model
who is the other i mean
well hyping it all has a point
right how do we score it paul
has appointed high scoring game or is
it yeah i guess i was paul
has a point and i have a
point okay because i guess i guess
fuck way could i have had two
points if i've said woodstock because i
wrote it and it was the correct
isn't it that you are tricking people
into thinking i
your answer is not it i don't
know anyway seven look it up while
we're playing i don't you're trying to
trick anyone i'm playing kind of guy
really i was i'd be tricking people
lauren read that in the rules of
it okay okay what would my parents
be referring to if they texted me
saying i know what you did when
you were younger
it's great
i know what love is to the
pain i know what you did when
you were younger
i've i feel like i've told every
embarrassing story about myself yeah i'm just
gonna pick one
my face okay ray ah yes
okay thank you this is from chev
and great i'm gonna tear mine off
and here we go are you all
ready and always ready
oh okay
ah right this is all good read
the question again okay the question is
what would my parents be referring to
if they texted me saying i know
what you did when you were younger
alright
we have rode a bike with sunglasses
on
classic story drew chicken pox dots on
my forehead other classic story jack off
in the pool class i mean that's
a classic sort of reverend not cool
up
alright okay and so the answer we're
going clockwise we go to chevron ah
chicken pox i think ah you you
wrote chicken pox
i think he wrote chicken pox
i wrote chicken yeah you write not
cool up paul the item oh nice
yeah i don't even understand that one
well that's what you didn't do when
you're younger because she didn't exist there
yeah fucking but you wrote jack off
in the pool yeah of course i
knew that i guess we gotta do
kevin gatlin
kind of weird shit is kevin been
up to we don't talk he doesn't
talk a lot in the show so
people don't know that much about him
but he does talk a lot maybe
down if you want yeah he has
his own show thanks okay what would
be the mission statement of a cult
that i started
the mission statement of a cult that
kevin started we all got one point
on the last one right yes
alright all i thinking i'm not i
think
you have yours yeah
okay all right we're turning them in
to kevin who is wrapping up his
answer as well and he could grab
these from me at any time and
i wouldn't be sitting here with my
arm stuck out thirty cool just
alright i got right mind sorry i
guy right man i go like i
write mine i sorry i got right
my eye sorry i got right mine
you could just say it you don't
have to write that's a good point
well but it's more believable if there's
more really every horrible although i didn't
write mine down you fucking unique moved
your pen for like ten minutes oh
i know we got it all out
but i was minding my dear alright
get me more mic time
yeah i guess right i miss my
mommy
called mission statement stay hydrated
and to listen to more podcasts wow
these are all exactly what you would
say so it's hard to pick
you pick i would say
ah to listen to more podcasts i
would also say to listen to more
podcasts i will say stay hydrated
um okay so i said stay hydrated
yeah wow yes a weight and but
do i get points because they picked
my thing oh my god who cares
we're not scoring that and i'm obviously
the winner and that's how we play
yahtzee
yeah awesome thank you all for listening
to the show thanks for the people
to the people that sent nice gifts
that is very sweet so kind and
look we're gonna roll on out here
you won't be hearing from us for
a while you're gonna come back someday
i hope someday i hope we come
back look here's the deal the last
time that
show ended we asked you to send
postcards to call in and he got
very mad at us and punished us
because it was too many it was
a deluge of of postcards that he
didn't know what to do with and
he was very upset with us we
didn't get any sticky toffee pudding for
a solid month yes um so this
time
i'm
what should they do if they want
to hear more of the show because
we have no plans to make any
more shows you tweet a column take
an ad out and the la times
yes tweeting page yeah tweeted call on
anderson tweeted colin anderson tell him you
want more show or tell him hey
look i think that's good that's enough
sure yeah o j online andor colin
an andor andor is how you may
also tweet at big grande's tweets tweets
yeah graduated we zig grundy twee tells
them you want poor three-day yeah and
less of what they do well no
you can you can like what they
do but you want more of what
we do right so then then what
they do tweet at yes tweet that's
we had a big grande's tweets and
say hey guys hey guys can you
talk to colleen anderson about getting more
threesome on the books please they want
to hear from you they want to
hear from you they want to know
so bad they want to know daddy
do you wanna know we gotta go
we gotta go i wanna but we
should thank
ah chev over here thank you chef
and what you're saying here sam sam
over here and all the people who
were thank you engineers zig producers zig
right easier the first episode i've never
seen him again i know but he
man he really cares about the first
episode the zoo i looked like for
everyone to follow all of us i
mean there's runner and instagram
usa and all are individuals because we
were aldermen doing other things that we
would like for you to check out
and so that's the best way to
know about them yes and thank you
so much for listening we really do
appreciate it and we love you bye
i love you too but i'm like
well this is not us kissing each
other
oh should we end on the song
oh yeah yes and before we go
let's hear a song that was sent
to us who sent us this tyler
beck with tyler beckwith census this this
is based on a previous episode this
is a beautiful remix here we go
this will take us out goodbye everyone
serious toe
serious tone
the street size
serious toe
hey watch it it starts right now
uh